- Mom?
- I am here.
Mom.
- You forgot that.
- How could I forget this.
Are you sure
this is the right thing?
It feels like it'd be better
if we thought about it.
Yeah, I do.
We don't have any other option, Clara.
We are going to be fine.
Okay.
If I get off early I can pick you up. Oh,
it really don't matter, I will take a bus.
I will be off early, I got a couple
of things to do for Jenny's party.
Don't worry.
- Have a good day.
- You too, Mom.
- How you doing?
- I don't know.
How we're paying for all of this?
- We put up the house.
- I knew it.
It's because of you I am still alive..
- We decided it together.
- What did you all decide together?
To live on the street... for 18 years.
Your mother and I have been
paying on that house...
just to fuck it all up.
Next year I will be a licensed electrician.
So, no more illegal odd jobs.
Going to be fine.
I never wanted to be a burden.
Don't say that, Dad.
I am leaving, babe.
So you got what you have been waiting for?
- Yeah, I got it.
- Would it be right?
- That's not your concern.
- You can go to hell.
That's exactly where I am going.
But if I make it back,
I going to make so much money,
you going to love me again.
Your brother would feel better
if family members visited more often.
A year is a long time
for someone in his condition.
I am the only family Ronald has.
I try to get down here as often as I can.
Overall, his condition is still...
borderline, Mr. Hodges.
To skip his medications even for a day
could be serious.
Yes, ma'am.
Sign here and here,
and Ronald is released.
Your brother is here, came to get you.
You have to go.
- They take care of you in there?
- Yeah.
- Good.
- It's a new car?
Yeah, do you like it?
- Yeah.
- Let's go.
When I turned five years old,
I got a little kitten.
And it was so cute that I took
them to bed with me every night.
I want a little lamb, and I will take
it to bed with me every night too.
- People don't keep sheep inside, silly.
- I will.
Didn't you hear?
We don't keep sheep inside...
and we don't take them to bed with us.
My little lamb has to be all white
with black ears.
Why black ears?
That way I won't get them mixed up
with the other sheep.
- I will be able to recognize him.
- Very clever.
Thanks, Mom.
What is going on, man?
Kico Tevero...
Hey, wait a minute. What the hell
you doing? Goddamn it.
What the fuck you doing?
Goddamn it.
Let me the fuck out of here.
Oh, shit.
Goddamn.
Get me the fuck out of here.
A lot of people would want that.
I am sorry.
Thank you.
That was his job, I mean
there's nothing I can do for you.
Maybe in a few days.
Hi, can I get you anything, coffee maybe?
I am good. No.
No, babe.
So what's this job about, man?
Dope?
No. Nothing like that.
- You need somebody taking care of?
- No.
I am just asking for a good word.
- What? You want to go in my place?
- Listen, I am broke.
I am on the street.
Hey, I haven't forgotten what you did
for me when I was away.
If this thing works out.
I will set you up. I promise.
- How long exactly will it take?
- One day.
Jesus. You make all that cash in one day?
If I make it.
- But you made it the last time, right?
- That was last time.
As long as my luck doesn't run out,
you can count on me.
Hey...
Vincent, do you still live at
135, Kissam Avenue, Talbot Ohio?
Yeah.
You have a phone number I can reach you
at if I have any further questions?
Sure, uh... 216-555-0145.
Okay Vincent, I think that about does it.
Thank you.
Can you recall anything else he could
have told you about this affair?
No. I already told you.
He never spoke about it.
- Even when he was high?
- No.
Did anyone else come into the house,
aside from the paramedics and the police?
There was an electrician.
He was the one that called 911.
Thank you, Mrs. Harrison.
Thank you.
- You sleep okay?
- Yeah, I feel much better now.
- Did you take your medication?
- No.
Look here...
you know the doctor says
that you're not supposed to skip a dose.
Fuck her.
I feel much better without it anyway.
Tails 40 fucking times, you know,
our luck's fucked.
I know, we're going to make it.
Don't pay attention to that shit.
You will be going for job
and nothing else.
- What do you think?
- You're very handsome.
They're going to love you.
Unshackle his legs.
Hey mister, you in charge here, you are
going to tell me what the hell's going on.
- How do you feel?
- How do I feel?
Hey man. I have been in this goddamn box
for two and a half days, man.
Tell me what's going on.
What do you all want from me?
Give him shower.
Change your clothes, something fresh.
Where you all taking me, man?
Fuck you.
- What about his stuff?
- What're you talking about?
Give it to him.
Fuck you, guys.
- Hello, Mr. Harrison?
- Yeah.
Tomorrow at noon, go to the post
next door to Grand Central.
- Hang on.
- 200 West 39 Street.
Okay.
With the key that you found with the
cellphone, you will open box 2-5-3.
Inside you will find another train ticket,
more instructions.
Your ticket will be to Macomb, but you
will get off one stop before Macomb.
- One stop "before". Is that clear?
- Yeah.
Ticket, please.
- He's getting off at Macomb.
- What time do we arrive?
Train gets in at 3:10.
Can I help you guys with anything else?
No, thank you.
Can I get a bottle of water
and a ham sandwich?
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
You Flink? Yeah, get in. Thanks.
I want to go here.
- You know it?
- Yeah.
- Is it far?
- No, it's right around the corner.
That will be $17.70.
- Keep the change.
- Wow, thank you.
Give me your phone.
Get in the car.
- Which number is it?
- 13.
Come on.
Stand in the middle of the carpet.
Take your clothes off.
Faster.
Take off the rest.
Get dressed.
You didn't find it strange dropping off
somebody in the middle of nowhere?
When the guy is paying me.
He's the customer.
So, he can get out wherever he wants.
- You didn't see anything else unusual?
- No.
I just left him there and I left.
Follow me.
Have a seat.
Who's that?
I can explain.
- I know...
- Shut up.
Go get Jack.
You're probably wondering...
- what I am doing here.
- Quiet.
Ah, Mr. Gomer.
Is this young man who's playing tonight?
Yes, that's him.
Very couragious.
Two million.
Put 700 thousand, on number six.
What's going on?
Who's he?
What do you mean? He's the guy
I picked up at the intersection.
He's not who I was expecting.
- Well, he had the number.
- Harrison is dead.
- What are you talking about?
- He OD'th.
And who the fuck are you?
I am an electrician.
I was working at his house.
Give me your ID.
- Did he tell you about this?
- No, I overheard him talking.
I knew he was waiting for a letter
and it could be a lot of money.
So I took it
and followed the instructions.
- Do you know what this is about?
- No.
No, I have no idea.
Follow me.
Do you think the cops send him?
Maybe we should... get out now.
If we leave and the cops show up...
then the others will think we ratted.
We would be dead men.
- Where you going?
- I should go and talk to them.
Excuse me, gentlemen.
Um...
If it's a problem... maybe, then...
then I think I should leave. I will leave.
It's too late.
What if I don't want to be here?
You have to play now.
600 thousand... on number 13.
Good luck.
Attention.
The first round is about to begin.
Go fuck your mother.
What's he saying?
Cocksucker go fuck your mother.
Attention.
You got to listen to him.
I am asking the guards
to please distribute the bullets.
One bullet to each player.
Hans, we are born only once
and we die only once.
You must be philosophical, huh?
You are the descended
of the great Schopenhauer.
I am asking all gamblers
to please step back.
Please, gentlemen. Back up.
Back up.
Thank you, gentlemen.
- Please boss.
- Have a seat.
Players.
Load your bullets... into their cylinders.
What's going on 13?
Do you have a problem number 13?
One second.
No. No. No one gets up into the ring.
I am asking you to step down immediately.
He doesn't know how to load his gun.
Do you?
- Pay attention.
- Open it like this.
Round.
Alright. Enough.
Take your places.
Raise your weapons.
Higher.
I want to see them.
Spin your cylinders.
More. More.
Keep it up.
Stop.
Aim.
Cock your hammers.
Number 13.
No turning around.
Players, all eyes on the bulb.
When the bulb lights up, you shoot.
Attention. Nobody move.
Number 13 did not shoot.
Mr. Joe Garver, if your man
does not shoot, we will.
And you will be fined.
What the fuck are you doing.
Pull the trigger.
Shoot.
Shoot, you son of a bitch.
- I am going to count, to three.
- Shoot.
- One.
Two.
Everyone, out of the ring.
- Are you done with your little drama.
- Fuck you.
This is the last time you're trying
the bullshit, you get it?
Hey... how much money
they're paying you to watch my ass?
What the fuck is it to you.
I will give you 50 times more
what they're giving you.
You let me get my ass out of here.
If you got that kind of money,
why the fuck did you come here?
What do you think,
I just waltzed in here, huh?
These people kidnapped my ass.
You like money, huh?
How's two millions sound?
You know what you can do
with two million, huh?
You get all the high class pussy,
all the fancy cars, all the bubbly shit
you can drink, brother.
Well, I can't do nothing for you so,
don't even think about it.
What's the matter?
- You don't like money?
- It's impossible.
Come here, man.
Wait a minute.
Come on.
Come here, man.
- My man's out, I want to bet on yours.
- Sure.
I take 50 points of the top,
just for this round.
Okay.
- Want some morphin?
- No.
- They all do it...
- I said, no.
Hey, you lost your player, didn't you?
Son of a bitch.
So, you're betting on the wrong man?
Don't worry about him,
he has what he needs.
Look, I don't know
what your deal with this guy is.
I think I can do you one better.
60-40,
60 for you, 40 for me.
You have to bet at least 400 thousand.
Player number six,
he has the most experience.
- You know who I am talking about.
- I know your player.
Made your offer, I just made mine.
60-40 it is.
Place your bets, gentlemen.
Alright, on your feet now.
Move it, let's go.
Now.
- I said, move it.
- Let's go.
Get him on to his feet, now.
You, get him on his feet.
On your feet, gentlemen.
On your feet.
Two bullets in each weapon.
Two bullets.
Players, load your bullets
into their cylinders.
Raise your weapons.
Higher.
Spin your cylinders.
- Keep it up. Keep it up.
- Faster. Faster. Faster.
Stop.
Aim.
Cock your hammers.
Don't look me in the eye.
Eyes on the bulb.
- Out of the ring.
- Collect the weapons, now.
You're pretty lucky.
The bullet is in the chamber,
he didn't have time to shoot.
Lewis, one more round
and then we're through.
Hans.
Bring him to me.
Doctor, to the ring.
He can not continue.
Wait, hold on. Hold on. Is this a
fucking game or a slaughterhouse?
My player didn't die in the game.
He is still alive.
- What the hell is that.
- You know the rules Mr. Taylor.
Hans.
When you start something, you must
stay with it until the end.
Nobody forced you to do this.
You are two for two.
You are great.
You are great...
How much I win
for the first two rounds?
2.9 million.
Excuse me, sir.
Excuse me.
You need to pick your number.
What you got?
I will be standing behind Player 13.
I want to bet the 2.9 plus an
addition of 1.2.
If you make it to the end,
you will make a lot of money.
What the fuck do you care?
Just making conversation.
Three million.
Okay, three million.
I will give you three million dollars.
Okay, that will change your life forever.
Where you planning
on getting all this money?
Listen.
Me and a couple of my boys,
we hit this armored car in Mexico.
My two partners they got blown away.
I got away for about a day and a half.
I had enough time where I got rid
of the truck and I hid the money.
If you got that kind of money, how is
it they let you out of the prison?
You should have been a gold mine for them.
Shit man... They beat my ass in that
jail, but I didn't talk, okay?
I didn't say a goddamn word.
Listen, if I would have said something...
they would have smoked my ass,
and taking the money.
I got the money.
I got a lot of fucking money.
Finish the game and you will leave peacefully.
In your case there's no way you escape.
They will blow both our brains out,
before we got in to front door.
You have a better chance
to survive in the ring.
Please, give me something to write with it.
- I want my money.
- Don't worry about the money.
What's important,
to see you go all the way.
It's pretty fucked up, huh?
We two are brothers.
I hate that fucking number.
Bang.
Calm down.
- Just let it go.
- Calm down a little bit.
Forget about it.
Shot two already.
He shoots three, you get a bonus.
Uh-huh.
That would be wonderful.
- How much do I have?
- 1.1 million.
Listen, man...
I got all the details, of where I buried
all the money, there's a map here.
- Listen to me, man.
- I got a son.
He's doing some time.
He got another...
I don't know 18 months to go, so...
If anything happens to me,
and I don't make it out of here...
I want you to take this note
out of my pocket,
go get that money, and I want
you to split with him.
- We got a deal?
- Okay, you got it.
Thirteen.
Number six.
Number three.
Eleven.
You can take him now.
You're going down.
What the fuck do you want?
Alright, enough.
Mr. Schlöndorf.
Why isn't your player in the ring?
He must step up immediately.
- He will be there. He will be there.
- The third round is about to begin.
- What's wrong with him?
- Just a little case of the runs.
Get him up there.
Come on.
Give him his gun.
For the third round,
I will ask the guards to distribute...
three bullets to each player.
Three bullets.
Sir, please.
Can I please have a chair for my player?
He's not feeling too well.
That guy wants a chair for Number 3.
He's got a hard time standing.
Get him a chair.
Thank you.
Players... load the bullets
in their cylinders.
Raise your weapons.
Spin your cylinders.
More.
Stop.
Aim.
Cock your hammers.
All players... eyes on the bulb.
- Out of the ring.
- Collect the weapons.
Gentlemen, we are at the last stage
of our game.
The duel.
On the table, there are five balls.
Three white, two black.
The black, will designate the duelists.
I will now call the gamblers
representing number 6, 9, 13, 17 and 3.
I will ask that you unwrap the balls,
high above your heads...
so that everyone can see.
Gentlemen, good luck.
Gentlemen, place your bets.
Okay. Wait. Wait.
I am not accepting any offers
under 85 percent.
Nothing less than 300 thousand.
Hey. Let him go.
What the fuck are you doing?
Nobody touches the survivors. Nobody.
Fuck.
You know that story I told you about,
and all that money?
All that money I told you about. Huh?
All that money you think
you were going to be holding on to...
huh? All that money?
You think you would have been
a holding on to, Jimmy,
would have been your dick.
Okay, son?
Happy trails, partner.
What's going up between you two?
I just want to get the fuck out of here.
Well get dressed and come get your money.
You free to go.
# Happy trails to you.
Until we meet again. #
# Happy trails to you, motherfuckers,
until we meet again. #
# Happy trails to you. #
Mr. Gomer.
I would like to bet on your boy.
Our player has no experience, and at
this stage of the game, it's important.
- How much do you want?
- I want 80 percent.
No, no, no, no, no.
That's too much.
The two brothers they're not offering
you much better.
Besides we launch out at 5 to 1,
You'd make more money,
everyone is betting on them.
Yeah.
Alright, we will do business.
- It's almost time number one.
- Oh.
If this works out well, Jasper.
I want my fucking share.
Of course. But there's not a
lot of people betting on us.
We're not going to be able
to make that much money.
Shut your fucking mouth, you cunt.
Shut your fucking mouth.
I fucking know you.
I know you.
Oh, I have been, uh...
thinking a lot, lately.
What're you talking about?
Mummy and daddy had left you
enough money to look after me.
You stucked me in that fucking hospital.
- That hospital cost me a lot of money.
- Hm...
You have earned more money on me playing
this fucking game in these past years.
- And you're a fucking monster.
- That's horseshit.
When I am in that certain hell,
I want my fucking money.
Against the wall.
- Shit.
- What?
The trigger's too fucking tight.
It's too big.
They're all the same.
Thirteen.
Six.
One.
Two.
Three.
- Good for you?
- Okay.
Players to the center of the ring.
Raise your weapons.
Spin your cylinders.
More.
Stop.
Aim.
Cock your hammers.
Eyes on the bulb.
When it lights up, you shoot.
Attention, gentlemen.
The duel will continue.
I will ask for an additional bullet,
in each cylinder.
One, two, three... four.
One, two, three... four bullets.
Players, please step forward.
Raise your weapons.
Spin your cylinders.
More.
Stop.
Aim.
Cock your hammers.
When the bulb lights up, you shoot.
I win my bets,
when the odds are against me.
- Gentlemen.
- The game is over.
It's finished.
And the winner... is Number 13.
Congratulations, 13.
Congratulations.
Fuck. Fuck.
Fuck it.
Well done, young man.
Well done.
Have a seat.
...Five, six, seven, eight, nine, ten.
Congratulations.
1 million 850 thousand dollars.
You realize how lucky you are?
Your opponent won his last three duels.
- Are you satisfied?
- Yeah.
If you want we can give you a ride.
- Where?
- It doesn't matter.
We can drop you off to the nearest
train station if... you like.
Yeah, I will get my things
I meet you downstairs.
- Would you like a drink?
- No, thank you.
- Where you going?
- I am going with him.
Why don't you go to the room,
get our coats.
I couldn't find him.
Get in the car.
Sir, your total is going to be 38.
Thank you.
Hi.
Hi, Officer Stellar. This is Claudio,
the cab driver from yesterday.
Yeah.
Yeah, I just saw your guy.
Yeah, at the station.
Huh? Yeah, he's here now.
That's him, right there.
- He's on your side.
- That's your guy. That's him.
Blue jacket, seated.
Excuse me, sir,
come with us, please.
- You want him uncuffed?
- Uncuff him.
Leave us alone.
Thank you.
Where did you hide the money?
I don't know what you're talking about?
Sit down.
I said, sit down.
You're not under arrest, Vincent.
And you won't be as long as you tell me
everything that went on out there.
- I never met them.
- Don't bullshit me.
I am telling the truth.
Why did they pick you up
at the intersection...
if they're looking for Harrison.
The driver didn't know Harrison.
When he pulled up,
I flashed him the signal.
A signal?
A piece of cardboard with a number.
- Where did he drop you?
- Somewhere in the forest.
What happened?
When I got there, there were
2 other guys waiting in another car.
When they saw me, I knew I was screwed.
I told them Harrison was dead,
and I was willing to take his place.
But they didn't go for it. Either
they didn't believe me, or whatever.
But they didn't want me to be there.
I saw one of the men had a gun.
When he reached for it, I reacted.
I ran and I just kept running.
- Did they chase you?
- They chased me, they shot at me.
But I just kept running.
I ran so hard that I lost the heels
of my shoes.
If you saw them again,
would you be able to identify them?
Of course.
Could you take me to that place
in the forest?
I was in a panic.
I have been running for hours.
It was dark. How the fuck do you
expect me to remember where I was?
But if we took you to that intersection,
you'd get your bearings, right?
The driver blindfolded me.
You're lying.
I am telling the truth.
Put your boots back on.
Can I go now?
Twenty two dollars please.
Hello?
- Mom?
- Vince.
How's dad?
How is everything?
Everything is the same.
He was wondering about you.
- Where are you?
- I am still in Chicago.
- How much longer?
- Not long, I will be home soon.
What... what happened? Everything go okay?
Listen mom, I send some money in the mail.
Certified mail.
- Money?
- A lot of money.
If you are not home,
have Clara wait for it, okay.
What do you mean money?
From where?
I will explain everything later.
Just make sure somebody is home.
You're scaring me, Vincent.
Are you in trouble?
No, everything's fine. Just make sure
somebody is home tomorrow, okay.
Vincent, please tell me what's going on.
I love you.
Eighteen twenty-five.
How much for the lamb?
- It's not for sale.
- I will give you 100 bucks.
- For the lamb?
- Yeah.
It's snowing.
Yeah.
Going far?
I am going home.
Where?
Ohio.