Created and Encoded by -- Hillelitz -- of www.YIFY-TORRENTS.com. The Best 720p/1080p/3d movies with the lowest file size on the internet.
Yo, Jimmy. Give me the status.
Tell me we good.
- You got it, man.
- Beautiful.
It's gonna be an all-timer tonight.
All right, fire them up!
We go live in five!
It's time for ignition
and straight automobile pimping.
- Girl!
- Sorry! My bad!
All right, ladies! We're good.
We're good.
That's it, babies.
Come on, Tej!
Let's get this race going!
Wait a second, man.
You cats are first wave.
Where's your fourth at?
Whoa, wait a second.
Why don't I find you a fourth
and we settle this on the streets?
- Bring him on.
- Anybody I want?
No matter who it is?
Yeah.
Yeah?
Yeah, man. You want to race tonight?
I could use the money.
You got four minutes.
All right, girls, let's do this.
- You think you'll win, baby?
- What do you think?
- You better. We got rent to pay.
- I know this.
I'll get you when you
get a car worth racing.
There's our fourth.
Shit. It's Brian.
- What's up, Tej?
- What's happening, dude?
- Thanks for the invite.
- No problem at all, man.
Just remember me
when you wax, all right?
They got deep pockets?
Real deep.
- What's up, Suki?
- What's up, Bullitt?
What do you say we kick it a nickel?
Nobody mentioned raising stakes.
Stay.
What's going on here?
Tell me.
Thank you for coming
on such short notice.
My red Ferrari was confiscated.
It sits in an impound lot
in Little Haiti.
It's about 20 miles from here.
The car isn't important. The package
I left in the glove box is.
The first team back here
with the package...
will have an opportunity
to work for me.
What are you saying?
We got to audition?
Nobody has a gun to your head.
That's it.
Driver's licenses. Pass them up.
Before Christmas, guys.
Let's go!
Come on, cuz!
Let's see what this thing can do.
Agent Markham.
They're heading south on I-95.
I got it.
They're running. What a surprise.
Stick with me, Rome.