1
00:00:18,143 --> 00:00:20,353
[DOG BARKING]

2
00:01:06,775 --> 00:01:08,651
Hey, take it easy.

3
00:01:08,819 --> 00:01:09,819
See you.

4
00:01:20,497 --> 00:01:22,331
[CHATTERING AND LAUGHING]

5
00:01:22,499 --> 00:01:24,167
[ROCK MUSIC PLAYING ON STEREO]

6
00:01:24,334 --> 00:01:26,169
BOY:
Turn it down.

7
00:01:29,423 --> 00:01:31,090
[CHATTERING INDISTINCTLY]

8
00:01:52,029 --> 00:01:53,696
GIRL 1: Ew, that geek?
GIRL 2: I'm serious.

9
00:01:53,864 --> 00:01:55,865
GIRL 1:
No way, I don't care.

10
00:02:22,893 --> 00:02:25,603
No way, you're such a liar.

11
00:02:25,771 --> 00:02:27,897
-I don't know, he's right behind us.
-What?

12
00:02:28,732 --> 00:02:30,066
No way.

13
00:02:30,275 --> 00:02:32,193
[GIRLS LAUGHING]

14
00:02:40,577 --> 00:02:42,119
That one's for you. He's a live one.

15
00:02:42,287 --> 00:02:45,248
Uh-uh, he's yours.
Oh, we're coming to my house.

16
00:02:46,416 --> 00:02:48,417
Hey, driver. Hey!

17
00:02:49,044 --> 00:02:50,586
Hey, driver, that was my stop.

18
00:02:52,256 --> 00:02:53,589
Driver, that was my stop.

19
00:03:05,727 --> 00:03:06,894
Driver, what's going on?

20
00:03:07,312 --> 00:03:09,105
Where are we going?

21
00:03:10,315 --> 00:03:12,108
Let us out. Come on.

22
00:03:12,276 --> 00:03:13,609
-Driver?
-What are you doing?

23
00:03:14,319 --> 00:03:15,778
Stop it!

24
00:03:25,372 --> 00:03:26,789
[SCREAMING]

25
00:03:26,957 --> 00:03:28,040
GIRLS:
Stop!

26
00:03:31,587 --> 00:03:32,753
Stop!

27
00:03:53,233 --> 00:03:54,609
Please. Please stop.

28
00:03:57,738 --> 00:04:00,239
GIRL 1: What's happening?
GIRL 2: I don't know.

29
00:04:01,033 --> 00:04:02,783
[GIRLS WHIMPERING]

30
00:04:06,538 --> 00:04:07,622
Oh, my God.

31
00:04:07,789 --> 00:04:10,041
What's going on?

32
00:04:12,002 --> 00:04:13,377
Oh, my God.

33
00:04:22,346 --> 00:04:24,138
Oh, my God. We're stuck here.

34
00:04:43,867 --> 00:04:46,702
GIRL 1:
Oh, my God! What is this?

35
00:04:58,966 --> 00:05:00,758
[SOBBING]

36
00:05:02,386 --> 00:05:03,427
[GASPS]

37
00:05:03,595 --> 00:05:04,887
What's that?

38
00:05:05,055 --> 00:05:06,472
[CHUCKLES]

39
00:05:06,640 --> 00:05:09,976
-What is it?
-Oh, my God, it's him! Come on!

40
00:05:10,143 --> 00:05:12,561
Oh, my God!

41
00:05:15,107 --> 00:05:16,232
[LAUGHS]

42
00:05:24,533 --> 00:05:26,534
Open this thing. He's coming!

43
00:05:29,788 --> 00:05:32,289
GIRL 1: No!
GIRL 2: God!

44
00:05:34,001 --> 00:05:36,836
-Oh, my God, come on!
-Save us!

45
00:05:43,969 --> 00:05:45,011
Get the door.

46
00:05:47,973 --> 00:05:49,473
[GIRLS SCREAMING]

47
00:05:53,562 --> 00:05:54,645
[FREDDY YELLS]

48
00:05:59,943 --> 00:06:02,945
[JESSE SCREAMING]

49
00:06:05,407 --> 00:06:08,993
Mommy, why can't Jesse wake up
like everybody else?

50
00:06:09,161 --> 00:06:10,619
Oh, honey, he's all right.

51
00:06:10,787 --> 00:06:13,247
He's just having a bad dream.

52
00:06:14,583 --> 00:06:15,875
[CLOCK TICKING]

53
00:06:16,418 --> 00:06:18,085
[ALARM RINGING]

54
00:06:49,701 --> 00:06:51,869
Mm. Thank you.

55
00:06:52,829 --> 00:06:53,996
Good morning, honey.

56
00:06:54,164 --> 00:06:55,414
Hi, Ma.

57
00:06:55,582 --> 00:06:58,667
Well, two more. Hallelujah.

58
00:06:59,127 --> 00:07:01,587
I want that room unpacked by tonight,
young man.

59
00:07:01,755 --> 00:07:03,047
Okay, Dad. I promise.

60
00:07:03,215 --> 00:07:05,674
I don't want any more promises,
Jesse.

61
00:07:05,842 --> 00:07:09,011
-I want that room cleaned up, okay?
-All right, I'll get on it.

62
00:07:11,181 --> 00:07:12,848
No.

63
00:07:13,016 --> 00:07:16,519
-Angie, what are you up to?
-I'm trying to get the Fuman fingers.

64
00:07:16,686 --> 00:07:18,187
CHERYL: Want some eggs?
JESSE: No.

65
00:07:19,147 --> 00:07:20,689
Jesse, are you okay?

66
00:07:20,857 --> 00:07:23,234
It's so hot up there,
I'm having trouble sleeping.

67
00:07:23,401 --> 00:07:26,737
I know. Ken, I wish you'd call
somebody and have the air conditioning--

68
00:07:26,905 --> 00:07:29,907
There's absolutely nothing wrong
with that air conditioning, Mom.

69
00:07:30,075 --> 00:07:31,367
Just needs a shot of Freon.

70
00:07:31,535 --> 00:07:32,785
-Here they are.
JESSE: Oh, no.

71
00:07:32,953 --> 00:07:35,871
Come on, Dad, you're not trying
to fix something again.

72
00:07:36,039 --> 00:07:37,873
Nobody likes a smart ass, buddy boy.

73
00:07:38,041 --> 00:07:39,083
CHERYL:
Look.

74
00:07:42,879 --> 00:07:44,421
[DOORBELL RINGS]

75
00:07:44,589 --> 00:07:46,048
Who's that?

76
00:07:46,675 --> 00:07:47,758
JESSE:
It's Lisa.

77
00:07:47,926 --> 00:07:48,968
I gotta get to school.

78
00:07:49,136 --> 00:07:51,428
Whoa, whoa. Who's Lisa?

79
00:07:52,973 --> 00:07:54,640
Who is Lisa?

80
00:07:54,933 --> 00:07:56,350
Just eat your eggs, dear.

81
00:08:04,526 --> 00:08:06,861
-Hi.
-Hi.

82
00:08:08,572 --> 00:08:10,406
[ENGINE STARTS]

83
00:08:10,574 --> 00:08:12,408
Don't you ever use a key?

84
00:08:12,576 --> 00:08:13,826
Why?

85
00:08:13,994 --> 00:08:16,579
Somebody could steal your car,
couldn't they?

86
00:08:16,746 --> 00:08:18,038
The deadly dinosaur?

87
00:08:19,082 --> 00:08:20,207
[CHUCKLES]

88
00:08:36,850 --> 00:08:38,642
[CHATTERING AND CHEERING]

89
00:08:38,935 --> 00:08:40,144
SCHNEIDER:
Strike.

90
00:08:40,312 --> 00:08:43,272
PLAYER 1:
Grady, come on, you can hit this stuff.

91
00:08:47,194 --> 00:08:49,111
You ready, girls?

92
00:08:50,655 --> 00:08:51,864
INSTRUCTOR:
That was very good.

93
00:08:52,032 --> 00:08:53,908
PLAYER 2:
Easy out.

94
00:08:54,451 --> 00:08:55,868
PLAYER 3:
Easy hit. Easy hit.

95
00:08:56,036 --> 00:08:57,661
-Ha!
-Strike.

96
00:08:57,829 --> 00:08:59,330
PLAYER 4:
Get him out of there already.

97
00:08:59,497 --> 00:09:01,457
Didn't feel right, okay?
Give me a break.

98
00:09:01,625 --> 00:09:03,250
So you getting any yet, Lise?

99
00:09:03,418 --> 00:09:05,836
Kerry, he's my ride to school, okay?

100
00:09:08,965 --> 00:09:10,299
PLAYER 5:
Put it out. Put it out.

101
00:09:12,052 --> 00:09:13,385
[GRUNTS]

102
00:09:18,308 --> 00:09:20,100
PLAYER 6: You all right?
JESSE: Yeah.

103
00:09:20,268 --> 00:09:21,977
PLAYER 7: You okay there?
-Yeah.

104
00:09:22,979 --> 00:09:25,439
PLAYER 8:
Good shot, good shot.

105
00:09:26,650 --> 00:09:27,983
You okay?

106
00:09:28,151 --> 00:09:29,360
Yeah, I'm fine.

107
00:09:29,527 --> 00:09:31,987
Well, pay attention next time.

108
00:09:32,155 --> 00:09:33,822
GRADY:
Very heads-up play.

109
00:09:33,990 --> 00:09:35,199
PLAYER 9:
Nice catch, Walsh.

110
00:09:35,367 --> 00:09:36,825
SCHNEIDER:
Come on, come on. Let's go.

111
00:09:37,869 --> 00:09:39,119
PLAYER 10:
Come on, Mitch.

112
00:09:40,121 --> 00:09:41,413
Come on, Mitch.

113
00:09:41,581 --> 00:09:42,915
PLAYER 11:
All right!

114
00:09:43,083 --> 00:09:44,333
[PLAYERS CHEERING]

115
00:09:47,420 --> 00:09:49,129
PLAYER 12:
Come on.

116
00:09:51,508 --> 00:09:53,008
PLAYER 13:
Knock him down.

117
00:09:53,843 --> 00:09:55,010
JESSE:
You're out.

118
00:09:55,178 --> 00:09:56,637
Heads up play, Grady.

119
00:09:56,805 --> 00:09:58,222
PLAYER 13:
All right! All right!

120
00:09:58,431 --> 00:09:59,640
[LISA CHUCKLES]

121
00:09:59,808 --> 00:10:01,850
Nice ass.

122
00:10:03,687 --> 00:10:05,562
[PLAYERS SHOUTING]
Come on! Get him!

123
00:10:05,730 --> 00:10:07,022
Come on, slug him!

124
00:10:07,190 --> 00:10:09,233
Go on, slug him!

125
00:10:09,859 --> 00:10:11,694
Slug him. Come on, slug him!

126
00:10:11,861 --> 00:10:13,028
Slug him!

127
00:10:13,196 --> 00:10:15,364
PLAYER 14: Here comes Schneider.
PLAYER 15: Watch out.

128
00:10:15,532 --> 00:10:17,992
-You can get him, come on!
SCHNEIDER: Get out of my way.

129
00:10:19,035 --> 00:10:20,286
-Come on.
-Okay, dirtballs.

130
00:10:20,453 --> 00:10:21,954
Come on.

131
00:10:22,455 --> 00:10:24,540
Assume the position.

132
00:10:33,466 --> 00:10:35,676
See you around, coach.

133
00:10:39,806 --> 00:10:41,515
BOY 1:
Hey, man, chill out, dude.

134
00:10:41,683 --> 00:10:43,475
BOY 2:
Shut up, dude.

135
00:10:47,897 --> 00:10:49,565
GIRL:
Come on. Come on.

136
00:10:51,192 --> 00:10:53,819
How much longer do you think
he's gonna keep us out here?

137
00:10:53,987 --> 00:10:55,571
It could be all night.

138
00:10:56,072 --> 00:10:58,032
The guy gets his rocks off like this.

139
00:10:58,199 --> 00:11:00,409
Hangs around queer
S&M joints downtown.

140
00:11:02,495 --> 00:11:04,413
He likes pretty boys like you.

141
00:11:04,581 --> 00:11:06,415
Get out of here.

142
00:11:09,085 --> 00:11:12,588
What about you and that babe you've
been cruising to school with every day?

143
00:11:12,756 --> 00:11:13,881
What about her?

144
00:11:14,049 --> 00:11:15,758
Are you mounting her nightly or what?

145
00:11:15,925 --> 00:11:18,427
Look, Grady,
you got some problem with me?

146
00:11:18,845 --> 00:11:20,012
No, bro.

147
00:11:20,180 --> 00:11:21,930
Just killing time.

148
00:11:22,098 --> 00:11:23,724
BOY 1:
Oh, God, that's gross.

149
00:11:23,892 --> 00:11:26,935
Okay, dirtballs, hit the shower.

150
00:11:27,145 --> 00:11:29,063
[BOTH PANTING]

151
00:11:33,777 --> 00:11:35,694
So you live around here or what?

152
00:11:35,862 --> 00:11:37,863
Yeah, my parents just bought a place
on Elm Street.

153
00:11:38,031 --> 00:11:39,490
Elm Street?

154
00:11:39,783 --> 00:11:42,618
You moved into that big white house
with bars in the window?

155
00:11:42,786 --> 00:11:43,869
Yeah, what about it?

156
00:11:44,037 --> 00:11:46,955
Shit. You can tell your old man
he's a real chump.

157
00:11:47,123 --> 00:11:49,416
What are you talking about now, Grady?

158
00:11:49,584 --> 00:11:52,878
Some chick was locked in there
by her mother and she went crazy.

159
00:11:53,630 --> 00:11:57,466
She watched her boyfriend get butchered
across the street by some maniac.

160
00:11:58,968 --> 00:12:01,095
You're full of shit, Grady.

161
00:12:06,893 --> 00:12:08,519
[DOG BARKING]

162
00:12:18,279 --> 00:12:20,030
[CLOCK TICKING]

163
00:12:27,080 --> 00:12:28,664
[SIGHS]

164
00:12:31,209 --> 00:12:33,001
[MUTTERING]

165
00:12:49,352 --> 00:12:50,853
[SIGHS]

166
00:13:10,748 --> 00:13:12,583
[DOOR SLAMS IN DISTANCE]

167
00:13:20,717 --> 00:13:22,551
[DOOR SQUEAKS NEARBY]

168
00:13:35,607 --> 00:13:37,357
[FIRE CRACKLING]

169
00:14:45,343 --> 00:14:46,802
Dad?

170
00:14:47,011 --> 00:14:49,179
[HEAVY BREATHING]

171
00:14:50,139 --> 00:14:51,682
Dad!

172
00:14:55,645 --> 00:14:57,020
Help!

173
00:14:59,482 --> 00:15:01,858
Daddy can't help you now.

174
00:15:03,361 --> 00:15:05,320
Shh.

175
00:15:11,077 --> 00:15:13,662
I need you, Jesse.

176
00:15:14,414 --> 00:15:17,499
We've got special work to do here,
you and me.

177
00:15:22,297 --> 00:15:24,590
You've got the body...

178
00:15:25,967 --> 00:15:28,218
...I've got the brain.

179
00:15:29,053 --> 00:15:30,679
[CHUCKLING]

180
00:15:30,847 --> 00:15:32,514
[SCREAMS]

181
00:15:32,974 --> 00:15:34,766
[LAUGHING]

182
00:15:35,351 --> 00:15:37,060
[SCREAMS]

183
00:15:38,521 --> 00:15:40,355
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]

184
00:15:41,566 --> 00:15:42,608
Jess?

185
00:15:42,775 --> 00:15:44,526
Jesse.

186
00:15:46,362 --> 00:15:49,072
-Do you think we should call the doctor?
-No.

187
00:15:49,240 --> 00:15:50,824
No, I'm fine.

188
00:15:50,992 --> 00:15:54,202
It's just a bad dream, okay?

189
00:15:55,121 --> 00:15:56,371
Yeah.

190
00:15:56,956 --> 00:15:58,707
Yeah, go to sleep.

191
00:16:02,295 --> 00:16:05,297
So to review.

192
00:16:05,465 --> 00:16:09,885
The solid wastes, those nutrients
not absorbed in the lining of the stomach...

193
00:16:10,053 --> 00:16:12,888
...the large intestine,
the small intestine...

194
00:16:13,056 --> 00:16:16,016
...and the elementary canal
are passed out through the colon.

195
00:16:16,184 --> 00:16:17,309
[BOY MlMICS FARTING NOISE]

196
00:16:17,477 --> 00:16:18,560
[SNICKERING]

197
00:16:19,771 --> 00:16:23,357
Liquid nutrients are then carried
through an elaborate system of filtering...

198
00:16:23,524 --> 00:16:27,235
...aided by the pancreas, liver
and gall bladder.. .

199
00:16:27,403 --> 00:16:31,073
...or collected in the bladder
to be expelled at a later time.

200
00:16:31,240 --> 00:16:32,449
[MIMICS VOMITING SOUND]

201
00:16:32,909 --> 00:16:34,951
And this entire process is kept moving...

202
00:16:35,119 --> 00:16:39,623
...through the circulatory system,
the center of which is...

203
00:16:42,627 --> 00:16:43,710
...the heart.

204
00:16:43,878 --> 00:16:46,713
-Yeah!
GIRL: Ew.

205
00:16:47,340 --> 00:16:48,590
TEACHER:
Four chambers.

206
00:16:48,758 --> 00:16:50,467
Just like the human heart, really.

207
00:16:52,178 --> 00:16:56,306
From the body to the right auricle,
to the right ventricle...

208
00:16:56,474 --> 00:16:59,101
...and out the pulmonary arteries
to the lungs.

209
00:16:59,268 --> 00:17:02,979
There it trades off carbon dioxide
for oxygen.

210
00:17:03,147 --> 00:17:07,401
Carbon dioxide is exhaled
and the oxygenated blood continues to...

211
00:17:11,030 --> 00:17:14,783
Into the left auricle through
the left ventricle passing out of the...

212
00:17:35,513 --> 00:17:36,805
No!

213
00:17:37,140 --> 00:17:38,306
[STUDENTS GASP]

214
00:17:38,474 --> 00:17:40,350
[STUDENTS SNICKERING]

215
00:17:46,607 --> 00:17:51,153
If you wanna play with animals, Mr. Walsh,
join the circus.

216
00:17:51,362 --> 00:17:52,946
[STUDENTS CHUCKLING]

217
00:18:00,288 --> 00:18:01,830
[LAUGHS]

218
00:18:10,173 --> 00:18:14,092
Lisa, sweetheart,
there's a Jesse on the phone.

219
00:18:14,260 --> 00:18:16,511
Okay. Thanks, Mom.

220
00:18:29,901 --> 00:18:31,318
Jesse?

221
00:18:31,486 --> 00:18:32,527
Hi.

222
00:18:32,695 --> 00:18:34,237
WOMAN [ON TV]:
<i>On the national front...</i>

223
00:18:34,405 --> 00:18:36,698
-Where are you going, Jess?
-Just out for a little while.

224
00:18:36,866 --> 00:18:39,451
I told you I want that room unpacked.

225
00:18:39,619 --> 00:18:41,620
-I'm just going out for an hour or two.
-No.

226
00:18:41,788 --> 00:18:43,121
Upstairs.

227
00:18:43,289 --> 00:18:44,873
Right now, son.

228
00:18:45,041 --> 00:18:46,500
Right now.

229
00:18:55,218 --> 00:18:56,927
[GRUMBLES]

230
00:19:10,274 --> 00:19:11,608
[WISH'S "TOUCH ME" PLAYING]

231
00:19:11,776 --> 00:19:15,612
<i>Ooh, you know how to love me, yeah</i>

232
00:19:16,531 --> 00:19:19,908
<i>When we make love tonight</i>

233
00:19:20,243 --> 00:19:21,409
How do you like that, Dad?

234
00:19:21,577 --> 00:19:23,453
<i>I need you so bad, baby</i>

235
00:19:25,039 --> 00:19:26,832
<i>Oh, oh</i>

236
00:19:28,251 --> 00:19:31,211
<i>This is where you belong</i>

237
00:19:32,421 --> 00:19:38,969
<i>Don't make me wait too long</i>

238
00:19:39,136 --> 00:19:41,721
<i>No</i>

239
00:19:42,932 --> 00:19:45,851
<i>All night long</i>

240
00:19:52,275 --> 00:19:56,236
<i>Hold me, baby</i>
<i>Drive me crazy</i>

241
00:19:56,529 --> 00:20:00,448
<i>Touch me all night long</i>

242
00:20:00,616 --> 00:20:03,577
<i>Make me love you</i>
<i>Kiss and hug you</i>

243
00:20:03,744 --> 00:20:05,161
Jesse.

244
00:20:05,329 --> 00:20:09,040
<i>Touch me all night long</i>

245
00:20:09,625 --> 00:20:12,377
<i>You're my candy man</i>

246
00:20:14,380 --> 00:20:15,755
[MUSIC STOPS]

247
00:20:15,965 --> 00:20:18,967
Ha. I'll, uh--
I'll leave the two of you alone.

248
00:20:19,135 --> 00:20:20,552
Excuse me.

249
00:20:26,225 --> 00:20:28,894
I told her you invited me over.

250
00:20:29,061 --> 00:20:31,313
I guess maybe I should have called.

251
00:20:31,480 --> 00:20:33,982
No. Ha, ha. It's fine, really.

252
00:20:34,775 --> 00:20:36,484
I mean, I was just cleaning my room.

253
00:20:36,652 --> 00:20:38,028
I know.

254
00:20:38,487 --> 00:20:41,448
I figured you might like some help.

255
00:20:48,664 --> 00:20:50,290
Where does this go?

256
00:20:53,336 --> 00:20:55,545
Um...
Do your sweaters go in the closet?

257
00:21:09,226 --> 00:21:10,685
What's this?

258
00:21:10,853 --> 00:21:13,939
JESSE:
I don't know. Looks like a diary to me.

259
00:21:18,694 --> 00:21:20,111
Let's see.

260
00:21:20,279 --> 00:21:23,198
"Nancy Thompson. 1428 Elm Street."

261
00:21:23,366 --> 00:21:25,033
That's right here.

262
00:21:27,161 --> 00:21:29,829
Hey, you know,
this thing is five years old.

263
00:21:29,997 --> 00:21:33,959
-You know her?
-Uh-uh. No. Before my time.

264
00:21:35,836 --> 00:21:37,087
Wait, listen to this.

265
00:21:37,755 --> 00:21:39,631
"Sometimes when I'm lying here in bed...

266
00:21:39,799 --> 00:21:44,094
...I can see Glen in his window
across the way getting ready for bed.

267
00:21:44,887 --> 00:21:46,513
His body is slim and smooth...

268
00:21:46,681 --> 00:21:50,934
...and I know I shouldn't watch him
but that part of me that wants him...

269
00:21:51,102 --> 00:21:53,228
...forces me to.

270
00:21:53,646 --> 00:21:54,854
That's when I weaken.

271
00:21:55,022 --> 00:21:56,940
That's when I wanna go to him."

272
00:21:59,902 --> 00:22:01,486
-Can I see that?
-Mm-hm.

273
00:22:04,573 --> 00:22:06,825
"March 15th.

274
00:22:06,993 --> 00:22:08,535
He comes to me at night.

275
00:22:08,703 --> 00:22:12,580
Horrible, ugly, dirty,
under the sheets with me.

276
00:22:12,748 --> 00:22:13,790
[LISA CHUCKLING]

277
00:22:13,958 --> 00:22:17,585
Tearing at my nightgown
with his steel claws.

278
00:22:20,756 --> 00:22:22,757
His name is Fred...

279
00:22:22,925 --> 00:22:25,510
...and he keeps trying to take me
to the boiler room.

280
00:22:27,054 --> 00:22:29,014
He wants to kill me."

281
00:22:35,146 --> 00:22:36,771
What is it?

282
00:22:40,234 --> 00:22:42,527
"Tina is dead."

283
00:22:46,449 --> 00:22:48,408
Jesse, are you okay?

284
00:22:49,910 --> 00:22:52,495
It's just something
that Grady said to me.

285
00:22:53,748 --> 00:22:56,124
About the girl that used to live here?

286
00:22:56,292 --> 00:23:00,462
How she went crazy when she saw her
boyfriend get murdered across the street.

287
00:23:18,189 --> 00:23:19,981
JESSE:
Ugh.

288
00:23:42,505 --> 00:23:44,547
[PANTING NERVOUSLY]

289
00:24:27,883 --> 00:24:29,884
[WATER DRIPPING NEARBY]

290
00:25:14,763 --> 00:25:16,598
[SQUEAKING]

291
00:25:45,085 --> 00:25:47,503
[FREDDY LAUGHING]

292
00:25:51,091 --> 00:25:53,092
Go ahead, Jesse.

293
00:25:53,260 --> 00:25:54,510
Try it on for size.

294
00:26:02,686 --> 00:26:04,229
[SIZZLING]

295
00:26:04,396 --> 00:26:06,147
Kill for me.

296
00:26:26,335 --> 00:26:28,211
JESSE:
It was kind of like I was sleepwalking.

297
00:26:28,379 --> 00:26:31,089
LISA: Maybe you were having
a premonition or something, you know.

298
00:26:31,257 --> 00:26:35,009
Like the guys who help police
solve crimes and find missing people.

299
00:26:35,177 --> 00:26:36,844
Ever have anything like this
happen before?

300
00:26:37,012 --> 00:26:38,346
Nope. Never.

301
00:26:38,514 --> 00:26:41,557
-You think that's what it is?
-I don't know.

302
00:26:42,142 --> 00:26:44,394
Can I see the diary for a little while?

303
00:26:45,396 --> 00:26:46,521
Thanks.

304
00:26:46,689 --> 00:26:48,940
-Hi, guys.
-Hi, Kerry.

305
00:26:49,108 --> 00:26:51,985
I got your invitation
for the party this weekend.

306
00:26:52,152 --> 00:26:53,611
Any cute guys gonna be there?

307
00:26:53,779 --> 00:26:55,488
All of them. Ha, ha.

308
00:26:55,656 --> 00:26:58,533
Is your dad gonna be the DJ again?

309
00:26:58,701 --> 00:27:01,327
-Mom is gonna keep him upstairs this time.
-Oh, good.

310
00:27:01,495 --> 00:27:03,037
Uh, ha, ha.

311
00:27:03,205 --> 00:27:04,205
Last party I had...

312
00:27:04,373 --> 00:27:07,250
...my Dad insisted on playing
Benny Goodman records all night.

313
00:27:07,418 --> 00:27:08,793
[BELL RINGS]

314
00:27:08,961 --> 00:27:11,587
-Well, I'll see you later, okay?
-Okay.

315
00:27:24,810 --> 00:27:27,562
Hey, Grady,
do you remember your dreams?

316
00:27:27,730 --> 00:27:29,230
Only the wet ones.

317
00:27:29,398 --> 00:27:31,024
No talking.

318
00:27:32,067 --> 00:27:34,068
BOY:
Hey, Grady.

319
00:27:37,906 --> 00:27:41,075
You know, Schneider shouldn't have called
you out on that last play.

320
00:27:41,243 --> 00:27:44,704
Yeah, well, Schneider has got
a stick up his ass today.

321
00:27:44,872 --> 00:27:46,956
Schneider's always got a stick up his ass.

322
00:27:47,124 --> 00:27:48,166
[JESSE CHUCKLES]

323
00:27:48,334 --> 00:27:50,251
Hello, dirtballs.

324
00:27:52,921 --> 00:27:54,547
[PANTING AND GRUNTING]

325
00:28:02,765 --> 00:28:04,432
[CHIRPING]

326
00:28:13,609 --> 00:28:17,195
-Ugh. It is so hot in here.
-Yeah, babe.

327
00:28:18,822 --> 00:28:21,240
Let me look at the thermostat.

328
00:28:29,750 --> 00:28:32,752
My God, it is hot as an oven in here.

329
00:28:32,920 --> 00:28:36,506
Shh. The birds are sleeping.

330
00:28:37,132 --> 00:28:40,676
Cheryl, it's 97 degrees in here.

331
00:28:43,347 --> 00:28:45,056
[RATTLING]

332
00:28:57,111 --> 00:28:58,611
[BIRDS SCREECHING]

333
00:29:00,322 --> 00:29:01,948
Damn it. Ow!

334
00:29:02,116 --> 00:29:03,157
[ANGIE SHRIEKS]

335
00:29:03,325 --> 00:29:04,325
CHERYL:
Angela, watch out.

336
00:29:06,537 --> 00:29:07,620
KEN:
Watch out, Jesse.

337
00:29:09,623 --> 00:29:10,998
-Ah!
CHERYL: Ken, are you all right?

338
00:29:11,166 --> 00:29:15,294
Cheryl-- Damn bird.
Look out, Angela, get out.

339
00:29:16,463 --> 00:29:18,089
Look out, Jesse.

340
00:29:20,426 --> 00:29:21,926
CHERYL: Come on.
KEN: Look out, Angela.

341
00:29:22,094 --> 00:29:23,469
[SCREAMS]

342
00:29:25,097 --> 00:29:26,597
Jesse, get out of here.

343
00:29:26,765 --> 00:29:28,224
Cheryl.

344
00:29:52,249 --> 00:29:54,584
What are you doing, Jesse?
Help me move this thing.

345
00:29:54,751 --> 00:29:57,420
JESSE: It isn't the gas.
-Don't tell me it's not the gas.

346
00:29:57,588 --> 00:29:59,589
Your mother thought she smelled gas.

347
00:29:59,756 --> 00:30:03,384
-Well, I thought I did, I wasn't sure.
-All right, so, what is it, bird rabies?

348
00:30:03,552 --> 00:30:06,387
-It's that seed you've been buying.
CHERYL: Please, Ken, really.

349
00:30:06,555 --> 00:30:08,848
No, it could be.
Got to be a rational explanation.

350
00:30:09,016 --> 00:30:11,642
Animals don't explode into flames
for no reason, do they?

351
00:30:11,810 --> 00:30:13,478
-That's right.
-All right.

352
00:30:13,645 --> 00:30:15,146
Well, it's sure not a leaky gas pipe.

353
00:30:15,314 --> 00:30:16,772
[GRUNTS]

354
00:30:17,566 --> 00:30:19,817
-You all right?
-Oh, it's all right.

355
00:30:19,985 --> 00:30:22,945
You set this whole thing up,
didn't you?

356
00:30:24,239 --> 00:30:25,531
What are you talking about?

357
00:30:25,699 --> 00:30:28,618
You know what I'm talking about.
What did you use, firecrackers?

358
00:30:28,785 --> 00:30:31,204
You know what he did,
he used a goddamn cherry bomb.

359
00:30:31,371 --> 00:30:32,788
CHERYL: Stop it.
-That's what he did.

360
00:30:32,956 --> 00:30:34,624
Look, you can't talk to me like that.

361
00:30:34,791 --> 00:30:36,250
-Jesse, come back. Jesse.
-Ken.

362
00:30:36,418 --> 00:30:38,669
-Come back, Jesse!
-Stop it, you're being ridiculous.

363
00:30:38,837 --> 00:30:39,879
-Now come on, stop it.
-Jesse!

364
00:30:53,477 --> 00:30:54,977
Shit.

365
00:30:56,939 --> 00:30:58,147
[SIGHS]

366
00:30:58,941 --> 00:31:00,608
[WlND HOWLING]

367
00:31:13,121 --> 00:31:15,081
[THUNDER CRASHES]

368
00:31:52,953 --> 00:31:54,787
[CHATTERING]

369
00:31:54,955 --> 00:31:57,081
[SYNTH ROCK MUSIC
PLAYING OVER SPEAKERS]

370
00:31:59,376 --> 00:32:00,835
WOMAN 1:
Oh, jeez.

371
00:32:01,003 --> 00:32:05,006
-I don't know, he always wants to--
WOMAN 2: Don't touch me.

372
00:32:38,582 --> 00:32:40,875
Can I have a beer, please?

373
00:33:37,808 --> 00:33:39,100
Hit the shower.

374
00:34:02,624 --> 00:34:04,291
[DOOR CREAKS]

375
00:34:26,189 --> 00:34:27,690
[TWANGING]

376
00:34:45,167 --> 00:34:53,924
[GRUNTS]

377
00:35:01,308 --> 00:35:03,017
[CREAKING]

378
00:35:10,358 --> 00:35:11,817
[GRUNTS]

379
00:35:48,855 --> 00:35:52,566
No, no, no! No!

380
00:35:59,825 --> 00:36:01,700
No, no!

381
00:36:01,868 --> 00:36:04,078
No, goddamn it, no!

382
00:36:04,246 --> 00:36:06,247
[SCREAMS]

383
00:36:10,335 --> 00:36:11,502
No!

384
00:36:26,518 --> 00:36:27,810
[YELLS]

385
00:36:49,124 --> 00:36:51,458
No, no.

386
00:36:52,627 --> 00:36:56,255
No!

387
00:37:17,694 --> 00:37:19,278
[SCREAMS]

388
00:37:19,446 --> 00:37:21,655
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]

389
00:37:24,951 --> 00:37:26,827
Oh, boy.

390
00:37:28,663 --> 00:37:30,789
Good evening, uh,
does this belong to you?

391
00:37:30,957 --> 00:37:33,042
Uh, yes, sir, he's my son.

392
00:37:33,209 --> 00:37:35,544
COP 1: We found him out on the highway
wandering around.

393
00:37:35,712 --> 00:37:38,672
He was naked.

394
00:37:38,840 --> 00:37:41,008
I'd keep a short leash on him
if I were you.

395
00:37:41,176 --> 00:37:42,217
Thank you, officer.

396
00:37:42,385 --> 00:37:44,970
Jesse, come here, come.

397
00:37:45,138 --> 00:37:47,389
KEN:
Hey, hey.

398
00:37:49,351 --> 00:37:50,768
Come here.

399
00:37:52,562 --> 00:37:54,730
Two questions.

400
00:37:54,898 --> 00:37:57,650
You answer them and
we can all go to bed, all right?

401
00:38:02,364 --> 00:38:04,490
What are you taking, son?

402
00:38:04,950 --> 00:38:06,867
Who are you getting it from?

403
00:38:08,995 --> 00:38:11,538
I'm not taking drugs.

404
00:38:13,083 --> 00:38:16,293
-Mom, I wanna go to bed.
-Yeah, come on.

405
00:38:28,848 --> 00:38:31,058
JESSE: It's just a problem I have
to work out on my own.

406
00:38:31,226 --> 00:38:32,893
-But something's bothering you.
JESSE: Mom.

407
00:38:33,061 --> 00:38:34,812
We're just concerned
about you-- Jesse.

408
00:38:34,980 --> 00:38:36,897
-I'm fine, just leave me alone.
-Can't--?

409
00:38:37,649 --> 00:38:40,317
-Can't we at least talk about it?
-No.

410
00:38:44,489 --> 00:38:46,407
[ENGINE REVS]

411
00:38:51,788 --> 00:38:55,249
He needs professional help. I think
we have to take him to a psychiatrist.

412
00:38:55,417 --> 00:38:58,419
Come on, Cheryl, you're out of your gourd.
What will that do?

413
00:38:58,586 --> 00:39:01,422
I don't know. He needs help
and we don't know how to give it.

414
00:39:01,589 --> 00:39:03,924
-Oh, come on, Cheryl.
-Are you hearing me?

415
00:39:04,092 --> 00:39:07,594
-That boy's in trouble.
-No, he's not in trouble.

416
00:39:07,762 --> 00:39:10,264
What that boy needs is
a good goddamn kick in the butt.

417
00:39:10,432 --> 00:39:12,016
That's what he needs.

418
00:39:12,892 --> 00:39:16,270
I'll tell you what he needs.
He needs a methadone clinic.

419
00:39:21,151 --> 00:39:22,693
[HORN HONKS]

420
00:39:29,034 --> 00:39:30,951
[INDISTINCT RADIO CHATTER]

421
00:39:33,997 --> 00:39:35,956
LISA:
What's happening?

422
00:39:36,708 --> 00:39:40,002
TEACHER: I want all you students
back to your classes...

423
00:39:41,546 --> 00:39:43,964
Don't worry about what... .

424
00:39:44,132 --> 00:39:47,134
Just don't worry about it.
Let them do their work, all right?

425
00:39:47,302 --> 00:39:48,802
Yo, man, where have you been?

426
00:39:48,970 --> 00:39:51,138
-Schneider got wasted last night.
-Oh, my God.

427
00:39:51,306 --> 00:39:54,641
He must have been working late.
Some maniac sliced him like a kielbasa.

428
00:39:54,809 --> 00:39:58,228
Hacked him in the shower.
Got bloody footprints all over the place.

429
00:39:58,396 --> 00:39:59,730
COP:
Stand back from the line, please.

430
00:39:59,898 --> 00:40:00,939
[SIRENS WAILING]

431
00:40:06,112 --> 00:40:07,946
[METALLIC GRINDING]

432
00:40:36,601 --> 00:40:39,853
FREDDY:
<i>Kill for me.</i>

433
00:40:45,443 --> 00:40:48,112
[RHYTHMIC THUDDING]

434
00:41:01,751 --> 00:41:04,795
ANGIE [SINGING]:
<i>One, two</i>

435
00:41:04,963 --> 00:41:10,050
<i>Freddy's coming for you</i>

436
00:41:10,218 --> 00:41:14,179
<i>Three, four</i>

437
00:41:14,347 --> 00:41:19,560
<i>Better lock your door</i>

438
00:41:20,728 --> 00:41:23,480
<i>Five, six</i>

439
00:41:23,648 --> 00:41:28,485
<i>Grab your crucifix</i>

440
00:41:33,116 --> 00:41:35,909
-Morning, Jess.
-Morning.

441
00:41:45,211 --> 00:41:49,256
Dad, how come it took them
five years to sell this house?

442
00:41:49,424 --> 00:41:50,424
Oh, I don't know.

443
00:41:50,592 --> 00:41:52,885
They just couldn't get
the right price, I suppose.

444
00:41:53,052 --> 00:41:55,179
Didn't know about the murder
across the street?

445
00:41:55,346 --> 00:41:57,598
The girl that lived here
that saw the whole thing.

446
00:41:57,765 --> 00:41:59,933
They told me something
about it, yeah, but I--

447
00:42:00,101 --> 00:42:02,394
-You knew something about this--
-Come on, Cheryl.

448
00:42:02,562 --> 00:42:05,939
How do you think we got
such a good deal here, hon?

449
00:42:06,191 --> 00:42:09,109
Did they tell you that
that girl lost her mind?

450
00:42:09,277 --> 00:42:11,612
And her mother killed herself
in our living room?

451
00:42:11,779 --> 00:42:13,447
-What?
-Did they tell you that?

452
00:42:13,615 --> 00:42:15,866
Mom, I'm scared.

453
00:42:16,034 --> 00:42:18,368
-Come here.
-Oh, honey, it's all right.

454
00:42:18,536 --> 00:42:20,913
Daddy and Jesse
are just pretending, that's all.

455
00:42:21,080 --> 00:42:23,290
I don't think this is something
we should discuss.

456
00:42:23,458 --> 00:42:25,542
KEN: See? Don't wanna hear
one more word about it.

457
00:42:25,710 --> 00:42:28,962
There's absolutely nothing,
I mean nothing, wrong with this house.

458
00:42:29,130 --> 00:42:30,547
Come on.

459
00:42:31,049 --> 00:42:32,799
Is something burning?

460
00:42:32,967 --> 00:42:34,635
[CRACKLING]

461
00:42:36,638 --> 00:42:37,763
Good Lord.

462
00:42:48,149 --> 00:42:51,443
It's the craziest damn thing
I've ever seen.

463
00:42:52,278 --> 00:42:54,488
Look here, Cheryl.

464
00:42:54,656 --> 00:42:56,657
It wasn't even plugged in.

465
00:43:00,787 --> 00:43:04,164
LISA: Jesse, you can't blame yourself
for what happened to Schneider.

466
00:43:04,332 --> 00:43:06,833
And just because you dreamt it
doesn't mean you did it.

467
00:43:07,001 --> 00:43:09,753
JESSE: Where are we going?
LISA: Veer left over here.

468
00:43:12,674 --> 00:43:15,342
Look, I really think
this is all in your mind, you know...

469
00:43:15,510 --> 00:43:17,803
...like you're picking up
some psychic signals.

470
00:43:41,703 --> 00:43:45,080
Wow, what is this place?

471
00:43:46,916 --> 00:43:48,250
Do you remember in the diary?

472
00:43:48,418 --> 00:43:51,211
When Nancy said she kept finding herself
in a boiler room?

473
00:43:51,379 --> 00:43:55,507
Well, Fred Krueger worked here.
It's an old power plant.

474
00:43:57,677 --> 00:44:00,512
-Here.
-What is all this?

475
00:44:00,680 --> 00:44:04,266
I did some reading on our friend,
Fred Krueger.

476
00:44:22,410 --> 00:44:24,578
-How long has it been closed down?
-A long time.

477
00:44:24,996 --> 00:44:26,413
Come on.

478
00:44:29,459 --> 00:44:30,876
Jesus.

479
00:44:31,044 --> 00:44:33,086
Fred Krueger kidnapped 20 kids.. .

480
00:44:33,254 --> 00:44:36,757
...and brought them here and killed them.

481
00:44:44,891 --> 00:44:48,060
-Do you feel anything?
-What do you mean?

482
00:44:48,227 --> 00:44:52,064
I don't know. I thought you might be able
to make a connection or something.

483
00:45:00,823 --> 00:45:04,117
-I feel like a jerk.
-Shh. Just concentrate.

484
00:45:12,835 --> 00:45:15,170
Do you feel anything?

485
00:45:15,463 --> 00:45:17,130
Uh-uh.

486
00:45:57,630 --> 00:45:58,755
[SQUEAKING]

487
00:45:58,923 --> 00:46:00,006
[LISA GASPS]

488
00:46:05,096 --> 00:46:06,596
[LISA SIGHS]

489
00:46:43,676 --> 00:46:46,720
FREDDY:
Wake up, little girl.

490
00:46:50,725 --> 00:46:52,809
What time is it?

491
00:46:58,357 --> 00:47:02,736
It's late, go back to sleep.

492
00:47:27,970 --> 00:47:32,098
CHERYL: Morning, honey.
Did you sleep okay?

493
00:47:32,266 --> 00:47:34,100
Yeah, fine.

494
00:47:34,268 --> 00:47:37,437
Good. You're looking better.

495
00:47:48,032 --> 00:47:50,575
You had another nightmare, didn't you?

496
00:47:50,743 --> 00:47:52,702
Yes, I had a bad night.

497
00:47:52,870 --> 00:47:55,080
Do you wanna talk about it?

498
00:47:56,624 --> 00:47:58,708
My dad thinks I'm on drugs.

499
00:47:58,876 --> 00:48:00,418
My mom thinks I'm crazy.

500
00:48:00,586 --> 00:48:03,880
And you know, at this point,
I don't know if I don't agree with her.

501
00:48:07,385 --> 00:48:10,762
Hey, what's wrong with Jesse?
He seems kind of freaked out.

502
00:48:14,976 --> 00:48:17,310
Hey, wanna go to a movie
or something, hang out?

503
00:48:17,478 --> 00:48:20,272
Maybe get these things off your mind.
Get a pizza or something.

504
00:48:20,439 --> 00:48:22,107
LISA:
Hey, guys.

505
00:48:23,985 --> 00:48:25,694
Hi, Ronnie.

506
00:48:26,904 --> 00:48:29,155
-You going to Lisa's house tomorrow night?
-No.

507
00:48:29,323 --> 00:48:32,200
-I can't, I'm grounded.
-How come?

508
00:48:32,368 --> 00:48:35,495
I threw my grandmother
down a flight of stairs.

509
00:48:36,163 --> 00:48:37,914
Jesse.

510
00:48:38,082 --> 00:48:39,916
Jesse, I think
you should eat something.

511
00:48:40,084 --> 00:48:43,003
-I'm not hungry.
-I wish you would talk to me.

512
00:48:43,170 --> 00:48:46,506
You know, we can figure it out.
We can figure it out together.

513
00:48:46,674 --> 00:48:48,341
There is nothing to figure out.

514
00:48:49,343 --> 00:48:51,177
I don't know
why you're wasting your time.

515
00:48:51,345 --> 00:48:54,306
-He's a basket case.
-Shut up, Grady.

516
00:48:55,641 --> 00:49:00,270
Want me to shut up?
Fine, I'll shut up, no problem.

517
00:49:00,438 --> 00:49:02,355
See you around, buddy.

518
00:49:09,614 --> 00:49:12,115
[BIG BAND JAZZ MUSIC
PLAYING ON STEREO]

519
00:49:17,705 --> 00:49:19,372
Here you are.

520
00:49:35,306 --> 00:49:36,473
[ALL CHEERING]

521
00:49:36,641 --> 00:49:37,932
BOY 1: Hey.
BOY 2: All right.

522
00:49:38,100 --> 00:49:39,726
Hey, now cut that out.

523
00:49:41,020 --> 00:49:42,729
I've got it.

524
00:49:44,482 --> 00:49:46,733
MR. WEBBER:
But, sweetheart, it's a nice party.

525
00:49:46,901 --> 00:49:49,778
Come on, Skinny, it's time for bed.

526
00:49:51,447 --> 00:49:53,698
You're in charge, hotshot.

527
00:49:56,285 --> 00:49:58,745
Twelve-thirty, miss, no later.

528
00:49:58,913 --> 00:50:01,665
-Twelve-thirty.
-Have a nice time.

529
00:50:08,589 --> 00:50:10,090
Hi.

530
00:50:10,966 --> 00:50:13,176
What's the matter with Jesse?

531
00:50:13,344 --> 00:50:15,095
I don't know.

532
00:50:20,643 --> 00:50:21,726
[KNOCK ON DOOR]

533
00:50:21,894 --> 00:50:24,979
-Jesse?
JESSE: I'll be out in a second.

534
00:50:25,147 --> 00:50:27,982
Can I please come in and talk to you?

535
00:50:38,661 --> 00:50:40,286
[JESSE SIGHS]

536
00:50:41,872 --> 00:50:45,291
Listen, I'm gonna leave. I'm not into this.

537
00:50:46,335 --> 00:50:48,128
I'm sorry.

538
00:50:48,295 --> 00:50:51,256
Jesse, why won't you talk to me?

539
00:50:53,718 --> 00:50:56,803
-Will you just leave me alone?
-You're not being fair.

540
00:50:57,430 --> 00:50:59,514
I wanna help you.

541
00:51:00,099 --> 00:51:02,100
How can you help me?

542
00:51:02,935 --> 00:51:04,436
What are you gonna do for me?

543
00:51:04,854 --> 00:51:08,440
Look, I feel like I'm losing my mind.

544
00:51:09,108 --> 00:51:12,318
And I don't want you
to watch me fall apart.

545
00:51:12,486 --> 00:51:16,114
I'm afraid to go to sleep.

546
00:51:16,282 --> 00:51:17,907
I'm afraid to stay awake.

547
00:51:18,325 --> 00:51:20,535
I'm ruining your party.

548
00:51:20,703 --> 00:51:23,830
-They're gonna take me away.
-Come on, don't say that.

549
00:51:23,998 --> 00:51:26,082
Listen, we'll stay up all night
if we have to.

550
00:51:26,250 --> 00:51:29,711
I'm not gonna let anything
happen to you.

551
00:52:05,915 --> 00:52:08,708
Come on, any second now, any second.

552
00:52:08,876 --> 00:52:10,543
[CHUCKLES]

553
00:52:22,181 --> 00:52:23,973
Yeah, party time.

554
00:52:24,141 --> 00:52:25,558
[ALL CHEERING]

555
00:52:26,477 --> 00:52:27,560
GIRL:
I got the music.

556
00:52:31,106 --> 00:52:33,107
[BOBBY ORLANDO'S
"WHlSPER TO A SCREAM" PLAYING]

557
00:52:36,153 --> 00:52:42,325
<i>I wanna tell you</i>
<i>Exactly how I feel</i>

558
00:52:44,578 --> 00:52:47,497
-What the hell are they doing down there?
-Oh, Eddie, they're kids.

559
00:52:47,665 --> 00:52:50,917
I know they're kids.
I gotta get some rest.

560
00:52:51,085 --> 00:52:56,965
<i>Now that you're leaving</i>
<i>lt's time that I confess</i>

561
00:52:58,092 --> 00:53:01,845
<i>The way we planned our love together</i>

562
00:53:02,012 --> 00:53:04,681
<i>Sometimes doing more is less</i>

563
00:53:05,057 --> 00:53:12,063
<i>From a whisper to a scream</i>
<i>Now I know just what it means</i>

564
00:53:12,439 --> 00:53:18,361
<i>From a whisper to a scream</i>
<i>I said I love you</i>

565
00:53:19,613 --> 00:53:26,369
<i>From a whisper to a scream</i>
<i>Now I know just what it means</i>

566
00:53:35,337 --> 00:53:41,593
<i>Yesterday you were only mine</i>
<i>Today you're loving somebody new</i>

567
00:53:44,138 --> 00:53:45,805
What is it?

568
00:53:47,516 --> 00:53:49,809
Jesse, what's wrong?

569
00:53:55,816 --> 00:53:56,900
[SIGHS]

570
00:53:57,067 --> 00:53:59,402
[LAUGHING AND CHEERING]

571
00:54:04,366 --> 00:54:05,491
[MUFFLED YELL]

572
00:54:05,659 --> 00:54:09,537
Jesus Christ,
you scared the shit out of me, man.

573
00:54:09,705 --> 00:54:12,498
Hey, what are you doing?

574
00:54:15,586 --> 00:54:18,171
Hey, what the fuck are you doing
in my room?

575
00:54:19,214 --> 00:54:22,592
Listen, I'm in trouble.

576
00:54:22,760 --> 00:54:24,594
I need you to let me stay here tonight.

577
00:54:24,762 --> 00:54:26,304
Are you out of your mind?

578
00:54:27,222 --> 00:54:28,681
I don't know.

579
00:54:29,975 --> 00:54:31,851
Oh, man.

580
00:54:35,189 --> 00:54:38,483
Why don't you just go home
and take a bottle of sleeping pills?

581
00:54:40,444 --> 00:54:42,153
I killed Schneider.

582
00:54:42,863 --> 00:54:44,489
You what?

583
00:54:44,657 --> 00:54:46,866
Only it wasn't me, see?

584
00:54:47,034 --> 00:54:48,868
There's something inside of me.

585
00:54:49,036 --> 00:54:51,663
And last night it made me go
to my sister's room.

586
00:54:51,830 --> 00:54:55,959
And tonight with Lisa in the cabana
it started to happen again.

587
00:54:56,126 --> 00:54:58,795
I think you are seriously losing it, bro.

588
00:54:58,963 --> 00:55:01,255
I'm scared, Grady.

589
00:55:02,675 --> 00:55:04,926
Something is trying
to get inside my body.

590
00:55:05,094 --> 00:55:07,303
Yeah, she's female,
she's waiting for you in the cabana.

591
00:55:07,471 --> 00:55:08,721
And you wanna sleep with me.

592
00:55:08,889 --> 00:55:12,225
Look, I don't care
if you believe me or not.

593
00:55:12,393 --> 00:55:14,060
Hey, I believe you.

594
00:55:14,228 --> 00:55:16,187
You've had some scary dreams, okay?

595
00:55:16,355 --> 00:55:17,814
No.

596
00:55:22,945 --> 00:55:26,447
I don't know.

597
00:55:27,533 --> 00:55:29,367
I'm all messed up.

598
00:55:30,327 --> 00:55:32,495
What difference does it make?

599
00:55:32,913 --> 00:55:37,166
I'm in trouble.
And I need you to help me.

600
00:55:39,169 --> 00:55:40,586
Okay?

601
00:55:53,809 --> 00:55:55,727
All right, man.
What do you want me to do?

602
00:56:01,275 --> 00:56:03,151
Just watch me.

603
00:56:04,862 --> 00:56:07,363
And if anything starts to happen...

604
00:56:07,573 --> 00:56:11,284
...if I start to act weird,
start dreaming weird...

605
00:56:11,994 --> 00:56:14,620
...or try to walk out of here,
you gotta stop me.

606
00:56:15,164 --> 00:56:18,624
I don't care if you have to hit me
over the head, just don't let me leave.

607
00:56:18,792 --> 00:56:20,376
And, Grady...

608
00:56:22,337 --> 00:56:24,422
...don't fall asleep.

609
00:56:26,133 --> 00:56:27,633
Hot dog?

610
00:56:27,801 --> 00:56:30,053
[WlLLY FlNLAYSON'S "ON THE AIR
TONlGHT" PLAYING ON STEREO]

611
00:56:31,597 --> 00:56:33,514
Come back in the water.

612
00:56:33,682 --> 00:56:36,100
I'm busy, okay?

613
00:56:38,645 --> 00:56:41,064
I don't know, Kerry.
I feel like I should go see him.

614
00:56:41,231 --> 00:56:43,316
But I can't just leave the party.

615
00:56:43,484 --> 00:56:45,568
Fuck the party.

616
00:56:46,278 --> 00:56:48,071
Go see him.

617
00:56:50,866 --> 00:56:51,991
Yeah.

618
00:56:52,159 --> 00:56:53,451
[CHUCKLES]

619
00:56:56,330 --> 00:56:59,248
NARRATOR [ON TV]: Leaving the land
<i>of the dead, and with Torch--</i>

620
00:56:59,416 --> 00:57:01,292
<i>I want you to meet Louie--</i>

621
00:57:01,460 --> 00:57:03,669
MAN [SINGING ON TV]:
<i>And now I see the--</i>

622
00:57:03,837 --> 00:57:05,004
<i>See, kid, you're a dog.</i>

623
00:57:05,172 --> 00:57:07,632
<i>You sure handled that situation--</i>

624
00:57:08,509 --> 00:57:12,095
MAN [ON TV]: Throw me a line.
<i>That changes into a bottomless pit!</i>

625
00:57:21,355 --> 00:57:22,522
Sweet dreams, pal.

626
00:57:40,541 --> 00:57:43,209
-Grady.
-What?

627
00:57:44,878 --> 00:57:46,379
It's starting to happen again.

628
00:57:47,881 --> 00:57:49,549
[PANTING]

629
00:57:49,716 --> 00:57:51,050
[GRUNTING AND GROANING]

630
00:57:55,722 --> 00:57:57,723
Jesus.

631
00:57:58,100 --> 00:57:59,851
Hey, man.

632
00:58:01,895 --> 00:58:03,646
What the fuck's wrong with you, dude?

633
00:58:17,411 --> 00:58:18,744
Shit.

634
00:58:29,464 --> 00:58:30,548
[MOUTHS]
<i>Oh, my God.</i>

635
00:58:38,724 --> 00:58:41,434
GRADY:
Dad!

636
00:58:42,144 --> 00:58:45,813
Dad, open the door!

637
00:58:45,981 --> 00:58:47,940
Dad!

638
00:58:48,108 --> 00:58:52,111
No!

639
00:59:07,419 --> 00:59:09,462
Dad! Dad!

640
00:59:11,506 --> 00:59:13,299
Dad!

641
00:59:17,638 --> 00:59:19,222
Oh, my God!

642
00:59:19,389 --> 00:59:20,723
[SCREAMING]

643
00:59:20,891 --> 00:59:23,059
Dad, open the door! Dad!

644
00:59:23,936 --> 00:59:34,195
Dad!

645
00:59:37,908 --> 00:59:39,325
Ron.

646
00:59:39,493 --> 00:59:41,077
Ron, what is it?

647
00:59:42,162 --> 00:59:45,456
Dad!

648
00:59:45,624 --> 00:59:47,124
Ron, open the door!

649
00:59:47,668 --> 00:59:49,460
Ron, are you all right?

650
00:59:53,090 --> 00:59:55,341
Ron, this is your father, open this door!

651
00:59:57,177 --> 00:59:58,678
No! No!

652
00:59:58,845 --> 01:00:00,137
-No!
-Ron!

653
01:00:04,309 --> 01:00:06,644
Ron, open it up! Ron!

654
01:00:06,812 --> 01:00:08,521
[MRS. GRADY SCREAMS]

655
01:00:13,652 --> 01:00:15,361
MR. GRADY:
Get help!

656
01:00:20,951 --> 01:00:22,952
[CHUCKLING]

657
01:00:31,878 --> 01:00:33,379
No.

658
01:00:36,466 --> 01:00:38,301
[SOBBING]

659
01:00:42,723 --> 01:00:44,307
[FREDDY CHUCKLING]

660
01:00:51,732 --> 01:00:54,483
You son of a bitch!

661
01:00:54,901 --> 01:00:57,236
You killed him!

662
01:01:06,538 --> 01:01:08,497
[SIRENS WAILING NEARBY]

663
01:01:10,751 --> 01:01:12,084
You killed him!

664
01:01:12,252 --> 01:01:13,336
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]

665
01:01:13,503 --> 01:01:14,670
No!

666
01:01:14,838 --> 01:01:16,839
MAN 1:
Somebody in there? Open up.

667
01:01:17,007 --> 01:01:19,759
MAN 2:
It's locked. Break it down.

668
01:01:30,562 --> 01:01:33,064
<i>Take a rose</i>

669
01:01:34,066 --> 01:01:36,067
<i>Call it sorrow</i>

670
01:01:36,777 --> 01:01:40,404
<i>But it's a rose by any other name</i>

671
01:01:49,331 --> 01:01:50,456
[LISA GASPS]

672
01:01:50,624 --> 01:01:52,458
Jesse, my God, what happened?

673
01:01:52,626 --> 01:01:55,002
I killed him. I killed him.

674
01:01:58,632 --> 01:02:01,133
Jesse, my God, you're hurt.
What happened?

675
01:02:01,301 --> 01:02:04,095
I-- I killed Grady.

676
01:02:05,097 --> 01:02:07,264
I killed Grady.

677
01:02:08,266 --> 01:02:10,893
Lisa, I killed Schneider.

678
01:02:11,478 --> 01:02:14,605
Oh, no, my God.

679
01:02:15,315 --> 01:02:16,816
I'm so scared.

680
01:02:16,983 --> 01:02:20,111
Jesse, what are you talking about?

681
01:02:20,612 --> 01:02:22,613
He's inside me.

682
01:02:23,615 --> 01:02:25,699
-I'm scared.
-Jesse, who is doing this to you?

683
01:02:25,867 --> 01:02:28,077
Fred Krueger.

684
01:02:29,287 --> 01:02:33,707
He's inside me,
and he wants to take me again.

685
01:02:35,627 --> 01:02:37,378
No. No.

686
01:02:37,546 --> 01:02:38,838
Jesse.

687
01:02:39,005 --> 01:02:41,924
Jesse, this is not happening.

688
01:02:42,092 --> 01:02:47,513
It's got to be everything you've taken in.
Uh, Schneider, the diary, the glove.

689
01:02:47,681 --> 01:02:48,806
Only it's all mixed up--

690
01:02:48,974 --> 01:02:54,186
Christ, what do I have to do
to make you understand me?

691
01:02:54,771 --> 01:02:58,357
Last night
he made me try to kill my sister.

692
01:03:00,777 --> 01:03:04,280
I've got blood on my hands.

693
01:03:08,201 --> 01:03:11,537
He owns me.

694
01:03:29,014 --> 01:03:31,891
Hey, could somebody turn down
the heat in the pool?

695
01:03:36,062 --> 01:03:37,897
[SIZZLING]

696
01:03:38,440 --> 01:03:40,441
What's going on?

697
01:03:46,406 --> 01:03:48,032
BOY 1:
Shit.

698
01:03:48,533 --> 01:03:51,994
BOY 2: Hey, Rocky.
GIRL: Our hero.

699
01:03:58,585 --> 01:04:00,294
Jesse.

700
01:04:00,462 --> 01:04:03,047
Come on,
I just want you to listen to this.

701
01:04:03,215 --> 01:04:06,842
It's something Nancy said
in the last page of her diary.

702
01:04:07,010 --> 01:04:08,677
Listen.

703
01:04:09,179 --> 01:04:11,263
"He is evil itself.

704
01:04:11,431 --> 01:04:14,433
I know now that I brought him
into my world.

705
01:04:14,601 --> 01:04:15,726
We all did.

706
01:04:15,894 --> 01:04:17,770
Gave him all the energy he needed.

707
01:04:17,938 --> 01:04:21,065
Our screams were all he needed."

708
01:04:21,775 --> 01:04:23,901
[UPBEAT POP MUSIC
PLAYING ON STEREO]

709
01:04:29,950 --> 01:04:30,950
Lisa?

710
01:04:31,117 --> 01:04:35,287
Jesse, she wasn't crazy.
All this really happened.

711
01:04:35,455 --> 01:04:37,289
You can fight him.

712
01:04:41,294 --> 01:04:43,045
[PANTING]

713
01:04:43,755 --> 01:04:45,965
Oh, God, he's coming back.

714
01:04:46,132 --> 01:04:48,384
-Get out of here, Lisa.
-Jesse, fight him.

715
01:04:48,927 --> 01:04:50,302
I can't.

716
01:04:52,806 --> 01:04:53,973
Fight it, Jesse.

717
01:04:56,434 --> 01:04:59,144
You created him, you can destroy him.

718
01:04:59,312 --> 01:05:01,605
MR. WEBBER:
Lisa, open this door.

719
01:05:01,773 --> 01:05:04,400
He is living off of your fear.

720
01:05:04,568 --> 01:05:06,110
-Jesse, fight him.
-I can't!

721
01:05:06,278 --> 01:05:07,987
Yes, you can.

722
01:05:08,488 --> 01:05:09,488
Fight him.

723
01:05:09,656 --> 01:05:10,781
You are not afraid of him.

724
01:05:10,949 --> 01:05:12,616
-He doesn't even exist.
-No!

725
01:05:12,784 --> 01:05:14,493
[CRACKLING]

726
01:05:16,663 --> 01:05:18,247
[LISA SHRIEKS]

727
01:05:18,665 --> 01:05:19,832
[GIRLS SHRIEKING]

728
01:05:22,586 --> 01:05:23,627
Oh, my God.

729
01:05:26,381 --> 01:05:27,881
[FREDDY CHUCKLING]

730
01:05:28,508 --> 01:05:30,426
LISA:
Jesse?

731
01:05:33,513 --> 01:05:36,181
He can't fight me. I'm here.

732
01:05:36,474 --> 01:05:37,933
LISA:
No, no!

733
01:05:38,435 --> 01:05:39,476
Help!

734
01:05:40,228 --> 01:05:41,645
No!

735
01:05:48,612 --> 01:05:49,778
Jesse!

736
01:05:58,038 --> 01:05:59,079
[SHRIEKS]

737
01:05:59,247 --> 01:06:00,789
Help!

738
01:06:01,207 --> 01:06:02,583
Oh, my God!

739
01:06:02,751 --> 01:06:06,378
No!

740
01:06:06,546 --> 01:06:08,130
Don't.

741
01:06:08,298 --> 01:06:09,798
[CRYING]

742
01:06:10,216 --> 01:06:11,550
No!

743
01:06:12,552 --> 01:06:14,178
[SCREAMS]

744
01:06:23,938 --> 01:06:27,024
BOY 1: It's gotten a little hot.
BOY 2: What's going on in there?

745
01:06:27,192 --> 01:06:29,234
My God!

746
01:06:32,155 --> 01:06:33,238
[FREDDY YELLS]

747
01:06:42,540 --> 01:06:43,874
Jesse, help.

748
01:06:44,042 --> 01:06:45,542
FREDDY:
There is no Jesse.

749
01:06:45,710 --> 01:06:48,087
I'm Jesse now.

750
01:06:48,338 --> 01:06:50,255
LISA:
Get away from me!

751
01:06:50,423 --> 01:06:52,758
Get away from me!

752
01:06:54,302 --> 01:06:56,345
[IN JESSE'S VOICE]
Kill me, Lisa.

753
01:06:56,513 --> 01:06:58,097
Please, kill me.

754
01:06:58,765 --> 01:07:00,974
[FREDDY LAUGHS]

755
01:07:03,603 --> 01:07:05,813
[IN NORMAL VOICE]
Come on, Lisa, kill him.

756
01:07:05,980 --> 01:07:07,690
Kill him.

757
01:07:14,197 --> 01:07:15,948
[FREDDY CHUCKLING]

758
01:07:25,333 --> 01:07:27,209
[IN JESSE'S VOICE]
I love you, Lisa.

759
01:07:29,963 --> 01:07:31,130
No.

760
01:07:31,297 --> 01:07:34,174
Oh, God.

761
01:07:35,009 --> 01:07:36,343
[SCREAMS]

762
01:07:36,511 --> 01:07:38,053
Help, please.

763
01:07:38,221 --> 01:07:39,388
Please.

764
01:07:39,556 --> 01:07:41,306
No.

765
01:07:41,474 --> 01:07:42,975
[IN NORMAL VOICE]
I love you, Lisa.

766
01:07:48,189 --> 01:07:50,983
LISA:
Jesse, help.

767
01:07:53,737 --> 01:07:54,820
[GRUNTS]

768
01:08:26,561 --> 01:08:28,145
BOY 1:
Hey, is everybody okay?

769
01:08:28,313 --> 01:08:30,189
BOY 2:
Search me.

770
01:08:34,068 --> 01:08:35,778
BOY 3:
What's going on?

771
01:08:36,362 --> 01:08:37,696
[CHATTERING]

772
01:08:40,533 --> 01:08:42,534
[ALL SCREAMING]

773
01:08:49,876 --> 01:08:52,294
BOY 4:
Wait a minute! Wait!

774
01:08:58,718 --> 01:09:01,220
Ah! It's hot.

775
01:09:06,226 --> 01:09:08,811
Lisa. Lisa.

776
01:09:19,531 --> 01:09:22,241
Lisa. Oh, my God,
are you all right?

777
01:09:22,408 --> 01:09:24,326
Mommy.

778
01:09:36,422 --> 01:09:38,090
[SCREAMS]

779
01:09:39,843 --> 01:09:41,093
MR. WEBBER:
Get her out of here!

780
01:09:41,261 --> 01:09:43,053
-Get out of here!
-All right.

781
01:09:43,221 --> 01:09:44,638
Hey.

782
01:09:46,808 --> 01:09:48,934
Just calm down, all right?

783
01:09:49,102 --> 01:09:50,519
Relax.

784
01:09:51,980 --> 01:09:55,607
Yeah. It's gonna be all right.

785
01:09:56,609 --> 01:09:58,193
Nobody's gonna hurt you.

786
01:10:02,448 --> 01:10:04,783
Just tell us what you want, all right?

787
01:10:07,662 --> 01:10:09,580
Okay, I'm here to help you.

788
01:10:09,747 --> 01:10:12,583
FREDDY:
Help yourself, fucker.

789
01:10:15,086 --> 01:10:16,461
[SCREAMS]

790
01:10:24,304 --> 01:10:27,806
You are all my children now.

791
01:10:34,314 --> 01:10:36,231
Oh, shit.

792
01:10:37,317 --> 01:10:39,359
LISA:
No! Don't.

793
01:10:39,527 --> 01:10:41,320
What the hell are you doing?

794
01:11:02,216 --> 01:11:03,967
Where did he go?

795
01:12:04,237 --> 01:12:05,862
[ROARING AND GROWLING]

796
01:13:30,656 --> 01:13:32,616
[GRUNTS]

797
01:13:44,337 --> 01:13:45,962
[WHIMPERS]

798
01:13:47,006 --> 01:13:48,423
[SHRIEKS]

799
01:13:48,591 --> 01:13:50,467
[SOBBING]

800
01:14:08,986 --> 01:14:10,654
[SQUEAKING]

801
01:14:30,842 --> 01:14:31,883
[LISA SHRIEKS]

802
01:14:32,051 --> 01:14:33,510
[SCREECHES]

803
01:14:36,180 --> 01:14:37,597
[ROARS]

804
01:14:45,064 --> 01:14:46,565
[SHRIEKS]

805
01:15:11,174 --> 01:15:12,424
[FREDDY CHUCKLING]

806
01:15:14,177 --> 01:15:16,553
Come to me, Lisa.

807
01:15:22,518 --> 01:15:24,269
Jesse, I know you're in there.

808
01:15:24,437 --> 01:15:26,646
-Stop him.
-No, no, no, Jesse's dead.

809
01:15:27,190 --> 01:15:28,273
Jesse.

810
01:15:29,442 --> 01:15:30,734
[GRUNTS]

811
01:15:33,779 --> 01:15:35,322
[WHIMPERING]

812
01:15:36,324 --> 01:15:37,949
JESSE:
Lisa.

813
01:15:39,202 --> 01:15:41,161
I love you, Jesse.

814
01:15:46,626 --> 01:15:48,335
[GROANING]

815
01:15:58,304 --> 01:15:59,763
FREDDY:
Lisa.

816
01:16:11,400 --> 01:16:13,944
Come back to me, Lisa.

817
01:16:14,111 --> 01:16:16,029
[CHUCKLES]

818
01:16:18,574 --> 01:16:20,367
I am not afraid of you.

819
01:16:21,202 --> 01:16:22,827
[CHUCKLES]

820
01:16:23,537 --> 01:16:28,166
He's in there and I want him back.

821
01:16:29,669 --> 01:16:32,671
I'm gonna take him away from you.

822
01:16:32,838 --> 01:16:37,842
And you are gonna go straight back to hell,
you son of a bitch!

823
01:16:38,010 --> 01:16:39,803
No, Jesse's dead.

824
01:16:43,641 --> 01:16:46,059
Come back to me, Jesse.

825
01:16:46,852 --> 01:16:48,478
I love you.

826
01:16:48,646 --> 01:16:50,188
Come back to me.

827
01:16:50,356 --> 01:16:51,773
He's dead.

828
01:16:53,776 --> 01:16:55,402
[FREDDY HISSING]

829
01:16:56,988 --> 01:16:58,697
He can't hold you, Jesse.

830
01:16:58,864 --> 01:17:00,323
He's losing his grip.

831
01:17:00,491 --> 01:17:01,533
You can get out.

832
01:17:01,701 --> 01:17:03,159
[FREDDY GRUNTS]

833
01:17:06,163 --> 01:17:09,040
He'll die with me.

834
01:17:18,634 --> 01:17:21,678
He'll die with both of us.

835
01:17:25,933 --> 01:17:28,476
[LISA SOBS AND FREDDY YELLS]

836
01:18:03,429 --> 01:18:05,513
[FREDDY YELLING]

837
01:18:10,269 --> 01:18:12,604
FREDDY:
Lisa! Lisa!

838
01:18:15,858 --> 01:18:17,400
[SOBBING]

839
01:19:47,867 --> 01:19:50,201
Jesse.

840
01:20:44,924 --> 01:20:46,799
CHERYL:
It's great to have you home again, Jess.

841
01:20:46,967 --> 01:20:48,968
I can't believe I'm going back. I'm glad.

842
01:20:49,136 --> 01:20:50,637
-Good.
-I'm glad.

843
01:20:50,804 --> 01:20:53,431
-Have a good day, huh?
-Okay.

844
01:20:53,641 --> 01:20:55,266
Thanks, Mom.

845
01:20:56,435 --> 01:20:57,936
CHERYL:
Bye.

846
01:21:02,983 --> 01:21:04,234
JESSE:
Hi.

847
01:21:04,401 --> 01:21:05,652
Hi.

848
01:21:05,819 --> 01:21:07,612
KERRY:
Hi, Jesse.

849
01:21:09,907 --> 01:21:11,574
[KERRY CHUCKLES]

850
01:21:12,618 --> 01:21:14,786
What is so funny?

851
01:21:15,746 --> 01:21:18,081
That was a really great party.

852
01:21:18,249 --> 01:21:21,459
-Thanks, Lise.
-Thanks a lot.

853
01:21:21,627 --> 01:21:24,045
I can't believe it's actually all over.

854
01:21:24,213 --> 01:21:27,632
-Let's not talk about it.
-Okay.

855
01:21:32,805 --> 01:21:35,473
LISA: Ooh. Ha, ha.
-ls this--?

856
01:21:35,641 --> 01:21:38,560
Am I going crazy
or is this bus going too fast?

857
01:21:38,727 --> 01:21:40,019
It's going fine.

858
01:21:40,187 --> 01:21:42,146
No problem.

859
01:21:44,650 --> 01:21:46,150
No.

860
01:21:46,610 --> 01:21:48,403
This bus is going too fast.

861
01:21:50,364 --> 01:21:53,408
-Lisa, it's starting to speed up.
-It's fine.

862
01:21:53,576 --> 01:21:54,826
It's fine.

863
01:21:54,994 --> 01:21:55,994
Driver.

864
01:21:56,370 --> 01:21:59,414
-Driver, stop.
-Jesse, just sit down.

865
01:22:12,261 --> 01:22:19,017
I'm sorry.

866
01:22:19,602 --> 01:22:22,562
It's okay. It's all right.

867
01:22:23,105 --> 01:22:25,398
Jesse, it's okay.

868
01:22:25,566 --> 01:22:27,525
It's all over.

869
01:22:27,693 --> 01:22:29,485
[ALL SCREAM]

870
01:22:29,653 --> 01:22:31,738
[FREDDY LAUGHING]
