1
00:06:16,259 --> 00:06:19,091
Sixty-eight... sixty-nine...

2
00:06:19,128 --> 00:06:20,891
seventy... seventy-one...

3
00:06:20,930 --> 00:06:22,124
Come on, will you?

4
00:06:22,164 --> 00:06:23,495
Shut up!

5
00:06:23,532 --> 00:06:24,897
You'll make me lose the count.

6
00:06:27,036 --> 00:06:28,333
Seventy-two...

7
00:06:34,709 --> 00:06:36,039
Seventy-three.

8
00:06:36,075 --> 00:06:38,236
Close enough. It's a hundred.

9
00:06:38,278 --> 00:06:39,438
Let's go.

10
00:06:40,914 --> 00:06:42,677
No, wait!

11
00:07:14,043 --> 00:07:16,238
Hey, Alice! Alice, wake up!

12
00:07:19,849 --> 00:07:21,043
Jesus.

13
00:08:11,295 --> 00:08:14,263
And as adults, we must
now prepare for a new life...

14
00:08:14,297 --> 00:08:15,889
outside
this wonderful environment...

15
00:08:15,932 --> 00:08:18,024
known as Springwood High.

16
00:08:19,901 --> 00:08:22,062
So let's blow this pop stand!

17
00:08:27,108 --> 00:08:29,701
Alice! Yvonne!

18
00:08:35,114 --> 00:08:36,776
Girl, what's wrong?
Let's see a smile.

19
00:08:36,816 --> 00:08:38,511
I had kind of a long night.

20
00:08:38,551 --> 00:08:40,518
Dan keeping you up again?

21
00:08:40,552 --> 00:08:41,986
Girl, you better put a lock
on that window.

22
00:08:42,888 --> 00:08:44,685
The Dan part was nice.

23
00:08:44,723 --> 00:08:46,315
These things are wild.
What do you think?

24
00:08:46,358 --> 00:08:47,620
You look like a nun.

25
00:08:47,659 --> 00:08:49,490
Dying to break her vows.

26
00:08:49,528 --> 00:08:51,358
Find me a man!

27
00:08:51,395 --> 00:08:52,863
Fabulous.

28
00:08:52,898 --> 00:08:54,524
Maybe I should
spell it out for you.

29
00:08:54,565 --> 00:08:56,430
Maybe God's trying to tell you
something.

30
00:08:56,468 --> 00:08:57,798
When are you gonna
run away with me?

31
00:08:57,835 --> 00:08:59,735
Next life. What's that?

32
00:08:59,770 --> 00:09:02,739
My undying love. Have some.

33
00:09:03,807 --> 00:09:06,207
Mark, give it up.
It's hopeless.

34
00:09:06,243 --> 00:09:08,142
I think I'm starting
to wear her down.

35
00:09:08,177 --> 00:09:09,336
Have a taste anyway.

36
00:09:09,377 --> 00:09:13,074
Greta! That's not what
a cover girl puts in her body!

37
00:09:13,114 --> 00:09:14,514
Shit!

38
00:09:14,550 --> 00:09:15,710
She read you.

39
00:09:15,751 --> 00:09:17,810
Ladies,
where's the party tonight?

40
00:09:18,253 --> 00:09:20,551
Why don't we go to Alice's?

41
00:09:20,588 --> 00:09:23,217
No. My dad's got this thing
about drinking in the house.

42
00:09:23,259 --> 00:09:24,417
We gotta do something.

43
00:09:24,458 --> 00:09:27,825
Guys, I got swimming practice
until six-thirty.

44
00:09:27,861 --> 00:09:28,987
So?

45
00:09:29,029 --> 00:09:32,896
They're gonna give me the key,
so I can lock up after I'm done.

46
00:09:32,932 --> 00:09:34,866
Pool party!

47
00:09:36,036 --> 00:09:37,663
Oh, damn, I gotta work tonight!

48
00:09:37,704 --> 00:09:39,831
Hey, Mark! Picture time!

49
00:09:39,872 --> 00:09:42,669
Come get immortalized...
parents and brats.

50
00:09:45,777 --> 00:09:48,575
Greta! Photo opportunity, dear!

51
00:09:49,748 --> 00:09:51,045
Damn it, they caught me.

52
00:09:51,082 --> 00:09:53,709
I have to go gnash my teeth
for the paparazzi.

53
00:09:54,317 --> 00:09:56,411
You guys go on.
I'll catch up with you later.

54
00:10:09,499 --> 00:10:12,297
- Hey, beautiful.
- Oh, Jesus, don't do that!

55
00:10:13,836 --> 00:10:16,098
Sorry. I got a present for you.

56
00:10:17,838 --> 00:10:19,396
You got the tickets?

57
00:10:19,440 --> 00:10:21,339
Yeah. They're coach seats...

58
00:10:21,374 --> 00:10:24,104
but this plane stops in Paris.

59
00:10:24,144 --> 00:10:25,543
It's gonna be a great summer.

60
00:10:26,180 --> 00:10:27,339
Yeah, I know.

61
00:10:28,316 --> 00:10:30,908
Hey... what's the matter?

62
00:10:30,950 --> 00:10:32,315
Nothing. It's just...

63
00:10:33,185 --> 00:10:36,154
I didn't see my dad
at the ceremony.

64
00:10:36,188 --> 00:10:37,349
Well, he'll show up.

65
00:10:38,724 --> 00:10:39,850
Hey, come on.

66
00:10:39,892 --> 00:10:41,484
What's really wrong?

67
00:10:42,528 --> 00:10:44,518
I had one of those dreams
last night.

68
00:10:46,364 --> 00:10:47,887
About him?

69
00:10:47,931 --> 00:10:50,593
Well, not exactly.

70
00:10:50,634 --> 00:10:54,934
It's that I just felt like
I wasn't in control...

71
00:10:54,972 --> 00:10:57,167
for the first time
since all that.

72
00:10:58,775 --> 00:11:03,473
Look, if you don't dream him up,
he can't hurt you or us.

73
00:11:03,513 --> 00:11:04,671
Remember?

74
00:11:04,713 --> 00:11:06,374
You're right.

75
00:11:06,414 --> 00:11:08,541
There you go. Love you.

76
00:11:08,583 --> 00:11:10,743
- I love you.
- Hey, Danny! Dan!

77
00:11:12,386 --> 00:11:14,115
You look sweet today.

78
00:11:14,154 --> 00:11:15,781
Hello, darling.

79
00:11:15,823 --> 00:11:18,850
Dan, this is Coach Ostrow.
He's interviewing next week.

80
00:11:18,893 --> 00:11:20,383
Finest quarterback in the state.

81
00:11:20,428 --> 00:11:21,654
You know what they say...

82
00:11:21,694 --> 00:11:24,163
this boy
feels the need for speed.

83
00:11:24,697 --> 00:11:25,892
So I've heard.

84
00:11:26,499 --> 00:11:29,127
Dad, could we
get into this later?

85
00:11:29,168 --> 00:11:30,965
Summer's just starting.

86
00:11:31,004 --> 00:11:33,598
Dan, we're talking about
your future here.

87
00:11:33,639 --> 00:11:35,902
Excuse us, dear.

88
00:11:35,941 --> 00:11:38,306
- Listen.
- It's OK, Dan.

89
00:11:38,342 --> 00:11:39,969
We take care of our boys.

90
00:11:42,813 --> 00:11:44,041
Say "cheese."

91
00:11:47,818 --> 00:11:49,751
"Congratulations, Alice.

92
00:11:50,153 --> 00:11:51,586
"You looked beautiful
up there."

93
00:11:52,456 --> 00:11:54,481
"I'm so proud of you.

94
00:11:54,525 --> 00:11:55,786
"Gee, thanks, Dad."

95
00:11:55,825 --> 00:11:57,257
You do look beautiful.

96
00:11:59,328 --> 00:12:01,592
I was afraid you weren't coming.

97
00:12:01,630 --> 00:12:04,097
I watched
from behind the stands.

98
00:12:04,132 --> 00:12:05,657
I didn't want to embarrass you.

99
00:12:05,701 --> 00:12:08,168
"The drunk showed up."
That kind of thing.

100
00:12:08,202 --> 00:12:09,863
That's in the past.

101
00:12:09,904 --> 00:12:11,599
Unless you've stopped going
to your meetings.

102
00:12:11,639 --> 00:12:14,129
No. A deal's a deal.

103
00:12:15,008 --> 00:12:16,168
Come on.

104
00:12:19,146 --> 00:12:20,738
Where are we going?

105
00:12:20,781 --> 00:12:23,750
Oh... to take a picture.

106
00:12:23,784 --> 00:12:25,774
I don't take good pictures.

107
00:12:56,478 --> 00:12:58,105
Call me
when your shift ends, OK?

108
00:12:59,915 --> 00:13:01,075
Good-bye, sir.

109
00:13:02,650 --> 00:13:05,619
Don't worry.
I'll have her home by August.

110
00:13:07,421 --> 00:13:08,581
Just kidding.

111
00:13:09,323 --> 00:13:10,483
See you later.

112
00:13:11,559 --> 00:13:12,821
Thanks for everything, Dad.

113
00:13:13,561 --> 00:13:14,926
You sure you don't want
a ride to work?

114
00:13:14,962 --> 00:13:17,429
No. It's just across the park.

115
00:13:17,464 --> 00:13:18,624
Have fun tonight.

116
00:13:31,710 --> 00:13:33,007
Oh, sorry!

117
00:13:35,180 --> 00:13:38,443
Freddy's coming for you

118
00:13:38,482 --> 00:13:40,416
Three, four

119
00:13:40,450 --> 00:13:43,646
Better lock your door

120
00:13:43,686 --> 00:13:45,779
Five, six

121
00:13:45,821 --> 00:13:48,915
Grab your crucifix

122
00:13:48,958 --> 00:13:50,892
Seven, eight

123
00:13:50,926 --> 00:13:53,189
Better stay up late

124
00:14:22,888 --> 00:14:24,651
Seven, eight

125
00:14:24,689 --> 00:14:27,089
Better stay awake

126
00:14:27,125 --> 00:14:28,614
Nine, ten

127
00:14:28,659 --> 00:14:31,127
He's back again

128
00:14:58,186 --> 00:14:59,517
Wait!

129
00:16:47,382 --> 00:16:50,612
Let me go! Let me go!

130
00:16:55,290 --> 00:16:57,757
There's nothing to be afraid of.

131
00:16:57,790 --> 00:17:00,156
Just do exactly what I say.

132
00:17:14,205 --> 00:17:15,365
Help me!

133
00:17:16,106 --> 00:17:17,574
Why is this happening again?

134
00:17:17,608 --> 00:17:19,542
Oh, please don't let him
do this!

135
00:17:21,245 --> 00:17:22,542
Don't panic, Amanda.

136
00:17:23,147 --> 00:17:24,740
We have a breech birth here.

137
00:17:24,783 --> 00:17:26,079
It's backward!

138
00:17:27,351 --> 00:17:29,341
We're going to have
to turn it around.

139
00:17:30,019 --> 00:17:31,281
Take a deep breath.

140
00:17:32,621 --> 00:17:35,089
I'm going to need you to push.
Now push!

141
00:17:44,132 --> 00:17:45,463
Holy shit.

142
00:17:46,600 --> 00:17:47,761
What is it?

143
00:17:49,670 --> 00:17:50,830
Careful!

144
00:17:51,539 --> 00:17:55,530
Sister,
this is one of God's creatures.

145
00:17:55,574 --> 00:17:57,133
Take solace in that.

146
00:17:57,177 --> 00:17:59,110
That is no creature of God!

147
00:18:00,480 --> 00:18:02,072
Stop it! Give it to me!

148
00:18:02,715 --> 00:18:03,910
Don't let it get away!

149
00:18:59,197 --> 00:19:00,630
Where are you?

150
00:19:07,038 --> 00:19:10,632
No! Not again!

151
00:21:07,778 --> 00:21:11,042
It's a boy!

152
00:21:14,984 --> 00:21:17,179
You can't come back!

153
00:21:21,891 --> 00:21:23,448
I locked the door on you.

154
00:21:28,195 --> 00:21:30,356
Well, I found the key!

155
00:21:35,036 --> 00:21:38,597
Your birth was a curse
on the whole of humanity.

156
00:21:40,740 --> 00:21:43,231
I will not allow it
to happen again.

157
00:21:43,276 --> 00:21:45,470
You brought me back
to give you life...

158
00:21:45,510 --> 00:21:48,172
but now I must take yours.

159
00:21:49,047 --> 00:21:50,776
We'll see, bitch.

160
00:21:51,549 --> 00:21:54,110
We'll just see.

161
00:21:55,020 --> 00:21:57,250
I must be released
from my earthly prison.

162
00:21:57,289 --> 00:21:58,347
How?

163
00:21:59,791 --> 00:22:01,655
Look for me in the tower.

164
00:22:02,525 --> 00:22:05,426
You'll never find her.

165
00:22:25,380 --> 00:22:27,006
Anne.

166
00:22:27,048 --> 00:22:28,845
Oh, God, I'm glad it's you.

167
00:22:28,883 --> 00:22:30,179
- It was terrible.
- What happened?

168
00:22:30,216 --> 00:22:31,808
I was in the dream...

169
00:22:31,851 --> 00:22:34,444
and I don't know how,
but now he's back.

170
00:22:35,254 --> 00:22:38,746
I thought you were dead.
You're four hours late.

171
00:22:39,592 --> 00:22:40,752
Four hours?

172
00:22:42,861 --> 00:22:46,422
I wish I had a prescription
for whatever it is you're on.

173
00:22:46,465 --> 00:22:47,693
What?

174
00:22:47,733 --> 00:22:50,759
Listen, thanks a lot, Alice,
for nada.

175
00:23:03,646 --> 00:23:04,978
Bombs away!

176
00:23:26,766 --> 00:23:28,826
What'd your dad say about
you and Alice going to Europe?

177
00:23:29,636 --> 00:23:30,933
Nothing, really.
Just screamed a lot...

178
00:23:30,970 --> 00:23:33,666
and tried to convince me
that I'm throwing my life away.

179
00:23:33,706 --> 00:23:35,037
Who's throwing their life away?

180
00:23:35,074 --> 00:23:37,269
Dan, and he's taking Alice
with him.

181
00:23:38,111 --> 00:23:40,636
Pretty good dive, Yvonne.
You've been practicing.

182
00:23:40,680 --> 00:23:42,738
That's right. Two hours a day,
six days a week.

183
00:23:42,781 --> 00:23:44,339
Have another one.
I think you need it.

184
00:23:44,383 --> 00:23:45,508
No. I got a shift
in a couple of hours.

185
00:23:45,549 --> 00:23:47,106
Aren't you going in?

186
00:23:47,150 --> 00:23:51,178
No. My mom's got this asshole
photographer coming over...

187
00:23:51,222 --> 00:23:53,452
and I'm not supposed
to mess up my hair.

188
00:23:53,758 --> 00:23:56,521
Aren't you sick of your mom
trying to run your life?

189
00:23:59,329 --> 00:24:00,488
Don't let 'em.

190
00:24:00,530 --> 00:24:02,121
Sure, no problem.

191
00:24:02,164 --> 00:24:03,324
You know, he's right.

192
00:24:03,365 --> 00:24:06,095
Sometimes I feel like I'm living
with Melicertes.

193
00:24:06,136 --> 00:24:07,727
- Who?
- Melicertes.

194
00:24:07,770 --> 00:24:10,069
He's this ancient guy
I read about, right?

195
00:24:10,106 --> 00:24:12,073
Who, like, killed his kids...

196
00:24:12,106 --> 00:24:14,734
because he didn't like the way
they were running the kingdom.

197
00:24:14,776 --> 00:24:16,436
You're really weird,
you know that?

198
00:24:18,979 --> 00:24:20,446
Screw 'em!

199
00:24:20,480 --> 00:24:22,675
Open the champagne!
Let's have a party!

200
00:24:22,716 --> 00:24:23,876
- All right!
- All right!

201
00:24:23,917 --> 00:24:25,976
That's for Alice and me later.

202
00:24:26,653 --> 00:24:28,280
Sorry.

203
00:24:29,356 --> 00:24:31,483
- Ow, are you OK?
- Oh, my God.

204
00:24:32,525 --> 00:24:35,289
I could have gone all night
without looking at that.

205
00:24:35,327 --> 00:24:37,886
I think it's very strange
how you draw all your comics...

206
00:24:37,929 --> 00:24:39,691
loaded with blood and guts.

207
00:24:40,231 --> 00:24:41,755
That freaks you out.

208
00:24:42,701 --> 00:24:44,328
Yeah,
it's just a little blood, guy.

209
00:24:44,369 --> 00:24:47,132
I know what it is,
you big, dumb jock.

210
00:24:49,540 --> 00:24:51,371
Dan, telephone. Come on.

211
00:24:52,375 --> 00:24:54,536
I'll be right back.
Don't touch this, OK?

212
00:24:54,577 --> 00:24:56,603
OK, we'll guard it
with our lives.

213
00:24:59,348 --> 00:25:01,975
- Dan, it was Krueger.
- What?

214
00:25:02,017 --> 00:25:03,314
It happened while I was awake.

215
00:25:03,351 --> 00:25:04,818
Do you understand
what I'm saying?

216
00:25:04,853 --> 00:25:06,285
Now, wait a second. How could...

217
00:25:06,320 --> 00:25:08,618
He must have dreamt himself up.
I don't know.

218
00:25:09,423 --> 00:25:10,947
Jesus, Dan, I'm scared.

219
00:25:11,526 --> 00:25:13,720
All right. Stay right there.
I'm on my way.

220
00:25:13,761 --> 00:25:14,887
OK, I will.

221
00:25:14,929 --> 00:25:16,328
Just hurry, OK?

222
00:25:23,336 --> 00:25:24,495
Shit.

223
00:25:27,706 --> 00:25:29,333
What happened? Somebody die?

224
00:25:30,776 --> 00:25:32,107
Nah. I got to go.

225
00:25:32,144 --> 00:25:33,303
Alice beckons.

226
00:25:33,344 --> 00:25:36,075
Hey, Romeo,
forgot the secret ingredient.

227
00:25:37,649 --> 00:25:40,980
There he goes,
the fastest man on three legs.

228
00:25:50,494 --> 00:25:53,257
The sounds of Springwood.

229
00:25:53,295 --> 00:25:55,627
It's a beautiful evening
here in downtown Springwood...

230
00:25:55,664 --> 00:25:58,598
and we'll be back
with the music in just a moment.

231
00:25:59,334 --> 00:26:02,326
Right now,
we're open for your calls.

232
00:26:04,405 --> 00:26:06,600
I'm calling about
my wayward ex-son Daniel...

233
00:26:06,641 --> 00:26:09,906
who's been acting
like an ungrateful dickweed...

234
00:26:09,944 --> 00:26:12,968
ever since he was seduced
by that bimbo slut whore Alice!

235
00:26:13,012 --> 00:26:14,571
Mom?

236
00:26:14,615 --> 00:26:16,479
If I were you, lady...

237
00:26:16,516 --> 00:26:19,212
I'd kill the ungrateful piggy.

238
00:26:29,860 --> 00:26:32,489
Put your pedal
to the metal, Dan!

239
00:26:54,650 --> 00:26:56,675
Bad year, Dan!

240
00:27:12,431 --> 00:27:14,957
Better buckle up, dear!

241
00:28:31,201 --> 00:28:33,965
This boy
feels the need for speed.

242
00:28:37,040 --> 00:28:38,507
Gotcha!

243
00:28:46,982 --> 00:28:50,314
Fuel injection!

244
00:28:52,620 --> 00:28:55,315
Power drive!

245
00:28:55,355 --> 00:28:57,881
Fast lane!

246
00:29:08,969 --> 00:29:12,301
Hey, Danny,
better not dream and drive.

247
00:29:18,310 --> 00:29:19,469
Coffee, please?

248
00:29:52,006 --> 00:29:54,099
He just came fucking
flying out of nowhere!

249
00:29:54,141 --> 00:29:55,972
It was some kind
of a frigging jet!

250
00:29:56,010 --> 00:29:57,875
I didn't even see him!

251
00:30:08,920 --> 00:30:10,319
Want to make babies?

252
00:30:26,203 --> 00:30:27,261
You're all right.

253
00:30:28,071 --> 00:30:29,833
It's OK, honey, I'm right here.

254
00:30:33,776 --> 00:30:35,539
Dan's been in an accident.

255
00:30:35,578 --> 00:30:37,569
It was no accident.
It was Krueger.

256
00:30:37,613 --> 00:30:39,773
He used to come in through
my dreams and not anymore.

257
00:30:39,814 --> 00:30:41,509
He found some other way.

258
00:30:46,221 --> 00:30:47,984
I'm sorry.

259
00:30:48,023 --> 00:30:49,319
It was no dream.

260
00:30:52,826 --> 00:30:54,487
Dan's dead.

261
00:30:57,897 --> 00:30:59,523
Not Dan.

262
00:31:04,903 --> 00:31:06,268
Honey.

263
00:31:06,304 --> 00:31:07,498
I'm so sorry.

264
00:31:07,539 --> 00:31:10,100
Daddy, it wasn't an accident.
Krueger killed Dan.

265
00:31:10,143 --> 00:31:12,702
Calm down. Take it easy.
You're in shock.

266
00:31:12,744 --> 00:31:15,542
The police found fragments
of a champagne bottle.

267
00:31:15,578 --> 00:31:18,571
Dan didn't drink. You know that.

268
00:31:18,616 --> 00:31:21,641
I mean, it was probably for me
to celebrate our trip!

269
00:31:21,684 --> 00:31:23,845
We gotta do something!

270
00:31:23,887 --> 00:31:25,855
Dan's already dead.
Don't you see?

271
00:31:25,889 --> 00:31:27,322
It's starting again.

272
00:31:27,357 --> 00:31:31,259
These sorts of outbursts
aren't entirely uncommon.

273
00:31:31,294 --> 00:31:33,158
Many women
have them at the beginning.

274
00:31:33,195 --> 00:31:35,685
Especially if they've suffered
a traumatic shock.

275
00:31:37,832 --> 00:31:41,165
Don't worry, young lady.
You're gonna be fine.

276
00:31:41,202 --> 00:31:42,500
What do you mean?

277
00:31:45,439 --> 00:31:47,339
What's he talking about?

278
00:31:52,578 --> 00:31:54,170
What's wrong with me?

279
00:31:55,414 --> 00:31:56,779
Nothing.

280
00:32:00,453 --> 00:32:01,886
You're just a little pregnant.

281
00:32:06,591 --> 00:32:08,616
The doctor
wants to keep you overnight.

282
00:32:10,061 --> 00:32:12,358
Just for routine observation...

283
00:32:13,329 --> 00:32:15,821
to make sure you're
as comfortable as possible.

284
00:32:16,767 --> 00:32:18,530
You're gonna be fine, honey.

285
00:32:18,569 --> 00:32:20,627
Everything's gonna be OK.

286
00:33:12,283 --> 00:33:13,442
What's your name?

287
00:33:14,417 --> 00:33:15,611
Jacob.

288
00:33:16,919 --> 00:33:19,718
Really?
I've always loved that name.

289
00:33:24,360 --> 00:33:25,952
Shouldn't you be in your room,
Jacob?

290
00:33:28,764 --> 00:33:30,390
It's lonely there.

291
00:33:33,600 --> 00:33:34,726
Well, my name is...

292
00:33:34,768 --> 00:33:36,861
I'm sorry your boyfriend
got killed.

293
00:33:39,574 --> 00:33:40,733
How did you know that?

294
00:33:41,341 --> 00:33:43,502
I could tell you were sad.

295
00:33:43,544 --> 00:33:45,876
I just wanted to see
if you were all right.

296
00:33:52,117 --> 00:33:53,641
Jacob, wait. Don't go.

297
00:34:23,878 --> 00:34:25,004
Greta, dear...

298
00:34:25,046 --> 00:34:27,640
it's time
to get your beauty sleep.

299
00:34:29,350 --> 00:34:32,649
We don't want circles
under those beautiful eyes.

300
00:34:41,728 --> 00:34:44,127
Have you visited that little boy
on my floor?

301
00:34:44,163 --> 00:34:45,323
You know, Jacob?

302
00:34:46,131 --> 00:34:48,827
He has kind of sad eyes.

303
00:34:48,867 --> 00:34:50,858
There aren't
any little boys on your floor.

304
00:34:51,737 --> 00:34:54,296
He must have wandered in
from the children's ward.

305
00:34:54,339 --> 00:34:55,965
I was just wondering
what's wrong with him.

306
00:34:56,006 --> 00:34:57,564
We don't have a children's ward.

307
00:34:58,610 --> 00:35:01,544
He was wearing a hospital robe.

308
00:35:01,578 --> 00:35:03,045
I don't know what to tell you.

309
00:35:05,917 --> 00:35:07,406
Did you call everyone?

310
00:35:07,451 --> 00:35:08,781
Yup. Listen...

311
00:35:10,386 --> 00:35:12,751
let's keep this dream stuff
between you and me, OK?

312
00:35:19,861 --> 00:35:21,522
Amanda Krueger
was part of a religious order...

313
00:35:21,563 --> 00:35:24,054
that ran that asylum
in the 1940s.

314
00:35:24,099 --> 00:35:27,296
She was raped by the lunatics
and had the baby there.

315
00:35:28,068 --> 00:35:30,798
That baby grew up to be
Freddy Krueger...

316
00:35:30,838 --> 00:35:33,327
who murdered
twenty or thirty kids...

317
00:35:33,372 --> 00:35:34,806
right here on Elm Street.

318
00:35:35,441 --> 00:35:36,567
He got caught...

319
00:35:36,609 --> 00:35:39,806
but the courts cut him loose
on a technicality.

320
00:35:39,846 --> 00:35:41,814
So, the parents
of the murdered kids...

321
00:35:41,848 --> 00:35:44,407
got together and killed him.

322
00:35:45,617 --> 00:35:46,845
Torched him.

323
00:35:48,487 --> 00:35:50,785
But that was just the beginning.

324
00:35:50,822 --> 00:35:52,619
He keeps on killing...

325
00:35:53,557 --> 00:35:56,391
but he kills people
in their dreams...

326
00:35:56,428 --> 00:35:58,019
their nightmares.

327
00:35:59,162 --> 00:36:01,495
He uses my dreams
to bring him his victims.

328
00:36:02,665 --> 00:36:04,826
It's my fault that Dan's dead.

329
00:36:04,867 --> 00:36:06,892
Stop saying that.
That's bullshit.

330
00:36:07,636 --> 00:36:09,195
Let's talk about the baby.

331
00:36:09,938 --> 00:36:11,769
Yeah, congratulations.

332
00:36:12,508 --> 00:36:13,736
I guess.

333
00:36:13,776 --> 00:36:15,903
That's not what we're here for.

334
00:36:15,944 --> 00:36:18,276
Look, Dan's parents
were really pushing him hard.

335
00:36:18,315 --> 00:36:20,281
He was bitching about it
last night at the party.

336
00:36:20,315 --> 00:36:22,215
He was under
a lot of pressure. We all are.

337
00:36:22,250 --> 00:36:23,978
Pushy parents
can drive you nuts.

338
00:36:24,017 --> 00:36:25,450
What does that
have to do with it?

339
00:36:25,485 --> 00:36:28,079
When Dan died,
you weren't even asleep.

340
00:36:28,689 --> 00:36:31,419
You even said so. End of story.

341
00:36:38,596 --> 00:36:40,291
He must have found
some other way.

342
00:36:43,469 --> 00:36:44,766
Listen to me!

343
00:36:44,804 --> 00:36:47,465
This isn't some kind of joke!

344
00:36:47,505 --> 00:36:49,938
He gets in
through my dreams somehow...

345
00:36:49,973 --> 00:36:51,463
and I thought
I could control it...

346
00:36:51,508 --> 00:36:53,065
but something's changed...

347
00:36:53,109 --> 00:36:55,339
and I don't know
what he'll do next.

348
00:36:55,378 --> 00:36:58,472
Look, Alice,
we all know you're upset.

349
00:36:59,450 --> 00:37:01,247
The bottom line, Alice...

350
00:37:01,285 --> 00:37:02,751
if anybody's
trying to hurt you...

351
00:37:02,785 --> 00:37:04,218
supernatural or not...

352
00:37:04,253 --> 00:37:06,016
they're going to have
to go through us first.

353
00:37:06,055 --> 00:37:08,216
All of us. Right?

354
00:37:12,260 --> 00:37:13,851
That's what I'm afraid of.

355
00:37:39,118 --> 00:37:40,847
How was the meeting?

356
00:37:40,886 --> 00:37:42,785
- Sobering.
- Very funny.

357
00:37:45,589 --> 00:37:47,614
When did you become
such a smart shopper?

358
00:37:48,892 --> 00:37:52,191
Ever since my little girl
became a mom.

359
00:37:55,065 --> 00:37:56,532
You disappointed in me?

360
00:38:00,202 --> 00:38:01,601
No, I'm not.

361
00:38:05,840 --> 00:38:07,432
I sort of hope it's a boy.

362
00:38:10,144 --> 00:38:12,705
It'd be nice to hear a boy
playing in the house again.

363
00:38:16,717 --> 00:38:19,514
Just don't make a habit of it.

364
00:38:24,724 --> 00:38:26,022
It's true.

365
00:38:26,059 --> 00:38:29,289
People are always mistaking us
for sisters.

366
00:38:30,595 --> 00:38:33,825
Greta certainly has
the perfect body for modeling.

367
00:38:33,864 --> 00:38:36,332
You know,
Eileen Ford is a friend of mine.

368
00:38:37,701 --> 00:38:38,862
I told her about you.

369
00:38:39,503 --> 00:38:41,164
She's very interested.

370
00:38:41,205 --> 00:38:45,574
Greta, you're being offered
the opportunity of a lifetime.

371
00:38:45,609 --> 00:38:48,544
I think you should show
a little gratitude.

372
00:38:49,580 --> 00:38:52,070
One of my friends
died yesterday, Mother.

373
00:38:52,115 --> 00:38:54,878
Do you mind if I take
a few hours off to remember him?

374
00:38:55,951 --> 00:38:58,010
But we're having a party, dear.

375
00:38:58,053 --> 00:38:59,520
I read about him.

376
00:39:00,189 --> 00:39:01,850
Drunk or something, wasn't he?

377
00:39:01,890 --> 00:39:04,255
Oh, he was just a friend
of Greta's.

378
00:39:04,292 --> 00:39:06,192
Not someone special.

379
00:39:06,227 --> 00:39:07,694
Not someone she was seeing.

380
00:39:08,496 --> 00:39:09,860
You understand.

381
00:39:12,533 --> 00:39:14,262
No, thank you. I'm not hungry.

382
00:39:16,604 --> 00:39:18,401
Aren't you eating?

383
00:39:18,439 --> 00:39:20,803
I really don't feel up to it.

384
00:39:21,608 --> 00:39:24,837
Really, dear,
you ought to try something.

385
00:39:24,876 --> 00:39:27,107
You're the one
who's always slapping my hand...

386
00:39:27,146 --> 00:39:29,340
about my weight, Mother.

387
00:39:29,380 --> 00:39:31,439
That's why we diet, dear...

388
00:39:31,483 --> 00:39:35,419
so we can eat at social events
and not upset the other guests.

389
00:39:35,453 --> 00:39:36,579
Tell you what.

390
00:39:36,621 --> 00:39:38,953
Why don't I just eat
the whole goddamn tray...

391
00:39:38,990 --> 00:39:41,787
go throw up, and come back
for seconds, all right?

392
00:39:41,825 --> 00:39:44,157
Madam, if I may.

393
00:39:48,631 --> 00:39:50,599
Bon appétit, bitch.

394
00:39:53,135 --> 00:39:54,897
Filet de Barbie.

395
00:39:56,571 --> 00:39:59,096
Nothing but the best for Greta.

396
00:40:02,042 --> 00:40:04,739
Open wide!

397
00:40:08,917 --> 00:40:10,645
Second helping!

398
00:40:12,386 --> 00:40:14,477
Don't talk
with your mouth full, dear!

399
00:40:14,520 --> 00:40:17,284
You are what you eat!

400
00:40:27,833 --> 00:40:29,801
Poor baby.

401
00:40:29,835 --> 00:40:30,994
There.

402
00:41:02,397 --> 00:41:04,057
Dad!

403
00:41:04,098 --> 00:41:05,791
Dad, help!

404
00:41:36,393 --> 00:41:38,485
Honey? How's dinner coming?

405
00:41:45,000 --> 00:41:47,765
I can't believe
this shit is happening.

406
00:41:47,804 --> 00:41:49,294
Just hang in there, Yvonne.

407
00:41:50,205 --> 00:41:52,765
Man, I know Mark
is gonna be wigging out.

408
00:41:53,674 --> 00:41:55,107
We just got to keep tight.

409
00:41:55,142 --> 00:41:57,042
We'll get through, OK?

410
00:41:58,479 --> 00:42:00,504
I know he's back here somewhere,
girls.

411
00:42:00,548 --> 00:42:02,345
I think he's pretty upset.

412
00:42:11,291 --> 00:42:12,416
Mark, you OK?

413
00:42:12,458 --> 00:42:14,892
Fine. Just aces.

414
00:42:14,927 --> 00:42:16,757
I want to talk to you guys
about Greta.

415
00:42:16,794 --> 00:42:19,262
I'm terribly sorry,
but Greta's dead today.

416
00:42:19,297 --> 00:42:22,027
Perhaps we could interest you
in someone else.

417
00:42:22,066 --> 00:42:24,000
Look, it was an accident,
just like Dan's.

418
00:42:24,035 --> 00:42:25,366
No accident.

419
00:42:25,403 --> 00:42:27,337
I tried to warn all of you
about Krueger.

420
00:42:27,372 --> 00:42:28,497
Alice, please.

421
00:42:28,538 --> 00:42:31,029
I thought about that.

422
00:42:31,074 --> 00:42:33,268
She must have fallen asleep
while she was at the table.

423
00:42:33,309 --> 00:42:34,641
This is getting
a little sick, guys.

424
00:42:34,678 --> 00:42:35,804
Too bad.

425
00:42:35,846 --> 00:42:38,076
I don't understand
what's happening.

426
00:42:38,115 --> 00:42:40,514
Krueger has to use my dreams...

427
00:42:40,549 --> 00:42:42,812
but he got to Dan and Greta
while I was awake.

428
00:42:42,851 --> 00:42:44,182
How's he doing it?

429
00:42:44,219 --> 00:42:45,652
Why don't you two
stick to reality?

430
00:42:45,687 --> 00:42:47,916
Why don't you shut up
and let her talk?

431
00:42:47,955 --> 00:42:50,116
Two of us have died
in the past two days.

432
00:42:50,157 --> 00:42:52,752
Does that just strike you
as particularly normal?

433
00:42:52,794 --> 00:42:54,158
I'm not finished.

434
00:42:55,896 --> 00:42:58,229
I loved Greta, a lot.

435
00:42:58,999 --> 00:43:01,833
And if maybe, just maybe...

436
00:43:01,870 --> 00:43:04,393
someone or something
killed her...

437
00:43:05,972 --> 00:43:07,438
I'd like to hear about it.

438
00:43:08,373 --> 00:43:10,898
- I'm not gonna listen to this.
- Then get out!

439
00:43:10,942 --> 00:43:12,432
Come on.

440
00:43:12,477 --> 00:43:14,001
Yvonne, wait a minute.

441
00:43:14,046 --> 00:43:15,980
I'm... sorry.

442
00:43:19,450 --> 00:43:21,247
I'm an asshole, OK?

443
00:43:22,085 --> 00:43:24,316
I know I'm not dealing with this
very well...

444
00:43:25,256 --> 00:43:27,952
but it's not your fault, and...

445
00:43:28,926 --> 00:43:30,291
I'm sorry.

446
00:43:32,861 --> 00:43:34,261
It's OK.

447
00:43:36,831 --> 00:43:38,890
You stick around for a while?

448
00:43:38,933 --> 00:43:40,628
I wish I could, but...

449
00:43:42,203 --> 00:43:43,398
I got a shift tonight.

450
00:43:43,438 --> 00:43:45,134
I got to get going.

451
00:43:46,709 --> 00:43:48,266
I'll stay with you for a while,
if you want.

452
00:43:48,309 --> 00:43:49,799
Bye, you guys.

453
00:43:51,212 --> 00:43:52,441
See you.

454
00:43:55,315 --> 00:43:57,840
Do you think I'm an idiot
for being in love with her?

455
00:43:57,883 --> 00:43:59,373
Nobody thinks that.

456
00:44:04,457 --> 00:44:07,517
I know I didn't stand a chance
in hell, but...

457
00:44:07,560 --> 00:44:09,390
She cared a lot about you.

458
00:44:10,261 --> 00:44:11,819
Maybe it was her mother
who killed her...

459
00:44:11,863 --> 00:44:14,490
with all that
Polly-Perfect shit.

460
00:44:15,700 --> 00:44:16,826
It wasn't her mother.

461
00:44:16,868 --> 00:44:19,859
We have these scumbags
here on "The Hot Seat" tonight.

462
00:44:20,905 --> 00:44:22,599
The Phantom Prowler
wouldn't have been afraid...

463
00:44:22,639 --> 00:44:24,038
to tell her how he felt.

464
00:44:24,074 --> 00:44:26,439
If I only had a tenth
of his guts.

465
00:44:26,476 --> 00:44:27,807
Jesus, he's not even real...

466
00:44:27,844 --> 00:44:30,244
and he's more of a human being
than I am.

467
00:44:30,279 --> 00:44:33,407
This guy isn't one of your
comic book characters, Mark.

468
00:44:34,082 --> 00:44:36,516
He's not the Phantom Prowler.
He's for real.

469
00:44:37,220 --> 00:44:39,211
Tell me more
about this Krueger guy.

470
00:44:41,456 --> 00:44:42,617
You look tired.

471
00:44:43,390 --> 00:44:44,880
Why don't I make some coffee?

472
00:44:45,659 --> 00:44:47,092
There's a lot to tell.

473
00:46:08,766 --> 00:46:10,563
Help!

474
00:46:26,982 --> 00:46:28,414
Mark, take my hand!

475
00:46:29,250 --> 00:46:30,615
Take it!

476
00:46:45,932 --> 00:46:47,489
We got to get out of here.

477
00:46:53,105 --> 00:46:54,265
Mark, come on.

478
00:47:00,110 --> 00:47:01,635
Oh, shit.

479
00:47:24,032 --> 00:47:25,431
You don't look very well.

480
00:47:27,369 --> 00:47:28,597
Are you feeling all right?

481
00:47:29,504 --> 00:47:31,562
Been having bad dreams.

482
00:47:34,942 --> 00:47:36,671
Is this where you live, Jacob?

483
00:47:38,746 --> 00:47:40,577
Just waiting for someone.

484
00:47:42,883 --> 00:47:44,213
It's sad about Greta.

485
00:47:45,885 --> 00:47:47,442
Is that who you're waiting for?

486
00:47:49,855 --> 00:47:52,584
I don't think this is
a very nice place for you to be.

487
00:47:53,659 --> 00:47:55,422
Maybe we should go look
for your mom.

488
00:47:55,460 --> 00:47:57,223
She doesn't want me around.

489
00:47:57,262 --> 00:47:59,456
Oh, I'm sure that's not true.

490
00:47:59,497 --> 00:48:02,125
I'll bet she's very worried
about you.

491
00:48:02,166 --> 00:48:03,292
I would be.

492
00:48:03,334 --> 00:48:06,666
No, you're not! You don't even
care about being a mom.

493
00:48:06,703 --> 00:48:08,331
How come you
don't think about me?

494
00:48:08,371 --> 00:48:10,736
- Who said I... What?
- I like you.

495
00:48:10,773 --> 00:48:12,502
I want to stay with you.

496
00:48:12,541 --> 00:48:14,372
How come you don't like me?

497
00:48:15,244 --> 00:48:17,041
Who said I don't like you?

498
00:48:18,714 --> 00:48:20,807
My friend with the funny hand.

499
00:48:22,583 --> 00:48:25,017
Come on, honey.
We're gonna get out of here.

500
00:48:25,053 --> 00:48:27,749
No, I have to go now.
He's calling me.

501
00:48:27,789 --> 00:48:28,949
Jacob, wait!

502
00:48:45,070 --> 00:48:46,264
Holy shit.

503
00:48:46,304 --> 00:48:48,602
He's really real, isn't he?

504
00:48:52,711 --> 00:48:53,871
Are you OK?

505
00:48:54,780 --> 00:48:57,372
He's doing something to my baby.
I know it.

506
00:48:57,414 --> 00:48:58,847
He's trying to hurt Jacob.

507
00:48:58,882 --> 00:49:00,143
Who's Jacob?

508
00:49:00,183 --> 00:49:01,411
My baby.

509
00:49:02,218 --> 00:49:03,913
What, you named him already?

510
00:49:08,524 --> 00:49:09,718
I guess so.

511
00:49:11,928 --> 00:49:13,155
I got to get away from here.

512
00:49:13,195 --> 00:49:15,322
Someplace where Krueger
can't find him.

513
00:49:17,432 --> 00:49:18,592
Slow down.

514
00:49:19,201 --> 00:49:21,328
Now, how you gonna hide
from a guy like that, huh?

515
00:49:22,269 --> 00:49:23,464
Leave the planet?

516
00:49:24,338 --> 00:49:25,464
I don't know.

517
00:49:25,506 --> 00:49:26,666
Look...

518
00:49:27,441 --> 00:49:29,305
if you're worried
about your baby...

519
00:49:29,342 --> 00:49:32,368
call Yvonne and have the doctor
check him out.

520
00:49:33,412 --> 00:49:36,382
I'm gonna go see what else
I can find out about Krueger.

521
00:49:40,186 --> 00:49:42,244
You had me scared on the phone.
What's wrong with the baby?

522
00:49:42,287 --> 00:49:43,879
I think Krueger's
trying to do something to him.

523
00:49:44,757 --> 00:49:46,189
Alice! Honey, no.

524
00:49:46,224 --> 00:49:48,158
I love you, but you're gonna
have to get ahold of yourself.

525
00:49:48,192 --> 00:49:50,216
Mark knows I'm not crazy.

526
00:49:50,260 --> 00:49:51,989
Ask him to show you his hands.

527
00:49:52,462 --> 00:49:55,022
I think you just need
to calm down, OK?

528
00:49:55,065 --> 00:49:58,057
I can't figure out how
he's getting in when I'm awake.

529
00:49:59,503 --> 00:50:01,368
Do unborn babies dream?

530
00:50:03,539 --> 00:50:04,699
They do.

531
00:50:04,740 --> 00:50:06,139
But do us both a favor.

532
00:50:06,842 --> 00:50:08,833
Don't mention any of this
to Dr. Moore.

533
00:50:10,780 --> 00:50:13,305
I can't believe you had me
drag Dr. Moore down here...

534
00:50:13,349 --> 00:50:15,316
on a Sunday morning for this.

535
00:50:15,350 --> 00:50:16,680
I'm sorry, Yvonne.

536
00:50:16,717 --> 00:50:18,083
I thought
it was something serious.

537
00:50:19,020 --> 00:50:21,112
If this isn't serious,
I don't know what is.

538
00:50:22,756 --> 00:50:25,156
Don't dare say a word.
You're gonna get me fired.

539
00:50:27,226 --> 00:50:29,956
Dr. Moore,
do unborn babies dream?

540
00:50:32,099 --> 00:50:33,224
As the fetus develops...

541
00:50:33,266 --> 00:50:35,827
it can spend up to
seventy percent of its day...

542
00:50:35,869 --> 00:50:37,232
in a dream state.

543
00:50:38,503 --> 00:50:39,993
More as it matures.

544
00:50:41,406 --> 00:50:42,599
Will I be able to sense them?

545
00:50:44,308 --> 00:50:46,276
Is that why you're here?

546
00:50:46,310 --> 00:50:48,505
To see if your baby's
having nightmares?

547
00:50:49,580 --> 00:50:52,014
We're here to find out
everything we can, aren't we?

548
00:50:53,583 --> 00:50:55,517
Frankly, I have found
nothing about you...

549
00:50:55,552 --> 00:50:57,645
that would indicate
the necessity of ultrasound...

550
00:50:57,687 --> 00:50:59,211
at this stage
of your pregnancy.

551
00:51:00,090 --> 00:51:02,320
I just want to make sure
my baby's all right.

552
00:51:05,528 --> 00:51:07,392
Well, the heart seems strong.

553
00:51:08,230 --> 00:51:09,218
Let's hear it.

554
00:51:15,470 --> 00:51:17,301
There's your baby.

555
00:51:25,712 --> 00:51:26,871
Get her file.

556
00:52:36,940 --> 00:52:38,909
See any family resemblance?

557
00:52:45,949 --> 00:52:47,644
Feeding time.

558
00:52:48,552 --> 00:52:50,247
Soul food for my boy.

559
00:52:52,188 --> 00:52:53,415
Don't touch him!

560
00:52:58,394 --> 00:53:00,418
What's he doing to my baby?

561
00:53:00,461 --> 00:53:03,089
Please, young lady,
try to keep calm.

562
00:53:04,165 --> 00:53:06,599
Your baby is perfectly healthy.

563
00:53:06,634 --> 00:53:08,157
A little large
for so early on...

564
00:53:08,202 --> 00:53:10,136
but as normal
as I've ever seen.

565
00:53:10,170 --> 00:53:12,433
He's taking their souls,
their spirits...

566
00:53:12,471 --> 00:53:14,531
and making the baby like him.

567
00:53:14,575 --> 00:53:15,871
Look, sweetie, you're tired.

568
00:53:16,609 --> 00:53:18,168
You'll feel much better
after I take you home...

569
00:53:18,212 --> 00:53:20,873
and get some rest, OK?
Come on, let's go.

570
00:53:20,913 --> 00:53:22,107
Come on.

571
00:53:41,131 --> 00:53:42,927
Greta and Dan were there.

572
00:53:43,532 --> 00:53:45,557
Krueger killed them.

573
00:53:45,601 --> 00:53:46,796
Now he was...

574
00:53:47,803 --> 00:53:50,204
feeding them to Jacob.

575
00:53:52,008 --> 00:53:53,497
Alice,
stop and listen to yourself.

576
00:53:53,542 --> 00:53:55,476
Do you know what you sound like?

577
00:53:55,511 --> 00:53:58,910
Completely insane, but I'm not.

578
00:53:58,946 --> 00:54:02,506
And if you're my friend,
you would believe me a little.

579
00:54:02,549 --> 00:54:04,813
I am your friend,
and I'm worried sick about you.

580
00:54:04,852 --> 00:54:07,479
It's time to leave the Twilight
Zone and face reality.

581
00:54:07,520 --> 00:54:09,454
- Krueger is reality.
- So is your baby.

582
00:54:09,489 --> 00:54:11,582
You got more to think about
than yourself.

583
00:54:11,625 --> 00:54:13,217
What do you think I'm doing?

584
00:54:16,595 --> 00:54:17,822
Look...

585
00:54:18,998 --> 00:54:21,228
whether you believe it or not,
Krueger is back.

586
00:54:21,267 --> 00:54:22,461
He's after my baby...

587
00:54:22,501 --> 00:54:26,494
and if I don't try to do
something about it, who will?

588
00:54:26,538 --> 00:54:29,973
All I know is you're not doing
you or your baby any good...

589
00:54:30,008 --> 00:54:31,236
by acting like a crazy woman.

590
00:54:31,276 --> 00:54:33,106
Why don't you take off?

591
00:54:33,143 --> 00:54:35,043
Leave Springwood.
Cool off for a while.

592
00:54:35,078 --> 00:54:37,637
God damn it, you don't run away
from this guy!

593
00:54:37,680 --> 00:54:39,580
He finds you in your dreams!

594
00:54:39,615 --> 00:54:42,015
He found a lot of other people
before he found us.

595
00:54:42,886 --> 00:54:45,912
- You, too?
- He invited me to his house.

596
00:54:47,023 --> 00:54:48,286
Look, we're all tired...

597
00:54:48,325 --> 00:54:50,848
and we haven't had any sleep
since Friday night.

598
00:54:50,892 --> 00:54:52,416
That's the only reason
you're alive.

599
00:54:52,460 --> 00:54:54,222
No, it's not!

600
00:54:54,261 --> 00:54:55,751
Look through this stuff,
will you?

601
00:54:55,796 --> 00:54:57,287
She's not crazy!

602
00:55:07,006 --> 00:55:08,166
You OK?

603
00:55:09,475 --> 00:55:11,375
I know what's happening.

604
00:55:12,879 --> 00:55:15,745
Krueger's using Jacob's dreams.

605
00:55:15,781 --> 00:55:17,147
We gotta stop him.

606
00:55:20,385 --> 00:55:21,545
Well, there is...

607
00:55:22,520 --> 00:55:23,885
one way.

608
00:55:26,289 --> 00:55:28,382
Have you thought about
not having the baby?

609
00:55:29,126 --> 00:55:32,060
I mean, no baby...
no baby's dreams.

610
00:55:34,331 --> 00:55:35,992
No, I can't do that.

611
00:55:37,200 --> 00:55:39,258
I saw him inside of me, growing.

612
00:55:41,437 --> 00:55:43,802
He's part of me and Dan.
I want to keep him.

613
00:55:45,206 --> 00:55:47,174
OK, then we'll find another way.

614
00:55:53,081 --> 00:55:54,241
I've seen her.

615
00:55:57,617 --> 00:55:59,744
Alice, can you come down
a minute?

616
00:56:11,997 --> 00:56:15,158
Mr. Jordan and I wanted to see
how you're feeling.

617
00:56:17,000 --> 00:56:18,797
Well, come sit down.

618
00:56:20,371 --> 00:56:21,964
This really isn't a good time.

619
00:56:22,006 --> 00:56:23,496
Maybe you could come back.

620
00:56:23,541 --> 00:56:27,977
Frankly, we wondered what
you intend to do with your baby.

621
00:56:29,080 --> 00:56:30,306
What I what?

622
00:56:35,450 --> 00:56:39,409
Well, I've thought about it,
and I plan to keep him.

623
00:56:43,792 --> 00:56:45,657
We were concerned
that all this...

624
00:56:45,694 --> 00:56:48,059
might be a little bit too much
for you.

625
00:56:48,095 --> 00:56:50,689
I mean,
being single and everything.

626
00:56:52,066 --> 00:56:55,297
What Mr. Jordan means is that
we're aware of the burden...

627
00:56:55,336 --> 00:56:59,101
that raising a child
would place on you.

628
00:57:00,372 --> 00:57:02,237
We want to help.

629
00:57:02,275 --> 00:57:05,709
We want to adopt it and raise it
as though it were our own.

630
00:57:08,881 --> 00:57:12,339
Look, I appreciate
what you're offering...

631
00:57:12,384 --> 00:57:13,976
but, no.

632
00:57:14,019 --> 00:57:15,509
He's my responsibility.

633
00:57:15,554 --> 00:57:16,850
And ours.

634
00:57:17,589 --> 00:57:19,113
It's our grandchild.

635
00:57:19,158 --> 00:57:20,817
Now, Doris, maybe
this wasn't such a good idea.

636
00:57:20,857 --> 00:57:24,190
Alice, we're worried that
in your present condition...

637
00:57:24,226 --> 00:57:26,217
that you don't have
the ability...

638
00:57:26,262 --> 00:57:29,095
to take care of a child.

639
00:57:31,233 --> 00:57:34,725
What are you talking about,
"my condition"?

640
00:57:38,072 --> 00:57:41,007
We got a call from Dr. Moore.

641
00:57:41,042 --> 00:57:43,510
He said that
Alice was hysterical...

642
00:57:43,545 --> 00:57:46,843
and that she was having
paranoid delusions.

643
00:57:46,880 --> 00:57:48,871
You don't understand.

644
00:57:48,916 --> 00:57:50,406
We know you've been through
a lot...

645
00:57:51,718 --> 00:57:54,514
but there is more at stake here
than just your feelings.

646
00:57:54,553 --> 00:57:57,421
You're not taking my baby.

647
00:57:58,558 --> 00:58:00,321
Well, the courts
might not agree with you.

648
00:58:00,359 --> 00:58:01,723
But I do.

649
00:58:01,760 --> 00:58:03,694
I've heard enough of this crap.

650
00:58:03,728 --> 00:58:05,320
You think you can just
walk into my house...

651
00:58:05,363 --> 00:58:06,853
and threaten my daughter?

652
00:58:06,898 --> 00:58:10,027
Please, we have
a legitimate claim to it.

653
00:58:11,268 --> 00:58:13,236
He's not a thing.

654
00:58:13,271 --> 00:58:14,736
He's part of me...

655
00:58:14,771 --> 00:58:17,934
and I'm not giving him to you
or anyone else!

656
00:58:31,019 --> 00:58:32,486
They think I'm nuts.

657
00:58:33,355 --> 00:58:34,754
That's their problem.

658
00:58:34,790 --> 00:58:36,348
No, it's our problem.

659
00:58:36,391 --> 00:58:37,983
If I don't deal with this...

660
00:58:38,026 --> 00:58:39,755
they really might try
to take Jacob.

661
00:58:41,929 --> 00:58:43,328
You said she committed suicide.

662
00:58:43,364 --> 00:58:45,991
Yeah, that's what
the papers thought.

663
00:58:46,032 --> 00:58:48,363
She spent the rest of her life
in the asylum.

664
00:58:48,400 --> 00:58:50,596
After Krueger's trial,
she flipped out...

665
00:58:50,637 --> 00:58:53,037
and hung herself...
so they thought.

666
00:58:53,073 --> 00:58:54,198
Meaning?

667
00:58:54,240 --> 00:58:55,730
Meaning...

668
00:58:55,774 --> 00:58:57,139
they couldn't prove it.

669
00:58:58,578 --> 00:58:59,737
No body.

670
00:59:00,979 --> 00:59:02,674
But I've seen her grave.

671
00:59:02,714 --> 00:59:04,443
Ah, empty plot.

672
00:59:04,482 --> 00:59:06,676
A memorial stone.

673
00:59:07,485 --> 00:59:09,612
Vacant.
They never put her under.

674
00:59:09,654 --> 00:59:11,120
Cool, huh?

675
00:59:12,222 --> 00:59:13,348
I don't understand.

676
00:59:13,390 --> 00:59:18,692
If she killed herself,
her soul's gonna be in torment.

677
00:59:18,728 --> 00:59:20,059
Where'd you hear that?

678
00:59:22,330 --> 00:59:24,322
Right here, somewhere.

679
00:59:31,239 --> 00:59:34,833
Yeah. "Transmigration...

680
00:59:34,875 --> 00:59:36,967
"Soul of a sinner..."

681
00:59:37,010 --> 00:59:40,377
Yeah. "Trapped
in its earthly resting place."

682
00:59:41,115 --> 00:59:43,845
In the dream,
she was trying to stop him.

683
00:59:43,884 --> 00:59:46,249
She started to tell me how,
then the door slammed.

684
00:59:48,154 --> 00:59:49,315
He must have done it.

685
00:59:50,256 --> 00:59:53,486
We have to find where she died
to release her soul.

686
00:59:54,160 --> 00:59:56,457
I want you to stay awake
and watch me, OK?

687
00:59:56,495 --> 00:59:57,688
No problem.

688
01:00:23,218 --> 01:00:25,185
Hey, you missed practice.

689
01:00:25,219 --> 01:00:28,017
What happened? You fall in love?

690
01:00:28,056 --> 01:00:29,454
Don't ask.

691
01:00:30,425 --> 01:00:31,949
You don't even want to know.

692
01:00:33,695 --> 01:00:35,526
Pool still open?

693
01:00:35,563 --> 01:00:37,463
I think, if you hurry.

694
01:03:25,679 --> 01:03:27,408
Let's rock...

695
01:03:27,447 --> 01:03:30,347
and roll!

696
01:03:50,167 --> 01:03:52,397
Where are you going, piglet?

697
01:03:54,404 --> 01:03:56,837
The party's just starting.

698
01:03:57,407 --> 01:03:59,671
I know
exactly what you're up to.

699
01:03:59,710 --> 01:04:04,908
I thought I was up to Yvonne!

700
01:04:09,283 --> 01:04:10,546
Why don't you just shut up?

701
01:04:29,803 --> 01:04:31,464
What happened?

702
01:04:31,504 --> 01:04:34,164
He's scared to come in
because of Amanda.

703
01:04:37,275 --> 01:04:39,436
Hey, are you all right?

704
01:04:39,477 --> 01:04:40,637
Oh, God.

705
01:04:42,880 --> 01:04:44,780
You're not crazy.

706
01:04:46,617 --> 01:04:49,279
We have to find Amanda.
She's the key.

707
01:04:49,320 --> 01:04:50,786
Come on. Come on.

708
01:05:27,752 --> 01:05:29,049
Jesus.

709
01:07:15,682 --> 01:07:19,277
Mark, help me, please!

710
01:07:21,654 --> 01:07:25,021
Is she delicious, or am I crazy?

711
01:07:25,058 --> 01:07:26,649
You leave her alone!

712
01:07:41,272 --> 01:07:45,730
Time to die,
you scar-faced limp-dick!

713
01:08:16,401 --> 01:08:19,030
Faster than a bastard maniac!

714
01:08:22,474 --> 01:08:24,704
More powerful
than a loco-madman!

715
01:08:28,412 --> 01:08:31,108
It's... Super Freddy!

716
01:08:32,116 --> 01:08:35,415
Told you comic books
was bad for ya!

717
01:09:27,330 --> 01:09:28,991
Oh, God! Oh, shit!

718
01:09:36,672 --> 01:09:38,003
Damn it!

719
01:09:38,040 --> 01:09:40,234
Nothing in that room
was up to code.

720
01:09:40,275 --> 01:09:42,265
It's a miracle
they both weren't killed.

721
01:09:43,078 --> 01:09:46,514
No! He won't hurt me.
He needs me alive.

722
01:09:46,548 --> 01:09:48,948
Who? What's she talking about?

723
01:09:48,983 --> 01:09:51,042
No, she's just very upset.

724
01:09:52,353 --> 01:09:54,787
Maybe both of you
should come down to the station.

725
01:10:02,627 --> 01:10:04,151
What's going on? Where's Mark?

726
01:10:05,631 --> 01:10:07,292
Mark fell asleep.

727
01:10:07,333 --> 01:10:09,562
Krueger got him.

728
01:10:09,601 --> 01:10:11,091
No! God!

729
01:10:11,136 --> 01:10:13,797
Hey, come on!
I need you to be strong now!

730
01:10:13,838 --> 01:10:16,602
Listen, we have to get
to Krueger...

731
01:10:16,640 --> 01:10:18,608
before he gets to Jacob again.

732
01:10:18,642 --> 01:10:20,371
How do we stop him?

733
01:10:21,245 --> 01:10:22,405
Through Amanda.

734
01:10:23,582 --> 01:10:25,482
So... we have to find her?

735
01:10:27,083 --> 01:10:30,314
Just don't ask me to take
a Jacuzzi with that guy again.

736
01:10:31,753 --> 01:10:32,878
You know...

737
01:10:32,921 --> 01:10:36,378
I was in the tower
when he used you to distract me.

738
01:10:38,760 --> 01:10:39,919
What are we gonna do?

739
01:10:40,863 --> 01:10:42,227
I want you
to go to the asylum...

740
01:10:42,264 --> 01:10:44,926
the one I told you about,
where all of this started...

741
01:10:44,967 --> 01:10:46,696
and find her!

742
01:10:46,735 --> 01:10:48,133
Alice,
you're coming home with me.

743
01:10:48,169 --> 01:10:50,137
No, Dad,
I've got something to do.

744
01:10:50,171 --> 01:10:52,138
Alice,
you're coming with me right now.

745
01:10:54,707 --> 01:10:57,609
Find Amanda! And hurry!

746
01:12:27,624 --> 01:12:29,147
Come on out, Krueger!

747
01:12:33,460 --> 01:12:35,019
The game's over!

748
01:12:51,877 --> 01:12:53,606
I was stronger than you!

749
01:12:54,948 --> 01:12:57,938
So you picked on Jacob!
You bastard!

750
01:12:59,017 --> 01:13:00,678
You're trying to make him
like you...

751
01:13:00,719 --> 01:13:03,084
so you can live
through his dreams!

752
01:13:04,054 --> 01:13:06,352
Well, I won't let you!

753
01:13:06,390 --> 01:13:08,255
You hear me, Krueger?

754
01:13:20,169 --> 01:13:23,626
OK, if you won't talk to me...

755
01:13:23,672 --> 01:13:25,866
maybe you'd like to talk
to Amanda!

756
01:14:12,982 --> 01:14:15,542
Come on, you fucking coward!

757
01:15:18,573 --> 01:15:20,838
Good night, asshole!

758
01:15:43,863 --> 01:15:45,694
I'm your real friend, Jacob.

759
01:15:45,731 --> 01:15:46,891
Just like a daddy.

760
01:15:51,735 --> 01:15:54,602
I gotcha! I gotcha!

761
01:15:54,638 --> 01:15:56,299
Mommy, meet my friend.

762
01:15:59,041 --> 01:16:01,202
Nice try, Alice.

763
01:16:01,244 --> 01:16:02,506
Thanks, babe.

764
01:16:02,545 --> 01:16:04,979
It's my new look. Like it?

765
01:16:17,426 --> 01:16:20,258
Come downstairs.

766
01:16:20,294 --> 01:16:22,057
He won't hurt you.
He needs us both.

767
01:16:22,096 --> 01:16:24,188
I've got you both.

768
01:16:25,965 --> 01:16:28,695
Come on, Jacob.
It's time to go home.

769
01:16:33,106 --> 01:16:36,166
Jacob, run!

770
01:16:42,480 --> 01:16:44,711
Come on! Come on!

771
01:16:44,750 --> 01:16:46,478
Come to Papa!

772
01:16:51,655 --> 01:16:53,316
It's all right, son.

773
01:16:57,426 --> 01:16:58,984
Now come with me.

774
01:17:02,097 --> 01:17:03,928
Jacob, he's not your father!

775
01:17:16,410 --> 01:17:17,775
Kids.

776
01:17:17,811 --> 01:17:20,609
Always a disappointment.

777
01:17:53,176 --> 01:17:54,336
Where is he?

778
01:17:55,011 --> 01:17:57,241
Inside you... where he hides.

779
01:17:57,947 --> 01:17:59,575
What do you mean?

780
01:17:59,616 --> 01:18:02,106
Where he hides out. Inside.

781
01:18:03,086 --> 01:18:04,313
That's how he found me.

782
01:18:04,353 --> 01:18:05,410
But how?

783
01:18:05,453 --> 01:18:09,412
He says it's easy
because he knows you so well.

784
01:18:15,162 --> 01:18:16,356
All right, Krueger...

785
01:18:17,864 --> 01:18:20,060
this time it's for keeps!

786
01:18:49,660 --> 01:18:51,286
Come on, Alice...

787
01:18:51,327 --> 01:18:54,455
now we can really get to know
each other.

788
01:19:23,423 --> 01:19:25,049
Sister Amanda?

789
01:19:44,307 --> 01:19:46,433
Thank you.

790
01:20:13,800 --> 01:20:16,564
Jacob! Alice will not triumph!

791
01:20:17,537 --> 01:20:19,800
Only you can help her now.

792
01:20:22,440 --> 01:20:23,738
Hey, leave her!

793
01:20:26,912 --> 01:20:29,436
Let's go!
I want to learn stuff from you.

794
01:20:30,115 --> 01:20:32,378
She's no fun anymore.

795
01:20:32,416 --> 01:20:33,815
Teach me?

796
01:20:49,532 --> 01:20:50,828
Now, Jacob.

797
01:20:52,001 --> 01:20:54,866
Unleash the power
he has given you.

798
01:20:57,872 --> 01:20:59,896
School's out, Krueger.

799
01:22:52,840 --> 01:22:53,999
Stay back!

800
01:22:54,976 --> 01:22:56,500
Take your baby and leave!

801
01:23:06,952 --> 01:23:08,111
Let me out!

802
01:23:30,973 --> 01:23:32,099
You do good work, Alice.

803
01:23:32,141 --> 01:23:33,437
So did Dan.

804
01:23:34,343 --> 01:23:35,776
Is he still keeping you up
at night?

805
01:23:35,812 --> 01:23:37,575
Oh, it's OK.

806
01:23:39,982 --> 01:23:42,642
He has the rest of his life
to catch up on his sleep.

807
01:23:44,785 --> 01:23:46,047
Hi, honey.

808
01:23:48,389 --> 01:23:50,722
Sweet dreams, Jacob Daniel.

809
01:23:52,092 --> 01:23:53,616
Hey, sugar.

810
01:23:54,395 --> 01:23:56,589
How's my little grandson, huh?

811
01:23:58,330 --> 01:23:59,490
Look.

812
01:24:00,532 --> 01:24:01,830
Hungry?

813
01:24:01,867 --> 01:24:04,392
Mm-hmm. We all are.

814
01:24:06,338 --> 01:24:08,067
Hey, sweetie.

