1
00:02:41,537 --> 00:02:43,788
[TICKING]

2
00:02:44,081 --> 00:02:45,706
[DOKKEN'S "INTO THE FIRE"
PLAYING LOUDLY]

3
00:02:45,874 --> 00:02:50,211
<i>I know it's wrong</i>
<i>But I can't turn away</i>

4
00:02:53,090 --> 00:02:58,719
<i>The flames draw near</i>
<i>They're telling me to stay</i>

5
00:02:59,471 --> 00:03:01,597
<i>Into the fire</i>

6
00:03:02,349 --> 00:03:05,017
<i>I'm falling</i>

7
00:03:06,603 --> 00:03:09,021
<i>Into the fire</i>

8
00:03:09,523 --> 00:03:12,984
<i>I'm falling</i>

9
00:03:13,819 --> 00:03:23,661
<i>Into the fire</i>

10
00:03:24,705 --> 00:03:26,956
Are you crazy?
You'll wake up the whole neighborhood.

11
00:03:27,124 --> 00:03:28,165
[MUSIC STOPS]

12
00:03:28,333 --> 00:03:30,042
-Hi, Mom.
-Don't "Hi, Mom," me.

13
00:03:30,210 --> 00:03:32,336
What are you still doing up? It's past 1.

14
00:03:32,504 --> 00:03:34,130
Just thought I'd wait for you.

15
00:03:34,298 --> 00:03:36,549
Well, I'm home.
Now you can get to sleep.

16
00:03:36,717 --> 00:03:39,635
Come on, ándale.

17
00:03:40,721 --> 00:03:42,346
Mom, I'm really not tired.

18
00:03:42,514 --> 00:03:45,308
Kristen, don't start with me.
You know what your shrink said.

19
00:03:45,475 --> 00:03:46,809
He's full of it.

20
00:03:46,977 --> 00:03:49,687
I'm not gonna let you get me
into an argument, not tonight.

21
00:03:49,855 --> 00:03:50,897
Now get to sleep.

22
00:03:51,064 --> 00:03:52,356
Mom...

23
00:03:52,858 --> 00:03:55,484
...I'm still having those awful dreams.

24
00:03:55,652 --> 00:03:58,654
MAN:
Elaine, where do you keep the bourbon?

25
00:03:58,822 --> 00:04:00,865
Uh, I'll be right down.

26
00:04:01,033 --> 00:04:04,368
-Honey, I've got a guest.
-And you don't wanna keep him waiting.

27
00:04:04,536 --> 00:04:06,913
That's right, I don't.

28
00:04:08,790 --> 00:04:11,459
-Good night.
-Good night.

29
00:05:00,550 --> 00:05:02,343
GIRLS:
<i>One, two</i>

30
00:05:02,511 --> 00:05:05,137
<i>Freddy's coming for you</i>

31
00:05:05,305 --> 00:05:06,847
<i>Three, four</i>

32
00:05:07,015 --> 00:05:08,391
<i>Better lock your door</i>

33
00:05:08,558 --> 00:05:09,684
[BIKE BELL RINGING]

34
00:05:09,851 --> 00:05:11,394
<i>Five, six</i>

35
00:05:11,561 --> 00:05:14,063
<i>Grab your crucifix</i>

36
00:05:14,231 --> 00:05:16,065
<i>Seven, eight</i>

37
00:05:16,233 --> 00:05:18,818
<i>Gonna stay up late</i>

38
00:05:18,986 --> 00:05:20,611
<i>Nine, ten</i>

39
00:05:20,779 --> 00:05:23,572
<i>Never sleep again</i>

40
00:05:23,740 --> 00:05:25,366
<i>One, two</i>

41
00:05:25,534 --> 00:05:28,077
<i>Freddy's coming for you</i>

42
00:05:28,245 --> 00:05:29,745
<i>Three, four</i>

43
00:05:29,913 --> 00:05:31,998
<i>Better lock your door</i>

44
00:05:32,499 --> 00:05:34,166
<i>Five, six</i>

45
00:05:34,334 --> 00:05:36,711
<i>Grab your crucifix</i>

46
00:05:36,878 --> 00:05:38,379
<i>Seven, eight</i>

47
00:05:38,547 --> 00:05:41,048
<i>Gonna stay up late</i>

48
00:05:41,216 --> 00:05:44,093
<i>Nine, ten</i>

49
00:05:55,439 --> 00:05:57,898
Hi, what's your name?

50
00:05:58,400 --> 00:06:00,985
Kristen. What's yours?

51
00:06:01,153 --> 00:06:02,737
[GIGGLES]

52
00:06:03,488 --> 00:06:05,614
What is this place?

53
00:06:05,782 --> 00:06:07,783
[SCRAPING]

54
00:06:08,243 --> 00:06:11,287
I gotta go now.

55
00:06:11,455 --> 00:06:13,247
Wait, little girl, don't go in there!

56
00:06:15,333 --> 00:06:17,126
Little girl!

57
00:06:23,258 --> 00:06:24,383
Little girl?

58
00:06:24,551 --> 00:06:26,260
[BIKE BELL RINGING]

59
00:06:59,211 --> 00:07:03,005
This is where he takes us.

60
00:07:03,381 --> 00:07:04,548
Come on, we're going.

61
00:07:04,716 --> 00:07:06,175
[DOOR SLAMS THEN KRISTEN GASPS]

62
00:07:06,343 --> 00:07:07,718
[SCREAMS]

63
00:07:16,186 --> 00:07:17,645
Freddy's home.

64
00:07:31,535 --> 00:07:33,369
[YELLING]

65
00:07:59,104 --> 00:08:00,688
[FREDDY GROWLS]

66
00:08:12,576 --> 00:08:14,285
[SCREAMING]

67
00:08:19,833 --> 00:08:21,500
GIRL:
Put me down, you're hurting me.

68
00:08:22,085 --> 00:08:23,419
[SCREAMING]

69
00:08:52,407 --> 00:08:53,699
[YELLS]

70
00:08:58,955 --> 00:09:01,248
[KRISTEN SCREAMS 
AND FREDDY LAUGHS]

71
00:09:22,479 --> 00:09:24,188
Kristen!

72
00:09:24,648 --> 00:09:26,565
Mom?

73
00:09:29,486 --> 00:09:31,070
[GROANS]

74
00:09:38,036 --> 00:09:39,495
REPORTER [ON RADIO]:
<i>In local news...</i>

75
00:09:39,663 --> 00:09:41,997
<i>...two more teenage deaths have occurred.</i>
<i>Both suicides.</i>

76
00:09:42,165 --> 00:09:46,252
<i>County health officials are at a loss</i>
<i>to explain this alarming trend.</i>

77
00:09:46,419 --> 00:09:49,004
Nothing like a little cheery news
to start the day, huh?

78
00:09:49,172 --> 00:09:50,589
Yeah. Say, listen, doc.

79
00:09:50,757 --> 00:09:53,801
I got a new theory
about all these suicides, right?

80
00:09:53,969 --> 00:09:56,720
Don't hold back on us, Max,
we need all the help we can get.

81
00:09:56,888 --> 00:09:58,889
Yeah, well, it's fucked up
chromosomes, man.

82
00:09:59,057 --> 00:10:02,184
Think about it, all their parents
dropped acid during the '60s.

83
00:10:02,352 --> 00:10:03,435
It beats Simms' theory.

84
00:10:03,603 --> 00:10:06,230
She thinks it's nothing
but sex, drugs and rock 'n' roll.

85
00:10:06,398 --> 00:10:09,358
-Shit, that's what keeps people alive.
-Heh.

86
00:10:10,193 --> 00:10:11,527
Hi, Taryn.

87
00:10:11,695 --> 00:10:15,281
You don't look so hot, kid.
Are you getting some sleep?

88
00:10:16,533 --> 00:10:18,617
-I didn't think so.
-Good morning, Dr. Gordon.

89
00:10:18,785 --> 00:10:20,703
Good morning, Jennifer.
How are the burns?

90
00:10:20,870 --> 00:10:23,539
-Regular, menthol, ultra-light.
-They're healing up nicely?

91
00:10:23,707 --> 00:10:24,832
Yeah, I've been good.

92
00:10:25,000 --> 00:10:27,584
So, um, when do I get
my cigarette privileges back?

93
00:10:27,752 --> 00:10:29,753
Don't hold your breath.

94
00:10:30,588 --> 00:10:32,965
-Phillip.
-Hey, doc.

95
00:10:42,392 --> 00:10:45,227
-How is he?
-He's cooling down.

96
00:10:45,395 --> 00:10:48,981
If he continues having these outbursts,
I'll have to have him isolated permanently.

97
00:10:49,149 --> 00:10:51,900
Aw, don't worry, it won't come to that.

98
00:10:52,068 --> 00:10:55,237
I, uh-- I read the report
on the new staff member.

99
00:10:55,405 --> 00:10:56,739
Oh, what did you think?

100
00:10:56,906 --> 00:10:58,324
Frankly, I don't understand...

101
00:10:58,491 --> 00:11:03,287
...why some grad-school superstar
is being treated like a seasoned pro.

102
00:11:03,455 --> 00:11:06,415
She's been doing groundbreaking research
on pattern nightmares.

103
00:11:06,583 --> 00:11:09,835
Elizabeth, we don't need any outside help.
I know these kids.

104
00:11:10,003 --> 00:11:14,757
I don't want some hotshot taking chances
with them just so she can get published.

105
00:11:14,924 --> 00:11:18,260
MAN [ON INTERCOM]:
<i>Dr. Gordon, Dr. Simms to Examination, stat.</i>

106
00:11:18,428 --> 00:11:20,763
<i>Dr. Gordon, Dr. Simms</i>
<i>to Examination, stat.</i>

107
00:11:20,930 --> 00:11:21,972
[KRISTEN SCREAMING]

108
00:11:22,140 --> 00:11:23,807
This is ridiculous.
I know my own daughter.

109
00:11:23,975 --> 00:11:27,311
She's trying to get attention, that's all.
And I'm not gonna play her games with her.

110
00:11:27,479 --> 00:11:29,605
Suicide attempt from County General.

111
00:11:29,773 --> 00:11:31,315
-What's her name?
-Kristen Parker.

112
00:11:31,483 --> 00:11:33,317
She was fine until we tried to sedate her.

113
00:11:33,485 --> 00:11:35,277
[CONTINUES SCREAMING]

114
00:11:38,406 --> 00:11:40,324
Watch it, she tore her stitches out.

115
00:11:40,492 --> 00:11:43,243
Kristen, we wanna help you.

116
00:11:43,787 --> 00:11:46,789
-Hold her, hold her.
KRISTEN: Aah!

117
00:11:48,249 --> 00:11:49,458
No, no, no.

118
00:11:49,626 --> 00:11:52,544
I'm Dr. Gordon.
I'm not gonna hurt you, I wanna help you.

119
00:11:52,712 --> 00:11:54,463
-Why don't you--?
-No!

120
00:11:55,965 --> 00:11:57,049
SlMMS:
Be careful, Max.

121
00:11:58,635 --> 00:12:00,177
Back off, Max.

122
00:12:00,345 --> 00:12:03,263
Kristen, put the scalpel down.

123
00:12:03,973 --> 00:12:06,350
Nobody is gonna hurt you.

124
00:12:08,978 --> 00:12:10,604
<i>Five, six</i>

125
00:12:10,772 --> 00:12:14,024
<i>Grab your crucifix</i>

126
00:12:14,192 --> 00:12:16,151
<i>Seven, eight</i>

127
00:12:16,319 --> 00:12:19,321
<i>Better stay up late</i>

128
00:12:19,489 --> 00:12:21,490
<i>Nine, ten</i>

129
00:12:21,658 --> 00:12:24,284
<i>Never, never--</i>

130
00:12:24,452 --> 00:12:25,744
Never sleep again.

131
00:12:33,628 --> 00:12:35,379
Where did you learn that rhyme?

132
00:12:49,227 --> 00:12:51,562
Tell me about the kids.

133
00:12:51,938 --> 00:12:55,524
Well, they're survivors in a way.

134
00:12:55,692 --> 00:13:00,154
They're all severely sleep disordered.
Insomnia, narcolepsy, bed-wetting.

135
00:13:00,321 --> 00:13:02,823
-But the nightmares are the common thread.
-Right.

136
00:13:02,991 --> 00:13:07,286
They seem to share a group delusion,
a bogeyman, for lack of a better word.

137
00:13:07,454 --> 00:13:11,165
They're so traumatized,
they'll do almost anything not to sleep.

138
00:13:11,332 --> 00:13:13,333
Anything?

139
00:13:16,421 --> 00:13:19,423
We lost a kid about a month ago
to Fairview.

140
00:13:19,591 --> 00:13:23,260
I don't know where he got the razors,
but he cut off his eyelids to stay awake.

141
00:13:23,428 --> 00:13:27,139
-Oh, God.
NElL: Shook the kids up pretty badly.

142
00:13:27,307 --> 00:13:30,392
Oh, by the way, that was really great work
with the new patient.

143
00:13:30,560 --> 00:13:32,227
Pretty smooth for an intern.

144
00:13:32,395 --> 00:13:34,938
I have had some experience
with pattern nightmares.

145
00:13:36,441 --> 00:13:40,068
-I've got to get going.
-Okay, well....

146
00:13:40,236 --> 00:13:41,653
Let me help you with that.

147
00:13:45,074 --> 00:13:47,326
-Thanks.
-You're welcome.

148
00:13:49,579 --> 00:13:51,747
Now, uh, be sure
that you check in with Max. . .

149
00:13:51,915 --> 00:13:54,708
...and he'll give you
the whole 25-cent tour and everything.

150
00:13:54,876 --> 00:13:56,835
-All right, I'll see you later.
-All right.

151
00:13:57,003 --> 00:13:58,378
Oh, um, Miss Thompson?

152
00:13:58,546 --> 00:14:00,589
-You can call me Nancy.
-All right.

153
00:14:00,757 --> 00:14:05,344
You call me Neil, all right?
What was that nursery rhyme all about?

154
00:14:06,471 --> 00:14:12,351
That was just something that the kids say
to keep the bogeyman away.

155
00:14:37,502 --> 00:14:38,669
Anyway, that's group therapy.

156
00:14:38,836 --> 00:14:42,047
This whole wing is devoted
to the program. Um....

157
00:14:42,799 --> 00:14:46,969
I guess, yeah, you can use this office
for the time being, okay?

158
00:14:47,136 --> 00:14:48,887
-This will be fine.
-All right, great.

159
00:14:49,055 --> 00:14:52,307
Because I'll have you set up
in your own space by the end of the week.

160
00:14:52,475 --> 00:14:55,686
Um, the patients' rooms
are down this way.

161
00:15:01,067 --> 00:15:03,777
This is Phillip.
We call him "The Walker."

162
00:15:04,279 --> 00:15:06,780
-Why is that?
-Because I sleepwalk.

163
00:15:06,948 --> 00:15:08,115
Perfectly normal event...

164
00:15:08,283 --> 00:15:12,494
...that our illustrious staff loves
to theorize about endlessly.

165
00:15:12,662 --> 00:15:14,329
Phillip, this is Nancy.

166
00:15:14,497 --> 00:15:17,791
Hi, welcome to the snake pit. Heh.

167
00:15:18,293 --> 00:15:20,127
Thanks.

168
00:15:21,004 --> 00:15:22,421
Nice work.

169
00:15:22,589 --> 00:15:27,092
They really ought to be carved out of wood,
but they won't let me have a knife.

170
00:15:27,677 --> 00:15:30,012
I might, you know, pfft!

171
00:15:32,849 --> 00:15:36,435
Um, this lump over here, this is Kincaid.

172
00:15:36,603 --> 00:15:38,562
Now, I want you to take a good look.

173
00:15:38,730 --> 00:15:42,649
He gets thrown in the quiet room so often,
you probably won't see a lot of him.

174
00:15:42,817 --> 00:15:44,401
Ain't that right, cool breeze?

175
00:15:44,569 --> 00:15:48,447
Right, I do it so I don't have to look
at your ugly face all the time.

176
00:15:48,615 --> 00:15:50,365
Yeah, I love you too.

177
00:15:50,533 --> 00:15:52,534
Nice meeting you.

178
00:15:55,330 --> 00:15:58,582
Yeah, they're really good kids
but, uh, don't let them fool you.

179
00:15:58,750 --> 00:16:02,544
They're dangerous,
to themselves and to each other.

180
00:16:10,219 --> 00:16:11,928
Hi, Joey.

181
00:16:13,890 --> 00:16:15,724
Why, thank you.

182
00:16:16,559 --> 00:16:18,310
-Hey, Marcie, how you doing?
-Great.

183
00:16:18,478 --> 00:16:19,811
-These going to C Ward?
-Yeah.

184
00:16:19,979 --> 00:16:21,772
Come on, I'll walk you down.

185
00:16:22,774 --> 00:16:24,733
See you later, Joey.

186
00:16:33,117 --> 00:16:36,078
Mrs. Parker,
was Kristen acting any different?

187
00:16:36,245 --> 00:16:39,581
Did you notice anything strange
before she made the attempt?

188
00:16:39,749 --> 00:16:41,792
Kristen specializes in strangeness.

189
00:16:41,959 --> 00:16:44,920
I've spent thousands on psychiatrists.

190
00:16:46,631 --> 00:16:48,507
Did she always have nightmares?

191
00:16:48,675 --> 00:16:52,010
No, they've gotten worse
since I took away her credit cards.

192
00:16:52,178 --> 00:16:53,261
I'm serious.

193
00:16:53,429 --> 00:16:55,722
Miss Thompson, I don't know
what you want from me.

194
00:16:55,890 --> 00:16:56,932
Just some answers.

195
00:16:57,100 --> 00:16:59,267
There are other kids involved,
not just Kristen.

196
00:16:59,435 --> 00:17:00,852
All good kids, smart kids.

197
00:17:01,020 --> 00:17:04,189
Look, I'm sorry to hear that
but you're the experts on this, not me.

198
00:17:04,357 --> 00:17:08,235
If I had any insight into any of this,
I would share them with you, believe me.

199
00:17:08,403 --> 00:17:09,695
I'm sure you would.

200
00:17:09,862 --> 00:17:11,947
If you'll excuse me,
I have to get downtown.

201
00:17:12,115 --> 00:17:14,157
I'll need to get her things.

202
00:17:14,325 --> 00:17:16,118
I have them packed in a suitcase.

203
00:17:16,285 --> 00:17:19,621
Theresa!

204
00:17:19,789 --> 00:17:21,998
I'll get them, please, I don't mind.

205
00:17:22,166 --> 00:17:25,085
It's the first door at the top of the stairs.

206
00:19:05,561 --> 00:19:07,229
[METAL SQUEAKING]

207
00:19:22,954 --> 00:19:24,996
[BIKE BELL RINGING]

208
00:19:54,652 --> 00:19:56,278
[SCREAMING]

209
00:20:18,676 --> 00:20:20,677
[FLlES BUZZING]

210
00:20:36,736 --> 00:20:38,987
[SNARLS THEN KRISTEN SCREAMS]

211
00:20:53,502 --> 00:20:55,587
[CREAKING]

212
00:21:05,723 --> 00:21:06,973
[SCREAMING]

213
00:21:45,554 --> 00:21:47,555
Nancy!

214
00:21:55,690 --> 00:21:57,524
KRISTEN:
Nancy!

215
00:22:07,159 --> 00:22:08,743
[KRISTEN SCREAMING]

216
00:22:10,871 --> 00:22:15,750
No!

217
00:22:16,836 --> 00:22:18,253
[FREDDY ROARING]

218
00:22:28,264 --> 00:22:31,141
-You.
-Oh, my God.

219
00:22:31,308 --> 00:22:32,475
Run!

220
00:22:34,603 --> 00:22:36,938
Get us back out, Kristen, do it now.

221
00:22:39,191 --> 00:22:40,442
Aah!

222
00:22:55,291 --> 00:22:56,791
I used to live in this house.

223
00:22:57,209 --> 00:22:58,793
That's just a house I dream about.

224
00:22:59,462 --> 00:23:04,340
Have you ever done that before,
pull someone into your dream?

225
00:23:05,134 --> 00:23:09,304
When I was a little girl, like 4 or 5...

226
00:23:09,472 --> 00:23:12,766
...if I had a nightmare,
I would always bring my dad in.

227
00:23:12,933 --> 00:23:15,393
The dreams would always get better.

228
00:23:16,145 --> 00:23:20,774
He used to tell me about it the next day.
He used to think they were his dreams.

229
00:23:20,941 --> 00:23:24,069
-Ha, ha.
-And when did that stop?

230
00:23:24,528 --> 00:23:26,571
When I was still a kid.

231
00:23:26,739 --> 00:23:29,157
My folks got divorced.

232
00:23:29,325 --> 00:23:32,660
And after a while, I just thought
I imagined the whole thing.

233
00:23:32,828 --> 00:23:34,621
I guess I didn't.

234
00:23:34,789 --> 00:23:37,373
It's an amazing gift.

235
00:23:37,833 --> 00:23:41,044
The man in my dreams,
he's real, isn't he?

236
00:23:45,424 --> 00:23:47,258
He's real.

237
00:23:48,719 --> 00:23:52,388
Okay, group's in session.
Straight talk only in this room.

238
00:23:53,224 --> 00:23:55,683
Today, I'd like to start
getting us acquainted. . .

239
00:23:55,851 --> 00:23:58,561
...with our new staff member,
Nancy Thompson.

240
00:23:58,729 --> 00:24:00,105
Let's make her all welcome.

241
00:24:00,272 --> 00:24:01,689
MAN: Hi, Nancy.
-Hi.

242
00:24:01,857 --> 00:24:03,024
-Hi, Nancy.
-Hey, Nancy.

243
00:24:03,192 --> 00:24:06,611
Now, you've already met Phillip and Kincaid
and, of course, Kristen.

244
00:24:06,779 --> 00:24:10,949
How about the rest of you all tell Nancy
something about yourselves?

245
00:24:12,201 --> 00:24:15,120
Will, how about you first?

246
00:24:16,122 --> 00:24:20,708
Hi, I'm Will Stanton and, um,
I've had a little accident, as you can see.

247
00:24:20,876 --> 00:24:21,918
Ended up in this chair.

248
00:24:22,086 --> 00:24:23,795
Accident, my ass.

249
00:24:23,963 --> 00:24:26,548
I thought this was supposed to be
straight talk in here.

250
00:24:26,715 --> 00:24:27,757
Hey, so he took a jump.

251
00:24:27,925 --> 00:24:31,302
At least, he wasn't sticking needles
in his arm with a bunch of lowlifes.

252
00:24:31,470 --> 00:24:33,555
Save it, Kincaid.

253
00:24:33,722 --> 00:24:35,765
-Jennifer?
JENNlFER: Um, ahem.

254
00:24:35,933 --> 00:24:37,559
I'm Jennifer Caulfield.

255
00:24:37,726 --> 00:24:42,063
And, um, as soon as I get out of here,
I'm going to Los Angeles to be an actress.

256
00:24:42,231 --> 00:24:43,857
I'm gonna be on TV.

257
00:24:44,024 --> 00:24:46,776
<i>Yeah, Lifestyles of the Rich</i>
<i>and Psychotic.</i>

258
00:24:46,944 --> 00:24:47,986
Screw you.

259
00:24:48,154 --> 00:24:49,612
[KIDS LAUGHING]

260
00:24:51,031 --> 00:24:52,407
This is Joey.

261
00:24:52,575 --> 00:24:56,411
He used to be a debater in school,
but now he doesn't talk much.

262
00:24:57,746 --> 00:24:58,955
TARYN:
I'm Taryn White.

263
00:25:00,166 --> 00:25:03,751
The only reason I'm in here is because
it's a better deal than juvie hall...

264
00:25:03,919 --> 00:25:06,921
...also, because I'm going
through some very strange shit.

265
00:25:07,423 --> 00:25:08,798
Your dreams?

266
00:25:08,966 --> 00:25:11,467
Hey, everybody has bad dreams.

267
00:25:11,635 --> 00:25:14,429
Can I interject something here
just to save us all some time?

268
00:25:14,597 --> 00:25:15,805
NElL:
Sure, Phillip, go ahead.

269
00:25:15,973 --> 00:25:17,891
Well, according to our kind hosts. . .

270
00:25:18,058 --> 00:25:23,104
...our dreams are a group psychosis,
sort of a mellow mass hysteria.

271
00:25:23,272 --> 00:25:27,400
The fact we dreamt about this guy before
we met doesn't seem to impress anybody.

272
00:25:27,568 --> 00:25:28,818
KINCAlD: Yeah.
TARYN: That's right.

273
00:25:28,986 --> 00:25:33,198
So we go in circles, making minimal
progress with maximum effort.

274
00:25:33,365 --> 00:25:37,619
You won't make any progress until you
recognize your dreams for what they are.

275
00:25:37,786 --> 00:25:39,370
And what are they?

276
00:25:39,538 --> 00:25:41,873
The by-products of guilt.

277
00:25:42,041 --> 00:25:47,128
Psychological scars, stemming
from moral conflicts and overt sexuality.

278
00:25:47,296 --> 00:25:50,173
Oh, great,
now it's my dick that's killing me.

279
00:25:50,341 --> 00:25:51,799
[KIDS LAUGHING]

280
00:25:56,722 --> 00:25:59,224
TARYN: Tell me what's supposed
to be happening again.

281
00:25:59,391 --> 00:26:02,936
Okay, you're being attacked
by the bog demon. Go ahead.

282
00:26:03,103 --> 00:26:04,145
[CLEARS THROAT]

283
00:26:04,313 --> 00:26:05,897
-Uh, 1 4.
-Doesn't count.

284
00:26:06,065 --> 00:26:07,774
You got to say the words.

285
00:26:07,942 --> 00:26:09,150
This is stupid.

286
00:26:09,318 --> 00:26:11,027
Oh, come on.

287
00:26:13,864 --> 00:26:18,993
In the name of Lowrek, Prince of Elves,
demon, begone.

288
00:26:19,161 --> 00:26:23,665
Good, you conquered the demon
but your horse is sinking in the bog.

289
00:26:23,832 --> 00:26:25,458
What do you do?

290
00:26:26,877 --> 00:26:28,461
I go to bed. . .

291
00:26:28,629 --> 00:26:31,089
...and get a new horse in the morning.

292
00:26:33,008 --> 00:26:36,469
Well, how do I score that?
Enchanted slumber or death?

293
00:26:37,263 --> 00:26:39,847
All right, fellas, lights out.

294
00:26:40,599 --> 00:26:42,392
-Oh, Max.
MAX: "Oh, Max."

295
00:26:42,559 --> 00:26:43,685
You know the rules.

296
00:26:43,852 --> 00:26:45,853
-Yeah.
-Come on, Joey, you too.

297
00:26:46,522 --> 00:26:48,022
Every time we get a good game going...

298
00:26:48,190 --> 00:26:50,191
-. . .it's always lights out.
-Mm-hm.

299
00:26:55,698 --> 00:26:57,323
Okay.

300
00:27:01,036 --> 00:27:03,830
-Good night, fellas.
-Good night, Max.

301
00:27:08,419 --> 00:27:10,336
Okay, you get first shift tonight.

302
00:27:10,504 --> 00:27:12,130
Oh, come on, I had it last night.

303
00:27:14,049 --> 00:27:16,884
Good, just remember,
keep your eyes open.

304
00:27:17,052 --> 00:27:20,430
And one whimper
and you wake me up, okay?

305
00:27:35,029 --> 00:27:38,072
-This is nice.
-You've never been here before?

306
00:27:38,240 --> 00:27:41,534
No, um, I think they opened this
when I was at school.

307
00:27:41,702 --> 00:27:43,911
Best Thai food in Springwood.

308
00:27:44,079 --> 00:27:46,831
Of course, it's the only Thai food
in Springwood.

309
00:27:47,333 --> 00:27:49,584
Uh, do your parents still live around here?

310
00:27:51,295 --> 00:27:53,379
My mother passed away.

311
00:27:53,547 --> 00:27:56,257
She, uh, died in her sleep.

312
00:27:56,425 --> 00:27:58,009
I'm sorry.

313
00:27:58,385 --> 00:28:00,428
My father and I, um--

314
00:28:01,555 --> 00:28:04,223
Well, things just seemed to fall apart
after that.

315
00:28:04,433 --> 00:28:06,601
Sounds like a rough time.

316
00:28:06,769 --> 00:28:08,603
It was.

317
00:28:09,855 --> 00:28:14,108
Neil, what if I told you. . .

318
00:28:14,276 --> 00:28:20,573
...that, um, your patients are in real physical
danger from their dreams.

319
00:28:21,575 --> 00:28:25,286
The nightmares are nothing but a symptom
of the real problems.

320
00:28:25,454 --> 00:28:29,540
All right, well, then let's just eliminate
the symptom for the time being.

321
00:28:30,584 --> 00:28:34,045
-With Hypnocil?
-That's right.

322
00:28:34,213 --> 00:28:35,755
You want me to prescribe...

323
00:28:35,964 --> 00:28:39,801
...an experimental psychoactive drug
to a bunch of suicidal teenagers?

324
00:28:39,968 --> 00:28:42,053
Just until we get things under control.

325
00:28:42,221 --> 00:28:45,181
Dream deprivation is nothing
to fool around with.

326
00:28:45,349 --> 00:28:47,266
You have no business taking it yourself.

327
00:28:47,434 --> 00:28:51,104
I used to be like them, Neil.
I know what they're going through.

328
00:28:51,271 --> 00:28:52,522
So do l.

329
00:28:53,649 --> 00:28:57,568
You told me they were survivors
and they all are.

330
00:28:57,736 --> 00:29:00,780
But how much longer they survive
is up to us.

331
00:29:02,783 --> 00:29:05,159
I'm sorry, Nancy.

332
00:29:05,327 --> 00:29:07,412
The answer is no.

333
00:30:02,384 --> 00:30:04,385
-Shh.
-Ah--!

334
00:30:09,183 --> 00:30:10,600
[GROANING]

335
00:30:16,315 --> 00:30:18,065
[FREDDY LAUGHING]

336
00:30:19,943 --> 00:30:21,736
[PH lLLlP GROANING]

337
00:30:25,491 --> 00:30:26,949
Phillip.

338
00:30:29,661 --> 00:30:30,745
Phillip, wake up.

339
00:30:35,584 --> 00:30:38,586
Have a nice stroll, asshole.

340
00:30:39,713 --> 00:30:41,881
[GROANING]

341
00:31:25,342 --> 00:31:27,426
What? What are you doing?

342
00:31:27,594 --> 00:31:29,095
Hey, come on, man.

343
00:31:29,263 --> 00:31:31,514
What, are you crazy?

344
00:31:33,559 --> 00:31:36,310
Oh, shit, what is he doing?

345
00:31:36,478 --> 00:31:38,437
Get help! Get help!

346
00:31:38,605 --> 00:31:41,816
Phillip! Phillip!

347
00:31:45,320 --> 00:31:48,406
Phillip, no!

348
00:31:51,535 --> 00:31:53,035
Joey?

349
00:31:54,037 --> 00:31:55,997
What's the matter?

350
00:31:57,958 --> 00:32:00,042
WlLL:
Phillip! Phillip!

351
00:32:00,210 --> 00:32:02,545
Phillip! Phillip, no!

352
00:32:02,713 --> 00:32:04,505
Phillip, no!

353
00:32:04,673 --> 00:32:07,341
Don't do it, no!

354
00:32:07,509 --> 00:32:10,720
Phillip, don't do it! Phillip!

355
00:32:10,887 --> 00:32:12,305
Goddamn!

356
00:32:12,472 --> 00:32:14,056
Phillip!

357
00:32:14,224 --> 00:32:17,268
-Phillip!
-Phillip!

358
00:32:17,436 --> 00:32:18,686
[ALL SCREAMING]

359
00:32:18,854 --> 00:32:19,895
-Phillip!
-Phillip!

360
00:32:20,063 --> 00:32:21,981
-Don't jump!
-Phillip, don't jump!

361
00:32:22,190 --> 00:32:23,608
[GROANING]

362
00:32:23,775 --> 00:32:25,234
KRISTEN:
Phillip!

363
00:32:25,402 --> 00:32:26,777
-Don't you jump!
-Aah!

364
00:32:29,698 --> 00:32:31,115
[PH lLLlP YELLING]

365
00:32:31,283 --> 00:32:32,825
[LAUGHING]

366
00:32:39,833 --> 00:32:41,417
[CRYING]

367
00:32:44,880 --> 00:32:47,173
I want us to talk
about what happened last night.

368
00:32:48,300 --> 00:32:51,260
I want us to all get our feelings out
in the open.

369
00:32:52,888 --> 00:32:55,556
He wasn't strong enough
so he got wasted, that's all.

370
00:32:55,724 --> 00:32:58,225
That's all? Is that what you think?

371
00:32:58,393 --> 00:33:00,895
He couldn't hack it
so he got nailed, period.

372
00:33:01,063 --> 00:33:05,316
Oh, yeah, big, tough bad ass.
How long are you gonna last?

373
00:33:05,484 --> 00:33:07,109
I'm gonna last longer than any of you.

374
00:33:07,277 --> 00:33:10,112
Well, just go ahead and fight
because that's what he wants.

375
00:33:10,280 --> 00:33:12,365
-Who?
-Who do you think?

376
00:33:12,532 --> 00:33:14,075
What does he want?

377
00:33:14,242 --> 00:33:17,161
To turn us against each other
so we'll be weak, easy prey.

378
00:33:17,329 --> 00:33:19,205
KINCAlD: Horse shit.
-No, she's right.

379
00:33:19,373 --> 00:33:21,999
I think we're all missing the point here.

380
00:33:22,167 --> 00:33:25,628
Phillip's death was
a sleepwalking accident, nothing more.

381
00:33:26,797 --> 00:33:27,838
No.

382
00:33:28,006 --> 00:33:29,674
I could see him up there.

383
00:33:29,841 --> 00:33:31,217
His face--

384
00:33:31,385 --> 00:33:35,096
He was wide awake all the way down.

385
00:33:35,263 --> 00:33:38,265
Well, then it was suicide.
Phillip quit, he gave up.

386
00:33:38,433 --> 00:33:39,725
Joey says it wasn't suicide.

387
00:33:39,893 --> 00:33:42,645
Listen to me, Joey, Phillip killed himself.

388
00:33:42,813 --> 00:33:45,231
Now, that's a cowardly thing.
That's an empty thing.

389
00:33:45,399 --> 00:33:47,692
He let himself down.
He let all of us down.

390
00:33:47,859 --> 00:33:51,112
It was murder.
Can't you understand that?

391
00:33:51,279 --> 00:33:53,280
That bastard murdered him!

392
00:33:53,448 --> 00:33:55,324
I'm not gonna listen to any more of this.

393
00:33:55,826 --> 00:33:57,702
How much longer are you going
to go on...

394
00:33:57,869 --> 00:34:00,287
...blaming your dreams
for your own weaknesses?

395
00:34:00,455 --> 00:34:03,749
-How much longer you gonna keep throw--
-That's enough, Kincaid.

396
00:34:03,917 --> 00:34:07,586
There will be no repeat occurrences
of last night's events.

397
00:34:07,754 --> 00:34:11,257
From now on your doors will be locked
during sleeping hours.

398
00:34:11,883 --> 00:34:14,427
We'll start a policy of evening sedation
for everybody.

399
00:34:14,594 --> 00:34:17,972
The fuck you will. Anybody who tries
drugs on me, gets his ass kicked.

400
00:34:18,140 --> 00:34:21,142
You just bought yourself a night
in the quiet room, mister.

401
00:34:21,309 --> 00:34:24,145
-Now, sit down.
-Fuck you, you sit down.

402
00:34:24,312 --> 00:34:26,772
-Easy, Kincaid.
KINCAlD: Nobody is gonna put me to sleep.

403
00:34:26,940 --> 00:34:28,482
Get away from me. Leave me alone.

404
00:34:28,650 --> 00:34:34,029
I don't wanna go to sleep.
Nobody gonna put me to sleep.

405
00:34:34,197 --> 00:34:35,948
Get your hands-- I ain't gonna sleep.

406
00:34:36,116 --> 00:34:37,324
Stay in your seats.

407
00:34:37,492 --> 00:34:39,326
KINCAlD:
Get your hands off me, I don't wanna--

408
00:34:39,494 --> 00:34:41,328
We'll begin sedation tonight
starting with him.

409
00:34:41,496 --> 00:34:44,248
You can't. They'll be defenseless
against their dreams.

410
00:34:44,416 --> 00:34:45,875
That's precisely what they need.

411
00:34:46,042 --> 00:34:49,670
Some uninterrupted REM sleep
to release all that negative energy.

412
00:34:49,838 --> 00:34:53,758
Elizabeth, I'm prescribing Hypnocil.
It's a dream suppressant.

413
00:34:53,925 --> 00:34:57,094
I know what it is.
I just can't believe what I'm hearing.

414
00:34:57,262 --> 00:34:59,096
-What has she talked you into?
-Nothing.

415
00:34:59,264 --> 00:35:00,765
My patients, my decision.

416
00:35:00,932 --> 00:35:03,809
I want these dreams stopped
till we get some answers.

417
00:35:04,895 --> 00:35:06,312
I can't allow that.

418
00:35:06,480 --> 00:35:08,731
Then I'll go straight to Carver
if I have to.

419
00:35:08,899 --> 00:35:11,859
And he'll either back me up
or accept my resignation.

420
00:35:12,360 --> 00:35:13,778
All right.

421
00:35:13,945 --> 00:35:17,323
But if something goes wrong,
I'll make sure that you're held responsible.

422
00:35:17,491 --> 00:35:20,868
I mean that. Fully responsible.

423
00:35:22,996 --> 00:35:24,538
I can't believe I just said that.

424
00:35:24,706 --> 00:35:27,875
Do you think we can get the Hypnocil
by tomorrow?

425
00:35:28,043 --> 00:35:30,044
We're gonna try.

426
00:35:30,754 --> 00:35:34,048
I hope you know
what you're getting us into.

427
00:35:41,223 --> 00:35:46,393
[SINGING]
<i>Ain't gonna dream no more, no more</i>

428
00:35:46,561 --> 00:35:50,648
<i>Ain't gonna dream no more</i>

429
00:35:51,733 --> 00:35:56,946
<i>All night long, I sing this song</i>

430
00:35:57,113 --> 00:36:01,033
<i>Ain't gonna dream no more</i>

431
00:36:02,202 --> 00:36:04,161
<i>-April!</i>
<i>-He shot me with a slingshot!</i>

432
00:36:04,329 --> 00:36:06,455
<i>-I did not!</i>
<i>-Liar!</i>

433
00:36:06,623 --> 00:36:07,665
<i>WOMAN: April.</i>
GIRL: Liar.

434
00:36:07,833 --> 00:36:08,874
MAN:
<i>Hold it, hold it.</i>

435
00:36:09,042 --> 00:36:11,710
-Girl, what are you doing?
-Watching TV.

436
00:36:11,878 --> 00:36:13,170
I can see that.

437
00:36:13,338 --> 00:36:16,173
Why don't you read a book?
You watch too much damn TV.

438
00:36:16,341 --> 00:36:17,466
Research.

439
00:36:17,634 --> 00:36:20,845
Oh, right, you're gonna be a TV star.

440
00:36:21,012 --> 00:36:22,471
Wait and see.

441
00:36:22,639 --> 00:36:26,767
Yeah, well, if Simms catches you here
after lights out, she's gonna chew my ass.

442
00:36:26,935 --> 00:36:29,645
-I got to stay up, Max.
-Jennifer.

443
00:36:29,813 --> 00:36:31,397
Just tonight, please.

444
00:36:32,190 --> 00:36:34,608
I can't handle the nightmare.

445
00:36:35,402 --> 00:36:38,195
Not after Phillip, not tonight.

446
00:36:42,450 --> 00:36:44,368
Okay.

447
00:36:46,079 --> 00:36:47,663
But I never saw you.

448
00:36:48,790 --> 00:36:50,291
-Thanks, Max.
-Okay.

449
00:36:50,458 --> 00:36:52,293
BOY [ON TV]:
<i>This is a great meal, Mrs. Brown...</i>

450
00:36:52,460 --> 00:36:54,336
<i>...really one of the best I've ever had.</i>

451
00:36:54,504 --> 00:36:56,338
WOMAN:
<i>Thanks, thank you, Steve.</i>

452
00:37:04,222 --> 00:37:05,472
[CHUCKLES]

453
00:37:10,645 --> 00:37:13,147
Hi, sweet stuff, good news.

454
00:37:13,315 --> 00:37:15,107
It can't be good news
coming from you.

455
00:37:15,275 --> 00:37:17,276
I pulled night duty.

456
00:37:17,444 --> 00:37:21,906
-So?
-So got the keys to heaven, baby.

457
00:37:22,073 --> 00:37:24,533
-What?
-The dispensary.

458
00:37:24,701 --> 00:37:29,747
I am talking clean pharmaceutical high,
a night at Club Meth.

459
00:37:29,915 --> 00:37:32,499
-I don't do that shit.
-Yeah?

460
00:37:32,667 --> 00:37:36,170
-What are those, beauty marks?
-Those are ancient history.

461
00:37:36,338 --> 00:37:37,838
Oh, yeah?

462
00:37:38,006 --> 00:37:40,591
Well, if you're ever in the mood
for a history lesson...

463
00:37:40,759 --> 00:37:43,052
...I'm your teacher, understand?

464
00:37:43,219 --> 00:37:47,139
Stay out of my face
or I'll go straight to Max.

465
00:37:47,307 --> 00:37:48,349
Oh, yeah?

466
00:37:48,516 --> 00:37:51,435
Now, who's gonna take the word
of a crazy junkie chick like you?

467
00:37:51,603 --> 00:37:53,228
Fuck off!

468
00:37:53,396 --> 00:37:55,272
[LAUGHING]

469
00:38:00,487 --> 00:38:04,156
<i>MAN [ON TV]: Hon, I kind of figured</i>
<i>you'd watch me bowl tonight.</i>

470
00:38:04,324 --> 00:38:06,283
<i>We're defending the championship,</i>
<i>you know?</i>

471
00:38:06,451 --> 00:38:09,078
<i>-Oh, we're--</i>
<i>WOMAN: Maybe we'll come by later.</i>

472
00:38:09,245 --> 00:38:12,206
<i>Don't suppose anybody would</i>
<i>like some dessert before they leave.</i>

473
00:38:12,374 --> 00:38:14,458
<i>GIRL: No, thanks, Mom.</i>
<i>MAN: No, it was very good.</i>

474
00:38:14,626 --> 00:38:16,543
<i>-Thank you.</i>
WOMAN: Thanks.

475
00:38:21,216 --> 00:38:22,716
<i>MAN: Helen?</i>
WOMAN: Hmm?

476
00:38:22,884 --> 00:38:27,805
<i>MAN: Have you, you know,</i>
<i>talked to her about the way things are?</i>

477
00:38:27,973 --> 00:38:29,765
WOMAN:
<i>Years ago.</i>

478
00:38:30,725 --> 00:38:32,101
MAN:
<i>Years?</i>

479
00:38:32,268 --> 00:38:34,019
BOY:
<i>What do I want to see an old barn for?</i>

480
00:38:34,187 --> 00:38:36,981
<i>GIRL: Come on, it's romantic.</i>
-Aah! Unh.

481
00:38:37,148 --> 00:38:38,399
BOY:
<i>Look, April.</i>

482
00:38:38,566 --> 00:38:41,110
GIRL:
<i>You want your car keys back, don't you?</i>

483
00:38:44,406 --> 00:38:47,741
<i>--silly thing to ask you, but how many</i>
<i>of what did they have to kill?</i>

484
00:38:47,909 --> 00:38:49,660
GABOR:
<i>Don't say that because I love animals.</i>

485
00:38:49,828 --> 00:38:50,995
<i>I've seen animal shelters.</i>

486
00:38:51,162 --> 00:38:54,456
<i>I bought it only red with black in it,</i>
<i>so I didn't know what it was.</i>

487
00:38:54,624 --> 00:38:56,583
<i>-Probably from an artificial bird.</i>
GABOR: Ha.

488
00:38:56,751 --> 00:38:58,794
<i>CAVETT: Did you ever go</i>
<i>to any kind of acting school?</i>

489
00:38:58,962 --> 00:39:01,213
<i>GABOR: Not in the beginning.</i>
<i>I started on a talk show.</i>

490
00:39:01,381 --> 00:39:03,924
<i>When a young actress says,</i>
<i>"How do you succeed in this?"</i>

491
00:39:04,092 --> 00:39:05,759
<i>-You don't always say study?</i>
<i>-Study.</i>

492
00:39:05,927 --> 00:39:07,136
<i>I think you should study.</i>

493
00:39:07,303 --> 00:39:09,596
<i>They have to study, work.</i>

494
00:39:09,764 --> 00:39:11,432
<i>And then maybe you can make it.</i>

495
00:39:11,766 --> 00:39:13,642
<i>-Can I ask you something?</i>
<i>-Certainly.</i>

496
00:39:14,227 --> 00:39:16,186
<i>Who gives a fuck what you think?</i>

497
00:39:16,396 --> 00:39:17,730
[SCREAMS]

498
00:39:23,778 --> 00:39:27,281
GIRL [ON TV]:
<i>This is your break, Jennifer.</i>

499
00:39:27,741 --> 00:39:30,451
[DlSTORTED SCREAMING]

500
00:39:30,618 --> 00:39:32,411
<i>One, two</i>

501
00:39:32,579 --> 00:39:35,247
<i>Freddy's coming for you</i>

502
00:39:35,874 --> 00:39:37,166
<i>Three, four</i>

503
00:39:37,333 --> 00:39:40,753
<i>Better lock your door</i>

504
00:39:43,381 --> 00:39:46,508
<i>This is your break, Jennifer.</i>

505
00:39:49,054 --> 00:39:50,929
<i>This is your break, Jen--</i>

506
00:39:51,097 --> 00:39:52,639
[SCREAMING]

507
00:40:00,315 --> 00:40:04,651
-This is it, Jennifer, your big break in TV.
-Aah!

508
00:40:04,819 --> 00:40:07,946
-Welcome to prime time, bitch!
-Aah!

509
00:40:34,432 --> 00:40:37,184
Don't be ashamed, young man.

510
00:40:37,769 --> 00:40:40,229
This is a place for sorrow.

511
00:40:41,022 --> 00:40:42,523
What faith do you follow?

512
00:40:45,193 --> 00:40:46,735
Science, I suppose.

513
00:40:47,904 --> 00:40:50,364
Sad choice.

514
00:40:50,532 --> 00:40:53,742
There are times when it doesn't offer
much comfort.

515
00:40:57,831 --> 00:41:00,958
I've seen you before, uh, Sister. . .?

516
00:41:01,417 --> 00:41:03,627
Mary Helena.

517
00:41:04,671 --> 00:41:08,090
You do volunteer work at the hospital.

518
00:41:08,258 --> 00:41:12,219
From time to time, when I'm needed.

519
00:41:16,224 --> 00:41:18,892
I should have been able to save them.

520
00:41:19,060 --> 00:41:21,478
Only one thing can save the children.

521
00:41:22,397 --> 00:41:26,692
The unquiet spirit must be laid to rest.

522
00:41:27,902 --> 00:41:31,947
It is an abomination to God and to man.

523
00:41:32,949 --> 00:41:33,991
NANCY:
Neil.

524
00:41:38,371 --> 00:41:40,455
Excuse me, Sister.

525
00:41:42,667 --> 00:41:44,293
What are you doing up here?

526
00:41:44,460 --> 00:41:46,128
Uh, I was just talking to--

527
00:41:47,881 --> 00:41:49,298
NANCY:
To who?

528
00:41:51,593 --> 00:41:53,385
Doesn't matter.

529
00:41:53,553 --> 00:41:56,597
-Are you ready to go now?
-Sure.

530
00:42:07,317 --> 00:42:08,609
Are you finished?

531
00:42:08,776 --> 00:42:11,737
Yeah, I'm sorry. I guess I, uh--
I'm not hungry.

532
00:42:11,905 --> 00:42:13,697
That's okay.

533
00:42:18,661 --> 00:42:21,663
That's pretty. What is it?

534
00:42:24,667 --> 00:42:27,544
This is my Malaysian dream doll.

535
00:42:27,962 --> 00:42:30,923
It's supposed to bring good dreams.

536
00:42:31,466 --> 00:42:33,967
Could use some of that right about now.

537
00:42:41,684 --> 00:42:43,769
You know, I used to think...

538
00:42:43,937 --> 00:42:48,523
...I could do something for the kids,
make some kind of difference.

539
00:42:48,691 --> 00:42:51,693
But they're slipping through my fingers,
every one of them.

540
00:42:52,320 --> 00:42:55,697
You're doing the best you can
for them, Neil.

541
00:42:56,658 --> 00:42:58,158
Am l?

542
00:42:58,618 --> 00:43:00,827
I'm running out of answers.

543
00:43:01,454 --> 00:43:03,914
A patient sleepwalks out
of a high-security ward.

544
00:43:04,082 --> 00:43:05,582
A girl alone in a room dies.

545
00:43:06,501 --> 00:43:08,126
I can't believe this is happening.

546
00:43:09,295 --> 00:43:11,255
Nothing makes any sense.

547
00:43:14,926 --> 00:43:17,135
Then maybe you're ready.

548
00:43:18,304 --> 00:43:19,972
For what?

549
00:43:20,473 --> 00:43:22,307
The truth.

550
00:43:22,725 --> 00:43:24,518
Try me.

551
00:43:25,144 --> 00:43:29,731
Only if you're willing to put aside everything
you've learned and trust me.

552
00:43:30,441 --> 00:43:31,817
Can you do that?

553
00:43:34,195 --> 00:43:36,029
I can do that.

554
00:43:38,866 --> 00:43:40,450
Okay.

555
00:43:40,618 --> 00:43:42,619
Straight talk only in this room.

556
00:43:42,787 --> 00:43:44,371
Is this group?

557
00:43:44,539 --> 00:43:46,290
Well, yeah, unofficially.

558
00:43:46,457 --> 00:43:49,501
Pretty soon, there won't be enough of us
left to call it "group."

559
00:43:49,669 --> 00:43:51,545
Okay, listen up, you guys.

560
00:43:51,713 --> 00:43:54,047
Nancy has something to say.

561
00:43:54,841 --> 00:43:56,967
I know who's trying to kill you.

562
00:43:57,135 --> 00:43:59,970
Don't humor us.
We're not in the mood.

563
00:44:00,680 --> 00:44:04,141
He wears a dirty, brown hat.

564
00:44:04,726 --> 00:44:06,226
He's horribly burned.

565
00:44:08,104 --> 00:44:10,731
He has razors on his right hand.

566
00:44:13,401 --> 00:44:14,526
Who is he?

567
00:44:15,903 --> 00:44:18,739
His name is Freddy Krueger.

568
00:44:19,657 --> 00:44:22,826
He was a child murderer before he died.

569
00:44:22,994 --> 00:44:25,579
And after he died...

570
00:44:25,747 --> 00:44:28,332
...well, he became something worse.

571
00:44:28,499 --> 00:44:32,836
Six years ago, he killed my friends.

572
00:44:33,171 --> 00:44:34,755
He almost killed me.

573
00:44:34,922 --> 00:44:36,506
Why is he after us?

574
00:44:36,674 --> 00:44:38,842
Yeah, what did we do?

575
00:44:39,469 --> 00:44:41,261
It's not you.

576
00:44:41,429 --> 00:44:45,724
Your parents, my parents,
they burned him alive.

577
00:44:45,892 --> 00:44:49,186
And now we're paying for their sins.

578
00:44:50,396 --> 00:44:53,899
You are the last
of the Elm Street children.

579
00:44:55,234 --> 00:44:56,318
WlLL:
Mom and Dad?

580
00:44:56,861 --> 00:44:59,321
I mean, that's crazy.
They never mentioned anything--

581
00:44:59,489 --> 00:45:02,491
Oh, sure, that's the sort of thing
parents tell their kids.

582
00:45:02,658 --> 00:45:04,534
"Good night, darling, say your prayers.

583
00:45:04,702 --> 00:45:08,330
And, oh, by the way, your father and I
torched some maniac last night."

584
00:45:08,498 --> 00:45:10,874
So what do we do about this creep?

585
00:45:11,042 --> 00:45:12,584
Kristen is the key.

586
00:45:13,628 --> 00:45:16,713
She has a very special talent, a gift.

587
00:45:16,881 --> 00:45:19,674
I haven't been able to do that
since I was a little girl.

588
00:45:19,842 --> 00:45:21,635
You did it the other night.

589
00:45:22,220 --> 00:45:23,303
That was different.

590
00:45:23,471 --> 00:45:28,308
NANCY: You never lose a gift like that.
You just forget how to use it.

591
00:45:28,476 --> 00:45:30,185
How about it, will you try?

592
00:45:32,397 --> 00:45:35,524
All of you have this inner strength.

593
00:45:35,691 --> 00:45:40,237
Some special power that you've had
in your most wonderful dreams.

594
00:45:40,988 --> 00:45:44,449
Together, we can learn to use that power
if we try.

595
00:45:44,617 --> 00:45:45,784
You sound like Peter Pan.

596
00:45:47,245 --> 00:45:48,912
Remember, open mind.

597
00:45:49,747 --> 00:45:50,789
Okay.

598
00:45:50,957 --> 00:45:54,668
Uh, Taryn, would you pull
the shades down please?

599
00:45:54,836 --> 00:45:58,630
We're gonna try a little,
uh, group hypnosis.

600
00:46:09,183 --> 00:46:13,603
I want you all to follow this pendulum
with your eyes.

601
00:46:15,606 --> 00:46:17,816
Tune out everything else.

602
00:46:18,276 --> 00:46:21,069
Nothing else exists but the pendulum.

603
00:46:21,237 --> 00:46:23,697
Take us there, Kristen.

604
00:46:24,282 --> 00:46:28,243
NElL:
Breathe deeply and relax.

605
00:46:28,411 --> 00:46:33,457
Starting with your toes, relax everything
till there's no tension left in your bodies.

606
00:46:35,418 --> 00:46:37,711
Keep following the pendulum.

607
00:46:39,380 --> 00:46:41,673
You find yourselves getting tired.

608
00:46:43,259 --> 00:46:45,844
Nothing would feel better right now.. .

609
00:46:46,012 --> 00:46:51,349
...than a nice, long, deep sleep.

610
00:46:53,019 --> 00:46:55,520
I'm gonna count backwards from five.

611
00:46:55,688 --> 00:46:57,898
When I finish...

612
00:46:58,441 --> 00:47:02,277
...you will all be asleep.

613
00:47:03,404 --> 00:47:04,946
Five.

614
00:47:05,114 --> 00:47:06,656
Four.

615
00:47:06,824 --> 00:47:08,533
Three.

616
00:47:08,701 --> 00:47:10,285
Two.

617
00:47:10,453 --> 00:47:12,078
One.

618
00:47:25,218 --> 00:47:26,551
Sorry.

619
00:47:26,719 --> 00:47:28,803
That's okay, we'll try again.

620
00:47:28,971 --> 00:47:30,764
Everybody take five. Ahem.

621
00:47:37,605 --> 00:47:41,358
I was willing to go through with this
for the kids' peace of mind and yours...

622
00:47:41,526 --> 00:47:44,110
...but you're gonna have to face reality.

623
00:47:44,779 --> 00:47:46,154
[WHEELS SQUEAKING]

624
00:47:46,322 --> 00:47:47,739
[KIDS CHATTERING QUIETLY]

625
00:47:49,408 --> 00:47:52,786
WlLL: No, I'm serious, I happen to be
very susceptible to hypnosis.

626
00:47:52,954 --> 00:47:55,455
-I've been told by professionals.
TARYN: What professionals?

627
00:47:55,623 --> 00:47:56,998
Where are these professionals?

628
00:47:57,166 --> 00:48:00,919
WlLL: Well, "professionals" as in,
like, magic-users and illusionists.

629
00:48:18,646 --> 00:48:22,274
Listen, Joey, I just wanted
to get you alone for a second.

630
00:48:22,441 --> 00:48:27,070
I mean, look, I really like you.

631
00:48:27,238 --> 00:48:29,114
Do you like me?

632
00:48:29,282 --> 00:48:30,532
I know this sounds crazy...

633
00:48:30,700 --> 00:48:36,162
...but I make up excuses to come
into the ward every day just to see you.

634
00:48:36,330 --> 00:48:38,790
You're so cute.

635
00:48:42,461 --> 00:48:44,504
Neil, let's just try one more time.

636
00:48:44,672 --> 00:48:47,257
If it doesn't work, I promise I'll--

637
00:48:54,098 --> 00:48:56,182
We're here.

638
00:48:56,350 --> 00:48:57,976
Where here?

639
00:48:58,144 --> 00:48:59,311
We're in the dream.

640
00:49:00,438 --> 00:49:02,856
Well, no, we're not.
We're still here in the group.

641
00:49:07,194 --> 00:49:09,362
In my dreams, I can walk.

642
00:49:09,530 --> 00:49:11,656
My legs are strong.

643
00:49:11,824 --> 00:49:15,243
In my dreams, I am the wizard master.

644
00:49:23,586 --> 00:49:27,339
Try something, Kristen.
What can you do in your dream?

645
00:49:37,725 --> 00:49:39,559
[ALL CHEERING]

646
00:49:40,561 --> 00:49:43,730
A perfect score.
The crowd goes wild. Ahh!

647
00:49:43,898 --> 00:49:46,316
-Ha, ha!
-Fucking A, dig this.

648
00:49:52,365 --> 00:49:55,075
Kincaid, please.

649
00:49:55,242 --> 00:49:56,451
That's very unnerving.

650
00:49:56,619 --> 00:49:58,286
Hey, check out Taryn.

651
00:49:58,829 --> 00:50:01,873
In my dreams, I'm beautiful. . .

652
00:50:02,792 --> 00:50:04,959
...and bad.

653
00:50:05,586 --> 00:50:08,797
Look, I could get
into a lot of trouble for this.

654
00:50:10,841 --> 00:50:14,594
But I know you won't say anything,
will you?

655
00:50:15,930 --> 00:50:17,722
Unzip me.

656
00:50:32,113 --> 00:50:34,614
Do you like my body, Joey?

657
00:50:49,755 --> 00:50:51,005
[GRUNTS]

658
00:51:05,938 --> 00:51:07,564
[SNARLS]

659
00:51:12,570 --> 00:51:14,446
[LAUGHING]

660
00:51:24,165 --> 00:51:25,290
What's wrong, Joey?

661
00:51:25,833 --> 00:51:27,500
Feeling tongue-tied?

662
00:51:27,668 --> 00:51:29,669
[LAUGHING]

663
00:51:57,531 --> 00:51:58,782
Aah!

664
00:52:01,911 --> 00:52:03,661
What's happening?

665
00:52:03,996 --> 00:52:05,038
-He's close.
-Who?

666
00:52:05,206 --> 00:52:06,790
-Freddy?
-He's out in the halls.

667
00:52:06,957 --> 00:52:08,708
-Where's Joey?
-Freddy's got him.

668
00:52:11,754 --> 00:52:13,004
Aah!

669
00:52:13,172 --> 00:52:15,423
Quiet, everyone, listen.

670
00:52:18,803 --> 00:52:20,887
[LOW RUMBLING]

671
00:52:22,848 --> 00:52:24,724
The room's changing.

672
00:52:24,892 --> 00:52:26,142
What the heck is going on?

673
00:52:26,310 --> 00:52:28,353
-Doctor--
-What's happening?

674
00:52:32,483 --> 00:52:34,901
NElL:
Get away from the wall!

675
00:52:35,611 --> 00:52:37,612
[ALL YELLING]

676
00:52:54,755 --> 00:52:56,923
Don't panic! Quiet down!

677
00:52:58,467 --> 00:53:00,051
Aah!

678
00:53:01,387 --> 00:53:02,887
Help! Help!

679
00:53:03,055 --> 00:53:04,597
-This isn't real!
-Dr. Gordon!

680
00:53:04,765 --> 00:53:07,225
-No!
-lt's not!

681
00:53:07,393 --> 00:53:08,893
Quiet, the door.

682
00:53:11,146 --> 00:53:13,273
What's going on in here?

683
00:53:14,567 --> 00:53:16,276
What's wrong with Joey?

684
00:53:17,403 --> 00:53:18,862
Joey.

685
00:53:19,947 --> 00:53:21,823
-Code blue.
-Oh, my God.

686
00:53:24,702 --> 00:53:26,286
[MACHINE BEEPING]

687
00:53:29,582 --> 00:53:32,542
He's in a deep coma.
There's nothing we can do for him.

688
00:53:32,710 --> 00:53:34,669
This is inexcusable.

689
00:53:34,837 --> 00:53:36,546
The session was unauthorized.

690
00:53:36,714 --> 00:53:38,923
It was purposely conducted
without my knowledge.

691
00:53:39,091 --> 00:53:41,634
Unusual steps were called for, Dr. Carver.

692
00:53:41,802 --> 00:53:44,220
Is that what I should tell
that young man's parents?

693
00:53:44,388 --> 00:53:46,931
I understand you prescribed
a highly experimental drug.

694
00:53:47,099 --> 00:53:49,058
Dr. Carver, he's not in a coma
because of--

695
00:53:49,226 --> 00:53:51,477
Young lady, your opinion
is of no interest to me.

696
00:53:51,645 --> 00:53:53,605
Furthermore, according to Dr. Simms...

697
00:53:53,772 --> 00:53:56,065
...you've been creating panic
among the patients.

698
00:53:56,233 --> 00:53:58,151
-That's not true.
-Dr. Gordon.

699
00:53:58,319 --> 00:54:00,695
In the last four days,
we've had two suicides.

700
00:54:00,863 --> 00:54:02,447
Now that young man is in a coma.

701
00:54:02,615 --> 00:54:05,909
I think it's safe to say that your approach
has failed, entirely.

702
00:54:06,452 --> 00:54:09,287
You're both relieved of duty.
I want you out of here today.

703
00:54:12,708 --> 00:54:16,920
I'm sorry, Neil.
I'm afraid you brought it on yourself.

704
00:54:17,087 --> 00:54:21,674
For God's sake, Elizabeth, please.
Will you please just try to help the kids?

705
00:54:21,842 --> 00:54:23,760
Will you listen to them?

706
00:54:23,928 --> 00:54:26,012
Of course, I will.

707
00:54:31,018 --> 00:54:33,353
What are we going to do?

708
00:54:34,730 --> 00:54:38,232
There is nothing that we can do.
It's out of our hands.

709
00:55:17,231 --> 00:55:18,648
Sister!

710
00:56:20,335 --> 00:56:22,295
Sister?

711
00:56:36,435 --> 00:56:38,144
Hello?

712
00:56:47,821 --> 00:56:49,530
Sister?

713
00:57:00,751 --> 00:57:03,586
This is where it began.

714
00:57:04,379 --> 00:57:06,589
This wing has been closed for years.

715
00:57:07,382 --> 00:57:09,050
What was this place?

716
00:57:09,218 --> 00:57:10,843
Purgatory.

717
00:57:11,011 --> 00:57:14,138
Fashioned by the hands of men.

718
00:57:14,640 --> 00:57:18,351
Twisted, lonely souls.

719
00:57:18,519 --> 00:57:22,021
The worst of the criminally insane...

720
00:57:22,356 --> 00:57:26,067
...were locked up in here like animals.

721
00:57:26,485 --> 00:57:29,570
This whole facility was shut down
in the '40s, wasn't it?

722
00:57:29,738 --> 00:57:32,406
Some sort of scandal?

723
00:57:33,117 --> 00:57:35,326
A young girl on the staff...

724
00:57:35,494 --> 00:57:39,872
...was accidentally locked in here
over the holidays.

725
00:57:40,040 --> 00:57:44,418
The inmates kept her hidden for days.

726
00:57:44,586 --> 00:57:49,549
She was raped hundreds of times.

727
00:57:50,008 --> 00:57:53,511
When they found her,
she was barely alive.. .

728
00:57:54,596 --> 00:57:56,722
...and with child.

729
00:57:57,850 --> 00:58:00,143
That girl was Amanda Krueger.

730
00:58:00,936 --> 00:58:03,020
-Her child--
-Freddy.

731
00:58:03,564 --> 00:58:08,234
The bastard son of a hundred maniacs.

732
00:58:09,361 --> 00:58:12,071
Some say he was murdered. . .

733
00:58:12,531 --> 00:58:14,323
...though no body was ever found.

734
00:58:16,910 --> 00:58:22,707
You said something before
about laying him to rest.

735
00:58:22,875 --> 00:58:26,002
You must find the remains.. .

736
00:58:26,170 --> 00:58:30,256
...and bury him in hallowed ground.

737
00:58:36,471 --> 00:58:38,598
Hallowed ground?

738
00:58:39,057 --> 00:58:40,766
Sister?

739
00:58:42,936 --> 00:58:47,023
If your only faith is science, doctor...

740
00:58:47,608 --> 00:58:52,111
...it may be you that's laid to rest.

741
00:58:54,656 --> 00:58:57,783
Wait! Sister!

742
00:59:17,012 --> 00:59:19,096
Let go of him, you bastard.

743
00:59:23,894 --> 00:59:26,229
Oh, my God.

744
00:59:37,282 --> 00:59:39,492
NANCY: I've got to go in.
We don't have a choice.

745
00:59:39,868 --> 00:59:42,536
Getting yourself killed
won't help the kids at all.

746
00:59:44,539 --> 00:59:47,416
Besides, we do have a choice.

747
00:59:47,584 --> 00:59:50,461
Well, assuming your mysterious nun
is right.

748
00:59:50,629 --> 00:59:53,422
I've heard weirder things this week.

749
00:59:54,716 --> 00:59:56,175
All right.

750
00:59:56,343 --> 00:59:59,887
Whoever she is, she does seem to know
more about Krueger than I do.

751
01:00:00,097 --> 01:00:03,599
The question is,
what happened to his body?

752
01:00:04,351 --> 01:00:09,105
They burned him to death in his boiler room
and they hid the remains.

753
01:00:09,273 --> 01:00:11,440
Who would know where they're hidden?

754
01:00:12,192 --> 01:00:14,694
Well, only one man knows.

755
01:00:16,196 --> 01:00:18,864
And it's time for him to talk.

756
01:00:19,199 --> 01:00:22,159
No!

757
01:00:22,327 --> 01:00:24,161
You can't take Nancy away from us!

758
01:00:24,329 --> 01:00:26,038
You can't! She's all we have!

759
01:00:26,206 --> 01:00:28,082
You're a sick girl, Kristen.

760
01:00:28,250 --> 01:00:30,584
If you wanna get better,
you must trust me now.

761
01:00:31,169 --> 01:00:32,545
[GRUNTING]

762
01:00:37,301 --> 01:00:38,342
No!

763
01:00:38,510 --> 01:00:41,053
-No, no!
-Take her to the quiet room and sedate her.

764
01:00:41,221 --> 01:00:45,099
-Take it easy.
-You stupid bitch, you're killing us!

765
01:00:45,267 --> 01:00:47,226
You're killing us!

766
01:00:47,394 --> 01:00:48,686
No!

767
01:00:48,854 --> 01:00:51,230
You're killing us!

768
01:00:51,398 --> 01:00:52,940
No!

769
01:00:53,108 --> 01:00:55,067
All right, everybody, back to bed.

770
01:00:55,235 --> 01:00:57,111
KRISTEN:
No! No!

771
01:00:57,279 --> 01:00:59,071
[ROCK MUSIC PLAYING]

772
01:01:14,588 --> 01:01:16,255
Hi, Daddy.

773
01:01:19,926 --> 01:01:23,304
Well, if it isn't my little girl.

774
01:01:25,390 --> 01:01:29,477
My baby come to see her daddy, huh?

775
01:01:29,644 --> 01:01:32,271
-lt's been a long time.
-Yeah.

776
01:01:32,439 --> 01:01:35,066
But you're here, sit down.

777
01:01:35,776 --> 01:01:39,570
What did I do to, uh, get so lucky?

778
01:01:39,738 --> 01:01:43,032
I thought
that you were trying to forget me.

779
01:01:43,200 --> 01:01:46,160
That's not true.
You're the one who's trying to forget.

780
01:01:46,328 --> 01:01:49,538
Oh, come on.

781
01:01:50,332 --> 01:01:52,416
I need your help, Dad.

782
01:01:52,584 --> 01:01:53,751
Krueger is back.

783
01:01:56,129 --> 01:01:57,755
[CHUCKLES]

784
01:01:58,840 --> 01:02:02,093
Fred Krueger is dead.

785
01:02:02,260 --> 01:02:05,471
You always had a little trouble trying
to understand that, sweetheart.

786
01:02:05,639 --> 01:02:07,098
You know what he did.

787
01:02:09,434 --> 01:02:10,768
He's doing it again.

788
01:02:12,562 --> 01:02:13,979
She's telling you the truth.

789
01:02:14,147 --> 01:02:16,190
I don't believe we've ever met, friend.

790
01:02:16,358 --> 01:02:19,318
And I don't think this is any
of your goddamn business.

791
01:02:19,486 --> 01:02:23,781
I think we can stop him this time.
Stop him for good.

792
01:02:23,949 --> 01:02:27,576
But we need to know
where his bones were hidden.

793
01:02:29,413 --> 01:02:34,041
I've lost too much over this already.

794
01:02:34,209 --> 01:02:35,292
I'm through with it.

795
01:02:35,460 --> 01:02:38,546
People are still dying after all this time.

796
01:02:38,713 --> 01:02:41,715
Stop running away from it.

797
01:02:43,301 --> 01:02:45,219
You owe me.

798
01:02:46,555 --> 01:02:48,681
It was nice seeing you again, princess.

799
01:02:48,849 --> 01:02:53,018
Next time, don't stay away so long.

800
01:02:58,024 --> 01:02:59,733
Nancy?

801
01:03:01,027 --> 01:03:05,197
-Nancy.
-I'll be okay, just give me a minute.

802
01:03:05,365 --> 01:03:06,782
[BEEPER BEEPING]

803
01:03:08,535 --> 01:03:09,577
That's the hospital.

804
01:03:20,213 --> 01:03:21,255
[PHONE RINGS]

805
01:03:21,423 --> 01:03:23,048
-Dr. Gordon?
NElL: Taryn?

806
01:03:23,216 --> 01:03:26,594
You've got to come right away.
It's Kristen, she had a total shit attack.

807
01:03:26,761 --> 01:03:28,888
Simms doped her up,
put her in the quiet room.

808
01:03:30,056 --> 01:03:33,225
Simms put Kristen in the quiet room
for the night. They sedated her.

809
01:03:33,393 --> 01:03:34,435
Oh, no.

810
01:03:34,895 --> 01:03:37,897
She can't stay awake for long.
She's all alone in there.

811
01:03:38,064 --> 01:03:39,190
Freddy is gonna get her.

812
01:03:39,357 --> 01:03:41,358
<i>Okay, none of you panic, just stay cool.</i>

813
01:03:41,526 --> 01:03:42,776
Help is on the way.

814
01:03:42,944 --> 01:03:44,403
<i>-Just hurry.</i>
-Okay.

815
01:03:44,571 --> 01:03:46,864
-We better get there now.
-You go, I gotta get the remains.

816
01:03:47,032 --> 01:03:50,075
-lt's no use. You see him.
-I'll talk, you get to the hospital.

817
01:03:50,243 --> 01:03:51,952
-Make Simms understand.
-She'll never.

818
01:03:52,120 --> 01:03:54,288
I got to get to Kristen somehow.

819
01:03:54,456 --> 01:03:55,789
Nancy, be careful.

820
01:04:11,932 --> 01:04:14,642
My name is Neil Gordon.
Pleased to meet you.

821
01:04:14,809 --> 01:04:16,810
There, now we've met.

822
01:04:16,978 --> 01:04:18,437
Now, listen to me!

823
01:04:18,605 --> 01:04:21,941
I don't know if you care
whether Nancy lives or dies but I do!

824
01:04:24,611 --> 01:04:27,780
You and I are going
on a little scavenger hunt.

825
01:04:45,131 --> 01:04:47,716
Please, God.

826
01:04:47,884 --> 01:04:50,636
Don't make me sleep.

827
01:05:01,064 --> 01:05:03,482
What the hell are we doing here?

828
01:05:04,276 --> 01:05:07,486
Hey. Hey!

829
01:05:07,654 --> 01:05:09,363
I won't be long.

830
01:06:00,248 --> 01:06:02,458
-What do you think you're doing?
-Uh--

831
01:06:02,626 --> 01:06:04,627
Look, uh, sorry. Heh.

832
01:06:04,794 --> 01:06:07,546
I really need this. I got, uh--

833
01:06:08,214 --> 01:06:10,090
I'll reimburse you.

834
01:06:10,800 --> 01:06:13,469
Here, you can keep my driver's license.
I'll be back.

835
01:06:19,434 --> 01:06:20,934
[DINGS]

836
01:06:28,818 --> 01:06:31,445
Max, I need to see Kristen.

837
01:06:31,613 --> 01:06:32,946
You don't understand.

838
01:06:33,114 --> 01:06:36,784
Look, Miss Thompson, save your breath.
Dr. Simms gave me specific instructions.

839
01:06:36,951 --> 01:06:39,828
No one gets to see Kristen,
especially you.

840
01:06:39,996 --> 01:06:42,915
But Max, she needs me, she's in danger.
You got to believe me.

841
01:06:43,083 --> 01:06:48,420
Listen, I really think you mean well, I do.
But my kids have been dying off.

842
01:06:48,588 --> 01:06:50,673
And even if I didn't have orders
from Simms. . .

843
01:06:50,840 --> 01:06:53,092
...I wouldn't let you near her, no way.

844
01:06:55,679 --> 01:06:59,014
Okay, Max, I understand.

845
01:06:59,182 --> 01:07:01,809
-Can I say goodbye to the others?
-I don't know.

846
01:07:02,435 --> 01:07:04,687
It will be my last chance.

847
01:07:06,231 --> 01:07:08,941
Okay, you got five minutes.
They're in the TV room.

848
01:07:14,447 --> 01:07:16,156
Where have you been?
We've been going crazy.

849
01:07:16,324 --> 01:07:18,575
-Shh! There's no time for that, come on.
WlLL: Where?

850
01:07:18,743 --> 01:07:19,868
Our last group.

851
01:07:20,912 --> 01:07:22,371
All right.

852
01:07:34,843 --> 01:07:36,635
In there.

853
01:07:38,346 --> 01:07:41,515
We knew nobody
would ever find it in that place.

854
01:07:42,976 --> 01:07:45,102
I'm not sure I can find it myself anymore.

855
01:08:16,176 --> 01:08:19,428
All right, it's deep in the heart
of the place.

856
01:08:19,596 --> 01:08:21,472
Take it slow.

857
01:08:37,864 --> 01:08:40,199
Straight talk only in here.

858
01:08:40,658 --> 01:08:41,742
What about Kristen?

859
01:08:41,910 --> 01:08:44,661
We can't get to her, I tried.

860
01:08:45,497 --> 01:08:48,415
I was hoping we would have more time
to learn to use the dreams.

861
01:08:49,334 --> 01:08:52,711
But Joey is in there.
And Kristen is going in with or without us.

862
01:08:52,879 --> 01:08:54,338
They need us.

863
01:08:54,506 --> 01:08:57,716
You mean, we're gonna try
to go in with her? To link up?

864
01:08:57,884 --> 01:08:59,218
It's now or never.

865
01:08:59,385 --> 01:09:02,262
I'm not gonna kid you.
This is as dangerous as it gets.

866
01:09:02,430 --> 01:09:05,098
If you die in this dream, it's for real.

867
01:09:05,266 --> 01:09:07,434
Nobody has to go in
that doesn't want to.

868
01:09:12,273 --> 01:09:13,857
I'm in.

869
01:09:14,567 --> 01:09:15,984
Me too.

870
01:09:17,695 --> 01:09:20,364
Let's go kick the motherfucker's ass
all over dreamland.

871
01:09:20,532 --> 01:09:21,573
-Yeah.
-Ha, ha.

872
01:09:21,741 --> 01:09:25,494
So remember, we have to stay together
whatever happens.

873
01:09:25,662 --> 01:09:28,247
It's the only way we can beat him.

874
01:09:34,629 --> 01:09:37,422
All right, clear your mind of everything.

875
01:09:42,387 --> 01:09:44,680
Picture yourself in the quiet room.. .

876
01:09:44,848 --> 01:09:49,768
...the soft white walls,
the total silence.

877
01:09:49,936 --> 01:09:52,688
Only the sound of your heart beating.

878
01:09:53,523 --> 01:09:55,858
Picture yourself there with Kristen.

879
01:09:56,651 --> 01:09:59,444
I'm gonna count backwards from five.

880
01:09:59,612 --> 01:10:02,531
And when I'm done, we'll all be asleep.

881
01:10:03,283 --> 01:10:05,951
We'll all be in the quiet room.

882
01:10:08,079 --> 01:10:09,872
Five.

883
01:10:12,125 --> 01:10:14,585
Four.

884
01:10:15,670 --> 01:10:17,296
Three.

885
01:10:19,674 --> 01:10:21,508
Two.

886
01:10:23,511 --> 01:10:25,137
<i>One.</i>

887
01:10:27,724 --> 01:10:30,726
Nancy, heh, I knew you would come.

888
01:10:30,894 --> 01:10:33,312
You don't think we'd let you
go in alone, do you?

889
01:10:33,479 --> 01:10:35,898
-No way, we are a team.
WlLL: Yeah.

890
01:10:36,065 --> 01:10:39,818
Listen, everybody, Joey needs us.
I can feel him.

891
01:10:39,986 --> 01:10:41,194
Where is he?

892
01:10:41,654 --> 01:10:43,238
How do we find him, Kristen?

893
01:10:43,406 --> 01:10:45,908
[ALL YELLING]

894
01:10:52,332 --> 01:10:54,374
NANCY:
Stay in the middle of the room!

895
01:10:56,961 --> 01:10:58,712
No matter what happens, stay together!

896
01:10:59,839 --> 01:11:01,381
KRISTEN: Help!
TARYN: Nancy!

897
01:11:01,549 --> 01:11:03,383
Help me!

898
01:11:04,469 --> 01:11:05,802
[DOKKEN'S "INTO THE FIRE" PLAYING]

899
01:11:05,970 --> 01:11:15,562
<i>Into the fire</i>

900
01:11:16,147 --> 01:11:18,523
Honey, you're gonna wake up
the whole neighborhood.

901
01:11:18,691 --> 01:11:19,942
[MUSIC STOPS]

902
01:11:20,485 --> 01:11:23,528
What are you still doing up? It's past 1 .

903
01:11:24,822 --> 01:11:26,198
I--

904
01:11:27,575 --> 01:11:29,618
I just thought I'd wait for you.

905
01:11:29,786 --> 01:11:32,037
Well, I'm home.
You can get to sleep now.

906
01:11:32,205 --> 01:11:34,122
Come on, ándale.

907
01:11:40,546 --> 01:11:41,755
[LAUGHING]

908
01:11:41,923 --> 01:11:43,715
What's that for?

909
01:11:43,883 --> 01:11:46,093
I'm just glad you're home.

910
01:11:51,683 --> 01:11:54,685
Mom, I had the most awful dream.

911
01:11:54,852 --> 01:11:57,312
MAN:
Elaine, where do you keep the bourbon?

912
01:11:57,480 --> 01:11:59,564
I'll be right down.

913
01:12:00,650 --> 01:12:02,359
Kris, I've got a guest.

914
01:12:02,527 --> 01:12:05,028
Please, Mom,
I just don't wanna be alone.

915
01:12:05,947 --> 01:12:07,155
Aah!

916
01:12:07,323 --> 01:12:11,243
-I said, where is the fucking bourbon!
-Mom!

917
01:12:13,413 --> 01:12:15,414
You should listen to your mother.

918
01:12:15,623 --> 01:12:19,626
Goddamn it, Kristen, you ruin everything.
Every time I bring a man home, you spoil it!

919
01:12:19,794 --> 01:12:23,171
You know what your shrink says,
you're just trying to get attention!

920
01:12:25,508 --> 01:12:27,009
[SCREAMING]

921
01:12:48,322 --> 01:12:57,122
Nancy!

922
01:12:57,290 --> 01:12:59,541
Kristen!

923
01:12:59,709 --> 01:13:00,917
Is that you?

924
01:13:55,431 --> 01:13:57,724
Welcome home, Taryn.

925
01:13:58,684 --> 01:14:00,185
Look familiar?

926
01:14:00,353 --> 01:14:03,730
Okay, asshole, let's dance.

927
01:14:05,858 --> 01:14:07,317
[BOTH GRUNTING]

928
01:14:14,534 --> 01:14:17,577
Taryn, Taryn, Taryn.

929
01:14:18,996 --> 01:14:22,207
Why--? Why should we fight?

930
01:14:22,667 --> 01:14:25,502
We're old friends, you and I, remember?

931
01:14:29,298 --> 01:14:31,091
Let's get high.

932
01:14:31,259 --> 01:14:33,468
[LAUGHING]

933
01:14:40,893 --> 01:14:41,935
[GRUNTS]

934
01:14:42,103 --> 01:14:45,230
[SCREAMING]

935
01:14:53,281 --> 01:14:55,574
What a rush.

936
01:15:07,295 --> 01:15:08,461
[TARYN SCREAMING IN DISTANCE]

937
01:15:08,629 --> 01:15:10,088
Hello?

938
01:15:10,256 --> 01:15:13,758
You guys, where are you?

939
01:15:17,096 --> 01:15:18,305
Is somebody there?

940
01:15:18,472 --> 01:15:20,307
[FREDDY LAUGHING]

941
01:15:25,438 --> 01:15:27,522
[CLATTERING]

942
01:15:36,991 --> 01:15:38,742
Oh, Will.

943
01:15:39,535 --> 01:15:42,078
You look tired.

944
01:15:42,246 --> 01:15:44,497
Have a seat.

945
01:15:44,999 --> 01:15:47,959
No, thanks.
I'm fine just the way I am.

946
01:15:48,127 --> 01:15:49,544
For now maybe.

947
01:15:49,712 --> 01:15:52,631
But when you wake up. . .

948
01:15:53,966 --> 01:16:00,305
...it's back in the saddle again.

949
01:16:09,232 --> 01:16:11,066
My leg!

950
01:16:15,238 --> 01:16:17,280
It's the chair for you, kid.

951
01:16:17,740 --> 01:16:19,783
I am the wizard master.

952
01:16:21,619 --> 01:16:23,161
I am the wizard master!

953
01:16:33,339 --> 01:16:37,467
In the name of Lowrek, Prince of Elves,
demon, begone.

954
01:16:43,849 --> 01:16:45,850
[GRUNTING]

955
01:16:47,103 --> 01:16:50,689
Sorry, kid.
I don't believe in fairy tales.

956
01:16:51,023 --> 01:16:53,358
[SCREAMING]

957
01:16:55,778 --> 01:16:57,821
KRISTEN:
Hello?

958
01:16:59,198 --> 01:17:00,907
Somebody?

959
01:17:02,952 --> 01:17:04,661
Hello.

960
01:17:07,081 --> 01:17:09,833
-Kristen!
-Nancy! Aah!

961
01:17:11,210 --> 01:17:12,752
[WOOD CRUNCHING]

962
01:17:12,920 --> 01:17:16,256
-What is that?
-I don't know.

963
01:17:22,805 --> 01:17:25,348
Yo, I thought I heard voices.

964
01:17:25,516 --> 01:17:28,393
Kincaid, I could kiss you.

965
01:17:32,356 --> 01:17:34,566
-What's stopping you?
-Mm!

966
01:17:34,942 --> 01:17:36,735
Cool. So where's Joey?

967
01:17:36,902 --> 01:17:39,154
I don't know.
This place is like a maze.

968
01:17:39,322 --> 01:17:41,573
Then it's time to stop guessing
and start messing.

969
01:17:41,741 --> 01:17:42,824
Yo, Freddy!

970
01:17:42,992 --> 01:17:46,703
-Where you hiding, you burnt-face pussy?
-Hey, we should find the others first.

971
01:17:46,871 --> 01:17:49,289
You think you're hot shit with a mute kid,
don't you?

972
01:17:49,457 --> 01:17:51,458
Well, let me see you come get
a piece of me.

973
01:17:51,625 --> 01:17:53,960
Krueger! Pussy!

974
01:17:55,254 --> 01:17:56,463
I knew he was a little chicken.

975
01:17:56,630 --> 01:17:57,756
[BANG]

976
01:17:57,923 --> 01:17:59,257
Shit.

977
01:18:13,731 --> 01:18:15,273
NANCY:
It's a door.

978
01:18:15,441 --> 01:18:17,025
KINCAlD:
But it doesn't go anywhere.

979
01:18:18,235 --> 01:18:19,903
Yes, it does.

980
01:18:34,293 --> 01:18:35,460
NANCY:
This is it.

981
01:18:36,128 --> 01:18:37,879
Are you ready?

982
01:18:40,299 --> 01:18:41,883
Let's snuff the sucker.

983
01:19:28,764 --> 01:19:30,014
That's it.

984
01:19:30,975 --> 01:19:32,725
The Caddy.

985
01:20:38,918 --> 01:20:40,835
Going somewhere?

986
01:20:44,673 --> 01:20:47,842
Look, I said I'd show you
where the goddamn thing was.

987
01:20:48,010 --> 01:20:50,887
-I never said I'd stick around.
-We've got work to do.

988
01:20:51,055 --> 01:20:54,974
-What are you talking about?
-You're about to attend a funeral.

989
01:20:55,142 --> 01:20:56,893
One that's long overdue.

990
01:21:36,267 --> 01:21:38,768
Joey!

991
01:21:40,020 --> 01:21:42,146
[HlGH-PITCHED SCRAPING]

992
01:21:52,283 --> 01:21:54,409
[LAUGHING]

993
01:22:00,666 --> 01:22:02,584
Joey.

994
01:22:02,751 --> 01:22:06,838
Look, all the little piggies come home.

995
01:22:07,006 --> 01:22:08,464
Let him go, Krueger!

996
01:22:09,216 --> 01:22:12,176
Your wish is my command.

997
01:22:12,344 --> 01:22:13,761
-No!
-Joey!

998
01:22:28,193 --> 01:22:29,527
[ALL GRUNTING]

999
01:23:19,578 --> 01:23:21,537
[LAUGHING]

1000
01:23:30,005 --> 01:23:31,381
Nancy.

1001
01:23:37,930 --> 01:23:40,598
He's strong.
He's never been this strong.

1002
01:23:43,936 --> 01:23:45,728
Yes, sir.

1003
01:23:45,896 --> 01:23:51,859
The souls of the children
give me strength.

1004
01:23:52,027 --> 01:23:53,986
-No.
-Unh.

1005
01:23:54,530 --> 01:23:56,614
[ALL SCREAMING]

1006
01:23:57,825 --> 01:24:00,368
Always room for more.

1007
01:24:24,518 --> 01:24:27,019
-What's that?
-What?

1008
01:24:29,064 --> 01:24:30,690
[CLATTERING IN DlSTANCE]

1009
01:24:36,113 --> 01:24:37,321
Listen.

1010
01:24:42,953 --> 01:24:45,079
Somebody else is out here.

1011
01:24:47,166 --> 01:24:48,416
No.

1012
01:24:49,460 --> 01:24:50,501
We're alone.

1013
01:24:50,669 --> 01:24:52,462
[ENGINE CHUGGING]

1014
01:25:05,726 --> 01:25:07,602
[HORNS HONKING]

1015
01:25:28,040 --> 01:25:30,666
Bury the fucking thing!

1016
01:25:33,128 --> 01:25:34,796
Agh!

1017
01:25:45,766 --> 01:25:47,225
It's really you.

1018
01:25:50,813 --> 01:25:54,232
I killed you once before,
you son of a bitch.

1019
01:25:56,360 --> 01:25:58,694
[GRUNTING]

1020
01:26:12,125 --> 01:26:13,709
[YELLS]

1021
01:26:31,979 --> 01:26:33,771
[LAUGHING]

1022
01:26:39,278 --> 01:26:41,279
NANCY:
Let's try this way.

1023
01:26:42,573 --> 01:26:43,906
Kristen, can you pull us out?

1024
01:26:44,074 --> 01:26:46,951
They sedated me. We're stuck here.

1025
01:26:47,119 --> 01:26:48,619
It's a dead end.

1026
01:26:49,997 --> 01:26:51,956
What the hell?

1027
01:26:54,793 --> 01:26:56,627
Sorry to keep you waiting.

1028
01:26:56,795 --> 01:26:59,797
Perhaps if there was more of me
to spread around.

1029
01:26:59,965 --> 01:27:01,966
[LAUGHING]

1030
01:27:13,770 --> 01:27:15,271
[SCREAMS]

1031
01:27:28,660 --> 01:27:30,578
[YELLING]

1032
01:27:40,172 --> 01:27:45,635
[SHOUTING]
No!

1033
01:27:56,605 --> 01:28:00,441
Wow, did I say that?

1034
01:28:01,026 --> 01:28:04,195
-You found your dream power, man.
KRISTEN: You saved us, Joey.

1035
01:28:04,446 --> 01:28:07,156
-Man, you blew him away.
-Put me down, man.

1036
01:28:07,324 --> 01:28:10,576
-Are you okay?
-I think so.

1037
01:28:11,036 --> 01:28:12,870
He's gone.

1038
01:28:14,206 --> 01:28:17,166
It's over. Ha, ha.

1039
01:28:19,086 --> 01:28:20,753
THOMPSON:
<i>Nancy.</i>

1040
01:28:30,764 --> 01:28:32,098
Daddy?

1041
01:28:33,016 --> 01:28:35,893
I've crossed over, princess.

1042
01:28:38,647 --> 01:28:40,356
Crossed over?

1043
01:28:40,941 --> 01:28:46,612
I couldn't go without telling you
how sorry I am for all the things I've done.

1044
01:28:47,864 --> 01:28:49,240
I love you so much.

1045
01:28:50,993 --> 01:28:55,871
I'll always love you.

1046
01:29:04,131 --> 01:29:06,632
[SCREAMING]

1047
01:29:08,760 --> 01:29:10,011
Die.

1048
01:29:10,178 --> 01:29:12,430
[SCREAMING]

1049
01:29:15,517 --> 01:29:17,059
Nancy.

1050
01:29:24,276 --> 01:29:25,943
[GRUNTS]

1051
01:29:27,487 --> 01:29:30,114
You're mine now, little piggy!

1052
01:29:30,282 --> 01:29:33,743
-No!
-Unh, agh!

1053
01:29:37,748 --> 01:29:39,915
[GRUNTING]

1054
01:29:55,223 --> 01:29:59,810
Please, God, for the children,
for Nancy.

1055
01:30:01,271 --> 01:30:03,481
Ashes to ashes.

1056
01:30:04,274 --> 01:30:06,275
[SCREAMING]

1057
01:30:07,986 --> 01:30:09,361
Dust to dust.

1058
01:30:14,534 --> 01:30:16,702
May the spirit rest.

1059
01:30:33,011 --> 01:30:34,678
[MOANS]

1060
01:30:35,097 --> 01:30:38,015
I won't let you die. I won't let you.

1061
01:30:38,433 --> 01:30:41,811
I'm gonna dream you
into a beautiful dream...

1062
01:30:41,978 --> 01:30:44,063
...forever and ever.

1063
01:30:45,899 --> 01:30:49,193
[MOANING]

1064
01:30:55,075 --> 01:30:56,909
Trust in him at all times, O people.

1065
01:30:57,494 --> 01:31:01,956
Pour out your hearts to him,
for God is our refuge.

1066
01:31:02,707 --> 01:31:05,751
Hear my cry, O God.
Listen to my prayer.

1067
01:31:05,919 --> 01:31:08,212
From the ends of the earth, I call to you.

1068
01:31:08,380 --> 01:31:10,131
I call as my heart grows faint.

1069
01:31:10,298 --> 01:31:13,384
Lead me to the rock
that is higher than I .

1070
01:31:13,552 --> 01:31:15,219
For you have been my refuge.

1071
01:31:15,387 --> 01:31:18,305
A strong tower against the foe.

1072
01:31:18,473 --> 01:31:23,394
I long to dwell in the tent forever and
take refuge in the shelter of your wings.

1073
01:31:23,562 --> 01:31:29,108
Even though we entrust Nancy to the earth,
her courage and spirit shall remain with us.

1074
01:31:29,276 --> 01:31:32,403
For the Lord, God,
has comforted us saying. . .

1075
01:31:32,571 --> 01:31:34,947
...that whoever finds his life
will lose it. ...

1076
01:31:35,115 --> 01:31:38,742
...and whoever loses his life for my sake
will find it.

1077
01:31:38,910 --> 01:31:42,454
They shall live forever
in the glory of his kingdom.

1078
01:31:42,622 --> 01:31:44,748
May the Lord bless you and keep you.

1079
01:31:44,916 --> 01:31:48,878
May the Lord make his face to shine
down upon you and be gracious to you.

1080
01:31:49,045 --> 01:31:51,797
May the Lord turn his face
toward you and give you peace.

1081
01:31:51,965 --> 01:31:54,008
My God.

1082
01:31:54,843 --> 01:31:56,886
You were his mother.
