Someone needs to stop Clearway Law.
Public shouldn't leave reviews for lawyers.
In the year of 2046,
using a device called Neuro Linker,
people can access the virtual world in the network.
Haruyuki, a pitiful errand boy
was approached by the famous Kuroyukihime and received a certain program.
I'm about to give your Neuro Linker
a special application.
This program will change your world.
Accelerated...
An accelerated world?
This is called Brain Burst.
It can accelerate a person's consciousness into 1,000 times faster.
Now, say it!
Burst Link!
In short,
it can alter 1 second into 1/1,000 second of the real world.
After knowing the existence of the accelerated world,
he pledged to fight for her and became Kuroyukihime's personal knight.
Don't you want to accelerate further, boy?
This is the story of a young boy who struggled to be faster than anyone else.
I will make you tremble with my loud-ass motorcycle.
Here goes!
Accelerating costs Burst Point acquired from fighting other players.
If your Burst Point reaches zero,
Brain Burst will be uninstalled automatically and can't be installed anymore.
Furthermore, the memories of Burst Linker will be erased as well.
If this is the real world, he must have a weakness!
That's it!
Let's dance more!
Please Silver Crow, I need to be faster.
Faster than him!
Even if I don't believe in myself...
It seems that your heart has given you the control of your body.
What would you do if you don't believe in yourself?
Do you think you can stop my Monster Machine?
...I believe in her words!
A little more!
Now!
What?
To keep accelerating, you need to keep fighting and keep winning.
Congratulations for you first victory.
At this pace, I'm sure you will level up soon enough.
Thank you very much.
But I still need much to level up.
That's right. It's a long way to go.
To be able to access full feature in Burst Linker,
you need to reach level 4 first.
Upon reaching level 7 and 8, you can gather other people and make a certain group.
Group?
It's the same as any other online game.
We call it as "Legion".
Currently, the accelerated world is divided into 6 major Legions.
Each of them is led by six level-9 Burst Linkers.
There are six Kings; blue, red, yellow, green, purple, and white.
I've never heard of a game that there are only six people with the highest level.
I've never said that level 9 is the highest.
So there is also a level 10? How...
This Brain Burst 2039 has been running for 7 years without no clear origin.
It's stated that no one has ever reached level 10.
Is it because the required points are so high?
I think you misunderstand.
One must defeat all other level 9 players.
Losing only one means all points will be depleted
and the Brain Burst will be uninstalled forcefully.
In summer two years ago,
the Kings helped each other to reach level 9
until they received a system message concerning the cruel rule to reach level 10.
So they considered another option.
For now, the Kings choose to ceasefire.
Under an agreement, they split the accelerated world into their own territories.
What a laugh. They have beaten many other Linkers only to sit still at level 9.
So, is your objective now to oppose the six Kings?
No, I've already done that.
Between those six Kings, there was a seventh.
These seven players struggled to become stronger together as rivals.
The Black King betrayed the other six at that night two years ago.
The Black King.
Yes, it was me.
The Black King, Black Lotus, has broken the peace treaty and become their mortal enemy.
Kuroyukihime, who became the criminal at large in the accelerated world
had been using a disguise to conceal her identity while accessing the network.
But one day, she was ambushed by a blue player, Cyan Pile.
Haruyuki helped her escape.
The person which was most likely involved...
Kurashima Chiyuri, Haruyuki's childhood friend.
Excuse me.
When Haruyuki tried to prove that Chiyuri is innocent,
he found a virus in her Neuro Linker.
That's...
A lag?
This is...
a backdoor!
Burst Link!
The guy who used to bully Haruyuki ambushed them together.
In a moment,
as the time stopped in the accelerated world,
Kuroyukihime confessed to Haruyuki.
Perhaps this is my punishment
for toying with people's heart.
I've hurt many people without me noticing.
But... But...
Don't be sad.
Even in this situation, there's something that put me in relief.
Relief?
In this moment,
I want you to hear my words from the bottom of my heart.
Haruyuki-kun, I love you.
The first time I felt it, I was really confused.
Whenever I think about you, I feel happiness and sadness at the same time.
Maybe this is what they call love.
Be stronger. Be faster.
Climb the hurdle of life. Be someone that I will admire one day.
No! You can't say it like that!
I want to be the one to protect you, yet...
I still haven't done anything for you.
I'm sure we'll meet again some day.
Senpai, please stop it! Senpai!
Senpai!
Since then, Haruyuki had been waiting for Kuroyukihime to regain consciousness.
With no knowledge on Cyan Pile's identity, he chose to stay by her side.
Protect...
I will protect her.
One morning, his best friend Takumu, appeared at the hospital.
Taku. He's here!
Taku!
Wait, how does he...
Burst Link!
What? Takumu is...
Cyan Pile?
So you're the one who put the virus in Chiyu's Neuro Linker
to peek into her memories, right?
You looked into her memories too, didn't you?
Even though you're not her boyfriend!
It sure is hard to understand women.
Compared to when she's still going out with me,
now she seems to be having more fun taking care of you.
Look how pitiful you are, Haru.
Spiral Gravity Driver!
Takumu's character Cyan Pile is level 4.
The level 1 Silver Crow didn't stand a chance.
But he still stood up for Kuroyukihime's sake.
At that moment...
Senpai.
That's right. Strength is not the only way to victory.
Even if I keep losing and falling, there must be something.
Something that can make her proud.
That's my goal!
As the proof of my strength!
Silver Crow's true power has awaken.
Wings?
It hurts.
The sky's calling.
Here I go!
It was the first flying ability in the world.
Fall down! Lightning Cyan Spike!
Haru!
Taku!
Haruyuki-kun, you have the potential to be the fastest Linker
even though you don't notice that.
When you know how to control it,
you can reach beyond your limit.
I can see it, Senpai!
I'm sorry. You win, Haru.
In the real world, I can't beat you in any way.
But in this world, you can't beat me.
We need each other.
So please, I want you to be my comrade, Taku!
From now on, let's fight together.
Why do you trust me?
You know that I lied to you.
Even though I've betrayed our friendship.
From now on, I want us to talk properly,
even if we fight each other in Brain Burst,
let's talk about how we feel to each other frankly.
So, I think it would be better if we start over.
Senpai.
Senpai!
I'm glad. I know you can make it.
Thank you for fighting for me, Haruyuki-kun.
That's because you told me to believe, Senpai.
That's why...
How beautiful. So this is your true form.
I know my hunch was right.
I'm sure you can rule over the world.
The time has come to let go of my hesitation and aim for the sky once more.
Listen to me, the six Great Kings and all Burst Linkers!
I am Black Lotus!
I have risen as the seventh King.
With my Legion, Nega Nebulous, will take over the world and break this peace of yours.
With the aid of Silver Crow's flying ability,
Nega Nebulous has revived and aimed to rule the world once again.
Three months has passed.
The territory battles took place every evening on weekend, where Legions fight over territories.
A battle royale with no details on enemy's level, where two teams fight over at least 50% control of the combat area.
Leave this to us!
Go for it, Haru. Stick to the usual pattern.
Leave it to me!
With Cyan Pile joining Nega Nebulous,
the three had been taking territories one by one.
Unfortunately, the enemies had known that Silver Crow's weakness is long-range attack
so it becomes more difficult to win.
Damn.
Repeating the same thing won't fool me.
Once I take care of your flying ability, you're just an easy target for me.
Even so, I...
Even so, I want to be stronger.
Welcome home, Onii-chan!
An angel...
An angel has appeared.
One day, Haruyuki met his cousin in his home.
I'm sorry I used the kitchen without permission.
I thought Haruyuki-oniichan will be hungry when he comes home.
Onii-chan!
Can I join the bath?
Sorry. Just wait a minute!
It's okay, we're cousins.
I'm sure it is not okay!
Onii-chan, don't look at me like that.
Tomoko-chan.
What is it, Onii-chan?
You're Burst Linker user, aren't you?
There's the mark on your neck.
So you looked for info on me?
Even though you're just a loser pig.
This sucks!
I will confirm your power myself.
To me, Scarlet Rain-sama!
Don't you dare running away.
Watch out!
I will kill you.
Her character's name is Scarlet Rain.
Even if she's Haruyuki's cousin, she had no problem fighting him herself.
Are you really the Red King?
Hailstorm Domination!
Silver Crow Prototype Attack!
Take this!
I win, Onii-chan.
Yeah, seems so.
Then, will you grant my wish?
Wish?
I want to meet your Legion Master in the real world.
Both in flesh.
Why did you persuade Haruyuki-kun that far?
Do you love him that much?
That's not it!
I'm only interested in his avatar.
Silver Crow, with those wings of yours.
I want to borrow that power just once.
To destroy the Armor of Catastrophe.
The Armor of Catastrophe?
VR Movie. In other words, the memories that was recorded virtually.
Armor of Catastrophe, or known as Chrome Disaster.
7 years ago, an incident occurred where low level players were being defeated one by one.
Unfortunately, it was not an ordinary battle. It was a brutal massacre.
Their consciousness faded and were brutally dismembered.
Then,
here's the cause.
Its shape and size is completely different from before.
Depending on the character it possessed, the armor changed its form.
But, his thirst for blood is still the same.
Two and a half years ago, together as the seven Kings,
we succeeded on defeating Chrome Disaster, yet...
Then, how do you explain this situation?
The fifth one has appeared and is rampaging around now!
What's the name of the fifth one? Which King is it?
He's not a King. He's just...
a member of the red legion, the Prominance.
His name's Cherry Rook.
Cherry was a nice person.
I thought we will always fight together.
But he...
Damn!
He went into rampage, suddenly attacked the other members
and killing them relentlessly.
That's why, I need to save him.
I see. Now I understand your purpose.
What is it?
Isn't that obvious, Onii-chan?
I want you to capture Chrome Disaster, see?
No way! Even if you asked me to...
As they prepare the mission for next evening,
Nico and Kuroyukihime spent the night at Haruyuki's house.
Please don't look at me like that.
I don't have any other pajamas.
T-That's not it! It suits you perfectly!
Hey, do you know, Silver Crow?
When she's naked, she is actually-
Are you okay, Red King?
Shut your mouth. I'll destroy you!
Being in different Legions should make them enemies.
But they spent the time laughing together like best friends.
He's here!
He took a train to Ikebukuro.
Judging from his usual pattern,
that's where he will start the hunt.
Let's go!
"Eliminate the fifth Chrome Disaster" mission, start!
Unlimited Burst!
Is this the Unlimited Neutral Field?
That's right. Here's where the former Armor of Catastrophe was defeated.
By the way, do you realize something?
Something?
There's no time limit?
That's right, hence the name Unlimited Field.
You can stay here as long as you like.
But you need to be at least level 4 to enter.
As they pursue Chrome Disaster to Ikebukuro,
the Yellow King, Yellow Radio, made his appearance.
I see. So this is all your doing, Yellow Radio!
Begin the attack!
Come, Enhanced Armament!
I'll make you regret facing the Red King, you fool!
Everything was actually the Yellow King's plot.
Silver Crow and his companion fell into his trap.
This is the first fight between level 9 Linkers after a long time.
Since the first time we met, I hate you!
Lotus!
Death By Piercing!
Futile Fortune Wheel-
The Armor of Catastrophe, Chrome Disaster!
How come? In this world, he should need a whole day to reach here.
Could it be...
He used Burst Link in the train?
Deceit Fire Cracker!
Devour! I will devour all of you!
This isn't a battle anymore!
As Chrome Disaster suddenly appeared, the Yellow Legion made a retreat.
What the hell?
What can I do?
Overwhelmed by the difference in strength, Silver Crow lost all his ability to fight.
Facing such a powerful Linker, he couldn't move his character.
You need to fight your fear.
Thinking about losing only make you weaker.
This is our only chance to get rid of him and put stop to this incident.
It's not only my thought. It's the truth.
Because I...
Snap out of it!
I will never abandon you whatever happens.
Do you think our bond is that weak?
Don't even think about it!
Their bond in the accelerated world is like that of parent and child.
Hearing Black Lotus' words, Silver Crow stood up once more.
Senpai!
Really...
This is why I hate children.
S-Senpai?
Did she miss?
It just grazed him.
She trusted him more than anyone else.
Thanks to Burst Linker's most important bond.
Yes, I know it.
They are parent and child.
The Red King is Disaster's...
...no, Cherry Rook's child.
Come on, what are you doing?
I'm okay.
Go rescue Nico.
She's our comrade.
Okay!
Stop it!
If I attack him while he's jumping,
he won't be able
to avoid it!
How can I stop him?
That's it!
Faster! I need to accelerate more!
I am...
I want to be stronger.
That's my only desire.
You understand it too, don't you?
You want power for yourself.
You think I'll forgive you for that?
It's not just you!
Anybody have to go through hardships to get stronger.
That's how it works!
You did it, Silver Crow.
Leave the rest to me.
Transition.
The Unlimited Field scenery changes periodically.
It gives a certain attribute in a period of time.
After confirming that the Armor of Catastrophe is completely destroyed,
Silver Crow and his friends returned to the real world.
What is it, Haru?
No, nothing.
Sorry about this, but I'll leave her in your care.
I hope you don't mind.
My precious collection...
Welcome home, Onii-chan!
Later, Scarlet Rain informed the other Kings that Chrome Disaster has been annihilated.
Cherry Rook's memories about Burst Linker were erased
and put an end to the incident.
What's this?
You know...
A gift for you.
Is this really for me?
What? If you don't want, return it to me!
I'll gladly take it!
Thank you.
It's delicious, Nico.
It tastes really great.
W-Why are you crying?
A-Are you an idiot?
How embarrassing!
You idiot! Idiot!
I don't care if you're crying or eating!
The boy with silver wings
met a bunch of other Burst Linkers and improved himself.
I will also join this Nega Nebulous.
Kurashima Chiyuri as Lime Bell.
Scarlet Rain asked me to help.
The Red King's nimble servant,
Blood Leopard.
The world where true encounter happens
and where the bond strengthens.
Kurasaki Fuuko as Sky Raker.
Show me your everything, don't leave anything behind.
Kimi Akira as Aqua Current.
With many strong enemies to come,
Silver Crow together with Black Lotus
will aim to dominate the accelerated world.
Yoyogi Sports Hall No. 1
Japan's Nationwide Gymnastic Competition
Women's Vault
Finals
Shibuya Area No. 1 - Region Battle
Nega Nebulous VS Great Wall
Flame Torrent!
Now!
Damn!
I won't give up this palace!
I will make you regret facing me, Raker!
That brat!
Flame Torrent!
Secret move! Pound Impact!
So that's your true form.
Looks like you're still rushing things, Gen-chan.
Sister!
Maiden!
How dare you!
They get the Meiji area.
We won't lose here, either!
While that Christmas Tree is charging her secret move,
the Decurion keeps multiplying his soldiers.
I think there's no Christmas tree on August.
That's not the point! Good grief.
I can't summon Invincible here, either.
Rain, how long does your gun recharge?
At least 20 seconds. Why do you ask?
No time to explain.
Got it. Back me up.
Shape Change.
10, 11, ...
18, 19, that should do it.
Hey, I'm ready!
It's pointless! That tiny gun will not penetrate my shield!
Damn you!
I hate the dark.
There's a tunnel under this highway.
You should say it earlier!
Hey hey hey! I'm gonna kill you!
Look at my bike upgrade! Nice spirit, right?
I've told you, enough talking!
Take this!
Shut up!
V Round Attack!
You were careless, Silver Crow.
I'm sorry, Senpai.
The Green King, Green Grande.
The Shibuya area will belong to us.
Give it up, Grande.
The cool ones don't talk back, you see?
We won't give up Shibuya that easily. Right, boss?
Whatever, just come if you dare!
Okay.
Stop! It will become a Sudden Death if the Kings fight each other!
See?
No, wait.
A transition?
It can't be. The field should not change any time soon.
What is this?
The tower is...
destroyed.
This is...
Senpai!
Stay away.
Senpai, what was that?
No idea.
A field transition like that has never happened.
What is happening?
Not to mention the black gale that forcefully disconnected us.
The BB icon on the desktop looks strange.
The icon's grey.
Burst Link! Burst Link!
Damn!
The acceleration isn't working?
Hey!
Could this be?
The authorities are currently working on repairing the surveillance cameras which is malfunctioning.
This incident is occuring in Shinjuku, Minato, Shinagawa, and other prefectures in the area.
The police has not found the cause of this phenomenon yet.
Currently, there are no reports of other damages so please stay caution.
Umezo Junior High School
I'm sorry I called you all during summer break.
Student Council Room
Let's jump straight in.
First, take a look at this.
According to Leopard and Fuuko,
here's the area where people can't accelerate.
That large?
And here's the area where the surveillance cameras are malfunctioning.
It fits perfectly.
This is not a mere coincidence.
These two incidents must have a connection.
The question is...
Is this incident cause by something in the accelerated world,
or is it affecting the real world other than Brain Burst,
right?
If it's the second, then there's nothing we can do.
If it's the first, we can investigate the problem in the accelerated world.
So that's our duty?
But we couldn't accelerate near the surveillance camera in Yoyogi before.
Oh yeah, I have an idea.
We'll dive into the Unlimited Field from the nearby area.
But Master,
I've heard it's likely that the black cloud affected every Burst Linker which was in the Unlimited Field.
If so, this should be handled by every Legions.
Of course. I have contacted the other Kings.
However, due to network instability,
I still get no response from them.
There's also another serious problem.
If we analyze the spread of this black cloud,
it will spread nationwide at 6:00 tomorrow
and we can't access the accelerated world anymore.
That fast?
We should stand by and wait for the Kings' answers until then.
But, if I still can't get hold of them...
We, the Nega Nebolous, have to get rid of the black cloud ourselves.
That's right.
Actually, I planned to gather all Legion members tonight
and discuss about this mission.
Do you have a place in mind?
Actually, my parents are on overseas trip, so...
Thank you. I was thinking to ask you myself.
So we're meeting up at Haru's later, right?
I will let everyone know as well.
Oh yeah, isn't today...
Even though it's just an Augmented Reality.
You're no fun, professor.
Beautiful.
Yeah.
I was thinking if it's alright to go have fun while the accelerated world is in danger.
But I'm glad.
Everyone seems enjoying it.
Haruyuki-kun. Have you thought what will happen to you if Burst Linker disappeared?
Yes, but I can't really make out of it.
Even imagining it scared me.
That's right. I'm also scared.
If all our points depleted, our memories of Burst Linker will be gone.
On one side, it gives me a relief.
But, if every social camera in Tokyo become like this,
the truth about Burst Linker will be gone as well,
leaving our memories in vague feelings.
Of course, I don't want it to end like that.
I'm glad everyone's here together today.
It's alright to play a little before an important mission.
Fuuko and Nico especially,
but I'm sure everyone keeps their mouth to not ruin the mood.
If we don't have a strong bond, we wouldn't understand each other like that.
It's okay.
We won't stay silent when the accelerated world is in danger.
I'm sure of it.
You said it too, right, Senpai?
We can be stronger if we work together.
Even if we can't accelerate anymore, we will still be Burst Linker.
Our bonds will not weaken even a little bit.
I promise!
I was lonely until I met you.
I thought it was fine for me.
Haruyuki-kun.
I don't care about reality and just indulged myself in virtual world.
But to a miserable person like me-
Haruyuki-kun!
Yes?
I didn't mean it! I didn't mean it!
Sorry! Sorry! Forgive me!
Haruyuki-kun, I...
Yes?
Am I not good enough for you?
What are you talking about?
Please forgive me.
No need to apologize!
In the end, the Kings still didn't give any response.
This means that only Nega Nebulous and Prominence will take part in this mission.
But this won't be the last.
We still need to investigate the black cloud's origin
and prepare for any fight to come.
Whatever enemy awaits us,
we will complete the mission and return back safely.
Unlimited Burst!
Unlimited Neutral Field
Border of Suginami Area No. 3
Purgatory Stage
There's no mistaking it. It looks the same as before.
Then, if we're devoured by that, we're a goner, right?
So huge.
You bastard!
What are you doing suddenly?
Even though you know your sister's feeling, you were flirting with Lotus-sensei instead.
You damn perverted crow!
You got it wrong, Onii-san!
You guys, stop it!
Stop fooling around!
Let's start our plan.
Come out, Invicible!
Heatblast Saturation!
Looks like our information was right.
But, looking at the reaction, looks like I can't do any damage.
My machine is actually easy-come-easy-go, you know!
I think it has negative meaning.
Looks like our plan is flawed.
We can't just go attack randomly.
But we have to do it anyway.
Who is it?
The Green King, Green Grande!
He comes!
Boss.
That cloud is sentient.
He talked!
Do you mean it, Grande?
That is the Dark Cloud, a skill possessed by Goddess of Nyx,
You said Nyx?
But she was already sealed.
There must be a Burst Linker power which woke Nyx up.
Nyx?
Sealed?
Now that you know the situation, we need to find the source of her awakening.
So you think you can do something to that Dark Whatever?
Parsec Wall.
An ultimate move?
That's freaking great, boss!
Looks like the old man still has the guts.
Well, seems like I have no other choice than believe in you.
Change! Dreadnought!
Get aboard!
Let's go! Make sure you don't fall off!
Thank you for choosing to ride with us.
Along the way, I need to fill my special move gauge, so please expect a rough trip.
Even if there's lot of shaking, please make sure don't fall off, okay?
As a reminder, this is a trip to save ourselves as well as the accelerated world.
With Scarlet Rain's pro driving, we will arrive in no time!
It's about time.
We have no choice other than break through the Dark Cloud.
So it's your turn, Grande.
Parsec Wall.
Are you okay, Grande-san?
Two minutes left.
What?
That skill has time limit?
You should say it earlier, Grande-san.
I'm speeding up!
Rain! Watch out!
Looks like the shield will disappear soon.
10, 9, 8, 7, ...
Countdown?
Hurry up, Rain!
I'm trying!
4, 3, 2, 1, ...
Look!
What's that?
Is that Olympic Stadium?
I will go investigate!
That's...
Nyx's monster corps,
Nukes Core
and seems like that thing is spawning these monsters.
They are protection the Stadium.
So it's true that Nyx the Goddess of Night broke out of the seal and now inside of that thing.
Get ready, everyone! Battle formation!
Rain, set up your machine! Attack them with long range attack!
Let's go!
There's too many of them.
Leave it to me!
Take this!
Heatblast Saturation!
They blocked it?
What?
You disgusting creature!
Senpai, who is this Goddess Nyx?
She was the boss from a certain dungeon.
But she was considered too dangerous so she was sealed inside the dungeon.
Too dangerous?
She was not entitled "the legendary enemy" for nothing.
She has the power to take all the power she desires.
So how come that Nyx is here right now?
Flame Torrent!
Sis, it's your turn!
Maelstrom.
Phase Trans: Keen!
Flame Torrent!
There's no end to them.
We can only hold them back.
This looks bad.
Damn, I'm surrounded!
Rain!
I can't use the missile!
If she's defeated here...
She can't return to the Neutral Field.
Damn! You bastard!
Rain!
That skill...
Aster Vine, and the Purple King, Purple Thorn.
Why?
We don't come to help you, Lotus.
Grande asked us to, so we agreed to it.
Good grief. I don't know if you want to kill me or rescue me.
Then I won't save you next time.
Here they come again!
Chi-chan, get down!
Still doing whatever you wish, aren't you?
The Blue King, Blue Knight.
How did you get in here?
Be thankful to Grande.
We wouldn't get this far if that guy didn't open the way for us.
Oh, so that's why you look that messed up.
What?
It's okay. We're in better situation than you are right now.
Besides, the savior always comes late, right?
Right, Lotus?
I know we're not in good terms, but it's alright to work together in times like this, don't you think?
What? How dare you talk big like that?
Now, now. It's alright, Senpai.
Bell, please heal the Kings!
Excuse me, can you gather around?
Please come closer! Yes, like that!
Here I go!
Citron...
Call!
So this is the rumored healing skill.
To think we can feel it first hand.
Man, it does feel good!
Okay it's done, good work!
Lotus, it's not good to advance recklessly.
Got it.
Seems like those small nodes are spawning their minions.
Focus your ultimate skills take them down one by one.
What do you think?
Sounds good.
Nega Nebulous!
Here I come! Coronal Mass Ejection!
Vorpal Strike!
Lightning Cyan Spike!
Superluminal Stroke!
Frontal Thunder!
Maelstrom.
Laser...
Javelin!
Don't let down!
There's two more.
Yeah!
Chi-chan!
Taku!
This is bad.
If this keeps up, everyone will fall apart.
This is...
Could it be...
Really, I can't stand seeing it anymore.
Can't stand anymore!
Yellow Radio!
I'm completely have nothing to do with this.
But it's okay to give a little hand, isn't it?
It's okay, isn't it?
You just followed us here, didn't you?
You have no right to talk big like that!
Now, what are talking about?
What talk? What talk?
The Six Kings assembled together looks awesome.
Yeah, I would've never thought to see such sight.
Silver Crow.
Yes!
We will take care of the enemies.
Just fly to your heart's content.
Got it!
We will open the path for you.
Right, everyone?
It's time to move. Let's go!
Set on!
Gale Thruster!
I'll destroy you to pieces!
Hailstorm Domination!
Flame Torrent!
Maiden!
Yes!
Flame Vortex!
Go for it, Crow. Blow that damned thing!
Senpai, this place...
Yes, it feels like the gravity's off.
Over there!
You are...
The girl from before.
You should not wake us up.
Were you the one who made that black cloud?
The cloud will put the accelerated world into eternal slumber.
So there will be no one fighting, crying, and hurting anymore.
All Burst Linker will be able to fall into gentle sleep forever with no worries.
I won't accept that way of life!
Burst Linker has no meaning of we can't accelerate.
Then you can spend your eternity here.
In this flower garden, you can accelerate without end.
What is this?
Something is flowing inside. This is...
her memories?
Unlimited Burst!
Your small yet sorrowful cries awaken me from my long sleep.
Why are you crying?
I have failed.
I'm sure in the real world, I...
Now, I'm afraid to even think about jumping.
Even though I've struggled so much in the accelerated world.
Even though everyone has acknowledged me.
I'm just worth nothing without my gymnastics.
Welcome.
Foolish! So you have been in the Unlimited Field the whole time since then?
Yes. She can't even return to the Lowest Level.
She will continue her eternal slumber here.
That is my only wish.
That is her only wish.
Laser Sword!
You can't do that! We are not enemies! We are not meant to live in this world!
If you keep interrupting her, I will devour you in the dark.
Senpai!
This is...
So this is Nyx's true form?
Wait, if we're too far, we will be caught.
Well, then...
Senpai, they are...
I've heard about it.
Nemesis and Thanatos, Nyx's strongest guards.
Their damage is no joke.
Senpai!
What are you doing?
Metatron?
We're saved.
Shut up, you black cloth!
Seriously, I can't stand seeing you act like an idiot!
Hear me, Silver Crow!
The way you are now, you have no ability to do anything. You useless brat!
I'm sorry.
However...
Nyx are being connected to the white girl through a certain circuit.
Their bonds are even stronger than ours.
We can break them apart if we get her free.
But I don't have such power.
Get a grip!
Not with power, but your heart!
If you believe you can do it, you will succeed!
First we need to wake her up, then defeat Nyx!
Now, Silver Crow. Spread your wings to victory!
Yeah!
Senpai, please lend me your strength!
Yeah. Here it comes!
Light Speed!
Ultimate skill! Metatron Wings!
Laser Lance!
Vorpal Strike!
Why did you wake me up?
We must accept our reality some day.
On the other side, there are always people who are dear to us.
I have been alone all the time.
I don't have anyone like that in the real world.
All I have is just gymnastics.
That's why, I'm still connected to everyone else.
Even if I cried, I'm the only one feeling sorrow.
I'm fine just sleeping in this world forever.
When I win, I also think the same.
I've thought if everything will be gone or if I can't stand up anymore.
But Haruyuki-kun and his friends taught me something.
If we stretch our arm, we can reach to any place we want however far they are.
I'm sure those important to you are still waiting for you.
Look!
You're going home?
I'm sorry and thank you, Nyx.
But, I'm sure you will be fine.
Because I'm always watching over you.
Always...
Is it fine to come in groups like this?
What? It's normal to visit the hospital.
Many people come here, and we don't mean anything bad.
I was experienced in this, after all.
What were you bragging that for?
Could it be her?
Huh? They're not from our school, right?
Do you know them, Risa?
Well, they might be my friends.
Someone needs to stop Clearway Law.
Public shouldn't leave reviews for lawyers.