[BIRDS CHIRPING]
[GULL CAWING]
Man: MORNING, RICH!
[BELL TOLLING]
HA HA!
Boy:
COME ON, BUDDY.
WE'VE GOT
TO PRACTICE.
[WOOF]
GOOD BOY.
NOAH, HE DOESN'T
HAVE MUCH TIME.
REMEMBER, IT'S ANDREA'S
LAST DAY OF SCHOOL.
SHE'LL BE EXPECTING HIM.
WE'LL BE FAST.
[WOOF]
OK, BUDDY.
YOU READY?
[WOOF]
REMEMBER,
GO FAST AS YOU CAN.
AND GO.
[CREAK]
STOP.
ISN'T HE GOOD, MOM?
16 SECONDS.
HO HO!
I THINK WE SHOULD
GIVE HIM AN ICE CREAM.
Mom: OH,
YOU DO, HUH?
WELL, MAYBE
AFTER DINNER,
BUT ANDREA
NEEDS BUDDY
TO PICK HER UP
AT SCHOOL.
HE BETTER GO.
Man:
I TOLD YOU, GORDON.
THIS ROAD TAKES US
STRAIGHT TO FERNFIELD.
Gordon:
I DON'T KNOW, DOUG.
I THINK WE'RE LOST.
THERE IT IS--
"WELCOME TO FERNFIELD."
HOO HOO HOO!
HA HA!
[PLAYING HARMONICA]
Boy: I'LL JUST
TAKE IT OUT BACK.
Different boy:
OK. I GOT IT.
Woman: HI, MEGAN.
[POWER TOOL GRINDS]
[WOOF WOOF]
OH, LOOK. IT'S BUDDY.
[WOOF]
HEY, HEY, BUDDY!
HEY, BUDDY!
Doug: TAKE A RIGHT.
IT'LL LEAD US
RIGHT TO THE MUSEUM.
WATCH OUT FOR THAT MUTT!
[TIRES SCREECH]
[RRR WOOF]
SO REMEMBER, GORDON,
WE'RE PRETENDING
TO BE PLUMBERS.
WE GOT THE TRUCK.
WE GOT THE UNIFORMS.
THEY'LL TOTALLY
FALL FOR IT,
AND AS SOON AS THEIR
BACKS ARE TURNED,
THE JEWEL
WILL BE OURS.
YOU ARE SO GOOD.
[SCHOOL BELL RINGING]
[WOOF]
[CHEERING]
Boy: YEAH!
Different boy:
GUYS, WAIT UP!
HAVE A GREAT SUMMER.
WE'LL SEE EVERYBODY HERE
BACK NEXT SEPTEMBER.
OK. OK.
I'M ALL RIGHT. AAH!
THE LAST DAY
OF JUNIOR HIGH
IS SUPPOSED
TO FEEL GOOD.
WHY DO YOU
HAVE TO MOVE?
I DON'T EVEN WANT
TO THINK ABOUT IT.
OH, HO HO HO!
[BUDDY BARKING]
HEY, THERE'S BUDDY.
HEY, BUDDY.
COME ON.
Woman: OH, HO HO HO!
Man: WHAT A FLUKE THAT YOU
TWO PLUMBERS JUST SHOWED UP.
IT'S LIKE YOU HAD
ESP OR SOMETHING.
I WAS JUST ABOUT
TO CALL THE BOYS
AT FERNFIELD PLUMBING.
YOU GUYS NEW IN TOWN?
IT'S STARTING TO SMELL
REALLY BAD IN THERE.
OF COURSE, YOU GUYS
ARE USED TO THIS, I'M SURE,
BUT WITH THE JEWEL
ARRIVING AND WHATNOT,
WE CAN'T HAVE
JOHN Q. PUBLIC
SMELLING LIKE...
OH!
[FLIES BUZZING]
[SQUISHING]
UHH.
UH...UGH.
I MAY HAVE CONTRIBUTED
A LITTLE.
Man on radio:
COME IN, PHIL.
THE JEWEL E.T.A.
IS ONE MINUTE. OVER.
I'M SORRY, GUYS. I'M GONNA
HAVE TO LEAVE YOU TO IT.
THAT'S NO PROBLEM.
WE'RE FINE. HEH!
EW! HOO HOO HOO!
Phil: JUST GOT
OFF OF ONE-NINER.
I'M RUNNING STRAIGHT
FOR THE ADMINISTRATOR DOOR,
AND NOW I'M TAKING A LEFT.
OK. GET READY.
[SIREN]
Girl: I CAN'T BELIEVE
THE JEWEL OF ETERNITY
CAME HERE.
Other girl: TOO BAD
YOU'RE GONNA
MISS THE EXHIBIT.
I'M REALLY GONNA
MISS FERNFIELD.
MAYBE A POPSICLE
WILL CHEER US UP?
MM-HMM.
AH.
[BOTH INHALE]
AS SOON AS THEY LEAVE,
WE'LL JUST GRAB IT.
[GASP]
OHH.
[BEEPING]
Phil: WHAT A BEAUTY.
AHHHH.
OHH.
DO YOU WANT TO,
FOR OLD TIMES' SAKE?
LAST ONE IN'S
A ROTTEN EGG.
I DON'T REALLY
FEEL LIKE IT.
COME ON.
IT'S OUR LAST CHANCE.
WELL...NO...I...
HA HA HA!
TAMMY!
[WOOF WOOF]
WAIT UP!
WHOO WHOO!
[LAUGHTER]
[WOOF]
AAH!
Girl: BUDDY!
[LAUGHTER]
BUDDY.
[CREAK]
UH!
[SQUISHING]
UHHH.
UH!
HUH!
OH, MY--
WHY ME?
[WHINES]
[SOBBING]
IT'S OK. IT'S OK.
[WHIMPERS]
Doug: GORDON, LOOK.
HUH?
THE VENT.
OH.
[STRAINING]
UH!
Doug: IT LEADS
RIGHT TO THE JEWEL.
THAT'S A GOOD
IDEA, DOUG,
BUT I DON'T THINK
ANY OF US
ARE GONNA FIT
IN THIS VENT.
WELL, WE HAVE TO FIND
SOMEONE WHO CAN.
[POWER TOOL GRINDING]
Girl:
I CAN'T BELIEVE
YOU HAVE TO MISS
THE FAIR TOMORROW.
WE ALWAYS
GO TOGETHER.
DON'T REMIND ME.
[BUDDY BARKING]
BUDDY, WAIT UP!
[WOOF]
[BOTH LAUGHING]
YOU WIN, BUDDY.
Man: ALL RIGHT.
A COUPLE MORE LOADS AFTER THIS,
AND WE'RE OUT OF HERE.
Mom: ANDREA.
OH, YOU GUYS ARE HERE.
TAMMY, YOUR MOM WAS JUST HERE
LOOKING FOR YOU.
SHE NEEDS YOU HOME
TO HELP FINISH PACKING.
I'LL SET UP
THE TENT.
Tammy:
I MADE THIS FOR YOU.
TAMMY,
IT'S BEAUTIFUL.
OPEN IT.
IT'S THE FIRST BALL
YOU EVER HAD AT THE PARK,
REMEMBER?
WE SPENT A WHOLE HOUR
LOOKING FOR IT
AFTER WE WON.
YEAH. WHEN DID WE WIN
AFTER THAT GAME?
TAMMY, THANKS.
YOU'RE WELCOME.
THAT'S SO YOU
DON'T FORGET ME.
FORGET YOU?
YOU'VE BEEN MY
BEST FRIEND FOREVER.
[SNIFFLES]
WILL YOU COME BACK
FOR MY WEDDING?
YOU'RE GETTING MARRIED?
I GOT THESE
FOR YOU...
OH.
SO THAT YOU'LL
REMEMBER TO WRITE.
OF COURSE I'LL WRITE.
WILL YOU PROMISE TO
COME BACK AND VISIT?
WELL, I WAS THINKING
MAYBE YOU COULD
COME STAY WITH ME
IN SAN DIEGO?
YOU MEAN IT?
WELL, I COULD ASK.
THAT WOULD
BE FANTASTIC.
AAH!
HA HA HA!
THANKS, BUDDY.
Mom: LIGHTS OUT, GIRLS.
[LAUGHTER]
♪ DOO OOH DOO DOO ♪
♪ DOO DOO DOO
DOO DOO DOO DOO ♪
OHH.
NOAH, WE'RE
STILL SLEEPING.
BUT I NEED BUDDY.
WE'VE GOT
TO PRACTICE.
IT'S TODAY.
[WOOF]
GOOD BOY.
OH, I THOUGHT I HEARD
YOUR VOICE, ANDREA.
I'M GLAD
YOU GIRLS ARE UP.
IT'S TIME WE WERE
HEADING OUT.
OHH.
AWW.
I'LL SEND YOU A POSTCARD
AS SOON AS I GET THERE,
AND I PROMISE
I'LL ASK
ABOUT YOU COMING
RIGHT AWAY.
Woman:
♪ SAYING GOOD-BYE... ♪
OK.
♪ AS HARD AS I TRY ♪
♪ JUST ISN'T EASY... ♪
BYE, TAMMY.
SEE YOU.
♪ WHEREVER YOU GO ♪
♪ I WANT YOU TO KNOW ♪
♪ YOU'RE NEVER
TOO FAR FROM ME... ♪
I'LL MISS YOU,
TOO, BUDDY.
♪ I HEAR THE SILENCE
OF THE DISTANCE BETWEEN... ♪
BYE.
Woman: TAMMY?
♪ ARRIVE WITHOUT REASON ♪
♪ NONE OF THIS MATTERS TO ME ♪
♪ 'CAUSE WE SHARE
THE SAME MOONBEAMS ♪
♪ THAT DANCE THROUGH THE SKY ♪
♪ WE SHARE THE SAME DREAMS,
WE SHARE ALL OUR LIVES ♪
♪ WE SHARE IT ALL ♪
♪ YOU AND I ♪
[CALLIOPE MUSIC PLAYING]
THE SHERIFF.
GOOD DAY FOR
A RACE, RIGHT?
Doug: QUICK.
DUCK IN HERE.
BUT WE HAVEN'T DONE
ANYTHING WRONG YET, DOUG.
OOH!
UGH!
Man on P.A.:
NOW IT'S TIME
FOR THE HIGHLIGHT
OF THE AFTERNOON--
THE ANNUAL CANINE
OBSTACLE COURSE.
THIS EVENT
IS GENEROUSLY SUPPORTED
BY TILLY'S DAIRY BAR
AND WILL, AS IS CUSTOM,
BE COMMENTATED ON
BY ITS EVER-POPULAR OWNER
NORBERT TILLY.
[LAUGHING]
[HUMMING]
Woman: IT'S OK.
OH!
[CRYING]
UH-UH.
I THINK
IT'S OUR TURN.
Boy: ALL RIGHT, BUDDY!
Tilly: AND THE NEXT DOG UP
IS BUDDY FRAMM,
COACHED BY NOAH FRAMM.
HE'LL BE RACING
AGAINST LAST YEAR'S CHAMPION--
BILLY THE BORDER COLLIE.
ALL RIGHT.
OWNERS...
UNLEASH YOUR DOGS.
YOU READY?
[RRR]
ON YOUR MARK...
Man:
GOOD LUCK, BUDDY!
GET SET...
GO!
[CROWD CHEERING]
AND THEY'RE OFF!
Noah: GO, BUDDY.
[WOOF]
YOU CAN DO IT.
FASTER. FASTER.
Tilly:  HA HA HA!
LOOK AT THEM GO!
COME ON, BUDDY.
[CROWD MOANS]
HA HA HA!
[CROWD CHEERING AND APPLAUDING]
DID YOU SEE
THE WAY HE WENT
THROUGH THAT TUNNEL
AND UNDER THOSE HURDLES?
Doug: THAT DOG MAY BE
THE KEY TO GETTING
THAT JEWEL.
Both: WE GOT TO GET THAT DOG.
YOUR RIBBONS.
YOUR TROPHY.
HA HA HA!
[WHIMPERS]
Tilly:
THE GRAND PRIZE--
A SUMMER'S WORTH OF
FREE-ICE-CREAM COUPONS
FROM MY
ICE CREAM SHOP,
TILLY'S DAIRY BAR.
DID YOU HEAR THAT,
BUDDY?
A SUMMER OF
FREE ICE CREAM.
[WOOF]
Man: DID YOU SEE
MOMMY AND DADDY
AND YOUR SISTER
WAVING AT YOU SAYING,
"RUN, NOAH, RUN"?
YOU KNOW WHY
YOU CAME IN FIRST.
I THINK YOU NEED
A NICE, COLD
GLASS
OF LEMONADE.
[WOOF WOOF]
BUDDY, I DON'T
FEEL LIKE PLAYING.
MAYBE LATER.
[WHIMPERS]
[GULLS CAWING]
[SNIFFLES]
[MAN WHISTLING]
HEY, BUDDY.
THERE'S SOMETHING IN HERE
FROM CALIFORNIA FOR ANDREA.
THANKS, BUDDY.
[WOOF]
YES! HA HA!
MORNING, MOM.
MORNING, HONEY.
Andrea: HOW ARE
WE ALL DOING TODAY?
ARE YOU ALL READY
FOR THE BIG HOLIDAY?
Mom: WELL, A VET
CONFERENCE IN IDAHO
IS NOT EXACTLY WHAT
YOU'D CALL A HOLIDAY,
BUT WE'RE GETTING CLOSE
TO BEING READY.
MORNING, EVERYBODY.
MORNING, HONEY.
MORNING, DAD.
HOW ARE
THE PREPARATIONS
FOR YOUR BIG
PRESENTATION COMING?
WELL, TODAY I HAVE
TO FINISH MY DIAGRAMS
ON FOAL DEVELOPMENT.
YOU SEEM TO HAVE
CHEERED UP, ANDREA.
WELL, I GOT A LETTER
FROM TAMMY TODAY...
OH.
AND...
GUESS WHO'S INVITED
TO CALIFORNIA THIS SUMMER.
ME?
[ANDREA GIGGLES]
WELL, I CHECKED
A COUPLE OF AIRLINES,
AND IT'S NOT THAT BAD,
AND I COULD EARN
HALF THE MONEY.
UH...WELL...
WELL...
WELL, I'VE GOT
MOST OF THE SUMMER.
I THINK I CAN DO IT.
I'LL FIND A WAY.
PLEASE?
[WOOF WOOF]
WELL, LET'S, UM...
LET'S JUST SEE
HOW IT GOES.
YES!
WELL, THANK YOU,
ANYWAY.
ANOTHER COLOR,
PLEASE, BUDDY.
[RRR]
HONEY, I'M JUST
ON MY WAY OUT
TO GET SOME THINGS
FOR GRANDMA'S VISIT.
CAN YOU WATCH NOAH
FOR A WHILE?
THAT'S IT.
WHAT? WHAT'S IT?
I COULD BABY-SIT NOAH.
WELL, THAT WOULD
HELP YOU OUT, RIGHT?
AND THEN
WHEN GRANDMA COMES,
IT COULD
HELP HER OUT, TOO.
OOH!
[CHUCKLES]
OH, BY THE WAY,
I FORGOT TO TELL YOU.
I MET OUR
NEW NEIGHBOR--
MRS., UM--
OH, WHATEVER.
ANYWAY, SHE HAS
A SON YOUR AGE.
OH, WELL, I'LL PROBABLY
MEET HIM IN SCHOOL.
UH, YEAH, YEAH,
BUT, HONEY, HONEY,
IT'D BE REALLY NICE IF
YOU WENT OVER TO SAY HI.
YOU KNOW WHAT
I MEAN?
REMEMBER,
HE JUST MOVED HERE,
AND HE PROBABLY DOESN'T
KNOW A SINGLE SOUL.
OK, MOM.
BYE.
ALL RIGHT.
SEE YOU SOON.
BYE-BYE,
SWEETIE.
BYE, MOM.
ANDREA, COME ON.
HELP ME.
OK. HOP IN, ANDREA.
THE TRAIN'S
GOT TO GO.
HERE.
SAY, "ALL ABOARD,"
ANDREA.
ALL ABOARD.
LOUDER!
ALL ABOARD!
HERE WE GO, BUDDY.
TOOT TOOT!
[WOOF]
CHUGGA-LUGGA,
CHOO-CHOO!
COME ON, ANDREA.
CHUGGA-LUGGA.
CHUGGA-LUGGA!
[WOOF]
Both: CHUGGA-LUGGA,
CHUGGA-LUGGA,
CHOO-CHOO.
CHUGGA-LUGGA, CHUGGA-LUGGA,
CHUGGA-LUGGA, CHOO-CHOO.
NEXT STOP--
CALIFORNIA.
HERE WE GO.
NO! IT'S
THE ICE CREAM STORE!
NOAH,
IF I'M DRIVING,
WE'RE GOING
TO CALIFORNIA.
HERE WE GO, BUDDY.
WHOO WHOO!
BUT, ANDREA,
WE AREN'T THERE YET.
UM, I THINK THAT'S
ENOUGH FOR TODAY, NOAH.
HI.
HI. I DIDN'T MEAN TO--
THAT'S OK.
UM, YOU JUST
MOVED IN?
I'M ANDREA,
AND THIS IS NOAH,
AND THIS IS BUDDY.
I'M CONNOR.
COME OVER.
YEAH. SURE.
Noah: YOU WANT TO GET IN?
WE'RE GOING TO CALIFORNIA.
COME ON.
I JUST CAME
FROM THERE.
FROM CALIFORNIA?
MY BEST FRIEND,
SHE JUST
MOVED THERE.
SHE USED TO LIVE
IN YOUR NEW HOUSE.
I'M SAVING UP TO VISIT
HER THIS SUMMER.
WHAT DO PEOPLE LIKE TO DO
AROUND HERE IN THE SUMMER?
GO SHOPPING.
EAT ICE CREAM.
I MEAN, LIKE, SPORTS.
UH, DEPENDS.
WHAT DO YOU LIKE?
SKATE AND PLAY BALL...
BEACH VOLLEYBALL.
WELL, THERE'S SOME
SKATE PARKS AROUND HERE,
AND THEY PLAY
BEACH VOLLEYBALL--
WELL, I THINK--
DOWN BY THE BEACH.
I'M PRETTY SURE THERE'S
A SUMMER LEAGUE.
GREAT. I'LL HAVE
TO CHECK IT OUT.
ANDREA, THE TRAIN
HAS GOT TO GO.
NOAH.
WELL, I'LL
LEAVE YOU TO IT.
BYE.
Noah: COME ON.
THE TRAIN IS GOING.
I THINK I'VE HAD ENOUGH
FOR ONE DAY, NOAH.
PPBBBT.
5...
6...
7...8...
9.
BUDDY, I'M NEVER GONNA
MAKE ENOUGH MONEY.
[WHIMPERS]
YOU SEE,
THE OBSTACLE COURSE
IS ALMOST
EXACTLY THE SAME.
THE DOG CAN GO
THROUGH THE VENT
JUST LIKE HE DID
THE TUNNEL,
GRAB THE JEWEL,
AND BACK OUT
THROUGH THE LASERS.
YOU'D BETTER
FINISH THAT
BEFORE YOU
GET THERE, NOAH.
I WASN'T SUPPOSED
TO LET YOU HAVE
ANY MORE
ICE CREAM TODAY.
HI, CAT.
HI, DONNA.
ANDREA, GREAT
TO SEE YOU.
IS MY DAD AROUND?
JUST ONE SECOND.
HI, TURTLE.
PATRICK! ANDREA'S
HERE TO SEE YOU!
THANK YOU, DONNA.
HEY, WHAT
A PLEASANT SURPRISE.
HI, NOAH.
HI, DAD.
[WOOF]
YEAH. YOU, TOO,
BUDDY. WHAT'S UP?
DAD, I NEED
SOME IDEAS.
THIS MONEY THING ISN'T
WORKING OUT LIKE I'D HOPED.
I THOUGHT I'D HAVE
AT LEAST HALF
THE MONEY BY NOW.
Woman: OH, COME ON.
IT WON'T BE FOR LONG.
COME ON.
WHAT'S HE IN FOR
THIS TIME, MRS. MILLER?
WELL, IT'S THE ANNUAL
BAKE-OFF TOURNAMENT
IN PORTLAND, AND--
OH, HE HATES THIS
BOARDING THING.
DON'T TAKE IT
PERSONALLY.
JUST HARD ON HIM.
OH, TOODLES,
COME ON OUT.
COME ON OUT
OF THERE, SWEETIE.
Woman:
COME ON, SWEETIE.
COME ON
OUT OF THERE.
HERE, BOY.
WE WON'T HURT YOU.
OH. WELL, DON'T YOU
HAVE THE MAGIC TOUCH?
WAIT A SECOND.
MRS. MILLER,
WHAT IF TOODLES
STAYED WITH ME?
I COULD
TAKE CARE OF HIM.
HAVE YOU DONE
THAT BEFORE?
NO, BUT I HAVE
A DOG--BUDDY.
OH, BUDDY.
OH, WELL, YOU'RE USED
TO TAKING CARE OF DOGS,
AND YOU'VE DONE SUCH
A GREAT JOB WITH BUDDY.
THIS IS
A SUPERB IDEA.
TOODLES
WILL LOVE IT.
I'LL GO GET HIS
THINGS FROM THE CAR.
[GIGGLING]
Patrick:
ALL RIGHT. LISTEN.
I'M GOING TO HAVE TO
GO PICK UP GRANDMA
SO I'M GONNA BE HOME
IN ABOUT AN HOUR OR SO.
GRAM GRAM? YAY.
HEY, NOAH?
LET'S HAVE A LOOK HERE.
LOOKS LIKE YOU GOT
A LITTLE DIRT ON YOUR FACE.
MMM.
TASTES A LOT LIKE DIRT
FROM A ROCKY ROAD.
ANDREA?
I BETTER GET
TOODLES'S STUFF. BYE.
COME ON, NOAH.
HA HA HA! YES.
GRAM GRAM!
OHHHH!
HI.
AND LOOK WHO'S HERE.
[SQUAWK]
LOOK WHO'S HERE.
POLLY!
OH, MY,
HOW YOU'VE GROWN.
HEY, NOAH,
CAN YOU TAKE
THIS UPSTAIRS
FOR GRANDMA, AND
WE'LL HELP HER, OK?
OK, EVERYBODY.
LET'S GO.
Patrick: LET'S JUST
GRAB STUFF. LET'S GO.
OH!
COME ON, GUYS.
LET'S GO UPSTAIRS.
Patrick: WE'LL GET THE STAND
UP THERE FOR POLLY.
OH, MY,
HOW YOU'VE GROWN.
[WOOF]
WOOF.
Patrick: I HOPE YOU'RE
GONNA BE COMFORTABLE, MOM.
Gram: AM I
IN JOSH'S ROOM?
HEY, BUDDY,
WHERE'S THAT LITTLE BAG?
Doug: THAT KID AND HIS DOG
WILL SHOW UP HERE.
WHAT KID WOULDN'T?
HE'S GOT A WHOLE BOOK
OF ICE CREAM COUPONS, HUH?
OH. OH!
I WISH I HAD A BOOK
OF ICE CREAM COUPONS.
WELL, I GUESS
WE'RE LEAVING NOW.
Noah: I WANT TO COME.
AWW.
NOAH,
IT'S A VETERINARIAN
CONVENTION.
I THINK YOU'D BE
REALLY BORED.
PLUS, I THINK YOU'RE
GONNA HAVE A LOT OF FUN
HERE WITH
ANDREA AND GRAM.
GOOD LUCK, DAD.
YOU GUYS BE SURE
TO HELP GRAM
WITH WHATEVER
SHE NEEDS.
REMEMBER, SHE'S
A REAL SOFTIE,
SO DON'T TRY TO GET AWAY
WITH TOO MUCH, RIGHT?
NOAH, THAT'S GOES
FOR YOU, TOO.
YOU CAN'T HAVE ICE CREAM
FOR EVERY MEAL
WHILE WE'RE GONE.
Patrick: OK, AND
LET'S REMEMBER NOW,
GRANDMA IS NOT
THE GREATEST COOK
IN THE WORLD.
PLEASE TRY AND BE
REALLY SENSITIVE, OK,
BECAUSE GRANDMA TRIES
REALLY, REALLY HARD.
Andrea: WE'LL EAT
EVERYTHING, DAD.
WELL, EXCEPT FOR
THE CAULIFLOWER CUPCAKES.
[WHIMPERS]
[COUGHS]
Patrick: MOM.
HA HA HA!
THE KIDS WERE JUST
SAYING HOW MUCH
THEY LOVE
YOUR COOKING.
VERY GOOD. WELL,
I HAVE GOT A BATCH
OF CAULIFLOWER CUPCAKES
READY FOR THE OVEN.
YUMMY.
HA HA HA!
ANDREA, CAN YOU HELP
ME OUT WITH THE BAGS?
YEAH. SURE.
MOM, I GOT ALL THE NUMBERS
THAT YOU NEED...
YOU BE A GOOD BOY, OK?
WE'LL BE FINE.
NOW YOU DO GOOD.
[CHIRPS]
[SKATEBOARD APPROACHING]
HEY.
DID YOU FIND
THE VOLLEYBALL LEAGUE?
YEAH.
HOW'S IT GOING?
HARD.
WE DON'T HAVE
A FULL TEAM,
SO IT'S
KIND OF TIRING.
THAT'S A BUMMER.
DO YOU PLAY
VOLLEYBALL?
NOT REALLY.
HEY, I HEARD YOU HAVE
AN OLDER BROTHER.
YEAH. JOSH.
HE'S AWAY AT COLLEGE.
HE STAYED THE SUMMER
TO PLAY FOOTBALL.
ALL RIGHT. WELL,
IF YOU DECIDE
YOU WANT TO PLAY
OR KNOW ANYBODY ELSE
WHO MIGHT WANT TO JOIN,
LET ME KNOW.
OK.
BYE.
SEE YOU LATER.
ARE THEY GONE?
YEP. THEY JUST LEFT.
HOO HOO! ICE CREAM.
SHH.
[WHIMPERS]
Polly: OOPS.
WAH HA!
[METAL SQUEAKING]
YOU SEE, GORDON?
THERE THEY ARE.
Polly: [SQUAWK]
WHOO WHOO!
HEY!
OH, GOSH! SHHHH!
Doug: DON'T BLOW
OUR COVER, GORD.
Man: GOOD TO SEE YOU, DAN.
OHH.
[SQUEAK]
OH. OH.
[SQUAWK]
ICE CREAM
FOR EVERY MEAL.
WHAT'S WITH THE BIRD?
[WOOF]
HEY!
I'M GOING
TO GET YOU.
G-G-GET GOING.
WAIT UP, BUDDY.
UH...
YOU ATE ALL
THE ICE CREAM.
THE SHERIFF! DUCK!
OW. UNGH!
HEY, NOAH.
HEY, BUDDY.
Noah: HI, SHERIFF.
HI, POLLY.
Sheriff:
SEE YOU LATER.
THANKS.
UH! BUDDY, SLOW DOWN.
WHERE'D THEY GO?
[LAUGHING]
Andrea:
TOODLES, LOOK.
BABY.
[BARKING]
OH, TOODLES.
OH, HO HO.
BABY, BABY.
MY BABY. OH, HO HO!
IT'S SO WONDERFUL.
YOU HAVE A REAL GIFT.
OOH, BA BA BABY.
Andrea: GRAM!
40 BIG ONES
FROM MRS. MILLER.
OH, HOW GENEROUS.
YEAH.
YOU KNOW,
IF I DO MORE OF THIS,
I JUST MIGHT BE ABLE
TO GO TO CALIFORNIA AFTER ALL.
AND SHE'S AN ANGEL,
LET ME TELL YOU THAT,
AN ANGEL FROM HEAVEN.
MY LITTLE TOODLES
HAD A GREAT TIME
OVER THERE.
OH.
Woman: ♪ THERE AIN'T
NOTHING THAT WE CAN'T DO ♪
♪ TOGETHER, TOGETHER ♪
♪ JUST TAKE A LOOK AT WHAT
WE'VE BEEN THROUGH TOGETHER...
HI.
♪ TOGETHER, ME AND YOU ♪
YOU'RE GONNA BE
SO HAPPY HERE.
♪ THE BIG DARK CLOUD
HAS DRIFTED AWAY ♪
♪ THE SUN IS
STARTING TO SHINE ♪
♪ IN A REAL BIG WAY ♪
[WOOF]
THANK YOU.
♪ ...WE'RE OFF TO HAVE
A LITTLE FUN ♪
♪ THERE ARE LOTS OF THINGS
TO BE DONE ♪
♪ THAT TWO CAN DO
BETTER THAN ONE ♪
♪ THERE AIN'T NOTHING THAT
WE CAN'T DO TOGETHER... ♪
TWO TERRIERS FOR 5 DAYS.
♪ JUST TAKE A LOOK AT WHAT
WE'VE BEEN THROUGH TOGETHER ♪
♪ TOGETHER, ME AND YOU ♪
YEAH. I'LL BOOK YOU
ON THE 20th.
[GRUNTING]
WHOA.
NOAH, HOLD HIM TIGHT.
♪ ...TILL I GET WHAT I WANT ♪
HA HA HA!
♪ OH, IT'S GONNA
TAKE A LITTLE TIME ♪
THANKS.
♪ TILL I GET
WHAT I NEED, YEAH ♪
♪ WORKING REAL HARD
IS ON MY MIND... ♪
I GUESS NOT.
♪ BEEN A HARD DAY AND A... ♪
LAST ONE IN'S
A ROTTEN EGG.
HA HA HA!
♪ ...THAT'S WHY ♪
♪ THERE AIN'T NOTHING THAT
WE CAN'T DO... ♪
AHH.
♪ TOGETHER, TOGETHER ♪
AAH!
♪ JUST TAKE A LOOK AT WHAT
WE'VE BEEN THROUGH TOGETHER...
[SQUAWK]
RUB-A-DUB-DUB.
♪ WELL, I ♪
♪ I WOULD DO ANYTHING FOR YOU ♪
♪ YOU WOULD DO
ANYTHING FOR ME ♪
♪ TOGETHER WE CAN DO ANYTHING ♪
♪ THERE AIN'T NOTHING
THAT WE CAN'T DO... ♪
I'M POOPED.
♪ TOGETHER ♪
♪ TAKE A LOOK AT WHAT
WE'VE BEEN THROUGH.... ♪
COME AND GET IT!
[BARKING]
♪ TOGETHER, ME AND YOU... ♪
THANK YOU.
♪ ...CAN'T DO TOGETHER... ♪
I'M ALMOST THERE, BUDDY.
[GROANS]
YEE-HAW! GIDDYAP!
♪ TOGETHER, ME AND YOU ♪
YES!
NOW, IF WE COULD JUST
GET THAT BIRD ALONE.
I THOUGHT WE WANTED
THE DOG, DOUG.
OH, HO, BUT THE BIRD IS
EASIER TO CATCH THAN THE DOG,
AND WE CAN USE THE BIRD
AS DOG BAIT.
HEE HEE HEE!
Man on TV:
SHAKE, CONE, OR SUNDAE,
OR MAYBE A BANANA SPLIT.
COME ON INTO TILLY'S...
[BARKING]
Man on TV:
WE'VE GOT ALL THE FLAVORS.
Andrea: NO PROBLEM.
YEAH, THEY ALL GET
THEIR OWN BOWLS.
Man on TV:
KITTY-CORNER TO THE MUSEUM
IN DOWNTOWN FERNFIELD.
Different man:
IS YOUR CAT A HUNGRY CAT?
IS YOUR CAT
A HUNGRY CAT?
♪ MEOW, MEOW, MEOW,
MEOW, MEOW... ♪
Andrea: YEAH.
NO, YOU DON'T HAVE
TO BRING ONE. THAT'S FINE.
MEOW. MEOW.
♪ MEOW, MEOW... ♪
NO PROBLEM. YEAH.
♪ MEOW, MEOW, MEOW ♪
Andrea: MM-HMM.
[MEOWING]
POLLY, SHH.
[MEOWING CONTINUES]
[WOOF]
[POLLY AND CATS
ON TV MEOWING]
YEAH. THEY ALL GET
THEIR OWN BATHS.
[WOOF]
[BARKING]
HEE HEE HEE!
♪ MEOW, MEOW, MEOW,
MEOW, MEOW... ♪
POLLY! SHH!
TOMCAT KIBBLE?
[SQUAWK]
[DOGS GROWLING]
[MEOWING]
Andrea: TWO DOBERMANS
FOR TOMORROW?  NO PROBLEM.
GOOD RALLY, NOAH.
HA HA HA!
THAT WAS BUDDY!
LOOK. I'VE GOT TO GET
TO PRACTICE PRETTY SOON.
I NEED MY BALL BACK.
OK. I GOT IT.
OH! NOAH, THE GATE!
[MEOWING]
[DOGS BARKING]
CALL YOU BACK?
[PANTING]
NOAH, YOU STAY HERE.
CONNOR, HELP.
WHOO-HOO!
MEOW, MEOW, MEOW, MEOW!
[DOGS BARKING]
POLLY, COME BACK!
Polly: [SQUAWK]
HA HA! [SQUAWK]
[MEOWING]
OH, WOW.
[BARKING]
[POLLY SQUAWKS]
MEOW. WHOO-HOO!
Woman: WATCH OUT!
OH! UGH!
Man: AAH!
RASCAL, PRINCESS,
PEANUT, STOP!
GIVING IT UP, UP, OW!
[SQUAWK]
HOWDY! ♪ MEOW, MEOW, MEOW... ♪
GOT TO GO, GO, GO! WHOA!
AHA! HUH?
AAH!
OH! UNH!
Woman: WHAT'S GOING ON?
Andrea: THANKS, BUDDY.
I WISH GRANDMA NEVER
BROUGHT THAT BIRD.
Andrea: WHERE IS HE,
ANYWAY?
THIS IS NOT GOOD.
NOT GOOD.
WHOA!
[CROWD OOHS]
AH!
UH-OH.
OH, NO.
Crowd: OHH!
[WOOF]
[CROWD CHEERING]
UH-OH.
Man: INCLUDING THE
DAMAGE TO MY STALL,
LET'S MAKE IT
AN EVEN 120 BUCKS.
I'M REALLY SORRY.
THERE GOES MY TRIP
TO CALIFORNIA.
IT WAS PROBABLY A DUMB IDEA
IN THE FIRST PLACE.
IT'S ALMOST HALFWAY
THROUGH THE SUMMER.
THERE'S NO WAY
I CAN START OVER.
I KNOW.
I FEEL TERRIBLE.
NOAH WAS JUST
BRINGING MY BALL.
IT'S NO ONE ELSE'S
FAULT.
BUT POLLY'S.
OH. I'M REALLY
LATE FOR PRACTICE.
I GOT TO GO.
SEE YOU LATER?
THANKS FOR COMING
WITH ME TODAY.
BYE.
Gram:
MAY I COME IN?
DID YOU FIND HIM?
NO. NOT YET.
I KNOW HOW MUCH
YOU WANTED TO GO
AND VISIT WITH TAMMY,
ANDREA.
I DON'T THINK I'LL EVER
FIND ANOTHER FRIEND
LIKE HER AGAIN.
MAYBE NOT...
BUT LIFE IS LIKE THAT.
YOU KNOW? IT JUST THROWS
YOU SOME CURVES AND...
YOU KIND OF
HAVE TO FIGURE OUT
HOW TO RESPOND.
I'M NOT SAYING
IT'S EASY.
BUT JUST MAYBE
THERE'S SOMEONE ELSE
OUT THERE
WHO NEEDS A FRIEND,
AND JUST MAYBE...
YOU HAVE SOME SPACE
IN YOUR HEART NOW
TO LET SOMEONE ELSE IN.
THAT'S MY GIRL.
[SNIFFLING]
I WISH GRANDMA...
PTUI!
NEVER BROUGHT THAT BIRD.
[AWK]
HERE, ANDREA.
I WANT YOU
TO HAVE IT.
BUT HOW WILL YOU
BUY YOUR ICE CREAM?
MY COUPONS.
OH.
THANKS, NOAH.
IS POLLY BACK?
NOT YET, BUT...
WE'LL FIND HIM.
CAN I SLEEP IN HERE
FOR A BIT?
YEAH, SURE.
[SNORING]
YOU KNOW, NONE OF THEM
ARE EVER GONNA
SHOW UP HERE THIS LATE.
I'LL GO DOWN TO THE STORE
AND STEAL SOME GUM.
UH, GRAB ME A PEPPERONI
STICK, WILL YOU?
[POLLY SOBBING]
OH, GRAM, GRAM.
OOH. OOH.
DOUG.
[AWK]
Gordon: YOU AIN'T GONNA
NEVER BELIEVE THIS.
[AWK]
Doug: WHAT ARE YOU
WAITING FOR?
OH. OH.
GRAM, GRAM.
HI, LITTLE PRETTY.
THERE YOU GO.
I GOT YOU!
I GOT YOU--OOH!
UH-HUH.
WHOO-HOO!
Polly: SQUAWK!
AH!
[POLLY SQUAWKING]
HERE.
HA HA HA!
AAH! GREAT BALLS
OF FIRE! HOO! HOO!
[SKATEBOARD APPROACHING]
THERE YOU ARE.
Connor: THE BEACH VOLLEYBALL
CHAMPIONSHIPS ARE COMING UP.
YOU'LL NEVER BELIEVE IT.
THE GRAND PRIZE IS
A TRIP TO MALIBU
TO WATCH THE CALIFORNIA
PRO BEACH VOLLEYBALL TOUR.
MALIBU, ANDREA.
THAT'S IN CALIFORNIA.
WAIT. DID YOU SAY
CALIFORNIA?
YES, I SAID CALIFORNIA.
NO!
YES!
THE WHOLE TEAM GETS TO GO
IF WE WIN THE TOURNAMENT HERE.
[WOOF]
OK. SO WHAT DO I DO?
Connor: OK.
NOW, REMEMBER,
EYE ON THE BALL.
Woman: ♪ SHOW ME ♪
♪ HOW TO SING THAT SONG
YOU'RE SINGING ♪
♪ SHOW ME... ♪
YOU SHOULD HAVE YOUR
HANDS ABOVE LIKE THAT.
♪ SHOW ME ALL THE BEAUTY... ♪
TRY TO GET
UNDER IT MORE.
♪ ...HAPPINESS THAT
WE CAN SHARE... ♪
GOOD. ALL RIGHT.
♪ TOGETHER ♪
NOW LET'S TRY THE BUMP.
PUT YOUR HANDS OUT
LIKE THIS.
POINT YOUR THUMBS
DOWN.
HERE WE GO.
♪ ...GET TO KNOW ME... ♪
ALMOST.
Connor: NOT BAD.
THERE'S ONE LAST THING
I HAVE TO SHOW YOU.
IT'S THE SPIKE.
♪ BE MY COMPANION... ♪
WHOA! THAT LOOKS HARD.
IT JUST TAKES TIME.
REMEMBER--
EYE ON THE BALL.
YEAH.
LET'S DO IT.
[WHIMPERS]
[GASP]
HA HA HA!
WE'LL HAVE TO WORK
ON THAT ONE.
OH, THEY'VE BEEN
AT THIS FOR HOURS.
THEY'VE GOT TO BE
GETTING HUNGRY.
OHH. I'M SO USED
TO TALKING TO YOU.
WHERE ARE YOU,
POLLY?
Gram: I KNOW TEENAGERS
ARE ALWAYS HUNGRY.
NOW, SHARE WITH
THE LITTLE ONE.
THANKS, GRAM.
RAISINS AND LETTUCE.
YUCK!
MMM!
[GIGGLES]
Andrea: MMM.
I HAD NO IDEA
VOLLEYBALL COULD BE
SO MUCH FUN.
HA HA HA!
[CHUCKLES]
[RRR]
[GROWL]
Andrea: MMM. SO WHEN
DO I MEET THE TEAM?
Connor: SO THAT'S COACH
THERE IN THE BACK,
PUMPING UP THE BALL.
THIS IS CHRIS, TASHA,
BILLY, AND JUSTIN.
HI.
I THOUGHT ANOTHER PLAYER
WOULD HELP US OUT.
IT'S BEEN SO HARD
WITH THE 5 OF US.
COACH McKAY.
[GASP]
OHH.
COACH, THIS IS
THE NEW PLAYER
I WAS TALKING
ABOUT--ANDREA.
Andrea: HI.
THANKS SO MUCH FOR
LETTING ME JOIN, COACH.
I'M A BIT NEW AT THIS,
BUT I'LL TRY
REALLY HARD.
OK, WARMUP TIME!
LET'S GO!
SHUFFLE! SHUFFLE!
SHUFFLE! YEAH!
CONNOR, I GOT IT.
ALL RIGHT.
I GOT IT.
LET'S GO! LET'S GO!
DARN.
KEEP IT UP.
TRY AND SET,
ANDREA.
UNH!
OOH.
UH-OH.
[RRR]
Girl: NICE ONE.
Girl:
NICE TRY, ANDREA.
Noah: I GOT IT.
Coach: THERE WE GO.
DON'T FORGET,
BE THE BALL.
YEAH. OK.
THAT'S ALL RIGHT.
COACH IS FINE.
GIVE ME 5.
OK. LET'S GO. COME ON.
MINE.
TAKE IT, ANDREA.
Coach: OK.
OVER THE NET NEXT TIME.
UP WE GO.
Girl: ALL RIGHT,
ANDREA.
Coach: ALL RIGHT!
OOH.
OH.
ONLY SEE THE BALL,
ANDREA.
FORGET
EVERYTHING ELSE.
OK. REMEMBER
TO STAY FOCUSED--
OH! OK.
[LAUGHTER]
ALL RIGHT. GOOD.
[WHISTLE BLOWS]
Team: HUDDLE!
NOW, WE'RE UP AGAINST
THE RATS TOMORROW.
SO I SUGGEST YOU ALL
GET A GOOD NIGHT'S SLEEP
AND EAT PLENTY OF PASTA.
TIMBER...
All: WOLVES!
[CHEERING]
IT'S EASIER
IN THE BACKYARD.
IT JUST
TAKES PRACTICE.
I'M NERVOUS ABOUT
THE GAME TOMORROW.
YOU'LL DO GREAT.
Gram: POLLY!
POLLY!
[BUDDY BARKING]
[WOOF]
POLLY!
WHERE IS HE,
GRAM GRAM?
OH, I DON'T KNOW,
BUT WE'LL FIND HIM.
POLLY!
NOW THAT WE
HAVE OUR BAIT...
WE CAN GO FISHING?
HA HA HA!
NO, YOU IDIOT.
WE CAN SET THE TRAP
FOR THE DOG.
OHH.
[POLLY SQUAWKS]
HI, BABY.
HEY.
[WHISTLE BLOWS]
Andrea: WHAT'S THIS
TEAM CALLED AGAIN?
THE RIVERSIDE RATS.
THEY'VE WON
THE STATE CHAMPIONSHIPS
TWO YEARS IN A ROW.
OK, TEAM.
HANDS IN.
FERNFIELD!
GO, RATS!
HERE YOU GO.
NO, THANKS,
GRAM GRAM.
I'M GONNA LOOK
FOR POLLY.
OH, NOW, NOAH,
WE LOOKED FOR HIM
ALL MORNING LONG,
AND ANDREA--SHE NEEDS
OUR SUPPORT RIGHT NOW.
WE'RE GONNA
FIND HIM SOON.
HE CAN'T STAY AWAY
FROM MY COOKING
MUCH LONGER, HUH?
Coach: LET'S GO!
COME ON!  YEAH!
GOT IT!
SPIKE IT!
OHH.
POINT, TIMBERWOLVES.
YEAH!
[WOOF]
[CHEERING]
OK.
YOUR BALL!
GOT IT!
Girl: ALL RIGHT.
[WHISTLE BLOWS]
[GROANING]
[RRR]
Girl:
COME ON, ANDREA.
EYE ON THE BALL.
[WHISTLE BLOWS]
[WOOF]
GOT IT!
Andrea: I GOT IT.
IT'S MINE.
UNH!
[GROANING]
[WHIMPERS]
IT'S OK. IT'S ALL RIGHT.
SERVICE, RATS.
[WHISTLE BLOWS]
WHAT'S UP WITH HIM?
Andrea: IT'S MINE.
[WHISTLE BLOWS]
Referee: POINT, RATS.
SET IT UP!
[WHISTLE BLOWS]
POINT, TIMBERWOLVES.
[CHEERING]
Andrea: SORRY.
Boy: AWW.
[WHISTLE BLOWS]
[CHEERING]
POINT, RATS.
[WHISTLE BLOWS]
YEAH!
[WOOF]
GO, T'WOLVES!
GOOD ONE, GUYS.
Boy: BUMP! BUMP IT!
MINE!
[CHEERING]
Referee:
POINT, TIMBERWOLVES.
GO, T'WOLVES!
SERVICE, TIMBERWOLVES.
Crowd: AWW.
[CHEERING]
Man: YOU CAN DO IT,
GUYS.
Referee: GAME POINT, RATS.
Andrea: I GOT IT.
IT'S MINE.
Girl: WHOO! THAT'S IT.
THAT'S IT.
MY BALL. MY BALL.
Crowd: OHH.
Girl:
ANDREA, IT'S YOURS.
Crowd: OHH.
EEE. OOH.
[RRR]
GAME, RATS.
[WHISTLE BLOWS]
DON'T WORRY ABOUT IT.
WE'LL GET THEM NEXT TIME.
SOLID EFFORT.
FORTUNATELY, WE STILL HAVE
A FEW MORE GAMES
UNTIL THE CHAMPIONSHIP
TOURNAMENT.
TIMBERWOLVES.
Gram: I THINK THAT'S
ONE OF THE BETTER GAMES
YOU'VE PLAYED.
GRAM, I'VE ONLY
PLAYED ONE GAME.
OH, WELL,
IT WAS STILL GOOD.
Noah: I CELEBRATED
WITH ICE CREAM.
Gram: HA HA HA!
HA HA HA!
[WOOF]
Crowd: OHH.
OK. LET'S WORK
ON YOUR SPIKE.
GOOD.
AWESOME, ANDREA.
I THINK
I'M GETTING BETTER.
[WOOF]
[WHISTLE BLOWS]
TIMBERWOLVES!
[HOWLING]
HOW'S THAT?
EYE ON THE BALL.
[WHISTLE BLOWS]
YES!
[WOOF]
[CHUCKLES]
Connor: BYE, MOM.
Girl: WE'VE ONLY GOT
TWO GAMES TO GO.
Boy: THAT'S AWESOME.
HEY, TASHA.
[SNIFFS]
IS EVERYTHING OK,
COACH?
WELL, I GOT SOME BAD NEWS.
TASHA CAN'T PLAY ANYMORE.
WHAT?
Coach:
HER PARENTS JUST DECIDED...
TO TAKE HER TO SPEND
THE REST OF THE SUMMER
WITH HER GRANDMOTHER.
BUT SHE'S
OUR SETTER!
THE TOURNAMENT!
I KNOW.
Boy: OH, MAN.
I HAVE AN IDEA.
WHERE'S NOAH?
NOAH.
HE'S A LITTLE...
WELL, LITTLE,
DON'T YOU THINK?
Andrea:
DON'T WORRY, COACH.
I'LL BE BACK
IN A FEW MINUTES.
SHE'S BACK!
Girl:
SHE'S KIDDING.
OH.
[WOOF]
HA HA HA!
Connor: I'VE SEEN
BUDDY SET BEFORE.
HE'S AWESOME.
BUT HE'S NOT AN IRISH
SETTER. HA HA HA!
[KIDS GROAN]
Andrea: WHAT DO YOU THINK?
WELL, TEAM,
I SAY WE GO FOR IT
OR WE GO HOME.
[WOOF]
All: GO, T'WOLVES!
[CHEERING]
BUDDY'S HERE! OK!
OH, YAY!
[CHEERING]
LET'S GET THIS SHOW
ON THE ROAD!
Boy: LET'S GO, BUDDY!
[PLAYERS HOWLING
AND CHATTERING]
Girl:
ALL RIGHT, ANDREA.
Boy: MINE.
[WOOF]
[WHISTLE BLOWS]
YAY!
GOOD JOB, BUDDY.
[BARKING]
[CHEERING]
GOOD!
HOW LONG HAS BUDDY
BEEN PLAYING VOLLEYBALL?
Girl: GOT IT!
GOT IT!
[BUDDY BARKING]
[WHISTLE BLOWS]
YAY!
ALL RIGHT, BUDDY.
[WOOF WOOF]
Boy: GOOD BLOCK,
BUDDY.
I GOT IT.
HUSTLE!
IN.
[WOOF WOOF]
UH!
YAY!
DIG! DIG!
OVER THE NET.
Man: GO, ANDREA.
AAH!
EEYAH!
BUMP IT.
Girl: GET IT UP!
GOT IT.
POINT, TIMBERWOLVES.
YAY!
SERVICE, TIMBERWOLVES.
[BLOWS WHISTLE]
UH!
Crowd: OH.
Girl: GET IT UP!
Noah: BUDDY!
YEAH!
Gram: YAY!
[BLOWS WHISTLE]
OK, SERVICE.
Girl: IT'S SHORT.
MINE.
Girl: OVER.
I GOT IT!
[WHISTLE BLOWS]
YAY!
WAY TO GO, BUDDY.
OK, GUYS.
COME ON, GUYS.
Girl: LET'S GO.
GAME POINT,
FERNFIELD TIMBERWOLVES.
Crowd: LET'S GO, T'WOLVES!
[CLAPPING]
LET'S GO, T'WOLVES!
I GOT IT!
Girl: YEAH!
AAH!
[WHISTLE BLOWS]
YEAH, YEAH!
HA HA!
YAY!
GOOD GAME, GUYS.
GOOD GAME.
YEAH, BUDDY!
HA HA HA!
Man: HEY, BUDDY,
HOW ABOUT A PICTURE?
Man: ♪ WELL, WE'RE
PUTTING DOWN THE TOP ♪
♪ AND WE'RE RIDING
DOWN THE COAST TO L.A. ♪
♪ GOING TO L.A,
GOING TO L.A ♪
♪ HEADED FOR THE BEACH ♪
♪ WHERE THE SURFING BUNNIES
ARE PRETTY ♪
♪ THE BOARDS
AND THE BEACH ♪
♪ AND THE SURFING ARE HOT ♪
♪ I'M HEADING
THROUGH THE WAVE ♪
♪ GONNA NEVER STOP ♪
♪ WE'RE PUTTING DOWN THE TOP ♪
♪ AND WE'RE RIDING
DOWN THE COAST TO L.A. ♪
♪ PUTTING DOWN THE TOP ♪
♪ AND WE'RE RIDING
DOWN THE COAST TO L.A. ♪
♪ WE'RE PUTTING DOWN THE TOP ♪
♪ AND WE'RE RIDING
DOWN THE COAST TO L.A. ♪
OK, GUYS.
Coach: THIS IS IT.
TWO POINTS AWAY
FROM EARNING A SPOT
IN THE CHAMPIONSHIP GAME.
AND DO YOU KNOW
WHAT HAPPENS
IF WE WIN THAT?
MY BAGS ARE PACKED.
GO, FERNFIELD!
[WOOF WOOF]
BREAK!
OK, GUYS, LET'S GO!
GOOD SERVE!
IT'S YOURS.
UNH!
Crowd: ALL RIGHT!
HA HA HA!
Referee: GAME POINT,
TIMBERWOLVES.
[WHISTLE BLOWS]
CALL IT!
GOT IT!
[WOOF]
[WHISTLE BLOWS]
YEAH!
YAY! YAY!
OHH! WAY TO GO!
[WOOF]
HA HA HA!
COME HERE.
ANDREA, I AM
SO PROUD OF YOU.
DO YOU GET TO GO
TO DISNEYLAND?
WE STILL HAVE TO WIN
THE GAME TOMORROW.
KIDS, I'D LIKE YOU ALL
HERE BY 8:30 TO WARM UP.
SHOULD WE BRING
OUR LUGGAGE?
WE PLAY THE RATS.
GET LOTS OF REST.
IT'S GONNA BE
A REAL DOGFIGHT.
ARRH!
[WOOF]
[GIGGLING]
WHOO!
AAH!
Connor: ANDREA.
[RRR]
ANDREA!
ANDREA, LET'S GO.
LET'S GO WARM UP.
IT'S 7:00
IN THE MORNING.
I KNOW. WE GOT
TO GET GOING.
OK. UM, I'LL BE DOWN
IN A BIT.
WHOA! YOU'RE UP EARLY.
Andrea: YEAH.
CONNOR THINKS
WE SHOULD BE UP
EARLY TO PRACTICE.
Noah:
COME ON, BUDDY.
WE SHOULD
PRACTICE, TOO.
[WOOF]
WELL, WHAT ARE YOU
PRACTICING FOR, NOAH?
OH, JUST STUFF.
JUST STUFF,
GRAM GRAM.
MMM. BYE, GRAM.
OH, WHAT?
FOR THE ICE CREAM
EATING CONTEST.
OH. DON'T BE LONG.
BUDDY HAS TO BE
AT THE VOLLEYBALL COURTS
BY 8:30.
SO YOU MAKE SURE
YOU TAKE HIM THERE.
Noah:
WE'LL BE THERE.
OH. OHH.
HEY, CONNOR?
YEAH?
I WAS WONDERING.
WHEN THE SEASON'S
ALL THROUGH
AND THE GAME'S DONE,
IF WE CAN STILL DO THIS
ONCE IN A WHILE?
I'D LIKE THAT.
HA HA HA!
Polly:
♪ I'M A YANKEE DOODLE DANDY ♪
♪ YANKEE DOODLE,
DO OR DIE ♪
♪ A REAL LIVE NEPHEW
OF MY UNCLE SAM'S... ♪
AAH!
♪ I'VE A YANKEE DOODLE
SWEETHEART... ♪
WOULD YOU JUST GET
THAT BIRD TO BE QUIET?
♪ YANKEE DOODLE
CAME TO LONDON ♪
♪ LA LA LA LA LA LA LA ♪
♪ I'M A YANKEE DOODLE DANDY ♪
UGH! HUH!
OH, MAMA.
[RRR]
Noah: WAIT HERE,
BUDDY.
HE'S IN THERE ALREADY.
I'LL GO AROUND BACK.
[PANTING]
[BELLS JINGLE]
Doug: HEY, GORDON.
IS THAT HIM?
Gordon: THAT'S HIM
ALL RIGHT.
OHH!
WELL, NOAH.
LOOKS LIKE
YOU FOUND THE BACK DOOR.
A LITTLE EARLY
FOR ICE CREAM, ISN'T IT?
NOT FOR US!
[WHIMPERS]
[BRAKES SQUEAK]
TWO COUPONS IT IS.
PREPARE THE BIRD!
COME ON. MOVE IT!
[BUZZ]
HEE HEE!
OK, BIRD. NOW SING.
♪ I'M A YANKEE DOODLE
DANDY... ♪
NO. THE OTHER ONE.
♪ MEOW, MEOW,
MEOW, MEOW... ♪
Doug: YEAH.
♪ ASK FOR IT
BY NAME ♪
[RRR]
♪ MEOW, MEOW, MEOW ♪
♪ TOMCAT KIBBLE... ♪
IT'S WORKING!
WELL, NOAH, I USUALLY
DON'T START SERVING
FOR ANOTHER HOUR,
BUT SINCE YOU'RE
MY NUMBER-ONE CUSTOMER...
Polly: ♪ MEOW,
MEOW, MEOW... ♪
JUMP IN, PUPPY.
YOU KNOW THIS BIRD?
[WOOF]
♪ MEOW, MEOW,
MEOW, MEOW ♪
♪ MEOW,
THANKS.
SEE YOU TOMORROW.
HA HA HA!
WE'RE IN THE HOMESTRETCH
NOW, GORDON!
[DOUG AND GORDON LAUGHING]
[ENGINE REVVING]
Doug: WHOO-HOO-HOO!
WHOO! WHOO! WHOO!
WHOO-HOO!
BUDDY? BUDDY?
I GOT US SOME ICE CREAM.
[TIRES SQUEALING]
Doug: WHOO! WHOO!
[GROWLING]
[WHISTLING]
BUDDY?
[ALL TALKING AT ONCE]
Sheriff: HOWDY, FOLKS.
I'M SHERIFF BOB,
AND TODAY, I'LL BE
THE COMPETITION OFFICIAL.
SO ON BEHALF
OF THE FERNFIELD TIMBERWOLVES,
I'D LIKE TO WELCOME YOU
TO THE FINAL GAME
OF THE SUMMER
VOLLEYBALL TOURNAMENT.
BALLS UP!
I DON'T UNDERSTAND
IT EITHER.
THEY KNEW WHEN
TO BE HERE.
15 MINUTES TO GAME TIME.
OH. I KNOW, I KNOW.
BUDDY? BUDDY?
[SNORING]
[BUDDY WHIMPERING]
[PHIL SNORING]
SHH! HE'S ASLEEP.
Polly: AWW. HE'S ASLEEP.
[SQUAWKING]
BUDDY, YOU HERE?
[ALL TALKING AT ONCE]
A COUPLE MORE
MINUTES, COACH.
THAT'S ALL I CAN
GIVE YOU.
WELL, GUYS.
THIS ISN'T THE WAY
WE WANTED IT TO BE,
BUT I'M AFRAID
WE HAVE NO CHOICE.
EVERYBODY GO OUT THERE
AND GIVE IT YOUR ALL!
TIMBERWOLVES,
WHAT ARE WE?
GO, TIMBERWOLVES!
Crowd:
GO, T'WOLVES!
WHERE'S BUDDY?
OH, DEAR. WE THOUGHT
HE MUST BE HERE.
OH, SWEETIE.
WE'LL GO FIND HIM.
YEAH. WE'LL FIND HIM.
LET'S GO.
Man: LET'S GO, WOLVES!
HA HA HA!
[SQUAWK]
[RRR]
HMM.
[GRR]
IT'S SIMPLE.
IF YOU WANT YOU
AND YOUR LITTLE FRIEND
TO GO FREE,
YOU JUST HAVE TO
COOPERATE. HMM.
[SQUAWK]
GO.
Girl: WAY TO GO,
ANDREA!
GOOD SERVE.
MINE. I GOT IT!
Girl: BLOCK IT!
Crowd: AWW.
Sheriff: IT'S ANOTHER
POINT FOR THE RATS,
WHO ARE LOOKING STRONG.
FOR YOU, THIS OUGHT
TO BE A CINCH.
ALL YOU GOT TO DO
IS GO TO THE OTHER
END OF THE TUNNEL
AND GET THE DIAMOND.
BUDDY? COME OUT,
COME OUT,
WHEREVER YOU ARE.
BUDDY, YOU HAVE
A GAME TO PLAY.
Girl: COVER!
[WHISTLE BLOWS]
Sheriff: THE TIMBERWOLVES
MISPLAY THAT ONE.
ONCE AGAIN, THE RATS
INCREASE THEIR LEAD.
[PANTING]
OH, HO, HO!
OH, YEAH!
Gordon: HA HA HA!
Doug:
COME ON, PUPPY.
ALMOST THERE.
[RRR]
SHH. SHH. SHH.
Doug: AHH, AHH.
AHH, AHH, AHH.
YES! WAY TO GO,
PUPPY!
CONGRATULATIONS.
VERY GOOD JOB.
I'M VERY PROUD
OF YOU.
Boy: MY BALL.
MY BALL!
I GOT IT!
OH!
Crowd: OHH!
YEAH! IN YOUR FACE!
Girl: NICE TRY.
GOOD ONE.
AWESOME.
[MUTTERING]
NOW, COME ON BACK
THROUGH THE LASERS,
BUT DON'T
TOUCH THEM.
OH. OHH. LATCH.
UH.
[LASER HUMMING]
[RRR]
[SQUAWK]
OHH.
UH.
[PANTING]
[RRR]
OK.
Boy: MY BALL!
MY BALL!
UNH!
Andrea: OHH!
Girl: NICE TRY,
ANDREA!
Sheriff: ANOTHER POINT
FOR THE RATS.
THIS IS
GETTING UGLY, FOLKS.
GOOD PUPPY-WUPPY.
HMM. NOW, BRING US
THE JEWEL.
[SQUAWK]
[RRR]
[LASER HUMMING]
COME ON.
Gordon:
YOU'RE ALMOST THERE.
OHH.
OH. DO--DO--NO.
Doug: JUST LIFT UP
THE TAIL A LITTLE BIT.
JUST, LIKE, 3 DEGREES.
[RRR]
SHH. SHH. SHH.
[SQUAWK]
MEOW. MEOW.
MEOW.
[SQUAWK]
[GORDON AND DOUG LAUGHING]
AHH.
[RRR]
COME ON.
AHA! AWW!
HA HA HA!
OHH!
Polly:
AHH! WHOO-HOO!
WE'RE BUSTED!
[WOOF]
UNH!
AAH!
OHH!
Girl: ANDREA!
Different girl:
IT'S YOURS!
Connor: I GOT IT!
Sheriff:
MATCH SCORE AGAIN.
FERNFIELD IS REALLY
MISSING BUDDY.
Man: HEY, LOOK!
THERE'S BUDDY!
AHH! AHH! AHH!
MOVE!
YEE-HA! HA HA HA!
[SCREAMING]
Mom: HELLO.
WE'RE HOME!
BUDDY!
Patrick: "SORRY
WE MISSED YOU.
MEET US AT THE BEACH.
LOVE GRAM."
THERE HE IS!
I'LL GET YOU!
OHH! OHH!
HE'S ON HERE
SOMEWHERE!
I'LL TAKE
THE GIRAFFE!
THE YELLOW CHOO-CHOO.
[RRR]
[GASP]
[BELL RINGS]
WHOA!
[CALLIOPE MUSIC PLAYING]
[TRAIN WHISTLE BLOWING]
OHH.
[HORN BLOWS]
UGH!
OHH!
AAH!
[WHISTLE BLOWS]
OHH! AAH!
AAH!
[RRR RRR]
AAH! COME ON!
[BURP]
AAH!
[BOTH SHOUTING]
UNH!
OHH!
[RRR]
OHH! OHH!
UNH!
UH.
[STOMACH GRUMBLING]
[RRR]
UH. EASY.
UH. UH. UH.
UH. OHH.
[BRAKES SQUEAK]
[WOOF]
Doug: THERE HE IS.
[BARK ECHOING]
OHH! UH.
OHH!
BUDDY?
[WOOF WOOF]
LOOK. THERE'S BUDDY!
[WOOF]
WHY ARE THEY
CHASING BUDDY?
WELL, WE'RE GONNA
FIND OUT, AREN'T WE?
[POLLY WHISTLES]
WAKEY, WAKEY.
WHOA. WHOA. AAH.
Phil on radio:
SHERIFF! SHERIFF!
EXCUSE ME.
GO FOR OFFICIAL BOB--
UH, GO FOR SHERIFF BOB.
SHERIFF!
THE DIAMOND!
Phil: THE JEWEL
OF ETERNITY!
IT'S BEEN STOLEN!
IT'S TWO GUYS
AND A DOG!
[BUDDY BARKING]
Andrea: BUDDY'S HERE!
Boy: HEY!
THERE HE IS!
I THINK I SEE THEM.
OVER.
OHH!
Sheriff: I'LL BE
A MONKEY'S UNCLE.
[GORDON AND DOUG MOANING]
THANKS, BUDDY.
[WHIMPERS]
UH, BUT, UH, UH.
OHH!
AAH!
HOLD IT RIGHT THERE,
YOU DADGUM CROOKS.
THEY GOT US
SURROUNDED.
WE SURRENDER!
OHH! OHH!
YOUR TRY IT!
YOU JUST TRY IT!
PLEASE STOP THE WORLD
FROM SPINNING.
GET IN THE CAR.
NO!
GET IN THE CAR!
GOOD JOB, BUDDY.
[WOOF]
NOW, IF I'M
NOT MISTAKEN,
YOU'VE GOT A GAME
TO WIN! COME ON!
OK, EVERYBODY.
BUDDY IS IN THE GAME!
[CROWD CHEERING]
GO, FERNFIELD!
Connor:
ALL RIGHT, BUDDY.
Sheriff:
GO GET THEM, BUDDY!
[WOOF]
POLLY!
Polly:
GRAM GRAM!
[RRR]
OH! HO HO HO!
OH, LOOK, NOAH.
HE CAME BACK.
I'M SO GLAD
TO SEE YOU.
OH, GRAM GRAM.
LET'S PLAY
SOME VOLLEYBALL!
[BLOWS WHISTLE]
SERVICE, TIMBERWOLVES!
IT'S MINE. BACK OFF.
IT'S MINE!
Girl: SET IT.
Boy: BLOCK IT.
UNH!
WHOO! YES!
HA HA!
Referee:
POINT, TIMBERWOLVES.
[WOOF]
[CROWD CHEERING]
WAY TO GO, BUDDY.
Girl: BUMP.
SET IT.
IT'S SHORT.
[WHISTLE BLOWS]
OH, YES!
Sheriff:
WOW. WHAT A GREAT SPIKE
BY CONNOR ON A GREAT SETUP
BY ANDREA.
TIMBERWOLVES ARE
CLAWING THEIR WAY
BACK INTO THE GAME.
OH, MOM, HI!
OH, YOU MADE IT!
HI!
MOM! DAD! HI!
AWW.
WERE YOU A GOOD BOY?
WE MISSED YOU.
YOU GOT HERE
JUST IN TIME!
Gram: ANDREA AND BUDDY
ARE DOING SO WELL.
Girl: GOOD SERVE.
I GOT IT!
NO. I GOT IT!
WHOO-HOO!
YES! WE COULD
STILL DO THIS.
YES!
[WOOF WOOF]
IT'S MINE.
I GOT IT.
GO UP.
BLOCK IT!
[WOOF WOOF]
AWW.
Sheriff:
WHAT A SPIKE.
Y'ALL, SHE PUT SOME MUSTARD
BEHIND THAT ONE.
Referee: SERVICE, RATS.
BRING IT ON.
[WOOF]
Girl: BUMP IT.
Connor: BUMP IT.
GOT IT!
I GOT IT!
[WHISTLE BLOWS]
[WOOF WOOF]
WHOO!
Girl: WAY TO GO,
CONNOR!
THAT'S WILD, MAN!
THAT'S WILD!
Girl: I GOT IT!
Boy: I GOT IT!
[WOOF]
Girl: GET IT!
[CROWD CHEERING]
YES!
Sheriff:
GREAT PLAY BY BUDDY.
MAN, THAT DOG IS
SOMETHING ELSE!
THIS IS IT, EVERYBODY.
GAME POINT!
[WHISTLE BLOWS]
THIS IS THE FINAL POINT.
Timberwolves:
HUDDLE, HUDDLE, HUDDLE.
OK, GUYS.
WE CAN DO THIS.
WE MADE IT THIS FAR.
WE CAN'T GIVE UP NOW.
WE WANT TO GO
TO CALIFORNIA, DON'T WE?
[BUDDY BARKS]
EXACTLY. SO COME ON.
GO, T'WOLVES!
OHH. THANK YOU.
[RRR RRR]
POINT!
AND THE TIMBERWOLVES WIN!
YEAH!
WHOO! YEAH!
YEAH! WE DID IT!
WHOO-HOO!
HA HA! HA HA!
OH, YEAH!
WHOO!
OH, YES!
[WOOF]
WELL, LOOKS LIKE
YOU DID IT.
YOU GET TO GO SEE
TAMMY AFTER ALL.
I COULDN'T HAVE DONE IT
WITHOUT YOU, CONNOR.
THANKS FOR EVERYTHING!
NO PROBLEM.
[BUDDY BARKS]
Andrea: WAY TO GO, BUDDY.
Y'ALL BETTER PACK
YOUR SUITCASES
AND GET READY FOR THAT TRIP
TO CALIFORNIA
FOR THE BEACH VOLLEYBALL
CHAMPIONSHIPS!
OH, HO! HOO!
LAST ONE IN'S
A ROTTEN EGG.
WHOO!
YAY!
AHH! POLLY!
[WOOF]
Connor: COME ON,
YOU GUYS.
Andrea: HEY, BUDDY!
WHOO!
YEAH!
HA HA HA!
COME HERE, NOAH.
HEY!
[WOOF]
Andrea: COME ON, BUDDY.
GET IN HERE. HEY!
HA HA! WHOO!
Man: WELCOME, FANS.
WE'RE HERE TODAY
TO WATCH
THE CHAMPIONSHIP ROUND
OF THE MALIBU BEACH
PROFESSIONAL INVITATIONAL
VOLLEYBALL TOURNAMENT.
I CANNOT BELIEVE THAT
YOU'RE REALLY HERE!
I KNOW!
NEITHER CAN I!
CAN WE DO THIS
EVERY SUMMER?
Announcer: GABBY REECE
AND HER PARTNER AIR BUD
ARE JUST MOMENTS AWAY
FROM VICTORY.
[CROWD CHEERING]
MY BALL.
[WOOF]
THAT BRINGS US
TO THE CHAMPIONSHIP POINT.
OK, BUDDY, GAME POINT.
LET'S GO.
[WOOF]
Crowd: NO!
[WOOF WOOF]
Andrea: ALL RIGHT,
BUDDY
YEAH! YEAH!
YEAH, BUDDY, WE WON.
GOOD JOB.
YOU DID GREAT.
YOU'RE AWESOME.
Andrea: BUDDY!
Coach:
WHOO! WHOO!
BUDDY! WHOO!
Announcer: AIR BUD
HAS DONE IT AGAIN!