*
- COME ON, BOY, LET'S GO.
LET'S GO, BUDDY.
COME ON.
ALL RIGHT.
GO.
HEY--OH!
UHH!
TAKE THE SHOT.
YEAH, GOOD BOY.
ALL RIGHT.
HYUH!
COME ON, BUDDY.
- GOOD SHOT.
GET IT.
LET'S GET IT.
OHH!
ALL RIGHT, BOY,
HERE'S MY ADVERSARY.
THIS IS GAME POINT.
LET'S GO.
- OH...
- OH, MAN, WE GOTTA GO, BOY.
- HEY, MOM,
SORRY WE'RE LATE.
- HI, JOSH!
- HI!
- STOP BRAGGING.
- GET YOUR COAT.
- SORRY, BUDDY, YOU CAN'T GO.
LOVE YOU. BYE.
WHY CAN'T BUDDY COME?
- OH, LET'S ZIP UP
YOUR COAT.
- ALL RIGHT, BOY, I'LL GIVE YOU
THE PLAY-BY-PLAY
WHEN I GET BACK,
ALL RIGHT?
- OKAY, BUCKLE UP.
- YES, COURSE I DO.
- TOO BAD BUDDY COULDN'T COME.
- UHH!
- GOT TICKETS HERE!
WHO NEEDS TICKETS?
I HAVE TICKETS.
LET'S GO HERE.
TICKETS! I GOT TICKETS.
- TICKETS HERE, COME ON.
- UHH! UHH!
- TICKETS!
I GOT TICKETS.
[game announcer
speaking indistinctly]
- UHH!
- MY DOG CAN SHOOT
BETTER THAN THAT!
- UH, YOU MEAN
LIKE THAT DOG OVER THERE?
- OH, NO!
DOG! COME HERE!
- OH!
- WHOA, WHOA, WHOA, WHOA!
- YEAH, A DOG!
- SORRY.
- UHH!
- OHH!
- HE'S OVER THERE!
- YO, YO, YO, GO!
- WHOA!
- GRAB HIM, GRAB HIM!
- SO...WHOA!
- THIS DOG'S GOT
A MEAN JUMP SHOT.
- THANKS...MR. BLUE.
- HEY, GUYS,
HOW ABOUT A PICTURE?
- HEY, TOM,
I GOT TO TAKE BUDDY
TO THE VET
AFTER SCHOOL TOMORROW.
IT'S KIND OF A TWO-MAN JOB.
- YOU CAN COUNT ON ME,
KEMO SABE.
- HELLO, BOYS!
both: HELLO, MS. SALTER.
- HEY, YOU KNOW WHAT
THE BEST THING
ABOUT THE EIGHTH GRADE IS?
- GIRLS HAVE TURNED
INTO WOMEN.
- HI, TAMMY.
SHE LIKES ME SO MUCH,
SHE'S SPEECHLESS.
YEAH, RIGHT.
- SHE'LL LIKE ME EVEN MORE
WHEN SHE SEES ME
IN A FOOTBALL UNIFORM.
WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
- WOMEN DIG FOOTBALL PLAYERS.
SO I'M GOING OUT
FOR THE TEAM.
- NO, I'VE BEEN...
WORKING OUT ALL SUMMER.
YEAH.
ANYWAY, TOM,
YOU CAN'T PLAY FOOTBALL.
I MEAN, YOU'RE
A BASKETBALL PLAYER.
- WELL, DEION SANDERS
PLAYED TWO SPORTS.
- JOSH...THEY'RE ALL
LOOKING AT US FUNNY.
YOU KNOW BUDDY
HATES THE VET.
- BUDDY.
COME ON, BUDDY.
SIT. GOOD.
- LET'S GO, BUDDY.
- I TAKE IT
HE'S A LITTLE NERVOUS?
- WHOA! GOT HIM!
- UHH!
- OHH.
- UH, HE'S TAKING
A YEAR'S SABBATICAL.
I'M FILLING IN.
MY NAME'S PATRICK SULLIVAN.
- HI, I'M JOSH.
AND THIS IS BUDDY.
- HELLO, BUDDY.
LOOK AT YOU.
WHAT A HANDSOME DOG.
GOOD DOG.
LET'S GET HIM
UP ON THE TABLE.
- ALL RIGHT.
COME ON, BOY.
HE DOESN'T REALLY
LIKE THE VET.
HE MIGHT NEED SOME HELP.
- COME ON, BOY.
- WELL.
- OKAY.
GOOD.
OKAY, OKAY.
HOLD STILL.
- JUST MAKING SURE
EVERYTHING'S IN PLACE.
SPINAL COLUMN FEELS RIGHT.
NO SLIPPED DISCS.
MUSCLE TONE'S GOOD.
YEAH, YOUR DOG
COULD RUN A MARATHON.
- OR PLAY BASKETBALL.
UHH!
THAT'S A GOOD ONE.
- HMM.
- OH, LOOKS LIKE BUDDY'S DUE
FOR HIS DISTEMPER SHOT.
- OH, UH, YOU MIGHT
WANT TO USE THE STRAPS.
BUDDY'S NOT VERY GOOD
WITH NEEDLES.
- OH, I DON'T THINK
HE'S GOING ANYWHERE.
- UH...ALL RIGHT.
IF YOU SAY SO.
IT'S NOTHING
TO BE AFRAID OF.
- OHH.
UGH. OH!
UH, I'M OKAY.
- LET'S TRY IT AGAIN.
HELLO, CHILDREN,
AND WELCOME TO NATALYA'S
AMAZING AND STUPENDOUS
ANIMAL CIRCUS.
SHOW ME THE MONEY.
- ONE MORE TIME.
HELLO, CHILDREN,
AND WELCOME TO NATALYA'S--
- I'M BACK,
MY LITTLE MACKEREL.
- AHH!
parrot:
I'M KING OF THE WORLD!
- IDIOT!
HOW MANY TIMES
DO I HAVE TO TELL YOU?
NEVER INTERRUPT ME WHEN I AM
THROTTLING A PERFORMER!
- SORRY, NATALYA.
- AND THIS PLACE STINKS
LIKE FISHES!
- IT'S ALL I COULD FIND
ON OUR BUDGET.
BUT LOOK, I BROUGHT YOU
THE AMAZING MORTIMER.
- WHAT IS SO AMAZING
ABOUT HIM?
- WATCH THIS.
- OOH!
- SO...WE GO BACK
TO RUSSIA NOW?
- NO! MY CIRCUS
IS NOT COMPLETE!
WE STILL NEED TO FIND
A MAIN ATTRACTION!
male newscaster:
THERE HAS BEEN ANOTHER
IN A SERIES
OF ANIMAL ABDUCTIONS.
A PRIZED CHIMPANZEE
WAS STOLEN FROM A HOME
IN DOWNTOWN SEATTLE.
POLICE ARE BAFFLED
AS TO THE MOTIVE.
ALL RIGHT, TIME NOW
FOR SOMETHING SPECIAL.
- NUMBER ONE CIRCUS IN RUSSIA.
DO YOU KNOW WHY?
BECAUSE OF THIS!
- MAKE WAY FOR AIR BUD,
THE NEWEST TOP DOG
IN BASKETBALL.
- WE HAVE TO FIND
THE PERFECT CREATURE!
- STOLE HIS WAY
ONTO THE COURT
AND INTO
OUR PLAY OF THE WEEK.
TAKE A LOOK.
HE'S GOOD.
WHAT DO YOU THINK,
MORTIMER, HUH?
OH, DA!
- WE HAVE FOUND
OUR MAIN ATTRACTION.
- FOOD, YES.
THERE WE GO.
GOT THIS.
- STARVING.
SO, UH, WHO WAS THAT
ON THE PHONE?
- OH, THAT WAS, UM...
JUST A GUY FROM WORK.
HERB.
- OH.
WHAT DID HE WANT?
- WELL, HE WANTED TO KNOW
IF HE COULD
TAKE ME TO THE MOVIES.
SO IT'S A DATE.
DOESN'T...WEIRD YOU OUT?
- NO.
DOESN'T MATTER.
YOU SHOULD
GO ON A DATE, MOM.
- OH, MAYONNAISE.
- HEY!
BUDDY.
- SO, UH, YOU MUST BE 'ERB.
I'M JOSH.
IT'S, UH, H-ERB.
SEE?
OHH.
DO YOU HAVE A, UH...
CAT?
- UM, NO, BUT I HAVE A DOG.
COME HERE, BUDDY.
HEY, COME HERE, BOY.
OHH.
OH.
AAH!
OHH. OHH.
BYE, 'ERB.
- UM...WELL,
HE KIND OF HAD TO RUN, SO...
- THESE ARE FOR YOU.
SO...YOU'RE RICHARD.
- THAT'S RIGHT.
I'M IN LEGAL.
- OH, MY.
I MUST BE
IN THE WRONG HOUSE.
I WAS EXPECTING JACKIE FRAMM,
NOT CINDY CRAWFORD.
- HEH HEH.
- AHEM.
- I DON'T KNOW.
YOU KNOW, I'M NOT JUST
THINKING ABOUT MYSELF.
I'M ALSO THINKING
ABOUT JOSH AND ANDREA.
MAYBE IT'S TOO SOON
FOR ME TO BE DATING.
DO YOU THINK IT'S TOO SOON?
MAYBE I'M JUST NOT MEANT
TO FALL IN LOVE AGAIN.
- OHH OHH!
OHH...
BUDDY, IT'S A RAMP.
IT'S A RAMP, STOP IT!
BUDDYYYY!
- BUDDY...BUDDY!
LOOK OUUUUT!
- AHH! HEY!
- SORRY!
BUDDY, DID YOU SEE
WHAT YOU JUST DID?
BUD--BUDDY...
AAAAH!
NO! STOP!
LOOK OUUUUT!
OOF!
- UHH!
- UM, MOM...
HI, SWEETIE.
- SO...WHERE'S THIS VET
TAKING YOU?
- I DON'T KNOW.
HE WANTS TO SURPRISE ME.
- HMM.
SO, UH, WHAT TIME
ARE YOU PLANNING TO BE HOME?
- WHA--
NOW, WHEN DID YOU
BECOME THE MOM
AND ME THE ADOLESCENT?
- OH...SORRY.
- JOSH, BE NICE.
- HI.
WOW, YOU LOOK BEAUTIFUL.
- OH, YOU LOOK...RUMPLED.
- OH, YEAH.
I, UH, LEFT MY IRON
IN SAN DIEGO.
- BETTER THAN LEAVING
YOUR HEART IN SAN FRANCISCO.
- HEY, THERE HE IS.
HI, BUDDY.
- HI, ANDREA.
WHOA.
- HI, PATRICK.
- HEY, JOSH.
- HEY, DR. SULLIVAN.
- HEY, I HEARD
YOU WERE INTO SPORTS.
GOT YOU SOMETHING.
- OH.
- I STARTED PLAYING
WHEN I WAS ABOUT YOUR AGE.
- GEE, THANKS.
- UM, WELL, NO, ACTUALLY.
BASKETBALL
IS KIND OF MY SPORT.
BUT THANKS.
IT'S--IT'S NICE.
- WELL, I GUESS
WE BETTER GO.
UH, JOSH,
NO TV AFTER 9:00.
AND I'VE WRITTEN DOWN
MRS. CLUMSKY'S PHONE NUMBER
ON THE PAD
RIGHT BESIDE THE--
- I KNOW, MOM.
- OKAY.
ALL RIGHT, I LOVE YOU GUYS.
BYE, SWEETIE.
- GOOD TO SEE YOU
AGAIN, JOSH.
- YEAH, GOOD TO SEE YOU TOO.
- OH, JOSH, YOU LEFT
THE GARAGE OPEN.
- OH, SORRY.
LET'S GO, BOY.
COME ON.
- ALL RIGHT.
OHH!
HOW DID THIS GET IN HERE?
[Oh, Where Has My Little Dog
Gone playing]
*
- I TOLD YOU TO GET
PLAIN WHITE TRUCK,
NOT MUSICAL TRUCK.
- IT WAS GOOD DEAL.
IT CAME WITH ALL
THE ICE CREAM YOU COULD EAT.
- AAH!
- UNH!
- STUPID BOY AND DOG.
WAIT A MINUTE!
- UNH!
- THAT WAS OUR BOY AND DOG!
- OH, NATALYA!
OHH. OOF!
- THEY'VE BEEN ON FOUR DATES
ALREADY.
YOU KNOW WHAT HAPPENS
AFTER FOUR DATES, DON'T YOU?
- SPEED DIAL.
- YEAH.
IF HIS NUMBER'S BEEN
PROGRAMMED INTO YOUR SPEED DIAL,
YOU MIGHT AS WELL GO SHOPPING
FOR YOUR TUXEDO.
- AH.
- WHEN DOGGY GETS CLOSE,
WE NAB HIM WITH NET.
GOT IT.
NAB HIM WITH NET.
- IT WILL BE PIECE OF PIE.
- AND IF HE BUYS YOU A GIFT...
HE'S TRYING TO BRIBE YOU.
- CALL HIM DAD.
NICE.
- OOF!
- OH, MY! OH, MY!
both: WHOA!
- HEY, CHECK THE SPEED DIAL.
- HEY, JOSH,
YOU GOT A GREAT ARM.
- I'M NOT GOING OUT
FOR THE TEAM, TOM.
woman:
FERNFIELD NAPKIN FACTORY.
HOW MAY I DIRECT YOUR--
- OH! SORRY.
WRONG NUMBER.
- WOULD YOU JUST
THINK ABOUT IT?
- NO.
- THIS IS REALLY HEAVY.
- DON'T HURT YOURSELF.
- MOMMY, CAN I HELP YOU
WITH THE GAZEBO?
- OH. OH, SORRY.
GRANDMA, WRONG NUMBER.
UM, IT'S JOSH.
LOVE YOU. BYE.
HE COMES HERE
EVERY AFTERNOON.
- WELL, YOU KNOW,
FOOTBALL PRACTICE
IS EVERY AFTERNOON.
- HMM.
HE'S HELPING MY MOM
BUILD THE GAZEBO.
- I FEEL LIKE A WHOLE NEW MAN.
- OHH.
THAT'S WORSE
THAN SPEED DIAL, BUDDY.
- HI, THIS IS PATRICK.
LEAVE A MESSAGE
AFTER THE BEEP.
- WHEN'S THE NEXT
FOOTBALL PRACTICE?
- TOUCHDOWN.
- UHH!
- THAT'S IT, ON THE BREAK!
cheerleaders: WHEN I SAY
BOOGIE, YOU SAY DOWN!
- UHH! OHH!
- UH! OH! UHH!
- RRR!
- HOLD! TAKE FIVE.
LOW, REMEMBER?
- UH--
- USE THOSE LEGS!
GET UNDERNEATH THEM.
- UH, EXCUSE--
EXCUSE US, COACH FANELLI.
- HI, I'M TOM; HE'S JOSH.
- AH, HI.
- WE WERE WONDERING
IF YOU STILL GOT ROOM
FOR A COUPLE MORE PLAYERS?
- I ALWAYS GOT ROOM
FOR PLAYERS ON MY TEAM.
WHAT POSITIONS
DO YOU PLAY?
- I'M WIDE RECEPTOR.
- RECEIVER.
- UH, YEAH.
AND YOU?
- OH, WELL, I'M--
I MEAN, WHATEVER.
YOU KNOW, I COULD...
- HE'S A QUARTERBACK.
HE'S GOT A KILLER ARM.
LET'S SEE.
- UH, HERE, TOM.
HERE.
YOU, UH, PUT THIS ON.
GO AHEAD, GO DEEP.
TOWARD THE END ZONE, DEEP.
COME ON, LET'S SEE
THAT KILLER ARM.
- LOOK OUT.
ALL RIGHT, HURRY UP.
- OHH!
- OHH. OH.
MR. RECEPTOR
WILL FIT RIGHT IN.
- YEAH.
- NICE ARM.
- THANKS.
- YOU KNOW, I COULD USE
A BACKUP QUARTERBACK.
- YOU BACK UP
COLE POWERS OVER THERE.
HE'S THE HOTTEST QUARTERBACK
IN THE LEAGUE RIGHT NOW.
YOU MIGHT NOT GET
MUCH PLAYING TIME.
- OH, THAT'S OKAY.
MY PRACTICES ARE NO PICNIC.
CAPISCE?
- WELL, YEAH,
I THINK I CAN HANDLE IT.
- OKAY, ALL RIGHT, COME ON.
ONCE AROUND THE FIELD,
FULL LAP.
GO.
- GO 'HEAD, NOW.
GO, GO! COME ON.
GO! HIT IT!
LET'S GO!
EXTEND! EXTEND!
- OH, I GOT A HEADACHE.
- OH! OH, OH.
- OHH! I GOT HIM!
- WATCH IT.
HEY, WATCH IT!
- UHH! OHH.
- UHH!
- UHH.
- HEY, TAMMY.
OW!
OHH!
Andrea: WOULD YOU LIKE
SOME MORE TEA, BUDDY?
- WHEW.
- HI.
OKAY.
- UHH!
- WHAT A MESS.
- OKAY.
ALL RIGHT.
OHH!
- OW.
- YOU JOINED
THE FOOTBALL TEAM?
- YEAH.
YEAH, I LOVE FOOTBALL.
- UM, WELL, SINCE, UH...
SINCE I, UH...
- HMM...
- TALKED TO, UM...
- I'LL, UH...
PUT THIS IN THE WASH.
OKAY.
- BRING DOWN YOUR PANTS TOO.
- ALL RIGHT.
MY...PANTS.
HEY, BOY.
OH, NOT NOW, BOY.
MY HEAD HURTS.
- IT'S OKAY.
- IT'S NEVER GONNA WORK,
TOM, I JUST KNOW IT.
- TRAVELING DOCTORS ARE WORSE
THAN TRAVELING SALESMEN.
HE'S PROBABLY GOT A WOMAN
AT EVERY PORT.
OKAY, WELL, JUST GO IN THERE
AND CHECK IT OUT, ALL RIGHT?
- WHATEVER.
- WHAT SEEMS
TO BE THE TROUBLE?
- HIS HIP BONE.
- HIS TAIL BONE.
- H-HIS TAIL.
YOU KNOW...
THE BONE IN HIS TAIL.
- YEAH, YOU KNOW, HIS TAIL,
IT JUST HASN'T BEEN ITSELF
LATELY, YOU KNOW.
- MM, YOU KNOW, NO WAG.
- WELL, YEAH, I MEAN,
THERE'S SOMETHING WRONG
WITH THE TAIL THAT DOESN'T WAG.
- YEAH, EXACTLY.
- YEAH, SO, UH...
OH, UM...
WELL, YOU SEE, TOM AND I
KIND OF FIGURED OUT
THAT--THAT IT ONLY WAGS
WHEN HE'S LYING DOWN AND...
- NOT WHEN HE'S STANDING,
YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN?
- HMM.
WELL, IT, UH,
LOOKS FINE TO ME.
BUT IF IT'LL MAKE YOU BOYS
FEEL BETTER,
WE'LL GET IT X-RAYED
JUST TO MAKE SURE.
- OH, GREAT.
- GOOD IDEA.
- COME ON, BUDDY.
I'LL BE RIGHT BACK.
- THANK YOU.
- YEP.
- TOM, I DON'T FEEL
RIGHT ABOUT THIS.
I MEAN, WHAT ARE YOU
LOOKING FOR, ANYWAYS?
- ANYTHING THAT'LL SHOW
THAT THIS GUY'S
A ROAMING ROMEO.
- COME ON, TOM.
I MEAN,
THIS IS A WASTE OF TIME.
I MEAN, HE'S GONNA CATCH US.
LET'S GO, ALL RIGHT?
- WAIT, WAIT, WHOA.
WAIT A MINUTE.
WAIT, WAIT, WAIT.
GOT IT.
- COME ON, BUDDY.
- BUDDY'S TAIL
CHECKS OUT JUST FINE.
- OH, THAT'S GREAT.
THAT'S--THAT'S JUST GREAT.
THANKS.
- COME ON, BUDDY.
- THANKS, DR. SULLIVAN.
- PATRICK.
YOU CAN CALL ME...
- OKAY, THANKS.
- WHAT HAVE I
GOT MYSELF INTO?
STOP IT, BOY.
BUDDY!
STOP IT.
I DON'T WANT TO PLAY.
BUDDY...
- OH, MAN!
YOU CAN PLAY FOOTBALL.
HEH. HOLY COW.
GO! GO, BOY. GO!
UHH!
HEY, BOY.
HEY.
BRING THAT BACK.
HEY! BUDDY...
[Buddy growling
and barking playfully]
HEY!
AH, GET OFF ME.
BUDDY.
GOOD CATCH!
BRING IT, BOY.
COME ON, BRING IT.
HEY, GIVE IT.
HEY! UHH!
COME HERE.
COME HERE, BOY.
HERE, BOY, HERE YOU GO.
I'M READY FOR MY FIRST GAME,
ALL RIGHT?
I KNOW, I WISH
YOU COULD PLAY TOO, BUDDY
MISS YOU. BYE-BYE.
- I'VE BEEN A VOLUNTEER COACH
FOR 14 YEARS.
- I NEARLY BLEW A GASKET
ABOUT IT, JIMMY,
BUT THE SCHOOL BOARD ISN'T
BUDGING ON THIS ONE.
THEY'RE ALL MOANING
THAT YOU HAVEN'T HAD
A WINNING SEASON
IN TEN YEARS.
ATTENDANCE IS DOWN,
AND THE FOOTBALL PROGRAM
IS EXPENSIVE.
- WINNING ISN'T WHAT KIDS'
FOOTBALL IS ALL ABOUT.
- I KNOW.
THE SCHOOL BOARD
GAVE ME A CHOICE.
AT THE END OF THE SEASON,
I CAN EITHER DROP
THE FOOTBALL PROGRAM...
- THERE'S NOT EVEN AN OUNCE OF--
- OR...
I, UH, LET YOU GO.
I'M SORRY, IT'S JUST...
IT'S OUT OF MY HANDS.
Salter: ALL RIGHT, GIRLS,
COME ON!
MORE AROUND YOU.
COME ON, KICK IT!
- WEEBLE.
YOU FORGOT SOMETHING.
- OH...THANKS, GOOSE.
- YOU'RE WELCOME.
- UHH!
- JEEZ, YOU LOOK LIKE
YOU'VE SEEN A GHOST.
WHAT'S WRONG,
YOU GOT BUTTERFLIES?
- TOM, WHY WOULD I HAVE
BUTTERFLIES?
I'M A BENCHWARMER,
REMEMBER?
- WHEW.
- ALL RIGHT, COME ON.
LET'S GET OUT THERE AND WIN
THIS ONE FOR THE HOME TEAM!
all: YEAH!
- LET'S WIN!
- RAZZLE DAZZLE.
- YEAH, RIGHT, TOM.
- HEY, LET'S GO.
- YEAH, SURE, COACH.
- WELCOME, EVERYONE,
TO THE OPENING GAME
OF THE FERNFIELD JUNIOR HIGH
FOOTBALL TEAM!
- HYUH!
- AAH!
UHH!
- COME ON!
- UHH!
cheerleaders: WHEN I SAY GO,
YOU SAY FIGHT!
- OHH. EW.
- WAY TO GO, BABY!
WE GOT 'EM!
NOW LET'S KNOCK IT BACK!
AND LET'S HIT SOMEBODY,
ALL RIGHT?
cheerleaders: BOOGIE DOWN!
* GO, FIGHT, WIN TONIGHT
* BOOGIE ON DOWN,
ALL RIGHT, ALL RIGHT *
* GO, FIGHT, WIN TONIGHT
* BOOGIE ON DOWN,
ALL RIGHT, ALL RIGHT *
- ALL RIGHT.
[playing She'll Be
Coming Round the Mountain]
- REMEMBER,
WE GO INTO BACKYARD.
WE GRAB POOCH.
THEN WE MAKE LIKE BANANA
AND PEEL.
- YOU MEAN SPLIT.
- HELLO, I'D LIKE
AN ICE CREAM BAR.
AND MY SISTER WOULD LIKE
A CHOCOLATE SWIRL.
- WE'RE ALL OUT
OF CHOCOLATE SWIRLS.
BUT, UM, WE HAVE FUDGE STICK
WITH CANDY SPRINKLES.
- WE HAVE NO SPRINKLES.
GO AWAY!
IDIOT!
DID YOU HEAR SOMETHING?
HUH?
WE FOLLOW!
- AH!
- YEAH, TOM, YEAH, TOM.
YEAH, YEAH, TOM, YEAH!
GONNA BE A LONG SEASON.
[She'll Be Coming Round
the Mountain playing]
boy: WHOA! HE'S TURNING!
- WE WANT ICE CREAM, COME ON!
- FASTER!
- COME ON!
Salter: PAUL'S GOT IT!
HE'D RUNNING WITH IT!
- LET'S GO!
YES, BABY!
YES!
Salter: RUN, PAUL!
RUN!
YES! RUN!
YES! YES! YES!
GOOD JOB!
- YES! YES!
- AH, IT'S OVER!
Fanelli: THAT'S RIGHT! HEY!
- THERE HE IS.
*
- STOP THE TRUCK! OOF!
- LET'S GO.
- AGH! STOP HIM.
- HURRY, HURRY!
HURRY, HE'S GETTING AWAY!
- AH, WE GOT HIM NOW!
- OH, I'VE HAD IT!
THAT'S IT!
PEOPLE! KIDS! DOGS!
YOU IDIOTS!
I'M SICK AND TIRED OF EVERYBODY
RUNNING THROUGH MY YARD!
- OW!
- YOU'RE RUINING MY GARDEN!
- AAH!
- STOP!
- OH, HE'S GETTING AWAY!
- STOP HIM!
Salter: HIGH SNAP!
COLE'S PICKED IT UP!
HE'S RUNNING!
HE'S AT THE 30!
40!
- OH, NO.
- OH, NO, COLE'S DOWN!
NATE, MARLON, COME HERE!
- COME ON, COLE.
COME ON, BUDDY! GET UP!
Salter: GRACIOUS.
COLE IS HURT.
- IT'S ALL RIGHT.
Salter: IS HE ALL RIGHT?
- IT'S ALL RIGHT, COLE.
GOOD WORK.
COME ON, GIVE IT UP, GUYS!
GOOD WORK, COLE!
- WATCH IT.
- THAT A BOY!
- ALL RIGHT, TAKE HIM RIGHT
INTO THE TRAINERS.
YOU'LL BE ALL RIGHT, SON.
JUST HOLD IT STILL.
ALL RIGHT,
HE'LL BE ALL RIGHT.
POWELL'S GOT
A DISLOCATED SHOULDER.
PUDGE.
- HE--HE CAN PLAY WITH THAT,
THOUGH, RIGHT COACH?
- I'M AFRAID NOT, SON.
JOSH, YOU'RE GONNA BE FINE.
ALL RIGHT, COME ON.
GET IN THERE.
COME ON, OPEN UP
WITH B-52, GO!
- THERE GOES OUR SHOT
AT A WINNING SEASON.
- GIVE HIM TIME.
HE'LL BE FINE.
- HEY, JOSH IS GOING IN!
Salter: IT, UH,
LOOKS LIKE JOSH BROWN,
NUMBER EIGHT, IS STEPPING IN
TO TAKE THE HELM.
BREAK A LEG!
- CALL--GOOD QUESTION.
- OH, WE'RE GONNA DIE.
- GIVE HIM A BREAK.
- ALL RIGHT, B-52.
BREAK!
all: BREAK!
- CROSSING PATTERN, DEEP.
- ALL RIGHT! READY!
B-52! DOWN!
- JOSH, OVER HERE.
- OH.
ALL RIGHT!
- B-52!
READY! GO!
SET! HIKE, HIKE!
- HE'S OPEN!
HE'S OPEN!
- I'M WIDE OPEN!
UHH!
- UHH.
- OH, DEAR!
- AY.
- GREAT.
OHH.
- HANG IN THERE, DEFENSE!
HANG IN THERE!
[cheerleaders
chanting indistinctly]
COME ON.
IT AIN'T THE END OF THE WORLD.
COME ON, PUT ONE UP
ON THESE CLOWNS.
YOU'RE THE MAN, JOSH!
- ALL RIGHT, GUYS,
LET'S TRY B-52 AGAIN.
TRUST ME,
IT'LL WORK THIS TIME.
READY?
- BREAK!
- 52!
- SET! HIKE!
- HE'S OPEN!
HE'S OPEN!
Salter: JOSH IS GOING ON!
Salter: AND IT'S
A PERFECT PASS!
RIGHT TO...A DOG!
- BUDDY.
THERE IS A DOG
ON THE FIELD.
AND HE'S DOING A LOT BETTER
THAN THE TROJANS!
- UHH!
- WHOA!
Salter: AND TOUCHDOWN!
- YES!
- SO THAT'S THE FAMOUS
AIR BUD, HUH?
AMAZING DOG.
GREAT FORM.
HE REMINDS ME A LOT
OF FRED BILETNIKOFF.
EXCEPT HE'S BETTER LOOKING
THAN FRED.
YOU ALL RIGHT?
YOU KNOW, YOU GOT A GREAT ARM
ON YOU OUT THERE, SON,
BUT...IT'S LIKE
YOU'RE PLAYING
FOR ALL THE WRONG REASONS.
FOOTBALL'S ALL ABOUT
HAVING FUN.
THAT'S GOT TO BE
YOUR BOTTOM LINE, JOSH.
COME ON.
SEE YA.
- I KNOW YOU WANT
TO PLAY ON THE TEAM, BOY.
BUT YOU JUST CAN'T,
YOU KNOW?
'CAUSE FOOTBALL'S
NOT LIKE BASKETBALL.
'CAUSE YOU MIGHT GET HURT,
AND I DON'T WANT YOU
TO GET HURT, DO IT?
AND YOU GOT TO WEAR EQUIPMENT
AND A HELMET.
I KNOW IT'S NOT FAIR.
- HEY, BOY.
PERFECT.
BOY, TRY THIS ON.
UHH.
- COME ON, GUYS, COME ON.
GUY, COME ON, MOVE IT.
COME ON, GUYS,
MEET ME HALFWAY HERE.
STOP. WE GOT A LOT OF WORK
TO DO HERE.
- GOT A NEW WIDE RECEPTOR
FOR YOU.
- WHAT IS THIS,
SOME KIND OF A JOKE?
- WELL, NO.
I MEAN, LIKE YOU SAID,
THERE'S ALWAYS
ROOM ON YOUR TEAM
FOR A COUPLE MORE PLAYERS.
- COME ON,
DOGS DON'T PLAY FOOTBALL.
- YEAH, THEY DON'T PLAY
BASKETBALL EITHER, RIGHT?
- COME ON, COACH,
WE'LL BE THE LAUGHING STOCK
OF THE LEAGUE.
- HAVE YOU ALL FORGOTTEN
WE'VE BEEN THE LAUGHING STOCK
OF THE LEAGUE
FOR THE LAST DECADE?
- ALL RIGHT, ALL RIGHT.
FELLAS, FELLAS, FELLAS.
COME ON, WHOA, WHOA.
QUIET DOWN HERE, COME ON.
WHY ARE YOU
DOING THIS, JOSH?
- READY TO HAVE
SOME FUN, COACH.
BOTTOM LINE.
- ALL RIGHT.
LET'S SEE WHAT THIS POOCH
IS MADE OF.
- GO, SET!
HIKE, HIKE!
- UP, DOWN.
KICKERS TOO, JUAN.
NO KNEES, WEEBLE.
UP, DOW--
THAT'S THE WAY
TO DO IT, BOYS.
- YEAH!
- I'LL TELL YOU
ONE THING, BOYS.
THAT AIN'T
NO GOLDEN RETRIEVER.
THAT THERE
IS A GOLDEN RECEIVER.
HEY HEY, THERE HE IS.
SAY HELLO
TO YOUR NEW TEAMMATE, FELLAS.
* OR THE LAND
* OF THE FREE
* AND THE
* HOME
* OF THE
* BRAVE
*
- ALL RIGHT, COME ON, NOW.
LET'S GO, LET'S GO.
COME ON.
- THAT'S IT.
GOOD BOY.
- RAMS!
- UHH!
WE'RE GONNA KICK
SOME RAM BUTT TODAY.
I CAN FEEL IT.
- AAH!
UHH!
- SINCE WHEN ARE YOU
MR. CONFIDENT?
- SINCE I GOT MY HANDS
ON A GENUINE
JERRY RICE NOSE SPREADER.
- COME ON, NOW.
HIT SOMEBODY OUT THERE.
- OKAY, COACH.
NO PROBLEM.
- I DON'T WANT TO SEE A GREEN
SHIRT STANDING, ALL RIGHT?
LET'S GO, OFFENSE!
ALL RIGHT, JOSH.
YOU KNOW WHAT TO DO.
- HEY, BUDDY,
JUST LIKE WE PRACTICED.
LET'S GO.
COME ON.
Salter: KICK IT, GIRLS!
WHAT'S YOUR FAVORITE COLOR?
NAVY BLUE AND GOLD!
cheerleaders:
BLUE AND GOLD!
WHAT'S YOUR FAVORITE COLOR?
NAVY BLUE AND GOLD!
- ALL RIGHT, GUYS, B-52,
ON TWO.
man: OH, THAT'S SO CUTE!
team: BREAK!
- ALL RIGHT!
- B! 52!
DOWN! SET!
HIKE, HIKE!
- UHH!
- YEAH!
- WAH!
- LET'S DO RED 48,
ALL RIGHT?
ON TWO.
- HYUH!
- LET'S DO G-28 ON TWO,
ALL RIGHT?
- READY!
all: BREAK!
- GO! "K"! HIKE!
- HEY!
- UHH!
- OH...OH!
- AHH...OH, AH!
- DOES ANYBODY ON THIS TEAM
WANNA PLAY FOOTBALL? OHH!
COME ON, GET HIM!
CUT OFF THE ANGLE!
COME ON, TAKE OUT HIS PAWS!
DOG PILE HIM!
all: DOG PILE HIM!
- DOG PILE HIM!
DOG PILE HIM!
DOG PILE!
AAH!
ALL RIGHT!
YEAH!
- BUDDY!
- UHH!
- GET OFF OF HIM!
- MOVE! GET OFF!
GET OFF NOW!
AWW!
- THAT IS ONE
TALENTED DOG.
YOU'RE DOING FINE TOO, JOSH,
YOU KNOW?
YOU JUST NEED TO...
FACE UP TO THE PRESSURE.
NOT DESERT THE POCKET
TOO EARLY.
- I FOUND THESE
IN YOUR OFFICE.
WHO ARE THEY?
- WELL...
THAT'S LAURA.
SHE LIVES IN SEATTLE.
AND THAT'S GAIL.
SHE'S IN SANTA FE.
AND THE PRETTY ONE
WITH THE RED HAIR,
THAT'S SHANNON MARIE.
SHE'S IN BOSTON.
- SO...
- AND THIS IS A PICTURE
OF THE WHOLE SULLIVAN CLAN.
SEE, THERE'S MOM AND DAD
AND ME AND...
- YOUR THREE SISTERS.
- YOU KNOW, JOSH,
I THINK WE COULD BE FRIENDS.
FIRST, WE GOT TO LEARN
TO TRUST EACH OTHER.
"BROKEN TAIL."
- OH, PATRICK,
THIS IS SO ROMANTIC.
- IF I DIDN'T HAVE
TO FIX THE ENGINE,
WE COULD HAVE BEEN...
- NO, I THINK
THIS IS PERFECT.
- WELL...
I'VE BEEN OFFERED
A PERMANENT JOB IN SAN DIEGO.
BUT...I DON'T KNOW
IF I'M GOING TO ACCEPT IT.
- OH.
I-I DON'T WANT TO COMPLICATE
THINGS FOR YOU.
BUT I WILL,
IF YOU INSIST.
- I THINK JOSH WOULD BE
VERY HAPPY
TO SEE ME LEAVE TOWN.
- WELL, IN LIEU OF GROWING
FUR AND A TAIL,
FOR NOW...
JUST BE HIS FRIEND.
- ALL RIGHT, GIVE ME HANDS!
GIVE ME HANDS!
HOW WE GONNA PLAY?
- ROUGH! ROUGH! ROUGH!
- LET'S GET 'EM!
- UHH!
- 25! DOWN!
SET! HUT!
- YES!
- SO YOU RUN X-CURL,
AND BUDDY
IN THE DEEP FLY PATTERN.
STRAIGHT UP THE MIDDLE.
BETTER KNOWN
AS THE CANINE KNOCKOUT.
THIS IS THE ONE
FOR ALL THE MARBLES.
AFTER THAT, I WANT TO DO
A COUPLE OF MOTION THINGS.
- YES!
- YES! YES!
YES! YES!
COME HERE, PUDGY!
YEAH! WE DID IT,
LITTLE GUY, WE DID IT!
- WHEN JOSH THREW THAT PASS
TO BUDDY
AND HE SCORED THE HOMERUN,
THOUGHT I WAS GONNA
HAVE A HEART ATTACK.
- TOUCHDOWN.
- OH, FOOTBALL IS SO DRAMATIC.
YEAH.
HMM.
- I'VE COME TO A DECISION
ABOUT THAT CONSULTING JOB
IN SAN DIEGO.
- YOU'RE GONNA ACCEPT IT.
- ONLY IF YOU DON'T
ACCEPT THIS.
OHH.
PATRICK.
- NOTHING.
I MADE YOU A CAKE.
SHAPED LIKE A FOOTBALL.
ISN'T IT CUTE?
JOSH, PLEASE.
NO, BUDDY.
YOU CAN'T COME.
I MEAN IT, BUDDY, STAY.
- WAY TO GO, NATALYA!
*
- IT'S JACKIE FRAMM.
UH, JOSH HAS RUN AWAY.
IS HE THERE WITH YOU?
- JOSH ISN'T
AT TOM'S HOUSE.
UH, I'LL TRY
COACH FANELLI.
- THIS IS ALL MY FAULT.
- TRAIN NUMBER 14
FROM PORTLAND
IS DELAYED 20 MINUTES
AND WILL BE ARRIVING
ON TRACK TWO.
THAT'S TRAIN NUMBER 14
FROM PORTLAND
ARRIVE 20 MINUTES LATE
ON TRACK TWO.
- YOU KNOW WHAT I HATE MOST
ABOUT TRAIN STATION FOOD?
THERE'S NOTHING
EVEN REMOTELY ITALIAN
ABOUT THE ITALIAN SUBS.
- OH, HI, COACH FANELLI.
YOU MIND IF I GRAB SOME WOOD?
- SURE.
- EH...I RAN AWAY
MORE THAN A FEW TIMES
WHEN I WAS YOUR AGE.
USUALLY,
I GOT ABOUT THIS FAR.
- HMM.
I'M LEAVING.
- SAN FRANCISCO.
- BOY, MY STAR QUARTERBACK
IS WILLING TO PASS UP
THE STATE CHAMPIONSHIP GAME
THIS AFTERNOON,
IT MUST SOMETHING
PRETTY SERIOUS.
- HMM.
- NOPE.
- IT WOULDN'T HAVE
ANYTHING TO DO
WITH THE NEW MAN IN YOUR MOM'S
LIFE, NOW, WOULD IT?
WOULD IT?
- HE'S NOT MY DAD,
ALL RIGHT?
- NO, I GUESS HE ISN'T.
AND YOU LOVED YOUR FATHER
VERY MUCH.
AHEM, SO...
SO WHERE YOU HEADING
AFTER FOOTBALL SEASON?
- I'M RUNNING AWAY,
REMEMBER?
- YEAH, I KNOW, WELL,
I MEAN, THEORETICALLY,
YOU KNOW, IF YOU WEREN'T
RUNNING AWAY,
WHAT WOULD YOU BE DOING?
- I DON'T KNOW.
PROBABLY PLAY BASKETBALL
OR SOMETHING.
- HMM.
WELL,
I WOULD HAVE THOUGHT
THE WAY YOU'VE
GOTTEN INTO FOOTBALL,
BASKETBALL WAS OUT.
- I NEVER SAID IT WAS OUT.
I STILL LOVE BASKETBALL.
IT'S JUST
THAT I LOVE FOOTBALL TOO.
- YOU CAN...
- YOU LIKE THIS GUY PATRICK,
JOSH?
DOESN'T MEAN
YOU GOT TO STOP
LOVING YOUR FATHER,
YOU KNOW.
YOUR MOM HASN'T.
- TRAIN NUMBER NINE
TO SAN FRANCISCO
WILL BE ARRIVING
IN FIVE MINUTES ON TRACK ONE.
- THAT'S ME.
- I GUESS THIS
IS ARRIVEDERCI HUH, JOSH?
GOOD LUCK, KID.
- OH, UM...
I KIND OF OVERHEARD
YOU AND MS. SALTER TALKING.
SHE SAID THAT THEY WERE GONNA
GET A NEW FOOTBALL COACH.
I'M SORRY.
- AH, DON'T SWEAT IT.
I ONLY COACH
'CAUSE I LOVE THE KIDS.
IF WINNING'S ALL
THEY'RE INTERESTED IN,
I'M NOT THE RIGHT GUY
ANYWAY.
TAKE CARE OF YOURSELF, KID.
- HEY, COACH...
UM...
IF IT'S NOT
TOO MUCH TROUBLE, UM...
CAN I GET A RIDE HOME
WITH YOU?
- SURE, KID.
COME ON.
- DON'T MIND IF WE
STOP FOR A SLICE OF PIZZA?
- OH, GOD, JOSH.
JOSH.
OH, I WAS SO WORRIED
ABOUT YOU.
- MOM.
- PROMISE ME YOU'LL NEVER
DO THAT AGAIN, JOSH.
PROMISE ME.
- I PROMISE.
I'M SORRY.
UM...
WHERE'S PATRICK?
I GOTTA TALK TO HIM.
- PATRICK'S GONE, HONEY.
- HE'S TAKEN A JOB
IN SAN DIEGO.
HE'S LEAVING
ON HIS BOAT TOMORROW.
- IT WAS TOO SOON.
- I'M SORRY.
I'M SORRY.
- I THOUGHT HE WAS WITH YOU.
- BUDDY!
BUDDY!
HE'S NEVER DONE THIS BEFORE.
HE'S NEVER RUN AWAY.
- BUDDY CAN TAKE CARE
OF HIMSELF, HONEY.
- BUDDY!
WE GOTTA KEEP LOOKING.
- JOSH, THE GAME
STARTS IN AN HOUR.
*
- LET'S ROCK!
- PLAY BALL! LET'S GO!
- GET 'EM! GO!
- HOW WE GONNA PLAY!
- ROUGH! ROUGH! ROUGH!
- LET'S GO KICK
SOME GIANT BUTT!
- GO!
- COME ON, COME ON,
LET'S GO.
- THAT A BOY.
- GO, ALL RIGHT, COME ON.
READY TO GO.
ALL RIGHT.
I NEED YOU OUT THERE
TODAY, JOSH.
- CAW, HOUSTON,
WE HAVE A PROBLEM.
- I'M GOING DOWN TO BOAT
TO GET THINGS READY FOR LOADING.
IN THE MEANTIME,
DON'T TOUCH ANYTHING,
DON'T FEED ANYTHING...
DON'T DO ANYTHING.
NOTHING!
- BACK!
game announcer:
THE FERNFIELD TIMBERWOLVES
AND THE TACOMA GIANTS.
IT'S PLAYOFF TIME!
THIS IS FRED DAVIS
WITH MY GOOD FRIEND PHIL PHIL,
35-YEAR-VETERAN
OF COLOR HERE,
TO BRING YOU
THIS EXCITING GAME TODAY.
I WOULD SAY THAT THE EXCITEMENT
IS AT FEVER PITCH, BILL.
THIS IS IT.
ALL THE MARBLES ON THE TABLE.
*
OH, NO, DISAPPOINTING NEWS
HERE, PHIL.
WE'VE JUST GOT WORD
THAT AIR BUD,
THE CANINE WONDER,
WILL NOT BE PLAYING TODAY.
NOT BE PLAYING, YES.
- OH, NO.
HAVE THEY CHECKED
THE KENNEL?
- COME ON, GUS,
YOU CAN DO IT!
- EUCH!
- I DIDN'T TOUCH
A THING, NATALYA.
- AAH!
AAAAAH!
- NO! OH HO HO HO!
Fred: WELL, THE GIANTS
WILL BE KICKING OFF,
SO THE TIMBERWOLVES
WILL BE--
- THEY'LL BE, UH, DOWN THERE
ON THE FIELD RIGHT WITH THEM.
- RECEIVING!
- THANK YOU.
Fred: ALL RIGHT,
COMING TO GOOSE.
HE'S ON THE FIVE.
HE' SON THE 10,
HE'S ON THE 15, HE'S AT--
HE'S AT THE 15,
HE'S AT THE 10.
HE'S...BACK AT THE FIVE.
- OHH.
ALL RIGHT, ALL RIGHT.
COME ON, OFFENSE.
LET'S GO! LET'S DO IT!
COME ON.
JOSH, OPEN UP RED-45.
GO, COME ON.
RED-45. LET'S GO!
- BREAK!
- HE'LL BE HERE.
HE WOULDN'T MISS THIS
FOR THE WORLD.
- HOPE YOU'RE RIGHT, TOM.
- HE'LL BE FINE.
- PREPARE TO EAT DIRT!
- UHH!
- READY!
DOWN!
SET! HIKE, HIKE!
- RAHR!
- OHH.
Fred: AND A FUMBLE
HELPED BY THE GIANTS.
AND INTO THE END ZONE,
THE GIANTS SCORE, "O"-50.
- OH, WE'RE DEAD.
WE'RE--WE'RE DEAD.
OHH.
Fred: WELL, LET'S LOOK
AT THE SCOREBOARD
AND SEE HOW MUCH TIME
ELAPSED THERE, PHIL,
BEFORE THAT TOUCHDOWN.
- OHH!
STOP!
COME ON, BABIES.
WORK WITH ME!
DUCKS ARE MY FRIEND!
COME BACK, PLEASE.
NO! OH, DOLLY!
OH! OH!
LISTEN TO ME.
LISTEN TO ME, ANIMALS.
- OH! NATALYA!
YOU'RE BACK.
OOF!
AAH!
Fred: WELL, IT LOOKS
LIKE COACH FANELLI
IS GOING TO TRY TO PUT
SOME POINTS ON THE BOARD.
THEY'RE GONNA GO
FOR A FIELD GOAL, PHIL.
- HIKE!
Fred: IT LOOKS LIKE
VAUGHN KICKING AND...
- UHH!
Fred: NO, IT HIT
WEEBLE'S HELMET,
AND IT'S WAY OFF
TO THE LEFT.
WELL, I GUESS THAT WASN'T SUCH
A GOOD DECISION AFTER ALL,
WAS IT, PHIL?
- I'LL TELL YOU,
THAT COULD GIVE YOU
SOME KIND OF HEADACHE.
YOU KNOW, YOU GET HIT
WITH A...
- AAAH!
- HOLD ON!
WHERE ARE YOU, POPOV?
- AAH!
- YOU...
I'LL GET YOU...
OH!
Fred: JOSH BACK TO PASS.
BALL IS IN THE AIR.
IT'S INTERCEPTED.
NOWHERE NEAR RECEIVER.
AND HERE THEY COME BACK
THE OTHER WAY, THE GIANTS.
BUT NO, JOSH HAS HIM.
JOSH HAS HIM ON THE 25.
HE HAS HIM ON THE 20.
HE HAS HIM ON THE 15.
HE HAS--HE HAS HIM
ON THE TEN.
HE'S--AH, BOY.
WELL, IT LOOKS LIKE
ANOTHER SCORE FOR THE GIANTS.
OH, HAVE YOU EVER SEEN--
- AAH!
AAH!
- EN GARDE!
TAKE THAT.
AND THAT!
UNH!
- NATALYA!
TAKE THIS!
I'VE GOT A NET!
- NOT NOW, POPOV!
CAN'T YOU SEE I AM BUSY?
I'M FIGHTING MONKEY!
- NATALYA!
MUST HAVE--MUST HAVE--
UHH!
GET OUT OF THE WAY!
NATALYA!
AAH!
NATALYA! AAH!
OH! AAH!
- COME DOWN!
- NATALYA!
- GET DOWN FROM THERE!
- COME GET ME!
- GET DOWN!
- AAH!
AAH!
- WHY DON'T YOU
GET YOURSELF DOWN
AND CLEAN UP THIS MESS
THAT YOU HAVE CREATED?
Fred: WELL, PHIL,
COACH FANELLI
TAKES A HEAVY ANCHOR
THROUGH THE HALFTIME
LOCKER ROOM.
DOWN 24 TO NOTHING.
DISAPPOINTED, DOWNTRODDEN...
[marching band
playing on TV]
*
- HEY, COACH...
ARE YOU GONNA TELL US
ANOTHER ONE OF YOUR STORIES?
- YOU BETTER BELIEVE I AM.
- THIS IS THE STORY
OF A FOOTBALL TEAM.
FROM THE BEGINNING,
THIS FOOTBALL TEAM
HAD HEART AND ABILITY.
BUT THERE WAS ONE
BIG PROBLEM.
THEY DIDN'T BELIEVE...
THAT THEY COULD WIN.
AND THEN THIS DOG
CAME ALONG.
AND THIS DOG COULD DO
AMAZING THINGS.
AND SUDDENLY,
THE TEAM STARTED WINNING.
BUT THE TRUTH IS...
EVEN WITHOUT THE DOG,
THEY WERE WINNERS.
EACH AND EVERY ONE OF THEM.
SO IF YOU BELIEVE
THAT A DOG
CAN PLAY FOOTBALL,
THEN YOU BETTER BELIEVE
THAT WE'RE GONNA WIN THIS GAME.
ALL RIGHT, NOW,
LET'S GET OUT THERE
AND GIVE THEM SOME
OF THAT RAZZLE DAZZLE!
ROUGH.
ROUGH!
all: ROUGH!
ROUGH! ROUGH!
ROUGH! ROUGH! ROUGH! ROUGH!
ROUGH! ROUGH! ROUGH!
YOU GUYS ARE THE BEST.
WAY TO GO, MARCO.
COME ON, BABY.
IT WORKED, BUDDY.
all, chanting:
TIMBERWOLVES! TIMBERWOLVES!
TIMBERWOLVES!
Fred: GIANTS
ON THE ATTACK AGAIN.
HERE'S MARTIN, BACK TO PASS.
HE'S LOOKING--
OH, AND HE GETS HIT
JUST AT THE LAST MINUTE.
TOOK A LITTLE OFF THAT BALL!
GOOSE STEPS IN,
HE HAS IT!
IT'S A INTERCEPTION.
- GO, GOOSE! GO! GO!
- THE 35!
- GO! GO!
GO, GOOSE, GO!
- UHH! OOF!
Fred: WELL!
THAT LOOKS LIKE A LITTLE BIT
OF INSPIRATION
FOR THE OLD TIMBERWOLVES,
DOESN'T IT?
Phil: IT JUST PROVES
MY THEORY.
Fred: WHAT IS THAT, PHIL?
Phil: SCORE MORE POINTS
THAN THE OTHER TEAM,
AND, BY GOLLY,
YOU'RE GONNA WIN!
- ALL RIGHT! YEAH!
- UH...
- RIGHT, GO, GO.
- UHH!
- OOF!
- RAAAHR!
- YES! YEAH!
- THAT'S GREAT.
- UHH!
MOTHER?
AAH! THE ANIMALS!
- "FISH GUTS."
OHH!
[Natalya and Popov
sputtering]
- NATALYA! GET UP!
GET UP!
- OHH! OH!
- OHH.
- AHH!
- TO INFINITY AND BEYOND!
- AHH.
- AAAAH!
- NO!
- OHH!
- GET THE VAN!
IT'S GOT THE VAN!
- AAH!
- I DON'T KNOW.
- BUT THERE IS DOG.
both: DOG!
- AHH!
NOW WE'VE GOT HIM.
- YOU DID IT!
- OH, AH. WHOA.
WHAT? STOP! STOP!
STOP! STOP!
STOP!
both: AAAAH!
IT'S OKAY.
I'M GLAD TO SEE YOU TOO.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING
DOWN AT THE DOCKS?
DON'T YOU HAVE
A GAME TO PLAY?
HUH?
COME ON.
[indistinct
police radio chatter]
- DO YOU HAVE
A PLAN "B"?
- WE ARE RUSSIAN CITIZENS!
WE DEMAND YOU TAKE US
TO THE RUSSIAN IMBECILE!
- IT'S EMBASSY, IMBECILE!
- AAH!
Fred: MARTIN DROPPING BACK.
VOSS--OH, IS HE
IN THE CLEAR!
THERE ISN'T A TIMBERWOLF
AROUND FOR 20 YARDS.
TOUCHDOWN!
LOOKS BAD NOW
FOR THE OLD TIMBERWOLVES.
OOH, EEH.
- NOW, COME ON, NOW,
FORGET ABOUT THAT.
ANCIENT HISTORY.
JOSH, JOSH, COME HERE.
GET IN HERE.
COME HERE.
ALL RIGHT.
WE'RE GONNA GET THEM
WITH A LITTLE DOUBLE TROUBLE.
ALL RIGHT?
LET'S GO!
BUT, COACH, WE'VE NEVER
DONE A DOUBLE TROUBLE
WITHOUT BUDDY.
- WE'RE GONNA HAVE
TO DO IT WITHOUT BUDDY.
BUDDY'S NOT HERE.
NOW LET'S GO.
COME ON, OFFENSE.
YOUSE TWOS, ALL RIGHT?
LET'S GO!
COME ON, NOW,
GET OUT THERE!
Fred: LADIES AND GENTLEMEN,
LISTEN TO THAT AUDIENCE.
THIS IS A SIGHT
TO BEHOLD!
IT'S AIR BUD!
- GOOD BOY. YEAH.
YEAH.
LET'S GO GET 'EM, BOY.
Fred: THE OLD AIR BUD
IS BACK IN THE GAME!
- YEAH, THIS DISPELS
THAT RUMOR, HEH HEH.
Fred: WHAT'S THAT, BILL?
- BUDDY...
WHERE WERE YOU?
audience, chanting: BUD-DY!
BUD-DY! BUD-DY! BUD-DY!
BUD-DY! BUD-DY!
- OOH, LIKE I SAID,
DOUBLE TROUBLE!
Fred: LOOKING FOR THAT BALL.
HANDOFF, DOUBLE REVERSE.
DOUBLE REVERSE AND...
IT'S OFF TO AIR BUD!
AND HE'S OFF!
HE'S DOWNFIELD!
THE GIANTS ARE ALL
CHASING HIM.
AIR BUD IN THE CLEAR!
AIR BUD'S DOWN
TO THE 30-YARD LINE!
- YEAH!
- BUD-DY! BUD-DY! BUD-DY!
BUD-DY! BUD-DY!
- OOF!
- WAH!
Fred: OLD AIR BUD
HAS SURE PUT THE TIMBER
BACK IN THESE TIMBERWOLVES.
I'M TELLING YOU, THEY'RE
ON A SCORING RAMPAGE NOW!
WHOA!
OOF! OOH!
- FIRST DOWN!
- OOF!
Fred: ANOTHER SCORE!
Phil: THAT IS JUST AMAZING.
Fred: IT'S NEW YEAR'S EVE
IN THE END ZONE
WITH AIR BUD.
- HE'S GOT FLEAS.
YOU CAN'T TELL ME
HE DOESN'T HAVE FLEAS.
- YAY, BUDDY!
Fred: AIR BUD HAS CERTAINLY
TIGHTENED UP THIS GAME
FOR THE TIMBERWOLVES.
BUT THEY'RE GONNA NEED
ANOTHER TOUCHDOWN
IN ORDER TO WIN.
AND NOW...
THIS COULD BE IT!
- BUDDY!
Fred: OHH, NO, 184-POUND
CRUSHING TACKLE BY TYLER.
AND AIR BUD IS DOWN.
TEAMMATES RUSHING
ONTO THE FIELD NOW, TRAINERS.
AIR BUD, WE SEE MOVEMENT.
- IT'S ALL RIGHT.
DON'T WORRY, I'M ALL RIGHT.
GET THE DOG.
- EXCUSE ME.
COMING THROUGH.
- I DON'T KNOW.
- JUST HANG ON.
- HE'S NOT SURE YET.
- HE'S GONNA
BE ALL RIGHT, JOSH.
WHY DON'T YOU GET OUT THERE
AND FINISH THE GAME.
- IT'S OKAY.
I'LL TAKE CARE OF HIM.
- GET UP, BUDDY, COME ON.
- COME ON, JOSH.
HE'LL BE OKAY.
- JOSH, LET'S GO.
- I HOPE HE'S OKAY.
Fred: WELL, THIS CERTAINLY
IS A CRUSHING BLOW.
POOR AIR BUD,
OUT OF THIS GAME.
- OH, I JUST--
- WELL, LET'S HOPE
THAT THESE GUYS
CAN GO ON BY THEMSELVES.
- READY!
SET!
HIKE, HIKE!
- UHH!
- OH!
- THIRD DOWN COMING UP.
WHAT DO YOU THINK, PHIL?
- WELL, I THINK THAT--
- THIRD DOWN,
HE'S BACK FOR ANOTHER PASS.
Phil: HE'S GONNA PASS THERE.
THAT'S WHAT.
- UHH!
- YEAH!
- ALL RIGHT!
Fred: WELL, IF THERE'S
A MIRACLE IN THE MAKING,
IT BETTER
SHOW UP NOW, PHIL,
BECAUSE THIS
IS THE LAST CHANCE.
WE GOT TEN SECONDS
LEFT IN THIS GAME.
- WELL, TEN IS ENOUGH
IF YOU PLAY YOUR CARDS RIGHT.
- SOMETIMES, YOU DON'T EVEN
HAVE TO PLAY CARDS, YOU KNOW.
- YEAH...
- COME ON, TOM, GET UP.
WE GOT A GAME TO PLAY.
- I CAN'T FIND
MY NOSE SPREADER.
- FORGET ABOUT
YOUR NOSE SPREADER, TOM.
- BUT I CAN'T CATCH
WITHOUT IT.
- TRUST ME, TOM,
YOU DON'T NEED IT.
- IT'S GONNA BE FINE.
- THIS IS OUR LAST SHOT,
JOSH.
- I KNOW.
ALL RIGHT, GUYS,
LET'S DO B
CROSSING PATTERN.
DEEP.
- THAT'S 60 YARDS.
YOU CAN'T THROW
60 YARDS.
- ARE YOU SURE
YOU WANT TO DO THIS?
- I'M POSITIVE--YOU GUYS
GOT TO TRUST ME, ALL RIGHT?
- WE'RE WITH YOU, JOSH.
- YOU JUST RUN.
ALL RIGHT, ON TWO.
READY...
- BREAK!
- LET'S ROCK.
- HEY, GUYS, LOOK!
- COME ON, GUYS, LET'S GO.
COME ON. PLAY.
- WHAT ABOUT
MY NOSE SPREADER?
- WHEW.
- ALL RIGHT!
READY!
B-52!
DOWN, SET,
HIKE, HIKE!
- UHH!
- GET OFF!
- YEAH!
- YES!
- WHOO! ALL RIGHT!
OH, HONEY,
I'M SO PROUD OF YOU.
- CONGRATULATIONS, JOSH.
YOU GOT POTENTIAL.
I GOT POTENTIAL!
- AAH!
IT'S A BEAUTIFUL DAY.
- PATRICK!
PATRICK!
UM...
- DON'T GO.
PLEASE DON'T GO.
- THIRD AND THREE.
WHAT WOULD YOU DO HERE?
- HUH, LET ME SEE.
I-I THINK I'D GO LONG
TO JOEY GALLOWAY.
- BLUE-38!
- GOOD CALL.
THEY'RE NOT EXPECTING THAT.
- HMM.
- OH, NO.
- I DON'T BELIEVE IT.
*
* WHEN I WAS ALONE
* AND FRIGHTENED
* I ALWAYS FELT LIKE
* NO ONE WAS THERE
* IT SEEMED HOPELESS
* TO DREAM THAT SOMEONE
* WOULD EVER HOLD ME
* AGAIN
* ONE MOMENT
* WAS MORE THAN I NEEDED
* TO KNOW THAT I HAD
* FALLEN FOR YOU
* OH, I SAW SOMETHING
* THAT CHANGED ME FOREVER
* THE MOMENT I MET YOU
* I KNEW
* WHEN I CLOSE MY EYES
* ALL I SEE IS
* THE MAGIC OF YOUR SMILE
* AND UP ACROSS THE SKY
* WE WOULD TRAVEL
THE MOONLIGHT *
* FOR MILES
* I WANT IT TO LAST ME
* MY LIFETIME
AND THEN SOME *
* I NEED YOU TO WANT ME
* LA DA DA DA
* DOO DOO DOO
* HA AH
*
* JUST LIKE THAT
* LOVE HAS SURPRISED ME
* AND TAKEN ME OUT
FOR THE RIDE OF MY LIFE *
* AND IT SURE FEELS IT
* WHENEVER YOU TOUCH ME
* PLEASE HOLD ME
TILL THE END *
* OF MY LIFE
*
* WE WILL FOLLOW
THE MOONLIGHT *
* FOR MILES
* I WANT IT
* TO LAST ME
* MY LIFETIME
* AND THEN SOME
* I NEED YOU
TO WANT ME *
* LA DA DA
* DOO DOO DOO