DO YOU WANT PIMENTO LOAF
OR BALONEY ?
HEY, PROFESSOR !
THEY ONLY GOT
A COUPLE OF SPOTS LEFT !
SHH.
OURS IS RIGHT OVER THERE.
- [ Laughing ]
- CARLTON.
YOU SEE, IF OUR EXPERIMENT
IS A SUCCESS,
WE WILL HAVE ISOLATED
THE SUPER SPORTS GENE.
AND THEN WE CAN SELL IT
TO PROFESSIONAL ATHLETES
ALL AROUND THE WORLD.
AMAZING.
OH, YES, IT IS.
BUT IT CAN ONLY BE DONE
IF WE HAVE ALL OF AIR BUD'S
PUPPIES AS WELL AS THE--
BUD.
NOW, YOU MUST MEMORIZE
THESE FACES.
WE HAVE TO CATCH EACH
AND EVERY ONE.
THIS IS BUDDY'S
OLDEST PUP, SHOOTER.
AND THIS ONE, DUKE.
HERE'S BUDDY'S
THIRD PUP, ZACK,
AN OUTSTANDING LINEBACKER.
BACKER.
AND A PUPPY
WHO ALREADY KNOWS...
HOW TO PLAY SOCCER--
STRIKER.
AND, OF COURSE,
THE BEST OF THEM ALL,
THEIR FATHER.
THE BUD.
THEN, AND ONLY THEN,
WILL I HAVE THE INGREDIENTS...
TO CREATE THE GREATEST
EXPERIMENT EVER.
[ Laughing ]
HEY, BUDDY,
CHECK THIS OUT !
ALL RIGHT, DUKE !
NICE CATCH !
YEAH !
WHAT ?  WHAT ?
NICE PLAY.
YOU BETTER RECOGNIZE.
DEFENSE, DEFENSE !
SHOOTER, TO YOU !
YEAH, SHOOTER !
YES !
HUT !
ZACK, GO DEEP !
YES !
- WAY TO GO, STRIKER !
- [ Barking ]
HEY, BUDDY, COME ON.
BUDDY, SHOOT !
[ Laughing ]
-  HONEY, FLAMES !
- IT'S FINE, IT'S FINE !
SEE ?
- YOU'RE KILLING ME HERE !
- [ Giggling ]
HEY, JOSH, PUT ME DOWN !
[ Laughing ]
[ Girl ]
SHOOT !
MAMA MIA !
YOU GONNA HAVE
SOME OF THAT ?
SO ?
HONEY, CAN YOU GET ANDREA ?
YEAH, SURE.
ANDREA, LUNCH !
I COULD'VE DONE THAT.
WILL YOU AND BUDDY
STILL BABY-SIT ?
IT DEPENDS
ON HOW BUSY WE ARE.
WE MIGHT HAVE A LOT OF HOMEWORK.
YOU'RE GONNA BE
IN HIGH SCHOOL ?
JUNIOR HIGH.
YEAH.
JUNIOR HIGH, HERE WE COME.
-  [ Mother ]
ANDREA !
- I GOTTA GO.
I DON'T THINK WE SHOULD
BE DOING THIS ANYMORE.
IT'S KIND OF ELEMENTARY.
YEAH,
YOU'RE PROBABLY RIGHT.
WELL, SEE YA LATER.
SEE YA.
WANT SOME JUICE ?
YOU WANT SOME
OF THAT TOO ?
GUESS WHAT.  TOM AND I ARE
IN TWO OF THE SAME CLASSES.
OH, GREAT !
-  DON'T LET HIM DISTRACT YOU.
- DON'T WORRY.
WHY DON'T YOU GO SEE
YOUR BROTHER ?
TAMMY AND I ARE IN FOUR
OF THE SAME CLASSES.
I THINK WE HAVE THAT
SAME HISTORY TEACHER YOU
GUYS USED TO MAKE FUN OF.
BUZZOO !
WHO WANTS A BUSY BEE ?
- THE ONE YOU SAID
LOOKED LIKE A GOPHER.
- PASS ME ONE OF THOSE RIBS.
WHO WANTS A BUSY BEE ?
LEFTOVERS !
[ Barking ]
OKAY.
[ Yelling ]
NEED ANY HELP ?
NOPE.  PRETTY MUCH
ALL PACKED UP.
THINK YOU'RE GONNA
MISS IT HERE ?
YEAH, SURE.
BUT, YOU KNOW,
IT DOESN'T MEAN
I'M GONE FOREVER, RIGHT ?
SO, ARE YOU GONNA COME
AND VISIT ?
YEAH, I THINK
I MIGHT SNEAK BACK
FOR A DAY IN THE SUMMER.
I'M JUST KIDDING.
I'LL BE BACK AT THANKSGIVING.
I WAS THINKING MAYBE YOU COULD
TAKE MY ROOM WHILE I'M GONE,
MAKE SURE NOBODY MESSES IT UP.
BUT IT'S YOUR ROOM.
SO, YOU COULD
BORROW IT, RIGHT ?
NAH, I'D RATHER HAVE
IT STAY JUST THE WAY IT IS.
GOOD NIGHT, JOSH.
NIGHT, ANDREA.
I'M REALLY GOING TO MISS YOU.
SURE YOU GOT EVERYTHING ?
YEAH.
I GOT IT.
THERE.
LET'S GO, BUDDY.
OKAY THEN,
I GUESS IT'S TIME.
WHERE'S ANDREA ?
I DON'T KNOW.
SHE WAS HERE A MINUTE AGO.
WHY DON'T I GO
FIND HER ?
I'LL GET NOAH READY.
WHERE'S YOUR SISTER ?
ANDREA !
ANDREA ?
[ Mother ]
ANDREA !
WE'VE GOTTA GO !
IF WE DON'T LEAVE NOW,
WE'RE GONNA MISS THE BUS.
LET'S GO.
HEY.
BUDDY, CAN YOU FIND ANDREA
FOR ME ?
GO FIND HER.
[ Barking ]
BUDDY, STOP !
LEAVE ME ALONE.
[ Barking ]
BUDDY,
WHERE ARE WE GOING ?
HEY, IT'S JOSH.
JOSH !  HOW'S IT GOIN' ?
AHH, GOOD TO SEE YA.
TOM, YOU LOOK READY.
I'VE BEEN READY ALL SUMMER.
[ Chuckling ]
JOSH, THEY'RE BOARDING.
I'LL GO SAY GOOD-BYE
TO MY FOLKS,
AND THEN I'LL GRAB US
SOME FRONT-ROW SEATS.
ALL RIGHT.  WE'LL SEE YA.
I'LL BE THERE IN A MINUTE.
I'LL PUT THESE ON THE BUS.
ALL RIGHT, SON.
GO WHERE YOU MUST GO.
OH, BABY !
[ Sobbing ]
OH, OH, GIVE ME ONE MORE.
GUESS IT'S TIME.
YEAH.
GUESS YOU'RE GONNA HAVE
TO SAY BYE TO ANDREA
AND BUDDY FOR ME.
I WILL.  I WILL.
DON'T WORRY, MOM, OKAY ?
I'M GONNA BE FINE.
I KNOW YOU WILL.
I LOVE YOU.
I LOVE YOU TOO.
OH, BYE.
OKAY.
BYE.
WANT A SANDWICH ?
NO.  THANK YOU.
THERE HE IS.
♪♪ [ Humming ]
[ Barking ]
- THAT'S IT, BUDDY !
THAT'S HIS BUS !
- [ Barking ]
[ Barks ]
BUDDY !
- BUDDY ?
- [ Barks ]
- JOSH !
-  ANDREA ?
WHAT'S WRONG ?
NOTHING.
I MEAN...
I DIDN'T GET
TO SAY GOOD-BYE.
I DON'T WANT YOU TO GO,
JOSH.
I KNOW, ANDREA,
BUT LISTEN TO ME, OKAY ?
IT'S JUST TIME.
ALL RIGHT ?
JUST LIKE IT'S TIME FOR YOU
TO GO TO JUNIOR HIGH.
YEAH, I KNOW.
ARE YOU GONNA COME OUT
AND VISIT ME ?
OKAY.
HERE, I, UH--
I WANT YOU TO HAVE THIS.
THAT'S DAD'S WATCH !
I KNOW, BUT...
YOU JUST KEEP IT FOR ME
TILL I GET BACK.
HEY.
I'LL MISS YOU, OKAY ?
YEAH.
YOU AND BUDDY
CAN LOOK AFTER EACH OTHER.
YOU LOOK AFTER ANDREA FOR ME,
OKAY ?
[ Sighs ]
SEE YA, BUD.
OKAY.  NOW I REALLY DO
HAVE TO GO, SO HERE.
I LOVE YOU.
I LOVE YOU TOO,
JOSH.
[ Bus Driver ]
THAT'S IT, FOLKS.
GET BACK
TO YOUR SEATS, PLEASE.
[ Sighs ]
I LOVE THAT DOG.
COME ON, BUDDY.
[ Chuckling ]
YOU LITTLE--
WILL YOU STOP FOOLING AROUND ?
I THOUGHT I TOLD YOU
TO GO BUY US A CAR.
WHAT ARE YOU LOOKING AT ?
SWEET !
[ Gasps ]
TA-DA !
CARLTON !
YOU DON'T LIKE IT ?
[ Barking ]
OKAY, OKAY, I'M UP !
I'M UP !
[ Giggles ]
MOM, HOW'S THIS ?
HONEY, THAT LOOKS GREAT.
DO YOU WANT SOME TOAST ?
- HOW 'BOUT THIS ONE ?
- HONEY, THAT LOOKS GOOD TOO.
DON'T FORGET YOUR LUNCH.
THANKS.
I'M SO NERVOUS.
- NEED A RIDE ?
- OH, NO.  TAMMY AND I
ARE GONNA WALK TOGETHER.
-  [ Doorbell Rings ]
- OH, THAT'S HER.
GOTTA GO.
DID YOU CHANGE ?
[ Father ]
IT LOOKS NICE !
HEY.
WELL, HERE GOES.
[ Tammy ]
I HOPE EVERYTHING
GOES OKAY.
YEAH.
LOOK AT YOU GO.
OKAY, I'M--
GOTTA GO.
HAVE A GOOD DAY, HONEY.
I HAVE TWO APPOINTMENTS,
BUT I'LL CALL YOU.
WHO'S GONNA CALL ME ?
HEY, BUDDY, B--
♪♪ [ Harmonica ]
HEY, BUDDY !
WHY DON'T YOU COME SHOW US
SOME MOVES ?
DO WE HAVE HOMEROOM
FIRST THING ?
THANKS, ZACK.
HEY, BUDDY.
JEEZ, THEY LOOK SO OLD.
THEY ARE.
READY ?
HERE GOES.
[ Barking ]
ANDREA, BUDDY'S HERE !
OH, MY BAG !
THANKS, BUDDY.
SEE YA.
THAT WAS LUCKY.
YEAH.
WHICH WAY DO WE GO ?
I DON'T KNOW !
THERE'S SO MANY PEOPLE.
[ School Bell Rings ]
[ Clears Throat ]
LADIES, SHOULDN'T YOU TWO
BE HEADED TO CLASS NOW ?
WE WERE JUST
HEADING THERE.
YEAH.
WHERE DO WE GO ?
I THINK IT'S THIS WAY.
HERE IT IS !  HERE !
WE'RE LATE
AND IT'S MRS. CRIPPIN.
[ Andrea ]
JOSH SAYS THEY CALL HER
"THE CRIPPLER."
LADIES.
[ Girl ]
THEY'RE IN SO MUCH TROUBLE.
WELL, NOW THAT WE HAVE BEEN
SO RUDELY INTERRUPTED,
LET ME REMIND ALL OF YOU
THAT TARDINESS...
WILL NOT BE ACCEPTED
IN MY CLASSROOM, NO EXCUSES.
AS I WAS SAYING,
MATHEMATICS IS FUN.
♪♪ [ Singing ]
STOP !
THERE, THAT'S HIM.
STRIKER.
- SHALL WE PREPARE ?
- WAIT.
IT'S THE SHERIFF.
OHH !
WE'LL HAVE TO COME BACK.
DRIVE, CARLTON.
WILL YOU DRIVE ?
[ Engine Revs ]
[ School Bell Rings ]
[ All Chattering ]
WHICH CLASS DID YOU HAVE
BEFORE THIS ?
SCIENCE.
[ Chattering,
Laughing Continue ]
HEY, THERE'S BUDDY !
HEY, BUDDY !
LET HIM IN !
[ Mother ]
WHO'S A HUNGRY BOY ?
ALL RIGHT !
HEY, HOW'S THAT LOOK ?
HONEY, THAT'S BEAUTIFUL !
SO, DID YOU MEET ANYONE NEW
AT SCHOOL TODAY ?
AH, SORT OF.
SORT OF ?
IT'S JUST YOUR FIRST DAY.
YOU'VE GOT TO GIVE YOURSELF
A CHANCE.
YEAH, I KNOW.
JOSH CALLED TODAY.
HE SAID THINGS ARE GOING
REALLY WELL.
HE SAID TO SAY HELLO.
WHAT'S THE MATTER ?
HE SAID HE OFFERED YOU HIS ROOM,
BUT YOU DIDN'T WANT TO TAKE IT.
YEAH, I'D RATHER
JUST HAVE MINE.
REALLY ?
- YOU SURE ?
- YEAH.
WHAT'S THE MATTER ?
AWW.
'CAUSE HE CAN'T HAVE ANY BEEF.
CAN I BE EXCUSED ?
I'M NOT REALLY HUNGRY.
[ Crying ]
WE GOTTA DO
SOMETHING.
YEAH, YOU'RE RIGHT.
DO WE ALWAYS HAVE
TO WEAR THESE ?
I HOPE NOT.
OKAY, ANDERSON, FRAMM
AND O'REILLY,
YOU'RE UP NEXT.
AND BEGIN.
SO, HOW'D I DO ?
REALLY GOOD.
♪♪ [ Orchestra ]
[ Cymbals Clang ]
ANDREA ?
THE COOKIES !
OH, MY GOSH !
- TAMMY, WHAT HAPPENED ?
-  I SWEAR IT SAID 350 MINUTES.
FIRE !
[ Coughing ]
OH, TOUGH DAY,
GIRLS ?
THAT'S IT.
BASEBALL.
WHAT'S IT ?
BASEBALL ?
WHAT DO WE KNOW
ABOUT BASEBALL ?
IT'S EASY.
I'LL TEACH YOU.
OH, BROTHER.
COACH ?
YEAH ?
I WAS WONDERING IF
WE COULD TRY OUT...
FOR THE BASEBALL TEAM ?
SURE, WHY NOT ?
TRYOUTS ARE TOMORROW
AT 3:30.
HEY, GOOD LUCK.
THANKS.
TRYOUTS ARE TOMORROW
AT 3:30.
I DON'T KNOW HOW
TO PLAY BASEBALL.
THERE'S ALWAYS HOME EC.
- [ Barks ]
- HI, HONEY.
HOW WAS SCHOOL ?
- FINE... I GUESS.
- OH, GOOD.
IF YOU DON'T COUNT THE EXPLOSION
AND THE FIRE IN HOME EC.
YEAH, EVERYTHING WAS GREAT.
THAT SOUNDS GREAT, HONEY.
OH, HERE COMES YOUR PANTS.
IT'S OKAY.
IT'S JUST STORAGE.
WHAT ARE YOU EATING ?
I'M GONNA BE FINE.
[ Mother ]
WHAT ARE YOU EATING ?
I JUST GOT A FINGERFUL.
I'LL STILL BE HUNGRY.
YOU ARE HOME.
YEAH, UM, I WAS WONDERING
IF ANYBODY WOULD HAVE
ANY TIME--
[ Pager Beeping ]
EMERGENCY.  THE SAMUELSON'S
HORSE IS ABOUT TO FOAL.
I'M SORRY, HONEY.
I GOTTA GO.
TIME TO THROW THE BALL ?
OH, SHOOT !  YOUR SOUP !
OH !
HE COULD USE A DIAPER CHANGE.
WOULD YOU MIND, HONEY ?
I CAN GET YOUR SOUP.
OKAY.
I KNEW IT.
YOU WANT THE BALL ?
HERE YOU GO.
THANKS, BUDDY.
MAKE SURE YOU COVER HIM.
HE LIKES TO GO.
THANKS, MOM.
[ Phone Ringing ]
MOM ?
HELLO ?
HI, TAMMY.
YEAH, DID YOU SAY PRACTICES
WOULD BE EVERY DAY
AFTER SCHOOL ?
YEAH, I'LL BE THERE.
YEAH, SEE YA.
HOW DID YOU GET SO WET ?
[ Mother ]
DID YOU SEE THAT ?
ALL RIGHT, KIDS,
I'M COACH CRENSHAW,
AND YOU CAN, UH--
YOU CAN JUST CALL ME COACH.
FIRST THINGS FIRST.
WHO ALL HERE
HAS PLAYED BALL BEFORE ?
I PLAYED CATCHER BEFORE
WITH MY BROTHER
AND HIS FRIENDS.
NEVER ON A TEAM
OR ANYTHING.
I HEARD THERE'S STILL
AN AUDITION FOR DANCERS
IN THE SCHOOL PLAY.
[ Boys Laughing ]
WE'RE GONNA WARM UP
WITH A FEW DRILLS, AND, RANDY,
YOU'RE GONNA LEAD THEM.
LET'S GO, GUYS.
ALL RIGHT, LET'S GO.
♪♪
I ALMOST GOT IT !
THIS IS A LONG ONE.
♪♪
I THINK WE'VE
WARMED UP ENOUGH.
♪♪
TAMMY, GET IN FRONT OF IT.
NICE !
♪♪
ANDREA, THIS ONE'S FOR YOU.
GET IN FRONT OF IT.
♪♪
NICE SNAG, TAMMY.
PUT YOUR BODY BEHIND IT.
GET IN FRONT OF IT, TERRANCE.
THAT'S IT.
KEEP YOUR EYES OPEN,
ANDREA.
USE YOUR MITT.
GET YOUR BODY BEHIND IT.
STARE AT THE BALL.
GET IN FRONT OF IT.
WE'LL WORK ON IT.
♪♪
NICE, TAMMY.
GET UNDER IT !
♪♪
MAYBE THE NEXT ONE.
ALL RIGHT, EVERYONE,
LET'S SCRIMMAGE.
♪♪
[ Chuckles ]
[ Whispers ]
OW.
♪♪
- [ Chuckles ]
- [ Barking ]
ANDREA FRAMM, YOU'RE UP.
C'MON, ANDREA !
YOU CAN DO IT !
KEEP YOUR EYE ON THE BALL.
FOLLOW THROUGH THE ZONE.
[ Boy ]
COME ON, RANDY !
SHE'S GONNA KILL SOMEONE
WITH THAT THING !
ALL RIGHTY THEN.
OKAY, ONE MORE BATTER
AND WE'LL CALL IT A DAY.
[ All Chatter ]
THAT'S PRACTICE !
TAMMY ?
COME ON IN.
[ Boy ]
RANDY GOT BEAT BY A GIRL.
YOUR SWING COULD COME IN
VERY HANDY THIS YEAR.
SO I MADE THE TEAM ?
I'LL POST THE ROSTER TOMORROW.
COACH ?
WHAT ABOUT ANDREA ?
WE JOINED TOGETHER.
SHE'S MY BEST FRIEND.
B.F.F.--
BEST FRIENDS FOREVER.
IF SHE CAN'T PLAY,
I WON'T BE ABLE TO JOIN.
WE MADE A PACT
TO STICK TOGETHER.
YOU HAVE TO WAIT
UNTIL TOMORROW.
EXCUSE ME.
SORRY.
YEAH !
FIRST PRACTICE,
TODAY AFTER SCHOOL.
D-D-D-D-D-D !
BALL, BALL, BALL !
YEAH, SHOOTER, MAN !
THAT WAS A WICKED SHOT.
YOU'RE GETTIN' BETTER EVERY DAY.
YO, MAN, GIVE ME SOME PAW.
- SHOOTER,
I MADE THE BASEBALL TEAM !
- [ Barking ]
NICE WORK, ANDREA.
HEY, YOU GUYS !
ANYBODY HOME ?
HELLO ?
- I MADE THE BASE--
- SHH !  HE'S ASLEEP.
[ Crying ]
[ Andrea ]
SORRY.
I MADE THE TEAM.
COME ON, BUDDY.
WAIT.
WATCH IT !
WATCH SHOOTER !
ARE YOU ALL READY ?
LET HIM LOOSE.
THERE YOU GO, ROCKY.
[ Barks ]
COME ON, ROCKY !
YES-YES-YES-YES-YES.
[ Chuckling ]
HUH ?
GO.
BALL, BALL, BALL !
HOLD UP, MAN.
WHERE'S SHOOTER ?
I DON'T KNOW.
HE TOOK A DOGGIE TIME-OUT
OR SOMETHING.
SHOOTER !
JUST REMEMBER,
WE ARE NOT THE BAD GUYS.
WE ARE THE SCIENTISTS.
WE ARE... GOOD GUYS.
GOOD.
SCIENCE IS GOOD.
[ Barking ]
SCIENCE IS GOOD, YES.
SHOOTER ?
C'MON, BOY,
WHERE ARE YA ?
SHOOTER !
WAIT TILL JOSH FINDS OUT.
HE WON'T BELIEVE IT.
- HEY !
- HELLO, ANDREA.
HOW ARE YOU DOING ?
GREAT !
I MADE THE--
WHOOPS !
- BASEBALL TEAM.
- SEE YOU AT THE BALLPARK.
SHERIFF ?  SHERIFF.
HMM ?
WHAT'S UP ?
I'M SORRY TO INTERRUPT, SHERIFF,
BUT MY SHOOTER'S GONE MISSING.
YOU GOT A PERMIT
FOR THAT GUN, SON ?
N-NO.  MY SHOOTER.
YOUR RIFLE ?
NO, MY DOG.
YOUR DOG.
WHAT'S HIS NAME ?
SHOOTER !
♪ O'ER THE LAND
OF THE FREE ♪
♪ AND THE HOME OF THE ♪
[ Sour Note ]
♪ BRAVE ♪♪
GOOD AFTERNOON, FERNFIELD.
THIS IS MAILMAN PHIL...
BROADCASTING LIVE ON
FERNFIELD COMMUNITY RADIO,
BRINGING YOU THE
TIMBERWOLVES' FIRST GAME
OF THE SEASON.
OKAY, YOU GUYS,
YOU ALL KNOW YOUR POSITIONS.
SO LET'S GET OUT THERE...
AND SHOW THEM
A LITTLE TIMBERWOLF TEETH !
COME ON, YOU GUYS !
[ Together ]
ONE, TWO, THREE--
TIMBERWOLVES !
COME ON, GUYS !
HERE WE GO.
♪♪ [ Humming: "Take Me Out
To The Ball Game" ]
NEXT LEG.
BEFORE WE START THE GAME,
I'D LIKE TO REMIND EVERYONE
THAT SHOOTER IS MISSING.
AND ALL THE BASKETBALL PLAYERS
WOULD APPRECIATE IT,
THAT IF YOU SEE HIM,
TO PLEASE GIVE THEM A HOLLER.
PLAY BALL !
COME ON, GUYS,
WE CAN DO IT !
I'M RIGHT BEHIND YOU ALL !
WHOO !
GOT IT.
- [ Cheering ]
- YEAH !
AWESOME CATCH, TAMMY !
AWESOME CATCH !
COME ON, TAMMY !
YEAH !  YES !
SAFE !
I GOTTA TELL YA, FOLKS,
TAMMY IS SOLIDIFYING
HERSELF...
AS FERNFIELD'S BEST PLAYER
AS SHE LEADS...
THE TIMBERWOLVES
TO ANOTHER VICTORY !
I SHOULD'VE GOT
AN AUTOMATIC.
STRIKE THREE !
YOU'RE OUTTA HERE !
YES !  YOO-HOO !
HI, BUDDY.
GOT IT !
HERE YOU GO.
SHOOTER'S MISSING ?
BUDDY ?
WE GOT A REAL
NAIL-BITER HERE, FOLKS.
WE'RE IN THE BOTTOM
OF THE NINTH.
TAMMY'S UP TO BAT.
SHE'S THE BEST HITTER.
HERE SHE GOES.
THERE'S A LONG DRIVE
OUT TO RIGHT CENTER FIELD.
IT'S BACK.  BACK.
IT'S GONE !
IT'S A HOME RUN !
- AH-OOGA !
- [ Cheering ]
TAMMY HAS WON THE GAME
FOR THE TIMBERWOLVES.
AND ANOTHER GREAT VICTORY
FOR FERNFIELD.
ANDREA !
ANDREA,
WAIT UP !
IF YOU PRACTICE ENOUGH,
I KNOW COACH WILL GIVE YOU
A CHANCE.
TAMMY, I DON'T EVEN BELONG
ON THIS TEAM.
COACH MADE A MISTAKE
EVEN LETTING ME JOIN
IN THE FIRST PLACE.
- ANDREA ?
- I GOTTA GO.
WE'VE GOT ANOTHER
EXCITING GAME ON OUR HANDS,
FOLKS.
IT'S THE BOTTOM OF THE NINTH
AND OUR FEISTY TIMBERWOLVES
ARE TIED UP...
WITH THE DEFENDING CHAMPION
BABOONS AT THREE RUNS APIECE.
- STRIKE TWO !
- [ Barks ]
NO.
[ Groans ]
TAMMY !
- TAMMY TOOK THAT
RIGHT OFF THE ELBOW.
- OH, NO.
OH.
OH, NO, NOT TAMMY !
OKAY, GUYS,
GET BACK.
OW.
OH, THAT'S A DOOZY.
I CAN'T MOVE IT.
YOU'LL HAVE
TO GET IT X-RAYED.
COME ON, HONEY.
MIKE, GET THE GEAR ON.
ANDREA, GO TAKE RIGHT FIELD.
THIS IS BAD NEWS, FOLKS.
IT DOESN'T LOOK LIKE TAMMY'S
GONNA BE ABLE TO CONTINUE.
SHE'S GONNA HAVE
TO LEAVE THE GAME.
IT'S ALL RIGHT.
TAMMY'S IN GOOD HANDS.
ANDREA FRAMM IS GONNA SEE
HER FIRST ACTION
OF THE SEASON.
[ Man ]
DO IT, ANDREA.
GOOD TEAMWORK, GUYS.
STRIKE ONE !
STRIKE TWO !
GOT IT !
NO, NO !  ANDREA !
ANDREA, NO !
[ Crowd Groans ]
SAFE !
THAT'S THE GAME !
THAT'S THE GAME.
SORRY.
"SORRY" ?
THAT JUST COST US THE GAME.
WAY TO GO.
WE'RE GONNA MAKE HER FEEL SO
GOOD WHEN SHE COMES HERE, OKAY ?
HEY, SWEETIE !
FOR YOUR FIRST GAME,
IT SURE WAS CLOSE.
WE WOULD'VE WON
IF IT WASN'T FOR ME.
IT WAS YOUR FIRST TIME
PLAYING.  YOU'VE GOTTA
GIVE YOURSELF A CHANCE.
TELL THAT TO THE TEAM.
WELL, MAYBE I COULD HELP YOU
PRACTICE A LITTLE.
EVEN YOU THINK I SUCK.
HEY, HONEY.
SO, HOW DID IT GO ?
OW.
♪♪ [ Singing ]
STILL NO SIGN OF SHOOTER,
HUH ?
DON'T WORRY ABOUT IT.
BECAUSE TOMORROW
WE'RE GONNA HAVE ANOTHER LOOK.
HOLY ITALIAN HAIRDO.
I ALMOST FORGOT THE SPECIAL
SHAMPOO FOR SENORA FUSILLI.
GET HIM OFF ME.
GET HIM OFF ME !
COME ON !
COME ON, ROCKY !
IN THE CAR !
CAR, CAR, CAR !
[ Barking ]
[ Chuckling ]
GOTCHA !
♪ QUE BELLA-- ♪
[ Speaking Italian ]
STRIKER !  NOW WHERE
DO YOU GO, MY BOY ?
GOOD WORK, CARLTON.
THANK YOU.
GOOD WORK, PROFESSOR.
SHUT UP.
STRIKER !
[ Speaking Italian ]
HEY.
IS IT BROKEN ?
NO.
JUST BADLY BRUISED.
THEN I GUESS YOU WON'T
BE ABLE TO PLAY.
OR HELP YOU PRACTICE.
YEAH.
[ Buddy Whimpers ]
TAMMY ?
DINNER !
I GOTTA GO.
YEAH, I'LL SEE YA.
I HOPE YOU FEEL BETTER.
THANKS.
STRIKE ONE !
STRIKE TWO !
COME ON, ANDREA !
KEEP YOUR EYE ON THE BALL !
STRIKE THREE !
GOOD TRY, SWEETIE !
GOOD SWING.
HEY, BUDDY.  NO SIGN
OF SHOOTER YET, HUH ?
YOU BE CAREFUL, OKAY ?
KEEP THE FAITH, BUDDY.
WE'LL FIND HIM.
SHE'S GOT IT !
THINGS ARE LOOKING
PRETTY BLEAK
FOR THE TIMBERWOLVES.
THEY'VE LOST THE LAST
THREE GAMES IN A ROW,
AND THEIR STAR PLAYER,
TAMMY, IS STILL OUT
WITH AN INJURY.
[ Whimpering ]
[ Whimpers ]
THROW THE KEYS.
[ Laughing ]
♪ WE GOT A DOGGIE ♪
ZACK ?
ZACK, WHERE'D YOU GO ?
[ Randy ]  YOU PRACTICALLY
FORCED COACH CRENSHAW
TO PUT ANDREA ON THE TEAM.
- WHAT WAS I SUPPOSED TO DO ?
SHE'S MY BEST FRIEND.
-  I DON'T KNOW.
IT'S NOT LIKE I MEANT
FOR US TO LOSE THE SEASON.
OH, NO.  I GOTTA GO.
ANDREA ?
ANDREA, WAIT UP !
ANDREA !
I WISH JOSH WAS HERE.
HE'D KNOW HOW TO HELP ME.
[ Whimpers ]
[ Barks ]
ALL RIGHT, BUDDY.
I'LL COME.
OKAY, BUDDY, I'M READY.
♪ THERE'S A POT OF GOLD
AT THE END OF THE RAINBOW ♪
♪ RING A BELL
WHAT A GREAT DAY ♪
♪ HOME RUN ♪
BUDDY, I GOT IT !
I GOT IT !
♪ I'M READY TO PLAY ♪
♪ AT THE CRACK OF THE BAT
I'LL BE OFF RUNNIN'
SLIDIN' INTO FIRST BASE ♪
♪ I'M MAKING THEM TAKE THE FIELD
FOR THIS PENNANT RACE ♪
♪ I'M READY TO SAY ♪
♪ TAKE ME
I'M READY TO PLAY ♪
[ Shrieks ]
BUDDY !
[ Shrieking ]
BUDDY, TURN IT OFF !
YOU CAN DO IT, BUDDY.
THAT'S A GOOD CATCH.
♪ THERE'S A BALL DOWN
THE MIDDLE OF THE PLATE NOW ♪
♪ HERE'S A CHANCE
FOR A GOLDEN GLOVE ♪
♪ GREAT CATCH
THAT'S THE WAY IT OUGHTA GO ♪
♪ IN THIS GAME I LOVE ♪
♪ IT'S THE BOTTOM OF THE NINTH
THE BASES ARE LOADED ♪
♪ TO THE CROWD
I TIP MY HAT ♪
I DIDN'T KNOW
YOU COULD DO THAT.
HERE COMES ANOTHER ONE,
BUDDY.
♪ HEY TEAM, HEY TEAM
I'M READY TO PLAY ♪
♪ LET ME GRAB A BAT
LET ME HIT AWAY ♪
♪ HEY TEAM, HEY TEAM
WON'T YOU PUT ME IN THE GAME ♪
♪ I'M READY TO LEAD US ON
ALL THE WAY ♪
♪ HEY TEAM
I'M READY TO PLAY ♪
♪ LET ME GRAB A BAT ♪
♪ HEY TEAM
WON'T YOU PUT ME IN THE GAME ♪
♪ I'M READY TO LEAD US ON
ALL THE WAY ♪
OH, MY GOSH, I DID IT !
[ Shrieks ]  BUDDY !
♪ AND IT'S GOIN'
GOIN', GOIN', GONE ♪
♪ GOIN', GOIN', GOIN', GONE ♪
♪ GOIN' ALL THE WAY
TO THE HALL OF FAME ♪♪
SHE'S GOING FOR HOME !
IS SHE GONNA MAKE IT ?
[ Laughing ]
SHERIFF, SHERIFF !
SORRY TO DISTURB YOU,
BUT DUKE-- HE'S GONE MISSING.
- DUKE ?  SOMEBODY I KNOW ?
- YEAH, MY DOG, DUKE.
WHAT ?
THOSE DAD-GUM DOGNAPPERS
ARE AT IT AGAIN !
WELL, WE HAVE GOT ONE OUT
AT THE TOP OF THE NINTH.
THE TIMBERWOLVES ARE
CLINGING TO A ONE-RUN LEAD
OVER THE TIGERS.
LET'S GO,
TIMBERWOLVES !
[ Father ]
WE GOT IT.
COME ON.
STRIKE TWO !
FOLKS, I DON'T THINK RANDY'S GOT
MUCH GAS LEFT IN HIS OLD ARM.
STRIKE 'IM OUT, RANDY !
BLITZ TWO !
PLAY IT TO TWO !
- SAFE !
- [ Cheering ]
I THINK WE MIGHT SEE
A PITCHING CHANGE HERE.
TIME.
TIME !
RANDY, YOU'RE DONE.
- WHAT ?  THE ARM'S FINE !
- GIMME THE BALL.
I'M NOT RISKING YOUR ARM.
NOW, WE'RE DOWN ONE PLAYER.
SO WE'RE GONNA HAVE TO GO
WITH TWO FIELDERS.
EXCUSE ME.  COACH ?
COACH, IS IT TOO LATE
IN THE SEASON FOR A NEW PLAYER
TO JOIN THE TEAM ?
WELL, NO, BUT-BUT--
WHO DO YOU HAVE IN MIND ?
[ Whistles ]
[ Girl ]
IT'S BUDDY !
WELL, I'LL BE.
LOOK, THEY'RE PUTTING
AIR BUD IN !
BUDDY ?
WHEN DID THAT HAPPEN ?
- THIS IS CERTAINLY
A STRANGE TURN OF EVENTS.
- YOU GOTTA BE KIDDING ME.
ANDREA FRAMM IS COMING IN
TO PITCH AND BUDDY'S PUT ON
A TIMBERWOLVES OUTFIT.
HE'S COMING IN
TO PLAY FIRST BASE.
AH, YEAH !
- THIS GAME'S GOING TO THE DOGS.
- YEAH, ANDREA !
SHE'S GONNA PITCH ?
[ Barking ]
LET'S PLAY BALL !
ALL RIGHT, ANDREA !
LET'S GO !
- MY BALL !
- YEAH !
- YOU'RE OUTTA THERE !
- [ Laughing ]
- GOOD JOB !
-  [ Child ]
ALL RIGHT, ANDREA !
- [ Barking ]
-  [ Child ]
YOU RULE, BUDDY !
- STRIKE ONE !
-  [ Crowd Cheers ]
[ Tammy ]
PITCH IT TO HIM HARD,
ANDREA !
STRIKE TWO !
NO BALLS !
TWO STRIKES !
[ Child's Voice ]
OH, HELLO, HELLO.
[ Kissing Sounds ]
YEAH, TERRANCE !
[ Tammy ]
YES !
GO, GO, GO !
- WAY TO GO, BOY !
- YEAH, BUDDY !
- [ Barking ]
AND THAT'S THE GAME !
THE TIMBERWOLVES WIN
FOUR TO THREE.
AND ANDREA FRAMM GOT
THE FINAL TWO OUTS TO WRAP
THINGS UP PRETTY GOOD.
- OUTTA THERE !
- [ Barking ]
- GOOD SHOT !
- [ Giggles ]
THE NEXT BATTER
FOR THE TIMBERWOLVES
IS BUDDY FRAMM.
GO, BUDDY !  WHOO !
YEAH, BUDDY !
[ Woman ]
THEY KNOW WHAT YOU'RE DOING.
- SAFE !
- [ Laughing, Cheering ]
WHOO !
I GOT IT !
YEAH !  YEAH, RUN !
STRIKE THREE !
HOW DO YOU LIKE THAT, FOLKS ?
THE TIMBERWOLVES WIN AGAIN.
NOW THEY'RE GOING TO FACE
THE DEFENDING CHAMPION BABOONS
IN THE LEAGUE FINAL.
[ Man ]
HEY, GANG, FREE HOT DOGS !
OH, I'M SO HUNGRY !
- HOW WAS BASEBALL ?
-  FINE.
I GUESS.
YOU SAW THE BABY'S ROOM ?
YOU MEAN, JOSH'S.
HONEY, WE'RE GONNA BUILD
A NEW ROOM ABOVE THE GARAGE
FOR JOSH.
THEN THE BABY CAN BE CLOSER
TO US AND HIS BIG SIS.
BUT, MOM--
HONEY, YOU SAID YOU
DIDN'T WANT HIS ROOM.
I KNOW.
I DIDN'T WANT JOSH'S ROOM
BECAUSE I JUST WANTED IT
TO STAY THE SAME.
OH.
HONEY, I WANT YOU
TO UNDERSTAND SOMETHING.
JUST BECAUSE WE'RE CHANGING
JOSH'S ROOM, DOESN'T MEAN...
WE'RE GETTING RID OF JOSH.
AND JUST BECAUSE WE HAVE
A NEW MEMBER IN THIS FAMILY,
DOESN'T MEAN
THAT HE OR YOU,
ANYTIME  EVER,
WILL BE REPLACED.
IT FEELS LIKE IT.
OH.
WE HAVE BEEN SO BUSY
WITH NOAH LATELY.
I'M SORRY IF YOU FELT LEFT OUT.
I SHOULD'VE TALKED TO YOU
ABOUT IT SOONER.
I MISS JOSH.
HONEY, I KNOW YOU DO.
SO DO I.
[ Whimpers ]
[ Sighs ]
OKAY, BUDDY, LET'S GO.
[ Gasps ]
OH, NO, JOSH'S WATCH !
[ Professor ]
THERE HE IS.
IT'S GOTTA BE HERE.
WHERE IS IT ?
ANDREA.
[ Chittering ]
WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE ?
YOUR MOM.
SHE SAID I'D FIND YOU HERE.
I CAME TO--
I DON'T NEED YOUR HELP.
YOU'VE HELPED ME ENOUGH.
DID YOU THINK YOU WERE HELPING
ME WHEN YOU HAD TO TALK TO THE
COACH TO GET ME ON THE TEAM ?
SORRY.  I SHOULD
HAVE TALKED TO YOU FIRST.
YEAH, YOU SHOULD'VE !
AND IF I HAD KNOWN--
WELL, I DON'T KNOW
EXACTLY WHAT.  BUT--
I ONLY DID IT
SO WE COULD PLAY TOGETHER.
WE DO EVERYTHING TOGETHER.
I DIDN'T WANNA PLAY
IF YOU WEREN'T GONNA BE
ON THE TEAM.
AND THAT'S EXACTLY WHAT
I TOLD COACH.
OH.
THERE'S ROCKY.
- [ Chittering ]
- [ Barks ]
[ Together ]
ROCKY !
-  [ Buddy Barking ]
- BUDDY ?  BUDDY !
BUDDY !
- WE HAVE GOT TO HURRY !
- BUDDY !  BUDDY !
-  HEY, THAT'S MY DOG !
- HURRY UP, GET IN THE CAR !
QUICK !  HURRY UP !
BUDDY !
QUICK,
GET YOUR BIKE !
GO, CARLTON, GO !
THEY'RE CHASING US !
FASTER !  FASTER !
I'M GOING AS FAST
AS I CAN.
[ Professor ]
MOVE !
-  [ Tires Screeching ]
-  PEDAL FASTER, ANDREA !
COME ON, TAMMY.
WE'RE GAINING ON 'EM !
QUICK !
THEY'RE AFTER US !  FASTER !
I'M GOING AS FAST AS I CAN.
DON'T.
STOP.  GET HIM OUTTA THE WAY.
[ Horn Honking ]
[ Both Screaming ]
MOMMY !
WHOO-OOO-OOO !
- [ Barking ]
- OKAY ?
-  [ Andrea ]
BUDDY !
- BEAUTIFUL.  [ Whistles ]
STOP !
THAT'S MY DOG !
OH, SHERIFF !
KEEP YOUR EYES ON THE ROAD !
I AM KEEPING MY EYES
ON THE ROAD.
[ Siren Wailing ]
THIS WAY !
[ Tammy ]
COME ON.
I THINK WE LOST 'EM.
[ Chuckles ]
WE'VE DONE IT, CARLTON.
WE HAVE THEM ALL.
[ Chuckling ]
THAT'S THEM !
HURRY, AFTER 'EM !
- GOOD WORK, CARLTON.
[ Chuckling ]OU, BOSS.
ANDREA, GO !
DAD-GUM,
WHERE THE HECK ARE THEY ?
[ Professor Chuckling ]
[ Laughing Continues ]
[ Barking ]
[ Laughing ]
[ Muttering ]
HEY, ROCKY.
HE STINKS !
[ Spitting ]
- WATCH THE ROAD !
- [ Screaming ]
BUDDY !
HEY THERE,
BASEBALL FANS !
WELCOME TO
THE CHAMPIONSHIP GAME
BETWEEN THE BABOONS...
AND YOUR OWN
FERNFIELD TIMBERWOLVES !
[ Grunting ]
GOOD NEWS FOR THE TIMBERWOLVES,
TAMMY SLAYTON WILL START TODAY'S
GAME BACK FROM THE INJURED LIST.
I DIDN'T SEE ANDREA, TAMMY
OR BUDDY ANYWHERE.
THEY SHOULD BE HERE
BY NOW.
COACH, I NEED A BATTER.
WELL, I'VE GOT THREE
OF MY PLAYERS STILL MISSING.
YEAH, I'M SORRY, COACH.
WE'RE GONNA HAVE TO START
WITHOUT 'EM.
LET'S... PLAY BALL !
THERE YA GO.
OH, NO !
IT LOOKS LIKE
THE TIMBERWOLVES...
ARE MISSING
THEIR THREE BEST PLAYERS--
ANDREA, TAMMY AND BUDDY.
[ Muffled Sounds ]
BATTER UP !
OH, THIS IS TERRIBLE NEWS
FOR FERNFIELD.
THEY'LL HAVE
TO START THE GAME
WITH NOT A FULL ROSTER.
WHAT WILL WE DO
IF THEY DON'T SHOW UP ?
[ Sighs ]
WELL, I'M AFRAID, TERRANCE,
WE'RE JUST GONNA HAVE TO DO
THE BEST WE CAN
WITH WHATEVER TEAM WE'VE GOT.
COME ON, THIS WAY.
THEY'RE SNEAKIN' AROUND.
OH, I BET THEY'RE ALL
IN THERE.
[ Barking ]
OH, YOU STUPID--
LET GO OF HIM.
WELL, FOLKS, IT LOOKS LIKE
THE BABOONS' PITCHER HAS BROUGHT
HIS "A" GAME TO THE BALLPARK.
STRIKE THREE !
[ Echo ]
THREE !  THREE !
HE IS THROWING SOME
SERIOUS HEAT OUT THERE.
EXCUSE ME.
DID YOU FIND HER ?
NO, I HAVEN'T.
I CALLED TAMMY'S HOUSE.
NOBODY'S HOME.
SHE KNEW WHEN THE GAME STARTED.
I CAN'T IMAGINE SHE'D FORGET.
I KNOW.
[ Terrance ]
MY BALL !
SAFE !
AND HE'S SAFE AT THE PLATE.
THE BABOONS ARE QUICKLY
ON BOARD, ONE TO NOTHING.
[ Cackling ]
[ Chitters ]
[ Barking ]
WELL, LET'S GO.
[ Chittering ]
[ Barking ]
- [ Barks ]
- BUDDY.
BUDDY.
[ Barks ]
TABLE.
- [ Barks ]
- HURRY.
- DID YOU HEAR SOMETHING ?
- SHH !
JOSH'S WATCH.
THANKS, BUDDY.
I GOTTA GET YOU OUTTA HERE.
[ Whispering ]
HURRY, ANDREA.
[ Barking ]
SHH !  QUIET !
[ Andrea ]
COME ON, GUYS, HURRY !
[ Gasps, Gulps ]
PROFESSOR !
GO... AFTER THEM !
[ Professor ]
GET IN THE CAR !
[ Barking ]
GO, GO, GO !
NO !  STOP, STOP, STOP !
IDIOT !  GO !
NOW GO !  GO !
RANDY'S GOT HIMSELF
IN A BIND HERE, FOLKS.
THE BASES ARE LOADED
AND THE BABOONS' CLEANUP
HITTER IS AT THE DISH.
[ Man ]
COME ON NOW.
AND THERE'S A LINE SHOT
UP THE MIDDLE THAT'S GOING
RIGHT TO THE FENCE, FOLKS.
TWO RUNS ARE GONNA SCORE
FOR SURE.
HERE COMES THE RELAY
FROM CENTER FIELD.
OH, IT'S NOT EVEN CLOSE.
S-SAFE !
THAT'S THREE RUNS.
AND THE BABOONS NOW LEAD
FOUR TO NOTHING.
I TELL YA, RANDY'S
LOSING IT OUT THERE.
AND STILL ANDREA,
TAMMY AND BUDDY ARE
NOWHERE TO BE SEEN.
WE'RE LOSING THEM.
FASTER, FASTER !
HURRY !
[ Siren Wailing ]
EH.  OH, DARN.
ALL RIGHT, COME OUT OF THERE,
YOU VARMINTS !
WHAT THE HECK ?
WHERE DO YOU THINK
YOU'RE GOIN' ?
- WHAT-WHAT DO YOU--
- [ Chittering ]
OKAY.  I HOPE
YOU DON'T GET CARSICK.
BACK AT THE BALLPARK,
AND THE TIMBERWOLVES...
ARE REALLY STRUGGLING
WITH THIS TOUGH
BABOON TEAM.
- RUN IT OUT, BABY !
RUN IT OUT !
-  SAFE !  OH !
BABOONS' BIG SLUGGER
STEPS UP TO THE PLATE.
[ Kid ]  HIT IT OVER THE FENCE.
HERE'S THE PITCH !
SWING !
IT'S A LONG HIT TO LEFT !
IT'S, IT'S OUTTA HERE !
TWO MORE RUNS SCORED.
THAT'S SIX TO ONE
FOR THE BABOONS.
THINGS ARE LOOKING HOPELESS
FOR FERNFIELD.
RANDY'S ARM IS SHOT.
THERE'S NO RELIEF
ON THE BENCH.
AND WORST OF ALL...
WE'RE STILL MISSING
ANDREA, TAMMY AND BUDDY
FROM THE FIELD.
THEY'RE GAINING ON US !
QUICK.  WE'VE GOT THEM !
WE'VE GOT THEM NOW !
[ Laughing ]
- HURRY UP, TAMMY !
- I'M A-GOIN'.
WAIT.
WHERE'S THE NET ?
OH, I'LL GET IT.
NO !
WHAT ARE YOU DOING, YOU IDIOT ?
GET THAT--
I CAN'T SEE !
PROFESSOR !
MY EYES !
GET IT OFF OF ME !
[ Squealing ]
GET IT OFF ME, CARLTON !
[ Barking ]
PROFESSOR !
WHAT ?
WHOA.  WHOA !
- [ Squealing ]
- [ Grunts ]
OH, NO, THE GAME !
COME ON !
STRIKE THREE !
YOU'RE OUTTA HERE !
HE STRIKES HIM OUT AGAIN.
THE FERNFIELD TIMBERWOLVES
GO OUT IN ORDER AGAIN,
AND THE BABOONS
KEEP ROLLING ALONG.
[ Siren Wailing ]
AHH... YUCK !
CARLTON !
SORRY.
YOU'RE SORRY ?
- YOU'RE SORRY ?
YOU, YOU IDIOT !
- I'M NOT AN IDIOT !
[ Siren Wailing,
Brakes Squealing ]
[ Siren Wailing ]
GET OUT OF MY WAY !
LET, LET GO OF ME !
OHHH !
WHAT ARE YOU LOOKING AT ?
THIS IS ALL YOUR--
OHHH !  A POND.
[ Laughing ]
NICE GOIN', BOYS.
Y'ALL SURE LOOK CUTE
OUT THERE.
[ Laughing ]
GIVE IT TO ME !
HMPH.
[ Groans ]
[ Laughing ]
[ Squealing ]
[ Barking ]
STRIKE... THREE !
SWING AND A MISS.  SHE STRUCK
HIM OUT.  THAT'S TERRANCE'S
THIRD WHIFF ON THE AFTERNOON.
[ Man ]
HURRY !
COME LOOK AT THE DOGS !
[ Tammy ]
I HOPE WE'RE NOT TOO LATE.
DON'T WORRY, WE'LL MAKE IT.
[ Crowd ]
♪ TAKE ME OUT
TO THE BALL GAME ♪
TO THE SHOW ♪
♪ BUY ME SOME PEANUTS
AND CRACKER JACKS ♪
♪ I DON'T CARE
IF I EVER GET BACK ♪
♪ 'CAUSE IT'S ROOT, ROOT
ROOT FOR THE HOME TEAM ♪♪
- THERE'S ANDREA AND TAMMY !
-  AND BUDDY AND THE PUPS !
- HEY, THERE'S BUDDY !
- [ Barking ]
- ZACK !
- SHOOTER ?
- STRIKER !
- DUKE !
[ Mailman Phil ]
HOLY COW !
I DON'T BELIEVE WHAT I'M SEEING.
FERNFIELD'S MISSING PLAYERS
ARE BACK !
IT'S A WHOLE NEW BALL GAME !
[ Laughing ]
THERE'S YOUR SISTER.
LET'S PLAY BALL !
YOU'RE UP.
[ Barking ]
[ Mr. Fusilli ]
LET'S GO, TIMBERWOLVES !
THE TIMBERWOLVES LOOK LIKE
THEY HAVE NEW ENERGY
WITH ANDREA AND BUDDY BACK.
BUT COULD IT BE TOO LITTLE,
TOO LATE ?
WE'LL HAVE TO SEE, BECAUSE
THE BABOONS HAVE A SEVEN
TO ONE COMMANDING LEAD...
HERE IN THE TOP
OF THE SEVENTH.
THERE'S A SHARP GROUND BALL
TO TERRANCE.
HE'S UP AND OVER
TO FIRST.
- YOU'RE OUTTA THERE !
- [ Cheering ]
GREAT ARM, ANDREA !
[ Child ]
YOU RULE, BUDDY !
HERE'S THE PITCH
FROM ANDREA.
IT'S A TOWERING FLY BALL
WAY OVER TOP
OF HOME PLATE.
- YEAH !  GOOD JOB !
- [ Barking ]
MMM, YEAH.
AND HERE'S THE PITCH
ON THE WAY FROM ANDREA.
POP FLY TO LEFT.
EASY OUT.
NICE WORK BY FRAMM.
SHE SHUT DOWN THE BABOONS
AT THE TOP OF THE SEVENTH.
NOW THE TIMBERWOLVES
ARE GONNA HAVE TO...
GET A RALLY GOING
IF THEY WANNA COME BACK
AND WIN THIS GAME.
-  THAT'S A SOLID LINE DRIVE
BASE HIT UP THE MIDDLE.
- GOOD JOB.
ANDREA TAKES A LEAD
OFF FIRST BASE.  SHE MIGHT
BE THINKING OF STEALING.
AND THERE SHE GOES !
LOOK AT HER GO !
RUN, ANDREA, RUN !
SAFE !
THAT'S SOME REAL HEADS-UP
BASE RUNNING BY ANDREA...
AS SHE MOVES
INTO SCORING POSITION.
SHE'S GOT THIS TIMBERWOLVES
TEAM ALL FIRED UP.
-  [ Player ]
THAT WAS GREAT, ANDREA !
-  HERE'S THE PITCH.
GROUND BALL RIGHT
TO THE SECOND BASEMAN.
ANDREA'S CAUGHT IN A RUN-DOWN.
OVER TO THE THIRD BASEMAN.
OH, SHE'S A DEAD DUCK.
UH-OH !
-  ANDREA'S SAFE AT THIRD.
- [ Cheering ]
SAFE !
[ Cheering ]
[ Shouting ]
[ Howling ]
AT THE END
OF THE SEVENTH INNING,
THE TIMBERWOLVES HAVE
NARROWED THE BABOONS' LEAD
TO FIVE RUNS.
THAT'S A HARD HIT BALL
TO TERRANCE.
HE'S UP WITH IT CLEANLY.
OVER TO FIRST.
AND IT'S BUDDY
WITH THE OUT !
[ Cheering ]
THERE'S A SWING AND
A HARD LINER TO LEFT FIELD
FOR A BASE HIT.
WHOO !
ALL RIGHT !
AND ANOTHER SHOT
TO LEFT FIELD !
- GO, TERRANCE !
-  HERE COMES TERRANCE.
HE'S GONNA TRY TO SCORE.
- SAFE !
- YEAH !  WHOO-HOO !
AT THE END OF EIGHT INNINGS,
THE BABOONS LEAD THE
TIMBERWOLVES SEVEN TO THREE.
A HARD-HIT BALL
TO LEFT FIELD.
SAF--  OUTTA THERE !
- AND THE PITCH FROM ANDREA.
-  YOU GOT IT, BUDDY !
-  OH, WHAT A GREAT CATCH
BY BUDDY !
- ANDREA !
- WAY TO GO, BUDDY !
-  WELL, DESPITE ANDREA'S
SOLID PITCHING PERFORMANCE,
IT'S STILL NOT LOOKING
TOO GOOD FOR FERNFIELD.
THEY'RE DOWN BY FOUR
HEADING INTO THE NINTH.
THEY'RE GONNA NEED
A MIRACLE IF THEY'RE GONNA
WIN THIS CHAMPIONSHIP.
ALL RIGHT, NOW,
WE'VE ALL BEEN HERE BEFORE.
YOU ALL KNOW WHAT TO DO.
AND I JUST WANNA TELL YOU GUYS
IT'S REALLY BEEN MY HONOR
COACHING YOU THIS YEAR.
ALL RIGHT ?
SO, ALL IN.
ONE, TWO, THREE--
TIMBERWOLVES !
HEY, MOM.
HONEY !
HI !
HOW'S IT GOIN' ?
OH, MY GOSH !
HOW'S IT GOING ?
I DIDN'T KNOW
YOU WERE GONNA DRIVE UP.
I DIDN'T KNOW YOU
WERE COMING.  YOU JUST--
SNUCK IN.
DID YOU COME TO SURPRISE
YOUR SISTER ?
YEAH, I JUST CAME.
OH !
YOU'RE SO BIG !
SEE, IT'S YOUR BROTHER.
IT'S NO BALLS AND
ONE STRIKE TO TERRANCE.
HERE'S THE PITCH.
STRIKE TWO !
STRIKE THREE !
YOU'RE OUTTA HERE !
THE BABOONS ARE ONLY
TWO OUTS AWAY FROM WINNING
ANOTHER LEAGUE TITLE.
LET'S GO !
OH, THE TIMBERWOLVES ARE
DOWN TO THEIR FINAL OUT.
IT LOOKS LIKE THE BABOONS
ARE GONNA WIN THEIR THIRD
STRAIGHT LEAGUE CHAMPIONSHIP.
THE NEXT BATTER
FOR THE TIMBERWOLVES
IS BUDDY FRAMM.
IT'S OKAY, GUYS.
I CAN HANDLE BUDDY.
[ Man ]
AHH, BUDDY !
THERE'S A SWING
AND A HOT GROUND BALL
TO THE SHORTSTOP.
HE'S UP WITH IT.
BUDDY'S GOT HIS JETS ON.
- SAFE !
- WHOO !
THAT'S WHAT I CALL
DOGGED DETERMINATION.
BUDDY'S ON FIRST
AND THE TIMBERWOLVES
ARE STILL ALIVE.
BUDDY'S GONNA TRY
FOR SECOND !
- AND HE'S THERE !
- WAY TO GO, BUDDY !
THERE'S A GROUND BALL
TO THE RIGHT SIDE OF
THE INFIELD FOR A BASE HIT.
BUDDY, HOME !
IT LOOKS LIKE BUDDY'S
GONNA TRY TO SCORE !
SLIDE, SLIDE, SLIDE !
- SAFE !
- WHOO !
GOOD SLIDE !
THE LEAD IS DOWN TO THREE.
NOW TAMMY IS UP
FOR THE TIMBERWOLVES.
LET'S SEE IF SHE CAN KEEP
THIS RALLY GOIN'.
HERE'S THE PITCH.
STRIKE ONE !
WAIT A MINUTE, FOLKS.
TAMMY IS SWITCHING
TO BAT LEFT-HANDED.
YOU DON'T SEE THAT
VERY OFTEN.  LET'S SEE HOW
THE BABOON PITCHER REACTS.
SWING AND A HARD BALL
TO LEFT !
WAY TO GO, TAMMY !
YEAH !
[ Crowd Cheering ]
NOW RANDY'S UP.
LET'S SEE WHAT HE CAN DO.
SWING AND IT'S A LONG DRIVE
TO RIGHT FIELD.
THE BALL IS GOING WAY BACK
TO THE FENCE.
- SAFE !
-  HE'S SAFE !
WELL, BASEBALL FANS,
IT DOESN'T GET ANY MORE
EXCITING THAN THIS.
THE TIMBERWOLVES ARE DOWN
BY ONE RUN.
BOTTOM OF THE NINTH.
TWO OUT.  ANDREA FRAMM
REPRESENTS THE WINNING RUN.
YOU COULD CUT THE TENSION
IN THIS BALLPARK
WITH A KNIFE.
YOU CAN DO IT,
ANDREA.
[ Whispering ]
OUT OF THE PARK.
JOSH !
GOOD LUCK.
WHAT A PRESSURE SITUATION
FOR ANDREA.
IT'S ALL UP TO HER NOW.
HERE'S THE PITCH.
OOH !  ANDREA TOOK
A BIG CUT ON THAT ONE.
STRIKE ONE !
IT'S OKAY, HONEY.
WAIT FOR IT.
KEEP YOUR EYE ON THE BALL.
FOLLOW IT THROUGH THE ZONE.
STRIKE TWO !
SHE'S DOWN
TO HER LAST STRIKE, FOLKS !
TIME.
TIME !
IT'S OKAY.
[ Barking ]
AND THERE'S A LONG DRIVE
BACK TO RIGHT FIELD !
RUN !
IT'S GOING BACK, BACK,
BACK, BACK !
RUN, ANDREA, RUN !
SAFE !
[ Cheering ]
FERNFIELD WINS !
[ Laughing ]
[ Crowd Chanting ]
ANDREA !  ANDREA !
[ Chanting ]
AND THIS JUST IN, FOLKS.
ANDREA FRAMM HAS WON M.V.P.
OF THIS YEAR'S FINALS.
WAY TO GO, ANDREA !
THANKS.
HEY, ANDREA.
GREAT GAME.
THIS BELONGS TO YOU.
THANKS.
JOSH, YOU CAME !
WOULDN'T HAVE MISSED
THE BIG GAME.
YOU PLAYED SO AWESOME !
LET'S GO.
I MISSED YOU SO MUCH.
[ Phone Ringing ]
HELLO ?
YOU MEAN BUDDY ?
WELCOME BACK TO EDISON FIELD
IN ANAHEIM, CALIFORNIA,
WHERE THE ANAHEIM ANGELS...
ARE NOW JUST TWO OUTS AWAY
FROM WINNING THEIR FIRST EVER
WORLD SERIES.
THIS WILL MOST CERTAINLY
BE REMEMBERED AS ONE OF THE
GREATEST WORLD SERIES OF ALL.
THESE ANAHEIM ANGELS
HAVE BEEN ELECTRIFIED...
BY THE SENSATIONAL PLAY
OF THEIR FIRST BASEMAN, AIR BUD.
HERE'S THE PITCH.
GROUND BALL
TO THE SECOND BASEMAN.
HE MIGHT BE ABLE TO TURN TWO.
HE TAGS THE BAG FOR ONE.
THERE'S THE THROW.
AND THAT'S IT.
THE ANAHEIM ANGELS HAVE WON
THE WORLD SERIES !
ALL RIGHT, BUDDY !
WHOO !  BUDDY !
BUDDY !  BUDDY !
AIR BUD HAS DONE IT AGAIN !
♪ MMM-MMM ♪
♪ WHAT WE'VE LEARNED
FROM EACH OTHER ♪
♪ COULDN'T FIT
IN A SINGLE BOOK ♪
♪ SOMETIMES A THOUSAND WORDS
AREN'T WORTH ♪
♪ AS MUCH AS A SINGLE LOOK ♪
♪ THEY SAY GRASSES ARE GREENER ♪
♪ ON THE OTHER SIDE
OF THE HILL ♪
♪ NOTHING CAN BRIGHTEN
YOUR OWN BACKYARD ♪
♪ THE WAY A FRIENDSHIP WILL ♪
♪ WHENEVER I NEED
A HELPING HAND ♪
♪ OR TWO OR THREE OR FOUR ♪
♪ YOU ARE THERE
TO UNDERSTAND ♪
♪ AND I DON'T NEED ANY MORE ♪
♪ THEY SAY YOU CAN'T WEATHER
THE STORM ♪
♪ TILL YOU LEARN TO FLY
WITH THE WIND ♪
♪ LIKE BIRDS OF A FEATHER
WE'LL STICK TOGETHER ♪
♪ GET OUT OF ANY TROUBLE
THAT WE GET INTO ♪
♪ FRIENDS
WE'RE SUCH AN UNLIKELY PAIR ♪
♪ TO THE END ♪
♪ KNOWING EACH OTHER
WILL ALWAYS BE THERE ♪
♪ TOGETHER WHENEVER
THE GOING GETS TOUGH ♪
♪ THE WATERS OF LIFE
SEEM TOO ROUGH FOR US ♪
♪ TOGETHER
OUR FRIENDSHIP WILL ALWAYS ♪
♪ ALWAYS BE THERE ♪
♪ MMM, MMM, MMM ♪
♪ WILL ALWAYS BE THERE ♪
♪ WILL ALWAYS BE THERE ♪♪