[ Backfiring ]
♪♪ [ Organ ]
- YOU HAVE THE RING, RIGHT ?
- YEAH.
OKAY.
UH-OH.
[ Whining ]
GO.  GO GET THE RING
ON THE DRESSER.
ARE YOU OKAY ?
YEAH.
BUDDY'LL BE RIGHT BACK.
[ Man ]
HEY, BUDDY.
[ Barking ]
[ Barks ]
HOW'D THAT GET UP THERE ?
- COME ON, FRANK.  LET'S GO.
- [ Whimpering ]
♪♪ [ Continues ]
♪♪ [ Humming ]
SHALL WE ?
OKAY.
[ Chuckling ]
[ Man ]
HEY !  LOOK OUT !
♪♪ [ Wedding March ]
[ Door Opens ]
[ Murmuring ]
[ Vehicle Approaching,
Backfires ]
[ Whining ]
[ Minister ]
WE ARE GATHERED HERE
IN THE SIGHT OF GOD...
TO WITNESS THESE TWO PEOPLE...
UNITED IN HOLY MATRIMONY.
[ Woman ]
WHERE ARE YOU GOING, BUDDY ?
NOW, PATRICK,
IF YOU WILL PLACE...
THE RING UPON
THE THIRD FINGER...
OF JACKIE'S LEFT HAND.
[ Barks ]
[ Clears Throat ]
HEY, THANKS, BUDDY.
BY THE POWER
INVESTED IN ME,
I PRONOUNCE YOU
HUSBAND AND WIFE.
YOU MAY KISS THE BRIDE.
-  [ Guests Murmuring ]
- [ Giggles ]
[ Chuckles ]
[ Laughing ]
♪ IT'S THE WAY YOU SMILE
WHEN YOU LOOK MY WAY ♪
♪ YOUR CRAZY MOVES
MAKE ME LAUGH ALL DAY ♪
♪ IT'S THE BUTTERFLIES
I GET INSIDE ♪
♪ WHEN I FEEL YOUR HEARTBEAT
NEXT TO MINE ♪
♪ LOVE ♪
♪ SPARKLES LIKE A DIAMOND RING ♪
♪ YOU FIND IT IN
THE LITTLE THINGS ♪
♪ IT'S PERFECTLY CLEAR
THERE'S NO DOUBT ♪
♪ THAT'S WHAT LOVE ♪
-SO, WHAT DO YOU THINK ?
THEY MAKE A PRETTY GOOD COUPLE.
-YEAH, THEY SEEM HAPPY ENOUGH.
♪ IT'S HOLDING HANDS
IN A MATINEE ♪
[ Girl ]
UH-OH, IT'S TIMMY SANDERS.
♪ IT'S A TOP-DOWN DRIVE
'NEATH THE AUTUMN MOON ♪
WHAT DO YOU SAY, ANDREA ?
TIME FOR A LITTLE SOCCER ?
I'D SAY...
IT SOUNDS GOOD TO ME.
♪ LOVE ♪
♪ YOU FIND IT
IN THE LITTLE THINGS ♪
♪ IT'S PERFECTLY CLEAR
THERE'S NO DOUBT ♪
♪ THAT'S WHAT LOVE
IS ALL ABOUT ♪
[ Chattering ]
[ Buddy Barking ]
- OVER HERE !  BUDDY.  HEY.
-  [ Barking Continues ]
[ Girl ]
ANDREA, PASS IT!
BUDDY !
♪ IT'S PERFECTLY CLEAR
THERE'S NO DOUBT
THAT'S WHAT LOVE ♪
♪ IS ALL ABOUT ♪♪
[ Vehicle Backfires ]
[ Whimpers ]
BUDDY !
[ Andrea ]
BUDDY, WHERE ARE YOU ?
[ Buddy Whimpers ]
[ Gasps ]
ONE RETRIEVER.
TWO RETRIEVERS ?
OOH-HOO.
SO, WHAT DO YOU SAY, KIDS ?
WHO'S GONNA HELP ME CARRY MOM
OVER THE THRESHOLD ?
I THINK YOU'RE GONNA HAVE
YOUR HANDS FULL JUST WITH
THE PRESENTS AND THE KIDS.
[ Andrea ]
ISN'T THAT WHAT THEY DO IN,
LIKE, OLD MOVIES OR SOMETHING ?
ALL RIGHT, EVERYBODY OUT !
ALL RIGHT, BUDDY.
LET'S GO.
COME ON.
OKAY, EVERYBODY
GRAB SOME PRESENTS.
[ Screams ]
I GOT IT.
[ Chuckling ]
LET'S GET THIS THING
OFF OF YOU.
CAREFUL.
OKAY, I GOT THESE.
OH, I'M FINE, MOM.
OH !
COME ON, ANDREA.
WHOA !
ARE YOU ALL RIGHT
BACK THERE ?
AAH !  ALL RIGHT, TREE.
ALL RIGHT.
MOM, WHAT DO YOU THINK
DAD'S THINKING RIGHT NOW ?
YOU MEAN
BECAUSE I'VE REMARRIED ?
YEAH.  DO YOU THINK
HE KNOWS ?
I'M SURE HE DOES.
I THINK HE'S VERY HAPPY
FOR US.
YOU THINK HE'S HAPPY ?
SURE I DO.
I KNOW HE'D LIKE PATRICK,
AND HE'D BE VERY HAPPY...
THAT I FOUND SOMEONE
WHO LOVES US SO MUCH.
YEAH, HE DOES LOVE US A LOT.
YOU REMEMBER,
YOU CAN TALK TO YOUR DAD
ABOUT HIM ANYTIME.
HMM ?  HE'D LIKE TO HEAR
WHAT YOU HAVE TO SAY.
I DO.  IT'S JUST--
I WISH I COULD HEAR HIM
TALKING BACK.
I KNOW.
GOOD NIGHT, SWEETHEART.
GOOD NIGHT.
[ Door Opens, Closes ]
[ Boy ]
HI, BUDDY.
[ Man ]
HEY, BUDDY.
[ Woman ]
HELLO, SUNSHINE.
HEY THERE, BOY.
[ Barks ]
HEY, BUDDY.
[ Barking ]
[ Door Closes ]
[ Whimpers ]
[ Man ]
ALL RIGHT, GIRL.  COME ON.
BACK INSIDE.
-  [ Door Closes ]
- [ Whimpering ]
[ Vehicle Backfiring ]
I THINK IT'S A POOL.
THEY GOT A POOL.
WHOA, YOU WEREN'T KIDDING.
THESE PEOPLE ARE RICH.
OH, MAN, I CHASED THAT
LITTLE POOCH ALL OVER TOWN
THIS MORNING.
SHE GAVE ME THE SLIP.
BUT AT SOME POINT...
ALL LITTLE DOGGIES
GOTTA COME HOME.
SO WE'RE GONNA GRAB HER
TONIGHT, RIGHT ?
WEBSTER, YOU'RE TALKING
ABOUT BREAKING AND ENTERING.
YOU DO NOT BREAK AND ENTER
WITHOUT DOING ALL
YOUR HOMEWORK FIRST.
YOU GOT THE FIRST WATCH,
RIGHT ?
"ENTER AND BREAK."
♪♪ [ Humming ]
[ Water Running ]
[ Water Off ]
WHAT'S THAT ?
WELL, IT'S...
A COMBINATION JACKKNIFE,
SCREWDRIVER, WHISTLE.
MY GRANDFATHER
GAVE IT TO MY FATHER,
AND MY FATHER GAVE IT TO ME.
YOU SHOULD HAVE IT.
OH.  YOU SURE ?
I'M SURE.
THANKS.
IT ALWAYS BROUGHT ME
GOOD LUCK.
HUH ?  BUDDY ?
[ Groans ]
[ Door Closes ]
[ Sniffing ]
[ Whimpers ]
[ Snoring, Murmuring ]
[ Bell Ringing ]
SO, UH, MOM'S GONNA
PICK YOU UP, ALL RIGHT ?
I GOTTA GO TO THE LIBRARY.
NO PROBLEM, BRO.
BYE, BUDDY.
HEY, TAMMY !
- [ Buddy Barks Softly ]
- COME ON, BUDDY.  LET'S GO.
[ Whistle Blowing ]
GATHER AROUND, PLEASE.
I'M SORRY I'M LATE.
YOU KNOW, FIRST DAY
OF SCHOOL AND ALL.
WELL, I'M EMMA PUTTER,
BUT YOU CAN ALL CALL ME EMMA.
I'LL BE HELPING YOU ALL WITH
THE FUNDAMENTALS FOR TODAY.
FOOTBALL IS A CHALLENGING SPORT
THAT WE CAN ALL ENJOY IF YOU
JUST UNDERSTAND THE BASICS.
COACH EMMA, I THOUGHT
WE WERE HERE TO PLAY SOCCER.
[ Tammy ]  YEAH.
WE ARE.  SOCCER AND FOOTBALL
ARE SYNONYMOUS.
[ Whispering ]
WHAT'S A "SIMINIMISH" ?
BEATS ME.
- WELL, HOW ABOUT
WE GET STARTED ?
- OKAY.
[ Girls Chattering ]
[ Emma ]
EVERYBODY GETS A BALL.
TRY AND KEEP IT OFF THE GROUND.
DO IT LIKE THIS.
THERE YOU GO.
KEEP YOUR KNEES UP.
♪ I FEEL LOVE IN THE AIR ♪
♪ WHEN I SIT HERE WITH YOU ♪
♪ NOTHING BOTHERS ME ♪
♪ WHERE IT ALWAYS USED TO ♪
♪ I WILL TAKE YOUR HAND
I WILL NEVER LET IT GO ♪
♪ AND THEN TIME'LL
STAND STILL ♪
♪ AS OUR FEELINGS GROW ♪
♪ AND IT TURNS ME 'ROUND
WHEN I SEE YOU SMILE ♪
♪ AND IT PICKS ME UP ♪
♪ WHEN I'M FEELING DOWN ♪
♪ AND IT SPINS ME 'ROUND ♪
♪ WHEN I SEE YOU SMILE ♪
♪ AND IT PICKS ME UP ♪
♪ WHEN I'M FEELING DOWN ♪
NO HANDS.
GO, TAMMY !
[ Emma ]
THAT'S GOOD.
♪ I LOOK INTO YOUR EYES ♪
♪ AND I SEE MYSELF WITH YOU ♪
♪ JUST TO WATCH YA SMILE ♪
♪ IS A GIFT I HOLD TRUE ♪
[ Whistle Blowing ]
OKAY.  WELL, THAT'S IT
FOR TODAY'S PRACTICE.
IT WAS A REALLY GOOD ONE.
AND I'LL SEE YOU ALL
TOMORROW AT 3:00.
[ All ]
OKAY.  THANK YOU.
BYE-BYE.
EMMA, EMMA, WAIT.
UM, THERE'S SOMEONE
I WANT YOU TO MEET.
OKAY.
- EMMA, THIS IS MY COOL
BIG BROTHER JOSH.
- HELLO, COOL BIG BROTHER JOSH.
NICE TO MEET YOU.
UM, NEW HERE ?
WE JUST MOVED HERE
FROM ENGLAND.
- I OVERHEARD YOU WERE
GOING TO SCHOOL AT, UM--
- FERNFIELD HIGH SCHOOL.
YEAH.
EMMA, HELP !  MY FOOT'S STUCK !
PLEASE, HELP !
EXCUSE ME.
SOMEBODY NEEDS MY HELP.
-  ♪ AND IT TURNS ME 'ROUND ♪
- WE'LL SEE YOU A-AROUND.
♪ WHEN I SEE YOU SMILE ♪
♪ AND IT PICKS ME UP ♪
HI, MOMMY.
♪ WHEN I'M FEELING DOWN ♪
HEY.
OH.  HEY, MOM.
[ Chuckling ]
WHY ARE YOU STILL HERE ?
UM, I WASN'T SURE IF
YOU'D REMEMBER TO, UH--
TO PICK UP ANDREA.
UH-HUH.
OH.  THERE WE GO.
THANK YOU, EMMA.
OH, I SEE.
[ Chuckling ]
WELL, I'LL, UH,
SEE YOU AROUND.
♪ AND IT TURNS ME ON ♪
♪ WHEN I SEE YOU SMILE
AND IT PICKS ME UP ♪
-  ♪ WHEN I'M FEELING DOWN ♪♪
- OH, MRS. BRIMSTONE, YOU WILL
NOT BELIEVE WHO I JUST MET.
[ Emma ]
KATE, OVER HERE !
THAT'S HER.
THE GIRL IN THE PURPLE.
ALL WE NEED
ARE THREE MORE PLAYERS
FOR THE FOOTBALL TEAM.
THE COACH'LL TAKE ANYBODY
WHO SHOWS UP AT THIS POINT.
[ Girl ]
THOSE GUYS ARE SO CUTE
IN THEIR UNIFORMS.
- WHAT TIME'S PRACTICE TODAY ?
I'M GONNA COME WATCH.
-  AFTER LAST CLASS.
SORRY, PAL.
I GOTTA GO.
YES, YOU SHOULD COME.
IT'S REALLY A BLAST.
PASS IT OVER HERE, MAN.
CHECK IT, DUDE.
[ Chuckling, Chattering ]
BOTH HANDS.
OH, SEE ?  SEE ?
[ Whistle Blowing ]
OKAY.
SHH.  COACH, COACH.
COME ON, GUYS.
WELL.
IS THIS EVERYONE ?
[ Clicks Teeth ]
[ Players Chiding,
Chuckling ]
EXCUSE ME.
READY, COACH.
ALL RIGHT.  FOR, UM--
FOR EVERYONE'S INFORMATION,
SHIN GUARDS ARE THE ONLY
REQUIRED PADDING...
[ Chuckling Continues ]
IN SOCCER.
WELL, THIS IS GOOD,
BUT BEFORE WE CAN FIELD A TEAM,
WE NEED TWO MORE PLAYERS.
ANYBODY ?
COUNT ME IN, COACH.
HEY, THERE'S NO ROOM HERE
FOR BASKETBALL PLAYERS.
THE TEAM'S FULL.
I ONLY COUNT NINE.  THAT MEANS
THERE'S TWO SPOTS LEFT.
[ Players Murmuring ]
SETTLE DOWN, BOYS.
THERE'S ROOM ON THE FIELD
FOR EVERYBODY.
[ Clears Throat ]
ARE YOU REALLY GONNA PLAY
WITH ALL THAT ON ?
UH, NO ?
- ALL RIGHT.
- OKAY.
UM, PHYSICAL CONTACT
IS A PENALTY, RIGHT, COACH ?
[ Players Laughing ]
EEEH, YEAH.
OKAY.  THE IDEA IS TO
KEEP THE BALL MOVING.
TRY TO ANTICIPATE
ANY OPPORTUNITIES.
ALL RIGHT.
LET'S SEE WHAT WE'VE GOT.
HERE.
♪ I TRY TO SEE
THE BRIGHT SIDE ♪
OKAY, COME ON, GUYS.
LET'S GO !  HUSTLE UP !
I GOT IT, I GOT IT.
WHOA, WHOA.
-  ♪ PAST A CERTAIN POINT ♪
- JOSH, TAKE IT.
- [ Grunts ]
- WATCH IT.  SORRY.
[ Coach ]
COME ON, JOSH.
GET ON YOUR FEET.
[ Spanish ]
♪ MAN, THIS IS GONNA BE TOUGH ♪
♪ BUT WE'RE STARTING SO LOW ♪
-  ♪ THERE'S NO WAY TO GO
BUT UP ♪
- [ Both Giggling ]
-  [ Whistle Blowing ]
-  [ Coach ]  USE YOUR HEAD.
COME ON !
♪ IT COULDN'T GET MUCH WORSE ♪
♪ AND THIS BETTER GET BETTER ♪
[ Coach Shouting ]
PASS THE BALL !
I AM THE MASTER.
-  [ Coach ]
YOU'RE NOT PASSING ENOUGH.
-  ♪ NOW I DON'T MIND ♪
♪ IF IT TAKES SOME TIME ♪
♪ BUT IT BETTER
GET BETTER FIRST ♪
♪ NOW, I DON'T MIND
IF IT TAKES SOME TIME ♪
-  ♪ BUT IT BETTER
GET BETTER FIRST ♪
-  [ Emma ]  YES !
[ Whimpers ]
SORRY.  I CAN'T
HELP MYSELF SOMETIMES.
NICE MOVES, PUTTER.
HEY, DO YOU WANT
TO SHOW ME SOMETIME ?
YEAH.  OKAY.
[ Coach ]
OKAY, TEAM, GATHER AROUND.
[ Whistle Blowing ]
SAM, YOU'RE UP.
WATCH AND LEARN.
I DARE ANYBODY,
EVEN THAT MUTT,
TO GET THE BALL PAST ME.
-  I'LL PUT IT BY YOU.
-  [ Tom ]
WHAT IS HE TALKING ABOUT ?
-  DOES HE NOT UNDERSTAND
THAT'S AIR BUD ?
- [ Whimpers ]
[ Player ]
BUDDY ?  NO WAY.
[ Chuckles ]
A DOG CAN'T PLAY SOCCER.
[ Claps Hands ]
BUDDY, COME HERE.
[ Tom ]
ALL RIGHT.  WAY TO GO, BUDDY.
COME ON, LET'S SEE YOU DO THIS.
COME HERE.
[ Player ]
YEAH, BUDDY CAN DO IT !
[ Tom ]
THIS IS GONNA BE SO FUNNY.
JUST HIT THE BALL
IN THE NET, ALL RIGHT ?
RIGHT THERE.  LET'S GO.
COME ON, FLEABAG,
I HAVEN'T GOT ALL DAY.
[ Buddy Whimpers ]
[ Tom ]
GOIN' DOWN !
- [ Scoffs ]
- [ Snorts ]
HUH ?
COME ON.
- [ Grunting ]
-  [ Players Exclaiming ]
-  [ Buddy Barking ]
-  YEAH !
- [ Sighs ]
-  THAT WAS A BEAUTY !
- GOOD BOY.
THAT WAS UNBELIEVABLE.
HEY, COACH, CAN HE PLAY ?
I GUESS, UH--
I GUESS WE JUST FOUND
OUR MISSING PLAYER.
YEAH !
ALL RIGHT !
WAY TO GO, BUDDY !
AWESOME !
WHY'D YOU
MOVE TO FERNFIELD ?
WELL, AFTER MUM PASSED AWAY,
DADDY DECIDED
WE NEEDED A CHANGE,
AND WE MOVED HERE.
SORRY ABOUT YOUR MOM.
IT'S OKAY.
LISTEN, JOSH.
DADDY WANTS TO THROW
A BASH FOR THE TEAM.
WOULD YOU LIKE TO COME ?
IT'S FRIDAY AT 7:00.
UNLESS, OF COURSE,
YOU'VE GOT OTHER PLANS.
NO.  I CAN FIT THAT
INTO MY SCHEDULE.
GREAT.  SEE YOU HERE ?
YEAH.
OKAY.  COME ON, MOLLY.
"I CAN FIT THAT
INTO MY SCHEDULE" ?
- I BLEW THAT ONE, DIDN'T I ?
- [ Whimpers ]
COME ON, GIRL.
I'LL RACE YOU.
OKAY.  TAILS.
OOH-HOO-HOO-HOO !  HEADS.
[ Chuckles ]
[ Crowd Cheering,
Applauding ]
- COME ON, COME ON.
LOOK UP.  STAY ALIVE !
-  [ Crowd Shouting ]
GET IT FAST !  COME ON !
WHAT ARE YOU DOING ?  WAKE UP !
- [ Groans ]
-  [ Man ]  WE'RE WINNING !
ALL RIGHT !
THAT'S ALL RIGHT.
WE'LL GET IT BACK.
LET'S GO !  HUSTLE UP !
WHOOPS.
WHOA.  WHOA.
OH, NO.  OH.
BUDDY, KICK IT IN.
[ Groaning ]
AY-YI-YI.
[ All Groaning ]
BOO !
- SAM, LOOK AROUND !
- JOSH IS OPEN !
- JUST WATCH ME.
- [ Groans ]
OH.
GET HER !  GET HER !
COME ON !
I GOT THE BALL.
THAT'S RIGHT.
[ Blows Raspberry ]
[ Chuckling ]
LEFT AND RIGHT.
YEAH, UH-HUH, UH-HUH.
OH, YEAH.
YEAH, I'M THE MASTER.
I'M THE MAN.
I COULD BET ALL--  OOH.
- [ Groans ]
- HOOK IT TO CENTER, TOM !
THE MIDDLE !
UP THE MIDDLE, TOM !
- SEND IT, TOM !  SEND IT !
- DON'T WORRY ABOUT THE...
BALL !
[ Grunts ]
- [ Crowd Cheering ]
- [ Whimpering ]
OKAY, I GOT IT.
- TAKE A SHOT !
- [ Barking ]
-  [ Tom ]  THAT'S MY BALL!
-  BUDDY, PLAY IT TO ME.
YEAH !  THAT'S TEAMWORK.
GOOD WORK.
- [ Beeping ]
-  [ Cheering Continues ]
[ Whistle Blowing ]
I HAVE JUST
ONE ANNOUNCEMENT.
I'M MOVING THE NEXT PRACTICE,
WHICH WAS ORIGINALLY SCHEDULED
FOR THIS SATURDAY, TO...
RIGHT NOW.
[ All ]
WHAT ?
COACH, WE JUST
PLAYED A WHOLE GAME.
WHAT GAME ?
I DIDN'T SEE A GAME.
I SAW ONE TEAM PLAYING SOCCER,
AND I SAW ANOTHER TEAM
PLAYING HOG THE BALL.
- WHAT'S THE MOST
IMPORTANT PART OF SOCCER ?
- NO CONTACT ?
[ Players Chuckling ]
THE EYES.
WHERE'S THE BALL GOING NEXT ?
WHO CAN I PASS TO ?
HOW CAN I CREATE SPACE
TO OPEN MYSELF UP
TO RECEIVE A PASS ?
I JUST WATCHED YOU GUYS FOR
AN HOUR AND A HALF OUT THERE.
AND ASIDE FROM EMMA AND BUDDY
HERE, I DON'T BELIEVE
I SAW ONE GIVE-AND-GO.
BUT I GUARANTEE YOU,
BEFORE THE NIGHT'S OVER,
YOU'LL KNOW WHAT IT IS TO PASS.
ALL RIGHT ?
OKAY, COME ON.
LET'S GO.
[ Whistle Blows ]
KEEP THE BALL NICE AND TIGHT.
PASS !  PASS, PASS !
NICE !
[ Players Chattering,
Chuckling ]
COME ON, GUYS.
LET'S GET THAT PASS THROUGH
TO YOU.  WHAT ARE YOU DOING ?
WE'RE GONNA BE HERE ALL NIGHT.
[ Shouting ]
[ Cheering ]
[ Grunting ]
AW, COME ON.
OH, YEAH.
[ Groans ]
HEY, EMMA'S HAVING A PARTY.
ARE YOU GOING ?
PARTY ?  WHAT PARTY ?
WHEN ?
[ Whistle Blowing ]
ALL RIGHT.
PIG IN THE MIDDLE.
- BUDDY, YOU BE THE PIG.
SO TO SPEAK.
- [ Growls, Whimpers ]
-  [ Buddy Barking ]
- KEEP AWAY !
- COME ON, BUDDY.
HEY, KEEP IT AWAY FROM BUDDY.
OKAY, BRING IT BACK HERE.
BRING IT ON, MAN.
COME ON.  DOWN !
[ Buddy Barking ]
HEY, EMMA'S HAVING
A PARTY ON FRIDAY.
ARE YOU GOING ?
YEAH, I AM.
ME TOO.
I FIGURE I SHOULD WEAR
SOMETHING KIND OF ENGLISH.
SHE MUST BE
INSTINCTIVELY ATTRACTED
TO SOMETHING LIKE THAT.
YEAH, I'M SURE SHE IS.
NICE HEADER.
[ Barking ]
[ Groaning ]
COME ON, LET'S GO.
ALL RIGHT.
OKAY.
[ Players Groaning ]
ALL RIGHT.
NOW YOU'RE PLAYING SOCCER.
ALL RIGHT.  OUR NEXT GAME
IS AGAINST THE LEAGUE CHAMPIONS,
THE SPRINGBROOK SPARTANS.
HOWEVER, LAST YEAR
AND SO FAR THIS YEAR,
THEY ARE UNDEFEATED.
[ All Groaning ]
[ Andrea Whispering ]
IT'S LIKE CLOCKWORK.
WHAT MAKES YOU SO SURE
HE'S SNEAKING ?
TRUST ME.
I'M AN EXPERT.
[ Faint Rustling ]
SHH.
[ Barking Softly ]
COME ON.  WE GOTTA
CATCH UP TO HIM.
- WHOA.  SLOW DOWN, GIRLS.
- [ Sniffing ]
WHAT ARE YOU WEARING ?
IS THAT PERFUME ?
IT'S AFTERSHAVE.
IT SMELLS LIKE
BUDDY'S SHAMPOO.
[ Both Giggling ]
[ Door Opens, Closes ]
[ Sniffs ]
OKAY.
ALL RIGHT.  YOU TAKE
FRONT STREET, AND I'LL
GO THROUGH THE PARK.
CONFIRM VISUAL CONTACT
IN CODE ONLY.
FOR WHAT ?
NO ONE'S LISTENING.
COME IN, BITS.
THIS IS KIBBLES.
WE FOUND OUR PESKY POOCH.
OVER.
HOLY COW !
I WONDER
WHO LIVES HERE.
COME ON.
[ Gasps ]
OH, MY GOSH !
WE'RE DONE FOR.
HURRY, DOWN HERE !
QUICK !
GET DOWN HERE !
- OH, NO !  THEY FOUND US.
WE'RE DEAD.
-  [ People Chattering ]
THIS WAS YOUR IDEA.
COOL IT, WOULD YA ?
NORMALLY, I'LL EAT ANYTHING
THEY HAVE UP THERE,
BUT IT'S JUST--  OH, MAN.
-  SEE HOW BIG THAT THING IS.
-  [ Andrea ]
THAT'S JOSH'S SOCCER TEAM.
THIS MUST BE EMMA'S HOUSE.
EMMA ?  YOU MEAN
OUR COACH EMMA ?
YEAH.
[ Door Closes ]
COME ON.
♪♪ [ Dance ]
[ Chattering ]
[ Rings ]
HEY, JOSH.  HEY.
HEY, MAN.
SO, WHAT DO YOU THINK ?
[ Chuckles ]
NICE SKIRT.
KILT.
CHICKS DIG A GUY
WITH A SENSE OF FASHION.
[ Sniffing ]
IS BUDDY HERE ?
[ Sighs ]
♪ THAT THE FEELIN' IS STRONG ♪
♪ LUCKY STARS ♪
♪ THEY'LL BE SHINING BRIGHT ♪
-  ♪ LUCKY STARS ♪
- HELLO, JOSH.
COME ON IN.
♪ LUCKY STARS ♪
HI.
♪ THEY'LL BE MINE TONIGHT ♪
TOM, IS YOUR FAMILY
SCOTTISH ?
UH, NO.
[ Chuckles ]
HEY, TOM, DID YOU
BRING YOUR BAGPIPES ?
[ Forced Chuckle ]
VERY FUNNY.
♪ THE WAY IT TAKES YOU
YOU'LL BE SURPRISED ♪
IT'S A NICE PLACE.
YOU'LL HAVE TO FORGIVE ME.
WE'RE ABSOLUTELY
HIGGELDY-PIGGELDY RIGHT NOW.
OH.
DADDY'S NOT BEEN ABLE
TO ENGAGE A BUTLER.
HE'S TRYING TO MANAGE
THIS WHOLE AFFAIR
WITH MRS. BRIMSTONE.
OH.  DO YOU NEED
SOME HELP OR SOMETHING ?
COULD YOU ?
YEAH.
♪ LUCKY STARS ♪
♪ JUST FOR ME
LUCKY STARS ♪
♪ THEY'LL BE MINE TONIGHT ♪♪
ISN'T THIS BEING
A PEEPING TOM ?
NO, THAT'S JUST GUYS.
THAT'S WHY THEY CALL IT "TOM."
OH.  HMM.
COMING THROUGH.  YES.
COMING THROUGH.  THANKS.
OKAY, OKAY.
DADDY.
OH, YES.
THIS IS MY FRIEND, JOSH.
HOW ARE YOU, JOSH ?
HI.  NICE TO MEET YOU.
WE'RE A BIT SHORTHANDED,
BUT WE ARE MANAGING.
YEAH.  DO YOU
WANT SHORTCAKE ?
IT'S THE END, I TELL YOU,
MR. PUTTER.  THE END !
WE'LL MANAGE, MY DEAR.
IT'S NOT THE QUEEN'S ROYAL BALL.
[ Doorbell Ringing ]
EXCUSE ME.
- I'LL GET THAT.
- [ Sniffing ]
OH, I'M JOSH.
HERE, TAKE THIS
TO THE KITCHEN.
ALL RIGHT.
THAT WAY.
YEAH, THIS IS
MY GRANDFATHER'S HAT.
I GOT IT YEARS AGO.
HEY.
OH, HEY, JOSH.
- ANYWAY--
- BINGO.
BUDDY'S GOT A GIRLFRIEND.
HOW LONG'S THAT
BEEN GOING ON ?
BEATS ME.  COME ON,
LET'S GET OUTTA HERE.
♪♪ [ Continues ]
[ Emma's Dad ]
HELP !
♪♪ [ Humming ]
HELP !  HELP !
EMMA !
IT'S MR. PUTTER, MISS.
IT'S A DISASTER.
- HE'S LOCKED IN.
-  DADDY, ARE YOU ALL RIGHT ?
JUST STAY CALM, EVERYONE.
I'M FINE.
EXCUSE ME.
ONE SEC, ALL RIGHT ?
THERE WE GO.
HELLO.
[ Chuckling ]
THAT'S BETTER.
WELL DONE, JOSH.
IT WAS GETTING A BIT CLOSE
IN THERE, BUT I'M ALL RIGHT.
[ Chuckling ]
YOU HAVE MY GRATITUDE, JOSH.
THANKS.
THAT'S ALL RIGHT.  THANK YOU
SO MUCH, MRS. BRIMSTONE.
OH, DEAR.
YOU SAVED THE DAY, JOSH.
OH, IT'S NO PROBLEM.
THAT'S AN ODD
POCKET KNIFE.
YEAH, MY STEPDAD
GAVE IT TO ME.
WHAT'S THAT ?
OH, IT'S JUST SOME WHISTLE,
I GUESS.
[ No Audible Whistle ]
- [ Growling ]
- [ Barking ]
- [ Barks ]
- [ Both Whimpering ]
- [ Growling ]
- [ Barks ]
- [ Barking ]
- I GUESS IT DOESN'T WORK.
-  [ Doorbell Ringing ]
- HOLD ON.
OKAY, I'LL GET IT.
-  [ Dogs Barking ]
- [ Shouts ]
[ Woman Screams ]
[ Barking Continues ]
[ Gasping ]
[ Shouts ]
[ Groaning ]
HUH ?
[ Groans ]
IT MUST HAVE BEEN
THE WHISTLE.
[ Glass Shattering ]
[ Barking ]
MR. PUTTER, YOU THROW
QUITE THE PARTY.
OH, YES.  IT WAS A BIT
OF THE ODD, ALL RIGHT,
WASN'T IT ?
WELL, UH, IT WAS A PLEASURE
MEETING YOU, JOSH.
YEAH, YOU TOO.
YES.  CHEERIO.
YEAH.
SO, UM, I WAS THINKING
MAYBE, UH--  I DON'T KNOW--
MAYBE SOMETIME--
EMMA, THERE YOU ARE.
I'VE GOT TO TALK TO YOU.
LET'S GO.
SEE YA.
[ Chattering, Chuckling ]
WE GOTTA GET SOMEBODY
ON THE INSIDE.
[ Engine Starts ]
[ Backfires ]
[ Whines ]
DO YOU MIND IF I ASK AFTER
YOUR GENERAL STATE OF HEALTH ?
I MEAN,
DO YOU FEEL THAT YOU'RE...
[ Flatulence ]
PHYSICALLY CAPABLE OF PERFORMING
THE NECESSARY DUTIES
OF HOUSEHOLD BUTLER ?
OH, NO.  YOU DON'T FOOL ME
FOR ONE MINUTE.
-  I HAD DINNER WITH THE QUEEN.
- [ Flatulence ]
OH, YES.
WELL, THANK YOU VERY MUCH
[ Flatulence ]
MRS. BRIMSTONE
WILL SEE YOU OUT.
THANK YOU.
A "WILL WEBSTER THE THIRD."
OH, SHOW HIM IN.
EXACTLY MY POINT.
OH, QUITE, YES.
COME, SIR.
PLEASE.  THIS WAY.
[ Flatulence ]
[ Sighs ]
NO, MY DEAR.
-  [ Flatulence ]
-  UPON MY WORD.
-  GOOD-BYE.
[ Muttering, Groans ]
GOOD EVENING, SIR !
GOOD AFTERNOON,
UH, MR. WEBSTER.
DO SIT DOWN.
- YOU CAN CALL ME WILLIE,
ACTUALLY.
- VERY WELL, UH, WILLIE.
UM, HAVE YOU EVER DONE
THIS SORT OF WORK BEFORE ?
UH, I WORKED IN
AN ADVISORY CAPACITY...
IN THE, UH, CANINE DIVISION.
SO YOU KNOW DOGS.
WELL, THAT'S EXTRAORDINARY.
VERY GOOD.  IT'S JUST THAT
OUR DAUGHTER'S RETRIEVER
HASN'T BEEN FEELING WELL LATELY.
- PERHAPS YOU COULD DIAGNOSE.
- MMM.  MMM.
WELL DONE, OLD CHAP.
YOU SEEM TO BE JUST THE MAN.
[ Chuckling ]
WELCOME ABOARD.
OH, JOLLY GOOD.
MRS. BRIMSTONE !
I'D LIKE YOU TO MEET
OUR NEW BUTLER.
WILLIE, THIS IS MRS. BRIMSTONE,
OUR HOUSE MANAGER.
CHARMED, I'M SURE.
[ Chuckles ]
[ Cheering ]
-  LET'S GO !
-  HEY, TIMBERWOLVES,
LOOKING GOOD !
- THEY GOT A GIRL ON THE TEAM ?
-  NO RULE AGAINST IT.
ALL THE BETTER FOR US.
GENTLEMEN, TAKE THE FIELD.
SPARTANS !
COME ON !
NOW, WHO'S THIS, UH,
BUDDY FRAMM, RETRIEVER ?
THAT WOULD BE THE DOG,
COACH.
MASCOT ?
STARTING FORWARD.
HEY, BUDDY !
[ Crowd Chanting ]
BUDDY !  BUDDY !  BUDDY !
BUDDY !
THAT'S A BIT OF THE OLD
DESPERATE MEASURES OR WHAT ?
[ Chuckling ]
IT LOOKS LIKE WE CAN GET ALONG
WITHOUT YOU FOR THIS ONE, SON.
YEAH, BUT, DAD,
IT'S AIR BUD.
[ Whistle Blowing ]
JACK.  TO MOOSE.
TOM !
GOT IT.  EMMA, TAKE IT.
- EXCELLENT !
-  GET HER !
-  [ Crowd Cheering ]
- YES !
-  [ Whistle Blows ]
- THAT WAS THE GIRL ?
I BELIEVE SO.
LUCK.
- [ Laughing ]
- COME ON, OUT THERE !
LET'S SETTLE DOWN !
[ Breathing Heavily,
Groans ]
OPEN.  I'M OPEN.
HEY !
HEY, I'M FOULED !
I GOT IT.
TAKE IT, JOSH !
[ Spartans' Coach ]
GET ON THAT GUY !
-  [ Crowd Cheering ]
- GREAT, BUDDY !
- NOT BAD.  NOT BAD.
- DID YOU SEE THAT ?
[ Shouts ]
- BUDDY !
- WILL SOMEBODY COVER THAT DOG ?
[ Grunting ]
CONTAIN !  CONTAIN !
COME ON !  PICK UP YOUR MARK !
- [ Grunts ]
- [ Crowd Cheering ]
- TOM, RUN ON !
MOOSE, SEND IT LONG.
- OKAY.
-  SEND IT LONG.
-  [ Coach ]  ONE MORE !
-  THAT'S A LONG BALL !
-  [ Moose ]  TOM, LOOK UP !
HUH ?  YES !
HUH ?  PRETTY CLOSE.
HEY, EMMA, MAYBE SOMETIME,
DO YOU WANNA GO TO A, UM--
A WHAT ?
YOU KNOW, LIKE A MOVIE
OR SOMETHING.
MAYBE SATURDAY ?
JOSH, WE'RE IN
THE MIDDLE OF A GAME.
- [ Whistle Blowing ]
- YES.  THAT'D BE LOVELY.
- ALL RIGHT !
- YEAH !
THAT TEAM'S ONLY BEEN PLAYING
THREE LOUSY WEEKS.
I'D SAY THIS WON'T LOOK GOOD
ON THE STAT SHEET, CHIEF.
YEAH, WELL, IF YOU THINK
I'M GONNA STAND BY...
AND PUT UP WITH THIS KIND
OF NONSENSE-- GIRLS, DOGS.
WHAT'S NEXT ?
A WATER BUFFALO ?
- COACH, I HAVE A DOG
YOU COULD PLAY.
- [ Groans ]
[ Clears Throat ]
WELL, I HOPE YOU ENJOYED YOUR
LITTLE BIT OF FUN, MONTOYA.
I HAVE TO TELL YOU,
THAT AS CHAIRMAN
OF THE CONFERENCE,
I INTEND TO INITIATE
A PROTEST.
WELL, I'M SORRY
YOU FEEL THAT WAY.
I THOUGHT YOUR TEAM PLAYED
WITH A LOT OF COURAGE.
ALL RIGHT, HERE'S THE THING.
DO NOT, UNDER ANY CIRCUMSTANCES,
LET HER KNOW THAT
YOU LIKE HER TOO MUCH.
IT'S THE KEY POINT,
THE BOTTOM LINE.
I DO LIKE HER
THOUGH, TOM.
WELL, I KNOW THAT.
BUT YOU GOTTA
KEEP HER GUESSING.
THAT'S RIGHT, JOSH.
JUST LISTEN TO CASANOVA.
♪♪ [ Jukebox: '50s Rock ]
THANKS A LOT.  ENJOY IT.
[ Register Bell Dinging ]
♪♪ [ Whistling, Humming ]
[ Blender Whirring ]
-  [ Whimpering ]
- ♪♪ [ Humming Continues ]
[ Whining ]
NOT AGAIN.
BUDDY !
♪♪ [ Ends ]
[ People Chattering ]
DID YOU SEE THE FIRST
ONE HE DID ?
I SAW THE TRAILER.
SO, DO YOU LIKE THIS
SCHOOL THING SO FAR ?
YEAH.
I FIGURE I'LL PUT IN
ANOTHER YEAR, AND THEN
HOP ON MY HOG AND HIT THE ROAD.
YOU'LL WHAT ?
MOTORCYCLE.
YOU HAVE A MOTORCYCLE ?
[ Chuckling ]
NOT YET, BUT, I MEAN,
I WILL GET ONE.
NEXT, PLEASE.
UM, TWO FOR  NINJA
BLOODY NINJA,  PLEASE.
OKAY.
THERE YOU GO.
THANKS.
YOU'RE WELCOME.
ARE YOU SURE
ABOUT THIS MOVIE ?
IT SOUNDS
SORT OF VIOLENT.
RIGHT DOWN TO YOUR LEFT.
I LIKE VIOLENT MOVIES.
[ Groans ]
[ People Chuckling ]
ARE YOU ALL RIGHT ?
YEAH.  SURE, BABE.
OUCH.
[ Man ]
I WANT TO SIT IN THE FRONT ROW.
[ Woman Over TV ]
♪ I'VE WARMED UP TO YOUR SMILE ♪
♪ TOUCHED YOU
ON YOUR SLEEVE ♪
♪ LET YOU PAINT MY SOUL ♪
♪ WITH YOUR VISIONS
HOPES AND DREAMS ♪
♪ I NEVER KNEW WHAT LOVE WAS ♪
[ Buddy Whimpering ]
♪ UNTIL YOU RESCUED ME ♪♪
ALL RIGHT, DRINKS.
WHAT ABOUT
THE FLUFFERNUTTER ?
OH, RIGHT.
OKAY.
YOU HAVE AN EXTRA HAND ?
THAT SHOULD DO IT.
DON'T START WITHOUT ME.
I'LL BE RIGHT UP.
OKAY.
DON'T TAKE TOO LONG.
IT SEEMED LIKE THAT MOVIE
REALLY GOT TO YOU.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN ?
YOU KNOW, THE WAY YOU KEPT
COVERING YOUR EYES.
I DID ?
AND SCREAMING.
OH, I ALWAYS DO THAT
IN, LIKE, MOVIES.
I SEE.
JOSH, CAN I ASK YOU
A QUESTION ?
SURE, BABE.
FIRST OF ALL, MY NAME
IS EMMA, NOT "BABE."
WHAT HAS GOTTEN INTO YOU ?
WHY ARE YOU ACTING THIS WAY ?
- WHAT WAY ?
- YOU'RE BEING A TWIT.
I AM ?
I SAID I'D GO OUT WITH  YOU,
NOT SOME HIPSTER NUTCASE.
AND TAKE OFF THOSE
RIDICULOUS SUNGLASSES.
WE'RE AT YOUR HOUSE ALREADY.
GOOD NIGHT, JOSH.
GOOD NIGHT.
CAN I CALL YOU, OR--
YOU CAN CALL ME IF YOU WANT
OR WHATEVER.
YOU CAN CALL ME.
I'M GONNA KILL TOM.
HEY, BUDDY.
I HOPE YOU HAD
A BETTER NIGHT THAN ME.
YOU'RE LOOKING AT
THE LOSER OF THE UNIVERSE.
[ Footsteps Approaching ]
SO HOW'D
THE GREAT DATE GO ?
DON'T ASK.
IT WAS THAT BAD, HUH ?
WORSE.
YOU JUST DON'T KNOW HOW DUMB
YOU'RE ACTING UNTIL AFTERWARDS.
SOMETIMES IT JUST
TAKES PATIENCE.
BUT IF IT'S MEANT TO WORK OUT,
SHE'LL BE THERE.
I'M NOT SO SURE
AFTER WHAT HAPPENED TONIGHT.
A LITTLE FAITH IN YOURSELF.
IT GOES A LONG WAY.
THANKS.
ALL RIGHT.
I'LL SEE YOU IN THE MORNING.
YEAH.
[ Sighs ]
♪ I CAN'T BELIEVE IT'S THE END ♪
♪ THAT I'M LOSING
MY BEST FRIEND ♪
♪ AND I'M THE ONLY ONE
TO BLAME ♪
-  ♪ CAN'T STOP THE RAIN ♪
- I SHOULD HAVE JUST--
HUH ?
JOSH, WEREN'T
YOU LISTENING ?
UM, NO.
♪ MUST BE SOMETHING
I CAN CHANGE ♪
♪ ALWAYS YOU ♪
♪ ON MY MIND ALL DAY ♪
♪ REMEMBERING
ALL THE GOOD TIMES ♪
♪ THAT WE HAD ALONG THE WAY ♪
♪ ALWAYS YOU ♪
♪ I GOTTA FIND A WAY ♪
♪ TO SHOW YOU JUST HOW MUCH
I REALLY CARE ♪
♪ AND WHAT I ALWAYS
MEANT TO SAY ♪♪
WE'RE GONNA WIN THIS.
TIMBERWOLVES !
YEAH !  ALL RIGHT !
DON'T WORRY
ABOUT ANYTHING.
WAIT A MINUTE.
WHAT'S GOING ON HERE ?
WHERE ARE
ALL THE PEOPLE ?
HEY, COACH.
-  WHAT'S GOING ON ?
-  YEAH.
- I'M NOT SURE.
- COACH MONTOYA.
- OH, MAN, I HATE THIS GUY.
- WHAT'S HE DOING HERE ?
- I'M AFRAID YOU HAVE
A LITTLE PROBLEM.
- WHAT'S WRONG ?
I'VE JUST COME FROM A MEETING
OF THE ATHLETIC CONFERENCE,
OF WHICH,
AS I'M SURE YOU'RE AWARE,
I'M THE CHAIRMAN.
WE--  THE CONFERENCE HAS DECIDED
TO DISQUALIFY YOUR TEAM.
WHAT ?
WHY ?
-  THEY CAN'T DO THAT, CAN THEY ?
-  WHAT A JERK.
- OH, COME ON, JACK.
THAT'S RIDICULOUS.
AND FOR YOUR INFORMATION,
HE'S BEEN ON OTHER
FERNFIELD HIGH TEAMS.
THAT DOG HAS ALL THE RIGHTS
THAT THIS CONFERENCE GIVES HIM.
AND THIS CONFERENCE SAYS
HE CAN'T PLAY.
HE CAN PLAY.
NOW, YOU EITHER REMOVE HIM
FROM YOUR TEAM...
OR YOU REMOVE YOUR TEAM
FROM THE LEAGUE.
- THE CHOICE IS YOURS.
- BRUCE, GIVE ME THE BALL.
SURE, COACH.
EMMA, COME WITH ME, PLEASE.
[ Sighs ]
KICK THE BALL, PLEASE.
THERE.
[ Buddy Barking ]
FERNFIELD, ONE.
ROXBURY, NOTHING.
LET'S GO HOME.
THAT WON'T COUNT THOUGH.
NO.
[ Moose ]
GOOD SHOT, EMMA.
[ Buddy Whimpering ]
[ Barks ]
-  [ Barking ]
- WHAT IS IT ?
BUDDY, TAKE IT EASY.
BUDDY, WHAT'S WRONG ?
I THINK I KNOW.
GET THE CAR KEYS.
BUDDY, WHAT'S THE MATTER ?
WHERE ARE WE GOING, ANDREA ?
THERE'S NO TIME
TO EXPLAIN.
HURRY !  HURRY,
IT'S HAPPENING !
ANDREA, WHAT'S GOING ON ?
I THINK BUDDY AND MOLLY
HAVE SORT OF MADE FRIENDS.
I THINK THEY'RE MORE
THAN JUST FRIENDS.
HE'S OVER HERE EVERY DAY !
HE IS ?
WE NEED MORE WATER,
MR. PUTTER.
MORE WATER.
M-M-M-MORE--
- OH.
- DADDY, THIS IS BUDDY'S FAMILY.
- HELLO.  YES.
- HOW'S SHE DOING ?
- WELL, WE'RE-- WE'RE
NOT QUITE SURE, REALLY.
- WELL, DAD'S A VET.
-  HE CAN HELP.
- WHEN'S THE LAST TIME SHE ATE ?
IT'S BEEN ABOUT 20 HOURS.
I COULD USE A LITTLE HELP.
♪♪ [ Humming ]
THE FIRST PUPPY HAS ARRIVED.
[ Chuckles ]
OH, MY.
OUR LITTLE BUDDY.
[ Whimpering ]
[ Buddy Barks ]
IT LOOKS LIKE--
- OH, THREE !
- THREE, FOUR.  JEESH.
TWO MORE ?  WELL, THAT'S--
OH, THAT'S...
SIX NEW MOUTHS TO FEED,
CLOTHE AND EDUCATE.
OH, MY.  OH, DEAR.
I'M QUITE OVERCOME.
OH, DEAR ME.
- WOULD YOU LIKE
TO COME SEE THEM ?
- OH, YES.  WELL, YEAH.
AREN'T THEY CUTE ?
OH, THESE ARE SO CUTE !
LOOK.
OH, LOOK AT THEM.
OH, THEY'RE SO BEAUTIFUL.
[ Puppies Whimpering ]
BUDDY'S A FATHER.
[ Giggles ]
[ Whimpering Continues ]
[ Jackie ]
OH.
LISTEN, WHEN YOU AND BUDDY
JOINED THE TEAM,
IT MEANT SOMETHING.
YOU BECAME A PART
OF SOMETHING.
YOU CAN'T JUST QUIT.
I DON'T WANT US TO BE THE REASON
WHY THE TEAM CAN'T PLAY.
IT'S NOT JUST UP TO YOU.
WE'RE ALL PART OF IT--
THE TEAM.
WE'RE IN THIS TOGETHER.
I DON'T KNOW.
MAYBE IT'S JUST BETTER IF I--
IT'S NOT THE SAME
WITHOUT YOU AND BUDDY.
WE'LL MISS YOU.
YOU WILL ?
[ Chuckles ]
YOU WILL ?  YOU'LL MISS ME ?
WELL, JUST A LITTLE,
BABE.
COME ON, STEVE !
WE'RE LATE FOR THE GAME !
WHAT'S THIS ?
WHAT DID YOU DO ?
YOU HAVE TO PLAY
BY THE RULES, SON.
SO, WHAT,
YOU KICKED THAT TEAM OFF
'CAUSE THEY HAD A DOG ?
YOU REALLY DON'T THINK
WE CAN WIN, DO YOU ?
IT WAS UNFAIR PLAY, SON.
THAT'S THE ONLY REASON
WHY THEY WON.
THEY WON 'CAUSE WE DIDN'T
GIVE IT OUR BEST SHOT.
IT'S THAT SIMPLE.
[ Phone Ringing ]
YEAH.
MONTOYA HERE.
YEAH, STEARNS HERE.
JUST TO LET YOU KNOW
THE BOARD'S HAD
A CHANGE OF HEART.
YOUR DOG CAN PLAY.
I'LL, UH--
I'LL INFORM THE TEAM
RIGHT AWAY.
YEAH.  GOOD LUCK.
[ Grunts ]
[ Cheering ]
YES !
[ Yapping ]
[ Man ]
GET THE BALL !
- YES !
- OW.
[ Players Clamoring ]
COME ON, PUPPY.
[ Tammy Chuckling ]
[ Player ]
HUSTLE, HUSTLE.
I'M OPEN.
TAKE HIM OUT !
[ No Audible Dialogue ]
[ Chattering ]
[ Crowd Cheering,
Applauding ]
OH, HO.
[ Laughing ]
CAREFUL.  CAREFUL.
AH !
[ Screaming ]
WHOA !
CAREFUL.
DOWN, BOY.  DOWN.
[ Boy ]
GET YOUR HEAD ON IT.
[ Crowd Cheering ]
[ Chanting ]
BUDDY !  BUDDY !  BUDDY !
BUDDY !  BUDDY !
[ Vehicle Approaching ]
WEBSTER.
THE COAST IS CLEAR.
GET INTO YOUR BUTLER OUTFIT, GET
OVER TO THE PUTTER MANSION...
UH-HUH.
AND OPEN
THE FRONT GATE.
[ Snoring ]
[ Groans ]
[ Grunting ]
[ Panting, Grunting ]
[ Softly ]
OPEN THE DOOR.
WHICH ONE ?
RED, BLUE--
YEAH.
OH !  AH !
COME ON.  BACK IT UP.
OVER HERE.  THIS WAY.
A LITTLE.  A LITTLE.
THAT'S PERFECT.  PERFECT.
PERFECT, PERFECT, PERFECT.
COME ON.  LET'S GO GET
THOSE PUPPIES.
[ Molly Growling ]
OH, BOY.
THAT'S NOT GOOD.
SHH !
[ Puppies Yelping ]
- WHAT DO WE DO ?
- [ Growling ]
YOU GET THE DOG.
I'LL GET THE PUPPIES.
IN, MOLLY.
SHUT THE DOOR.
[ Shouting, Indistinct ]
GET THE PUPPIES !
COME ON, WEBSTER !
I CAN'T BELIEVE IT.
- [ Chattering ]
- [ Barking ]
[ Whining ]
SOMETHING'S WRONG !
COME ON !
[ Whining ]
QUICK, WEBSTER,
HAND ME THOSE PUPPIES.
OKAY.
GET IN THERE, YOU--
IN YOU GO.  ALL RIGHT.
WHATEVER YOU SAY, BOSS.
GET 'EM IN !
SH-SH-SH-SH-SH.
IT'S OKAY.
HERE YOU GO.
[ Grunting,
Groaning ]
WEBSTER, TAKE HIM !
C-COUNT 'EM.
HERE, PUT THIS IN
AND COUNT 'EM.
[ Webster ]
ONE, TWO--
ONE--  OOP.
ONE'S MISSING.
ONE'S MISSING !
IS THERE ONE MISSING ?
THERE HE IS.  COME ON.
COME ON.  LET'S GO.
COME ON, WEBSTER, MOVE IT !
I'M GOIN', I'M GOIN' !
[ Yelping ]
[ Grunts ]
OKAY, PUSH IT IN.
SHUT, SHUT THE DOOR.
WATCH IT.  GO !  GO !
[ Panting ]
[ Whining ]
[ Pounding ]
[ Emma's Dad ]
HELP !
THAT'S DADDY.
EMMA ?
I'M LOCKED IN THE CLOSET !
JOSH, WHAT'S WRONG
WITH MOLLY ?
SOMEBODY'S STOLEN
HER BABIES.
COME IN.
THIS IS KIBBLES. 9-1-1.
BITS, ARE YOU THERE ?
[ Tammy ]
KIBBLES, THIS IS BITS.
I READ YOU.  OVER.
THIS IS THE BIG ONE.
"PUPPY-NAPPERS."
-  WHAT ARE WE GONNA DO ?
- WE'LL START AT THE DOG POUND.
YOU BRING YOUR GEAR.  OVER.
[ Puppies Crying ]
IT'S OKAY.
IT'S FINE.
IT'S OKAY, BOY.
HEY !  HEY.
GO GET CHANGED.
ALL RIGHT ?
AND GET THAT
BOX READY.
JOSH ?
ANDREA ?
BUDDY !
PROBABLY ALREADY
LEFT FOR THE GAME.
BETTER GET THERE EARLY
IF WE WANT TO GET SEATS.
JUST GIVE ME TWO MINUTES.
I'LL BE READY.
[ Barking ]
THAT'S HIM !
THAT'S THE FELLOW
THAT LOCKED ME UP.
- WEBSTER'S MATE.
- YOU PICK THE OTHER ONE.
DO YOU KNOW THIS MAN ?
SNERBERT ?
AH, HE DOESN'T WORK HERE
ANYMORE.  HE WAS FIRED.
WHERE DOES HE LIVE ?
AH, SOMEWHERE
PAST THE TRACKS
ON THE EAST SIDE.
ANDREA, TAMMY.
COME ON !
[ Woman On P.A. ]
WELCOME, LADIES AND GENTLEMEN,
TO THE LEAGUE CHAMPIONSHIP
GAME...
BETWEEN
THE SPRINGBROOK SPARTANS...
AND THE FERNFIELD
TIMBERWOLVES !
BUT FIRST, WE WOULD LIKE
TO WELCOME...
A VERY SPECIAL GUEST
FROM THE UNITED STATES
WOMEN'S WORLD CUP SOCCER TEAM,
BRIANA SCURRY !
[ Man On P.A. ]
WELL, ALL THE HYPE
IS FINALLY OVER, BRAD,
AND NOW IT COMES DOWN
TO 90 MINUTES OF SOCCER...
TILL WE CROWN THIS YEAR'S
LEAGUE CHAMPIONS.
YES, TED, ALL THE MARBLES
ARE ON THE TABLE THIS AFTERNOON,
AND YOU'RE NOT GONNA
BELIEVE THIS, FOLKS,
BUT WORD HAS IT...
THAT THE FERNFIELD
TIMBERWOLVES WILL BE
STARTING THE GAME TODAY...
WITHOUT THREE
OF THEIR KEY PLAYERS.
[ Ted ]
YES, APPARENTLY FERNFIELD'S
STAR PLAYERS EMMA PUTTER,
JOSH FRAMM
AND THE FAMOUS AIR BUD
ARE MISSING FROM THE FIELD.
THIS IS REALLY
AN UNFORTUNATE TURN OF EVENTS
FOR THE TIMBERWOLVES.
[ Brad ]
ESPECIALLY WHEN YOU CONSIDER
THAT THE SPARTANS'...
ALL-STAR CAPTAIN STEVE STEARNS
HAS FINALLY RETURNED
FROM THE INJURED LIST.
T-WOLVES !
THE PRESSURE IS ON FERNFIELD
THIS AFTERNOON.
I DON'T KNOW HOW
THEY CAN HOLD IT TOGETHER.
WHERE ON EARTH CAN THEY BE ?
IT'S NOT LIKE JOSH TO BE LATE.
[ Josh ]
LET'S GO UP HERE.
JUST WAIT HERE, OKAY ?
BUT JOSH, THERE'S A--
I'M SERIOUS.
ANDREA, STAY HERE.
HMPH.
OH, COME ON, YOU GUYS.
THIS WAY.
RIGHT THROUGH HERE.
COME ON.  WE'LL
GET THE PUPPIES.
MOLLY !  OVER HERE.
COME ON.
ANDREA, WHAT ARE YOU DOING ?
I THOUGHT I TOLD YOU
TO WAIT OUTSIDE !
HEY.  DID YOU
HEAR SOMETHING ?
YEAH.
MAYBE YOU BETTER
CHECK IT OUT ?
OH !
[ Clattering ]
SOMEBODY'S COMING.
WE'VE GOT TO HIDE.
HELLO ?
IS ANYBODY OUT THERE ?
IT'S OKAY, BOSS.
IT'S JUST SOME WAGGING TAILS.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN,
"WAGGING TAILS" ?
- HEY, WAIT A MINUTE.
- [ Andrea ]  UH-OH.
- HUH ?
- LET'S GET OUT OF HERE.
LET'S GET 'EM !
OH, YEAH.
[ Puppies Whining ]
LET'S GO.
IN HERE.
COME ON.  COME ON.
HERE !
♪♪ [ Whistle ]
[ Ted ]
AND WE'RE UNDER WAY.  SPARTANS
TAKE EARLY CONTROL OF THE BALL.
LET'S GO.
GO, GO, GO !
- [ Cheering, Yelling ]
-  BREAKING AWAY IS STEARNS.
HE'S IN THE CLEAR.
FERNFIELD IS SCRAMBLING.
PASS TO STEARNS, AND A GOAL !
-YES !
-[ Brad ]  BEAUTIFUL GOAL.
SPARTANS TAKE THE EARLY LEAD...
ONLY 45 SECONDS
INTO THE GAME.
NO !
IT'S 1-0.
FERNFIELD'S ALREADY IN TROUBLE.
[ Exhales ]
GRAB THE DOG WHISTLE
OUT OF MY BAG, ALL RIGHT ?
IT'S JUST IN THE BACK.
RIGHT HERE.
RIGHT HERE.  RIGHT HERE.
ONE, TWO THREE, GO !
- [ No Audible Whistle ]
- [ Yapping, Growling ]
[ Whining, Yelping ]
[ Announcer, Indistinct ]
[ Ted ]
OH, AND THE REFEREE CALLS
A HAND BALL IN THE BOX...
AGAINST THE SPARTAN DEFENSEMAN--
THAT'S A BIG BREAK
FOR THE TIMBERWOLVES.
[ Brad ]  SAM DRAKE IS GONNA
GET A PENALTY KICK AND HAS
A CHANCE TO TIE THE GAME.
GOOD !
YOU KNOW HOW TO DO IT !
-  THIS WOULD PUT FERNFIELD
RIGHT BACK INTO IT.
-  [ Man ]  COME ON, SAM !
-  YOU CAN DO IT !
-  [ Man #2 ]  LET'S GO.
HE'S YOURS, SAM !
[ Ted ]
AND A GOAL !
WE'RE ALL TIED AT ONE.
[ Brad ]  THAT WAS
A BEAUTIFUL KICK BY DRAKE,
AND THE TIMBERWOLVES
HAVE SOME NEW LIFE
IN THIS GAME.
YOU WANT ME TO DO IT ?
PULL !  PULL !
[ Creaking ]
[ Dog Barking ]
YOU HEAR SOMETHING,
BOSS ?
GET BACK TO WORK.
[ Dogs Barking,
Howling, Yipping ]
-  [ Thundering Sound ]
- YOU HEAR  THAT,
DON'T YA, BOSS ?
COME ON, WEBSTER !
[ All Barking ]
OH, BOY.
THAT AIN'T GOOD.
LET'S GET OUTTA HERE !
[ Screaming ]
COME ON, WEBSTER.
MOVE !
GET IN !
[ Barking Fades ]
HUH.
[ Barking Stops ]
HUH !
THINK WE LOST 'EM.
LET'S GET OUTTA HERE.
[ Fierce Growling ]
NICE...
DOGGIES !
GOOD DOG.
S-S-S-SIT !
[ Webster ]
THEY'RE ALREADY SITTIN' !
[ Snerbert ]  STAY SITTING.
[ Scoffing ]
CAN'T GET US UP HERE.
[ Growling ]
[ Snerbert, Webster ]
WHOA-OH-OH-OH !
WHICH WAY ?
JUST LOOK EVERYWHERE.
THEY'RE IN HERE
SOMEWHERE.  LET'S GO.
COME ON.
[ Sniffing ]
[ Whining, Barking ]
HE FOUND THEM.
[ Yelping ]
[ Puppy Whining ]
- YOU GUYS ARE OKAY !
-  OH, GOOD.
GOOD BOY.
OH, I'M SO GLAD
YOU GUYS ARE OKAY.
IT'S ALL RIGHT.
OHH.
[ Both Groaning, Sighing ]
[ Growling ]
[ Webster ]
THIS AIN'T GOOD, BOSS.
[ Growling ]
OH, BOY.
THIS REALLY
AIN'T GOOD, BOSS.
WHAT DID YOU HOPE
TO ACCOMPLISH BY
STEALING OUR DOGS ?
- HE WANTED TO GET RICH.
- WEBSTER !
I JUST WANTED A PUPPY.
EVER SINCE I WAS A KID,
I ALWAYS WANTED ONE.
-  HE WAS GONNA SELL THEM.
- BE QUIET.
[ Gasps ]
[ Yipping ]
[ Softly ]
IT'S OKAY.  AWW.
[ Chuckles ]
AWW.
[ Emma ]
HE DOES SEEM TO LIKE YA.
JOSH !  THE GAME !
- WE'RE GONNA BE LATE.
WE GOTTA GO.
- I CAN GET YOU THERE.
- WELL, WHAT ABOUT  HIM ?
- HE'S NOT GOING ANYWHERE.
- [ Barks ]
- [ Growling ]
[ Tires Screeching ]
BITS, THIS IS KIBBLES.
WE'RE ON FRONT STREET,
HEADING FOR THE STADIUM.
WE'LL MEET YOU THERE.
[ Grunting ]
WELL, MAYBE.
[ Crowd Cheering,
Chattering ]
[ Ted ]  THERE'S A PASS
TO STEARNS.  HE SPINS AROUND.
HE SHOOTS-- AND A GOAL !
[ Brad ]
WOW, WHAT A MOVE BY STEARNS.
THIS KID IS INCREDIBLE.
THE SPARTANS TAKE
A ONE-GOAL LEAD WITH LESS THAN
SEVEN MINUTES LEFT IN THE GAME.
[ Screeching ]
IS THIS TRUCK
GOING TO MAKE IT ?
FEAR NOT, YOUNG LASS.
'TIS WEBSTER AT THE HELM.
YOUR TRUCK IS MAKING
PIT STOPS WITHOUT STOPPING !
HUH ?  UH-OH.
[ Man ]
CONTAIN !  CONTAIN !
[ Brad ]  WELL, THINGS
ARE LOOKING PRETTY BLEAK
FOR THE TIMBERWOLVES.
THEY'RE ONE GOAL DOWN
WITH LESS THAN
FOUR MINUTES TO PLAY,
AND THE TEAM
IS LOOKING DOG-TIRED.
THERE'S DADDY.
DADDY, LOOK !
OH, HERE THEY ARE.
HELLO, PUPPIES.
OH, GOOD.
LET ME TAKE ONE.
- THERE WE ARE.  THE MOTHER.
- HERE THEY ARE !
LET'S GO !
THIS WAY.
[ Ted ]
SOME SORT OF COMMOTION
DOWN ON THE FIELD.
- THE CROWD'S GOING CRAZY !
-  [ Brad ]  IT'S BUDDY !
AIR BUD IS BACK.
NOT A MOMENT TOO SOON !
FERNFIELD'S MISSING PLAYERS--
EMMA PUTTER, JOSH FRAMM
AND AIR BUD-- ARE BACK !
GET IN THERE, BUDDY,
YOU KNOW YOUR SPOT !
EMMA ON THE RIGHT SIDE !
MIKE !  DROP BACK !
MOOSE !  DROP BACK !
NOW WE GOT A GAME, DUDE.
NOW WE GOT A GAME.  YES, SIR.
SORRY.  WHOOP.
SORRY ABOUT THAT.
JOSH !  TAKE IT.
[ Ted ]
REBOUND, AND IT'S A GOAL !
GOOD SHOW !
ONWARD, FERNFIELD !
[ Chuckles ]
DID YOU SEE THAT ?
[ Brad ]  THE GAME
IS TIED AT TWO, WITH JUST
ONE MINUTE LEFT TO PLAY.
[ Emma ]
JOSH !  SEND IT TO BUDDY !
- [ Players ]  YES !
-  [ Ted ]  AND IT'S A GOAL !
AIR BUD SCORES !
- YE-E-EAH !
- [ Player ]
BUDDY SCORED THE POINT !
WE WON !  WE WON.
YOU GUYS PLAYED
A GREAT GAME.
BUDDY'S INCREDIBLE.
- [ Yips ]
- THANKS.
GREAT TEAM.
CONGRATULATIONS, COACH.
THANK YOU, JACK.
WELL PLAYED.
[ Chuckling ]
WELL DONE, GUYS.
YOU GUYS PLAYED GREAT.
BUDDY'S INCREDIBLE.
BRIANA SCURRY !
I'M EMMA, AND THIS IS JOSH.
HI.
HEY, JOSH.
NICE TO MEET YOU.
THIS IS BUDDY.
NICE TO MEET YOU, BUDDY.
NICE HEADER.
MAYBE WE COULD PLAY
SOMETIME.
YEAH.  AWESOME.
- I'LL BE KEEPING
MY EYES ON YOU GUYS.
- COOL !
- GREAT.
-  [ Crowd Chanting ]
BUDDY, BUDDY, BUDDY !
[ Chanting Continues ]
[ Announcer #1 ]  DOES IT
GET ANY BETTER THAN THIS ?
THE CHAMPIONSHIP ON THE LINE,
AND THE WORLD IS WATCHING.
[ Announcer #2 ]
AND HERE WE ARE AGAIN.
WHO WILL BE THE NEW
WORLD CUP CHAMPION ?
CAN THEY DO IT ?
[ Announcer #1 ]  IT ALL
COMES DOWN TO A SHOOTOUT
BETWEEN THE U.S. AND NORWAY.
AMERICAN GOALKEEPER
BRIANA SCURRY WILL NOW FACE
THE NORWEGIAN STRIKER...
WITH HER TEAM DOWN
TWO GOALS TO ONE.
[ Announcer #2 ]  AND THIS
IS HUGE PRESSURE ON SCURRY.
SHE NEEDS TO STOP THIS SHOT.
[ Announcer #1 ]  WHAT A SAVE
BY SCURRY !  THE U.S.A.
IS RIGHT BACK INTO IT.
[ Announcer #2 ]  NOW IT'S UP
TO BRANDI CHASTAIN OF THE U.S.
SHE HAS A CHANCE TO PULL
THE AMERICANS EVEN AT TWO...
IF SHE CAN PUT THIS KICK
PAST THE NORWEGIAN KEEPER.
[ Announcer #1 ]  SHE SCORES !
JUST PAST THE OUTSTRETCHED
HANDS OF THE GOALKEEPER,
AND IT'S ALL TIED AT TWO.
[ Announcer #2 ]  THE PRESSURE
SWITCHES TO BRIANA SCURRY, WHO
FACES NORWAY'S FOURTH KICKER.
SHE NEEDS TO STOP THIS ONE
TO PREVENT THE NORWEGIANS
FROM TAKING THE LEAD.
[ Grunts, Groans ]
[ Announcer #2 ]
WAIT A MINUTE, FOLKS.
SCURRY IS DOWN,
AND SHE APPEARS
TO BE INJURED.
[ Groans ]
[ Announcer #1 ]  SHE'S SLOWLY
GETTING UP, BUT SHE'S
DEFINITELY IN A LOT OF PAIN.
[ Announcer #2 ]  THIS WILL BE A
TERRIBLE BREAK FOR THE AMERICANS
IF SHE CAN'T CONTINUE.
NORWAY STILL HAS
ONE MORE KICK,
AND THINGS ARE NOT
LOOKING GOOD FOR THE U.S.
THE NEXT KICKER FOR
THE STARS AND STRIPES
IS TISHA VENTURINI.
SHE'S BEEN IN THIS SITUATION
BEFORE AND IS NO STRANGER
TO THE PRESSURE.
IF SHE CAN MAKE THIS ONE,
THE AMERICANS CAN PULL AHEAD
BY ONE GOAL...
AND PUT THE HEAT
SQUARELY BACK
ON THEIR OPPONENTS.
[ Announcer #1 ]
AND SHE SCORES !
NO DOUBT ABOUT THAT ONE.
WHAT A ROCKET.
THIS  REALLY  PUTS THE AMERICANS
IN THE DRIVER'S SEAT.
[ Announcer #2 ]  BRIANA SCURRY
HAS MADE HER WAY BACK
TO THE NET, BUT IT'S OBVIOUS...
SHE'S IN A LOT OF PAIN.
[ Announcer #1 ]  THERE'S
MOVEMENT AT THE U.S. BENCH.
THE COACH IS SIGNALLING--
I DON'T BELIEVE IT !  THE U.S.
HAS DESIGNATED BUDDY FRAMM
TO REPLACE SCURRY !
[ Barking ]
[ Announcer #2 ]  FRANK,
YOU'RE KIDDING !  A DOG ?
THAT'S NOT A SMART MOVE,
I'D SAY.  THEY'LL MAKE
PUPPY CHOW OUT OF THIS POOCH.
- GO GET 'EM !
- [ Barking ]
[ Laughing, Chattering ]
I HOPE THIS WORKS.
THEY SAY
HE'S PRETTY GOOD.
- [ Panting ]
- COME ON, BUDDY !
YOU CAN DO IT !
[ Snorting ]
- [ Barking ]
- [ Cheering ]
THE U.S. WOMEN'S TEAM
HAS JUST WON
THE WORLD CUP AGAIN !
HE DID IT !
[ Announcer #1 ]
SIMPLY UNBELIEVABLE !
A SUPERSTAR TEAM...
LED BY A SUPERSTAR DOG !
[ Crowd, Chanting ]
BUDDY !  BUDDY !
[ Announcer #2 ]
NOTHING BUT MAGIC, FRANK.
NOTHING BUT AIR BUD !
[ Chanting Continues ]
[ Buddy Barking ]
BUDDY ! HOW'S MY
FAVORITE WORLD PUP ?
HEY.  HEY, PUPPIES.
PUPPIES !
I DIDN'T KNOW
YOU WERE A FAMILY MAN.
KEEPIN' ANY OTHER
SECRETS FROM US ?
PUPPIES, PUPPIES !
[ Laughing ]
BRIANA AND THE GIRLS
WILL BE HERE.  WANT TO
PLAY SOME PICKUP ?
[ Kids ]
YEAH.  SURE.
LET'S GO !
♪ IT FEELS LIKE MAGIC
WITH YOUR HAND IN MINE ♪
♪ I'M HOPIN'
IT'LL NEVER END ♪
♪ I FEEL SO HAPPY
AND IT BLOWS MY MIND ♪
♪ THAT WE CAN BE
THE BEST OF FRIENDS ♪
♪ I CAN FEEL IT EVERYWHERE ♪
♪ SOMETHING MAGIC
IN THE AIR ♪
♪ IT'S IN THE WAY
YOU MAKE ME SMILE ♪
♪ THE WAY THAT YOU MOVE ME
LIKE WE'RE LAUGHIN' OUT LOUD ♪
♪ IN A SILENT MOVIE ♪
♪ I CAN FEEL IT EVERYWHERE ♪
♪ IT FEELS LIKE MAGIC ♪
♪ WHEN THE BEAT
STARTS HAPPENING
TO AN OLD-TIME SONG ♪
♪ A CERTAIN MAGIC
FILLS THE AIR ♪
♪ YOUR FEET START TAPPING
AND BEFORE TOO LONG ♪
♪ YOU'RE MAKIN' MOVES
LIKE FRED ASTAIRE ♪
♪ I CAN FEEL IT EVERYWHERE ♪
♪ SOMETHIN' MAGIC
IN THE AIR ♪
♪ IT'S IN THE WAY
YOU MAKE ME SMILE ♪
♪ THE WAY THAT YOU MOVE ME
LIKE WE'RE LAUGHIN' OUT LOUD ♪
♪ IN A SILENT MOVIE ♪
♪ I CAN FEEL IT EVERYWHERE ♪
♪ IT FEELS LIKE MAGIC ♪
♪ SOMETHIN' MAGIC IN THE AIR ♪
♪ IT'S IN THE WAY
YOU MAKE ME SMILE ♪
♪ THE WAY THAT YOU MOVE ME
LIKE WE'RE LAUGHIN' OUT LOUD ♪
♪ IN A SILENT MOVIE ♪
♪ I CAN FEEL IT EVERYWHERE ♪
♪ IT FEELS LIKE MAGIC ♪♪
♪♪ [ Drums, Guitar ]
[ Woman ]
♪ WHOO, OOH, OOH, YEAH, YEAH ♪
♪ YEAH ♪
♪ YOU DON'T KNOW
WHERE YOU'LL GO ♪
♪ WHEN YOU FOLLOW YOUR HEART ♪
♪ YOU JUST KNOW
IT'S WHERE YOU BELONG ♪
♪ YOU CAN'T SEE
WHERE YOU'LL BE ♪
♪ BUT THE MOMENT IT STARTS ♪
♪ YOU JUST KNOW
THAT THE FEELING IS STRONG ♪
♪ LUCKY STARS ♪
♪ THEY'LL BE SHINING BRIGHT ♪
♪ JUST FOR ME ♪
♪ LUCKY STARS ♪
♪ THEY'LL BE MINE TONIGHT ♪
♪ LUCKY STARS
WAIT AND SEE ♪
♪ SO LET IT GO
LET IT FLOW ♪
♪ LET YOUR HEART LEAD THE WAY ♪
♪ WHERE IT TAKES YOU
YOU'D BE SURPRISED ♪
♪ YOU CAN FEEL
WHEN IT'S REAL ♪
♪ BECAUSE THERE'S
NOTHING TO SAY ♪
♪ YOU CAN SEE IT
RIGHT THERE IN HIS EYES ♪
♪ LUCKY STARS ♪
♪ THEY'LL BE SHINING BRIGHT ♪
♪ JUST FOR ME ♪
♪ LUCKY STARS ♪
♪ THEY'LL BE MINE TONIGHT ♪
♪ LUCKY STARS
WAIT AND SEE ♪
♪ LUCKY STARS ♪
♪ THEY'LL BE MINE TONIGHT ♪
♪ LUCKY STARS
WAIT AND SEE ♪♪