Akira - Anime 1988 English
Groups of unemployed workers,
who have grown in number...
due to tax reforms enacted by the former Prime
Minister, are rioting all across the country.
There is confusion among parliament members
which was sparked by the comments...
of Finance Minister Takanashi
during the recent parliament inquiry.
There seems to be no compromise in sight
between the government and opposition.
Hey, there. Call it.
- Hey, there. Call it.
- Gimme something'. Three peanuts.
Let's see...
Now, uh...
The Clown bastards are herded
out on route number 5.
Damn it, don't scare me like that.
Open that damn door quietly.
You know, you wouldn't be so jumpy
if you didn't have anything to hide.
Why don't you sell
normal drinks for a change?
How about buying' something' for once?
This ain't a hangout for damn street gangs.
Yeah, right!
Drink your dog piss?
Twin ceramic rotor drives
on each wheel.
Let's see. And these are...
computer-controlled
anti lock brakes.
Huh, 200 horses at 12,000 R.P.M.
You want to ride it, Tetsuo?
All right! Let's hit it!
I customized that bike for myself.
It's too wild. You couldn't handle it.
I don't see how you could ride
something crazy like that, man.
Huh! I could.
Ha! If you want it so bad
then steal one yourself.
Unbelievable.
- Unbelievable.
- Punks!
Hey, waiter!
Where are you going?
They ran into the alley!
After 'em!
Quit fooling' around, you idiot!
Fuck!
What?
That's the...
- That's the...
- Huh?
This is unit 375.
We've got reports of biker gangs fighting
near the intersection of highway 14 South.
Request immediate assistance.
Car 375 en route to the scene...
It's the cops.
What should we do?
Damn it. My motor coils were
just getting warmed up.
Bastards!
Let's go, Tetsuo!
I'm coming!
Damn them!
- Damn them!
- Come on!
A skirmish has broken out between student
protesters and riot police.
There appear to be some
casualties. Next...
Don't make me get out of this car!
Jerk, I'm in a hurry!
What was that?
- What was that?
- Police is here!!
This area is off limits!
Go back! It's dangerous!
Hey, something strange
over there.
Let me through!
Sorry.
What're you doing?
It's blood. Look!
Please let me through.
Excuse me. Pardon me.
Watch it, jerk!
Pardon me. I'm sorry.
Ryu!
Hey, look!
They're running away!
He's got a gun!
Fire!
Wait! He's got a kid!
Run.
You gotta hurry.
Go to Ryu.
Ryu will help you now.
Get out of here... Now!
Kei!
We've gotta get out of here, Kei?
He's gone!
He's to the West.
West?
The old city...
Eat this!
Tetsuo!
Ryu! Where are you?
Kei!
No, that's...
How do you like that?
Well? Who is it?
It's not him.
It's not Tetsuo.
All right. Move out!
Why you... What'd you do,
you weird little...
Tetsuo! Just hang on!
What? What did you say?
That kid...
He's really hurt bad.
Hey! You, there!
We gotta get him to a hospital!
He needs an ambulance!
We can't move him!
Wha... What the...!
There's no escape.
We're here to take you
back with us.
You know we can't survive outside.
Well, come along.
Army helicopters!
It's the army!
Move out!
Kiss the ground!
Hands on your heads!
We're, uh, innocent bystanders,
that's all.
Kiss the ground!
Hands on your heads!
That hurts, damn it.
Kai!
Soldier.
Sir.
- Sir.
- Who are those kids?
They seem to be
an ordinary biker gang, sir.
We're returning.
Ouch! Will you just hold on a minute?
- Ouch! Will you just hold on a minute?
- My arms don't bend that way!
Pull the wounded
onto the helicopter.
Tetsuo! Hey, wait! You can't
take him away like that!
Kaneda!
What the hell are you guys doing?
We didn't do anything!
Get off!
All right. The story is, you and your
friends went out at night...
on your bikes to visit
your dying mother, and then...
another bunch of biker hooligans
called the Clowns attacked you.
They hurt your friend, you lost your temper,
and that's why eight of these Clowns...
your attackers... are all now in
the hospital, and that is the truth.
Wow! She sure is hot.
Hmm? This is confidential!
And how's your mother doing?
Fortunately, the worst is over.
She cleared the hump.
She cleared the hump,
and you left her for cruising, huh?
Wha...?
Ah, these bozos couldn't
have anything to do with it.
That goes without saying.
Wait out on that bench.
Do you understand?
All right.
Send in the next five.
So the army's working
with the police...
to hunt down anti government
groups, or so it seems.
You wanna put up a fight?
- You wanna put up a fight?
- Get your hands off me!
Long live
the freedom revolution!
He's got a grenade!
All right, that's enough.
Get him back in there.
I'll teach him a lesson.
He won't forget.
You dumb bastard!
If you wanna die, hang yourself!
Listen, you kids are free to leave.
We've contacted your schools.
Hold on a second, old man!
Wha... "Old man"?
There was someone else with us, you know.
What was that?
Excuse me, please?
Huh? Hey!
What are you doing?
Uh, it's this one right here.
Can't leave my friend.
Don't ever call me "old man,"
you little punk!
That's my foot!
You listen here, kid. I'm only 25
years old. I'm not even married yet.
Watch your mouth. Get out of
here and take your friend with you.
I'm starving!
- I'm starving!
- I need a doctor!
I think the army was chasing that weird kid
Kaneda saw. That's what I think.
Yeah, you're right.
I think I saw him too.
Speaking of Tetsuo, why the hell wouldn't
they tell us what hospital they threw him in?
Huh? What was that?
What I meant was
maybe we could go for a drink.
I figure we could have a nice,
long chat about something you're into...
like the whole revolution thing.
I think you're a skirt chaser
who'll try anything he can.
You'll help anyone so long as
it's a girl. Right?
You're wrong!
I have very high standards.
- I have very high standards.
- Line 'em up! Come on! Move it!
It's not their looks that count.
It's their... I don't know...
A girl's sensitivity
that makes me do it.
I suppose I owe you one.
Thank you very much, uh...
I'm Kaneda. It's nice to... Huh?
- I'm Kaneda. It's nice to... Huh?
- See you around, Kaneda.
Wait a second!
You're leaving just like that?
Hey! Now hold on. I'm the guy
that saved you back there.
You could at least tell me
your name, you cold bitch!
Yes, I'll try talking with him,
but it's risky business.
If they think you're avoiding responsibility,
the whole thing could blow up in your face.
I can't believe that there's
a mole in the executive council.
Even if there is a mole...
That's not what's important here!
What is are political manoeuvrers and
diplomacy which, apparently, you despise.
I never studied the two subjects
in school, it would seem.
In any case, at the next
executive council meeting...
your poor management and lack of
judgment on this last incident...
will be called into question.
There's a call for the colonel, sir.
Put your affairs in order,
if you want my advice.
Yes, it's me. What is it now?
This way, please, Colonel.
I'm terribly sorry to call you here,
but there's something you really must see.
Colonel, please look at this.
It's the special pattern
I'm getting from that young man.
It doesn't resemble any
that I've seen so far...
and I've never seen a developmental speed
or configuration like this.
It may have begun with the shock of
contact with number 26, or it could be...
Have you finished running the comparison
against Akira's pattern?
I'll show you right now.
This projection is made using mixed data,
and the results are not quite correct...
so a direct comparison is difficult.
But I believe based on what we see
here that this boy's pattern is the key...
to solving the riddle of
Akira's growth-pattern process.
Fine. You may continue.
- Fine. You may continue.
- Thank you very much, sir.
I'm certain he'll turn out to be a worthy
addition to the numbers, don't you?
It may be rough on the boy...
but I thought we might try starting
him off with level 7 capsules.
Is it safe, doctor?
I will take care of it.
No! I wasn't talking
about the boy at all!
If he turns out
to reach a power like Akira's...
are you positive that you are
able to control such power?
Uh, well, that's a...
Can you handle this?
Uh, well, then, in my opinion...
if we can use the latest examination
equipment to collect even more data...
and also do a multifaceted
analysis as we go, then surely...
But maybe we weren't meant to
meddle with that ultimate power.
You mean...
the power of a god?
"A-ki-ra."
But we have no choice
but to grasp that power...
grasp that power
and learn to control it.
And if this situation gets out
of hand, then he's to be terminated.
And without hesitation!
- And without hesitation!
- Yes, Colonel.
This school is your last chance!
If trash like you guys can't keep up with
the academic ability of regular students...
If you can't live a decent
social life, you end up here!
And if you screw up here,
it's the end of the road!
Also, even though you're under 15,
if you get more than 50 penalty points...
you're sent to the
regular court.
Aw, bite me. Don't mess
with us, you bald old goat.
Are you listening?
You lost me halfway through.
- You lost me halfway through.
- Discipline!
Discipline! Discipline!
Discipline! Dismissed!
Thank you very much, sir.
You loser! I'm gonna beat you up someday!
- You loser! I'm gonna beat you up someday!
- We're gonna remember this!
Yeah, you sick mother!
- Yeah, you sick mother!
- Damn!
Hi, Yamagata!
What happened to your cheek?
Don't bother me.
- Don't bother me.
- I heard you got into a fight.
My friends told me you fought
the Clowns on the highway in the old city.
Big deal.
Why didn't you wipe 'em out?
Those guys are so gross.
Clowns, demonstrators,
cops, the damn army...
and that idiot Tetsuo
had an accident!
What happened to Tetsuo?
He's in the hospital,
but we don't know where.
Dumb loser was trying
to show off.
Yeah, a real jerk.
Stupid idiot!
You're talking about Tetsuo, right?
- You're talking about Tetsuo, right?
- Shut up already!
Why do you have to be hanging'
on my arm every minute?
What the heck has got into you?
Tetsuo, it's time
for your medicines.
Doctor, hurry!
The boy is gone!
No, I can't. You know the dorm mother always
throws a fit if you go out before 10:00.
Yeah, you know, the one with a face
like a goat? That woman is such a pain.
She's always complaining about us girls.
Huh? Tomorrow at 3:00?
Yeah, that's cool. Hey, what
happened to that girl? You know who.
I don't like her at all.
She gets on my nerves.
Kaori!
Tetsuo!
Everyone's been worried about you.
They thought you were dead.
When I woke up, I was on an
operating table or something.
That examination... Ohh!
It's like they were messing
around inside my head.
No, I don't want to go back
there again. We'll run away.
Where would we go to?
I don't know. Some place.
Some place far away.
Self study today!
Where'd the teacher go to?
What about my burning desire
to study and learn a vocation?
Drag his butt in here!
Kaneda! Hurry! Your bike!
- Kaneda! Hurry! Your bike!
- What about my bike?
See? Look down there!
Wha... Tetsuo?
Is this okay?
- Is this okay?
- Aw, quiet! Shut up and hang on!
Huh? What the...
- Huh? What the...
- What's wrong?
Uuh! Aw, Shit!
- Uuh! Aw, Shit!
- Ooh!
Oops, it's... stopping...
stopped...
I get it. The engine can't drop below 5,000
R.P.M.S even when you're changing the gears.
Ouch, my butt hurts.
- Ouch, my butt hurts.
- I understand now.
Look, some bikes.
Is that Kaneda and...
Wha... No, it isn't!
Oh, shit! Kaori!
Any sign of 'em?
Kuwata and the others went
to go look around Kisarazu.
The only place we haven't
searched now is the industrial area.
Okay! Let's go!
We owe you from the other night.
Now it's time for payback.
Whoo-hoo!
Shut up!
Kaori! What happened?
No, don't!
If you put a single scratch on that bike,
I'm gonna kill you asshole!
Huh?
Run!
After them!
No, wait.
Tetsuo!
You're gonna kill him, Tetsuo!
You want that?
I want him more than dead!
I'll split his frigging' head open!
Just knock it off now!
This whole thing happened because you
took my bike for a spin. Enough already.
Shut up! Don't order me around!
We were just worried.
Why do you always
have to try to save me?
I could handle it on my own.
I admit that I've gotten beaten before,
but I won't always be on the receiving end.
Do you understand?
Tetsuo...
Shut up! Go away!
Hey, wait! Where're you going?
Leave me alone!
"Akira!"
Tetsuo!
Something wrong?
"Akira!"
I don't know who that is!
Tetsuo... What's wrong?
This is really strange. I'm getting
a blue pattern on scope number 3.
What? No! Retrieve the
subject now! Hurry!
Why don't you guys
just leave my friend alone?
What's with the getup, huh?
You going' to a funeral?
Tetsuo!
Kaneda!
Screw you!
No, wait!
Kaneda, what the hell's
going' on?
Well, well. I see we have
some real hip youngsters...
doing' their thing in spite of the tight
checkpoints they got going around tonight.
And that just means that they're
all pretty stupid, doesn't it?
This is boring.
Hey, what do you say?
Let's go home.
What?
But it's still early.
Yeah, but without their bikes,
they're just tail chasers outta water.
You mean "fish".
Come on.
Let's go and toss these fish back.
Hey, Kaneda.
What are we gonna do?
What the heck?
- What the heck?
- Look.
That's...
Here we go again. Look, let's get out
of here before we get caught up in it.
Huh? Kaneda?
- Huh? Kaneda?
- Hey!
This area is being cordoned off
due to a terrorist bombing.
Those who wish to get through,
line up in single file...
present your I.D. and proceed
through the checkpoint.
Get in.
What's wrong? Hurry.
I'll meet you shortly.
You know the rendezvous point, right?
Be careful.
- Be careful.
- You too. You be careful.
Hey! Hold it right there!
She's got a gun!
Okay, that's far enough!
All right, drop it!
Drop it!
Don't do it!
I think it came from over here.
- I think it came from over here.
- There were two shots.
No, three.
It's just up ahead!
Hey! Let's get out of here.
Come on!
Kaneda!
There. Now what's the matter?
Talk about it.
It was a dream that I saw.
A dream?
The city started to crumble apart,
covered by a big shadow.
Lots of people died.
And the three of us...
we get to meet Akira again.
Wha... Akira?
The city will crumble...
So many people...
So many will die.
When will it happen?
Do you know when? Kiyoko!
You mustn't let that boy go.
His power, it...
What's she talking about?
- What's she talking about?
- Well, there's, uh...
There seems to be nothing
physically wrong with her.
Her medication looks accurate.
There's no sign of any abnormalities...
in her EKG or her EEG either.
I think number 25's statement is probably
her precognitive power at work.
You know, this needs to be brought
before the supreme council for inquiry.
Do you believe her?
I have no doubts regarding
number 25's abilities.
We have lots of data
that substantiate it.
What do you believe, Colonel?
I'll tell you, my job isn't to believe
or disbelieve. It's to act or not act!
Here, sir. Cold gear, Colonel.
Please put it on. You too, doctor.
The other day, a young researcher
came to me and asked me something.
He wondered if their power was
the form of the next stage...
that human evolution was taking, and perhaps
we would all be able to control it some day.
Scientists are
a bunch of romantics.
Military men, on the other hand,
always consider the risks first.
Over 30 years it's taken.
We've come so far
crawling up from the rubble.
We can't just trade one
for the other.
But I've always thought that
you held a resentment...
even a hatred for this city, Colonel.
The passion to build has cooled,
and the joy of reconstruction forgotten.
Now... Now it's just a garbage heap
made up of a bunch of hedonistic fools.
But in spite of that,
you're trying to save the city.
I'm not a scientist.
I think like a soldier.
Colonel, we're here, sir.
This way, please.
Room 10, 148 degrees Kelvin.
Fluctuation tolerance range, check.
Room 9, 118 degrees Kelvin.
Fluctuation tolerance, check.
Emergency power generator, check.
Open the door.
- Open the door.
- Sir. Um...
The control room. Do it!
- The control room. Do it!
- Yes, sir!
Room 1 is at 0.0005 degrees Kelvin.
It's within tolerance range. No
abnormalities detected in any of the rooms...
dewar walls or defence system.
No abnormal atmospheric concentrations
or reactions recorded.
So then all systems are normal.
Look at what they abandoned
in their panic.
They were afraid. They were too scared,
so they hid it away from the public...
losing all sense of shame and hon our,
casting aside the civilization...
and abandoning the science
that created it.
Shutting the lid of the Pandora's
box they, themselves, had opened!
Ryu!
- Ryu!
- Hey, we're still young.
Ryu!
- Ryu!
- We could start over again.
I'll go with you.
- I'll go with you.
- Ryu!
Turn yourself in!
This was the first time
you killed a man, right?
Ryu!
- Ryu!
- Anyway, when you get out...
let's go out for drinks.
Don't kick yourself over it.
What's done is done.
You've heard that.
Identify yourselves!
Ryu! Oh, are you all right?
Kei, it's you!
- Kei, it's you!
- Ryu!
Who's this?
Who? Me?
Well, I guess if I say that I'm Kei's
boyfriend, it's stretching it a bit.
It depends on your point of view.
But we haven't gotten
physical or anything.
You understand, don't you?
- You understand, don't you?
- Are you a spy?
No, I'm not!
- No, I'm not!
- You're lying!
Well, is he a spy or not?
- Well, is he a spy or not?
- Whatever he is, he's certainly not a spy.
Ow!
Sneak into their lab?
Ridiculous!
Remember the fiasco with that kid?
They're last-minute orders,
and the plan is in place already.
These are the lab passes
they issue once a week.
From Mr. Nezu, right?
What's the objective?
We're to gather detailed
data on the new subject.
A new subject?
- A new subject?
- Yes.
Last week, on the same night we tried to abduct
the experimental subject called number 26...
a boy who was in an accident on an
old city highway was brought to the lab.
It seems that he's a student
at a vocational training school...
but now he's their new subject
for human experimentation.
Huh?
Ow, ouch!!
Hey, hey, hey!
What's the big idea?
You!
Should I kill him? He heard us.
- Should I kill him? He heard us.
- Ryu?
Wait! Now just hold on a minute!
Hear me out. Please listen to me!
Ryu, he did save me.
Yeah! Twice!
- Yeah! Twice!
- Maybe he did it just to get close to us.
The guy who was in that accident
in the old city is my friend.
I know it's hard for you to believe
what I'm saying, but it's the truth.
I was right there when it happened!
Come on! Don't they say the only
foolish questions are unasked ones?
They don't?
That's an intriguing story, isn't it?
Well, will you be
taking the boy with you?
He knows the subject and I think we can
use him as a decoy if we find it necessary.
Neo Tokyo is going
to change soon.
In all respects,
this city is saturated.
It's like an overripe fruit.
Buried within it is a new seed.
We need only wait for the wind
which will make it fall to fruition...
The wind called "Akira".
Ryu, look over here.
What is it?
We aren't the ones who will change it...
but rather, those citizens
who hope for Akira that will.
That which is called science
perverts providence!
That which is called progress
encourages extravagance!
That which is called civilization
devastates the spirit of man!
The time of atonement is upon us!
Are your hearts prepared?
The time is nigh!
The time of his awakening is nigh!
The moment of lord Akira's
awakening is drawing closer!
Are your minds prepared?
- Are your minds prepared?
- Break it up!
Holding meetings here
is prohibited.
This gathering is illegal!
Terrorist activities carried out
by anti government elements...
have skyrocketed this month.
The army, riot squad and even the
traffic police have been fully mobilized.
The overtime costs alone have
used up the public safety budget.
And then there's
the abduction of number 26.
Isn't their existence supposed to be
the highest of state secrets, Colonel?
No one's ever heard of peace
and order in Neo Tokyo then?
And this, this request of yours
for further... Ah, yes...
for further funding because of
subject number 25's prediction.
You must be joking! While straightening
out the historic tax-reform blunders...
of our former Prime Minister, we parliament
members have been bowing our heads down...
and begging the public
to bear with us.
And what does he ask for? Money! Where,
exactly, do we get that kind of money?
You've already spent
a fortune here...
and all we have to show for it
is that grotesque kindergarten!
The Olympics is next year,
and the postwar period is over.
How much longer will you keep throwing
away money on these worthless ghosts?
I always said we should put that
money into the welfare program!
Shut up, old man!
What was that?
Now listen here! That power is starting
to walk around free as we speak.
Unless we control that power now, we'll
lose everything we tried so hard to achieve.
- Take that "old man" comment back!
- Your lack of policy started this mess!
There's still no proof that the last world
war was caused by Akira, in my opinion.
Don't you understand?
Unless an Akira disaster actually happens...
Don't you people understand anything?
Has anyone ever seen the "Akira"...?
Akira was number 25, wasn't he?
He should be number 21.
I say that the colonel has lost
sight of his duty as a soldier!
And I have had several reports on
anti government elements...
how they're using your Akira madness
to whip up their terrorist fervour.
It's not true. It's just not!
Then what about that
Akira world renewal movement?
Wouldn't you say that
information's being leaked?
World renewal movement?
It's more like the end of the world.
Aren't you just using Akira as camouflage
to cover up your misconduct? Admit it!
What are you getting at?
Colonel...
Understand that we can no longer leave the
peace of Neo Tokyo to your sole discretion.
Get rid of him!
I'm sorry, but you are to be
put before an inquiry committee.
He should be suspended!
Excuse me!
What?
This discussion isn't over!
This is an outrage!
- This is an outrage!
- You should explain yourself!
Are you trying to insult
the supreme executive council?
Water.
Hey. Wait a minute.
Let's see. Isn't that cable
replacement due for next week?
Well, the cable they ordered
came in a whole week early.
And besides, I've got vacation time
coming, and I'm leaving this weekend.
If I bring the workers back,
there'll be overtime.
I could leave now and come back, but
the work's gotta be done sooner or later.
All right, guys. Let's go.
What the...!
It's milk.
Stay away!
- Whaa!
- Whoa!
It's blood!
- It's blood!
- I'm scared.
Weirdo!
What? Those kids...
"Patient, Room 887.
Shima, Tetsuo."
Oh. The automatic lock's off?
Hey, you! You're not
allowed to leave your room!
Let's go back into your room.
What happened?
- What happened?
- Looks terrible.
There are 58 blocks with circuits
that the computer won't display.
Of those, nearly 40 are concentrated
on underground levels 7 and 8.
That's probably the place.
The central wiring shaft
should be straight up ahead.
We'll be able to use that to go
straight down to the sublevels.
Be careful.
It's deeper in the middle.
Whew. What a stink.
Don't you ever stop talking?
I said it stinks because it stinks.
Is your nose busted?
Keep up and be quiet!
Damn! Hug the walls!
Huh?
What are you guys doing?
You idiot, get down!
Looks like they beefed up security,
doesn't it?
Must be that siren we heard.
- Must be that siren we heard.
- Should we scout a way around it?
No. Let's keep going.
- No. Let's keep going.
- Hey. Are you okay?
I want to check their security
at the very least.
Damn! They spotted us!
Run for it!
Don't shoot! Hold your fire!
Shimazaki!
You assholes!
- You assholes!
- Forget it! Run!
What the hell is that thing?
It's coming back!
Don't shoot!
This is unit 304, Shaft "H".
I have encountered intruders.
Requesting backup. Now engaging.
Here it comes!
Oh! Kei!
The gun!
Damn it!
Kaneda!
Kei! Over here!
Now!
Kaneda, come on! Hurry!
Kaneda, no!
What the hell...
Where are the brakes?
That's not it.
- That's not it.
- This is the central wiring shaft, I think.
I can't figure it out!
- I can't figure it out!
- What the...
There now.
That's right. Behave.
Ask the colonel for clearance
on the use of firearms.
Hey. Turn the radio up.
There must be some mistake here.
That boy looks like the patient
admitted in the lab.
Correct. Tetsuo Shima.
He broke out of his ward.
He's headed for "the baby room".
- He's headed for "the baby room".
- It's Tetsuo?
He's extremely dangerous.
Do not let him through!
Huh? What...?
It's no use hiding any more.
We have no choice, then.
Use your guns!
We can't let him go any further,
no matter what it takes!
Fire!
Good. All here, are you?
Stop it!
So how long are you gonna
keep playing around?
Where's the other one
hiding, huh?
Hey, you!
You're a cretin!
Huh?
Die!
Takashi!
What the hell is going on
with me? Am I dreaming?
These powers, are they real
or just a hallucination?
Damn it!
Where the hell am I going?
Proceed straight.
Proceed straight ahead.
Huh?
You'll find a freight elevator just ahead.
You can take it down
to sublevel 8.
That's good.
You're all together.
You thought you could kill me?
I'm through with it.
You tried to mess with me,
and now I'm gonna kill you!
Huh?
You were there. I remember.
Takashi!
Huh?
- Huh?
- Together, let's attack him.
O... Okay.
You little twerps!
All of you, that is enough!
Who the hell are you?
What's the matter?
Is your head hurting?
Tetsuo Shima, your power
isn't fully matured yet.
If you push yourself, you might do
irreparable damage. We can help.
What the hell?
What... did you people do?
You messed with my head!
Tetsuo Shima, calm yourself.
But he can't control it, sir.
What'd you say?
She said that big people
like you...
should never use the power
in the way that you are.
And bad things will come of it.
Mind your own business,
will you?
What?
More powerful than I am now?
He's the one! He's the one who's been
invading my head all along!
Where is he?
Where's this "Akira"?
Tell me now!
What?
Kiyoko says you'll wake him up
and if you awaken Akira like that...
when that happens,
no one will be able to stop him.
To prevent it,
we have to stop you.
Ridiculous. Akira's already...!
Where is he?
No! Don't!
- No! Don't!
- Stay back!
Red level to facility integrity
has passed level 7.
Enacting disaster protocol.
Red level to facility integrity
has passed level 7.
Enacting disaster protocol.
Wha...?!
Hands up! Now!
Where in the hell's
the frigging' baby room?
Heads up!
Coming through!
Kiyoko.
That hurt.
Kaneda.
What are you doing in here?
Tetsuo! You okay?
I'm here to rescue you.
Hurry up!
What are you, stupid?
If we don't get
out of here, those...
Huh?
There he is! Capture him!
You keep away!
Kaneda!
Oh, that's right.
I forgot you were there.
There. Do you see, Kaneda?
I won't be needing you to come
to the rescue ever again, okay?
From now on, I'll be in
charge of the heroics...
so if you need any saving,
just ask, Kanny.
Damn it, Tetsuo. Who the hell do you think
you're talking to, you moron?
Ha! You don't like
what you're hearing, do you?
Makes you angry. So what are
you gonna do now?
Well, Kaneda?
What are you gonna do now?
That's enough!
Stop it!
Don't hurt anyone else!
Where's this Akira?
I won't tell.
Olympic stadium...
Underground.
No! Don't! What you're
thinking is wrong! Akira is...
Oh! Wait!
What the hell?
I can do this too?
Kiyoko, are you all right?
It doesn't look like she's hurt.
What about you, Masaru?
You're bleeding.
Where'd he go to?
He flew away.
How can he have so much power?
How could this have happened?
Damn it!
Where are my men at?
He's developed so much power
in such a short time, it's unbelievable.
Find him!
Start searching for Tetsuo.
- Find him!
- Kaneda, come on! Get up!
Somebody, help me
with this rock.
Tetsuo went to where Akira is.
- Tetsuo went to where Akira is.
- What?
That's good.
You're all safe.
He's heading for the facility below
the Olympic construction site.
How'd he find out about it?
Damn it! You're saying
that he's managed to escape?
Then we'll follow him.
Prepare for pursuit!
He's heading west toward the stadium.
- He's heading west toward the stadium.
- Come on! Move!
I want additional checkpoints on all outbound
streets leading to the construction site.
It was you.
According
to the security team...
reviews of tapes showed five
intruders disguised as workers...
entering the wiring shaft.
I have to stop him
before his powers mature.
Your objective is the boy,
Tetsuo Shima.
If we are unable to capture him, we'll
lure him out to the old city and attack.
Request assistance from
the Eastern district battalion.
Yes, sir.
- Yes, sir.
- Tell them there isn't a moment to lose here.
I've been waiting here
a long time, Colonel.
What are you doing here?
I'm here to inform you of the supreme
executive council's decision.
"At 2400 hours today,
the colonel is hereby..."
"Stripped of his command
and rank..."
"And shall be placed
under arrest."
What the hell?
Kindly accompany us now.
You really expect me to hand Neo Tokyo
over to those fools at a time like this?
Shoot him.
- Shoot him.
- Yes, sir.
What? No! Wait!
Hold on! No!
Enough! Open your eyes
and look at the big picture!
You're all puppets of corrupt
politicians and capitalists!
Don't you understand?
It's utterly pointless to fight each other.
Announce a state of emergency, and arrest
all members of the executive council.
Break their chain of command.
Lift off!
We're going after Tetsuo.
Urgent message. Repeat, urgent.
To all district
battalion commanders.
Yo! What's up?
You're alone?
That's right.
Weren't you in an accident?
Your friends have been
really worried. You okay?
Give me some... capsules.
Huh? You sure
you want capsules, son?
You look kinda woozy.
You better get 'em now.
All right.
Whatever the customer wants, you know, but
with all those terrorist attacks lately...
and the demonstrations,
things are pretty rough.
In fact, they're hard to come by, so
the price is pretty expensive, right?
Tetsuo's run off somewhere,
Kaneda's disappeared.
Damn, I guess
the team is finished.
And the checkpoints are
so strict these days.
Even the Clowns are laying low.
Look!
He's dead!
What?
Who's that?
It's Tetsuo.
Why... Why are you here?
Look who's here.
Wanna pop one?
What the hell are you talking about?
What happened here?
Did you notice that
the owner's dead?
An octopus out of water dies, huh?
Are you... Tetsuo...
or someone else?
- Or someone else?
- Huh?
Kaneda sends
his warmest regards.
You saw Kaneda?
He's probably dead by now.
You did this, didn't you?
All you're good for now is telling
me where Kaneda's bike is.
Tetsuo!
It's a piece of shit anyway.
You son of a bitch!
Yamagata!
God damn it!
So is he off to find Akira?
Yes, that's what that girl was saying.
Now, the army,
Ryu and yourself...
are all trying at once
to find this Akira guy...
and that's also why you're
chasing after Tetsuo.
It must have to do
with the powers he's got.
What the hell is this Akira thing?
I asked Ryu one time.
He told me that Akira
is ultimate energy.
"Ultimate energy"?
Humans do all kinds of things
during their lifetime, right?
Discover things...
Build things...
Things like houses, motorcycles...
bridges and cities, rockets...
So where do you suppose all that
knowledge and energy comes from?
Humans were once
like monkeys, right?
And before that,
like reptiles...
and fish...
and even before that,
plankton and amoebas.
Even little creatures like those have
incredible amount of energy inside them.
Oh, yes...
It's in the genes, right?
And even before that.
Maybe there was genetic
material in the air and water...
even in the particles
of dust in space.
And if that's the truth, then what sort
of memories are hidden within them?
The beginning of the universe?
Or maybe even before that.
What's with all the crazy talk?
Are you sure you're okay?
Listen to yourself. Did you get
bonked on the head back there?
And what if everyone shares
those ancient memories?
What if there were some mistakes
in the progression?
Then something goes wrong,
like an amoeba is suddenly given...
the higher powers
that a human has.
Akira is an amoeba then?
Amoebas don't build their own
houses and bridges, do they?
They just devour all the food
they can find around them.
Is that what Tetsuo's doing?
Are you saying he has
that kind of energy?
Long ago...
there were people who tried
to gain control of that power.
That is, all of the government's
requests.
But they failed in their attempt,
and it triggered the fall of Tokyo.
And that power is...
something that is
totally beyond our...
Wha...!
The door's unlocked.
Huh?
It's a trap.
This is just too good of a setup.
Go back, then.
- Go back, then.
- No way.
I wanna find out how much
of a trap it is, don't you?
By the way...
what's going on with you
and that Ryu guy?
What in the world
are you talking about?
You're always together.
- You're always together.
- That's none of your business.
No, wait. Hear me out.
What I'm saying is, he doesn't
know about us, does he?
"About us"? Hey, wait a minute.
What's that supposed to mean?
Do you think it'll work?
- Do you think it'll work?
- It can't be helped.
At this point in time, our only
option left is to use her.
Well, the fact that,
without us even looking...
she turned up right under
our noses, says as much.
What do you think?
- What do you think?
- I guess so.
We have arrived at ward 13,
East Ginza intersection. Over.
Northern district battalion has not
responded to mobilization request!
Special search team to H.Q.
We're at the Harukiya bar near
the highway interchange at ward 8.
It doesn't look like a bomb explosion
to us, so we think it was him.
No, sir, it wasn't
a gas explosion either.
It was almost certainly the work of
the subject that escaped from the lab.
Yes, sir. Yes, sir.
Understood.
Kaneda, wait!
What? Yamagata's dead?
Something seemed strange about him
the second I saw his face.
It's odd. He was wearing what
looked like a white hospital gown.
He acted like a different person.
Yamagata asked him
if he was really Tetsuo...
or if he was someone else.
And then he... Yamagata!
Why?
We've always been together.
I've known everything
about him ever...
ever since we were
in the children's home together.
They tease... Everybody
tried to make him cry.
Oh. He really wanted to know
where your bike was at.
Where my bike was?
What are you gonna do?
I'm gonna go send
Yamagata his wheels.
You dumb bastard!
Kaneda!
Kei!
What's wrong?
That night. You were there.
Wait!
Kei!
They're gone!
You're the one, right?
You changed my friend, didn't you?
The thing about Akira's power is...
it exists within everyone
from the start.
Hey, who is that?
But when that power
is awakened inside...
it is important to wisely
choose how to use it.
When the time comes,
you might not know it...
let alone be prepared for it.
Your friend
has already made his choice.
Tetsuo is our newest companion.
He's our friend also.
His actions are out of control...
and for that
we're partly to blame too.
Great! Then what in the hell
did you take Kei for?
We're hoping she'll be able
to help us in some way.
They're people, not toys!
Bring her back to me!
And Tetsuo's our friend,
not yours!
If someone's gonna kill him,
it should be us!
Hey!
Are you sure? Mr. Omi and the others
have been arrested in the coup d'etat?
Yes, that's right. The house guards
are fighting them right now.
Yes. I'd like to have
a helicopter waiting. Yes.
That damn Colonel! I can't
believe he's taken up arms.
I've underestimated him.
Hold them here!
Mr. Nezu, I...
Oh! Ryu, is that you?
I came to apologize, sir.
The mission was a failure.
Damn you! I told you,
you can't be seen here!
My two best men, they're dead.
Everyone was killed.
You bastard! You sold me out!
What?
Kei!
Yeah, 7th avenue
is just up ahead.
It intersects this road
a hundred meters from here.
Battle stations!
Right! The subject
has been spotted.
What? Attack the kid?
But, sir, he's just a boy!
We can't attack him!
Look! There he is!
- Look! There he is!
- It's impossible.
Is this for real?
Fire range preparations
are complete.
Damn it! Fire!
Is it Akira?
Look, it's Lord Akira!
Don't be fooled! This isn't the rapture!
He's a false messiah!
Long live Akira!
Fire!
What the...
- What the...
- What's wrong?
Coming to you live aboard news
chopper 1 high over downtown.
Neo Tokyo broadcasting is exclusively
covering the news today...
in spite of martial law, in the
name of freedom of the press.
What in the world is happening
here in Neo Tokyo?
What you see here seem to be
fires caused by tank cannons.
But who is this boy standing alone? Is he
fighting the coup d'etat forces by himself?
I'm sorry.
We've been ordered to land.
The army has just illegally
ordered us to land!
What is at stake here is freedom of
the press! We've been ordered to...
Did they just get cut off?
- Did they just get cut off?
- What was that?
The bridge!
He's heading for the bridge!
Are you sure you want
to do this alone?
This is what he wants, isn't it?
At least give me time
to get the gang together.
Hey, wait!
I wouldn't want to keep him
waiting now, would I?
Hey, Kaneda, hold on!
Half of them seem to be anti government
demonstrators. The rest are...
They're more like some
crazy cult than onlookers.
They're following after the subject,
and more and more keep coming.
Flames of supreme purity...
rain down and raze
the corrupt city...
and drown forever all the
unclean believers of our time!
Give yourselves
into the flame, children...
and all of you
shall be reborn again!
Now consume our heart.
Wash our unclean hearts
in the eternal fire!
Your body is going to be
purified in the flames!
Ready!
What?
- What?
- Fire!
Set the switch to hold for 3 seconds.
Then converge your beams.
Aim, fire!
Watch this!
Look out!
Let's get out of here!
Save me!
Ground forces.
Ground forces, come in.
Report immediately.
What is the subject's status?
Do you read?
Line to the doctor.
We have confirmation of his recent
movements and are in pursuit.
His present position is...
coordinates 99871 by 4332.
That's about 2 kilometres south of
the Olympic construction site...
in the old city.
What?
Where did that blast come from?
Look!
- Look!
- Huh?
That must be out over at the tollbooth
being guarded by the second platoon.
What the hell?
Please turn around now.
This area is off-limits to civilians.
Huh? What? That's
the escaped subject? Stop!
Don't come any closer!
Stop, damn it!
Nice place you have here, isn't it?
You are the girl
that was with Kaneda.
You shouldn't use your power in this way,
for it is not correct.
What's that?
Because in the end, you won't be able to
control it, and it will control you.
It's the kids talking.
You're those brats, right?
Nice one!
What's going on?
It's not safe here, Colonel!
All right now. Next move.
Open now!
What the hell is this?
That is Akira before you,
Tetsuo.
That's the Akira
you wanted to meet!
There is your messiah, the chosen one that
you've been looking for.
Not long after
his transcendental awakening...
his organs and tissues were subjected to
every test known to modern science.
He's dead. That's it.
What you see there
is all that's left of him.
And all of the scientists
back then...
were unable to solve
the mystery...
so they decided to entrust all of
their collected data and test samples...
to future generations by preserving them
in frozen capsules and locking them away.
SOL. We will use SOL.
- SOL. We will use SOL.
- Huh?
Akira has been dead all this time.
Well, are you satisfied now,
Tetsuo?
Now will you return with us?
Like hell!
Contact the central
defence centre...
and tell them to patch us through into
SOL's main control circuits right away!
Hey, watch it, you jerk!
Move! Get out of the way!
Move it!
What is this,
a science classroom?
Huh?
What's wrong?
Have some trouble?
Yeah, but I already
took care of it.
And you're too late.
You missed the show.
Tetsuo,
you had me worried again.
I figured you'd be standing here,
sobbing like a little baby.
Kaneda. You've always been
a pain in the ass, you know.
You've been telling me
what to do since we were kids!
You always treat me like a kid.
You always show up and start
bossing me around, and don't you deny it!
And now you're a boss, too,
of this pile of rumble.
Kaneda!
- Kaneda!
- That's "Mister" Kaneda to you, punk!
Die!
Tetsuo!
Son of a bitch!
Kei!
Oh, damn it!
Let's do it!
Gotcha!
What?
Huh?
The damn battery's dead!
What's the matter now, Kaneda?
Damn it!
It ain't fair, Tetsuo!
Fight with your bare hands!
Oh, this is funny!
Feeling frustrated, Kaneda?
Now do you understand how it feels
being little and helpless?
Oh?
Where's this light coming from?
Were we on target?
- Were we on target?
- Hard to tell. Too close to the impact point.
The monitors are
getting too much electrical...
- The monitors are getting too much electrical...
- Prepare a second volley, now!
Hey!
Kaneda!
Tetsuo!
Shit!
What the...
Wh...!
Correcting error now
on tracking system.
T minus 20...
Get the fire extinguishers!
Are you okay?
Get that fire out!
- Get that fire out!
- What's going on?
Kaneda!
Kai! Kei!
- Kaneda!
Get on!
Where?
- Where?
- Hurry!
What is that?
Reports say it's SOL.
Magnificent.
When Tetsuo's power
reaches its peak...
is that what you're thinking?
That's when we do it.
But will it really work?
We know the future doesn't
necessarily proceed along a single course.
There ought to be a future we can choose.
It's up to us to find it.
What's Tetsuo's status, doctor?
- What's Tetsuo's status, doctor?
- Colonel.
We set up a camera in the
stadium if you want to check.
We have him under observation.
Colonel, you must take a look at this data.
It's phenomenal!
We're still analysing the energy given off
by the subject, but it's just magnificent.
Oh, yes, wonderful.
Of course, this is clearly
a proton collapse.
We're also detecting a fair number of what we
believe to be unknown particles to science.
If we can put this into
a theoretical framework...
then physics...
quantum physics...
humanity itself could know
the fundamental truths.
Uh... Uh... Well, you see...
we still haven't finished
making our adjustments.
Wait, Colonel.
What the... The pattern!
You bastard!
What did I tell you?
But, Colonel...
I couldn't throw away
such a magnificent subject.
Shut up!
Oh! Oh, oh! Oh, shit!
Quick! The battery!
Come on!
My bike's burning up!
Hey, what's losing
a bike or two, huh?
What? Then there's nothing wrong
with using yours, right?
I said that out loud, did I?
- I said that out loud, did I?
- Yeah, you did.
By the way,
your bike's still on fire.
Huh? Oh, man! Oh!
Tetsuo?
Tetsuo, why is everyone calling you Akira?
What does it mean?
It means nothing.
He never existed.
It doesn't matter who he is.
They don't care.
Just so long as he destroys things.
What's that?
Your arm! Look at it!
Well, it doesn't look like much,
but it still works pretty good.
What's wrong? Are you okay?
It's nothing!
Tetsuo, I just...
- Tetsuo, I just...
- Shut up! Just go away!
Medicine.
What's wrong, Tetsuo?
Are you in pain? Huh?
Go back to the lab
and get that medicine.
Doctor, did you hear that?
I did, Colonel.
- I did, Colonel.
- Well, any signs of it?
I can't be entirely certain here...
but it seems that the power which had been
held back by the drugs is breaking free.
He may not be able to control the power
that has awakened so suddenly!
He's in an extremely
critical condition!
Come back to the lab and
receive proper treatment.
If you don't, you may die.
You want me to enrol in your kindergarten
and live happily ever after, huh?
Be quiet
and do what you're told.
Take your medicine every day
and end up all shrivelled like those kids!
Kaori.
Fetch medicine, please.
No.
Stop, Tetsuo!
Tetsuo!
No, Tetsu...!
Kaneda!
Huh?
Son of a... Huh?
What are you three... doing here?
You didn't learn
your lesson, did you?
Heads up, Tetsuo!
Takashi.
Akira's here.
Help, Kaneda! Help, please!
Kaori!
Please, help me!
Help me!
Let her go!
Kaori. Kaori. Kaori!
Tetsuo, are you there?
Kaori!
Kaori's gonna die!
What? What did you say?
My body's not doing
what I tell it to.
My power's acting
on its own. Kaori!
Kaori's dying.
Kaneda, help me!
Stop this, Tetsuo!
Stop it now!
Kaori's pain is coming into me.
Tetsuo!
Kaneda, run away!
Kiyoko, Takashi, Masaru!
Hurry! Get away from here!
Come on!
I can't believe it. It's as if...
Kiyoko! Taka...
Hi.
Akira.
Oh, no! That's the...
But that's impossible!
Where am I?
Hurry. Get into the tunnel.
You'll be safe in there.
Kiyoko, where are you?
Oh...
Tetsuo!
Kaneda!
Hang on!
Hurry! You've got to get out of here!
- Hurry! You've got to get out of here!
- Out of the way!
Tetsuo!
- Tetsuo!
- Don't go near it!
No, don't! Wait, Takashi!
If you went in now, you'd
be trapped along with him.
But he... None of this
is his fault at all.
Takashi!
- Takashi!
If we went in there...
we wouldn't be strong enough
to come back out again.
But if the three of us tried...
maybe we could save that boy.
You're right.
Us three together.
Look at that. We should get
out of here now! Hey!
Kaneda's in there.
You see that? You're not revving
your engine enough already.
When you go into a corner,
lean in suicidally. Got it? Now watch.
What the hell do you call that?
- What the hell do you call that?
- Cornering, man.
You got it, Tetsuo?
Hey, look! They brought another kid!
Is he a transfer student?
His mom and dad left him.
- His mom and dad left him.
- You can see it in his face.
Are these... Are these all of your dreams
and memories, Tetsuo?
Uh, wait.
Is this Akira?
Yes. We called
him here to the three of us.
He's going to take
Tetsuo with him.
Take him where?
Where?
It's too much for Tetsuo...
and for the three of us also
and for Akira too.
It's way too big
for us, as we are now.
But someday we ought
to be able to...
Because it has already begun.
Your friend, she's...
My friend?
Kei! It's Kei
you're talking about!
Tetsuo.
This is yours, right?
They're always like that
with the new kids.
Hey, you came today, right?
They beat me up too, but the truth is,
those guys are wimps.
My name is... Tetsuo.
Tetsuo Shima.
The truth is,
I just got here myself.
My name is...
Kaneda. Kaneda.
Kaneda!
- Kaneda!
- Kei.
What in the world is happening?
What's this?
No, this isn't...
If this is correct, it's showing
that this is the birth of the universe.
Kei!
What's going on here?
Disappearing.
It's disappearing.
Kaneda, can you hear me?
Tetsuo.
Kaneda, what is it?
Thank you.
Huh?
You called me, didn't you,
and I heard you.
Kaneda! Oh, my!
Where's Tetsuo?
He just left.
Those kids did too.
Akira also.
Kaneda, back then...
Oh, did you just...
Kaneda!
You're alive!
I thought...
I thought you were
in there for sure.
Tetsuo!
What happened to Tetsuo?
Is he dead?
I'm not sure.
Something... Oh!
But someday we
ought to be able to...
Because it has already begun.
I am Tetsuo.