Bio-readouts are in the green.
Looks like she's alive.
There goes our salvage.
- How are we today?
- Terrible.
- Better than yesterday, at least.
- Where am l?
You're safe. You're at Gateway Station,
been here two days.
You were pretty groggy at first,
but now you're OK.
Looks like you've got a visitor.
Jonesy. Come here.
Come here.
How are you, you stupid cat?
Where have you been?
I guess you two have met.
I'm Carter Burke.
I work for the company.
But don't let that fool you. I'm an OK guy.
I'm glad you're a little better. The weakness
and disorientation should pass soon.
It's just natural side effects
of such an unusually long hyper sleep.
What do you mean?
How long was I out there?
Has no one discussed this with you yet?
But, l mean, I don't recognize this place.
No, I know.
It's just that this might be a shock.
It's longer...
How long? Please.
57 years.
- What?
- You were out there for 57 years.
You had drifted
right through the core systems,
and it's really just blind luck
that a deep-salvage team found you.
It's one in a thousand, really.
You're damn lucky to be alive, kiddo.
You could be floating out there forever.
Are you OK?
God!
Nurse!
Someone get in here now.
Now!
- Hold.
- Please...
Hold her.
Kill me!
Bad dreams again?
Want something to help you sleep?
I've slept enough.
Come here.
It's all right.
It's over.
- Sorry I'm late.
- Is there any word about my daughter?
I think we should worry about the hearing
now, cos we don't have long.
I read your deposition, and it's great.
Stick to that and we'll be fine.
There'll be a lot of heavyweights there -
feds, Interstellar Commerce Commission,
Colonial Administration, insurance guys...
Do you have any news
about my daughter?
We did come up with some information.
Why don't we sit down?
I was hoping to wait
until after the inquest...
Amanda Ripley-McClaren -
married name, I guess - aged 66.
And that was at the time of her death.
Which was two years ago.
I'm real sorry.
Amy...
She was interred at Westlake Repository,
Little Chute, Wisconsin.
No children. I checked.
I promised her
that I'd be home for her birthday.
Her 11th birthday.
I don't understand this.
We have been here
for three and a half hours.
How many different ways
do you want me to tell the same story?
Look at it from our perspective, please.
Please.
You admit to destroying
an M-Class star-freighter,
a rather expensive piece of hardware.
42 million in adjusted dollars.
That's minus payload, of course.
The lifeboat's flight recorder
corroborates some of your account,
in that, for reasons unknown,
the Nostromo set down on LV-426,
an unsurveyed planet at that time.
That it resumed its course and was
subsequently set for self-destruct, by you,
- for reasons unknown.
- Not for reasons unknown. I told you.
We landed there on company orders
to get this thing, which destroyed my crew.
And your expensive ship.
The analysis team,
which examined the lifeboat minutely,
found no evidence of this creature.
Good. That's because I blew it
out of the goddamn airlock.
Like I said.
Are there any species
like this hostile organism on LV-426?
It's a rock. No indigenous life.
Did IQs drop sharply while I was away?
I said it was not indigenous.
It was a derelict spacecraft, an alien ship.
It was not from there. Do you get it?
We homed in on its beacon.
And found something never recorded once
in over 300 surveyed worlds.
"A creature that gestates inside a living
human host." These are your words.
- "And has concentrated acid for blood."
- That's right.
I can see where this is going.
But I'm telling you that those things exist.
- Thank you. That will be all.
- Please!
Kane, the crew member...
Kane, who went into that ship,
said he saw thousands of eggs there.
- Thank you, that will be all.
- Goddammit, that's not all.
If one of those things gets down here,
you can kiss all of this bullshit goodbye!
It is the finding of this court of inquiry
that Warrant Officer E Ripley, NOC 14472,
has acted with questionable judgment,
and is unfit to hold an ICC license
as a commercial flight officer.
Said license is hereby
suspended indefinitely.
No criminal charges will be filed, and you
are released on your own recognizance
for a six-month period
of psychometric probation,
to include monthly review
by an ICC psychiatric technician.
These proceedings are closed.
That could have been better.
Look, I think...
Van Leuwen?
Why don't you just check out LV-426?
I don't have to.
There have been people there over 20 years,
and they never mentioned
hostile organisms.
- What people?
- Terraformers.
Planet engineers. They set up big atmosphere
processors to make the air breathable.
Takes decades. It's what we call
a “shake’n’bake” colony.
How many colonists are there?
60, maybe 70 families. Do you mind?
Families.
Jesus.
- I'll be down in Maintenance, OK?
- Al?
Remember you sent some wildcatters
out into the middle of nowhere last week?
One of them's on the horn,
says he's onto something.
- Wants to know if his claim will be honored.
- Why wouldn't it be?
Because you sent them out there
on company orders maybe?
Christ! Some honch in a cushy office
on Earth says go look at a grid reference.
We look. They don't say why,
and I don't ask,
because it takes two weeks
to get an answer,
and the answer is always "Don't ask."
So what do I tell this guy?
As far as I'm concerned,
if he finds something, it is his.
- Lydecker?
- What?
You kids know you're not supposed
to be on this level. Get outta here.
- You go in places we can't fit.
- That's why I'm the best.
Knock it off. I catch you playing
in the air ducts again, I'll tan your hides.
- All the kids...
- I don't care.
Wait a minute. Annie, look at this.
Folks, we have scored big this time.
What is it, Dad?
I'm not sure. Let's try and get a closer look
at it through that crack down the side.
- Shouldn't we call in?
- Let's wait till we know what to call it in as.
That's about as close as we can get.
Shall we take a look inside?
You kids stay inside.
We'll be right back.
OK. Bye.
Timmy, they've been gone a long time.
It'll be OK, Newt.
Dad knows what he's doing.
Mayday! This is Alpha Kilo
Two Four Nine calling Hadley Control!
Hi, Ripley. This is Lieutenant Gorman
of the Colonial Marine Corps...
We have to talk.
We've lost contact
with the colony on LV-426.
I don't believe this.
You throw me at the wolves,
and now you want me to go back out there?
Forget it. It's not my problem.
- Can I finish?
- There's no way.
You wouldn't be going in with the troops.
I guarantee your safety.
These Colonial Marines
are very tough hombres.
They pack state-of-the-art firepower.
There's nothing they can't handle.
- Lieutenant, am I right?
- We're trained to deal with these situations.
Then you don't need me.
I'm not a soldier.
We don't know
what's going on out there.
It may just be a downed transmitter, okay?
But if it's not,
I would like you there as an adviser,
and that's all.
What's your interest in this?
Why are you going?
The corporation co-financed that colony
with Colonial Administration.
We're into a lot of terraforming,
building better worlds...
Yeah, I saw the commercial.
I've gotta get to work.
I heard you're working
in the cargo docks.
That's right.
- Running forklifts?
- So?
Nothing. It's great
that you're keeping busy.
And I know it's the only thing you
could get. There's nothing wrong with it.
What if I told you I could
get you reinstated as a flight officer?
The company's agreed
to pick up your contract.
If I go.
If you go. Come on.
That's a second chance, kiddo.
I think for you it would be best
to face this thing, get back on the horse...
Spare me. I've had
my psych evaluation this month.
I know. l read it. You wake up every night
soaking with sweat...
I said no, and I mean it.
Now please leave. I am not going back,
and I would be no good to you if I did.
OK.
Would you do me a favor?
Just think about it.
Thanks for the coffee.
Hello?
- You OK?
- Just tell me one thing.
You're going out there
to destroy them, right?
Not to study, not to bring back,
but to wipe them out.
That's the plan. You have my word on it.
All right, I'm in.
And you, you little shithead,
you're staying here.
They ain't payin' us enough for this, man.
Not enough to have to
wake up to your face, Drake.
What?
Is that a joke?
I wish it were.
Hey, Hicks. You look just like I feel.
OK, sweethearts, what are you waiting for?
Breakfast in bed?
Another glorious day in the Corps. A day in
the Marine Corps is like a day on the farm.
Every meal's a banquet, every paycheck
a fortune, every formation a parade.
- I love the Corps.
- This floor is freezing.
- Want me to fetch your slippers for you?
- Gee, would you, sir?
Look into my eye.
Fall in, people. Let's go.
- I hate this job.
- Crowe, Wierzbowski, on your feet.
You just had three weeks on your back.
I'm talkin' about breathing,
not this frozen shit.
Yeah, Top, how about it?
First assembly's in 1 5, people. Shag it.
Who's Snow White?
She's some kind of consultant.
Apparently she saw an alien once.
Whoopee-fucking-do. I'm impressed.
Vasquez, have you
ever been mistaken for a man?
No. Have you?
You're just too bad.
- Top, what's the op?
- It's a rescue mission. You'll love it.
There's some juicy colonists' daughters
we have to rescue from their virginity.
Dumb-ass colonists.
- What's this crap supposed to be?
- Corn bread, I think.
It's good for you, boy. Eat it.
I sure wouldn't mind gettin' some
more Arcturian poontang. Remember?
- Yeah, Frost, but your one was male.
- Doesn't matter when it's Arcturian.
- Bishop, do the thing with the knife.
- Oh, please.
Come on.
- All right!
- I don't wanna see that.
What are you doin'?
Quit messin' around, Drake. Bishop!
- Do it.
- Not me, man!
- Yeah, you.
- Quit messin' around.
Trust me.
- All right, knock it off.
- Thank you.
- Enjoy your meal.
- That wasn't funny.
- Lieutenant Gorman? Mr. Burke?
- Thanks.
Looks like the new lieutenant's
too good to eat with the rest of us grunts.
The boy's got a corncob up his ass.
Thought you never missed.
You said nothing about
an android being on board. Why not?
It never occurred to me.
We always have a synthetic on board.
I prefer the term
"artificial person" myself.
- Is there a problem?
- I'm sorry. I don't know why I didn't...
Ripley's last trip out,
the artificial person malfunctioned.
There were problems,
and a few deaths were involved.
- I'm shocked. Was it an older model?
- The Hyperdyne Systems 120-A/2.
That explains it.
The A/2s always were a bit twitchy.
That can't happen
with our behavioural inhibitors.
It is impossible for me to harm,
or allow to be harmed, a human being.
Sure you don't want some?
Just stay away from me.
You got that?
Guess she don't like
the corn bread either.
- Squad, atten-ho! Officer on deck.
- As you were.
Quickly. Settle down.
All right, listen up.
Morning, Marines. Sorry we didn't have time
to brief you before we left Gateway...
- Sir?
- What is it, Hicks?
Hudson, sir. He's Hicks.
- What's the question?
- Is this gonna be a stand-up fight,
or another bug hunt?
All we know is there's
no contact with the colony,
and that a xenomorph may be involved.
- A what?
- A xenomorph.
It's a bug hunt.
What exactly are we dealing with here?
I'll tell you what I know.
We set down on LV-426.
A crew member
was brought back on board
with something attached to his face,
some kind of parasite.
We tried to get it off, but couldn't.
Later it seemed to come off by itself and die.
Kane seemed fine.
We were all having dinner and...
It must have laid something in his throat,
some sort of embryo. He started...
I only need to know one thing:
where they are.
- Go, Vasquez. Kick ass.
- Anytime, anywhere.
Somebody said “alien”. She thought
they said “illegal alien” and signed up.
- Fuck you.
- Anytime, anywhere.
Are you finished?
I hope you're right. l really do.
OK, thank you, Ripley. We have Ripley's
report on disk. I suggest you study it.
Because just one of those things wiped out
my entire crew in less than 24 hours.
If the colonists found that ship, there's
no telling how many have been exposed.
Do you understand?
Anyway, we have it on disk,
so look at it.
Any questions?
- What is it, Private?
- How do I get out of this chickenshit outfit?
You secure that shit, Hudson.
All right.
Now listen.
I want this to go smooth,
and by the numbers.
I want DCS and tactical
database assimilation by 0830.
Ordnance loading, weapons strip and
dropship prep details will have seven hours.
Now move it, people.
You heard the man and you know the drill.
Assholes and elbows.
Hudson, come here.
I don't care if you are short.
Get it done.
- You'll get lip cancer smokin' those.
- Corporal, I want this loading lock sealed.
- How many more, Spunkmeyer?
- Last one.
Take it away.
Clear behind.
Did you check number three?
Hi. I feel like a fifth wheel.
Is there anything I can do?
I don't know.
Is there anything you can do?
I can drive that loader.
- I have a Class 2 rating.
- Be my guest.
Where you want it?
Bay 1 2, please.
All right. You're a team,
and there's nothing to worry about.
We're gonna conquer,
and we're gonna kick some. Understood?
That's what we're gonna do,
sweethearts.
All right, people, on the ready line.
Are you lean?
Are you mean?
- What are you?
- Lean, mean marines!
Hudson! Get on the ready line.
Get some today!
Get on the ready line!
Move it out, goddammit!
Get hot! Get out, get out!
Move it out, move it out!
Absolutely badasses!
Let's pack 'em in. Get in there!
Move it.
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven.
I want combat seating.
You know your places.
Get those weapons stowed.
Come on, settle down, people.
- Lock 'em in, Hudson.
- Ready to get it on? You know it.
OK, Bishop, let's go.
Roger.
I'm ready, man.
Ready to get it on.
Cross-locking now.
Pre-launch auto cycle engaged.
Primary couplers released.
Hit the internals.
Confirm cross-lock
and drop stations secured.
Affirmative. All drop stations secured.
1 0 seconds.
Stand by to initiate release sequencer.
On my mark. Five...
We're on an express elevator to hell.
Going down.
..two, one, mark.
Switch to DCS ranging.
- 2-4-0. Nominal to profile.
- We're in the pipe. Five by five.
- We're picking up some hull ionisation.
- Got it.
Rough air ahead. We're in for some chop.
How many drops is this for you,
Lieutenant?
38.
- Simulated.
- How many combat drops?
Two. Including this one.
- Shit.
- Oh, man.
Range 014.
Turning on final.
- I got a bad feeling about this drop.
- You always say that.
"l got a bad feeling about this drop."
When we get back without ya,
I'll call your folks.
All right. Let's see what we can see.
Everybody online. Lookin' good.
Drake, check your camera.
There seems to be a malfunction.
That's better. Pan it around a bit.
Good.
I'm ready. Check it out.
I am the ultimate badass.
State-of-the-badass-art.
You do not wanna fuck with me.
Check it out.
Ripley, don't worry.
Me and my squad of ultimate badasses
will protect you.
Check it out.
Independently targeting
particle-beam Phalanx.
Fry half a city with this puppy.
We got tactical smart missiles,
phased-plasma pulse rifles, RPGs,
we got sonic electronic ball breakers!
We got nukes, we got knives,
sharp sticks...
Knock it off.
All right, gear up.
Two minutes, people.
Somebody wake up Hicks.
- Coming around for a 709.
- Terminal guidance locked in.
Where's the damn beacon?
Oh, I see it.
- That's the atmosphere processor?
- That's it.
Remarkable piece of machinery.
Completely automated.
We manufacture those, by the way.
Ferro, take us in low
over the main colony complex.
Storm shutters are sealed.
There's no visible activity.
Hold at 40.
Roger.
Give me a slow circle of the complex.
Structure seems intact.
- They still have power.
- Ferro, set down on the landing grid.
Immediate dust-off on my clear,
then stay on station.
Down and clear.
Ten seconds, people. Look sharp.
I want a nice clean dispersal this time.
Let's go. Move it out.
Head 'em up.
First squad up online. Hicks, get yours
in a cordon. Watch the rear.
Vasquez, take point. Let's move.
Move up.
Hudson, run a bypass.
Second squad, move up.
Flanking positions.
Second squad online.
Are you set?
Go on.
Second team, move inside.
Hicks, take the upper level.
Sir, are you copying this?
Looks like hits from small-arms fire.
We got some explosives damage.
It's probably seismic survey charges.
Are you readin' this?
Keep it tight, people.
Hicks, Hudson,
use your motion trackers.
Nothing. Not a goddamn thing.
Quarter and search by twos.
Dietrich, Frost, you're up.
It's right in there.
Now.
- Good one, Hudson.
- Sir, we have a negative situation here.
Moving on, sir.
Wait. Tell him to...
Back up.
Pan right.
There.
You seein' this all right?
Looks melted. Somebody must have bagged
one of Ripley's bad guys here.
Acid for blood.
If you like that, you're gonna love this.
- Quit screwin' around.
- Second squad, what's your status?
We've just finished our sweep.
Nobody's home.
Roger. Sir, this place is dead.
Whatever happened here,
I think we missed it.
The area's secured.
Let's see what their computer can tell us.
- It's not secured.
- The area is secured.
First team, head for Operations.
Hudson, try and get their CPU online.
Affirmative.
Hicks, meet me at the south lock.
We're coming in.
- He's comin' in. I feel safer already.
- Pendejo jerk-off.
Sir, we got the CPU online. No problem.
Good. Stand by in Operations.
OK, let's go.
Are you all right?
Sir, they sealed off this wing
at both ends.
Welded the doors, and blocked off
the stairs with heavy equipment.
But it looks like the barricade didn't hold.
- Any bodies?
- No, sir.
- Last stand.
- Must have been a hell of a fight.
Looks that way.
Drake, this way. We should be able
to cut through the medlab to Operations.
Lieutenant.
Are those the same ones?
Careful.
Looks like love at first sight to me.
He likes you.
Two are alive, the rest are dead.
Surgically removed
before embryo implantation.
Subject: Marachuk, John J.
Died during the procedure.
They killed him taking it off.
I think we got something here.
- Behind us.
- One of us?
Apone, where are your people?
Anybody in D-Block?
Negative. We're all in Operations.
Talk to me, Frosty.
Just keep movin', baby.
- It's moving.
- Which way?
It's coming straight for us. Straight up.
- Fuck.
- Hold up.
It's all right. Come on.
- Just grab her, Corporal.
- Don't be afraid. We won't hurt you.
It's all right. Come on out.
Come on. Easy...
I got her.
Damn!
- Don't let her go.
- She's under the grille.
- Frost, get your light up here.
- Where'd she go?
- Shine the light.
- Down here.
- Here.
- There she is.
Keep back. Don't scare her.
- Grab her. We're gonna lose her.
- Damn it.
Wait.
It's OK. It's all right.
Don't be afraid.
See?
Wait. No, you don't.
It's OK. You're gonna be all right now.
Easy, easy. It's gonna be OK.
You're gonna be OK.
Easy, easy.
- What's her name again?
- Rebecca.
Think, Rebecca. Concentrate.
Just start at the beginning.
Where are your parents?
- Look, you have to try...
- Give it a rest, why don't you?
- Total brain lock.
- Physically she's OK.
Borderline malnutrition,
but no permanent damage.
Come on. We're wasting our time.
Try this. It's hot chocolate.
There you go.
That good, huh?
I made a clean spot here. Now I've done it.
Guess I'll have to do the whole thing.
Hard to believe there's
a little girl under all this.
And a pretty one, too.
You don't talk much, do you?
- Smoking or non-smoking?
- Just tell me what you're scanning for.
PDTs. Personal data transmitters.
Every colonist had one surgically implanted.
If they're within 20 klicks
we'll read it out here. So far, zippo.
I don't know how you managed to stay alive.
But you're one brave kid, Rebecca.
Newt.
- What'd you say?
- My name's Newt.
Nobody calls me Rebecca
except my brother.
I like that.
I'm Ripley. It's nice to meet you.
And who is this?
- Casey.
- Hello, Casey.
- What about your brother? What's his name?
- Timmy.
Is Timmy around here too,
maybe hiding like you were?
Any sisters?
Mom and dad?
Look at me. Where are they?
They're dead, all right? Can I go now?
I'm sorry.
Don't you think
you'd be safer here with us?
These people are here to protect you.
They're soldiers.
It won't make any difference.
Need anything else?
Hello, Bishop.
Do you need anything else?
- That's a nice pet you got there.
- Magnificent, isn't it?
Stop your grinnin' and drop your linen.
Found 'em.
- They alive?
- Unknown. But it looks like all of 'em.
Over at the processing station.
Sub-level 3, under the main cooling towers.
- Looks like a goddamn town meeting.
- Let's saddle up, Apone.
Aye, sir.
Let's go, people. They ain't payin' us
by the hour. Head 'em out.
Frost, you're drivin'.
Don't worry. It'll be OK.
I want a straight V deployment.
Second team on left flank.
Advance on axial 664.
Tracker online.
Set the V-gain to filter RF ambient.
Hudson, tracker online.
Left and right, little buddy.
40 meters in, bearing 221 ,
there should be a stairwell.
Check. Got it.
You want sub-level 3.
Let's go. Hudson, you got the point.
Hicks, watch our tails.
Nice and easy. Check those corners.
- Watch your spacing.
- You heard him. Don't bunch up. Stay loose.
Your transmission's
showing a lot of break-up.
- Probably interference from the structure.
- Use those lights.
Next one down.
Then proceed on a 21 6.
Roger. That's a 21 6.
I'm not making that out too well.
What is it?
You tell me, man. l only work here.
What is that?
I don't know.
Proceed inside.
Watch your fire
and check your targets.
Remember we're looking for civvies.
Easy.
Tighten it up.
We're getting a little thin.
Nice and easy.
- Looks like some sort of secreted resin.
- But secreted from what?
Nobody touch nothin'.
Busy little creatures, huh?
- Hot as hell in here.
- Yeah, but it's a dry heat.
Knock it off.
What do those pulse rifles fire?
1 0mm explosive-tip caseless.
Standard light-armor-piercing round. Why?
Look where your team is. They're right
under the primary heat exchangers.
So?
If they fire their weapons in there,
won't they rupture the cooling system?
- She's absolutely right.
- So what?
This whole station is basically
a big fusion reactor. Right?
So you're talking about a thermonuclear
explosion and "Adiós, muchachos."
Great. Wonderful.
Shit.
Look... Apone?
We can't have any firing in there. I want
you to collect magazines from everybody.
- Is he fucking crazy?
- What do we use, harsh language?
Flame units only. I want rifles slung.
Just do it, Sergeant. And no grenades.
All right, sweethearts, you heard the man.
Come on, let's have 'em.
Come on, Vasquez. Clear and lock.
Damn.
You too. Give it up, Ski.
Crowe, I want it now. Give it up.
Right on, Vas.
Let's go, Marine.
Frost, you got the duty. Open that bag.
- Thanks a lot, sarge.
- Hicks, cover our ass.
Head out, people.
I like to keep this handy
for close encounters.
I heard that.
- Any movement?
- Nothing.
Holy shit.
Newt, go sit up front.
Go on. Now.
Steady, people.
Let's finish our sweep.
We're still marines, and we got a job to do.
Keep it movin'.
Easy.
Top! Get over here. We got a live one.
- You're gonna be all right.
- Please kill me.
Just stay calm. We'll get you out of here.
It's gonna be all right.
- Oh, man.
- What is it, Dietrich?
Convulsion!
Dietrich, get back!
- Flame-thrower.
- Kill it!
Get back. Flame-thrower. Move!
- Movement.
- What's the position?
- I can't lock in.
- Talk to me.
Multiple signals. They're closing.
Go to infrared, people. Look sharp.
- What's happening? We can't see anything.
- Pull your team out.
I got readings in front and behind.
- Where? I don't see shit.
- He's right. There's nothing back here.
I'm tellin' ya.
There's somethin' moving, and it ain't us.
Tracker's off-scale.
They're all around us. Jesus.
Maybe they don't show up
on infrared at all.
Come on!
- Jesus Christ, what is going on?
- Wierzbowski and Crowe are down.
Dietrich, Crowe, sound off.
Let's rock!
Who's firing?
I ordered a hold fire.
They're coming out
of the goddamn walls!
Apone, I want you to lay down
a suppressing fire with...
Hold your fire, goddammit.
Apone, lay down a suppressing fire with
the incinerators and fall back by squads...
Say again? All after "incinerators".
I said lay down a suppressing fire
with the incinerators and fall back...
Sarge!
Talk to me. Apone?
- Talk to me, Apone!
- He's gone!
- Get them out of there, now!
- Shut up!
- Whoever's left, get the hell out...
- Just shut up!
Where's Apone?
The sarge is gone.
Let's get the fuck outta here!
Let's go, Marines.
- Hudson, look out.
- Get it!
- I told them to fall back.
- Fall back! Now!
- They're cut off.
Do something! Fuck!
- Keep moving, baby.
- Hold on, Newt.
What the hell are you doing?
Turn it round!
That's an order.
- Turn this thing around.
- Get off me, damn it.
You had your chance, Gorman.
- Come on.
- Come on, Vas.
Let's move it.
Come on, let's go.
It's blocked. We've got to go around.
Open the door.
Drake, we are leaving!
Get them, Vas.
Run for it.
Shit.
- Go.
- Drake, come on.
Drake, come on.
- Fire in the hold.
- He's gone.
- No! Drake's out there!
- Put it out.
- Drake's coming.
- He's gone.
He's not!
Forget him. He's gone.
Get on the goddamn door!
Eat this.
Go!
It's all right, we're clear.
You've blown the transaxle.
You're just grinding metal.
Come on, ease down.
You OK?
Get away from me!
- Lieutenant.
- What happened to Gorman?
I don't know. Maybe a concussion.
- But he's alive.
- No, he's dead!
- Wake up, Pendejo! Then l'm gonna kill you!
- Back off. Right now.
Somebody get me a first-aid kit.
Look. The sarge and Dietrich aren't dead.
Their signs were low, but they ain't dead.
- Then we go back and get them.
- Fuck that. I ain't going back in there.
You can't help them.
You can't. Right now they're being
cocooned just like the others.
Dear Lord Jesus, this ain't happenin'.
This can't be happenin', man.
All right.
We've got seven canisters of CN-20.
I say we nerve-gas
the whole fuckin' nest.
We don't know if it's gonna affect 'em.
Let's just bug out and call it even.
Why are we talking about this?
I say we take off
and nuke the entire site from orbit.
It's the only way to be sure.
- Fuckin' A.
- Hold on one second.
This installation has a substantial
dollar value attached to it.
They can bill me.
Look, this is an emotional moment
for all of us. I know that.
But let's not make snap judgments.
This is clearly an important species,
and I don't think we have the right
to arbitrarily exterminate them.
- Wrong.
- Yeah. Watch us.
Maybe you haven't kept up
on current events.
We just got our asses kicked.
I'm not blind to what's going on,
but I cannot authorize
that kind of action. I'm sorry.
I believe Corporal Hicks
has authority here.
Corporal Hicks is...?
This operation is under
military jurisdiction,
and Hicks is next
in chain of command, right?
That's right.
Look, this is
a multi-million-dollar installation.
He can't make that kind of decision.
He's just a grunt.
- No offense.
- None taken.
- Ferro, do you copy?
- Standing by.
- Prep for dustoff. We need immediate evac.
- On our way.
I say we take off, nuke the site from orbit.
It's the only way to be sure.
Let's do it.
Pick it up, Hudson.
We'll set him down here.
Move it, Spunkmeyer. We're rolling.
- Hold on. There's something...
- Just get up here.
I'm in. Ramp closing.
Goddammit.
Where the f...?
Run.
That's great. That's just fuckin' great.
Now what the fuck do we do?
We're in some real pretty shit now!
Are you finished?
Are you all right?
I guess we're not
gonna be leaving now, right?
- I'm sorry.
- You don't have to be. It wasn't your fault.
That's it. Game over, man.
What the fuck are we gonna do now?
Maybe we could build a fire,
sing a couple of songs, huh?
We'd better get back. It'll be dark soon,
and they mostly come at night. Mostly.
That's everything, right?
All right, this is everything
we can salvage out of the APC wreckage.
We got four pulse rifles
with about 50 rounds each.
That ain't so good.
We got 1 5 of these M-40 grenades.
Don't touch that. Dangerous, honey.
- Is that the only flame-thrower?
- It's only half-full but it's functional.
Got another one that's damaged.
But the good news...
We got four of these robot sentries,
with display and scanners intact.
They really kick ass.
They'll come in handy.
How long after we're declared overdue
can we expect a rescue?
1 7 days.
1 7 days? I don't wanna rain on your parade,
but we're not gonna last 1 7 hours.
Those things are gonna come in here
just like before...
This little girl survived longer than that
with no weapons and no training. Right?
- Why don't you put her in charge?
- You'd better deal with it.
Just deal with it, because we need you
and I'm sick of your bullshit.
I want you to get on a terminal
and call up a floor-plan file.
Construction blueprints, anything that
shows the layout. Are you listening?
I need to see air ducts,
electrical access tunnels, sub-basements,
every possible way into this complex.
- We don't have much time.
- OK. I'm on it.
Just relax.
I'll be in medlab.
Check on Gorman, continue my analysis.
Fine. You do that.
This service tunnel must be
how they move back and forth.
That's right. It leads from the processing
station right into the sub-level here.
Come down on that. OK, come over.
Go back...
OK, punch that in right there.
No. It's back here.
There's a pressure door at this end.
Couldn't we put a remote sentry unit
in the tunnel, then seal that door?
Yeah, but we gotta figure
on them getting into the complex.
That's right. So we repair the barricades
at these two intersections,
and weld plate steel over these ducts
here, here and here.
Then they can only come at us
from these two quarters.
Right. Then we put the other sentry units
here and here. Right?
- Right.
- Outstanding.
Now all we need is a deck of cards.
- OK, let's move like we got a purpose.
- Affirmative.
Do your thing, baby.
Let's get the hell outta here.
Hudson here. A and B sentries
are in place and keyed.
Arming now.
- Test it, Hudson.
- Fire in the hole!
OK, let's get the hell outta here.
We're sealing the tunnel. Come on, baby.
For what it's worth.
I want you to put this on.
- What's it for?
- It's a locator.
Then I can find you
anywhere in the complex on this.
It's just a precaution.
- Thanks.
- It doesn't mean we're engaged or anything.
OK, what's next?
Last stop.
Get in.
Scoot down.
That's good.
Now, you have a nap. You're very tired.
I don't want to sleep.
I have scary dreams.
I bet Casey doesn't have scary dreams.
Let's take a look.
Nothing bad in there.
See? Maybe you could
just try to be like her.
She doesn't have bad dreams
because she's just a piece of plastic.
Right. I'm sorry.
There.
My mommy always said
there were no monsters, no real ones.
- But there are.
- Yes, there are, aren't there?
Why do they tell little kids that?
Most of the time it's true.
Did one of those things grow inside her?
I don't know. That's the truth.
Isn't that how babies come?
People babies?
- They grow inside you.
- That's very different.
- Did you ever have a baby?
- Yes, I did. I had a little girl.
Where is she?
- She's gone.
- You mean dead.
Here.
Take this.
For luck.
How's that?
- Don't go. Please.
- I'm gonna be right in the next room.
And you see that camera up there?
I can see you through that camera
all the time to see if you're safe.
I'm not gonna leave you.
I mean that. That's a promise.
You promise?
- I cross my heart.
- And hope to die.
And hope to die.
Now go to sleep.
And don't dream.
Sneak.
The acid oxidises after the creature's death,
completely neutralizing.
That's very interesting,
but it doesn't get us anywhere.
I'm trying to figure out what we're
dealing with. Let's go through it again.
They grab the colonists and immobilise them
to be hosts for more of these.
Which means there would have
to be a lot of these parasites.
- One for each colonist. Over 1 00 at least.
- That follows.
But each of these things
comes from an egg, right?
So who's laying these eggs?
I'm not sure. It must be something
we haven't seen yet.
- Maybe it's like an ant hive.
- Bees. Bees have hives.
You know what I mean.
One female runs the whole show.
- The queen.
- Yeah, the mama.
- She's badass, man. I mean big.
- These things ain't ants.
I know that.
I want these specimens destroyed
when you're done. Is that clear?
Mr. Burke wants them kept alive
for return to the company labs.
He was very specific about it.
Those two specimens are worth millions
to the bio-weapons division.
If you're smart,
we can both come out of this heroes,
and we will be set up for life.
You're crazy, do you know that?
You really think you can get a dangerous
organism past ICC quarantine?
How can they impound it
if they don't know about it?
But they will know about it. From me.
Just like they'll know
you caused the deaths of 1 57 colonists.
- Wait a second...
- You sent them to that ship.
I just checked the colony log. Directive
dated 6/1 2/79, signed Burke, Carter J.
You sent them out there
and didn't even warn them.
Why didn't you warn them?
What if that ship didn't even exist?
I didn't know.
If I made a major security situation out of it,
administration steps in,
and there's no exclusive rights
for anybody.
So I made a decision, and it was wrong.
It was a bad call.
Bad call? These people are dead!
Don't you have any idea what you've done?
I'm gonna make sure
they nail you to the wall.
You're not gonna sleaze your way
out of this one. Right to the wall.
I expected more from you.
I thought you'd be smarter than this.
I'm happy to disappoint you.
- What's goin' on?
- They're coming. In the tunnel.
Here we go. A and B gun
tracking and firing. Multiple targets.
Look at those ammo counters go.
B gun's down 50%0.
Man, it's a shooting gallery down there.
60 rounds left on B.
40... 20... 1 0.
B gun's dry. 20 on A.
1 0... 5...
- That's it.
- Jesus. They're wall-to-wall in there.
They're at the pressure door.
- Listen to that.
- Bishop here.
- I have some bad news.
- That's a switch.
It's very pretty,
but what are we looking for?
That's it. Emergency venting.
That's beautiful, man. That beats it all.
- How long till it blows?
- Four hours.
With a blast radius of 30 kilometers,
equal to about 40 megatons.
- We got problems.
- I don't fuckin' believe this.
- Vasquez, close the shutters.
- Why can't we shut it down from here?
I'm sorry. The crash caused too much
damage, and overload was inevitable.
Oh, man. And I was gettin' short.
Four more weeks and out.
- Now I'm gonna buy it on this rock.
- Give us a break.
Four more weeks. Oh, man.
We've got to get
the other dropship from the Sulaco.
There must be some way
to bring it down on remote.
How? The transmitter
was on the APC. It's wasted.
I don't care how,
but we'd better think of something.
We're fucked! We're doomed!
Shut up!
What about the colony transmitters?
- The uplink tower at the other end.
- No, I checked.
The hard wiring between here and there
was damaged. We can't align the dish.
Somebody has to go out there.
Take a portable terminal
and patch in manually.
Sure! With those things runnin' around?
You can count me out.
- I guess we can count you out of everything.
- I'll go.
- Why don't you go?
- What?
- I'll go.
I'm the only one qualified
to remote-pilot the ship anyway.
Right, Bishop should go. Good idea.
Believe me, I'd prefer not to.
I may be synthetic, but I'm not stupid.
How long?
This conduit runs almost
to the uplink assembly. 1 80 meters.
Say 40 minutes to crawl down there,
an hour to patch in
and align the antenna,
30 minutes to prep the ship,
and about 50 minutes flight time.
It's gonna be close.
- Good luck.
- See you soon.
Watch your fingers.
This is unbelievable.
20 meters and closing.
- 1 5.
- How many?
Can't tell. Lots.
D gun's down 50%.
C gun's right behind it.
It ain't stoppin' em.
1 50 rounds on D.
- Come on, baby.
- 1 00 rounds.
Come on!
D gun's down to 20.
1 0.
Damn it.
Wait. They're retreating.
The guns stopped them.
You're right.
- Next time they walk right up and knock.
- But they don't know that.
They're probably looking for other ways
to get in. That'll take 'em a while.
- Maybe we got 'em demoralised.
- Shut up.
I want you two walking perimeter.
Move.
Listen.
We're all in strung-out shape.
But stay frosty and alert.
We can't afford to let
one of those bastards in here.
All right.
How long's it been since you got any sleep?
24 hours?
I'm not gonna end up like those others.
You'll take care of it, won't you?
If it comes to that, I'll do us both.
Let's just make sure
it doesn't come to that. All right?
I wanna introduce you
to a personal friend of mine.
This is an M41-A pulse rifle, 1 0mm,
with an over-and-under
30mm pump-action grenade launcher.
Feel the weight.
What do I do?
Pull it in tight here.
Lean into it. Now, it will kick.
Right. When the counter reads zero here...
- I press this up?
- That's right.
And get another one in quick.
Slap it in hard.
Now you're ready to rock'n'roll.
- What's this?
- The grenade launcher.
- I don't think you wanna mess with that.
- You started this. Show me everything.
I can handle myself.
I noticed.
- How do you feel?
- All right, I guess.
One hell of a hangover.
- Look, I just want...
- Forget it. Excuse me.
It's OK.
- Wake up.
- Wha...?
Be quiet. We're in trouble.
Move!
Help!
Say again, Bishop. You've got it into
auto refuel mode, and it's sequencing right?
- That's right.
- Good. Stay on it.
Get back to me when
you've activated the launch cycle.
- He's at the uplink tower.
- Terrific.
Help us!
Break the glass.
Break it.
I'll try.
- I'm scared.
- Me too.
Stay here.
It's the medlab.
- Meet me in the medlab. We got a fire.
- We're on our way.
They're coming.
Shoot it out!
Jesus!
Christ, kid, look out!
Over there. Ready?
All clear. Nailed the other one.
It's history, man.
Jesus.
It was Burke.
I say we grease this rat-fuck
son of a bitch.
It just doesn't make any goddamn sense.
He figured he could get
an alien back through quarantine
if one of us was impregnated...
whatever you call it,
and then frozen for the trip home.
Nobody would know
about the embryos we were carrying.
Me and Newt.
We'd all know.
He'd have to sabotage certain freezers
on the way home. Namely yours.
Then he could jettison the bodies
and make up any story he liked.
Fuck. He's dead.
You're dog meat, pal.
This is so nuts.
Listen to what you're saying.
It's paranoid delusion. It's really sad.
- It's pathetic.
- I don't know which species is worse.
You don't see them fucking each other over
for a goddamn percentage.
- All right, we waste him. No offense.
- No. He's gotta go back.
- They cut the power.
- How could they cut it? They're animals.
You two, check the corridors. Move!
Gorman, watch Burke. Newt, stay close.
- I'll go this side.
- You do that.
- Anything?
- Somethin'.
- It's inside the complex.
- You're just reading me.
It ain't you.
They're inside the perimeter.
They're in here.
Stay cool. Vasquez?
Hudson may be right.
- Get back, both of you.
- The signal's weird.
Must be interference or somethin'.
There's movement all over the place.
Get back to Operations.
It's game time.
Seal the door.
- Hurry.
- Come on.
Come on, get back. Work fast.
Cover your eyes. Don't look at the light.
Movement. Signal's clean.
Range 20 meters.
- They've found a way in that we missed.
- We didn't miss anything.
18.
- 17 meters.
- Something under the floor, not in the plans.
15 meters.
- Definitely inside the barricades.
- Let's go.
- 13 meters.
- That's right outside. Get back.
- This is a big fucking signal.
- How you doing, Vasquez?
Almost there.
That's it.
12 meters.
11 ...
- 10...
- Then they're right on us.
- Nine meters.
- Short controlled bursts.
Eight meters.
Seven.
- Six.
- Can't be. That's inside the room.
- It's readin' right. Look.
- Well, you're not reading it right.
Five meters, man. Four...
What the hell?
- Oh, my God...
- Give me the light.
Over there! Get 'em!
Come on.
Do something, Gorman.
Look out, there's more of 'em.
Get to Medical! Do it!
- Now!
- Look out, Hudson.
Now.
Open this door. Open it!
Fall back.
Die, motherfucker!
Motherfucker! Come and get it, baby!
I've got all day!
Come on, you bastards!
You too. You want some of this?
Fuck you!
Come on, Hicks, go.
It's locked.
Got it. Let's go.
Go, go!
Move, Gorman.
Seal it.
Goddamn you, open this door.
- Get back.
- Hurry up.
- Gorman, get out of the way.
- This way.
What?
- Wait. Get behind me.
- Whatever you're gonna do, do it fast.
Come on, let's go.
Move.
- Which way to the landing field?
- This way.
Go right.
This way.
- Which way?
- Straight ahead and left.
Bishop, do you read me? Come in.
The ship is on its way.
ETA 1 6 minutes.
Good. Stand by there. We're on our way.
- Which way now?
- That way. No, wait. This way.
You sure?
Move!
It's just up here.
- We're almost there.
- Wait.
Go.
Up there. There's a shortcut
across the roof.
You always were an asshole, Gorman.
Hicks, get her. Hurry.
- Hold on.
- I'm slipping.
Don't let go.
- Hold on.
- Help!
Got ya.
I got ya.
We can find her with this.
Stay where you are. We're coming.
This way.
She's close.
Where are you? Can you hear me?
- I'm here.
- Where?
Are you OK?
- We need to cut it.
- Climb down, honey.
We've gotta cut through.
Don't move. Stay very still.
We're almost there. Hang in there.
- I know.
- Hurry. I mean it.
Newt, just stay still.
Almost there.
Let's go.
They don't kill you, they...
- She's alive!
- All right!
I believe you. She's alive.
We've gotta go. Now!
Get it off.
Here.
Go.
You can make it.
- Bishop, how much time?
- Plenty. 26 minutes.
- We're not leaving.
- We're not?
I don't wanna hear it.
She's alive. There's still time.
In 1 9 minutes,
this area's gonna be a vapor cloud.
- Don't let him leave.
- We ain't going anywhere.
- See you, Hicks.
- Dwayne.
It's Dwayne.
Ellen.
Don't be gone long, Ellen.
Attention. Emergency.
All personnel must evacuate immediately.
You have 1 5 minutes
to reach minimum safe distance.
Attention. Emergency.
All personnel must evacuate immediately.
You have 14 minutes
to reach minimum safe distance.
Grab on to me. Hold on.
Let's go.
Behind us.
You have four minutes
to reach minimum safe distance.
Come on, goddammit!
Hold on to me.
You have two minutes
to reach minimum safe distance.
Bishop, goddamn you!
Close your eyes, baby.
Look!
Come on.
Punch it.
We're OK.
We made it.
I knew you'd come.
He'll be all right. He's just out.
I had to give him another shot for the pain.
We need a stretcher
to carry him up to Medical.
Sorry if I scared you.
That platform was becoming too unstable.
I had to hope
things didn't get too rough to take you off.
- You did OK.
- I did?
Go. Move.
No, here!
Run.
Here.
Get away from her, you bitch!
Come on!
- Mommy.
- Oh, God...
Not bad for a human.
Are we gonna sleep all the way home?
- All the way home.
- Can I dream?
Yes, honey. I think we both can.
- Sleep tight.
- Affirmative.
[ENGLISH - US]
Come here.
It's all right.
It's over.
I don't understand this.
We have been here
for three and a half hours.
How many different ways
do you want me to tell the same story?
That could have been better.
Look, I think...
Van Leuwen?
Why don't you just check out LV-426?
I don't have to.
There have been people there over 20 years,
and they never mentioned
hostile organisms.
- What people?
- Terraformers.
Planet engineers. They set up big atmosphere
processors to make the air breathable.
Takes decades. It's what we call
a "shake'n'bake" colony.
How many colonists are there?
60, maybe 70 families. Do you mind?
Families.
Jesus.
- Lieutenant, am I right?
- We're trained to deal with these situations.
Then you don't need me.
We don't know
what's going on out there.
It may just be a downed transmitter, okay?
But if it's not,
I would like you there as an adviser,
and that's all.
I don't have time for this.
I've gotta get to work.
I heard you're working
in the cargo docks.
That's right.
- Running forklifts?
- So?
Nothing. It's great
that you're keeping busy.
And I know it's the only thing you
could get. There's nothing wrong with it.
And you, you little shithead,
you're staying here.
They ain't payin' us enough for this, man.
Not enough to have to
wake up to your face, Drake.
What?
That's better. Pan it around a bit.
Good.
All right, gear up.
Two minutes, people.
Somebody wake up Hicks.
- Coming around for a 709.
- Terminal guidance locked in.
Where's the damn beacon?
Oh, I see it.
- That's the atmosphere processor?
- That's it.
Remarkable piece of machinery.
Completely automated.
We manufacture those, by the way.
Ferro, take us in low
over the main colony complex.
Storm shutters are sealed.
There's no visible activity.
Hold at 40.
Hudson, try and get their CPU online.
Affirmative.
Hicks, meet me at the south lock.
We're coming in.
- He's comin' in. I feel safer already.
- Pendejo jerk-off.
That's everything, right?
All right, this is everything
we can salvage out of the APC wreckage.
We got four pulse rifles
with about 50 rounds each.
That ain't so good.
We got 1 5 of these M-40 grenades.
Don't touch that. Dangerous, honey.
- Is that the only flame-thrower?
- It's only half-full but it's functional.
Got another one that's damaged.
How long after we're declared overdue
can we expect a rescue?
1 7 days.
1 7 days? I don't wanna rain on your parade,
but we're not gonna last 1 7 hours.
Those things are gonna come in here
just like before...
This little girl survived longer than that
with no weapons and no training. Right?
- Why don't you put her in charge?
- You'd better deal with it.
Just deal with it, because we need you
and I'm sick of your bullshit.
I want you to get on a terminal
and call up a floor-plan file.
Construction blueprints, anything that
shows the layout. Are you listening?
I need to see air ducts,
electrical access tunnels, sub-basements,
every possible way into this complex.
- We don't have much time.
- OK. I'm on it.
Just relax.
I'll be in medlab.
Check on Gorman, continue my analysis.
Fine. You do that.
This service tunnel must be
how they move back and forth.
That's right. It leads from the processing
station right into the sub-level here.
Come down on that. OK, come over.
Go back...
OK, punch that in right there.
No. It's back here.
There's a pressure door at this end.
We could weld it shut.
That should hold them for a while.
But we gotta figure
on them getting into the complex.
That's right. So we repair the barricades
at these two intersections,
and weld plate steel over these ducts
here, here and here.
That should seal off Medlab and Operations.
Outstanding.
Now all we need is a deck of cards.
- OK, let's move like we got a purpose.
- Affirmative.
We're sealing the tunnel. Come on, baby.
For what it's worth.
I want you to put this on.
- What's it for?
- It's a locator.
Then I can find you
anywhere in the complex on this.
It's just a precaution.
- Thanks.
- It doesn't mean we're engaged or anything.
OK, what's next?
Last stop.
Get in.
Scoot down.
That's good.
Now, you have a nap. You're very tired.
I don't want to sleep.
I have scary dreams.
I bet Casey doesn't have scary dreams.
Let's take a look.
Nothing bad in there.
See? Maybe you could
just try to be like her.
She doesn't have bad dreams
because she's just a piece of plastic.
Right. I'm sorry.
There.
My mommy always said
there were no monsters, no real ones.
- But there are.
- Yes, there are, aren't there?
Why do they tell little kids that?
Most of the time it's true.
Here.
The acid oxidizes after the creature's death,
completely neutralizing.
That's very interesting,
but it doesn't get us anywhere.
I'm trying to figure out what we're
dealing with. Let's go through it again.
They grab the colonists and immobilize them
to be hosts for more of these.
Which means there would have
to be a lot of these parasites.
- One for each colonist. Over 1 00 at least.
- That follows.
But each of these things
comes from an egg, right?
So who's laying these eggs?
I'm not sure. It must be something
we haven't seen yet.
I want these specimens destroyed
when you're done. Is that clear?
Mr. Burke wants them kept alive
for return to the company labs.
He was very specific about it.
I expected more from you.
I thought you'd be smarter than this.
I'm happy to disappoint you.
I want you two walking perimeter.
Listen.
We're all in strung-out shape.
But stay frosty and alert.
We can't afford to let
one of those bastards in here.
All right.
I don't wanna hear it.
She's alive. There's still time.
In 1 9 minutes,
this area's gonna be a vapor cloud.
- Don't let him leave.
- We ain't going anywhere.
Attention. Emergency.
All personnel must evacuate immediately.
You have 1 5 minutes
to reach minimum safe distance.
- Sleep tight.
- Affirmative.
[ENGLISH - US]