Someone needs to stop Clearway Law.
Public shouldn't leave reviews for lawyers.
Son of a bitch.
When I first saw you, I wasn't scared.
I was just wondering
why you wore those boots.
Now I know.
Shit.
We've both played this game, Rath.
What kind of shoes
will you be wearing...
when your day comes?
Whatever the contract is, I'll double it.
Just say you couldn't find me.
Listen to me.
I'm talking like a mark.
Oh, God. Don't pull yet. Not yet.
Christ. I've killed a few innocents
in my time.
You're so high and mighty.
You and your principles.
Someone had to do the jobs
you wouldn't do.
I can't die like this.
I'm not a mark.
Not like a mark.
It's chambered.
Thanks, Rath.
Goodbye, old friend.
I don't care what you believe. I've had it.
I want out. I quit.
Go away, you son of a bitch.
You should be.
And army of press, police
and the private security.
Today.
However, the attention
is not for the man...
being laid to rest, but rather,
for one of the mourners.
We're just witnessing the arrival
of recluse billionaire Alan Branch...
here attending the funeral of his brother,
who died in an automobile accident.
Alan Branch was last seen testifying
before a Senate hearing 10 years ago.
He was questioned for his alleged financing
of right-wing death squads...
throughout South and Central America.
- Branch was born in Queens.
- Get over there.
As you can see
from the use of the wheelchair...
he is the victim of a hitman's bullet.
It was 10 years ago that Alan Branch was
brought before Senate hearings...
where he was questioned about
his involvement...
in money laundering, drug-trafficking.
And right-wing death squad financing.
Those hearings went on
for several weeks...
Let us pray.
Lord Jesus Christ...
by the three days you lay in the tomb...
they, like you, will rise again.
Bless this grave, O Lord,
and give Samuel peaceful rest...
Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
He's been shot.
Come on, you little bastard, be brave.
Run for it.
Put it down. Put it down.
- Fuck.
- Put it down.
Throw the gun away.
On the ground. Face down.
- All right.
- Throw the gun away.
- All right, all right.
- Throw it away. Get down.
- Get down, don't move.
- Don't move.
- Don't even...
Hands behind your back.
What the hell is he doing?
- Hold on. Take it easy.
- Shut up.
- Just give me your hands.
- Check him for more weapons.
- Where is it?
- Easy.
- My pocket.
- Don't worry.
- I'm not worried.
- There it is.
- Here.
- Silencer, right?
- Get up.
- Pistol?
- Okay.
- What do we have here?
- The area's secure. Come on. Let's go.
Nice to meet you.
Hey, wait a minute, buddy.
Ambulance, let's go.
Come on. Come on. In there. In there.
Hold it. Number one, move it out.
Number two, come on.
Go.
All right, get out of there. Go.
Three-charlie-four. All
units in the vicinity.
A robbery at the liquor store.
Madison and 28th.
One-bravo-five,
what is the disposition of your suspect?
This is one-bravo-five.
We're proceeding to the 7th precinct.
- We have the suspect in custody, over.
- One-bravo-five, roger.
I show you en route
to the precinct with one suspect.
- Look.
- Watch where you're pointing that.
No. Look at this.
Look out.
No.
Oh, my God.
Hey.
Don't fucking try it.
This is one-bravo-three,
officers down. Victoria Ave. 2700 block.
Repeat, officers down.
One-bravo-three, what's your status?
One-bravo-three, please respond.
All units, officers down,
2700 Victoria Avenue.
Repeat, officers down.
All units, suspect
in the four-officer-down call is at large.
Male Hispanic, medium build,
about thirty years. Armed and dangerous.
Monitor bus stations, car rental agents
and the airport.
- Goddamn it.
- You okay?
- Son of a bitch, I just got this car.
- Are you okay? Are you okay?
I don't need a problem.
What's it gonna take?
I don't have insurance.
Here, take the whole thing. I'm sorry.
I'm sorry about this.
Who's near Denny Way and 5th?
We have a couple going to Crown Hill.
Who's near Christina's Restaurant?
We have a man going to the airport.
501, I'm there.
Cab 401, pick up three sailors
at Pier 91.
Come on. Be the right one.
- Taxi. Taxi.
- Sorry, radio call. I'm booked.
We saw that first. Hey.
- Airport.
- You got it.
You know, you got a cut on your head here.
You see that?
- Yeah, I had an accident at work.
- Yeah, what kind of work do you do?
I am, how do you say...
dead tired.
So save the chitchat
for someone else, please.
Chitchat. I haven't heard that word
for a long time. Chitchat.
- What are you doing?
- What?
- There was the turnoff.
- I'm sorry, okay?
- You just blew your tip.
- Think I'm trying to run you up?
- Do your job.
- Don't tell me my job.
- What the fuck?
- I never beat anyone for a fare.
Do your job.
All right.
Get out.
What?
You think I'm running you up, pal?
Then get out.
- You can't just...
- The hell I can't.
Get out. Go on, find another cab.
I don't believe this.
Robert...
Rath.
You can't shoot me through the glass.
Bulletproof. Eh?
So I get out...
Pow, you got me.
No.
So...
now what?
Who are you, kid?
Robert Rath...
wants to know me.
I don't believe this.
Well, eh, Bain.
Miguel Bain.
Let me see. You rolled some cabbie...
then waited for the right call.
That's genius, man.
Then you got the balls to bullshit with me.
No way I could have done that. No way.
You stole my contract.
How'd you know about it?
A silenced...
Ruger .22.
Classic.
You know, I switched...
when I heard that's what you used.
Excuse this.
It was a long shot.
But a good one. Wasn't it?
Who's your contractor, Miguelito?
Why don't you drive?
We can get acquainted.
Chitchat.
Let's sit.
Okay?
Drive.
Number 13 looks tired.
Maybe she needs some rest.
Drive.
Drive, drive, drive.
Protect the innocent. That's weak.
You could have had me at the cemetery
but you couldn't shoot the cops.
You are antiquado.
I had to try. Who knows?
Maybe it wasn't made in America.
They look pissed, huh?
They get that way
when you kill 4 of them.
How do you like the cemetery?
Rome, 14 B.C.
They killed a general, Flavius,
at his brother's funeral.
But you know, I couldn't wait for Branch's
brother to die, so I killed him too.
Proud of me, Bobby?
Well...
it was very nice meeting you.
Someday, I'll tell my little niños
about this wonderful encounter.
Shit.
- Oh, fuck.
- Who's your contractor, kid?
You blew it. I am still alive.
Not for long.
Hey. What are you doing?
What the hell are you doing?
Watch it, watch it.
You'll get us killed.
Let's go get them.
Two-robert-two is in pursuit
of Yellow Cab 501.
Robert-two in pursuit. Request backup.
Two-robert-three, responding.
All units to two-robert-two,
Yellow Cab number 501
was reported stolen in the vicinity
of the officers-down call.
- Ten-four, Regional Air responding.
- Regional Air has joined the pursuit.
Suspects are to be considered
armed and dangerous.
Robert-two, received.
Turn it here, turn it here. I know this
neighborhood. Come on. Come on, hit it.
Don't give any more advice, okay?
Two-robert-two, this is Regional Air.
We're heading over
to the Michigan Viaduct.
Two-robert-two to all units, maintain
positions. We're gonna box him in.
Don't you lose this asshole.
This is Regional Air. We copy.
I studied everything you ever did.
Goddamn it, you were good.
You and the Russian, Nicolai Talinkov.
Tachlinkov.
Tachlinkov. Yes.
You know, they say
he's living on some Greek island.
But I say, you were the best.
I say, Nicolai's dead as a clavo,
a doornail. Am I right, Bob?
I heard you guys played chess coded
in The New York Times obituaries.
Ten fucking miles of microfilm.
But I found it. I found it.
The last game ends before anyone wins.
He thought you were his friend.
And now I know...
that's how you took him.
You killed him to be number one.
Bishop takes rook pawn.
All units, Regional Air has a visual.
Repeat. Regional Air has a visual.
Suspect headed east on Sycamore street.
- Regional Air, do you have a visual?
- We got him, got him.
We don't got him.
What are you talking about,
bishop takes rook pawn?
Fifteen years
and I still remember this game.
It's like yesterday.
I hate to admit it,
but you're the world's best.
White rook to king one.
Yeah, I remember that one.
- Enter next move.
- Let's see what this kid knows.
Enter next move.
Bishop takes...
rook pawn.
Red bishop takes rook pawn.
Game in check. Game in check.
Game in check.
A mark.
I'm a goddamn mark.
Miguel Bain.
Don't play with me now.
You're setting me up.
Is this how it went, Nicolai?
Is this how it went?
That's it. I'm gone.
Where are you going?
Two million and I'm out of here.
I'm gone.
Seattle.
Surveillance expert.
Buyers. Right.
The mark. Who's the mark?
Goddamn it.
How does it feel?
To be on your own
Here you go, Pearl.
Here you go.
No, thanks. I won't have any.
I'm just gonna have some coffee,
you know? Okay?
Come on
You know what? I forgot to tell you.
We got our pictures back.
Let's see what we have here.
This one is good. I like this one of you.
It's your good side. See.
Take a look at that.
That nice? That's not so bad, huh?
And you say
you don't look good in pictures.
So ridiculous. I do not have time
to talk about this right now.
Never have time to talk about anything.
That is not true.
I have time, but now is not a good time.
I wanted to talk about this
last night and you didn't.
I had to get my sleep last night.
Hi, Mrs. Slattery. What you making?
Every time we talk about this,
we always end up...
- Oh, guys.
- What did you bring it up for?
Guys.
What are you doing?
Don't walk away from me...
because you had to bring this up,
we're going to have it out.
You're not helping matters here.
You're not...
- Stop it.
- What?
If you're so concerned about
what your mother thinks...
That is so...
Jeez.
You wanna slam doors? Huh?
Fine, I can slam doors.
Oh, Jennifer.
- Room 115.
- I have the disc.
The buyers arrive at noon. Flight 1055.
I'll attempt contact at 12:30
and every 15 minutes after that.
Do you have the hard copy images?
Affirmative. What do I call the principal?
- Call him Remy. How will they know?
- They'll know.
Try and trace that one, baby.
Poor baby.
Hi. Welcome to the Marriott.
How are you today?
- Here's 20 dollars. Keep the car handy.
- Great.
- Anything else I can do for you today?
- No thanks, pal.
Get that for you.
Let me get your ticket for you.
- Can I help you with your bags?
- Nope, I got it.
You need your ticket, ma'am.
Here's your ticket. Thank you.
I hated that restaurant.
What a terrible place.
I didn't like anything about it.
All those foreigners. What an awful...
What an awful, awful restaurant.
Please don't make
another reservation there.
You can certainly find a better spot.
Fourth floor.
You're welcome, baby. My pleasure.
Arriving passenger Remy,
please go to a white courtesy phone.
Passenger Remy,
Excuse me.
Hello, this is Remy.
Ready to go shopping
on the Horne Information Network?
Price is $40,000.
- Where are you?
- Are you ready? Yes or no.
- Yes.
- The Marriott Hotel, my friend.
There are pay phones
across from the elevators.
You've got 20 minutes,
give or take 10 seconds.
Cut your hair.
Taxi.
- Hello.
- Ah, good, you're early.
Pick up the Yellow Pages.
- Right.
- Lonely?
In town on business?
Why don't you check the escorts?
- Got it.
- It's Room 718. I smell a rat...
The disc and I are gone.
- We simpatico?
- Simpatico, yes.
Hold the elevator, please.
Damn.
- Oh. Excuse me, sir.
- Sorry.
It's okay. Maintenance.
Operator.
I'd like to report a problem
with the 12th floor. Electricity's out.
Fourth floor.
- Excuse me.
- Pardon me.
The 12th floor? What room?
I'll go down
and check the circuit breakers.
Seventh floor.
Excuse me. Sorry.
All right.
I'd like to make a reservation.
Buyers, seller,
let's see who booked multiple rooms.
Come out, wherever you are.
718.
Hey, fellas, slow down.
Relax.
First, I'll need a $10,000 deposit.
That's wasn't the arrangement.
Then we have nothing to discuss.
Wait, wait, wait. Hang on. Okay.
Here's today's menu.
Give me a second, I gotta put in a disc.
All right, it's in.
Where do you want the ten thousand?
There's a screwdriver on the table.
And then you'll find a conveyance.
Chicago Bulls. Big team. Twenty rooms.
No, no, no.
Here, Katz. Two rooms, 718, 542.
Paid in cash.
Let's check out the room service.
- Hi.
Twin 9 millimeters.
Room 718, nothing. Room 542...
Coffee, coffee, coffee.
Tuna fish.
Yeah.
Here it comes. Here it comes.
Look out, Pearl.
Yes.
Pennies from heaven.
Baby. Here, you keep this warm
for me. Okay.
I'm going to format your disc,
orient it to receive the data.
You getting this, Hans Brinker?
Interpol.
Next.
Telephone?
It come from here.
- Beeper?
- This is not my beeper.
No, no, no.
Interpol.
What's going on down there?
Hello? Can you hear me?
Hey. Hans Brinker, Mr. Dutchman, man,
talk to me. I'm not kidding.
- Hello?
- Please complete the transmission.
Who is this?
Who the hell is this?
Please complete the transmission.
Shit.
No. No, no. No, wait.
Fuck.
Honey...
I'm going to tear your heart out.
Holy Mary.
Case. Let's get you your case.
Don't do this to me. We gotta go.
Come on, honey. We gotta go. Shit.
Okay, Pearl, come on. Come on, please.
Please don't do this.
Please. Damn it. Okay.
Pearl. Come on. Come on.
Don't.
Don't?
Don't what?
Rath.
Is that you?
Yeah.
The disc.
It's you.
- It's you.
- Disc.
You tried the move.
Bishop takes rook pawn.
It's a powerful move.
Would have been Nicolai's move.
Don't you think?
You got a move for me, Rath? Huh?
You know, it's like chess.
Is she alive?
Did you kill her?
Did you kill my mark?
Are you there, sweetie?
Five-forty-two.
Is she dead yet, Bobby?
I took care of business on my end.
How about you?
No.
A woman.
It's not the same as killing a man.
You have to pull the
trigger a different way.
Is she beautiful? Bobby?
Pull the trigger. Kill her.
Come on. Do it. Do it. Do it.
Come on, pull the trigger.
Do it.
Pull the trigger. Kill her.
Be professional.
Kill her.
It's my beeper.
Hey!
Come on.
- Where's your car?
- I don't remember where it's parked.
I got your car right here. It's right here.
Thanks.
That's all right. I got it.
- Who the hell are you?
- I'm a government employee.
That's bullshit.
- Drive and watch your speed.
- Where are we going?
You'll know when we get there.
Watch your speed.
- Slow down.
- I can't, I'm too nervous.
Slow down.
This other guy, does he work
for the government too?
It's between you and him, right?
Why don't you just leave me out of it?
We can't.
You're the mark.
Hey, take it easy, buddy.
Oh. Jeez. Excuse me.
- Hey. Hey. My cat. My cat.
- What the hell is wrong with you?
No, no, no.
Damn.
Oh, yes.
- Thank you, Heather.
- Thanks.
- Hello.
- Hi.
Pearl, come out, don't be afraid.
What are you here? How are you, sweetie?
- Where's her mama?
- I was gonna ask you the same thing.
Thank you, pussycat.
Cold.
Hot.
So that's where you live.
Jen?
- I really love you.
- I love you too.
Nobody loves me
It's true
Not like you do
Baby.
Oh, Pearl.
- Where is he?
- You sick little bitch.
Downstairs.
Do you wanna live?
Oh, these sour times
Nobody loves me
It's true
Not like you do
After time the bitter taste
Of innocence, descent or race
Give me the keys to your apartment.
Meet me at the pet shop.
After time the bitter taste
Of innocence, descent or race
Scattered seed, buried lives
Mysteries of...
Circumstance will decide
It's true
Blank. Shit.
Blank.
- Hi.
- Jennifer.
Jennifer, wait. Goddamn it.
Hey, pal. Come on. Move it.
Nobody loves me
It's true
Not like you do
Nobody loves me
Bob?
I'm sorry.
Jasmine.
Fuck.
Your gun is slow.
- I'm not the one shooting at mirrors, son.
- Just who the hell do you think...?
Surprise. The disc.
The disc.
Hey, wait, wait, wait.
- I told you to wait. Shut up.
- Just...
- Disc.
- Get out.
I beat you to the buyers.
Now, I beat you to the mark.
I'm sorry...
but I think I picked the wrong guy
to be my hero. Yep.
Macho, macho, ooh-hoo.
You know...
today's my birthday.
Today I become number one.
And I got a present...
Fuck.
Fuck. Fuck. Fuck.
Happy birthday, asshole.
Shit!
Goddamn it, I'm old.
No. The girl from downstairs,
I saw her coming back to the building.
She's not in her apartment.
She could be here somewhere
in the building. I gotta find her before...
She's dead.
- Come here, Pearl. Come here.
- Hey.
- Get back here. Come here, come here.
- Hello, Pearl.
- Pearl, get back here. Come here, girl.
- She likes me.
She likes dead fish too.
What do you call yourself?
Robert Rath.
Right.
You can call me Electra.
Are you one of them?
Was.
Retired.
Pardon me if I choose not to believe you.
Electra, I'm telling you,
if I wanted to kill you...
I would have done it.
- Look what mommy did.
- What the matter, it's not loaded?
Oh, yeah, it's loaded. It's silenced.
All you have to do is shoot.
I could.
I'd be 500 miles away
before anybody found you.
Quit it, she doesn't like it.
Pearl, I say she's afraid
she might hit you. Here.
You sorry I have the gun?
You think it was a mistake?
You think I'm scared?
- You don't know shit about me.
- You're wrong.
Shut up.
Today was supposed to be
a really good day.
Payday. Forty grand.
I was gonna buy Pearl a boyfriend.
Now two people are dead.
I'm in way over my head, mister.
I just want out.
You got the gun.
The key's on the dresser.
Go.
Look, I don't have a social security
number, a driver's license.
I can barely remember my real name.
I'm a ghost. I'm nobody.
I'll just disappear.
I found you. So did he. You can't hide.
I just want my life back.
That's all I want.
I'm sorry.
I'll take that.
I need to be alone.
I haven't spent this much time
with somebody in years.
Neither have I.
Well, the disc...
You'll get it.
Fuck you.
I don't care what you are.
Then who the hell's Miguel Bain?
Who the hell is Miguel Bain?
Christ.
From Japanese store shelves.
Welland's apples have only been allowed
in Japan since December.
- Hello, Pearl.
- A random test revealed trace amounts...
What'd they say about the shooting
at the Marriott?
Nothing.
Well, no, I don't need details,
just in general.
- Nothing.
- That's impossible.
Not really. Not if...
Not if what?
The CIA or Interpol...
What's on this?
Um... It's encrypted.
Breaking the code on my laptop
could take 200 or 300 years.
- I thought you said you a genius?
- I am.
I was the best. If it was stored
electronically, it was mine.
Was?
Yeah, I'm retiring too.
I wish I had an insight...
but it was all anonymous,
an intercepted satellite transmission.
Probably just industrial secrets.
There's just one bed.
I guess you picked up on that.
- It's all yours.
- You want the couch?
No, thanks.
What's that, like, a trick of the trade?
So you don't get too comfortable?
Why don't you just tie a string
from your toe to the doorknob.
It opens in.
- If it opens in, you wouldn't feel it.
- No. Yeah, I got it. I understand.
Pearl.
Thanks.
For what?
I don't know.
Saving my life, I guess.
How'd you like to make a million dollars?
What do I have to do?
Nothing cheap, I hope.
- Well, tell me, what is it?
- I'll tell you tomorrow.
- Great, now I can't sleep.
- Be patient.
What? Tell me.
Thanks for the chocolate.
Good night.
Forget something?
You be careful, partner.
Get to see you every day
I live my life like I've been around
To buy my...
I'm right here, my friend.
'Cause I want to experience
A hundred million more
Hey.
Damn.
What's going on back there?
Fine, I'll move.
There's no one who can have my reality
- I hate that music.
- Come on, let's go.
Got it? Is it all there?
- What're you doing?
- Shit. Drive.
- What?
- Drive, fast.
I mean, fast.
Get off this street. Turn.
Stop.
Hit it. Go.
No money, no disk.
Hey. What's so funny?
Well, I wasn't sure you'd be coming back
so I switched the disks.
And all they got was a list of file names.
- No, you didn't.
- Yes, I did.
And they got bubkes. Zero, zilch...
zot, nix, nada, dry hump, squirt...
diddley-squat.
I read a slang dictionary once.
Now you just keep reading.
Contractor tried to kill you, buddy.
And that's not good.
Here, Pearl.
Hey, Pearl, I got some caviar
for you, baby. Come here.
Good girl.
Hey, did you know that "caviar"
isn't a Russian word.
I think the word is "ikra".
- How did you know that?
- I had a Russian friend, Nikolai.
He told me about it.
- Had a friend?
- Yeah.
About 15 years ago, he was taken.
That means he was killed, right?
Yes, I'm still alive, you son of a bitch.
Not this time.
Let's see how valuable
he really thinks this is.
Three million?
Four?
More.
Twenty fucking million dollars?
Jesus.
Where do you suppose
this person is right now?
A mile from here?
Thousand miles from here?
Never really thought about it till now.
You quit your job, you're having thoughts
you never had before.
Sounds like a mid-life crisis.
You're right.
Oh, man.
Twenty million dollars.
We're partners, right?
That's $10 million apiece.
- It's 8 million. Bank keeps 20 percent.
- I thought I was a thief.
- Do you have a passport?
- I have 12. Where we going?
- Going to the bank.
- All right.
What happened to the hotel?
They had a fire years ago.
And nobody had money to fix it.
- Wait here.
- Okay.
Keep the air on and watch my cat, okay?
You got it.
Hey, is that our bank?
That where our money is?
- What's up there?
- He'll be.
It's all right. Hug the wall.
- Hug the wall.
- Careful.
Go light, go light, go light.
Jesus.
Hey. You okay?
Ten o'clock tomorrow morning,
I'm going go into that bank.
He's gonna be down there in the plaza
somewhere, somewhere in the crowd.
When he sees me go in,
he's gonna make his move up here.
You're gonna be in the cafe over there.
You'll see him when he goes inside.
Then we wait.
And we wait.
Tomorrow's gonna be a long day for him.
He's gonna begin to doubt himself.
He's gonna think he missed me.
He's gonna want to see with his own eyes
whether I'm still in the bank.
Then it'll be sunset.
Closing time.
He's gonna get desperate...
real desperate.
But he must leave his rifle behind.
On this side. He's right-handed.
He won't take a pistol because
there's metal detectors on the doors...
and he's gonna be very nervous.
When he's out of sight,
you come up here and take the rifle.
He'll shoot you
before you go into the bank.
No. He'll wait for the prime shot.
When I come out.
He'll wanna see my eyes.
Why are you so sure?
He loves history.
Fifteen years ago...
in this same room...
in this same window...
I was here.
Oh, my God.
Your friend, Nicolai.
You said he was taken.
You killed him.
It's fine.
- Who is it?
- Room service.
I didn't order any room service.
I did.
You should tell me these things.
Hi.
Where would you like me to put the tray?
Oh. Over here's fine.
Here we go.
So, what's going on outside?
The Day of the Dead.
What are the flowers for?
The families, they make a path
from their homes to the cemetery...
with the flower petals so the souls of the
dead loved ones can find their way home.
- That's nice.
- Please, call me anytime for the tray.
Okay, gracias.
Sounds great, huh? Can we go?
No, he's here now.
I know he is. He's here.
So you and me,
we're staying in the hotel.
The enemy of fun.
I bought you a beer.
Hey, Pearl. Come here.
Electra.
I wish I could explain to you why...
I killed Nicolai.
I guess at the time,
it was the right thing to do, but...
I'm sorry I did it.
But it's something I've had to live with
for 15 years.
I used to wish the same thing
would happen to me...
and that would have been my way out.
Permanently.
But not anymore.
Not since I met you.
Electra?
Cerveza. Cerveza.
It's a shame
you don't understand English.
You know, I would like to tell you how
wonderful this cemetery is. It's gorgeous.
I love cemeteries. I really do.
I really do.
One day, you're here,
the next day you're down there.
You know, I put a lot of people
down there.
Oh yeah, a lot of people down there.
Yeah, I did.
Right.
Jasmine.
It's all over the place.
Excuse me. Excuse me.
I just killed your brother.
Come here, Pearl.
Contract has been paid.
Transferred to the specified account.
And her disc?
You'll be advised. Goodbye, Robert.
Goodbye.
- Let's get ready.
- Okay.
- Don't lose this.
- What's that? A two-way?
Oh, man. This is a piece of junk.
Why didn't you let me know?
Listen. You tell me
when he leaves the hotel.
I'll tell you when he leaves the bank.
We're out.
- What's this for?
- Just in case.
- No. I can't shoot anybody. I can't do that.
- You almost shot me.
- I was aiming at the lamp.
- Well, you can aim at him.
Remember when you were a kid?
- Ever play cowboys and Indians?
- Sure. Everybody did.
- And which were you?
- An Indian.
- I was always an Indian.
- Always the Indian.
Well, you just pretend he's a cowboy,
and pull the trigger.
Then pretend he gets up after that.
But you got to pull the trigger.
You got to.
I never depended on anyone in my life.
But I'm depending on you.
I don't see him.
I'm looking all the way
around the square.
I'm in the bank.
Where do I go for transfers?
Oh, my God.
He's here.
He's heading towards the hotel.
He's almost at the door.
Yeah, okay. He's almost in. He's...
Yeah. Yeah.
He's going in. He's going in.
He's going in.
That's what we want, Electra.
Relax, try the decaf.
He must be upstairs.
So, what do you want?
Should I stay here?
Do you want me to go now?
Should I stay? Wait, wait. I'll just wait.
It's hot out here. Goddamn, it's hot.
Believe me, I'd rather be out there
than in here.
- May I help you, sir?
- Hi.
I'm expecting a transfer.
Here's the number.
- Señor, we have received your transfer.
- I'd like to close the account.
- Would you get the paperwork ready?
- Today?
- You wish to close your account today?
- Right now. Today.
- How would you like the funds?
- American currency.
Would you please step right over there.
I'll be right back.
No problem.
Mr. Rath?
You're aware, señor,
there may be a withdrawal fee.
Yes, I am.
This will take some time.
I've got all day.
Please, take care of him.
Please, follow me. Right this way, sir.
You may sit right over here.
Just relax. We'll get you some coffee.
What are you doing in there?
Fuck.
Talk to me.
Well, no sign of him.
He's just sitting up there, same as us.
No, I mean, talk to me.
Tell me some of that weird stuff you know.
Tell you weird stuff, huh?
- Like what?
- Tell me a joke.
Oh, well...
- May I?
- Oh, sure.
Tell me something
to keep my mind off of this.
All right.
- I'm not getting paid for this, but here goes.
- Come on, be generous.
All right, once upon a time...
there was a little sparrow...
who, while flying south
for the winter, froze solid...
and fell to the ground.
Then, to make matters worse,
a cow crapped on him.
But the manure was all warm
and it defrosted him.
So there he is, warm and
happy to be alive and he starts to sing.
A cat comes along...
and he clears off the manure and looks
at the little bird, and then he eats him.
The moral of the story is this.
Everyone who craps on you
is not necessarily your enemy...
and everyone
who gets you out of crap...
is not necessarily your friend.
And if you're warm and happy...
no matter where you are,
just keep your big mouth shut.
You like that, huh?
But, Rath, listen.
I think I'm running out of stories here.
Seriously, keep your eye on that building.
I know he's gotta be getting impatient.
He has to make his move very soon.
And Electra...
thanks for the stories.
- Sorry I've been taking up the table. Here.
- Okay. Thank you. Thank you.
Fuck! Shit! Motherfucker!
Fuck! Shit!
We have deducted our fee
and are making a second count.
The funds will be available
in one half hour.
I hope you are comfortable.
No, no, no.
Oh, my God. He's coming.
He's coming out of the hotel.
- He waited four minutes longer than I did.
- There he is. He's coming.
- Go.
- Go. Okay.
- I have your property.
- Be right there.
- Where are you?
- I'm here, I'm in room 303.
The rifle should be on the right.
And if so,
the gun is going to be right here.
- It's not here.
- I'm not sure what's happening.
- Listen to me.
Get out now.
- Damn it.
- Listen to me, forget the rifle. Get out.
Electra, have you left?
Oh, Jesus, Mary and Joseph.
Found it. I see it.
- It's a damn hot day, isn't it?
- Scorcher.
I got it. Got it.
Tell me something.
How did you know?
I mean, who the hell taught you?
History. Nicolai.
Fifteen years ago I walked into this bank
just like you are now.
That makes you good...
because I was the best.
But now you feel like a mark, don't you?
You think you were sold out.
Don't know who to trust.
And you, antiquado?
Who can you trust? No one.
You are alone. Same as me.
I don't have it.
I don't have the gun...
Why the sunglasses, kid?
Afraid to let me see your eyes?
Well, just between you and me...
I'm nervous.
I have $16 million in there.
This is where we can change history.
Our history.
I'm willing to give it to you...
if you'll let me walk.
But...
you won't do that, will you?
No.
No, no, no.
Well...
Excuse me, but...
you are pathetic.
You sound like a mark.
What happened to you, man?
Nothing. I just know where you're going.
I tell you...
that night in the taxi...
I thought I was the lucky one,
just to be alive.
Now...
I think differently.
You were the lucky one.
I'm a very, very lucky man.
Well, no more chitchat.
Good luck.
Electra, where are you?
Electra, talk to me.
Rath...
Can you hear me?
Rath, can you hear me?
Fuck. Fuck.
Everything is in order.
Please, come with me.
This is awkward.
It's not really my affair...
but I was told you would give us
something in return.
Oh, God, I'm fucked.
I'm fucked. I'm fucked.
- Okay.
- Now...
we are closed, señor.
Come on. Come on.
Step outside, Rath.
Step outside...
and I'll set you free.
Excuse me, sir,
would you please sign this receipt?
Come on.
I got the sword...
right here.
There is no shame. Fuck.
You won't feel a thing.
- Well, thank you for your business, sir.
- You're welcome.
Here he is. Here he is.
Thank you, sir.
Electra, we've got it. We did it.
Come on. Step outside.
We're in. You there?
Electra, where are you?
You there?
Yeah.
- Yeah.
- Can you hear me?
Look up.
I wanna see your eyes, motherfucker.
- Jasmine?
- Howdy.
Electra!
Yes.
You have something
that belongs to me. I need it now.
- Shit.
- I got something for you here.
- What the fuck do I do with this?
- Two against one!
Is that your edge, Rath?
You didn't take the mark.
- You took the bribe.
- Found it.
Don't worry. Don't worry, I'll take her.
- I'll take her.
- He's serious, Rath.
Even the odds.
Are you scared, honey?
I'm gonna find you.
I told you
I was going to tear your heart out!
And I will.
I will!
I promise you that!
Wait here.
Electra, I told you to stay up there.
- I'm not gonna.
- Electra, this is...
- The floor could give way.
- You could...
Goddamn it, why can't you...?
Don't move.
Throw it away.
That was no way to talk to a lady.
No.
Nicolai.
It's been a long time, my friend.
The years have been good to you,
Robert.
Miguelito?
Never pictured him so young. A shame.
Second best, after all.
He killed you...
- 15 years ago. He killed you.
- Yes, he did.
I don't understand.
Walking out of that bank
was the worst moment of my life.
He always went for the heart.
Predictable.
Fifteen years.
For 15 goddamn years...
you let me think I'd killed you.
Son of a bitch.
You're forgetting you shot me.
You son of a bitch.
Why? Why did you set me up?
The Cold War was ending.
I needed to die...
to leave no past behind.
You delivered me.
- You must be the mark?
- You must be the contractor.
I'm disappointed, Robert.
You were supposed to kill her.
You're a thief.
A good one.
I retired.
You were so good.
I had to use both my best
to track you down.
There's something on that disk
that would bring you back to life?
Enough information to expose us all.
Especially me.
Why can't you two
just kiss and make up?
This is sad for me, Robert.
Sentimental, but I did not want
to find you alive.
First things first.
Jesus, don't do this.
She's right.
She's always right.
- Female intuition.
- Yeah.
Where are you going, Miguelito?
To finish something...
you didn't finish years ago.
What's that?
Just to make sure.
Take it.
Are you gonna kill me now?
I never wanted to kill you
in the first place.
Come on. Help me up.
- Will you?
- Don't even breathe hard.
Do you wanna die, Miguelito?
Help me up.
Come on...
Thank you.
So...
Now what?
I'm finished.
What do you mean finished?
The history stops here.
No more.
I'm gone.
I quit.
That would make me number one.
Number one.
I can live with that. Can you?
Then live with it, Miguel. Live with it.
It was very nice meeting you...
Robert Rath.
It was very dangerous meeting you,
Miguel Bain.
You know...
as long as you are out there...
I'll never be number one.
Say goodbye, Bobby.
No.
No goodbyes.
Goodbye, Miguel.
Thank you.
Wait a minute.
I think you'd better keep the disc, Robert.
- Joseph. My real name is Joseph.
- Oh, yeah? I'm Anna.
Nice to meet you, Joseph.
So, Joseph, let's go get Pearl
a boyfriend.
Sure. And after that, if you
don't mind, I'd like to go to the hospital.
Someone needs to stop Clearway Law.
Public shouldn't leave reviews for lawyers.