Farid Morocco
[dramatic cello music]
- [Reporter] A round up
of the latest developments
in the finding of a flying disc.
Late this afternoon a
bulletin from New Mexico
suggested that the
widely publicized mystery
of the flying saucers
may soon be solved.
The Army may be getting
to the bottom of all
this talk about the so
called flying saucers.
As a matter of fact, the
509th atomic bomb group
headquarters at Roswell, New
Mexico reports that it has
received one of the
discs which landed on
a ranch outside Roswell,
when the rancher turned
it over to the Air Force.
[dramatic music]
- This is Jesse Rowen with
a breaking news alert.
Reports are in
that space pioneer
and billionaire Alexander Biggs
left earth and departed
for space unexpectedly.
What has led to this
sudden departure?
And, why were none of
the agencies informed?
Has he discovered something
we're yet to find out?
Or, is he trying to get
away from something?
There are many questions
that need to be asked.
Or, is this just the end
of fate as we know it?
I'm shocked, shocked.
Someone needs to stop Clearway Law.
Public shouldn't leave reviews for lawyers.
- I really miss my dad.
I need to find out
what really happened.
I know he's still alive.
[dramatic music]
[buzzing]
[ominous music]
- There's no need
to be afraid, Laura.
I'm not here to hurt you.
My name is Vivian, and I'm
here to show you the way.
[dramatic music]
[engines roaring]
- Happy birthday, Jack.
[buzzing]
Time to wake up.
Hi, honey.
[moaning]
[creepy buzzing]
[buzzing]
[alarm ringing]
- [Man] Father.
[cage rattling]
[pleasant music]
[tinkling music]
[engines roaring]
[dramatic music]
[computers beeping]
[air rushing]
[dramatic music]
- Hello Ramesh.
- 60 minutes right
on the dot, sir.
- Well you know what
they say, doctor.
Procrastination is
the thief of time.
[dramatic music]
[air hissing]
- [Ramesh] Right.
- So I take it the
craft has arrived, yes?
- Like clockwork, sir.
But, we've encountered an
anomaly when the spacecraft
returned.
Now I've cryogenically
frozen the specimen
but further testing
has to be done
to understand its
real consistency.
[air hissing]
[bassy music]
Come up here, sir.
Let me show you what
we're working on.
[air hissing]
[dramatic music]
- This is incredible.
- Have you started DNA
sequencing yet, doctor?
- Yes sir.
No match as of yet.
The test is going to take
a couple hours, Mr. Biggs.
[ominous music]
Dr. Cope.
- Sir?
- [Ramesh] Let's begin.
[dramatic music]
[electronic pulsing]
- Mr. Biggs, I have
never seen a species
be able to turn his emotions
on and off like this.
On one hand, he has shown
signs of pure empathy,
and then on the other
he's demonstrated
absolutely no emotions
at all whatsoever.
It's almost like he's
a biological mood ring.
- Well then I'd suggest you
keep a close eye on him,
doctor.
We need to now as much as
we can about this thing.
[computer crackling]
[computer ringing]
- [Dr. Rice] We got
a match on the DNA.
[computer burbling]
- That's Jack Adams.
[dramatic music]
- Are you recording this?
- Yes, I am.
- Make sure we have
no disturbances, okay?
- Yes, sir.
- We need everything.
- Unbelievable.
[ominous music]
[pleasant music]
- Happy birthday, daddy.
- Laura!
That's some pretty
good shooting.
- Thank you.
[pleasant music]
[alarm beeping]
- Whoa, what is going on here?
- Oh, I'm such a
dork in the kitchen.
Sorry, daddy.
- Don't worry about it, sweetie.
You're going to be
a wonderful husband
to some lucky guy someday.
- That's not funny.
- What do you say we start
over on the food together?
- How 'bout you
cook, and I'll wash.
- Fair enough.
[dramatic music]
Hello?
What do we got here?
[dramatic music]
[gun racking]
- Mr. Adams.
- You're trespassing.
Get off of my property.
- Dad, what are you doing?
[dramatic music]
- Jack.
Gorgeous place
you got here, man.
- Allen?
What the hell are
you doing out here?
- Well, I heard there's
a big Hee Haw style
birthday party going on
out here with banjos,
and hayride, and line dances,
and the whole shebang.
My God, is that
Laura all grown up?
- That's what happens
when you feed 'em.
- You know your father and
I are friends from way back.
As a matter of fact, you
used to call me uncle Al.
- What do you want Allen?
- Well, judging by the
tone you're not going
to invite me in for cake
and ice cream after all.
Maybe we should
take a walk, Jack.
- Take care of this for me, hun.
- I'm working with our
old friend from the unit,
Alexander Biggs.
You know he's made
himself a billionaire
with his aerospace
industries, right?
- How does a beer
drinking grunt like Biggs
build an aerospace empire
in less than 20 years?
- He's got something
in mind for you
in the way of a
birthday present.
- Well, that's good for
him, but I think I'm gonna
have to pass.
I want to spend
my 50th right here
with my 25 year old paint horse
and my 19 year old daughter.
- Jack, he'd really
like to see you.
Ever since he lost Sophia
in the car accident,
him and the kid get really
lonely this time of year.
It would mean a lot
to him if you'd come
and just hang out
with him for tonight.
- I'm gonna have to take
a rain check, Allen.
- He told me I
would have to beg.
Please Mr. Adams, he'll
fire me if you don't come.
I swear to God.
Jack don't make me put
my knee in the grass.
- Will you get up?
Allen, you're embarrassing
yourself, get up.
Get up.
- You'll come?
- Yeah, why not?
- You made me do
that, come here.
It'll be fun, believe me.
It's nice working for Biggs.
- I guess a little
reunion wouldn't hurt.
- Get the unit back
together, right?
[laughing]
You gonna ask me in for
ice tea or something?
- [Jack] How 'bout
some lemonade?
[dramatic music]
- Jack Adams.
[laughing]
Look at you.
- It's been a long time.
- [Alex] Yeah, it has.
And, happy birthday.
- Thank you.
- You're looking
crazy good at 50, man.
What the heck you been doing?
- What can I say?
Clean living.
This is my daughter Laura Lee.
- Laura.
- It's a pleasure to meet you.
- Nice to meet you.
Alexander Biggs.
She's grown up all
beautiful, Jack.
- This place is insane, Alex.
- It is, huh?
Not bad for an ex-solider, huh?
But, I would tell you my
friend there is so much more
to life than just all this.
Speaking of which, what do
you say we fire up the grill?
Have us a barbecue?
- Yes.
- You're the host.
- [Alex] All right.
[dramatic orchestral music]
Follow me.
Welcome to my home, Jack.
- It's very impressive, Alex.
- It'll do.
Well, just in time.
[ominous music]
Jack, Laura, my son Charlie.
- Hi, nice to meet you, Charlie.
- Well, it most certainly is.
- Charlie, I apologize.
All right, what do you say I
show you the rest of the house?
Come on.
[fire crackling]
[laughing]
50.
- The big Five, O.
- Hey, you know the drill.
Go ahead, Superman.
[blowing]
- I'm pretty exhausted.
I'm gonna call it a night.
- No cake?
- I don't eat cake.
Goodnight.
- Goodnight, Charlie.
He doesn't seem too
happy that we're here.
- Yeah well, nothing
makes that kid happy.
- That's a lovely
gesture, my friend.
- Nothing but the
best for the best.
- Cheers, Alex.
- As for my present to
you, I want to offer you
a vacation, you and
Laura, the two of you.
It'll be on me,
all expenses paid.
I'll have Allen make all
the travel arrangements,
and we can meet up in
about six or seven days,
relax, possibly talk about
your financial future.
Oh come on Jack, don't
be a stick in the mud.
I know where you're at.
We did a lot of things
when we were soldiers.
We did what we were told.
That's what we signed up for.
We saw a lot of war, but
a lot of human nature too.
Nothing good, I'm afraid.
- What do you think?
- Beach does sound pretty nice.
- You have to give me some
time to think about it.
- Here's to thinking
about it, Jack.
[glasses clinking]
Look you two, you can
visit me anytime you want
whether I'm here or
not, [speaking in a
foreign language].
Be safe.
- What are you thinking about?
- How I'm gonna tell you
that I decided to pass
on Alex's job offer.
- Daddy.
- Not the vacation,
just the job.
I gave it a great deal of
thought, but I just can't do it.
I'm not a company man, Laura.
I never have been,
and I never will be.
- I miss mom.
- Yeah, me too, sweetie.
[ominous music]
- [Alex] You know
what to do, Allen.
Make it fast and clean.
[rattling]
[tense music]
[gun firing]
- Dad?
Dad!
- Come on, get down.
There's someone in the house.
Let's go.
[tense music]
[gun firing]
[Laura yelling]
[tense music]
Go to the barn, get the bike
ready, and I'll meet you there.
- Okay.
[tense music]
- Be careful.
- [Gunman] Freeze.
Turn around.
[smacking]
[tense music]
[fleshy crunching]
[gun firing]
[kick snapping]
[grunting]
[fleshy crunching]
[smacking]
[tense music]
[bashing]
[smacking]
[thudding]
[blows bashing]
[kick snapping]
[dramatic music]
[panting]
[gun racking]
- Laura, Laura?
No, no, no.
Breathe, baby, breathe.
Come on, breathe.
Where's your inhaler?
Shit, it's in the house.
Breathe, baby, breathe.
Come on, breathe.
Come on.
Come on, baby.
[dramatic music]
[Laura gasping]
Breathe, come on be strong.
You've been here before, baby.
You can do this.
Breathe, breathe baby, breathe.
Come on.
Come on honey, you can do it.
- It's okay, baby.
I'm here now.
You're gonna be all right.
Breathe.
I'm here.
Everything's going
to be all right.
It's not your time, baby.
That's it.
You're gonna go
back with daddy now.
- Come on, honey.
Breathe, yes.
- Daddy.
- Come on.
[dramatic music]
I can't lose you.
Come on, we gotta go.
We gotta get outta here, okay?
Can you stand up?
- I think so.
Come on.
[dramatic music]
[doorbell ringing]
- Laura, Jack?
What are y'all
doing here so late?
- Heather, no questions.
I need a room with
a phone right now.
I'll pay you later.
- Okay.
- [Jack] It's all right.
[radio crackling]
[phone ringing]
- [Radio Dispatcher]
One Epi 34, be advised.
33 and 37 is code six with
the suspects and the victims.
- Fred.
- You got me dead to
rights on that one.
- Hey Fred, listen to me.
Laura and I were
attacked tonight
by a group of armed
men wearing ski masks.
They shot up my fucking
house, and we barely got
out of there alive.
- Tell me about it partner.
I'm here right now.
Neighbors called it in.
They said your house sounded
like a freaking war zone.
And, let me tell you
something, brother.
Looking around out here,
that's exactly what
it looks like.
We've already got
backup on the way.
Look Jack, I didn't want
to say nothing to you
at first because I didn't
want to worry you none
and Laura and all, but we
kind of got our timing off
tonight a little bit on this.
But, we've been keeping
a pretty close eye
on you for about the last week.
You know running by the
house a couple times a day
and all that.
- Yeah, why is that?
- Well, about a week ago,
I got me a call from a fed.
Apparently, some of the
guys you served with back
in the '90s are either
coming up missing,
or they're coming up dead.
And, he was telling me
all about how your life
might be in danger.
Jack, who could've done this
kind of damage in my town?
Jack, you there?
[booming explosion]
[bricks crumbling]
- Nice reunion, Alex, but we're
not sure you convinced him.
- Well if I know Jack Adams
the way I believe I do, Victor,
I can assure you it will.
- Well, I hope so.
Because we need to
know how Jack's DNA
is connected to Subject A,
and we need to know soon.
Oh, one more thing, Alex.
You need to settle down.
You're out of control.
The council is not only
aware, but they're getting
kind of tired of it, Alex.
- Alex, we gave you a
second chance in life.
that was because of your father.
We didn't have to do that.
And in one split second,
we could take it all away.
[ominous music]
- What's it all about?
What the hell's wrong with you?
[dramatic music]
- Yeah, I was like,
hey, we're gonna go out
for drinks and then
we're gonna party, cool?
- Rammed me, but it was okay,
and I felt really small.
I was like Willy get
up, and I'm gonna tag
you from behind.
[tense music]
[ominous music]
[booming explosion]
[guns firing]
[ominous music]
- You need to get
away from the vehicle.
- No, you gotta get outta here.
Go away!
- Jenny, come on.
I'm not leaving you.
Jenny, come on, let's go!
[guns firing]
No!
[booming explosion]
[guns firing]
[dramatic music]
[gun firing]
[air reverberating]
- It's okay, baby.
I'm here.
[machines beeping]
[buzzing]
- Alexander, Sophia,
I'm sorry to interrupt,
but I've been wanting
to congratulate
the both of you on your
one year anniversary.
Who knew I'd be doing
it standing over
a military hospital bed?
- Who are you?
How'd you get in here?
- I have friends in high places.
My name is Victor Khol, and
this is my assistant Vivian.
Alex, I used to work with your
father way back in the day.
- Sophia, could you
give us a moment please?
- Actually, Alex I think
what I'm about to share
is very, very important.
Your wife needs
to hear the truth.
- Alex, what's going on?
- Your husband has
suffered a severe injury
to the cervical spine at C
one and the C two vertebrae.
The surgeon said that
there is a good chance
that he may never walk again.
- Alex, I know this seems
hopeless, but I think
I can help make
all this go away.
- How?
She said I could be a
quad for Christ's sake.
I'll probably never walk
the rest of my life.
Wait a minute.
Victor Khol.
Shit, I remember your name.
My father used to talk to me
about you when I was a kid.
I thought he was
delusional in the end
always talking about ancient
aliens and conspiracy bullshit.
You know they institutionalized
him before he died
ranting this crazy
shit to the press
about how you were from
some faraway universe,
and you were over 400 years old.
- Alex, your father was
a genius and a real hero
in my eyes, and the
best friend I ever had.
- We need you to trust
us the way that we
trusted your father.
- Alex, your father
saved our lives.
He gave us a second chance.
Now it's our time
to return the favor.
[machines beeping]
[dramatic music]
- Yes Victor, you saved my life.
You gave me life.
And, for that I will
be forever grateful.
But, I must live my life.
I will not let you down.
- Do you remember a few
years after your operation?
Alex, we smoked cigars.
We walked, we talked.
You were so grateful,
so full of joy
for the betterment of humanity.
Do you remember this?
Alex, I must admit one of my
favorite human past times.
- Obviously, you've
never had sex.
- Actually Alex, I have.
But, where we come from
sex is more of a spiritual
and mental union rather
than just physical.
- So how do you have babies?
- How do we have babies?
With the power of
the mind, Alex.
[laughing]
- Do you feel anything?
- Of course, I do.
But, that would be
difficult to explain
to a man who's
governed by his penis.
- Well, I may be a
neanderthal to you,
but I'm smart enough to know
that there's a lot you can do
for humanity.
I mean knowing what
you did for me,
just think of how many
lives you can save on Earth
with your technology.
- Believe me Alex, I'd love to.
But, we are in fact governed
by rules of non engagement.
You see the council made an
exception on your behalf.
We needed a homo sapien
that we could trust
to be our liaison to do human
things that we simply cannot.
Technically, the council
does not get involved
with any planetary affairs
unless what they're doing
is affecting the
universe as a whole.
Kind of what your species
did back in July of 1945
when you began testing
your first atom bomb.
[booming explosion]
- Yeah, my father worked
on the Manhattan Project.
My mother told me how
much it haunted him.
I have a baby boy because
of you and a second chance
on life.
And for that, I'm
eternally grateful, sir.
- Shall we walk?
- I do, Victor.
- Good.
And, if I were you, I'd
do some soul searching
because as Vivian said
you are expendable.
[dramatic music]
[buzzing]
[machines beeping]
Alex, trust me.
When you wake up,
everything will be okay.
I promise.
You will be a new man both
physically and mentally.
[dramatic music]
- Okay, so I'll meet
you at the scarp yard
at O 800 tomorrow.
Yeah okay, I'll see you then.
- So what now?
- That was your uncle Kevin.
He's gonna bring us money,
clothes, whatever we need.
- What did Sheriff Fred say?
- Well, it's obvious
somebody's after us.
We don't know who it is
yet, so best thing is
to just lay low
until we know more.
- Who would want to
hurt us like this?
- Hun, it could be anybody.
You have to remember
Alex, Allen, myself,
guys like us, we made a lot
of enemies back in the day.
I had access to a lot
of top secret intel,
black ops directives,
you name it.
Most of it was high level
national security stuff.
- I'm really scared.
- Yeah, I know you are, honey.
Look, don't worry, okay.
Everything's going
to be all right.
Look, I took up Alex's
offer for a job, a vacation.
- Really?
- It's what you wanted, right?
[dramatic music]
- [Dr. Rice] Mr. Biggs?
- Jack and his daughter will
be here before too long.
I want to know everything
before they do.
- Yes, sir.
[dramatic music]
- Jesus, Jack.
I'm getting too old
for scares like that.
- Hey, it's good
to see you, man.
Thanks for coming on
such short notice.
- Of course.
Laura.
- Uncle Kevin.
- Look at you.
You keep getting more beautiful.
- Thank you.
- And, you just keep
getting uglier, don't you?
- It's good to see
you haven't changed.
[laughing]
- [Kevin] This is as
good as I could do
on such short notice.
- That's great, man.
I appreciate it.
- Look Jack, this Alex guy.
I realize that you two
have history, but I had
my CIA buddies look into him.
The guy's been a ghost
for the last 20 years.
Apparently, his wife died
in this horrific car crash
about 20 years ago, and
he just up and disappears.
Then he pops up mysteriously
as a multi billionaire
owner of Biggs Aerospace.
I don't know.
But, what I really want
to know is why does he
all of a sudden have
an interest in you.
I mean no offense,
but I mean why now?
You sure this is a
guy you can trust?
- Ever since Julie lost
her battle with cancer,
you're the only friend
that Laura and I have.
So basically you are
the only person I trust.
[dramatic music]
Biggs wants us to go on a
trip out of the country,
the two of us, but honestly
I don't feel comfortable
taking Laura along.
I want to ask if you can
take care of her for awhile.
- Of course, you know
Laura's always welcome.
I think I should go
first and check it out.
- What?
Dad, no.
You're not going alone.
I'm coming.
[dramatic music]
- Laura, this is
not open for debate.
A man just tried to
kill us in our own home.
This is not a game.
It's not open for
discussion, I'm afraid.
- You can't decide that.
Mr. Biggs says he
wants us both to go.
I'm not letting you go
off alone like this,
not now, not ever.
Especially after
what happened to mom,
I'm not losing you too.
- Laura, kiddo, maybe
you better listen
to your father on
this one, okay.
[dramatic music]
- Alex?
Hi, it's Jack.
Yeah.
Hey listen, I've been thinking
a lot about your generous
job offer.
Yeah, I'm sure she'll
be a little upset.
It's not about the money.
It's about my sanity.
We'll work out the details.
[dramatic music]
- So over there's our
science building, Jack.
Within those four walls, a
lot of fascinating research
goes on.
We've got our media
assessment offices.
And, that, my friend,
is my crown jewel, Jack,
the aviation department.
- I must admit, Alex,
when you said vacation,
I thought you meant spend
a few days on your yacht
on the ocean.
- Well [laughing] Jack,
there is that too.
But, I told you my
ideas were big, Jack.
They're very big.
They are Biggs big.
[laughing]
What do you say we visit
my science building, huh?
[dramatic music]
So what do you think, Jack?
- What do I think?
I think it's all
impressive as hell.
- [Alex] But?
- But, why are you
showing me all this?
- Jack, I want you
to join our team.
I want you to pilot our
first manned mission.
- Me, pilot?
I don't fly, Alex.
And, I don't see anything
here that I could--
- Jack, there is much
more to see, my friend.
But only if you're
truly interested,
and you are ready.
Oh, Dr. Rice.
- Yes.
- This is my friend Jack.
I thought he'd be interested
in our activities here.
- It's a pleasure, Mr. Adams.
We have been expecting you.
Would you follow me please?
- Oh, this is Dr. Ramesh.
He's one of my lead
research engineers.
None of this could be
possible without this amazing
team of minds we've
put together here.
- Dr. Ramesh, pleasure.
- Dr. Ramesh, this is
my friend Jack Adams.
- Mr. Jack Adams, Dr. Ramesh.
It's just a pleasure
to have you here.
We have prepared
everything for you,
and it's just gonna be great.
We are so excited to
have you here in person.
Shall we proceed?
- Lead the way, Ramesh.
- All right.
[dramatic music]
Hello doctor, how's it going?
- Hello, sir.
- The kids.
My pride and joy, Jack.
[dramatic music]
[screechy music]
- What the hell just happened?
[Alex laughing]
- I just love this thing, Jack.
I mean it gets me every
single time, Jack.
[dramatic music]
- That's amazing.
- Watch closely.
[electronic pulsing]
[Alex laughing]
- Great, thank you.
Great, thank you.
- So Jack?
- I don't know what to say.
What do you plan
on using this for?
Transporting water from the
Great Lakes to California
and the West.
- No, no, Jack.
Although that is a
wonderful thought.
I got bigger plans, Jack.
Get him a towel, Ramesh
and save the fish.
- Yes, sir.
[ominous music]
Clean yourself up.
[laughing]
[throat clearing]
Sorry.
- Water transfer was
a huge leap for us.
When we discovered
the right combination
of elements last year.
- Last year?
What about this year?
[dramatic music]
- So tell me, Jack.
What do you know
about the Red Planet?
I mean actually living there.
- Well, it's cold.
Too cold to live in
except in the center
where it's like our equator,
but at night, very cold,
a lot of ice.
It's not all red like
we normally show.
It does have a green side to it.
- Wow, pretty darn
accurate, my friend.
Good for you.
- Why are you planning
on going to Mars, Alex?
[laughing]
- Hell no.
It's too damn close to home.
[dramatic music]
We've discovered a way
to manipulate the gravity
of the planets
and the sun, Jack,
moving their orbits closer
to the sun like our orbit.
So living on Mars,
the Moon, meteors,
anywhere for that
matter for human beings,
it's possible.
[dramatic music]
[buzzing]
Come on.
[dramatic music]
- Hey cousin Laura, what are
you doing on the computer?
- Oh, I'm just
doing some research.
- I can help you.
I'm really good at doing
research on the computer.
- Adam, sport, why don't you
leave your cousin Laura alone?
- Uncle Kevin, it's okay.
I really don't mind
him asking questions.
- Speaking of homework little
one, have you finished yours?
- What, this guy?
I bet that you got
your homework done
before you even got
home, didn't you?
- Yeah, I did.
[Kevin laughing]
- That's my boy.
Come here.
Get over here.
- Aunt Kate?
- Yeah?
- Do you need any
help with dinner?
- Oh, thanks for
offering, honey.
I've got it, thanks.
- Oh hey, look at that.
It might be your dad calling.
- Jack?
- Hi, it's me.
- Hey buddy, it's good to
hear that you're getting
a signal with that
cell phone I gave you.
So tell me, how's it
going down there, brother?
- The research they're
doing here is so much more
advanced than anyone else
government or private.
Their technological
breakthroughs
are mind boggling.
Look, I know it's
crazy, but he showed me
some of their discoveries.
They've made huge,
wonderful steps forward,
displacing water from
one place to another,
stuff I could never
even of dreamed of.
- Wow.
You know I always
assumed Biggs was working
on something huge out there.
But, this sounds like
something beyond anything
I could've imagined.
- These things are far
beyond my understanding.
- Yeah, mine too.
- Look, but like any
scientific discoveries,
they have a dark side.
Look, I'm not sure exactly
what's going on here.
I gotta go.
- Hey Jack, I got
Laura right here.
You want to say hi to her?
- Hi dad?
- Laura, are you okay?
- Yeah, we're at uncle Kevin's.
Aunt Kate is making
dinner right now.
- Good girl.
All right baby girl, I gotta go,
but I love you, okay?
- Okay, I love you too.
Stay safe.
[dramatic piano music]
- Look kiddo, your dad is
the toughest guy that I know.
He's gonna be fine.
Trust me, he'll be back
before you know it.
- You're right.
[dramatic orchestral music]
- My crown jewel, Jack.
- See, that's right here.
- No, I don't think that is.
I'm having trouble with that.
- We figured out how
to handle the forces
of gravity through reverse
engineering 60 years ago.
We just figured out
how to master it.
It's all free and
unlimited energy.
- So the disclosures were true?
Amazing.
So this ship can get
us into outer space?
- I've already been there, Jack.
- You?
You've already been to Mars?
- And beyond, Jack.
And, we can go,
you and I, together
just as soon as you say yes.
It could be as early
as this afternoon.
It's as easy [snapping
fingers] as that.
- Be honest with me, Alex.
Why me of all people?
- Jack, a mission
to a foreign planet
exploring planet collectors,
anti gravitation devices
that'll swing it into a
friendly orbit around the sun
will take a man of great
courage and toughness.
Someone I can count on, Jack.
I've seen what you're
truly capable of out
in the field, Jack,
with my own eyes.
It's a lot to take
in, Jack, I know.
[dramatic music]
- What?
- Not what you were
thinking, huh Jack?
- Who is that, some
kind of prisoner?
- Jack, that is an
extraterrestrial being, Jack.
My robo-nauts came across
it from a newly discovered
planet, X Three, during
the last expedition.
It's our sister
galaxy next door.
We were able to tap
into a black hole, Jack.
[dramatic music]
[spooky music]
We need to revisit
that planet with you.
It has the same
negative type alien DNA
that you have
inside of you, Jack.
- What?
- I know we're still
trying to figure out why.
Theory is that, well
he's a version of you
from a parallel universe
perhaps even a star child.
My robo-nauts identified
him as a threat.
He got too close to
the ship, so they
actually froze him, picked
him up for analysis.
We need to learn everything
we can about him,
his species, his culture.
That is actually why I need
you to come with me, Jack.
You're the only earth
connection to it so far.
- This is unreal, Alex.
- No Jack, it is very real.
And, for you to even
to begin to understand
the magnitude of the work
that we are doing here,
you will have to take
the next step with me.
Jack, there could be
multiple versions of each
and every one of us out there.
Your wife could be there, Jack.
The possibilities are
endless, my friend,
a parallel universe.
[dramatic orchestral music]
Dr. Cope?
- Yes, sir?
- [Alex] Continue
with your work.
- Yes sir, Mr. Biggs, yes, sir.
[dramatic orchestral music]
- [Kate] Honey, do you mind
getting the door for me?
- I got it.
- Oh thanks, Laura.
- That's probably Ray.
I asked him to bring some
stuff from the office for me.
- Hey.
- [Ray] Hello.
- Hey Ray, come on in.
- Let me help you with this.
- Oh, thank you.
- [Kevin] There's space here.
Somewhere in here.
- Ray, you're staying
for dinner by the way.
- Well, there you go.
The boss has spoken.
- Yes mam, thank you.
- Oh Ray, I don't believe
that you've met my niece
Laura Lee.
I'm sorry.
Laura Lee, this is Ray.
- Nice to meet you, Laura.
- Nice to meet you too.
- She's gonna be staying
with us for the next couple
of days.
Her dad's out of town on work.
- Oh, that's nice.
Doc, I actually have
a few more boxes
left in the trunk.
You mind if I run
out and get it?
- [Kevin] Please, thanks.
- I could help you with that.
- Oh, thank you.
- Good evening, everyone.
We have a breaking news alert.
It's been reported
by eyewitness sources
that Charles Biggs,
the son of billionaire
and Biggs Aerospace
CEO Alexander Biggs
has been accused of
sexual misconduct.
Several of his accusers
- Turn this up.
- have come forward as part
of the recent me too movements.
And just in, we have
some live updates
on this breaking news
that Charlie Biggs
has lashed out against
his accusers and the media
with a statement on
his Zipper account
stating the following.
- Laura, look it's Charlie.
He's on breaking news.
You remember Charlie,
right, Biggs's son.
- None of your stupid
accusations matter.
My dad and I are off to
space with the aliens.
We will own you.
Wow, is this for real, Chuck?
I mean we've known that
Alexander Biggs' son
may have borderline
personality disorder
as even mentioned by his
father in his defense
when he got into trouble,
but this is just ridiculous.
We have not heard
a response back
from Alexander Biggs
or Biggs Aerospace
regarding this disclosure
by Charles Biggs.
However, we will provide
you with the most up to date
information on this
breaking news as we receive
further developments.
- Hey, dinner's ready, you guys.
I hope you're hungry.
- Actually aunt Kate, I'm sorry,
but I'm not feeling too well.
I think I should go lie down.
- Oh no honey, I'm sorry.
Maybe if you eat something
you'll feel better.
I can save you some
food for later.
I'll just leave it
in the fridge for you
when you're ready.
- Thank you.
- You sure you're feeling okay?
- Yeah, I should be fine.
- Look, it's stressful I know.
I get it.
Why don't you just go
rest up, and we'll be
down here if you need us.
- Okay.
- [Kate] Get some rest.
- Thank you.
- Of course.
- Inside of that
room right there.
Go on.
- Alex, open the door.
Open this door.
- I'm so sorry that it
had to be this way, Jack.
I truly am.
- Open this God damn
door, Alex, right now.
- Jack, I need you to
think things through.
Now, it's gonna start getting
a bit chilly in there.
- You're crazy, man.
You're fucking crazy.
- Until your answer is
yes, I'm ready to go, Alex.
- Don't hold your
breath waiting man.
Open the door.
- You will be going into
space with me, Jack,
perhaps even, hell, tomorrow.
[laughing]
- I wouldn't bet on it.
- Oh, and there is no need
for you know an elaborate
escape.
There is none.
And, don't you worry about
your sweet Laura Lee.
- You touch my daughter,
and I will kill you.
- Oh, and you know she's
due here any moment.
- You touch her,
you're a dead man.
I promise you I will kill you.
[dramatic music]
I swear to God I am
gonna kill you, Alex.
- Jack, you've seen
our technology,
and you know what
we're capable of here.
We can do this,
you and I together.
- Open this door.
- Laura's gonna be fine, Jack.
You're just going
to space with me.
- Alex, get back here, Alex!
Alex!
[electronic buzzing]
[ominous music]
[electronic sucking]
[dramatic music]
- [Alex] It's gonna start
getting a bit chilly in there.
[ominous music]
- Where's my daughter?
[electronic sucking]
[tapping]
- Jack is being complicated.
- Yes, I've noticed, sir.
I thought he would be.
- We don't have much
time to break him.
Are the others ready?
- Just in time.
- Excellent.
[electronic reverberating]
- I'm starting it up.
[buzzing]
[whirring]
[bassy echoing]
[tense music]
- I suggest we move
onto the provoking test.
- Yeah, let's do it.
Let's see if this thing
has any violent instincts.
- Excellent.
[tense music]
- What is happening?
Why are those soldiers armed?
- Relax, Dr. Rice.
- But, he has not
posed any threat to us.
It's obvious he's benevolent.
Anybody can see that.
- All creatures must
know to defend, doctor.
We need to know the
strengths and capabilities
of this thing, how he
attacks, how he defends,
how he thinks.
Without that data, we're
all potentially compromised.
I don't care how
peaceful he looks.
- It's just a test, Dr. Rice.
I promise he won't be hurt.
[tense music]
- Mr. Adams, I just need
a few minutes with you.
I'd like to explain
what we're up to
and also be able to
check your vitals.
Will you please
take your jacket off
and roll up your left sleeve up?
Leave us.
[dramatic music]
Give me a deep
breath and hold it.
Exhale.
[dramatic music]
[electronic beeping]
I just have a few seconds
'cause I've just jammed
the security cam.
Biggs is not who he
perceives himself to be.
He is abusing Subject A.
His intentions are not for
the betterment of mankind.
It is purely for his
own personal benefit.
Subject A is gonna die
if he doesn't stop it.
Do you understand this?
[dramatic music]
Okay, you look and
sound pretty good.
I'll be back in a little
bit to check up on you.
[dramatic music]
- Father?
Father?
[dramatic orchestral music]
- Where am I?
Is this a dream?
- No, we are in
your consciousness.
- Why are you calling me father?
Who are you?
- I am your offspring
from another world.
[dramatic orchestral music]
- That's not possible.
- My name is Metah, and I am
your star child, Jack Adams.
I come from an ancient planet
of highly evolved species.
Our predecessors
died 'cause of greed
and useless war.
Our great spiritual leaders
and advanced scientists
knew what was going to
happen, so they created us
using the best DNA strands
from across the universe.
They kept us secret
until the war was over.
Over the last century, we
have evolved into a beautiful
hybrid species.
We are a peaceful species with
no negativity in our hearts.
We were never meant to
be found by an evil man
like your Alexander Biggs.
Our planet, our sun is dying.
[dramatic orchestral music]
And if it goes,
we will also die.
- This is all...
This is incredible.
I don't know what to say.
- Our questors came to your
planet a long time ago.
Do you remember that father?
I vaguely remember
some childhood dreams,
but I never imagined
that they were real.
- Your dreams were reality.
Homo sapiens are one
of the few species
who can live without sunlight.
But, my people were
highly interested in you,
human but animalistic, yet
loving and compassionate,
a rare find on
your young planet.
- My son, yes, yes,
you are my son.
[dramatic orchestral music]
What can I do to help you?
- Help us, and we will help you.
Father.
[strange rattling]
[ominous music]
[yelling]
- Tell him to put
me down, Allen.
Put me down.
Come on.
Fucking, Allen, tell
him to put me down.
Allen, what are you doing?
Come on.
Tell him to put me down, Allen.
Just tell him to
put me down, please.
Tell him to put me down, man.
Come on.
Just tell him to
put me down, okay.
That's all you gotta do.
I can pay you.
I can pay you, Allen.
I know you want the money.
Please.
Dad, dad, tell Allen to
tell him to put me down.
Tell Allen to tell him
to put me down, dad.
Come on, what are you doing?
Come on, dad.
I think he's confused.
Dad?
All right Dad, look.
I'll stop fucking up, okay?
It was an accident.
Just fucking tell him.
Dad, tell him to put me down.
- Chill him.
- No!
No, no, no!
Dad, dad.
What are you doing?
Please just, dad, come on.
Tell him to get me
out of here, dad.
Dad, please.
[air sucking]
[ominous music]
- One too many times, Charlie.
It just had to be this way,
son or no son.
[dramatic music]
- Metah are you okay?
- Hey Jack, Jack?
You know I'm running
out of time, soldier.
I need your answer,
and I need it now.
- Shut the fuck up, Alex.
Where's Laura?
I want to see my daughter.
- You know Jack, today I
had to freeze my baby boy.
First my wife Sophia
and then my son.
You know how that feels, Jack?
Oh, that's right, you
know what it feels like
to lose a wife and a child, yes?
Yes, your wife Juile.
- Why don't you shut up, Alex?
- It's a shame her
dying in the hospital
with cancer like that.
I mean how could you ever forget
something like that, Jack?
You see there was nothing
you could do then.
Think of the
possibilities now, Jack.
She could be there.
I too long to see my
Sophia once again, Jack.
- You're a crazy son
of a bitch, Alex.
- Jack, you know that
wasn't very nice.
It's kind of rude.
[dramatic music]
Yeah, well this should
be quite interesting.
[dramatic orchestral music]
[fists thumping]
[smacking]
[fleshy crunchy]
[thudding]
[fists thumping]
[fleshy crunching]
[blows thumping]
[ominous music]
[fleshy crunching]
[thudding]
- [Jack] Metah.
[air roaring]
[glass shattering]
[Metah grunting]
[dramatic orchestral music]
Metah are you okay?
Metah?
- You idiots left me no
time and no choice, Jack.
I'm gonna have to continue
the operation from up there.
[tense orchestral music]
- All level must evacuate now.
We cannot let that
spacecraft go.
[grunting]
[clattering]
[glass shattering]
[orchestral music]
[grunting]
- Hey, don't you ever
call me an old man.
[gun firing]
[grunting]
Are you all right?
- I'm okay.
- Come on, let's go.
- Metah, wake up.
[ominous music]
[blade buzzing]
[fleshy crunching]
[ominous music]
[fleshy sucking]
[fleshy crunching]
[ominous music]
[grunting]
[fleshy crunching]
[blade buzzing]
[ominous music]
[blades singing]
[grunting]
[fleshy ripping]
[fleshy sucking]
[grunting]
[ominous music]
[fleshy ripping]
[thudding]
[dramatic orchestral music]
- [Alex] Ah, don't worry Jack.
I'm not gonna kill ya.
What's gonna happen is you
and our new alien friend,
you're now going to be
cryogenically frozen
just until we reach our
station in outer space.
- [Jack] Come on Metah.
We've gotta get out of here now.
I need you to wake up
and come with me, okay?
[air hissing]
- We can do it,
you and me, Jack.
The possibilities are endless.
[air hissing]
[dramatic orchestral music]
[engines roaring]
- This is Jesse Ronin with
a breaking news alert.
Reports are in that space
pioneer and billionaire
Alexander Biggs left Earth
and departed for space
unexpectedly.
What has led to this
sudden departure?
And, why were none of
the agencies informed?
Has he discovered something
we're yet to find out?
Or, is he trying to get
away from something?
There are many questions
that need to be asked,
or is this just the end
of things as we know it.
Today, we're lucky to
have two whistle blowers.
Two whistle blowers
who worked so closely
with Alexander Biggs.
They worked on a top
secret space project,
one that has the military
scratching their heads,
one that is about to change
life as you and me know it.
The questions need to be asked.
We're here now with one of
Alexander Biggs' top scientists.
You were with Biggs at
the time of the launch.
Can you please shed some
light into what is going on?
- I've worked for Alexander
Biggs for almost 15 years.
I was very proud and
excited to be able to work
for Biggs Aerospace.
But, it wasn't too long after
we acquired the specimen
that he exhibited a
behavior of ulterior motives
that was not for the
betterment of mankind.
- Could you go into a
little bit more detail?
- Well, there were
other subjects involved,
and we saw great
harm coming to them.
They were being
deceived, lied to,
and that's not what
we signed up for.
- Well, my son, technology
fascinated him, science, space.
He would always wonder
what's out there,
and he would always say to me,
"Dad I want to be like you.
"I want to be a scientist."
And, getting this job
at Biggs Aerospace
was a dream job,
a dream come true.
I hadn't spoken to him in
awhile until he called me,
and he said, "Dad, I love you."
I said I love you too, son.
He'd hoped that I'd
be proud of him.
I know this is hard for
you, so take your time.
- I wish I knew more
about what happned
and what was really in his mind.
That was one of the things
even when he was going up,
I couldn't never really
figure out my son.
So I wish I knew what he was
up to now and where he was.
- Dr. Rodgers and
I were on our own
when we realized that
Dr. Ramesh and Dr. Cope
launched off with Biggs.
And, then all hell
broke loose, the chaos.
We had one thing on
our mind was to be able
to stop this launch and
madness that was taking place.
Feds coming in and
trying to remove us.
I saw some things that, I
mean he cryogenically froze
his own son.
I mean he started
to look non human.
His behavior was
just like a monster.
We discovered that there
was so many more secrets
that Biggs was
withholding from us
and basically withholding
from the world.
And, we who survived
really feel that it's time
for the government to open this
up and show full disclosure.
This is something that
will affect all of us.
- I'm shocked, shocked.
[dramatic orchestral music]
- I really miss my dad.
I need to find out
what really happened.
I know he's still alive.
[buzzing]
[ominous music]
- There's no need
to be afraid Laura.
We're not here to hurt you.
[ominous music]
- Who, what are you?
- My name is Vivian, and I'm
here to show you the way.
- Show me the way, where?
- There's so much
for you to learn
about this universe, child.
[ominous music]
This is a Symptomani stone.
It has a connection between
this world, and others,
and even the next.
It can be used to interact not
only with these other worlds
but with the center of
the universe itself.
Those who possess
it control destiny.
All of your dreams
could come true.
Farid Morocco
[tense music]
[rock music]
♪ You set out on a dark road ♪
♪ Heading to a place
that's unknown ♪
♪ Hiding a secret
that's unshown ♪
♪ You lost your place
on the highest road ♪
♪ We are the fallen ♪
♪ Right to rely on you side ♪
♪ We are the chosen ♪
♪ We're gone and
broken for awhile ♪
♪ We are the chosen ♪
♪ Your hard road
has just begun ♪
♪ In turn, he has come undone ♪
♪ And now heaven is
calling your name ♪
♪ Please come home ♪
♪ Ignite the fire
that's inside ♪
♪ Explore the secret
that you hide. ♪
♪ Make up a story you contrive ♪
♪ And, hold it
forever to survive ♪
♪ We are the fallen ♪
♪ Right to rely on your side ♪
♪ We are the chosen ♪
♪ We're done and
broken for awhile ♪
♪ We are the chosen ♪
♪ Your hard road
had just begun ♪
♪ In turn, he has come undone ♪
♪ And, now heaven is
calling your name ♪
♪ Please come home ♪
♪ We are the fallen ♪
Someone needs to stop Clearway Law.
Public shouldn't leave reviews for lawyers.