Encoded By Deceit @ YIFY Torrents
October is
inventory time,
so right now,
Statler Toyota
is making the best
deals of the year
on all
1985-model Toyotas.
You won't find a better car
at a better price with better
service anywhere in Hill Valley.
That's Statler Toyota
in downtown Hill Valley.
The Senate is expected
to vote on this today.
In other news, officials at the
Pacific Nuclear research facility
have denied the rumor that
a case of missing plutonium
was in fact stolen from
their vault two weeks ago.
A Libyan terrorist group
had claimed responsibility
for the alleged theft.
However,
officials now attribute
the discrepancy to
a simple clerical error.
The FBI, which is investigating
the matter, had no comment.
Hey, Doc?
Doc?
Hello! Anybody home?
Einstein, come here, boy.
What's going on? Oh, God.
Oh, Jesus!
That is disgusting.
Where the hell is he?
Whoa!
Rock 'n' roll.
Yo.
Marty, is that you?
Hey. Hey, Doc.
Where are you?
Thank God
I've found you.
Listen, can you meet me at
Twin Pines Mall tonight at 1:15?
I made a major breakthrough,
and I'll need your assistance.
Wait a minute.
1:15 in the morning?
Yeah.
Doc, what's going on?
Where you been all week?
Working.
Where's Einstein?
Is he with you?
Yeah, he's right here.
You know, Doc, you left
your equipment on all week.
My equipment.
That reminds me, Marty.
You better not hook up
to the amplifier.
There's a slight
possibility of overload.
Yeah. I'll keep that in mind.
Good. I'll see you tonight.
Don't forget now.
1:15 a. m.,
Twin Pines Mall.
Right.
Are those my clocks
I hear?
Yeah, it's 8:00.
Perfect!
My experiment worked!
They're all exactly
25 minutes slow!
Wait a minute.
Wait a minute, Doc.
Are you telling
me that it's 8:25?
Precisely.
Damn!
I'm late for school.
Jennifer. Marty, don't go this way.
Strickland's
looking for you.
If you get caught, it'll
be four tardies in a row.
All right, come on.
I think we're safe.
You know, this time
it wasn't my fault.
The doc set all his
clocks 25 minutes slow.
Doc?
Am I to understand you're still hanging
around with Dr. Emmett Brown, McFly?
Tardy slip for you,
Miss Parker.
And one for you, McFly. I
believe that makes four in a row.
Let me give you a nickel's
worth of free advice, young man.
This so-called Dr. Brown is
dangerous. He's a real nutcase.
You hang around with him, you're
gonna end up in big trouble.
Ooh. Yes, sir.
You got a real attitude
problem, McFly. You're a slacker.
You remind me of your
father when he went here.
He was a slacker, too.
Can I go now,
Mr. Strickland?
I noticed your band
is on the roster
for the dance auditions
after school today.
Why even bother, McFly?
You don't have a chance.
You're too much
like your old man.
No McFly ever amounted
to anything
in the history
of Hill Valley.
Yeah, well,
history is gonna change.
Next, please.
Okay, guys,
let's rock 'n roll.
All right.
We're the...
We're the Pinheads.
One, two, three.
Okay, that's enough.
Thank you, fellas.
Hold it, fellas.
I'm afraid you're
just too darn loud.
Next, please.
Bring up
the next group, please.
Re-elect Mayor
"Goldie" Wilson.
Progress is
his middle name.
"Too loud. "
I can't believe it.
I'm never gonna get a chance
to play in front of anybody.
Marty, one rejection
isn't the end of the world.
I just don't think
I'm cut out for music.
But you're good, Marty.
You're really good,
and this audition
tape of yours is great.
You've gotta send it in
to the record company.
It's like Doc's always
saying. Yeah, I know. I know.
"If you put
your mind to it,
"you can
accomplish anything. "
That's good advice, Marty.
All right,
okay, Jennifer.
What if I send in the tape
and they don't like it?
What if they say
I'm no good?
What if they say, "Get out of
here, kid. You got no future"?
I mean, I just don't think I
can take that kind of rejection.
Jesus, I'm starting to
sound like my old man.
Come on. He's not that
bad. Save the clock tower.
At least he's letting you
borrow the car tomorrow night.
Check out that 4x4.
That is hot.
Okay. Back her up.
Someday, Jennifer.
Someday.
Wouldn't it be great to take
that truck up to the lake?
Throw a couple of
sleeping bags in the back.
Lie out
underneath the stars.
Stop it.
What?
Does your mom know?
About tomorrow night?
No, get out of town.
My mom thinks I'm going
camping with the guys.
Jennifer, my mother
would freak out
if she knew I was going
up there with you,
and I'd get the
standard lecture about
how she never did that kind
of stuff when she was a kid.
I mean, look, I think
the woman was born a nun.
She's just trying to
keep you respectable.
Well, she's not doing
a very good job.
Terrible.
Save the clock tower.
Mayor Wilson is sponsoring an
initiative to replace that clock.
Thirty years ago, lightning
struck that clock tower
and the clock
hasn't run since.
We at the Hill Valley
Preservation Society
think it should be preserved
exactly the way it is
as part of our history
and heritage.
There you go, lady.
There's a quarter.
Thank you.
Don't forget
to take a flyer.
Right.
Save the clock tower!
Where were we?
Right about here.
Jennifer!
It's my dad. I've got to go. Right.
I'll call you tonight.
I'll be at my grandma's.
Here, let me
give you the number.
Bye.
Bravo, Tango, Delta 6-2-9.
Tow for impoundment.
Any unit, please respond.
Perfect.
Just perfect.
I can't believe you'd
loan me your car
without telling me
it had a blind spot.
Blind spot? I could've been killed.
Now, Biff, now,
I never noticed
that the car had any blind spot
before when I would drive it.
Hi, Son.
What, are you blind,
McFly? It's there.
How else do you explain
that wreck out there?
Biff, can I assume
that your insurance is
going to pay for the damage?
My insurance?
It's your car.
Your insurance
should pay for it.
I wanna know who's
going to pay for this?
I spilled beer all over it
when the car smashed into me.
Who's gonna pay
my cleaning bill?
Ah...
And where's
my reports?
Well, I haven't
finished those up yet,
but I figured since
they weren't due till...
Hello? Hello?
Anybody home? Huh?
Think, McFly. Think!
All right.
I got to have time
to get them retyped.
Do you realize
what would happen
if I hand in my reports
in your handwriting?
I'll get fired.
You wouldn't want that
to happen, would you?
Would you?
Of course not, Biff.
Now, I wouldn't
want that to happen.
Now, look. I'll finish
those reports on up tonight,
and I'll run them on over
first thing tomorrow, all right?
Not too early.
I sleep in Saturday.
McFly, your shoe's untied.
Oh.
Don't be so gullible, McFly.
Got the place fixed
up nice, though, McFly.
I have your car towed
all the way to your house
and all you got for me
is lite beer?
What are you
looking at, butthead?
Say hi to your mom
for me.
I know what you're
going to say, Son,
and you're right.
You're right.
But Biff just happens
to be my supervisor,
And I'm afraid I'm just not
very good at confrontations.
But the car, Dad.
I mean, he wrecked it.
He totaled it.
I needed that car
tomorrow night, Dad.
Do you have any idea how
important this was to me?
Do you have any clue?
I know, and all I can
say is, I'm...
I'm sorry.
Believe me, Marty,
you're better off
without having to worry
about all the aggravation
and headaches of
playing at that dance.
He's
absolutely right, Marty.
The last thing you
need is headaches.
Kids, we're going to have to
eat this cake by ourselves.
Your Uncle Joey didn't
make parole again.
I think it would be nice if
you all dropped him a line.
Uncle
"Jailbird" Joey?
He's your brother, Mom.
Yeah. I think it's a major
embarrassment, having an uncle in prison.
We all make mistakes
in life, children.
God damn it.
I'm late.
David,
watch your mouth!
You come here and kiss your
mother before you go. Come here.
Come on, Mom. Make it
fast. I'll miss my bus.
See you later, Pop.
Time to
change that oil.
Hey, Marty. I'm not
your answering service.
While you were outside
pouting over the car,
Jennifer Parker
called you twice.
I don't like her, Marty.
Any girl who calls up a boy
is just asking for trouble.
Oh, Mother, there's nothing
wrong with calling a boy.
I think it's terrible.
Girls chasing boys.
When I was your age, I never
chased a boy or called a boy
or sat in a parked car
with a boy.
Then how am I supposed
to ever meet anybody?
Well, it'll just happen.
Like the way
I met your father.
That was so stupid. Grandpa
hit him with the car.
It was meant to be.
Anyway, if Grandpa
hadn't hit him,
then none of you
would have been born.
Yeah, well.
I still don't understand
what Dad was doing
in the middle
of the street.
What was it, George?
Bird-watching?
What, Lorraine? What?
Anyway, your Grandpa
hit him with the car
and brought him
into the house.
He seemed so helpless,
like a little lost puppy, and
my heart just went out to him.
Yeah, Mom, we know. You've told
us this story a million times.
You felt sorry for him,
so you decided
to go with him
to the Fish Under
the Sea dance.
No. It was the Enchantment
Under the Sea dance.
Our first date.
I'll never forget it.
It was the night of that terrible
thunderstorm, remember, George?
Your father kissed me for the very
first time on that dance floor.
It was then
that I realized
that I was going to spend
the rest of my life with him.
Hello.
Marty, you didn't
fall asleep, did you?
Doc.
No. No, don't be silly.
Listen, this is very important.
I forgot my video camera.
Can you stop by my place and pick
it up on your way to the mall?
Yeah. I'm on my way.
Einstein! Hey, Einstein,
where's the doc, boy? Huh?
Doc!
Marty! You made it!
Yeah.
Welcome to my latest
experiment. This is the big one,
the one I've been
waiting for all my life.
Well, it's a DeLorean...
Bear with me, Marty. All your
questions will be answered.
Roll tape
and we'll proceed.
Doc,
is that a DEVO suit?
Never mind that now.
Not now.
All right. I'm ready.
Good evening.
I'm Dr. Emmett Brown.
I'm standing on the parking
lot at Twin Pines Mall.
It's Saturday morning,
October 26, 1985, 1:18 a. m.,
and this is temporal
experiment number one.
Come on, Einie. Hey,
hey, boy, get in there.
That a boy!
In you go. Sit down.
Put your seat belt on.
That's it.
Whoa, whoa. Whoa.
Okay.
Please note that
Einstein's clock
is in precise synchronization
with my control watch.
Got it?
Right. Check, Doc.
Good.
Have a good trip, Einstein.
Watch your head.
You got that thing
hooked up to the car?
Watch this.
Yeah. Okay. Got it.
Jesus!
Not me!
The car! The car!
If my calculations
are correct,
when this baby
hits 88 miles per hour
you're going to see
some serious shit.
Watch this.
What did I tell you?
88 miles per hour!
The temporal
displacement occurred
exactly 1:20 a. m.
And zero seconds!
Jesus Christ!
Jesus Christ, Doc!
You disintegrated Einstein!
Calm down, Marty. I didn't
disintegrate anything.
The molecular structure of both Einstein
and the car are completely intact.
Then where the hell
are they?
The appropriate
question is,
"When the hell
are they?"
You see, Einstein has just become
the world's first time traveler.
I sent him
into the future.
One minute into the future, to be exact.
At precisely 1:21 a. m.
And zero seconds,
we shall catch up with him
and the time machine.
Wait a minute.
Wait a minute, Doc.
Are you telling me that
you built a time machine
out of a DeLorean?
The way I see it,
if you're going to build
a time machine into a car,
why not do it
with some style?
Besides, the stainless-steel
construction made the flux dispersal...
Look out!
What? Is it hot?
It's cold. Damn cold.
Einstein,
you little devil!
Einstein's clock is
exactly one minute
behind mine
and still ticking!
He's all right.
He's fine.
And he's completely unaware
that anything happened.
As far as he's concerned,
the trip was instantaneous.
That's why his watch is
exactly one minute behind mine.
He skipped over
that minute
to instantly arrive
at this moment in time.
Come here. I'll show you how it works.
All right.
First, you turn
the time circuits on.
This readout tells you
where you're going.
This one tells you
where you are.
where you were.
You input your destination
time on this keypad.
Say you want to
see the signing
of the Declaration
of Independence.
Or witness
the birth of Christ.
Here's a red-letter date
in the history of science.
November 5th, 1955.
Yes, of course.
What? I don't get it.
What happened?
That was the day I invented time
travel. I remember it vividly.
I was standing on the edge
of my toilet, hanging a clock.
The porcelain was wet.
I slipped,
hit my head on
the edge of the sink,
and when I came to,
I had a revelation,
a vision, a picture in my
head, a picture of this.
This is what makes time travel
possible. The flux capacitor.
Flux capacitor?
It's taken me almost 30 years
and my entire family fortune
to realize the vision
of that day.
My God,
has it been that long?
Things have certainly
changed around here.
I remember when
this was all farmland
as far as the eye
could see.
Old man Peabody
owned all of this.
He had this crazy idea
about breeding pine trees.
This is heavy-duty, Doc.
This is great.
Does it run on regular
unleaded gasoline?
Unfortunately, no.
It requires something
with a little more kick.
Plutonium.
Wait a minute.
Are you telling me that
this sucker is nuclear?
Hey, hey, hey! Keep
rolling. Keep rolling there.
No, no, no,
this sucker's electrical,
but I need
a nuclear reaction
to generate the 1.21 gigawatts
of electricity I need.
Doc, you don't just walk into
a store and buy plutonium.
Did you rip that off?
Of course. From a group
of Libyan nationalists.
They wanted me to
build them a bomb,
so I took their plutonium and, in
turn, gave them a shoddy bomb casing
full of used
pinball machine parts.
Come on. Let's get you
a radiation suit. Jesus!
We must prepare
to reload.
It's safe now.
Everything's lead-lined.
Don't you lose
those tapes now.
I need that
as a record.
Let's put this back here.
There we go.
I almost forgot
my luggage.
Who knows if they've got
cotton underwear in the future?
I'm allergic to
all synthetics.
The future?
That's where
you're going?
That's right,
25 years into the future.
I've always dreamed of seeing the
future, looking beyond my years,
seeing the progress
of mankind.
Why not?
I'll also be able to see who
wins the next 25 World Series.
Doc.
Huh?
Look me up when
you get there.
Indeed, I will.
Roll 'em.
I, Dr. Emmett Brown,
am about to embark on
an historic journey.
What am
I thinking of?
I almost forgot to
bring extra plutonium.
How did I ever expect to get
back? One pellet, one trip.
I must be
out of my mind.
What is it, Einie?
Oh, my God.
They found me. I don't
know how, but they found me.
Run for it, Marty!
Who? Who?
Who do you think?
The Libyans!
Holy shit!
I'll draw their fire!
Doc, wait!
No!
You bastard!
Go! Damn Soviet gun.
Go!
Come on!
Move, damn it!
Jesus!
Holy shit!
Let's see if you
bastards can do 90.
What is it?
What is it, Pa?
Looks like an airplane
without wings.
That ain't no airplane.
Look.
Children!
Listen... Whoa.
Hello?
Excuse me.
Sorry about your barn.
It's already mutated
into human form! Shoot it!
Take that, you mutated
son of a bitch!
Get away!
Hold it.
Shoot it, Pa!
My pine! Why you...
You space bastard!
You killed our pine!
All right. All right.
Okay, McFly.
Get a grip on yourself.
It's all a dream.
It's just
a very intense dream.
Listen,
you got to help me.
Don't stop,
Wilbur! Don't!
It can't be.
This is nuts.
Come on.
Perfect.
Remember, fellow citizens,
the future is in your hands.
If you believe in progress,
re-elect Mayor Red Thomas.
Progress is
his middle name.
Mayor Red Thomas'
progress platform
means more jobs,
better education,
bigger civic improvements
and lower taxes.
On election day, cast your
vote for a proven leader.
Re-elect Mayor Red Thomas.
This has got to
be a dream.
Hey, kid.
What'd you do? Jump ship?
What?
What's with
the life preserver?
I just want to
use the phone.
Yeah, it's in the back.
Brown.
Great. You're alive.
Come on.
Do you know where
1640 Riverside...
Are you going to
order something, kid?
Yeah. Give me a Tab.
Tab? I can't give you a tab
unless you order something.
Right.
Give me a Pepsi Free.
You want a Pepsi, pal,
you're going to pay for it.
Just give me something
without any sugar in it, okay?
Something without sugar.
Hey, McFly.
What do you think
you're doing?
Biff.
I'm talking to you, McFly,
you Irish bug!
Hey, Biff. Hey, guys.
How are you doing?
You got my homework
finished, McFly?
Well, actually, I figured since
it wasn't due till Monday...
Hello? Hello?
Anybody home?
Think, McFly. Think!
Okay.
I got to have time
to recopy it.
You realize
what would happen
if I hand in my homework
in your handwriting?
I'll get kicked
out of school.
You wouldn't want that
to happen, would you?
Would you?
Now, of course not,
Biff.
No. I wouldn't want that to happen.
What are you
looking at, butthead?
Biff, get a load of
this guy's life preserver.
Dork thinks he's
going to drown.
How about
my homework, McFly?
Okay, Biff. Well, I'll
finish that on up tonight
and then I'll bring it over
first thing tomorrow morning.
Not too early.
I sleep in Sundays.
Oh, McFly,
your shoe's untied!
Don't be so gullible, McFly. Okay.
I don't want to see
you in here again.
Okay. All right.
Bye-bye.
What?
You're George McFly.
Yeah. Who are you?
Say! Why do you
let those boys
push you around
like that for?
Well, they're
bigger than me.
Stand tall, boy. Have
some respect for yourself.
Don't you know, if you let
people walk over you now,
they'll be walking over you
for the rest of your life.
Look at me.
You think I'm gonna
spend the rest of my life
in this slop house?
Watch it, Goldie.
No, sir!
I'm gonna make
something of myself.
I'm going
to night school,
and one day,
I'm going to be somebody.
That's right.
He's going to be mayor.
Yeah, I'm...
Mayor!
Now that's a good idea!
I could run for mayor.
A colored mayor.
That'll be the day.
You wait and see, Mr.
Caruthers. I will be mayor.
I'll be the most powerful
man in Hill Valley,
and I'm going to
clean up this town.
Good. You can start
by sweeping the floor.
Mayor Goldie Wilson.
I like the sound of that.
Hey, Dad! George!
Hey, you on the bike!
He's a peeping Tom.
Dad!
Hey, wait a minute. Wait
a minute. Who are you?
Stella! Another one
of these damn kids
jumped in front
of my car!
Come on out here! Help
me take him in the house!
Mom? That you?
There,
there, now. Just relax.
You've been asleep for
almost nine hours now.
I had a horrible nightmare.
I dreamed that I went back
in time. It was terrible.
Well,
you're safe and sound now,
back in good old 1955.
1955?
You're my...
My name is Lorraine.
Lorraine Baines.
Yeah.
But you're...
You're so...
You're so thin!
Just relax, Calvin. You got
a big bruise on your head.
Where are my pants?
Over there,
on my hope chest.
I've never seen purple
underwear before, Calvin.
Calvin? Why do you
keep calling me Calvin?
Well, that is your name,
isn't it? Calvin Klein?
It's written all over
your underwear.
Oh, I guess they
call you Cal, huh?
No, actually,
people call me Marty.
Oh.
Pleased to
meet you, Calvin.
Marty.
Klein.
Do you mind
if I sit here?
No. Fine.
No. Good.
Fine. Good.
That's a big bruise
you have there.
Lorraine,
are you up there?
Oh, my God!
It's my mother!
Quick!
Put your pants back on!
So, tell me, Marty, how
long have you been in port?
Excuse me?
I guessed
you're a sailor.
That's why you wear
that life preserver.
Coast Guard.
Sam, here's
the young man
you hit with your car
out there.
He's all right.
Thank God.
What were you doing in the middle
of the street, a kid your age?
Don't pay attention to him.
He's in one of his moods.
Sam, you quit fiddling
with that thing.
Come in here
to dinner.
Now, let's see.
You already know Lorraine.
This is Milton, this
is Sally, that's Toby,
and over there in the
playpen is little baby Joey.
So, you're my uncle Joey.
Better get used
to these bars, kid.
Yes. Joey just loves
being in his playpen.
He cries whenever
we take him out,
so we just leave him
in there all the time.
Well, Marty, I hope
you like meatloaf.
Listen,
I really ought to...
Sit here, Marty.
Sam, stop fiddling
with that thing
and come in here
and eat your dinner.
Look at it roll.
Now we can watch Jackie
Gleason while we eat.
It's our first
television set.
Dad just
picked it up today.
Do you have
a television?
Well, yeah. You know
we have two of them.
Wow! You must be rich.
Oh, honey,
he's teasing you.
Nobody has two
television sets.
Hey. Hey,
I've seen this one.
I've seen this one!
This is a classic.
This is where Ralph dresses
up as a man from space.
What do you mean, you've
seen this? It's brand-new.
Yeah, well,
I saw it on a rerun.
What's a rerun?
You'll find out.
You know, Marty, you look so
familiar to me. Do I know your mother?
Yeah, I think
maybe you do.
Oh, then I want
to give her a call.
I don't want her
to worry about you.
You can't.
That is,
nobody's home.
Oh.
Yet.
Listen, do you know
where Riverside Drive is?
It's on the other
end of town.
A block past Maple.
East end of town.
Wait a minute,
a block past Maple.
That's John F.
Kennedy Drive.
Who the hell
is John F. Kennedy?
Mother?
With Marty's parents
out of town,
don't you think he ought
to spend the night?
I mean, after all, Dad almost
killed him with the car.
That's true, Marty.
I think maybe you
should spend the night.
I think you're
our responsibility.
Gee, I don't know.
And he can sleep
in my room.
I gotta go!
Thanks very much.
It was wonderful.
You were all great. See
you all later. Much later.
He's a very
strange young man.
He's an idiot.
Comes from upbringing. His
parents are probably idiots, too.
Lorraine,
you ever have a kid
who acts that way,
I'll disown you.
Doc?
Don't say a word.
I don't wanna
know your name.
I don't want to know
anything about you.
Listen, Doc...
Quiet!
Doc, it's me, Marty.
Don't tell me anything.
Doc, you got to help...
Quiet. Quiet.
I'm going to
read your thoughts.
Let's see now. You've come
here from a great distance?
Yeah. Exactly.
Don't tell me!
You want me to
buy a subscription
to the
Saturday Evening Post.
No.
Not a word.
Not a word now!
Quiet.
Donations. You want me
to make a donation
to the Coast Guard
Youth Auxiliary.
Doc.
I'm from the future.
I came here in a time
machine that you invented.
Now, I need your help to
get back to the year 1985.
My God.
Do you know
what this means?
It means that this damn
thing doesn't work at all!
Doc, you got to help me.
You are the only one
who knows how your
time machine works.
Time machine? I haven't
invented any time machine.
Okay. All right,
I'll prove it to you.
Look at my driver's
license. Expires 1987.
Look at my birthday,
for crying out loud!
I haven't even
been born yet.
And look
at this picture.
It's my brother,
my sister and me.
Look at her sweatshirt, Doc.
"Class of 1984"?
Pretty mediocre
photographic fakery.
They cut off
your brother's hair.
I'm telling the truth, Doc.
You got to believe me.
Then tell me,
future boy,
Who's President of the
United States in 1985?
Ronald Reagan.
Ronald Reagan?
The actor?
Then who's vice president?
Jerry Lewis?
I suppose Jane Wyman
is the First Lady.
Whoa. Wait, Doc!
And Jack Benny is
secretary of the treasury.
Doc, you gotta
listen to me.
I've had enough practical
jokes for one evening.
Good night,
future boy!
No, wait, Doc. Doc.
The bruise on your head,
I know how that happened.
You told me
the whole story.
You were standing
on your toilet
and you were
hanging a clock,
and you fell and you hit
your head on the sink.
That's when you came up with
the idea for the flux capacitor,
which is what makes
time travel possible.
There's something wrong with
the starter, so I hid it here.
After I fell off my toilet, I drew this.
The flux capacitor.
It works!
I finally invent
something that works!
You bet your ass
it works.
Somehow we've got to sneak
this back to my laboratory.
We've got to
get you home!
Okay, Doc, this is it.
Never mind that.
Never mind that now.
Why, that's me! Look
at me! I'm an old man.
Good evening.
I'm Dr. Emmett Brown.
I'm standing on the parking
lot at Twin Pines Mall.
Thank God,
I've still got my hair.
What's on Earth is
this thing I'm wearing?
This is a radiation suit.
Radiation suit?
Of course. 'Cause of all the
fallout from the atomic wars.
This is truly amazing.
A portable
television studio.
No wonder your president
has to be an actor.
He's gotta look good
on television.
Whoa. This is it. This is
the part coming up, Doc.
No, no, no,
this sucker's electrical,
but I need
a nuclear reaction
to generate
the 1.21 gigawatts...
What did I just say?
This sucker's electrical,
but I need
a nuclear reaction
to generate
the 1.21 gigawatts...
1.21 gigawatts!
1.21 gigawatts.
Great Scott!
What the hell
is a gigawatt?
How could I have been so
careless? 1.21 gigawatts!
Tom, how am I going to
generate that kind of power?
It can't be done,
can it?
Doc, look. All we need
is a little plutonium.
I'm sure that in 1985,
plutonium is available
in every corner drugstore,
but in 1955, it's a
little hard to come by.
Marty, I'm sorry, but I'm
afraid you're stuck here.
Whoa, whoa.
Doc, stuck here? I can't be
stuck here. I got a life in 1985.
I got a girl.
Is she pretty?
Doc, she's beautiful.
She's crazy about me.
Look at this. Look what she wrote
here, Doc. I mean, that says it all.
Doc, you're my only hope.
Marty, I'm sorry, but the only
power source capable of generating
1.21 gigawatts of electricity
is a bolt of lightning.
What did you say?
A bolt of lightning.
Unfortunately,
you never know
when or where it's
ever going to strike.
We do now.
This is it!
This is the answer.
It says here that
a bolt of lightning
is going to
strike the clock tower
at precisely 10:04 p. m.
Next Saturday night!
If we could somehow
harness this lightning,
channel it into
the flux capacitor,
it just might work.
Next Saturday night, we're
sending you back to the future!
Okay, all right.
Saturday's good. Saturday's good.
I can spend
a week in 1955.
I can hang out.
You can show me around.
Marty, that is completely
out of the question.
You must not
leave this house.
You must not see anybody
or talk to anybody.
Anything you do can have serious
repercussions on future events.
Do you understand?
Yeah. Sure. Okay.
Marty,
have you interacted with
anybody else today, besides me?
Yeah, well, I might've sort
of bumped into my parents.
Great Scott!
Let me see that photograph
again of your brother.
Just as I thought. This proves
my theory. Look at your brother.
His head's gone.
It's like it's been erased.
Erased from existence.
Whoa.
They really cleaned this
place up. Looks brand-new.
Now remember.
According to my theory,
you interfered
with your parents'
first meeting.
If they don't meet,
they won't fall in love,
they won't get married
and they won't have kids.
That's why your
older brother's
disappearing from
that photograph.
Your sister will follow, and
unless you repair the damage,
you'll be next.
Sounds pretty heavy. Weight
has nothing to do with it.
Which one's your pop?
That's him.
Okay.
Okay, you guys.
Very funny. You guys
are being real mature.
Maybe you were adopted.
Okay, real mature, guys.
Okay, pick up my books.
McFly.
That's Strickland.
Jesus, didn't that guy
ever have hair?
Shape up, man.
You're a slacker.
Do you want to be a slacker
for the rest of your life?
No.
What did your mother
ever see in that kid?
I don't know, Doc.
I guess she felt
sorry for him
'cause her dad hit him
with the car.
Hit me with the car.
That's the Florence
Nightingale effect.
It happens in hospitals when nurses
fall in love with their patients.
Go to it, kid.
Hey, George, buddy.
I have been looking
all over for you.
You remember me, the guy who
saved your life the other day?
Oh.
Yeah.
Good.
There's somebody
I'd like you to meet.
Lorraine?
Calvin!
I'd like you to meet my
good friend George McFly.
Hi. It's really
a pleasure to meet you.
How's your head?
Good. Fine.
Oh. I've been so
worried about you
ever since you ran off
the other night.
Are you okay?
Yeah.
I'm sorry.
I have to go.
Come on!
Isn't he a dreamboat?
Doc, she didn't
even look at him.
This is more serious
than I thought.
Apparently, your mother is
amorously infatuated with you,
instead of your father.
Whoa. Wait a minute, Doc.
Are you trying to tell me that
my mother has got the hots for me?
Precisely.
Whoa. This is heavy.
There's that word again.
"Heavy. "
Why are things so heavy
in the future?
Is there a problem with the
Earth's gravitational pull?
What?
The only way
we're going to get those
two to successfully mate
is if they're
alone together,
so you've got to get your
father and mother to interact
in some sort of social...
What? You mean like a date? Right!
What kind of date?
I don't know.
What do kids do
in the '50s?
They're your parents.
You must know them.
What are their
common interests?
What do they
like to do together?
Nothing.
Look! There's a rhythmic
ceremonial ritual coming up.
Of course! The Enchantment
Under the Sea dance!
They're supposed
to go to this.
That's where they kiss
for the first time.
All right, kid.
You stick to
your father like glue
and make sure he takes
her to that dance.
George, buddy.
Remember that girl I
introduced you to, Lorraine?
What are you writing?
Uh... Stories.
Science fiction stories
about visitors
coming down to Earth
from other planets.
Get out of town! I didn't
know you did anything creative.
Let me read some.
Oh. No, no, no, no.
I never let anybody
read my stories.
Why not?
Well, what if they
didn't like them?
What if they told me
I was no good?
I guess that would be pretty
hard for somebody to understand.
No. No, not hard at all.
So, anyway, George.
About Lorraine.
She really likes you.
She told me to tell you
that she wants you to ask her
to the Enchantment
Under the Sea dance.
Really?
Oh, yeah.
All you got to do is go
over there and ask her.
What? Right here, right
now, in the cafeteria?
What if she said no?
I don't know if I could take
that kind of a rejection.
Besides, I think she'd
rather go with somebody else.
Who?
Biff.
Don't kid around.
Come on.
I'm gonna leave.
You want it.
You know you want it.
You know you want me
to give it to you.
Shut your filthy mouth.
I'm not that kind of girl.
Maybe you are and you
just don't know it yet.
Get your meat hooks
off of me.
You heard her.
She said,
get your meat hooks off.
Please.
So what's it to you,
butthead?
You know, you been
looking for a fight.
Since you're new here, I'm
going to cut you a break, today.
So, why don't you make like
a tree and get out of here.
George!
Why do you keep
following me around?
Look, George...
I'm telling you, George,
if you do not ask
Lorraine to that dance,
I'm gonna regret it
for the rest of my life.
But I can't go
to the dance.
I'll miss my favorite television
program, Science Fiction Theatre.
Yeah, but, George, Lorraine
wants to go with you.
Give her a break.
Look, I'm just not ready to
ask Lorraine out to the dance,
and not you or anybody
else on this planet
is going to make me
change my mind.
Science Fiction Theatre.
Who are you?
Silence, Earthling.
My name is Darth Vader.
I am an extraterrestrial
from the planet Vulcan.
Marty!
Marty! Marty!
Hey, George, buddy.
You weren't at school. What
have you been doing all day?
I overslept.
Look, I need your help.
I have to
ask Lorraine out,
but I don't know
how to do it.
All right. Okay, listen, keep your
pants on. She's over in the cafe.
God! How do you...
What made you change
your mind, George?
Last night, Darth Vader
came down from Planet Vulcan
and told me that if I didn't take
Lorraine out, that he'd melt my brain.
Let's just keep this brain-melting
stuff to ourselves, okay?
Oh, yeah. Yeah.
All right, okay.
There she is, George.
Now just go in there
and invite her.
Okay. But I don't
know what to say.
Just say anything,
George.
Say whatever's natural, the first
thing that comes into your mind.
Nothing's coming
to my mind.
Jesus, George, it's a
wonder I was even born.
What? What?
Nothing.
Nothing. Nothing.
Look, tell her destiny
brought you together.
Tell her that she is
the most beautiful girl
you have ever seen
in the world.
Girls like that stuff.
What are you doing,
George?
I'm writing this down.
This is good stuff.
Yeah. Okay, let's go.
Can you take care of that? Right.
Lou, give me a milk.
Chocolate.
Lorraine. My density
has popped me to you.
What?
Oh.
What I meant
to say was...
Wait a minute. Don't I
know you from somewhere?
Yes.
Yes. I'm George.
George McFly.
I'm your density.
I mean,
your destiny.
Oh.
Hey, McFly.
I thought I told you
never to come in here.
Well, it's going
to cost you.
How much money
you got on you?
How much do
you want, Biff?
All right, punk.
Now I'm going to...
Whoa, whoa, Biff.
What's that?
That's Calvin Klein.
Oh, my God, he's a dream.
Whoa, whoa.
Kid! Kid, stop! Stop!
Hey!
I'll get it
back to you, all right?
You broke it!
Come back here!
Wow. Look at him go!
Get him!
To the car!
Go! Go!
What's that
thing he's on?
It's a board
with wheels.
He's an absolute dream.
Come on, come on!
Look out for the car!
Whoa!
I'm going
to ram him.
Shit!
Ooh!
Thanks a lot, kid.
I'm going to get
that son of a bitch.
Where does
he come from?
Yeah,
where does he live?
I don't know,
but I'm going to find out.
Oh, my God.
They found me. I don't
know how, but they found me.
Run for it, Marty!
Oh, my God.
They found me. I don't
know how, but they found me.
Run for it, Marty!
Doc?
Hi, Marty. I didn't
hear you come in.
Fascinating device,
this video unit.
Listen, Doc.
You know,
there's something
I haven't told you
about the night
we made that tape. Please,
Marty, don't tell me.
No man should know too
much about his own destiny.
You don't understand.
I do understand.
If I know too much
about my own future,
I can endanger
my own existence.
Just as you've
endangered yours.
You're right.
Now...
Let me show you my plan
for sending you home.
Please excuse the crudity
of this model.
I didn't have time to build
it to scale or paint it.
It's good.
Thank you. Thank you.
Okay, now.
We run some industrial-strength
electrical cable
from the top of
the clock tower
down, suspending it
over the street
between these
two lamp posts.
Meanwhile, we've
outfitted the time vehicle
with this big pole
and hook,
which runs directly
into the flux capacitor.
At the calculated moment, you
start off from down the street,
driving directly
toward the cable,
accelerating to
88 miles per hour.
According to the flyer, at precisely
10:04 p. m. This Saturday night,
lightning will strike the clock
tower, electrifying the cable
just as the connecting
hook makes contact
thereby sending 1.21 gigawatts
into the flux capacitor
and sending you
back to 1985.
All right, now.
Watch this.
You wind up the car
and release it.
I'll simulate
the lightning.
Ready.
Set.
Release.
You're instilling me with
a lot of confidence, Doc.
Don't worry. I'll take
care of the lightning.
You take care
of your pop.
By the way, what happened
today? Did he ask her out?
I think so.
What did she say?
It's your mom!
She's tracked you down!
Quick! Let's cover
the time machine.
Hi, Cal... Marty.
Mom. Lorraine.
How did you know
I was here?
I followed you.
Oh. This is my doc...
My uncle,
Doc Brown.
Hi.
Marty, this may
seem a little forward,
but I was kind of
wondering if you'd ask me
to the Enchantment Under
the Sea dance on Saturday.
Wow, you mean... You
mean nobody's asked you?
No. Not yet.
What about George?
George McFly?
He's kind of cute
and all, but not...
Well, I think
a man should be strong,
so he can stand up
for himself
and protect
the woman he loves.
Don't you?
Yeah.
I still
don't understand.
How am I supposed to
go to the dance with her
if she's already going
to the dance with you?
Well, because, George,
she wants to go with you.
She just doesn't
know it yet.
That's why
we got to show her
that you, George McFly,
are a fighter.
You're somebody who's
gonna stand up for yourself,
somebody who's
gonna protect her.
Yeah, but I've never picked
a fight in my entire life.
Look, you're not going to
be picking a fight, Dad.
Daddy-o.
You're coming to
her rescue, right?
Okay, let's go over
the plan again.
8:55, where are
you going to be?
I'm going to be
at the dance.
Right. And where
am I going to be?
You're gonna be
in the car with her.
Right, okay.
So, right around 9:00,
she's going to get
very angry with me.
Why is she going to
get angry with you?
Well, because, George,
nice girls get angry
when guys take
advantage of them.
You mean you're going
to go touch her on her...
No. No, George, look.
It's just an act, right?
Okay. So, 9:00, you're strolling
through the parking lot.
You see us struggling
in the car.
You walk up, you open
the door, and you say...
Your line, George.
Oh!
Hey, you, get your
damn hands off her!
You really think
I ought to swear?
Yes, definitely.
God damn it,
George, swear.
Okay.
So, now you come up.
You punch me
in the stomach.
I'm out for
the count, right?
And you and Lorraine
live happily ever after.
You make it
sound so easy.
I just... I wish
I wasn't so scared.
George, there's nothing
to be scared of.
All it takes is
a little self-confidence.
You know, if you
put your mind to it,
you can
accomplish anything.
...Hill Valley area weather
this Saturday night.
Mostly clear,
with some scattered clouds.
Lows tonight in
the upper 40s.
Are you sure
about this storm?
Since when can weathermen predict
the weather, let alone the future?
You know, Marty, I'm going
to be very sad to see you go.
You've really made
a difference in my life.
You've given me
something to shoot for.
Just knowing that I'm going
to be around to see 1985.
That I'm going to
succeed in this!
That I'm going to have a
chance to travel through time!
It's going to be really hard waiting
30 years before I can talk to you
about everything that's
happened in the past few days.
I'm really going
to miss you, Marty.
to miss you.
Doc, about the future...
No!
Marty!
We've already agreed
that having information
about the future
can be
extremely dangerous.
Even if your
intentions are good,
it can backfire
drastically.
Whatever you've
got to tell me,
I'll find out through
the natural course of time.
"Dear Dr. Brown.
"On the night that
I go back in time,
"you will be
"shot by terrorists.
"Please take whatever
precautions are necessary
"to prevent
this terrible disaster.
"Your friend,
"Marty. "
'Evening, Dr. Brown.
What's with the wire?
Oh, just a little
weather experiment.
What you got
under here?
No! Don't touch that!
Some new, specialized
weather-sensing equipment.
You got a permit
for that?
Of course I do.
Just a second. Let me
see if I can find it here.
Do you mind if we
park for a while?
That's a great idea.
I'd love to park.
Huh?
Marty, I'm almost
18 years old.
It's not like I've
never parked before.
What?
Marty, you seem so nervous.
Is something wrong?
No.
Lorraine! Lorraine,
what are you doing?
I swiped it from the old
lady's liquor cabinet.
Yeah, well,
you shouldn't drink.
Why not?
Because you...
You might regret it
later in life.
Marty, don't be
such a square.
Everybody who's
anybody drinks.
Jeez, you smoke, too?
Marty, you're beginning to
sound just like my mother.
We're going to
take a little break,
but we'll be back
in a while,
so don't nobody
go nowhere.
Marty?
Why are you so nervous?
Lorraine.
Have you ever
been in a situation
where you knew you had
to act a certain way,
but when you got there,
you didn't know
if you could go
through with it?
You mean like how you're
supposed to act on a first date?
Sort of.
I think I know
exactly what you mean.
You do?
You know what I do
in those situations?
What?
I don't worry.
This is all wrong.
I don't know what it is.
But when I kiss you,
it's like I'm kissing
my brother.
I guess that doesn't
make any sense, does it?
Believe me,
it makes perfect sense.
Somebody's coming.
You caused 300 bucks damage
to my car, you son of a bitch.
And I'm going to take it
out of your ass. Hold him.
Let him go, Biff.
You're drunk.
Well, look-ey
what we have here.
No, no! You're staying right
here with me. Come on, Lorraine.
Let me go!
Leave her alone,
you bastard!
Take him in back, all
right? I'll be right there.
Just admit that you want it. Come on.
Well, go on.
This ain't no peep show.
Hey, let's put him
in there.
Yeah!
That's for
messing up my hair.
What the hell are
you doing to my car?
Hey, beat it, spook.
This don't concern you.
Who you calling "spook,"
peckerwood?
Hey, hey,
listen, guys...
Look, I don't want to mess
with no reefer addicts, okay?
Get home to
your mama, boy.
Biff!
Hurry, Biff!
Let me out of here!
Reginald,
where are your keys?
The keys
are in the trunk.
Say that again?
I said,
the keys are in here.
Come on!
Hey, you,
get your damn hands off...
Oh.
I think you got
the wrong car, McFly.
George, help me!
Please!
Just turn around, McFly,
and walk away.
Please, George.
Are you deaf, McFly?
Close the door
and beat it.
No, Biff.
You leave her alone.
All right, McFly.
You're asking for it, and
now you're going to get it.
Biff, stop it!
Biff, you'll
break his arm!
Biff, no!
Give me
a hand here, Reginald.
Damn it, man!
I sliced my hand!
Whose are these?
Mine.
Thanks. Thanks a lot.
You're going to
break his arm!
Biff! Biff,
leave him alone!
Let him go!
Are you okay?
Who is that guy?
That's George McFly.
That's George McFly?
Excuse me.
The storm.
Hey, guys, you gotta get back
in there and finish the dance.
Hey, man.
Look at Marvin's hand.
He can't play with
his hand like that,
and we can't
play without him.
Yeah, well. Look,
Marvin, you got to play.
See, that's where they kiss for
the first time on the dance floor.
And if there's no music,
they can't dance.
If they can't dance,
they can't kiss.
If they can't kiss, they can't
fall in love and I'm history.
Hey, man,
the dance is over
unless you know somebody
else that can play the guitar.
This is for all
you lovers out there.
Earth angel, Earth angel
Will you be mine?
My darling dear
George, aren't you
going to kiss me?
I don't know.
Scram, McFly.
I'm cutting in.
Earth angel, Earth angel
The one I adore
Hey, boy,
you all right?
I can't play.
George!
George.
Excuse me.
The vision of your happiness
Earth angel, Earth angel
Please be mine
My darling dear
Love you for all time
I'm just a fool
A fool in love
with you
Yeah, man, that was good.
Let's do another one.
No. I got to go.
Come on, man. Let's do
something that really cooks.
Something that cooks.
All right.
All right!
All right,
this is an oldie, but...
Well, it's an oldie
where I come from.
All right, guys, listen,
this is a blues riff in B.
Watch me for the changes,
and try and keep up, okay?
Way down in Louisiana
Down in New Orleans
Way back up in the woods
among the evergreens
There stood a log cabin
made of earth and wood
Where lived a country boy
name of Johnny B. Goode
He never ever learned
to read or write so well
He could play the guitar
just like he's ringing a bell
Go, go
Go, Johnny, go, go
Go, Johnny, go, go, go
Hey, George, I heard you
laid out Biff. Nice going.
George, you ever think of
running for class president?
Johnny B. Goode
Go, Johnny, go, go
Go, Johnny, go, go, go
Johnny B. Goode
Chuck!
Chuck, it's Marvin.
Your cousin,
Marvin Berry.
You know that new sound
you're looking for?
Well, listen to this.
I guess you guys aren't
ready for that yet.
But your kids are
going to love it.
Lorraine.
Marty, that was
very interesting music.
Yeah.
I hope you don't mind,
but George asked if
he could take me home.
Great! Good.
Good, Lorraine.
I had a feeling
about you two.
I have a feeling, too.
Listen, I got to go,
but I wanted to tell you
that it's been educational.
Marty, will we ever
see you again?
I guarantee it.
Well, Marty, I want to thank
you for all your good advice.
I'll never forget it.
Right, George.
Well, good luck,
you guys.
Oh!
One other thing. If
you guys ever have kids,
and one of them,
when he's eight years old,
accidentally sets fire
to the living room rug,
go easy on him.
Okay.
Marty.
Such a nice name.
Damn!
Where is that kid?
Damn! Damn!
You're late! Do you
have no concept of time?
Hey, come on.
I had to change.
Do you think I'm going
back in that zoot suit?
The old man really
came through. It worked.
He laid out Biff
in one punch.
I didn't know
he had it in him.
He's never stood up
to Biff in his life.
Never?
No. Why?
What's the matter?
All right! Let's set
your destination time.
This is the exact time
you left.
Let's send you back at
exactly the same time.
It'll be like
you never left.
Now, I painted a white line
on the street way over there.
That's where
you'll start from.
I've calculated
the precise distance,
taking into account
the acceleration speed
and wind resistance
retroactive
from the moment
the lightning strikes,
which will be in exactly
7 minutes and 22 seconds.
When this alarm goes off,
you hit the gas.
Right.
Well, I guess
that's everything.
Thanks.
Thank you.
See you
in about 30 years.
I hope so.
Don't worry!
As long as you
hit that wire
with the connecting hook at
precisely 88 miles an hour,
the instant the lightning
strikes the tower
everything will be fine.
Right.
What's the meaning
of this?
You'll find out
in 30 years.
It's about the future,
isn't it?
It's information
about the future.
Wait a minute.
I warned you
about this, kid.
The consequences
could be disastrous!
Doc, that's a risk you're
going to have to take.
Your life depends on it!
No!
I refuse to accept
the responsibility.
In that case, I'll
tell you straight out.
Great Scott!
You get the cable, I'll
throw the rope down to you.
Right! I got it!
Doc!
Come on, come on.
Let's go!
All right!
Take it up!
Go!
Doc!
What?
I have to tell you
about the future.
What?
I have to tell you
about the future!
What?
On the night I go
back in time, you get...
Doc!
Go!
No, Doc!
Look at the time!
You've got less than four
minutes. Please, hurry!
Yeah!
Damn it, Doc! Why did you
have to tear up that letter?
If I only had more time.
Wait a minute.
I got all the time I want.
I got a time machine. I can
just go back early and warn him.
Okay. Ten minutes
ought to do it.
Okay. Time circuit's on.
Flux capacitor, fluxing.
Engine running.
All right.
No. No, no.
Come on. Not this time.
Come on. Come on.
Come on.
Here we go. Here we go.
This time. Come on.
Please. Please.
Come on!
Doc.
Crazy drunk driver.
Whoo!
All right. Fred.
You look great.
Everything looks great.
1:24. I still got time.
I'm coming, Doc!
No! No, not again!
Come on! Come on!
Libyans.
No!
You bastard!
Go!
Doc! Doc!
No! No!
You're alive.
Bulletproof vest?
How did you know?
I never got a chance
to tell you.
What about all that talk about
screwing up future events?
The space-time continuum?
Well, I figured,
what the hell?
So, how far ahead
are you going?
About 30 years.
It's a nice, round number.
Look me up when you get there,
all right? Guess I'll be about 47.
I will.
Take care.
You, too.
Right. Bye-bye, Einie.
Oh. And watch that re-entry.
It's a little bumpy.
You bet.
What a nightmare.
If Paul calls me, tell him I'm
working at the boutique late tonight.
Linda, first of all, I'm
not your answering service,
second of all,
somebody named Greg
or Craig called you
just a little while ago.
Well, which one was it,
Greg or Craig?
I don't know! I can't keep up
with all of your boyfriends.
Hey.
What the hell is this?
Breakfast.
Did you sleep in your
clothes again last night?
Yeah. I...
Yeah. What are
you wearing, Dave?
Marty, I always wear
a suit to the office.
You all right?
Yeah.
I think we
need a rematch, George.
A rematch?
Why? Were you cheating?
No.
Hello.
Good morning.
Mom! Dad!
Did you hit your head?
Marty, are you all right?
You guys look great.
Mom, you look so thin.
Why, thank you, Marty.
George!
Good morning,
sleepyhead.
Good morning, Dave.
Linda.
Good morning, Mom.
Marty, I almost forgot.
Jennifer Parker called.
I sure like her, Marty.
She is such a sweet girl.
Isn't tonight the night
of the big date?
What? What, Ma?
Aren't you going up
to the lake tonight?
You've been planning it
for two weeks.
Mom, we talked about this.
How can I go to the lake?
The car's wrecked.
Wrecked?
When did this happen?
Why wasn't I told?
Quiet down.
I'm sure the car is fine.
Why am I always the last one
to know about these things?
See? There's Biff out
there waxing it right now.
Now, Biff, I want
to make sure that
we get two coats of wax
this time, not just one.
I'm just finishing up
the second coat now.
Now, Biff,
don't con me.
I'm sorry, Mr. McFly.
I meant I was just
starting on the second coat.
Biff. What a character. Always
trying to get away with something.
I've had to stay on top of
Biff ever since high school.
Although,
if it wasn't for him...
We never would
have fallen in love.
That's right.
Mr. McFly! Mr. McFly,
this just arrived.
Oh, hi, Marty. I think
it's your new book.
Honey!
Your first novel.
Like I've
always told you,
you put your mind to it,
you can accomplish anything.
Oh, Marty,
here's your keys.
You're all waxed up,
ready for tonight.
Keys?
How about a ride,
mister?
Jennifer.
Oh, are you a sight for sore
eyes! Let me look at you.
Marty, you're acting like
you haven't seen me in a week.
I haven't.
You okay?
Is everything all right?
Oh, yeah.
Everything is great.
Marty! You've got to come back with me!
Where?
Back to the future.
Wait a minute.
What are you doing, Doc?
I need fuel.
Go ahead. Quick!
Get in the car.
No, no. Doc,
I just got here, okay?
Jennifer's here. We're gonna
take the new truck for a spin.
Well, bring her along.
This concerns her, too.
Wait a minute, Doc. What
are you talking about?
What happens to us
in the future?
Do we become assholes
or something?
No, no, no,
no, Marty.
Both you and Jennifer
turn out fine.
It's your kids, Marty.
Something has got to
be done about your kids.
Hey, Doc, we better back up. We don't
have enough road to get up to 88.
Roads? Where we're going,
we don't need roads.