[ Cawing ]
[ Panting ]
[ Cawing Continues ]
[ Cawing ]
[ Continues Cawing ]
[ Panting ]
[ Cawing Continues ]
[ Yelling ]
Balto, wake up!
[ Gasping ]
What? What?
What's the matter?
[ Yiddish Accent ]
The matter is,
you were having dream again.
Aah! Ugh!
So what if I was?
It's just a dream.
This "just a dream"
is keeping you from
a decent sleep.
And if your eyes get
any droopier,
you'll have to keep them
open with toothpicks.
Boris, they'll stop drooping
if you just go away
and let me get some rest.
Wrong! You won't be
getting rest--
not with that dream
hanging 'round like...
dark cloud.
[ Sighs ]
I hate it when you get dramatic.
How else to reach you?
I'm telling you, boychik,
if you keep having same dream
again and again.
it means something!
[ Grunts ]
Boris,
dreams don't mean anything,
they're just--
[ Yawns ]
dreams.
Now, you wanna come with me?
I have to go check on jenna.
Of course I come!
I'm not finished
nagging you yet!
So, if dreams mean nothing,
why does it always have raven
and pack of wolves, huh?
Why not pickled herring?
Because herring would be
in one of your dreams, not mine.
Precisely! Raven and wolves
have meaning only to you.
[Gasps ]
Balto, look!
On totem pole-
there is raven and wolf!
Calm down, Boris.
There's also a fox,
a wolverine-
Oy, such scary creatures!
They should only
live and be well...
far away from me.
And a bear and a caribou.
They're just wood carvings,
Boris.
Yes, I know, I know.
Humans use them
to tell stories.
But of what, I don't know.
Balto, maybe seeing raven
and wolf on totem pole...
is making you dream
something very important.
Well, like what?
Like something you forgot.
or maybe something
you are supposed to know.
Look, Boris, all I know is
that the totem pole marks
the shortcut to jenna's.
and that's good enough
for me.
Oh, boy!
Stubborn. Ach!
[ Yapping ]
[ Scottish Accent ]
Brrr! Oh!
There you are, laddies!
[Yapping]
I've been smelling all over
for you!
[ Continues Yapping ]
Would you stop with the bouncing
and make with the talking?
I'm getting dizzy!
[ Yapping, Panting ]
The stork has landed.
I repeat.
[ Yapping ]
the stork has landed!
jenna?jenna!
[ Yapping ]
What stork?
I thought we were
talking about raven.
Oh, boy. That stork.
I'm coming, Balto!
[ Continues Yapping ]
[ Sighs ]
- Hello, Balto.
- [ Gasps, Gulps ]
Well, come in.
They don't bite--
at least not yet.
[ Whimpering ]
Oh, jenna. They're--
they're so beautiful.
just like you.
[ Whimpering ]
And you.
Look at me!
I'm an uncle.
[ Yapping ]
[ Giggling ]
[ Laughing, Barking ]
[ Cawing ]
[ Continues Cawing ]
- Balto.
- jenna?
[ Continues Cawing ]
[Gasps ]
[ Panting ]
[ Sighs ]
Oh, I haven't had
that dream for a while.
Balto!
jenna?
Oh, no.
Good morning, sleepyhead.
Did you forget about
watching the pups today while
my girl and I go on a picnic?
What? Me? Forget?
[ Yawns ]
Never.
[ Barking, Laughing ]
Balto, you look so tired.
What's wrong?
Oh, nothing.
Hey, pups!
Good to see you too.
[ Laughing ]
Hey, watch it, now!
Come on. That tickles!
[ Growling, Barking ]
Say, why don't they spend the
night with me, and then tomorrow
we can all go on a picnic?
Balto, don't you remember?
Tomorrow is the day for our pups
to find their new homes.
Tomorrow?
But, jenna, they're-they're
only eight weeks old.
I mean, whats the hurry?
I know how you feel, Balto.
Puppy! Come to Uncle Boris!
[ Pups ]
Uncle Boris! Uncle Boris!
Oh, but it's their time now.
I was their age when I was
adopted by my girl.
But I - I don't think I can
let them go, jenna- not yet.
That's tickling me!
Ow! Ow! Ow!
[ Laughing ]
That's my wing!
Balto,
each of our children
have their own lives to live.
[ Boris Yelling ]
It's our job to love them
and then-
Let go!
If we wait until they're older,
it'll be harder for them
to find homes.
You know how humans have
a soft spot for puppies.
Yeah, and so do I.
Come on, Balto.
All their humans will be
from around here.
Oh! I've got to
go meet my girl now.
Enjoy them, Balto.
And watch out-
they're teething.
No kidding!
Come on now.
Uncle Boris isn't a chew toy.
[ All Barking ]
[ Growling ]
Hey, take it easy there,
tiger.
Oooh, oh!
[ Giggling ]
[ Mock Growling ]
Strange-- her brothers and
sisters look just like dogs.
yet Aleu looks just like--
A dog. Aleu looks
like a dog too.
[ Chuckling ]
Funny, but from where I stand,
I see daughter...
who looks even more wolf
than father.
Look, Boris,
I just don't want her to be...
different
But she is different!
And vive la difference!
[ Laughing ]
Come on.
Being different is painful.
Nobody knows that
better than me.
You know how some of the dogs
around here still tease me
because I'm half wolf?
оу.
Aleu may look like a wolf,
but she is going to be
all dog.
[ Howling ]
I wouldn't count on it.
Daddy, Daddy,
look at the puppies!
[ Howling ]
Aleu, honey, please
don't howl like that.
- [ Sighs ]
- Sorry, Mama.
It just happens
when I'm excited.
I'm excited too!
I can't wait to get a human...
and chew on their socks!
[ Giggles ]
Papa, are you gonna get
a human too?
Nah. See, humans like
cute little puppies like you.
not old grizzly grownups
like me.
These are Rosie's puppies,
Daddy. jenna had 'em.
[ Giggles]
I like this one.
I know that human.
He'll be a good boy for Dingo.
[ Puppies ]Bye! Bye-bye!
And my puppy can play with jenna
when Rosie and I play together.
Mommy, Mommy, look-- puppies!
[ Chuckling ]
Okay.
[ Woman ]
Somebody wants you
Somebody needs you
Someone is search ing
for уour heart alone
Someone is dreaming
waiting and watching
Someone is coming
to take you home
Time, it will fly
like the sun through the sky
And what once was hello
Turns to good-bye
He's so cute!
Oh, I love you!
Tomorrow is here now
Sings in your ear now
Child of my heart
Your life is уour own
Never you fear, now
Your path is clear now
Someone who loves you
Is taking you home
It's been a long day, jenna.
Let's go home.
But we can't. Well,
not until a human adopts Aleu.
Face it, jenna.
Aleu looks more like a wolf
than me
No human is
ever gonna want her.
That's not true!
We'll just
have to keep trying.
[Gasps ]
Hmm?
[ Snickers ]
[ Giggling ]
[ Both Chuckling ]
[ Both Scream ]
[ Whimpering ]
[ Panting ]
[ English Accent ] Right.
Who knew a game of hide-and-seek
could be so terrifyin'?
[ Snarling ]
[ Whimpering ]
[ Screaming ]
[ Howling ]
[ Whimpering ]
Okay, okay already!
Knock off the rough housing!
[ Whining ]
Oh--
Aleu, how can I baby-sit
if you won't sit?
You don't sit now here
for more than five seconds!
That's "anywhere, "
Uncle Boris.
[ Chuckling ]
What's anywhere?
Don't try to confuse me,
young lady.
I'm your baby-sitter.
Uncle Boris,
since I'm not a baby anymore,
I don't need a baby-sitter.
And you can tell that
to my father.
Come on, Aleu.
You'll always be my baby,
no matter how old you are.
Oh, you're hopeless.
Let's go.
What's going to happen
when a human picks me up,
huh. Papa?
Who are you
going to baby then?
Come on, guys!
She's a good pup.
"Good, " yes.
"Pup, " no.
At m ore than year old,
Aleu should have
home of her own.
When the right time comes,
she'll find a home.
Yes, but when
the right time comes.
will you let her?
Oy, I hope so.
[ Laughing, Whooping ]
Wheel
Ride 'em, cowboy!
Yippee!
[ Laughs ]
[ Cawing ]
[ Cawing Continues ]
[ Sniffing ]
[Gasps ]
No, it's a human.
He wouldn't hurt me.
Maybe he'll wanna adopt me.
[ Cawing ]
- [ Cawing ]
- [ Snarling ]
- [ Gun Firing ]
Sounds like trouble, mate.
[ Whimpering ]
Bears to the rescue!
[ Snarling ]
Papa, what's going on?
Stop!
Goose to the rescue!
[ Boris Yelling ]
- [ Shouting ]
- [ Whimpering ]
[ Crashing ]
[Balto ]
Is everyone all right?
[Gasps ]
Right as rain.
Come on.
We've gotta get outta here!
Aleu, now!
Whatsa matter?
You taking a nap?
Stand up! Come on!
Hurry up!
[ Gasping, Panting ]
Those spirits must be
trying to trick me.
I don't understand. Papa.
Why did you attack him?
What if he wanted
to adopt me?
Uh, guys?
Could you
help mе out here?
Oh, of course.
Oh! Uh, sorry, mate.
but a wise polar bear always
minds his own business.
[ Clears Throat ]
It is my opinion that-
Waah!
- Well?
- Okay.
See, that hunter was
looking for wild animals
to kill...
for food and fur.
So?
I'm not a wild animal.
Well, he thought you were.
[Gasps ]
What? Why?
He thought
you were a wolf.
Oh.
I knew there was
something wrong with me.
There is nothing wrong with you.
You have a proud heritage.
Oh, sure.
- Your mother is a purebred Husky.
- Then what are you?
I-I'm the one
who's part wolf.
How could this happen?
Look, Aleu,
my dad was a Husky
who had pups with a wolf.
Great. My grandmother
was a wild animal?
Did the wolf teach you
how to know when a human
wants to kill you?
I was accidentally separated
from her when I was young.
so, I-I never
spent much time with...
the wolf.
But I remember
that she was as white as snow.
that she had this warm voice
that made me feel safe.
Well, then Boris
took me in, and...
after being raised
by a goose, it's a wonder
I don't honk instead of bark.
Why didn't you
tell me this before?
Because... I wanted
to protect you.
Protect me? From what--
from the fact
that no human will ever want me
because I'm part wild animal?
Aleu, I-
And what about
my brothers and sisters?
They've got wolf in them too.
Why did humans want them?
Because they don't look it.
[ Sighs ]
and you do.
It's not fair.
I hate you!
[ Sobbing ]
Aleu!
Aleu, come back!
Leave me alone!
[ Sighs ]
[ Honking ]
[ Panting ]
Where do I belong?
[ Moaning ]
What is it?
What do you want?
[ Panting ]
[ Moans ]
[ Yelling ]
[ Cawing ]
[ Cawing Continues ]
[Female Voce]
My son, you need to know
the animal totems...
who will help guide you now.
The fox—
the cunning trickster.
The wolverine-
your fears.
The bear
inner knowing.
Cart bou- life.
[ Howling ]
[ Moaning ]
Huh? Oh.
[ Balto Sighs ]
[ Sniffing ]
Huh?
[ Chuckles ]
What are you two doing?
Shh!
We're here to play with Aleu.
- [ Chuckles ]
- [Crashing ]
But Aleu's not here
to play.
No, no, no, no.
[ Groans ]
She's around here
somewhere, I--
Wait a minute.
You mean you can't find her?
Uh, no.
No, no.
I just wanted
to give her some time.
I was sure she'd come home.
She's gotta be
at her mother's.
[ Sniffling, Sobbing ]
I know.
I wish we had a mum too.
[ Both Sobbing ]
jenna!
Balto! What are you
doing here so early?
Is Aleu all right?
I don't know.
I was hoping
she was with you.
She's... kinda mad at me.
Stay there.
Now, tell me what happened.
A hunter took aim at her.
[Gasps ]
No, no, don't worry.
We got away.
But I-- I finally had to
tell her how humans see her.
You mean, you told her
about being part--
Yes. We should have done it
sooner. I know that now.
She's so angry with me.
She must have run away.
Run away?
I'm sorry, jenna.
I never thought it would
turn out this way.
I thought I could keep her safe.
But she's not safe now.
She's running wild!
- We've got to find her.
- No, not you, jenna.
This is my fault, and it's
something that Aleu and I
have to work out together.
Don't worry. I'll find her.
Oh.
[ Sniffing ]
[Gasps ]
[ Cawing ]
You.
What is it you want?
[ Continues Cawing ]
- Am I supposed to follow you?
- [ Cawing ]
All right. But only if
you help me find my daughter.
Wait!
I can't follow you in this.
Where are you?
[Female Voice]
Wnere are you ?
Here. Keep talking,
and I'll find you.
Uh- Mmm-
[Mother's Voice]
A cunning trickster.
You look disappointed.
Sorry. I--
I just thought
you might be a raven.
And I thought
that you might be a hunter.
But unlike you,
I'm not disappointed.
Say, I'll help you find
your daughter if you'll
help me out of this trap.
- How did you know
I'm looking for my daughter?
- The raven told me.
What do you know
about the raven?
Less than you, I'm sure.
Now, do we have a deal,
or don't we?
Yes. But no tricks.
[ Grunting ]
There. Now, how can you
help me find my daughter?
Easy. By giving you
a little push.
[ Yelling ]
[ Gasping ]
Why did you do that?
Help me!
[ Chuckling ]
Oh, but I did.
And now you must
help yourself.
Are you crazy?
The current is too strong!
Then let the current
take you!
[ Yelling ]
[ Burps ]
- [ Chuckling ]
- [ Croaking ]
Huh!
[ Inhaling ]
What are you
meshugenah bears doing?
Uh, gee, Uncle Boris,
Luc and me-- we was just tryin'
to communicate with the toad.
Communicate with toad.
Ribbit
Yeah, see there?
Luc just asked it
if it's seen Aleu.
[ Croaking ]
You bears are
a bagel short of a bushel.
I don't know why
I put up with you.
Sorry, Uncle Boris.
Do you still need us?
Yes.
Like a hole in the head.
Now, close your mouths...
and keep nose out for them.
[ Sniffing ]
Ann! Ann! Ann!
[ Muffled Exclaiming ]
[ Muffled Shouting ]
Now what? You two have
ants in pants?
[ Squawks ]
Balto!
[Faint ]
Balto, can you hear me?
Boris?
Don't worry, boychik!
Boris is coming!
What's happening,
Uncle Boris?
I don't know.
I can't see nothing.
[ Shouting ]
Balto!
Balto! Balto!
[ Sniffing ]
It's Aleu!
- Answer me!
- Boris, I've got Aleu's trail.
Go back and tell jenna
not to worry. I'm going to
find Aleu and bring her home.
Oy. Come,
we do as Balto says
and go tell jenna.
But Uncle Boris,
Luc and me wanted to go
on a journey.
I'm sorry, boys,
but this journey is
for Balto and Aleu alone.
[jenna ]
What do you mean,
'he just ran off"?
I mean, he's got Aleu's scent.
Told me to tell you
not to worry, and away he went.
He's a wolf on a mission.
I'm going to go help him look.
[Gasps ]
No, jenna!
This is a journey
for father and daughter.
You must have faith in them.
You're sure
Balto has her trail?
- Mm-hmm.
- And you're sure
Balto's all right?
Don't worry, jenna.
Remember, they're well-equipped.
They are both part wolf.
[Mother's Vote]
Your fears.
I have no reason to fight
the wolverine clan.
What do you want?
You invade our territory.
Only to
pass through unharmed.
I'm looking for my daughter.
He's looking for his daughter.
[ Laughs Evilly ]
Yes, and he's following
a raven.
A raven?
Why not a fox?
Or did she outwit you?
[ Wolverines Laugh ]
Tell me, are you afraid?
[ All Laugh ]
- No!
- [ Growling ]
Come now.
Are you sure, huh?
[ Snarls, Laughs ]
[ Growling ]
Okay, okay, I'm afraid.
Of course you are!
And you must
listen to your fears.
Let them lead you
back to the safety
of your cozy little home.
[ Growling ]
Look how he's giving in
to the fear.
Yes, soon he'll run home...
like the whimpering dog
that he is!
No! I'm afraid,
but not of you.
[ Snarling Lessens ]
I'm afraid for my daughter,
and I have to find her,
so get out of my way!
Stop following the raven.
[ Echoing ]
Go home! Go home!
[ Fading ]
Go home!
Huh?
[ Sniffing ]
It's like they were...
never here.
[ Panting ]
What am I doing?
I'm running away.
but I have no idea
where I'm going.
I've got to
get out of the sun.
[ Cawing ]
[Gasps ]
[ Sighs ]
Are you following me?
[ Continues Cawing ]
A cave.
At least it'll be
dark and cool inside.
[ Singing, Faint ]
[ Continues ]
[ Continues, Louder ]
- [ Crunching]
- [ Gasping ]
Praise for the red dawn
Grass that we walk upon
Praise for the river's
whispered tune
Praise for the wind brother
Praise for the earth mother
Praise for father sun
And sister moon
Hey-ya, hey-ya, hey-ya
[ Howling ]
- Hey-ya, hey-ya, hey-ya [ Howling ]
Your singing is quite beautiful.
Oh, thank you.
Sometimes I just
can't help myself.
I'm sorry.
Did I interrupt you?
Oh, no!
I love to hear wolves sing.
It's one of your specialties.
[ Laughing ]
You also have such
a keen sense of smell.
[ Sighs ]
Such wonderful creatures
you are.
I'm not a wolf.
Oh! Then that is why
I'm not afraid of you.
[ Chuckles ]
Why should I be afraid
of one who does not know
who she is?
I know who I am. I am Aleu,
daughter of Balto and jenna.
who happens to be
a purebred Husky.
Who are you?
[ Growls ]
I am Muru,
son of Kahu and Quilac,
both of them
simple field mice.
This answer tells us what
we are, but not who we are.
Okay. Then how do I
find out who I am?
What... are you doing?
Wow!
I am shedding light...
where darkness lies.
When every creature
in the world is born,
a spirit stands beside them.
Why?
To light their way through
the long, dark night...
and sing them songs
to guide them.
Why?
Because each of us has a destiny
that sets us all apart.
The path is different
for you and mе,
but the journey begins
in the heart.
You must go to the east.
Go to the west
The road is rocky
and the way is far
It's a dangerous trail
a difficult quest
If you want to know
Who you really are
There are voices
all around you
То comfort
and to guide you
Fathers and teachers
powerful creatures
And a voice
That sings inside you
[ Various Voices]
Or you can
turn back around
Run along home
Back to the place
where уour friends are
Perhaps that is best
You need the rest
Who wants to go
on a ridiculous quest
Unless you want to know
You truly want to know
Wno you really are
Wno are you
Who are you
Muru, are you
my spirit guide?
Are you here to help me?
[ Мuru ]
Have faith and trust
in yourself.
And make the journey.
Muru?
Muru!
- [ Gasps ]
- [ Snarling, Roaring ]
[ Panting ]
[Roaring ]
[ Roaring ]
Papa!
- Glad you're still
speaking to me.
- [ Roars ]
- Save yourself. Papa!
- What? And miss
all the excitement?
[ Grunting ]
[ Roaring ]
Oh, no, you don't!
[ Grunting ]
[ Gasping ]
Papa!
[ Grunting ]
I'll hold him off.
You run for it.
No, I'll hold him off
and you run for it!
There's no time to argue.
I'm your father.
You do what I say!
And I say I'm too big
to be ordered around!
[ Snarling ]
[ Panting ]
How did you get
so stubborn?
I take after you,
remember?
[ Growling ]
[ Roars ]
Wow.
[Mother's Voice]
Inner knowing.
We've got to jump.
[ Grunts ]
But we'll be killed.
And we'll be killed
if we don't.
[ Barks ]
I hope you're right.
You knew
the ledge was here.
Yeah, I did, sorta.
How?
I looked
at the bear-- No.
I looked at his thoughts,
and I saw it.
Why did you come
and find me?
I came to bring you
home, Aleu.
No. I don't wanna go home--
not until I find out
who I am.
[ Chuckles Softly ]
That's ridiculous, Aleu.
You know who you are.
No. I know what I am,
but not who I am.
- And I'm not stopping
until I find out.
- Then I'm coming with you.
- Oh, Papa.
- [ Sniffing ]
It's saltwater. Aleu,
we're close to the ocean.
Come on.
[ Cawing ]
[Balto ]
I sure would like to know why
I keep seeing that raven.
You've been
following a raven?
Huh. Yeah.
I know it sounds dumb.
I've been
seeing this raven
in my dreams.
Your dreams?
Mm-hmm.
I only followed it
because it promised to
help me find you.
[ Exhales ]
I've been seeing a raven too.
- I wasn't sure if
I was following it or-
- You think that could be them?
[ Flies Buzzing ]
[ Russian Accent ]
It's "beating" me.
What do you think,
Nuk, huh?
[ Growls ]
I don't think. I just eat.
It's more filling.
[ Snorting ]
What are you waiting for?
Get them!
[ Whimpering ]
[ Grumbling ]
[ Yells ]
Okay, okay.
You don't have to yell.
[ Cawing ]
Why a raven?
Why here?
I wish I knew.
[ Sniffing ]
What is it?
Company. And it
doesn't smell friendly.
[ Balto ]
Let's get out of here.
See anything?
No. Maybe I was wrong.
[Gasps ]
Look, Papa!
Oh, I love it here.
It's so wild. Come on!
Don't go out too far, Aleu.
The tide's coming in fast.
I'll be fine.
Mm.
I don't like you
being out here.
You could slip and fall.
Papa, you've got
to stop worrying about me.
[ Wolves Growling ]
And start worrying
about us.
[ Snickering ]
[ Growling ]
Yes, us.
because we're-
[ Laughs Maniacally ]
mean.
Right, Nuk?
Yeah, especially
when I'm hungry.
Look, we don't want any trouble.
This is your territory.
We'll just go.
Sorry, but
you are not going...
nowhere!
That's "anywhere, "
flea bag.
Aleu, I hardly think
this is the time to be
correcting his grammar.
- Papa.
- [ All Growling ]
[ Cawing ]
- [ Raven Caws ]
- [ All Yelling ]
At least we know
the raven's on our side.
Come on. We can take 'em.
Aleu, no!
[ Aleu Grunts ]
[ Aleu Growling ]
[ Yelping ]
[ Growling ]
[ Gasping, Straining ]
[Nuk]
Bye-bye, doggy.
- [Balto]
Aleu!
- Ow!
[ Straining ]
[ Wolves Growling ]
Aw, and I thought
all doggies could swim.
[ Flies Buzzing ]
Yeah, yeah.
And don't they all go
to heaven?
[ Laughing]
"Doggies go to heaven. "
[ Snorts ] Oops.
The tide is coming.
[Gasps ]
Get out of here!
- [ All Gasping ]
- Get back there,
you sniveling cowards.
But, Niju, the tide!
We'll drown.
Yes, there's
always that chance.
But, then,
if you don't take it,
I'll make sure you drown.
If those two live,
they'll take what's left
of our food.
[ All Murmuring,
Growling ]
Stop! Clear a path
for our visitors.
- Now.
- [ Whimpering ]
[ Scoffs ]
I will not
let them go, Nava.
I will not let you,
an aging fool, destroy us
with your weakness!
- I admire your passion, Niju,
- [ Snorts ]
but do not mistake
my old age for weakness,
nor your youth for strength.
I ask again:
Will you clear the way
for our visitors?
No.
[ Niju Barks ]
Some day your tricks
will not be enough
to save you.
[ Growling ]
I am sorry it had
to be this way, Niju.
Thanks for your help.
You're welcome.
But it is I who thank you
for coming at last.
- You knew we were coming?
- Of course.
- It was I who sent for you.
- [ Aleu Gasps ]
[ Wolf Howls, Distant ]
[ Wolves Murmuring ]
My brothers and sisters,
our summer is almost passed,
and I have listened to the trees
and to the blades of grass.
And they have said this:
The caribou will not
return this year...
[ All Murmuring ]
nor any other year,
for they have crossed
the Great Water.
[ Wolves Gasping ]
If we are to survive,
we must follow them.
[ Scoffs ] The old one
believes that trees
and grass can talk.
It is time to realize
that our leader has
lost his ability to lead.
[ Wolves Murmuring ]
How dare you say that!
Yes, Nava has always
led us well.
- [ Growling ]
- Stop! Let him speak.
It is his right.
Nava would have us
leave the land that has been
our clan's home for generations.
So what if the caribou
do not return this year?
- This does not mean
they will not come again.
- Niju could be right.
And he could be wrong.
If we do stay, how will we
survive without the caribou?
- They bring us life.
- Simple. We take what we need
from other clans.
Steal from others?
It isn't right.
When you're hungry,
there is no "right. "
Yes, there is a "right"--
our right to survive.
And if we eat the food
of other clans, what
will they eat?
That is not our concern.
Is not the balance
of our world the concern
of all?
If we steal from other clans,
those clans will be forced
to steal as well.
Soon, we will all
be fighting for less
and less food.
Uh-oh. "Less and less food. "
That sounds bad,
doesn't it. Sumac?
Oh, yeah.
Yeah. Really bad.
Unless you're on diet.
Who's on a diet?
Aniu, the white wolf, has come
to me in dream visions...
and has told me
what we must do.
She said we must move on,
and we must be led...
by the one who is wolf
and does not know.
Huh?
Papa?
Look, I'm flattered.
Really.
I mean,
I've led a dog team before,
but never a wolf pack.
[ Cackling ]
See here.
Our wise leader, who visits
with the great Aniu
only in his dreams,
- has brought a mutt
to guide us.
- [ All Laughing ]
- What a "mutt"?
- Beats me.
- [ Aleu Growls ]
- [ Both Growling ]
- [Balto]
It's all right, Aleu.
His blood may be pure,
but his motives aren't.
[ Growling Continues ]
I say Niju is afraid
to cross the Great Water.
-[ All Gasping ]
-I am not afraid, but crossing
the Great Water is impossible!
We cannot swim it.
We would all die.
So now I, Niju,
say Nava must step down,
and let a true leader
take his place.
I will step down, Niju,
when a true leader
takes my place.
[ Snarling ]
Show yourself, Nava.
Your magic tricks
will not stop me.
[ Growls ]
I will be a leader
who does not depend
on foolish dreams!
Those who will, follow me!
[ Wolves Murmuring ]
How did you do that?
I simply became one
with the tree.
If I tried that,
I'd get splinters.
Would you teach me?
It is a thing
that cannot be taught.
One just knows.
But now we must speak
of how you will lead us
to the caribou.
Nava, I don't understand
how I can lead you anywhere.
[Aleu Thinking]
Caribou.
I had these dreams,
but I don't even know
what they mean.
Each of us
has a unique gift.
Perhaps your dreams
show us the way.
[ Aleu Thinking ]
Nava must be right.
[ Raven Cawing ]
This has gone too far,
Aleu, and it isn't our battle.
But, Papa,
I saw caribou.
Look, this
could get very dangerous.
Despite my dreams
or anything else, I will not
put you in any danger.
But this isn't
just about us anymore.
Papa.
This is about something bigger.
Don't you see? We're
supposed to help them.
I'm sorry,
but whether I stay or go
should be my decision.
[ Wind Whistling]
That wind is a sign
that winter's coming early.
Your mother
will be worried sick.
We both leave in the morning.
[ Raven Cawing ]
[ Cawing ]
[Gasps ]
A star dies,
and another is born.
All is a great dance
of balance.
You have questions.
Why is Niju so against
moving the clan?
What is he afraid of?
Niju is not a coward.
He is not afraid to die,
but he is afraid of change.
He would rather face starvation
than leave the land
he believes is ours.
This world through
which we wander...
is wonderful
and strange.
The only truth
we can really know...
is that everything
will change.
[ Chorus ]
Like the rain
that fills the ocean
Like the storm
that shakes the pine
We are all a part...
We are all a part
of the grand design.
Of the grand design
This has been our home forever!
This is where the clan belongs.
[Thunderclap ]
[ Chorus ]
We were born
beside this river
And we filled the night
with songs
- [ Howling ]
- We must fight
for what belongs to us
What is уours
and what is mine
We are all the masters
of our own design.
The land no more
belongs to us
Than the eagle
owns the sky
We must fight
for our survival
If we don't
we'll surety die
[ Howling ]
[Nava's Voice]
We are one with
what at surrounds us,
brothers to all we see.
[Chorus Vocalizing]
[Niju's Voice ]
We are wolves.
We take what we need...
to stay alive and free.
[ Wolves Howling ]
[ Chorus ]
The one thing
we will surety learn
As we walk the path
of timе
No one can ever
rise above
We are wolves,
the masters of!
[ Chorus ]
We are all a part
Of the grand design
[Chorus Vocalizing]
We strike the bear clan first.
[All]
Yeah I Yeah I
[ All Barking ]
-You're not
striking anyone, Niju.
-You're outnumbered, half-breed.
[ Growling ]
Papa!
Nava is right,
Aleu.
Following the caribou
is choosing life. I can't
ignore my dreams any longer.
- Your dreams will lead to our deaths!
- No, I've seen it too, Niju.
We must follow the caribou
across the water.
Staying here would mean
starvation for the clan.
- Hear that?
- She has seen it too.
- Maybe Niju is the fool.
I've heard enough.
You will not stop us.
Take them!
[ Growling ]
[ Barks ]
Look!
Aniu told me the time to leave
would come with the great
breaking of the ice.
but more than that,
I do not know.
The ice floes
are lining up.
It's like they're
making a bridge.
[Aleu ]
A bridge to the caribou.
Last winter, the caribou
crossed an ice bridge
to land on the other side.
and now that bridge
is forming again.
Now I understand.
- If we're to cross,
we must go now.
- [ Murmuring ]
The old one
spoke the truth
about Balto.
We must go!
I'm running now.
This is me running.
[ Yelps ]
And just where do you think
you three are going?
Urn, I know I don't usually...
make thinking a habit,
but Nava is right.
Besides, I'm hungry.
Come on, boys. Let's
go find some caribou.
Get back here!
I order you!
The ice path will
only hold for a short time.
Buddy up, then
stick with your partner in case
either of you needs help.
I'll lead. Mush!
Uh, I mean, move out!
No! You'll all die!
Nava!
[Indistinct Murmuring]
[ Grunting ]
[ Wolf ]
Let them go!
[Balto] Aleu!
[Wolf #2 ]
Nava!
[ Panting ]
[ Straining ]
[ Gasping ]
Aleu,
are you all right?
Yes. You go on
with the rest of the pack.
I'll get Nava.
[ All Murmuring ]
Be careful, Aleu.
[ Growling ]
[ Gasping ]
[ Gasps, Groans ]
[ Snarling ]
The old ways will die
along with you, old one.
[ Resumes Snarling ]
[ Aleu ]
Stop!
- You!
- [ Growls ]
I will teach you
to mind your place!
My place?
[ Both Grunting, Growling ]
[ Panting ]
- Niju, leave her be!
- Huh?
- [ Gasps ]
- Papa, you should be
with the rest of the clan.
-You've got to lead them across.
-I will, once I take care of him.
[ Growls ]
[ Raven Caws]
[ Whimpering ]
- [ Nava ]
We must go.
- No!
- No one's going anywhere.
- But the clan!
They've chosen their fate.
Now they will die.
Nava, Aleu and I
can hold Niju off
while you get to the clan.
- They need someone
to lead them.
- But, Papa,
Nava won't be able
to make the swim.
She is right.
Only my spirit
is strong now.
You wanted
to be a leader, Niju.
Well, now's your chance.
Go!
[Gasps ]
I-- I-I won't.
[ Groans ]
I'll never
leave our land. Never!
- [ Yells, Grunts ]
- [ Aleu Gasps ]
Papa!
[ Grunting ]
[ Whimpering Continues ]
I can help you
swim over, Nava.
No. You're right.
You won't make it.
I'll go.
No. You don't
belong here. Papa.
You belong home
with my mother.
But I do belong here.
It's my destiny.
Aniu told me
it would be the one...
who is wolf
but does not know.
I believed it was you,
but I was wrong.
It is your daughter.
Are you sure?
It's just so hard
to let my baby go.
Papa, I'm not your--
Okay. So I'll
always be your baby.
Good-bye, Papa.
Tell Mom I've finally
found my home.
[Gasps ]
[ Howls ]
Good-bye, daughter.
[ All Howling ]
[ Howls ]
She will be a great leader.
And now it is time
for you to go home.
What about you?
You're alone now.
Where will you go?
I will find Niju.
We are still a clan...
and would not be whole
without each other.
Good-bye, my brother.
[ Cawing ]
[ Groans ]
Now what?
Only the journey home,
my son.
Aniu, you're my--
[ Howls ]
Good-bye
to you, too. Mother.
[ Woman ]
Somebody wants you
Somebody needs you
Someone is searching
for уour heart alone
Someone is dreaming
waiting and watching
Someone is coming
То take you home
Time, it will fly
like the sun through the sky
And what once was hello
Turns to good-bye
Tomorrow is here now
Sings in your ear now
Child of my heart
your life is уour own
Never you fear, now
Your path is clear now
Someone who loves you
Is taking you home
[Man ]
On-ho
On, yeah
Oh-ho
Oh, yeah