( barking )
Everything,
everything flies
Da, da, da,
da, da, da, dah
Everything,
everything flies
-  Ah-ooo
- Hike!
Ah-ooo.
( bird twitters )
( chuckles )
Well, wake me up
when it arrives.
( motor whirring )
Huh?
Isn't it beautiful?
Come on, Jenna!
( panting )
I'm soaring
above the clouds,
free.
( growls playfully )
Huh, didn't think so.
Good girl.
( bell rings )
- Oh my!
- ( mimics bears growls )
What in the name
of Yukon Jack is that?
Mel:
Trouble,
that's what it is.
- ( barking )
- Hiyah! Hiyah!
Mush, mush!
Whoa, whoa.
- Fire us?
- ( laughing )
Hey there,
Mr. Simpson.
- ( yells, crashes )
- I'm okay.
What's here?
Hey, boy.
A dog welcoming committee, huh?
Why don't you guard my plane
for a few minutes?
I'll be back soon.
I would if I could.
So where's Boris?
( singing in Russian )
( singing continues )
( screams )
It's my first trip to Nome
and I like what I see so far.
But my friends
are calling me...
( honking )
Put me down.
- Not another game of--
- Slosh!
Three!
No, no, no!
- well--
- See you then, hot stuff.
Balto! Balto!
"Boris, come right away.
It's an emergency!"
Now you go.
Psst!
No, of course not.
Just a little.
Come on, Boris.
I have an idea.
Nothing! What do you
think I see?
in, in absurd,
illogical way.
except I have no idea
where I'm going.
( branches rustle )
You got it.
Now-- open your eyes.
( screams )
I am the goose!
- ( crashes )
- Ah!
Duke:
It'll be an honor to work for
you and the US mail, Mr. Connor.
Ohhhh!
Oh yeah.
( barking )
( barks echoing )
( barks )
( barking )
( icicles clattering )
( snores )
( barking continues )
( barking )
Whoa! Yikes!
You can count on me!
The most famous dog
in Nome.
Huh, now I looking good!
Stella:
Well, hi there,
flyboy.
( groaning )
- Sit down, Boris.
- Huh?
Let me tell ya something.
- ( honking )
- Come on down, boys.
On the loose
( laughs stupidly )
Chorus:
Bak, bak, bak, bak
On my own,
up here in Nome
Come on up
and do a little
Flying with me-eee.
Bye... Boris.
- I can't beat it.
- That could be problem.
- Let's do the call!
- ( howling )
If I'm in pain,
I cannot fly, yes?
( howling )
( sighs )
How can I look Kodi
in the eyes if we lose?
The great Balto
who saved Nome.
Oh, Balto.
He needs to know
you care
You've done
all you can do
( puppies barking )
If you give it
your best
You just
have to be you
Oooh-hhh...
you'll always be
his hero.
He will always
have a hero
have a hero...
Have you...
( sniffs )
( sniffing )
You saved a lot of lives
in that diphtheria scare.
That was some storm.
It's okay.
soaring above the clouds,
free.
Maybe just a few.
So, honey, what else
can I do to get you
back on your wings?
- Little to the left.
- Here?
Who knows
what could happen then.
Say, tomorrow?
Oh, mmm.
This is
gonna be great, Dad.
Oooh, oy, the pain!
I am a genius.
I am suddenly all better.
You don't know whole story.
( screaming )
Ouch! No! Oy!
( barking, howls )
Get set!
Ha! Hey! Hike!
( barking )
( engine grinding )
C'mon.
C'mon!
Go, go, go!
Oy! Ow!
We gotta
slow down.
Or not.
- Keep in line, boys.
- Kirby: You got it, Balto.
( groans )
C'mon, everybody.
( panting )
Oh no!
Don't give up now.
Ha, hi!
Thanks, Duke.
Here's the return batch
for you.
( plane engine cranking )
Oof!
( barking )
Thanks.
Let's load you up
for the return trip.
This mail goes
right back to Nome.
Good luck to you.
- ( barking )
- Boris: I am coming!
I'm going to spend the rest
of my days in White Mountain.
- I am--
- ( scraping )
--going home!
Ice, gotta get it off
the wings before I can fly.
Whew.
Ahhh-oh!
or-- never mind.
- Uh, go ahead, Dipsy.
- Thanks, I don't mind
if I do.
( barking )
Move, move, move!
( Boris honking )
Oy, I'm about
to lose my lunch.
Balto:
And we're beating it.
Whoa, whoa there.
I'm okay, I'm okay.
Do you hear the plane
anymore, Dad?
No.
Where the heck am I?
Come on, baby.
Oy!
- Not the plane?
- ( dogs barking )
Balto!
- They did it?
- I don't believe it.
Easy, easy!
( cheering, barking )
( howls )
Yeah, if this doesn't
prove us dogs rule--
what does?
But I've seen them.
We can't do this
every time.
You're just wrong.
( laughing continues )
Yeah... yeah, we do.
And we're gonna keep them.
Come on, let's go.
Balto!
Both:
The bush plane!
Oy! Ow! Ohh!
I must get help.
( grunts )
I thought the difference is
only one has a heart.
Who's coming with me?
Dad, wait!
And it served him right,
the stinker.
What?
in that funny way
on his neck-- you know?
Wish me luck, boys!
( screams )
Come on,
let's get going.
They'll be looking
for that bush plane for weeks.
Listen, if anyone
can find him, Balto can.
Yeah, Mom.
( sighs )
I should have gone
with Balto.
( wind moaning )
Oh, he's probably griping about
what's taking us so long.
Onward.
( yells )
( gasping )
( snickers )
if you have a thing
for polar bears.
Mmm-- huh?
( cracking )
( screaming )
This is no time
to be playing games!
( grunting )
Whoa!
Help, Stella-aaa!
- Help!
- Quick, grab my leg.
What was I thinking?
( groans )
Hang on, Balto.
Hurry!
Depends how you feel
about waterfalls.
( bears crying )
( crashes )
- No more!
- ( pants )
Ha, the big talker.
I'm not sure
that's what I want to be.
- Sharp and strong!
- ( growling )
Back in a flash,
fellas.
I'm going over.
( gasps )
Boris!
Where are you?
Come on!
Move those buns,
fellas.
- Balto: No...
- Muc: Uncle Boris!
( snorts )
We're talking
to you!
Now he gets it.
( screams )
I think
you're talking to me.
Ha!
- Balto, talk to me, honey.
- ( snorts )
Come on, sugar, this isn't
a good time for a snooze.
- ( Balto grunts )
- ( growls )
Male voice:
Hey, lamebrain!
Yeah, I'm looking at one.
( growling )
Where are you?
But I could swear he--
( gasps )
Luc says
he's found him!
You owe me an apology!
- it was enough!
- Easy does it, Luc.
( groans )
Come on, Stella,
we're going to take
Uncle Boris home.
( groans )
( sighs )
I guess I won't be
walking back to Nome.
( grunting )
What? Oh!
Oh no!
( groans )
Hang in there, boy.
Now what?
Kodi?
( howls )
Right on time, Son.
- Don't count him out.
- ( distant howling )
( howling )
( melancholy howl )
- Kodi!
- ( murmuring )
Good dogs!
Good boy, Balto.
( townspeople exclaiming )
- I knew he could do it.
- I lost my appetite.
I forgot to say
you were a rotten, lying,
good-for-nothing snow goose!
Now that's more like it.
I like it already.
( honking )
Hey!
Hey, there he is!
Living out a dream.
La, da, da, da, dah
Everything,
everything flies
The trout
that breaks the stream
Everything,
everything flies
Oh-hhh!
Everything flies
Everything flies.