-== [ www.OpenSubtitles.org ] ==-
This has been a long time coming, fellas.
Three years on the plates alone.
But I think you'll find the product
was worth the wait. Go ahead.
Take a good look, boys.
Jeez, Mr. Sol, I can't tell the difference.
You'd need one of them
neutron microscopes, Palmer.
It's identical,
down to Ben Franklin's stubble.
I want it laundered at a half mil a week.
Three-quarter mil by March.
Anybody got a problem with that?
The Bat!
Get him!
Chuckie Sol.
Batman! How did you get here?
Your angel of death awaits.
You ain't the Bat!
Who... Who are you? What do you want?
I want you, Chuckie boy.
This time I got you, you lousy, stinking...
What...
- Look at that!
- Good Lord!
- What happened?
- Look! It's Batman!
- Up there!
- Oh, my God.
I'm telling you, friends,
it's vigilantism at its deadliest.
How many times are we gonna
let Batman cross the line?
I'm sorry, councilman, but you can't blame
Batman for what happened to Chuckie Sol.
Why not? He's a loose cannon, commissioner.
It's not just my opinion. A lot of people,
including the police, I might add...
...think Batman's as unstable
as the crooks he brings in.
What kind of city are we running...
...when we depend on the support
of a potential madman?
Such rot, sir.
Why, you're the very model of sanity.
Oh, by the way, I pressed your tights
and put away your exploding gas balls.
Thank you, Alfred.
Might one inquire what this is?
A piece of windshield from Chuckie Sol's car.
There's a chemical residue on it.
Some kind of dense, long-chain
macromolecular polymer.
Adaptogenic, of course.
Of course.
I should be landing any minute.
- It'll be good to see you again, Arthur.
- You too.
And don't worry about a thing.
We'll clear up these old family finances.
Don't forget, you've got a bigtime
city councilman on your side.
I can't believe it's been 10 years.
Thinking of looking up some old friends?
Oh, Arthur, don't start that again.
He's ancient history.
That's encouraging. I'll see you soon.
Oh, come on, Bruce.
All alone in this big mansion.
Haven't you ever thought
about marriage, even once?
Oh, never say the M word in front of Bruce.
It makes him nervous.
What about the I word?
- The I word?
- "Ingagement."
I'd watch out for Brucie
if I were you, girls.
First he wines and dines you...
...makes you think you're the only
woman he's ever been interested in.
And just when you're wondering
where to register the china...
...he forgets your phone number.
That's Bruce Wayne's style.
- Bruce?
- Excuse me.
Oh, God. It's awful.
Bruce? Bruce?
- A friend in need?
- Councilman.
- So how goes the Bat bashing?
- Better than your love life.
It's almost as if you pick them because you
know there's no chance for a relationship.
At least since that one girl.
What was her name? Anne? Andi?
Andrea? Yes! Andrea Beaumont.
Now, there was a sweet number.
How did you let her get loose?
Thanks for the handkerchief, Arthur.
You know where you can stick it.
Andrea.
That's right. And if Daddy
gets any more protective...
...he's going to build a moat
around my bedroom.
Oh, it's times like this
I wish you were around to...
- Yes?
- Excuse me.
I thought you were saying something.
Well, to me, I mean.
No.
Okay.
Know who that was? Bruce Wayne.
You know, Wayne Enterprises.
I've seen him on campus. Very moody.
Cute, though.
- Yes?
- I heard my name. I thought...
- Who are you talking to?
- My mother.
- Oh, well, I didn't mean to...
- That's okay. We're done.
Mom doesn't have much to say today.
I'm not the only one who talks
to their loved ones, you know.
I didn't say anything.
It's just that when I talk to her out loud,
I can imagine how she'd reply.
I can hear her, like she's right there.
I've talked to my parents.
- What did you say?
- I made a vow.
- What vow?
- A secret one.
Ooh, a man of mystery.
Have you kept your vow?
So far.
- Andrea Beaumont.
- Bruce Wayne.
I know. The boy billionaire. So tell me,
with all that money and power...
...how come you always look like
you wanna jump off a cliff?
- Why should you care?
- I don't.
Mother was asking.
Let's step on it. We ain't got all night.
Wait for me!
- Coming through.
- Okay, Skaz. We're done shopping.
All clear here.
Well, Bruce, here goes.
Let's blow this pop stand.
On your stomachs, arms spread!
- Who's this clown?
- You heard me!
Yeah, you heard him, boys.
- You heard Mr. Kung Fu.
- Yeah, I'm shaking.
Say your prayers, sucker!
Yes!
Excuse me.
Hey, Jonesy. There!
I read about your anonymous exploits
this morning, and I must say...
...are you sure you won't reconsider rugby?
Sorry, Alfred, but the plan is working.
I had the edge. I could feel it.
There was only one thing wrong:
They weren't afraid of me.
I must strike fear in them from the start.
Pardon, Master Bruce, but we may want
to postpone the shoptalk, as it were.
I believe you have a visitor.
Hi. Hey, what happened to you?
Trip over some loose cash?
It's been three days since we met,
and still no calls.
I figured you must be dead or something.
You expect every guy you meet to call you up?
The ones that are smart enough
to dial a phone.
- What is that?
- Jujitsu.
Gesundheit.
- That was a joke.
- Jujitsu is no joke.
It takes years to master.
Hey!
Got a few moves of my own.
Miss Hovey's self-defense class for girls.
He laughs.
Nice footwork. Can you dance too?
Oh.
Pardon, sir, but Miss Bambi
is dancing on the piano.
Brucie! Where are you?
- You guys wait here.
- Whatever you say, Mr. Bronski.
- They say the Bat iced this guy.
- I know.
Tut, tut. Chuckie, Chuckie.
You always were a loser.
- Buzz.
- Huh?
Who's there?
Buzz Bronski. Your angel of death awaits.
Get away from me, you freak!
Time to pay for your sins, Mr. Bronski.
Buzz.
All right, creep. Catch this!
What the...
Dave! Dougan!
Boys!
Come on!
He was up here!
- Boss? Boss! Boss!
- Boss! Boss!
Boys! Hurry!
You always were a loser, Mr. Bronski.
Farewell, Mr. Bronski.
- Boss!
Oh, man.
Hey!
It's the Bat!
It's the stinking Bat!
Buzz!
No!
What do you mean, you won't?
You have to go after him.
He didn't do it. It's garbage, Mr. Reeves.
The Batman does not kill. Period.
You want him, you get him.
I'll have no part of it.
Well, gentlemen?
Any ideas?
Hm. He's usually here by now.
There appears to be some
chemical residue on the lawn.
Could match the traces I found on the glass.
Not much, but it's been that kind of day.
You'd think they could afford a weed-eater.
Sorry, Mom, but the whole world's
going to seed.
You.
Bruce?
So I'm having the banker
cut through some red tape.
Says he can roll your money
into a higher-yield account.
- Amount? What amount?
- I said, account.
Oh, I'm sorry, I was just reminiscing.
Hey, that's okay.
You must have a lot on your mind.
Monsieur?
- Remember this place?
- Sure.
You, me and Daddy
used to come here all the time.
How is the old guy?
You're still close, aren't you?
- Closer than ever.
- I'm sorry he couldn't make it this time...
...but then, I've always wished
I could have some time alone with you.
Well, who knows what the future might bring.
Welcome to Gotham World's Fair,
a dream of the future.
A bright tomorrow filled with hope
and promise for all mankind.
This is a vision of a shimmering utopia...
...where we shall all spend
the rest of our lives.
Do you think we'll really see
any of this in our lifetime?
Oh...
Bruce?
- Bruce, I'm talking to you.
- Huh?
Oh, I'm sorry, Andi.
My mind was on something else.
- Like what?
- Oh, just, you know, the future.
Anyone's in particular,
or just the generic brand?
- Well, you know.
- No, I don't.
Since when do you talk to me
about your plans?
By the way, Dad's been wanting to meet you.
- Oh, yeah?
- But I told him you're not up to it yet.
- Oh, I can meet him.
- Great!
I'll call him right now.
- You sure about this?
- Sure I'm sure.
What the heck am I doing, Alfred?
This isn't part of the plan.
I must be going nuts.
If I may make so bold, Master Bruce,
I'd say quite the reverse.
Excuse me, Mr. Beaumont.
Here are the partnership papers.
If you could just go over them, sir.
Knock, knock.
Andi.
Well, this is a most pleasant interruption.
At last I meet the elusive Bruce Wayne.
- Nice to meet you, sir.
- Sir? Oh, don't be so formal, Bruce.
Andrea's told me so much,
I feel like we're practically family.
Daddy.
- Don't mind me, I was just leaving.
- Oh, I'm sorry.
This is Arthur Reeves, one of the
Young Turks from my legal department.
He's someone you should get to know.
- I hope we're not interrupting anything.
- Not at all.
I'm never too busy for my Andi
and her friends.
I tell you, Bruce,
I do a lot of financial planning.
When it comes to money,
you can't take the future for granted.
But money means little if you
don't have loved ones to share it with.
Nothing's more important than family.
- Yes, Mr. Beaumont.
- Carl.
Excuse me, sir, but there's
a Mr. Valestra here to see you.
He says he has an appointment.
If Mr. Valestra says he has an appointment,
then Mr. Valestra has an appointment.
That's what I like about your pop,
kiddo. He knows his priorities.
Is my shirt too big,
or is that my flesh crawling?
Well, Mr. Valestra is not
what you'd call a people person.
- No kidding.
- Come on, Bruce.
That's just Daddy's business.
He deals with everyone.
It's not your father, Andi, it's...
It's everything!
I said, hand over the cash box, man.
Uh-huh.
Give me! Hey, Eddie,
pops here needs some persuasion.
- No, don't hurt me!
- Stay here.
- I gotta stop this.
- Bruce, no, don't.
What do you expect me to do, stand here?
Just come back to me in one piece. Please.
There you go!
Hey!
Better have your insurance paid up, sucker.
Here you go!
Come on! Pick up the box! Pick up the box!
Oh, thank God you're all right.
I was so frightened.
- Come on, let me have a look at you.
- Andrea, please.
What am I still doing this for?
It's gotta be one or the other.
I can't have it both ways.
I can't put myself on the line if there's
someone waiting for me at home.
Miss Beaumont would be glad to know
you feel that way, Master Bruce.
She's holding on line one, sir.
Master Bruce?
Alfred, I can't. Not now.
- Well, what shall I say, sir?
- I don't know.
I just don't know!
It doesn't mean I don't care anymore.
I don't wanna let you down, honest, but...
But it just doesn't hurt so bad anymore.
You can understand that, can't you?
Look, I can give money to the city,
they can hire more cops.
Let someone else take the risk.
It's different now.
Please. I need it to be different now.
I know I made a promise,
but I didn't see this coming.
I didn't count on being happy.
Please.
Tell me that it's okay.
Maybe they already have.
Maybe they sent me.
Hey!
Get in.
All I wanna know is, is it true?
- Is the Batman really hitting our people?
- We have eyewitnesses.
Beautiful. That's just beautiful.
Why? He never leaned on us before.
I'm too old for this.
I suppose you could demand police protection.
What are you, a comedian? This is
the Batman we're talking about here.
A freak job! He'll crucify me!
Pull over.
It's not very healthy in here.
O'Neil Funding Corporation.
Adam's Tool and Die.
- Oh, I should have known.
- Sir?
Chuckie Sol and Buzz Bronski.
They have some history together.
They were partners in dummy
corporations set up over 10 years ago.
The third director was
one Salvatore Valestra.
Hm. Sal's having company tonight.
Don't wait up.
Meaning, I trust, that once you're
done with him, you'll be seeing her?
You think you know everything
about me, don't you?
I diapered your bottom.
I bloody well ought to, sir.
Well, you're wrong.
Andrea's father.
You know how much I've always
wanted to see Europe, Bruce...
...and Dad has business there next week.
It's some sort of hush-hush deal.
He won't tell me a thing.
He can't even say when we'd be back.
Will you at least let me try
to talk you out of it?
- Bruce.
- Wait, please.
Oh, never mind.
I'm no good at this.
Here. You'll get the idea.
What do you say?
Of course I will.
I never thought this would happen.
I always felt like
I'd thrown you a curve ball.
Like you never knew what to do
with me, because I wasn't in the plan.
You are now. I'm changing the plan.
Uh-oh. Looks like Dad's got company.
Business-type company.
He doesn't usually see clients here.
At least, not at this hour.
Maybe we should wait till tomorrow
to give him the good news.
- Maybe.
- Good night, Bruce.
- Alfred.
- Miss.
It's another cave, all right.
Could be as big as the house, judging
from all the bats that came out of it.
- Alfred, what's wrong?
- This just arrived, sir.
"Left with Dad."
"Too young"? "Need time"?
"Forget about me."
My God.
If there was just some other way.
I hate that song.
Gasp! Can it be?
Old Sallie "The Wheezer" Valestra.
Welcome, paisan.
It's been a dog's age.
Hello, Joker. Didn't mean
to drop by unannounced.
Oh, Salvatore. Why so formal?
So, what's an old-timer like you
want with a two-timer like me?
Business. I got...
Business! Sounds like fun.
Come. We'll repair to more
comfortable environs.
Now, hold on to your hat
and watch those valuables.
It's going to be a bumpy ride.
Honey, I'm home.
Oh, don't mind my home-security system.
Down, Rusty.
Can't be too careful,
with all those weirdos around.
What? Meat loaf again?
Oh, I had it for lunch.
Isn't Hazel here a cutie?
True, she's a real homebody, but you
can't help who you fall in love with.
Come. Have a seat, Sal.
Tell me what's on your so-called mind.
It's Batman. He's gone nuts.
First he whacked Chuckie Sol, then Buzz...
...and now he's after me.
I've been reading lately how old Guano
Man is wound tight enough to snap.
Wouldn't it be great if I'd finally
driven him off the deep end?
This isn't a joke.
Batman's knocking us off.
You're the only one who can take him.
Look, 5 million up front with whatever
you want to finish him off.
What do I look like, pest control?
Think, you fool. Once he gets me,
how long till he gets you?
You know what I'm talking about.
Your hands are just as dirty.
Dirtier.
Don't touch me, old man.
I don't know where you've been.
Oh, Sal, no one could take a joke like you.
- Of course I'll help you out.
- Really?
No way is anybody gonna hurt my pal Sal.
That's it. That's what I want to see.
A nice big smile.
- Thanks for another lovely dinner.
- My pleasure.
You know, it's not good
to go to bed on a full stomach.
We could stay up, talk for a while.
Oh, Artie, I've got a killer day
tomorrow. But call me, okay?
- Good night.
Hmph. So we meet again. I like the cape.
Not sure about the mask, though.
Have you ever seen this?
- No.
- But that's your father.
He's the one who set up
their corporate partnership.
So? That's his job.
He was the one element
that tied these gangsters together.
- Where's your father now?
- Haven't a clue.
- Why don't you try Madagascar.
- That's not what you told Reeves.
You told him you were
closer than ever to your father.
- You had me bugged, is that it?
- I can read lips.
Then read them now: Get out.
You still following your dad's orders?
The way I see it, the only one in this
room controlled by his parents is you.
Sal Valestra. Your angel of death awaits.
Guess the joke is on me.
You're not Batman after all.
Looks like there's a new face in Gotham.
And soon his name will be all over town.
To say nothing of his legs and feet
and spleen and head.
Stay away. This is not your fight.
This madness ends now.
Batman, this is the police.
You are under arrest.
Step away from the edge of the roof.
Put your hands on top of your head
and stay in the light.
Stay on him.
Alpha 63 in pursuit, subject
moving north along Denny Drive.
All units, approach with caution.
Subject is considered armed and dangerous.
Use of deadly force is authorized.
Take it down. I gotta get closer.
Freeze!
He's heading for the construction site!
SWAT deployment teams, move into position.
All units, acknowledge.
Roger that, Charlie 3. Moving into position.
Come on, let's go. Let's move.
All available units to Fourth
and Madison, the construction site.
Charlie 3. Prepare for tear gas.
There he is, man.
Hey, wait!
You jerk!
Get a light up there.
Delta 3 to ground. He's down. We have him.
Fire.
- Quick, around the back.
- Come on.
Come on, you grunts.
- Andrea.
- Hurry.
Who's that?
There are certain advantages to having
a sturdy cranium, Master Bruce.
But then, hardheadedness
was always your virtue.
Well, I'm sure I have things to do elsewhere.
You have an excellent sense of timing.
It was all over TV. I had to do something.
I'm grateful, of course.
But I still need to know why you're not
telling me the truth about your father.
Well, I suppose the world's greatest
detective will find out eventually.
You remember Daddy was having
a meeting that night with his partners.
- You're a liar and a cheat, Carl.
- You've taken what's ours.
- You're gonna pay, one way or another.
- No, please.
Daddy, what's going on?
I'm sorry you had to see this, Miss Beaumont.
- Let her go!
- Watch it, Carl.
Please, Sal. Give me one more day.
I swear I'll get the money.
Convince me.
This time tomorrow. On my mother's grave.
As soon as the European banks open,
I'll have the whole amount wired to you.
Twenty-four hours.
This time tomorrow we'll have the money...
...or I'll have your heart in my hand.
Let's go, boys.
- Dad, are you all right?
- Pack a suitcase.
- We've got to get to the airport now.
- What?
- But you said you'd have the money.
- It's not that simple.
The money's tied up in investments.
It could take weeks to free up.
But I can't leave.
Bruce proposed to me.
We're going to get married.
Listen to me.
I just used up the last shred of pity
Sal Valestra has.
If I don't pay him back within 24 hours,
they'll find us and they'll kill us both.
How... Why did you do this, Dad?
Why did you get involved with these people?
I'm sorry, Andi.
I just wanted a chance for you...
I'll get you out of this.
Somehow, we'll be free of those guys.
Whatever it takes. That's a promise.
From that night, we were on the run.
We hid all over Europe.
Eventually settled on
the Mediterranean coast.
Dad was able to parlay the money
he embezzled into a fortune.
Finally he had enough
to pay them back, or so he thought.
It would never be enough.
They wanted interest compounded in blood.
We had to find another way.
The man in the costume. Your father?
He said he'd get them. Somehow.
When I heard about Chuckie Sol,
well, I had to come back to find him.
To stop him. I'm sorry, Bruce.
That's twice now I've come
into your life and screwed it up.
Can we make it work this time?
I want to say yes...
...but you know it's going to come down
between me and your father.
Daddy doesn't matter anymore.
- I'll see you tonight.
- I'll be here.
It's so good to see you
and Miss Beaumont together again.
Might one ask what this bodes
for your alter ego?
I'm not sure, Alfred.
Everything's happening so fast.
- So much has changed.
- You still love each other.
It's true.
I love her.
Maybe after this is settled...
...maybe then.
I'm sure they would've wanted you
to be happy, sir.
- Hm.
- Is something wrong?
Maybe.
Oh, no.
You're telling me there were four precincts
on Batman and he still got away?
Unbelievable.
Tsk, tsk.
And to think our tax money
goes to pay those jerks.
You!
That's right, Artie.
Bring in the press, why don't you.
What a photo op.
The councilman and his wacky pal.
You're no friend of mine.
Oh, Artie, I'm crushed.
How the high and mighty forget.
Don't you remember?
You, me, Sallie and the gang?
What are you talking about?
I never met them or you.
I worked for Beaumont.
- I didn't know what he was doing.
- Oh, but you knew about it afterwards.
And put it to good use, eh?
- What do you want?
- To find out who's iced the old gang.
Haven't you read the papers? It's Batman.
Wrong. It ain't the Bat.
Nope, nope. I've seen the guy.
He looks more like
the Ghost of Christmas Future.
Nowhere near as cute as Batboy.
- You're saying it's someone else?
- Yeah.
Someone who wouldn't mind seeing
our old pals out of the way.
Maybe... Gulp! Sob! ...me too.
That's when I thought about you, Arturo.
An important, upstanding guy like you
could find it awkward...
...if certain secrets
were revealed about his past.
Wait. You're not saying that I...
Mr. Reeves? Miss Beaumont on the line.
Beaumont?
Not the babe?
Oh, you devil.
Arthur?
- Arthur, are you there?
- Shh.
Hello, Andrea.
We're still on for lunch, right?
I'm sorry, I can't, I got hung up.
I'll explain everything tonight, okay?
All right. I'll see you then.
Now, ain't that a coinkidink.
We're talking about the old man, and the
spawn of his loins just happens to call.
Makes you want to laugh, doesn't it, Artie?
Good heavens.
Councilman, please,
you've got to control yourself.
- I'm trying, for God's sake.
- Here's the relaxant you ordered.
I need some help. Hold him still.
Councilman, please.
That's it.
That's right.
There. That should relax you enough
for the toxin to run its course.
Now, try to stay calm.
Okay.
Dr. Blair, come to Outpatient Counseling.
Oh, no.
Why did the Joker meet with you?
It has to do with the gangster murders,
doesn't it? He thinks you're involved.
Why?
I don't know.
That's not the answer I want.
Beaumont needed me to help him
and his kid get out of town.
We kept in touch.
When was the last time you spoke to him?
Years ago. My first election campaign.
I was running out of money
and asked Beaumont for help.
He said no.
So you sold him to the Mob.
I was broke, desperate.
They said all they wanted
was their money back.
- Councilman, please.
- Nurse.
Hello, anybody home?
Listen, boopsy, even though
you never call and never write...
...I still got a soft spot for you.
So I'm sending you a fun gift, airmail.
And there's no use jumping
out the window this time, toots.
The plane of the future
is going to make you history.
Hello? Hello, operator?
I believe my party's been disconnected.
You? But he paid you.
Dad?
Well, Haz, guess it's time
to call it a night.
What do you say, hon?
Feeling the old electricity tonight?
Ain't it always the way?
You get in the mood and company shows up.
Joker. Your angel of death awaits.
I'm impressed, lady.
You're harder to kill
than a cockroach on steroids.
So you figured it out?
Gotta hand it to you, nice scheme.
Costume's a bit theatrical,
but, hey, who am I to talk.
Very cute. But I can blow smoke too, toots.
Nice trick, sweetheart.
You could teach old Batsy
a thing or two about disappearing.
You're not smiling, Joker.
I thought you found death amusing.
Me? Oh, no.
You won't hear a giggle out of me.
Made you look.
Well, if it isn't Smokey the Babe.
Just in time to meet her biggest fan.
How about a little pick-me-up?
Your father's dead, isn't he?
You came into town early
to get Chuckie Sol...
...so you could shift the blame
to your father if you had to.
They took everything, Bruce.
My dad, my life. You.
I'm not saying it's right, or even sane,
but it's all I've got left.
So either help me or get out of the way.
- You know I can't do that.
- Look what they did to us.
What we could've had. They had to pay.
But, Andi, what will vengeance solve?
If anyone knows the answer
to that, Bruce, it's you.
Leave, Andi. Now.
Please.
Oh, Batsy.
Yoo-hoo.
Joker.
You're too late, Batman.
There are 20 miles of tunnels
under this place...
...and they're all filled
with high explosives.
In five minutes, everything goes up.
You just don't know when to quit, do you?
What are you doing?
You're crazy. I'm your only chance
to get out of here.
Let me go or we'll both die.
Whatever it takes.
For once, I'm stuck without a punch line.
Uh-oh.
Okay. I give up.
I surrendered already.
- Tell her, Batman.
- Andrea.
You've got to get out of here.
This place is wired to explode.
No. One way or another, it ends tonight.
Goodbye, my love.
Andrea!
I couldn't save her, Alfred.
I don't think she wanted to be saved, sir.
Vengeance blackens the soul, Bruce.
I always feared you would become
that which you fought against.
You walk the edge of that abyss
every night, but you haven't fallen in...
...and I thank heaven for that.
But Andrea fell into that pit years ago.
And no one, not even you,
could've pulled her back.
What is it?
- Quite a sight.
- Yes.
I'm sorry. Do you wanna be alone?
I am.
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org