Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
A woman? Of course.
But is she human?
Well, that's another story.
The Gotham Gaiety Girls presents...
...Ivy, the Plant Lady.
But be warned, fellas.
This ivy is poison.
Dare you taste her forbidden fruit?
Disarm them all already.
Let's see those leaves fall.
You gave me a start.
I thought for a minute...
Well, you're clearly a real gentleman.
You lonely? I hate to see a man lonely.
I got a generous nature.
And I'm sure you're generous too.
Ain't ya, mister?
My room's not far.
Or maybe you don't want to wait.
No. No! No!
You took the shortcut
through outsider's territory.
You gotta pay the tariff.
Ain't that right, Dickie?
Name's Jason. 'Member?
We don't say our names.
Oh, let's go back to the flop, fellas.
It's getting awful late.
Don't go yellow on me, boy...
...or you know what you'll get.
Don't you worry, Bill. We're on the job.
What are you scared of the dark, Little Tim?
Nah, it's just... after what
happened to Johnny Gobbs, I...
That ain't real, Timmy.
He's like Santa Claus.
Just a story they tell to keep young turfs
like us from making an honest living.
Oh, he's real, all right.
That's why you gotta pay us.
For protecting you from monsters.
Now pay up.
I think we might have broke 'em, boys.
Bat!
Holy shit!
Stick 'im, boys.
You're the galumph who's been
making a nuisance of yourself...
...all over Gotham, ain't ya?
Well, now you're
in Big Bill Dust's territory...
...interfering with my amiable Cock Robins.
You're bad for business.
Bad all 'round.
Too bad for you.
- Go home.
- Am home.
Home to mommy.
He ain't got one. None of us do.
Or we run off from something
even worse than this.
This is our family now.
Making something here.
- Taking something back from Gotham.
- Make something else.
- Something better.
- We got no choice.
He'll just chase us down, find us again.
He won't be chasing anyone for a long time.
Go to St. Caduales, ask for Sister Leslie.
She'll help you.
Get off the street, now!
Blood, sweat and tears.
That's what turned this dream
into a magnificent reality, gentlemen.
That and Bruce Wayne's money.
Spoken like a true,
county prosecutor, Mr. Dent.
Money always helps.
But it is the ingenuity
of the city's captains of industry...
...that provided these marvels.
And may you select few truly
enjoy this special preview...
...of the Gotham World's Fair.
The stairway to heaven.
A fully electronical lantern,
bright enough to illuminate...
...the very celestial firmament above.
Higher even than the police department's
new lighter-than-air patrol craft.
Let's see it.
The light tends to show off a bit better
in the night time, Ambrose.
But here's a sight you needn't
wait to marvel at.
Gotham's own answer to the Eiffel Tower.
The fox wheel will elevate you
two hundred and fifty feet into the sky...
...at the astonishing rate
of 15 miles an hour.
Heavens! Can the human body
even survive that kind of motion?
Most certainly, ma'am. I refer you to medical
expert and Gotham's premier alienist...
...Dr. Hugo Strange.
The human organs can withstand
velocities up to 35 miles per hour.
Ride the wheel, and I give you my
guarantee as a physician and surgeon...
- ...you will live.
- It's a shame you won't provide...
...this same assurance
to the ladies of Gotham, Mr. Mayor.
Women are being gutted
in the streets like wild game...
...and the Gotham police
stand twiddling their thumbs.
I'm sure Ms. Kyle's lovely voice is better
suited to the stage of the Monarch Theater...
- ...than a city council meeting.
- Mr. Dent...
Sure, and no ladies
have been killed, Ms. Kyle.
Some gin-soaked women of the street
have met their fate.
- As is common to their kind.
- Belay that, Chief.
Ms. Kyle, I assure you visitors
to this fair, men and women alike...
- ...will be safe from...
- Jack. Jack the Ripper.
That's what he calls himself in the letter
he sent the Gotham Gazette, isn't it?
Now, Sister Leslie,
that letter's likely just another hoax.
Really, Bulldog? Strange it would arrive
with a human kidney in the envelope.
There's a butcher in this town
preying on poor women.
And if you don't stop him,
so help me, I'll raise holy hell.
Sister, your selfless dedication
to Gotham's poor is...
Poor is the word.
If these murdered ladies were from
Crest Hill instead of Skinner's End...
...you'd have the killer by now.
My men are working triple shifts combing
every inch of this city for this mad man.
You know I've pledged to clean up
Gotham and I mean all of it.
It's that bat creature we've been
reading about. That's who it is.
That could very well be.
He's a devil, that one.
My men just can't seem to...
To do anything, Chief Bullock,
but sit on their fat arses and...
Just a damn minute.
Your charity house is what draws
these pests in in the first...
Well, as I live and breathe.
If it isn't himself.
Welcome! A hearty welcome
to Gotham's favorite native son.
Bruce Wayne.
Thank you, thank you, Mayor Tolliver.
Please don't stop on my account.
You know I like to keep a low profile.
I heard about this
little city council meeting...
...and thought it was a good opportunity
to see how my money was being spent...
...and all I see is sour faces.
Think nothing of that, my boy.
They're just a few disruptive
females in attendance.
Don't worry, sir. I was just about
to have them escorted away.
Leslie!
You were saying, Chief?
There were newspapers in Europe, James.
Is it as bad as I read?
Worse. Despite your best efforts
with this World's Fair.
...the city seems to be getting
more deplorable every day.
First, this masked Batman vigilante,
then this Jack the Ripper lunatic.
- They're not the same man?
- Rubbish.
The parish home is full of unfortunates who
swear the Batman saved them from the gangs.
- He's on the side of the angels.
- This Ripper, however, is not.
I've seen the bodies, Bruce.
Cut to pieces, like an autopsy.
Just absolutely appalling.
Strange the top man at Arkham
tells us he's never seen...
...this kind of controlled savagery before.
Bruce, the latest victim
was one of our orphanage girls.
It was Pamela.
What? No.
You wrote me. You said she was working.
Dancing, then the opium.
And now...
- We can't save them all.
- I'm sorry, Bruce.
I know those orphans are close to your heart.
If I didn't have Sister Leslie
when my parents...
...funding the orphanage
is the least I could do.
And now you're back in the manor.
Too remote. I've a town house on Bell Avenue.
I look forward to showing it to you.
Unfortunately, tonight I have to...
Don't say another word.
I'll not hear you lie.
And a rich bachelor is always up to no good.
I'm afraid it's unavoidable.
Isn't that right, Alfred?
Your evening attire
has already been laid out, sir.
Well, duty calls, I'm afraid.
Do you suppose his pressing business
is blonde, brunette, or a redhead?
James Gordon,
you've got a dirty mind, you do.
My money's on blonde.
- I hope you're unharmed, miss.
- Damn you.
You're a fool. I'll never have a better
chance of stopping that butcher...
...and you squandered it,
playing the knight in shining armor.
I can take care of myself.
Don't be so sure. He's more skilled
than I would have thought.
I don't need or want your help.
And before you gallantly offer
to escort me home...
...let me assure you,
I am quite capable of...
Well, thank you for that at least.
Barbara!
Barbara.
Hush! The children don't have
to be up for hours.
What is it, James? What's wrong?
Dream. Just a dream.
And then, you were gone.
I'm all right, dear.
James, these hours, you're working too hard.
And that's not likely to change.
I can't very well sit at home
while Gotham goes straight to hell.
No, you couldn't, could you?
I'll make your eggs.
- Damnation!
- Don't be alarmed.
So says the man dressed up like a bat.
I'm on your side, Commissioner.
I mean to rid Gotham of the Ripper.
Really? And who'll help me rid Gotham of you?
Your men don't search too hard for me.
I'm betting that comes from the top down.
Back in the union camp at Culpepper,
soldiers would sometimes ignore...
...a feral cat just to keep
the rat population in check.
Other times, we'd eat them.
I know a vigilante from a maniac.
This Ripper is far worse
than the lunatic you're searching for.
He's a skilled hunter,
and he's just getting started.
You ought to have breakfast
with Hugo Strange up at Arkham Asylum.
You can compare useless theories.
I prefer facts.
I ran into your Ripper earlier this evening.
Approximately 6'3", 250 pounds, left handed.
Good fighter. Trained, not just a brawler.
- You didn't happen to see his face, did you?
- I need your files on the Ripper.
Detailed descriptions of the crime scene...
...photo plates,
even profiles from your alienist.
Would you prefer them alphabetized
or in chronological order?
- James?
- Stay inside, Barbara.
I'll be in directly.
Every woman in Gotham
is in danger, Commissioner.
A letter from Jack to the Gotham Gazette.
We've convinced them
to refrain from publishing it.
Makes poor bedtime reading, I assure you.
Perhaps you'll find
something of use in there.
Thank you.
I'll leave a copy of the Ripper file
on the roof of the police station.
I know you fancy rooftops.
But understand that this uninvited visit
to my home will not be repeated.
This house is my refuge...
...set apart from all
the corruption of Got...
James, your eggs are ready.
Are you sure you won't come inside?
Yes, yes. I'm coming.
"Dear Boss, Gotham has become
a den of filth and scum.
I'm down on whores and I shan't quit
ripping them till I do get buckled.
Grand work, the last job was.
I hardly gave the lady no time to squeal.
How can they catch me now?
I love my work, cutting whores and then
degenerates what with defend them."
A little light reading, Master Bruce?
"Them cusses' of coppers
nor the false God you hide behind...
...won't spoil the game for me.
I will be on a job soon...
...and will send you another bit of innards."
Goes on like that in some detail
about his dissection plans.
Mrs. Cooper has sent up a portage.
Bon appetit. And what do you deduce
from this magnum opus?
Very little.
Cheap paper with no watermark.
The hand is that of a man with some education
disguised to look like a man with none.
I'm certain your displays
of graphology would duly impress...
...any young ladies you encounter.
Women are a distraction
from the mission, Alfred.
So you've said. Your evening attire, sir.
I believe you know that was not
the suit I was referring to...
...when I said I'd be
going out tonight, Alfred.
I've taken the liberty
of placing your other suit...
...in the seat compartment
of the carriage, sir.
Before the Batman can prowl, I'm afraid,
Bruce Wayne must needs make an appearance.
Tongues will wag.
What engagement have I accepted?
You are carousing with the lively
man-about-town and rake...
...your oldest school chum,
Master Harvey Dent.
Gotham's solicitor.
I'm certain you shall have a pleasant
and elegant evening's entertainment, sir.
When the circus came to town
Jay Augustus Henpecked Brown
Bought himself a ticket for the show
Passed by all the acrobats
All the clowns in funny hats
Went to see the animals below
Saw a tamer put his head into a lion's mouth
Waited till the tamer man was through
Shook his hand and said,
"at taming wild ones, you're a bird
"But just one thing I'd like to ask of you"
Can you tame Wild Wimmen?
You made a tiger stand
And eat out of your hand
You made the hippo do the flippo
Honest, it was grand
Can you tame Wild Wimmen?
So they'll always lead
A sweet and simple life
Bruce, I'm in love.
Well, that's great news, Harvey.
I'm sure your wife will be glad to hear it.
Oh, please, Bruce. This is the 19th century.
Don't be such a dinosaur.
Marriage is more like a business arrangement.
Besides, what Gilda doesn't know,
won't hurt her.
Selina is the most amazing gal,
Bruce. You'll see.
I think I already do.
Just make yourselves at home,
gentlemen. I'll make myself decent.
I certainly hope not.
Did you enjoy my performance, Mr. Wayne?
Bruce. And I'm told you also gave
quite an impassioned performance...
...at the World's Fair preview.
I'm passionate in everything I do, Bruce.
And boss Tolliver needed to get the message.
Come on, my pet.
Let's see if we can't make our way...
...to a more comfortable establishment
before Gordon's killjoy curfew takes effect.
Listen carefully, kitten...
...I'm many things but I'm nobody's pet.
And you can't doubt for one minute
that if men were being slaughtered...
...Tolliver would hire an army
of policemen to find this Ripper.
But I don't agree.
If it were affluent women, society ladies,
the outcry might be deafening.
Jack targets destitute women.
When the voiceless cry out, no one hears.
I think you're ignoring
the real tragedy here.
Every establishment in town is closing down.
What a shame. I was starting to suspect
that there was more to your friend...
...than a good family name
and prep school manners.
Well, there's the Wayne fortune.
But I'm sure you didn't forget that,
did you, Selina?
Steady, old man.
You'll have to excuse Harvey.
Oh, I know. When he drinks,
he's an entirely different person.
A regular Jekyll and Hyde.
This is my club. We can catch a hansom here.
I'd invite you in for a drink but,
unfortunately, men only.
At least we still have something.
I didn't take you for an anti-suffragist.
I don't think the doorman
was quite convinced that I'm a man.
If he was, I'd have to have him dismissed.
The Dionysus Club cannot tolerate
a doorman who is blind.
You'd never do that. Have someone fired.
You're too kind. I've heard.
You don't know me.
I know most other men would've
abandoned Harvey hours ago.
- Well, we've all had a few.
- You haven't.
You've been pouring your drinks
in potted plants all night.
A mutual friend told me you like to solve
mysteries, ever since you were a boy.
You're studying me.
You're a fascinating subject.
And what have you learned?
Only that you were raised
in a small, regional circus...
...probably in a family of performers.
That some traumatic event possibly
connected to the scar on your left arm...
...that you're trying to conceal,
led you to the continent...
...where you reinvented yourself
as a night club performer.
Nothing else?
That you take it upon yourself
to act as champion of the voiceless.
Which you, no doubt, learned from our
mutual friend, Sister Leslie Thompkins.
One of the few people who knew me as a boy.
Yes. She was the one
who told me you were kind.
And she should know. She took me in too.
She takes in all of the helpless,
the hopeless...
...feeds them, protects them.
- I've been a fool.
- Bruce, what?
Fetch me a hansom, quickly.
Oh, Sister. You gave me a fright.
Marlene, what are you doing here?
A warm cot is waiting for you
and you're out here in the cold.
You've been at the bottle.
I'm sorry, Sister.
I was having trouble sleeping.
I needed my medicine.
I don't know where you're hiding it, but
your sort of medicine will kill you for sure.
Back to bed with ya.
Keep it, don't wait.
So, this is it then.
Well, I won't beg...
...and I won't go hysterical.
I won't give you the satisfaction.
Know this...
...I forgive you.
Master Bruce, I took the liberty of...
- Bruce, I know how much Sister Leslie...
- What, Alfred? What did you say?
Nothing at all, sir.
I presumed and I presumed incorrectly.
What have you there?
It's a membership pin from the Dionysus Club.
It was at the scene.
The Batman will return it
to Gordon after my analysis.
Yours? You were there,
you might've dropped it.
No. There's blood splattered on the pin.
It was there when the murder
happened. Mine wasn't.
This does, however,
narrow the field considerably.
Including the Mayor,
Harvey, even Hugo Strange.
Virtually every wealthy man in Gotham.
Testing your fingerprints theory again?
You know, they'll never admit
that sort of thing as evidence.
There are no prints,
just a few fibers in the fastener.
If I could match these...
It will have to wait.
I've laid out your mourning clothes.
I have my own manner of mourning.
- Revenge.
- Her blood cries out for it.
Does it, sir?
"Beloved, avenge not yourselves,
vengeance is mine.
"I will repay," sayeth the Lord.
She wouldn't want you to be alone right now.
It's how I work best, Alfred.
But I can pay my respects.
For as much as it hath
pleased almighty God...
...of his great mercy...
...to take unto himself the soul
of our dear sister here departed.
We therefore commit her body to the ground.
Earth to earth.
Ashes to ashes.
Dust to dust.
In sure and certain hope
of the resurrection to eternal life...
...through our Lord Jesus Christ...
...who shall change
the body of our low estate...
...that it may be like
unto his glorious body.
Amen.
Mr. Wayne?
Dr. Hugo Strange, isn't it?
You know me.
I read your monograph on the habits
of the clinically degenerate lunatics.
You believe their cure lies in surgery.
Ablation of the frontal cortex.
The scalpel solves everything.
- You knew Sister Leslie?
- No, I came for professional reasons.
He is here. I am certain of it.
Jack.
His sick mind burns with the hatred
of all that he sees as evil and wicked.
Hatred of women. A hunger that never dies.
It is strong. Overpowering.
- You know who he is?
- Pardon me, Mr. Wayne.
The Commissioner was wondering
if you'll be coming to the memorial.
Yes, Chief. I'll be right there.
Well?
I should very much like to tell this...
...Batman I've heard so much
about all that I know.
- Then why come to...
- You know everyone in town, Mr. Wayne.
I'm sure you could find a way to tell
the Batman to come to my office.
Tonight. Midnight.
Strange, I don't know who...
Gotcha.
Let me go, geezer.
I'm afraid you lack the subtlety to be an
effective cat purse, young fellow, my lad.
And so near a bevy of policeman, too.
He didn't mean nothing, mister.
You idiot. You think that's how Sister Leslie
would want you to act at her own funeral?
But I'm hungry.
Mister, Jason here is not worth the trouble.
Cut him loose, huh?
Orphans.
Sister Leslie did what she could for us.
Fed us, tried to teach us right.
Look, knock Jason around
a little if you want, but...
...please don't get the cops.
I occasionally have odd jobs that need doing.
Call upon me here.
You'll not go away hungry.
Shoo.
- Not so hasty, if you please.
- What?
I know I'm too old now to catch
the eye of a gent like you.
But my eyes are still good, yeah?
They see everything.
- I don't quite follow.
- Of course, my memory ain't so great.
I forget things all the time
for the right price.
Follow me, Mr. Bruce Wayne?
I recognized you sneaking
around the church yard.
- I'm afraid you've made a mistake.
- Afraid?
Oh, you'll be afraid all right,
Mr. High and Mighty Bruce Wayne.
When I tell the coppers what I know!
- Now, let's just settle down.
- Get your hands off me.
If you think you can do me like you did
Sister Leslie, you're dead wrong, fella.
Now, what's all the commotion, granny?
Why don't we just quiet down a bit?
Arrest me, will ya?
I'm not the one you should be talking to.
Am I, Mr. Bruce Wayne?
Find me at Skinner's End, everybody knows me!
You'll pay up if you know
what's good for you.
Or mark me... you'll hang!
Here you are.
How punctual.
Even a bit early, Batman.
You should feel at home here
with my collection.
Usually, it's on our own face,
that is the mask.
These masks, the ones you choose to wear...
...they show the true self.
Of course, you understand
why I couldn't say more.
Now, we both know
you cannot do your work on me.
I'm not a street walker.
It's antithetical to your neurosis.
I'd stake my professional reputation on it.
You can't!
Help me!
Stop. Please.
No, my God, no!
Arkham to police headquarters.
The Batman has murdered Dr. Strange...
...and escaped in the police airship.
He's heading right for you.
This way, fellas.
Fire!
No.
There he is!
- Keep firing, boys. Shoot to kill.
- Belay that order!
Nice of you to join us, Commissioner.
Do you mind telling me exactly why we
shouldn't shoot the murdering lunatic...
- ...who's gutting whores all over town?
- Watch your tone, Chief.
We have witnesses who saw the Batman
at the time of the Isley murder.
And what about the two men
he just killed at Arkham?
We don't know what happened
for certain, Bulldog.
There'll be no lynch mob
on my watch, do you understand?
We catch him and if he's guilty,
he hangs, but I want him alive.
Now fan out. Find him!
Pick up everyone.
He could be anyone on the street.
Get in.
As you surmised, I get tired of Crest Hill.
I amuse myself by slumming with the unwashed.
Do your downtown escapades
usually end with excessive bleeding?
The belt and gloves must go immediately.
Any of the bat accoutrement.
They'll have the entire area cordoned off.
Homes, carriages searched.
It wouldn't do to have them
find your stage wear.
Hold! Hold, I say!
Open up, open up in the name of the law.
Is there a problem, Officer?
No, Mr. Wayne. We've just been...
You should head home. Dangerous
characters on the streets tonight.
Duly noted. Anything else, gentlemen?
No. Excuse me, sir.
And madam. Have a wonderful night.
Lucky bugger.
You were very convincing.
I'm an actress, darling. Didn't you know?
I'm the toast of Gotham.
You, on the other hand,
would never make it out of the chorus.
You must commit completely to the role.
And how exactly do I do that, Ms. Kyle?
Repetition. You must practice.
Practice, practice.
I want another squad moving
into Cape Carmine. And then...
Commissioner! We found something, sir.
The boys just found her.
Show me.
Well, I guess it's true what they say.
Practice makes perf...
I had these brought up.
I have a rather large wardrobe.
The entire production is mine, you know?
I'm not just another pretty face.
I feel a perfect fool for not
realizing your secret earlier.
When you first kissed my hand backstage,
I felt the callous on your palm...
...and thought, "This man's got
the hands of a trapeze artist."
I saw the circus in the acrobatic
dismount you used in your show.
And then of course,
your fighting style and the whip.
Expert lion tamer.
I grew up with those cats.
Looked after them, loved them.
Papa hated them.
He wasn't a kind man to them or to me.
He was always threatening to shoot them.
And I believed him.
One day he tried to but someone
had taken the bullets out of his gun.
And now, you look after all
those strays in Skinner's End.
Someone has to. They don't have
anyone else to protect them.
Until now.
Until the Batman.
Does he have a story?
Selina...
Oh, your parents.
Are you making them pay? The criminals?
I was but... it'd never be enough.
They couldn't ever pay enough. Could they?
They're here.
Police! Put your hands in the air.
What's the meaning of this?
Oh, a thousand pardons, Ms. Kyle.
For disturbing the sanctity
of a lady's bedchamber.
What do you want, Bullock?
Bruce Wayne, you're under arrest
for the murder of one Marlene Mahoney.
- Who?
- Oh, is that how it is now?
You've killed so many,
you don't even know their names.
Think hard, Wayne. Maybe you'll remember.
You'll have a long time to think about it.
Bruce, it'll be all right.
I'll contact Harvey. He'll clear this all up.
I wouldn't be countin' on Mr. Dent
being too helpful, lassie.
He's the one who suggested
we look for Mr. Wayne in your hotel.
Commissioner, James, this is absurd.
You can't imagine I'm actually the ripper.
Get him out of my sight.
The county of Gotham has abundant
evidence linking the accused...
...to at least three
of these vicious murders.
Physical evidence...
...a lapel pin of the Dionysus Club
to which Mr. Wayne is a member...
...was discovered at the site of Sister
Leslie's murder. Also, an eye witness...
...who was overheard placing
Mr. Wayne at the scene of the crime.
That witness, Marlene Mahony,
was subsequently discovered...
...mutilated in the same barbaric
manner as the other victims...
...after reportedly attempting
to extort cash from the accused.
Furthermore, the prisoner
was also acquainted...
...with reaper victim, Ms. Pamela Isley.
One wonders how many other
lovely young wards...
Enough! Enough!
You've made your point, Mr. Prosecutor.
The accused will be remanded to
the custody of Blackgate Penitentiary...
...until such time as a trial by jury
can be arranged by the county.
If it please the court, as the nature
of these crimes is so detestable...
...and Mr. Wayne has ample financial
resources to escape justice...
...I request the court to not set bail.
Granted. Bailiff will remove
the prisoner to Blackgate Prison.
Court adjourned.
Hey, Jack,
you're not the only one who can cut.
Let's see if Wayne blood really is blue.
Tell him.
Blackgate's real progressive.
Warden likes to encourage physical exercise.
You'll see.
The deluxe suite. Please, enjoy
your stay at the Hotel Blackgate.
Yeah, we're looking forward
to seeing you checkout.
I love what you've done with the place.
Selina, what are you doing here?
This is no place for a lady.
You should see some
of the houses I've played to.
They make this seem
like a command performance.
- You need to get out of here.
- No, you need to get out of here.
When my friend has gone
to all the trouble of building...
...this well-constructed gilded frame for me?
Your friend? You think one
of your friends is framing you?
One of my mentors says that
when you eliminate the impossible...
...whatever remains,
however improbable, must be the truth.
That's a lot of eyewash.
You must liberate yourself immediately.
Unfortunately, my nocturnal
habits preclude me...
...from providing an adequate
account of my whereabouts.
Well, you'll just have to explain
to Gordon that you are the Batman.
What? I think not.
You must. Batman has an ironclad
alibi for the first murder.
You'll be released. Gotham needs the Batman
to help rid the streets of this killer.
I'm sorry, Selina. I can't.
The Batman's effectiveness depends upon...
Every moment you're in here
puts women in danger.
If you won't tell Gordon,
then I will. Immediately.
He'll never believe you.
He'll believe this.
I'll be damned if I'll let
another girl be murdered...
...so you can keep your precious secret.
I'm sorry, Bruce, but I think ultimately
you'll find this was all for the best.
Chow time, your highness.
Listen to me, bring this to
my townhouse on Bell Avenue...
- ...and my man there will give you $100.
- If you think I can be bought...
Get it there within 30 minutes,
he'll give you $200.
Yes! Yes!
- Give it to him!
- Come on!
Lay him out!
Come on, put up a fight for Christ's sake!
Who is next?
Who will face Cyrus Gold?
I'll give it a whirl.
No weaklings. Can't get good
enough odds against you.
I'll beat you in private, later.
No time like the present.
While you're sittin' on your ass,
there's a damn donnybrook in there!
Shore up the west gate!
Fetch the riot gear from the arsenal!
May I help you, miss?
Yes, I need to see
Commissioner Gordon immediately.
- I'm afraid, that's impossible.
- I must insist, it's quite urgent.
You never slow down, do you?
As soon as one lover boy is unavailable,
you're on to the next chump.
I can imagine what I ever saw
in a whore like you.
Better sheath those claws, kitten.
Someone is liable to get hurt.
And sooner or later, you will.
James isn't here.
He's down at the fairgrounds,
making sure everything's shipshape.
Tomorrow is the big day. You'll have
to scratch up some business elsewhere.
The fairground, hurry.
This is it.
You're off your nut.
We're in the middle of nothin'.
This is where that geezer told us to go.
I can read, can't I?
So you keep tellin' us.
Come on, he said to unload it here.
I still say we take the wagon, the horse,
and whatever this is and skedaddle.
Serve him right for being so trusting.
But he fed us.
We're gonna do the job, Jason.
Now shut your boom box and push.
Good job. Now, go.
What are you doing here?
You're Ms. Kyle, the actress, aren't you?
Yes, Commissioner,
we met before, at the preview.
I thought I was all alone.
Embarrassing as it sounds,
you gave me quite a start.
Commissioner? Selina?
- Mrs. Gordon, don't be alarmed.
- What do you want?
I need to talk to your husband. Is he home?
You mustn't harm him. He's a good man.
The best man in this horrible city.
Did a woman come here looking for him?
A woman? Walking here off the streets?
I should hope not.
No! You're not allowed in there!
Where is he?
Doing what he needs to do.
His holy work.
Cleaning the scum from Gotham.
He needs to be severe.
But not with us. No.
No, he's gentle as a lamb with us.
He simply burns the sin out of us.
We need him to.
Good Lord.
It's the woman's sins that are the worst.
Because they're hidden inside.
James brings them out into the light.
Where is he?
I suspected, of course.
Who else, but Bruce Wayne...
...has either the time
or resources to create the Batman.
We'll see to this immediately.
Let me fetch my things.
I suppose it's a dreadful
betrayal of confidence.
But I simply see no other way.
No, no, Ms. Kyle, I understand completely.
It's in your very nature to play false
with your illicit lover.
An action ideal to expose...
...your absolute internal corruption.
A 7% solution of laudanum,
3% heroin and alcohol.
Barbara's physician
prescribes it for acute insomnia.
Effective, is it not?
But it's hardly a cure for harlotry.
Only, I. Only Jack
has the remedy for that vile ill.
Damnation! You'll pay for that, slut!
You can't get far.
The oversweet fragrance you used...
...to cover your putrefying
stench nearly burns my eyes.
Come to Jack, you little...
Nice try.
Wayne promised this World's Fair...
...would be a paradise
of cleanliness and light.
But what does a light in the darkness do?
It draws flies.
Vile, unclean, like you.
But for every one of you
I eradicate, two more arrive.
I promised the people of Gotham
to clean scum of the streets...
...thieves, murderers, confidence men...
...immigrants, illiterates, anarchists.
This city seems to spawn them.
But it's whores... you painted
whores that are the worst.
All rosy-cheeked,
soft and round on the outside...
...but on the inside...
My death prove...
...innocent.
Yes. Sadly, your death will exonerate Wayne.
But it will be worth it.
Your blood shall christen this fair, woman.
Your corruption and decay
will spill down over this carnival...
...as a warning to all your kind.
Shall we begin?
This may take quite some time.
Left handed.
Oh, the nuns beat that wickedness out of me.
Always use my right.
Except for Jack's work.
Can you speak? Have you any other injuries?
No. I'm... Bruce!
You were right. I'm a trained fighter.
Bare knuckle champion at Culpepper.
London Prize Ring rules.
There were no rules at Antietam,
though, were there, James?
There are no rules in hell.
The things I saw during the war...
...the entirety of humanity's
evil was there for all to see...
...on the inside of every man.
But nothing compared to the corruption
of every painted camp follower.
The vile diseases they spread,
destroy good men...
...destroyed them in both body and mind.
I saw your work on your wife.
Wives? They are the worst prostitutes of all.
Sell themselves too cheap.
Wives, brothers, that slut nun of yours.
Look, Bruce, the world
of tomorrow is burning.
Exposing the ashes
of degradation hiding beneath.
This is where we belong!
No.
I paid Houdini $300 for that trick.
Fight's over. Time to go.
Gordon!
You should have run when you had that chance.
Well, I was badly doped up.
My actions were quite questionable.
Help them in, lads. Lively now.
Where there's smoke, there's fire.
And there you'll always be, sir.
Do these belong to you, Alfred?
Good Lord. No, sir. They belong to you.
Gone. All gone.
And the hope of Gotham with it.
It was all phony anyway.
We'll make something new.
Something better.
Please rate this subtitle at www.osdb.link/5tsyy
Help other users to choose the best subtitles