Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org
[Bats squeaking]
[Sonar pinging]
Captain:
Secure from quarters.
All ahead 2/3.
Come left heading 1-9-0.
Set depth for 100 meters.
Aye aye. 20 degrees down
angle on the bow planes.
Come left 1-9-0.
Range
to destination?
8 kilometers.
Hoskins, what are
the conditions up there?
30 degrees
below zero, sir,
and we've got
a storm moving in.
Landing party
on deck.
Now, collect your data quickly
and get back to the ship.
No one can survive for
long in that kind of cold.
Koonak?
Do you have dinner?
Ooh, salmon.
[Grunting]
Ohh! Ohh!
Ohh!
100 meters to
surface, Captain.
Reading a thin layer of ice
beneath a mountainous terrain.
Possibly a cave.
All back 1/3.
15 years today,
darling.
Did you think
I would forget?
How could I?
The day we met was the
happiest day of my life.
A gift for you.
I found it
in the snow.
Fragile beauty clinging to
life in this frozen wasteland.
Like you, Nora.
30 meters below surface
and closing.
Estimate impact
in 15 seconds.
How long does she
have to stay in there?
Until a cure
can be found.
Until then, my love,
we'll be here together.
Huh?
Aah!
- Ohh!
- Aah! Ooh!
Nora!
Let's move out.
Ohh!
Uhh!
[Thunder]
Man, I've never
seen it that cold.
Let's get inside.
[Wind whistling]
What in the name of?
My God! What happened?
Woman:
It's the whole crew.
Freeze: Not quite.
- Aah! -
Aah! - Aah!
[Siren]
[Truck horn honking]
[Traffic noise]
Radio: Forecast,
plenty of sunshine...
[Baby crying]
Radio: Temperatures...
[Laughing and yelling]
Ha ha ha ha.
Yaaaaa!
Ooh! Ha ha ha!
Ooh!
[Alarm rings]
You punks have robbed me
for the last time!
Myron, let the police handle it.
Come away!
Do what she says,
old man.
I'm not afraid of you.
Ugh! Uhh!
Aah!
Ooh!
Myron!
I warned you,
mister.
[Whistles]
[Revs motor]
Drive!
[Whistles]
Man, there must be a couple
of grand worth of stuff here.
Yeah, I told you
it'd be easy.
What was that?
Huh?
[Yelling and screaming]
[Horn honks]
- Ohh!
- Aah!
Let's call the cops.
Yeah,
come on.
Ohh.
What happened?
I don't know.
Aah!
Jeez!
Ohh! Ohh! Ohh!
Aah... Oof!
Ohh!
Pl-Please don't hurt me.
Uhh! Uhh! Uhh!
Aah!
[Siren]
- Ohh!
- Ohh! Ow!
Listen, scum, we're
gonna be watching you.
[Siren]
Keep your hands
where we can see 'em.
[Telephone beeps]
Yes, Alfred?
Alfred: We're
running late, sir.
The party's
already started.
Batman: Meet us
in 2 minutes.
Very good, sir.
On my way.
[Music plays]
Thanks, Alfred. Don't know
what we'd do without you.
Frankly, sir,
neither do I.
Ahh.
Bruce!
John, it looks like
a good turnout.
Thanks for inviting us.
Have a good time.
There you are.
Hello, Bruce,
Dick.
Commissioner.
Good to see
a familiar face.
Where's Barbara?
You know my daughter. She's
probably still getting ready.
Ha ha.
My little girl.
You know, Dick,
there's no one sweeter
in this whole world.
Hyah!
Ohh!
You've got plenty
of competition.
Lots of guys
are after her.
I'm
out of here!
- Go! Go! Go!
- Move it!
Are you all right?
Uh-huh.
[Beeping]
Uhh!
Hey, thanks!
But don't worry.
You're on top
of her list.
You and Barbara
getting serious?
Hmm, maybe.
You got any advice
about women?
There you are!
Bruce, where
have you been?
My friends are just
dying to meet you.
Let me get back
to you on that.
Here he is, ladies.
Gotham's most
elusive bachelor.
Woman:
Isn't he handsome?
Bruce, this is Buffy
and Debra and Caitlin.
Hello, Bruce.
So nice to meet you.
Ahh!
Well, excuse you.
I'd keep my money
in low-risk mutual funds.
That way,
if the market dips...
We have to talk.
Gregory, I didn't know
we had a meeting scheduled.
- Would you excuse us for a minute?
- Hey!
How come you're not
returning my calls?
I told you, there's
nothing more I can do.
You're my stockbroker. You got
me into this, now you get me out.
I got you... Listen, you
got yourself into this.
I warned you that
futures are risky.
Everything I own is on the
line here. This will ruin me.
You roll the dice, you'd
better be able to cover the bet.
Those calls
come due in a few days,
and you're legally required
to make good on them.
But I don't
have the cash.
Can't you stall?
Buy me some time?
I'm sorry. There's
nothing more I can do.
Uhhhh!
Barbara: Thanks.
Hey there.
Hmm?
Sweetheart.
Ha ha. Hi, Dad.
Sorry I'm late.
[Kissing]
Wow, look at you.
Honey,
you're a knockout.
Well, thanks, Dad.
Someone's been
looking for you.
Boy, is he
one lucky guy.
Hey, what's the idea of
keeping me waiting so long?
Oh, just playing
hard to get.
She is hard to get.
Dad!
Well, before your dance
card fills up, may I?
I got the next dance.
Oh, don't count on it.
Radio: Expect record highs
for the rest of the week,
with temperatures
in the mid 90s.
[Changes stations]
Jeez!
Ohh!
Aah!
[Groaning]
Hello, Gregory.
Victor? My God,
is that you?
You're a hard man to
get a hold of, Doctor.
Your secretary wouldn't give me an
appointment until next September.
Now, is that any way to
treat an old colleague?
What do you want?
I've got a patient
who needs you.
Leaving so soon?
I have to
work late tonight.
I've heard that before.
I'll call you tomorrow,
Ronnie. I promise.
I've heard
that one, too.
We're gonna
dance some more.
Barbara will
give me a ride home.
Have a nice time.
Hmph. I wish I were.
♪ Are the stars
out tonight? ♪
Hey, I thought you
wanted to dance some more.
I do, but, um, first I
wanted to ask you something.
What?
Well, I... I
was wondering...
What?
You want to go up
the coast for the weekend?
Sure. With who?
With me.
Oh.
There's a jazz festival
up in Rockport,
and there's all kinds of
stuff going on at the beach.
Sounds fun.
I'd love to.
Really?
Hey, that's great!
♪ And I only have eyes ♪
♪ For you ♪
♪ Doo bop de bop ♪
Whew!
Ahh!
Alfred, would you mind turning
up the air-conditioning?
[Splash]
Good heavens!
Strange.
There's not
a cloud in the sky.
Belongs to someone
named Belson.
[Sighs]
It's not good.
When her containment
vessel ruptured,
her disease
relapsed.
She's got a couple
of weeks at best.
What?
Don't shoot
the messenger, Victor.
I'm just telling you
like it is.
Nothing can save her now,
short of an organ transplant.
Then do it.
Impossible. You need
a compatible donor,
and there's a patient
waiting list a mile long.
We'd never get
the organ in time.
I have confidence you'll
find a way, Gregory.
Don't threaten me, Victor.
I'm the only hope she's got.
And this is
going to cost you.
I mean, the kind of service we're
talking about here doesn't come cheap.
Ah, Gregory, I see
you haven't changed.
Gold?
There aren't any
available organs.
What about these?
Not compatible.
Nora's blood type
is extremely rare.
There aren't any
deceased donors that match.
Then we'll have
to use a live donor.
What? Are you crazy?
They'd die.
I know.
Man, you're
a piece of work.
I said I'd help,
but this...
this is gonna cost you more
than a little gold nugget.
I mean,
the risks involved...
This is just a small
sample from a large vein
I discovered
in the Arctic.
You do this,
and it's yours...
all of it.
These hospital files list
every blood donor in Gotham.
We want someone who is approximately
the same weight, height, and female.
Here's one.
Perfect.
Her name is...
Barbara Gordon.
♪ Am I blue? ♪
[Telephone rings]
[Turns volume down]
Hello?
Belson: Barbara Gordon?
No, she's not here. This
is Jenny, her roommate.
What time do you
expect her in?
She won't be back
till Monday.
Who is this, please?
This is County
Memorial Hospital.
Barbara's listed with us
as a blood donor.
Oh, she and her boyfriend
went out to dinner,
and then they're headed up
the coast for the weekend.
We've got an emergency. Do you
know where they went for dinner?
Well, I think she said
Shaugnessy's over on Madison.
[Big band
swing music plays]
[Crowd cheering]
Thanks.
Whoa!
Hey!
Didn't spill a drop.
Ugh!
Ha ha ha ha ha.
Oh, man!
It could
have been worse.
Yeah, how?
It could
have been me.
We got enough left
for a toast?
Sure.
What'll we drink to?
Mmm, how about the kiss
you're about to give me?
I'll drink to that.
- Hey!
- Aah!
- Ohh!
- [Bears growl]
- [Grrr]
Mr. Freeze?
- Aah! -
Aah! - Aah!
You, fruitcake!
No pets allowed!
[Grrr]
Which one of you
is Barbara Gordon?
Him.
Uhh!
[Grrr]
No! No! Aah! Aah!
Please, no!
Get him off me!
I'll ask again.
Which one of you
is Barbara Gordon?
Barbara, no!
I am.
Let him go.
Come with me.
Man: Get the gun!
[Grrr]
Notchka,
don't let her go.
[Grrr]
Uhh!
Stop it! I'll come with
you. Just don't hurt him.
[Grrr]
Shaka, come!
Uhh!
Aah!
Here, take my Corvette.
All units, this is unit 7
in pursuit of a grey van moving
east on highway 10. Request backup.
Dispatcher:
Roger, unit 7.
Hey!
Uhh!
Huh?
- Look out!
- Hey!
[Whistles]
Aah!
Ugh!
Ohh.
Mmm.
Who are you?
I'm a doctor.
Keep still.
Where am I?
Take these.
You'll feel better.
Hey!
Oof! Ungh!
Why'd you kidnap me?
Freeze:
Silence!
Aah!
Oof!
Do as you're told.
Take them.
Victor, no!
Miss Gordon obviously prefers not
to take any medication right now.
Why don't we give her
some time to herself?
I want to know
what's going on here.
[Sighs]
[Siren]
I want checkpoints
on a 20-mile radius
at I-13, I-54,
and out to route 27,
choppers in the air
with infrared scopes,
and a door-to-door search of every
possible hideout within 50 miles.
Montoya, set up a command
post in the operations room.
Right.
Did you get a rundown
on the license plate?
It's a stolen van.
They found it ditched in
Brisco Canyon about an hour ago.
All right, that's
pretty rugged terrain.
They can't have gotten
too far if they're on foot.
Set up checkpoints
at a 20-mile radius
and search every inch all
the way down to the ocean.
A guy in a weird suit with polar
bears can't be hard to spot.
I want my daughter found,
I want her found now!
Don't worry, sir.
We're on it.
Then why are you still
standing here talking to me?
Come on,
let's move out.
Dick, you OK?
Sorry, Commissioner.
I... I tried to stop it.
I know. When I get
my hands on this guy...
Jim, why would Freeze
want Barbara?
I don't know.
And how did he know
she was at that night-club?
Bullock: Her roommate.
Said someone called from the
hospital with an emergency.
Barbara's listed
as a blood donor.
Did she get a name?
No. The guy
hung up on her.
Get a hold of the phone records
and see if you can trace that call.
Commissioner, the rest of the
witnesses are in interrogation.
On my way.
Dick, thanks again
for trying to save her.
Mr. Grayson, what
is your blood type?
"O" positive.
[Beep] I need to get you down to x-ray.
You wait here.
I'll get a wheelchair.
Shut the door.
Does it say who
accessed her file?
No.
She has a rare blood type.
Not many others
on the list.
Wait a minute.
Look at this.
Nora Fries?
Victor Fries' wife.
[Metal banging]
She's over
the next room.
She's headed towards
the north-west corner.
[Door opens]
[Gasps]
Get away from her.
You get away from me.
Give it up, Barbara.
There's no place
to run.
Everybody,
just calm down.
No. You calm down!
I want to know
what I'm doing here.
I'm
Dr. Gregory Belson.
That's
Victor Fries.
I know who he is.
Everyone in Gotham
knows you.
And I know
who that is, too.
I thought
your wife was dead.
She will be dead
if you don't help her.
That's what this is
about, isn't it?
It's about her.
Belson: She needs an operation
that requires a transfusion.
You're one of the few people
with her rare blood type.
Uh-huh.
So why here?
She should be
in a hospital.
No hospitals
and no more questions.
Victor, you wouldn't
let her die, would you?
Listen, you kidnap me,
then expect me to cooperate?
I'll help her
but not here.
Not this way.
Enough talk!
Victor, no!
Don't freeze her!
- Aah!
The door!
[Gasps]
- [Snarl]
- [Grrr]
Aah!
Come on!
Whew!
Aah!
[Snarling]
Mariko?
Bruce! Dick! What a
nice surprise. Come in.
Come in.
What can I do for you?
Was wondering if you
might be able to help.
Are you kidding? One of our
major investors? What do you need?
How much do you know about the
medical aspects of cryogenics?
Well, it's not exactly
my specialty,
but I have done some reading
on it. What do you want to know?
Under what conditions would a person
who's been cryogenically frozen
need a blood
transfusion?
As far as I know,
never.
That's the point
of the procedure.
You really ought to talk to someone
who's more of an expert, though.
Who's the foremost authority
on the subject around here?
Oh, that's easy.
Dr Gregory Belson.
He did a lot of the original
research on the subject
with Victor Fries.
I'd like to talk to him.
Good luck. No one's seen
him for the past week.
Where is he?
Who knows? Comes and goes as he pleases.
Frankly,
he's kind of a jerk.
Belson's name was on the
registration of a wrecked car
Alfred and I found after
the party the other night.
It was surrounded
by water.
Melted ice.
Right.
So what does Freeze want
with the doctor?
Let's find out.
[Struggling]
You don't have to
chain me up, you creep.
Try to escape again, I'll
chain your feet as well.
How can you treat people
this way?
It's the way they've always treated me.
Nora was the only
good thing in my life.
Then they took her from me.
I don't care what I have
to do to get her back.
Nothing here
except some stock reports.
Keep looking.
Gregory, this is your broker
calling for the third time.
Payment is due
on those options,
and accounting is
breathing down my neck.
You can call me
at home.
The number's
555-0173.
Let's take care
of this, OK?
Hope it's a listed number.
Bingo.
Dinner.
Who are you?
My name is Koonak.
You're just a kid.
What are you
doing here?
Did Freeze
kidnap you, too?
No.
And I'm not just a kid.
I'm 12.
12, huh?
And very handsome.
You're kind of cute,
too, lady.
You sure
you're just 12?
13 next summer.
So where are
your parents, Koonak?
They're dead.
Oh, I'm sorry.
But Mr. Freeze
takes care of me now.
Freeze?
You got to be kidding.
You don't like him,
do you?
It's kind of hard
to like someone
who kidnaps you
and chains you up.
He just wants
his wife back.
He's not really bad.
You know this isn't right, Koonak.
Help me get out of here,
and I promise I'll do
everything I can to help her.
Sorry, lady. I can't.
You won't hurt her,
will you?
No, of course not.
Your wife's vital signs
have stabilized.
We'll be able to start the
operation in a couple of hours.
Good.
Aah!
Shh.
Please don't hurt me.
Where's Belson?
Belson?
I wish I knew.
I'm telling you
the truth.
What's your interest
in him?
I'm his stockbroker.
He owes $21/2 million,
and if he doesn't pay
by Friday,
they're going
to foreclose on him.
What are you
talking about?
Belson had inside
information on a new drug
that was going public.
He leveraged futures
with everything he had.
Then some side effects
were discovered,
and the FDA put everything
on hold.
He lost big time.
I want to see
his portfolio
and any holdings
he might have in...
[Telephone rings]
Hello.
Man:
Dean, this is Gregory.
Gregory?
Where are you?
You have to buy me one
more week with the S. E. C.
Stall them.
Say whatever you have to,
but I'll have cash
by then.
You will? How?
You said...
I know what I said.
But I just struck gold.
[Ship's horn blows]
So you'll take care
of that, right?
Where are you?
Never mind.
Just keep them from
foreclosing for one more week,
and they'll have
their money.
Got to go.
Gregory, wait a minute.
Alfred, run this list
of medical supplies
I found on Belson's desk.
I want to know what this
stuff would be used for.
Cross-reference it against
all likely medical procedures.
Very good, sir.
Arbagast's voice:
You said...
Belson's voice:
I know what I said.
But I just
struck gold.
So you'll take
care of that, right?
[Ship's foghorn blows]
That's a ship's
foghorn.
He's somewhere
near the water.
But the police have combed
every inch of the coast.
Listen to it again.
There's something else
in the background.
I'll try to enhance it.
Belson:
I just struck gold.
So you'll take care
of that, right?
Sounds like a bell.
Or a buoy.
Those are
the shipping lanes.
No wonder the police can't
find him on the coast.
Why?
He's 5 miles offshore
in the middle
of the ocean.
There's an abandoned
oil derrick out there.
[Gasps]
Miss Gordon,
we're ready to begin.
Well, I'm not.
I'm afraid
you have no choice.
Hyah!
Grab her!
No!
Hold her legs.
Pardon me, sir.
I've just completed
the research on this list,
and I found something
rather disturbing.
What is it?
It seems these
are surgical supplies
used in
an allograft procedure.
Oh, no.
What is it?
It's the medical term
for an organ transplant.
What?
I think
you'd better hurry.
Ow!
You're hurting me!
Let me go!
Belson:
Get her inside.
Barbara: Let me go!
Belson:
Put her on the table.
I'll get the anesthesia.
You don't need to put me
under for a blood transfusion.
It's more than that,
isn't it?
Hold her.
You promised
not to hurt her.
Koonak,
get out of here.
Stop it!
Hey!
Get away!
Aah!
Hyah!
Nora!
No! Nora!
Freeze: Don't let her get away.
I'll get her back!
Look. There.
Robin: Someone's there, all right.
Wait a minute.
I see something.
There's Barbara!
Hurry!
Hang on.
Stop shooting,
you idiot.
These are
fuel tanks.
Come down now!
Up here.
Are you all right?
[Gasps]
It's OK.
I got him.
Wait.
Now!
Help!
Batman: Over there!
Shoot me a line!
Stand back!
Hurry!
You!
Look out!
Aah!
Barbara!
We got to get out of here!
I'm working on it.
She's behind the generators. Over there.
You go that way.
Are you crazy?
There's no way now.
We're going
to finish this.
You're insane. The whole place
is going to blow any minute.
We got to get out!
We're not leaving until
you perform that operation.
Look out!
Gregory...
help me.
Brace yourself.
My leg is broken.
Come on!
Let's get out of here.
No.
Not without Nora.
Where is she?
Down below.
There's a boy there, too.
Come on! This way!
Aah!
There's no way.
Stand back!
Hurry!
You stay here.
You need me to show you where they are.
She's right.
Robin,
get the Batwing ready.
If this place starts to
blow, get out of here.
I won't leave
without you.
Go!
We're running
out of time.
This way.
No!
[Coughing]
Come on, big guy.
I've got you.
[Explosion]
Freeze!
Is there another way out?
The elevator.
Oh, no.
Let's go.
Take them first.
You can come back
for me.
Let's go. Let's go!
If I'm not back in time,
go without me.
What? Wait!
[Gasping]
Hold on.
Aah!
Freeze!
News announcer: Today's top 2
stories come from Gotham City
where local newscaster
Summer Gleason is standing by.
Summer Gleason: In a case
that could herald a new era
in cryogenic medicine,
Nora Fries has been revived
from her frozen state
and has undergone
a vital organ transplant.
Nora Fries is the wife
of the late Victor Fries
who was killed 2 weeks ago
when an offshore
drilling platform exploded
and collapsed
into the ocean.
The transplant operation, funded
by the Waynetech Corporation
under the auspices of
its CEO, Mr. Bruce Wayne,
was today declared
a resounding success
by Dr. Lyle Johnston,
chief surgeon
at Gotham General Hospital.
Mrs. Fries is reported to be
resting in stable condition.
Ironically,
the cryogenic technology
invented by Nora's husband,
which tragically
transformed him
into the criminal
Mr. Freeze,
was credited by Dr. Johnston
as having saved her life.
It's a shame
Victor Fries will never know.
In other news,
Gotham's mysterious defender,
the Batman,
was seen last night helping
police apprehend the leaders
of an underworld
gun-running operation.
Please rate this subtitle at www.osdb.link/5ttj2
Help other users to choose the best subtitles