Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
How's the defense here?
Vice-Captain Matsumoto, nothing out of the ordinary.
This is an important assignment, don't let your guard down.
Yes, ma'am.
Just what is this "King's Seal" though?
They demanded top security, yet they're being so conspicuous.
We don't even know any details about it.
It's a treasure of the royal family.
It is forbidden for anyone to lay eyes upon it, except for the royalty.
The knowledge of this coveted treasure has been kept from the public.
We don't even have the right to know its abilities, nor how to use it.
And every few years it is taken into safekeeping, just like that.
The power to change, that is the King's Seal.
Just kidding, I don't really know myself.
Anyway, this is a mission that was entrusted to the 10th Squad.
Don't let your guard down and keep a careful watch.
Yes!
Captain!
Matsumoto?
The situation is normal at every post.
It looks quite impressive when I look at it carefully.
That's because the details are always shrouded.
Even you're saying that, Captain?
They'll get mad if you say that.
More importantly, you're...
What?
Matsumoto!
Yes!
Vice-Captain!
Surround it!
Yes!
Die.
Howl, Haineko!
Haineko (灰猫): Ash Cat
Who... are you?
Hold it!
Who are you?
Where's the King's Seal?
I don't know.
Captain!
How nostalgic.
Show your face!
Hold it!
Captain!
The King's Seal has...!
Put out those fires!
I'm on it!
Forgive us, Vice-Captain Matsumoto!
We let them escape!
We have several wounded.
Vice-Captain?
What is this?
Geez, why is there always trouble around my town.
What happened here?
You're the...
The Secret Mobile Corps?
Wait! I'm the substitute shinigami, Kurosaki Ichigo!
Hold it.
What are you doing here, Kurosaki Ichigo?
You're...
I'm Soifon, Captain of the 2nd Squad, and Commander of the Secret Mobile Corps.
I believe there was a barrier in place.
What happened?
What is all this?
Normally, I wouldn't be inclined to speak to an substitute shinigami...
W-What'd you say?
No way...
If you find it, inform me immediately.
Hey, w-wait!
Kurosaki?
Ishida? What are you doing here?
I noticed that a barrier was put up in this area.
What happened here?
Well, actually...
It's snowing.
No, he probably hid his reiatsu.
Huh? His reiatsu?
Toushirou!
Hey!
Damn... it...
Is that so?
Yes.
We searched the entire perimeter, but we could not find the King's Seal.
I believe the attackers took it.
Furthermore, I have a report on the 10th Squad Captain, Hitsugaya,
who pursued them and had been charged with the escort.
There was evidence that he sealed his reiatsu...
Please wait!
You're saying it as if he abandoned his duties!
Then why did he act that way?
This is clearly a dereliction of his duties!
But, I...!
Stop.
The entire 10th Squad is hereby placed under house arrest.
Depending on developing circumstances, be prepared to disband.
Disband?
Do you mean to completely get rid of the 10th Squad?
The squad isn't at fault!
If someone should take responsibility, it should be me, the Vice-Captain!
Silence, Matsumoto!
Do you think the life of a single Vice-Captain can compensate for this crime?
Know your place.
First, prioritize the search and recovery of the King's Seal and, at the same time,
capture the one responsible for the deaths in this incident,
the 10th Squad captain, Hitsugaya Toushirou.
This is an urgent case.
The 10th Squad is hereby confined to this shrine.
Furthermore, until we capture Captain Hitsugaya and resolve this incident,
to guard against treason, we will take your zanpakutous.
W-Why?!
No way!
You don't trust us?!
Are you telling us to just stay here and do nothing?!
That's ridiculous!
This is tyranny!
Give us the chance to prove our innocence!
This is an order!
Vice-Captain!
Vice-Captain Matsumoto!
Excuse us.
I guess that's all.
They don't know anything yet, then.
Yet...
It just shows how important the stolen King's Seal is.
I'm sure Captain Hitsugaya will return soon.
Yeah.
Damnit, why does everyone just disappear without saying anything?
Captain Hitsugaya is different from Ichimaru!
Renji.
We've finished collecting the zanpakutou.
We'll take them to storage now.
Very well.
Everyone is to wait here patiently and await further instructions.
We'll be closing the shrine now.
Please return to the line, Vice-Captain Matsumoto.
It's time, Vice-Captain Abarai.
All right, I'll go now.
Let's go.
Excuse us.
Wait!
There's one thing I want you to investigate.
The man that the captain chased,
I think he has something to do with the captain.
Otherwise, the captain wouldn't have done that.
Are you the rumored boy genius, Hitsugaya Toushirou?
Who are you?
I'm going to become a shinigami, and risk my life for soul society!
Oh? Really?
I...
That's amazing, Toushirou! You really are a genius!
That has nothing to do with it.
I won't lose next time though.
Toushirou, we'll always be friends, right?
Where is this?
Hey.
Kurosaki?
Where is this?
My house.
You were all beat up, I couldn't just leave you.
I see, thank you.
The Secret Mobile Corps are searching for you.
Yeah.
"Yeah?" That's it?
Why are you hiding?
Say something!
It has nothing to do with you.
You bastard...!
Well, whatever.
I have to get it back.
They stole the royal treasure, the King's Seal.
This isn't something a substitute shinigami should be involved with.
You've really got zero charm, you know that?
H-hey, you okay?
It's nothing.
Sorry, but I need a little more rest.
Sheesh, I'll call Inoue tomorrow morning, so just stay still until then.
Man...
Stop sneaking around!
If you're going to leave, then leave through the front door!
Why are you acting like a fugitive?
Thank you for taking care of me.
Why are you going by yourself?
Why are you brooding over this so much?
What are you trying to say?
Does it have to do with this "Kusaka?"
Who is he?
Was Kusaka the one who attacked you and stole the King's Seal?
It's the name of a man who was killed.
Killed?
By who?
Toushirou!
What are you doing?!
Don't interfere!
Shut up! You were thrashed and bleeding at my feet, you expected me to leave you?!
Either I report you to the Secret Mobile Corps, or you go back to my house. Choose.
Who's there?!
Hand Hitsugaya Toushirou over to us.
What'd you say?
If you get in our way, then we'll eliminate you!
Toushirou!
What's going on?
Please!
Then how about this?!
Getsuga Tenshou!
Getsuga Tenshou (月牙天衝): Lunar Fang Piercing the Heavens
How could he repel that attack?
Just who is that man?
Wait!
Toushirou!
What are you trying to do?
Pull yourself together, Ichigo.
Ichigo!
How pathetic.
Well, looks like I win.
Wake up, damn Ichigo!
See? My way got him up faster, right?
You bastard! What the hell was that for?
It's your fault for staying knocked out!
What'd you say?
What happened, Ichigo?
Damnit...
Just how long was I out?
Where did Toushirou go?
Toushirou?
Don't tell me, you met Captain Hitsugaya?
When? Where he'd go?
You...
That coat... belongs to Captain Hitsugaya.
That guy...
Why didn't you stop him?
I did! But he just left!
He chased after some weird girls.
Girls?
They looked like Vizards, or Arrancar...
I don't really know.
So, what did Captain Hitsugaya say?
He didn't say anything?
Well, he said he'd get back the King's Seal.
But that's not it.
He had to...
That's right, who's Kusaka?
Kusaka?
He said it's the name of a man who was killed.
And then he...
Renji, can you go back to Soul Society and look into this Kusaka?
It might have to do with the attackers that Vice-Captain Matsumoto was talking about.
Sure, but why me?
I don't think I'll be allowed to meet with her.
Plus...
I don't like playing this role.
We don't need two shinigami.
We must decide,
We must choose...
One must be chosen!
The rightful owner!
Then I'll give up Hyourinmaru!
You cannot defy us.
You cannot doubt us.
The decisions of the Central 46 Chambers are absolute.
Stop! Kusaka is...
Kusaka is my important...!
How was Hitsugaya?
It seems the Gotei 13 haven't made contact with him yet.
Shall we capture him before they do?
No, let us keep watch a bit more.
As long as his power is the same as mine, he no longer belongs anywhere.
He'll have no choice but to join us.
Captain Hitsugaya entered the Shinou Spiritual Institute
after I was taken in by the Kuchiki family, so I don't really know.
We grew up in different parts of Rukongai.
I in Inuzuri and Captain Hitsugaya in Junrinan.
I heard that the 5th Squad's Vice-Captain Hinamori was like a sister to him.
Then we should talk to Hinamori.
Yeah.
Unfortunately, she's recuperating right now.
Also, this is just a guess, but I don't believe he told her anything important.
Even more so if it's a burden.
I think he's that kind of person.
He's strong.
He's not strong at all.
If he was so strong, why would he worry everyone around him?
There's no point thinking it over anymore.
I'll use some of my resources at hand, everyone is to search for Captain Hitsugaya.
No! Meeting Vice-Captain Matsumoto Rangiku is forbidden!
Come on!
We're just going to talk!
No, no! This is an order from the Commander-General and 2nd Squad Captain Soifon!
So all you can do is follow orders?
You otter-face.
What'd you say?
Did you just make fun of me?
I didn't.
You just called me a otter-face!
I don't know what you're talking about!
How lively!
Captain Kyouraku.
I'll go in with him, that'll be fine right?
You can't trust the 8th Squad Captain?
Kusaka?
I don't know, I've never heard of him.
I see.
How could a Vice-Captain not know anything about their Captain?
First, there are several things we don't know.
How is Captain Hitsugaya related to this Kusaka?
Just who is he?
Is he related to the incident?
And if he is, why?
One mystery after another.
We just need to look into it.
Could you?
It's impossible to know everything there is to know about a person.
It may take some time, but if we don't know, we'll just have to dig deeper.
Isn't it simple?
What, Captain?
Just as expected from Nanao-chan!
I'm sure you can do it, right?
Please help us!
Thanks a lot, Nanao. I'll pay you back someday.
You can thank us with this.
You wouldn't mind helping me then, Captain?
Eh? Me too?
Of course!
There's also this.
This is from Rukia and Ichigo in the real world.
He's hurt.
According to Ichigo, it's pretty bad.
Yet he left this and disappeared.
I don't know whether to be happy that he's alive,
or to be angry that he left his coat behind.
Well...
Man...
Everyone's so worried, so what the heck is he doing?
My name is Hyourinmaru.
Hyourinmaru (氷輪丸): The Icy Moon
Child, will you be the one to wield me?
That's right!
Obey me, Hyourinmaru!
I did it. I did it!
Toushirou?
What a coincidence.
I'm happy we got the same power.
I've researched the names of all Captains for the last 50 years, but there's no one named Kusaka.
Did you go back and search through the Spiritual Arts Academy?
Yes, there was no similar name there.
But I discovered a discrepancy in the number of registered students in Hitugaya's graduating class.
The missing student was registered in the north of Rukongai.
Of those registered from that district, was there a student named Kusaka?
There was.
Here he is...
Kusaka Sojiro.
This is Kusaka, eh?
He's... dead?
He's not on the registry. Maybe they just forgot to write it in?
No, something like that shouldn't be possible, right?
Especially if he died.
But with this, at least, the possibility of the assailant being Kusaka Sojiro is gone, right?
As soon as the extinguishment of his reiatsu was confirmed,
he should have been dead, however...
"However..." what?
I'm taking a little walk.
Nanao-chan, look into the cause of death.
Captain!
My, my... who is it?
Your silence is piquing my curiosity.
Kyouraku Shunsui...
That frivolous behavior is a mask for your prudence...
You wield your charisma and swagger like a finely honed blade.
You'd sniffed me out from the beginning after all?
What a compliment.  But instead of talking about me, how about talking about yourself?
That's unnecessary.
You'll be slain right here by Hitsugaya Toushirou.
That zanpakutou...
Show your face...
You're...
Captain Hitsugaya! It's the special forces.
We urge you. Please return to Seireitei.
I have no intention of obeying.
Please stop this. Further actions will be regarded as treason.
Stand down, Kira! Hisagi!
Captain Hitsugaya, I'm taking you into custody.
You'll die...
Way of Binding #62: A Hundred Stepped Rails!
Please come quietly...
Reign over the frozen sky... Hyourinmaru!
The preparation for the Spirit-cleansing barrier is complete.
I will start the surgery immediately.
It's my fault.
It wasn't under your control.
Captain Ukitake.
If Kyouraku was defeated, it's either because his opponent surprised him,
or truly was more powerful than him.
Am I wrong?
However?
I'll say once more.
It's not your fault.
Right now, the 6th Squad is investigating the scene.
We'll catch the assassin right away.
There's no mistake about it. It's Hyourinmaru!
What? Hyourinmaru?
Captain Hitsugaya.
You don't look like you have good news, either.
Reporting.
Kira Izuru of the 3rd Squad and Hisagi Shuuhei of the 9th Squad
engaged Captain Hitsugaya, and were severely injured in the real world.
He turned on them?
Toushirou-kun attacked his friends?
That's not all...
...it seems that Captain Kyouraku was attacked.
Kyouraku-san?
According to what Renji told me, he was attacked with Hyourinmaru, and is in serious condition.
Ishida, can you track his reiatsu?
It's your specialty, right?
It's impossible.
Shit, he slipped through our fingers again.
It's morning already...
Sorry, everyone.
Let's go home, and meet up again in the afternoon.
Don't you worry, I'm fine...
No, it will be alright.
Even if we rush it, it doesn't mean we'll find him right away, so...
Hitsugaya Toushirou is suspected of treason, and is hereby suspended from the Gotei Squads.
Excuse my interruption, but is that not something of a political measure?
I will take no objections!
The search for the King's Seal is to continue. Furthermore,
Hitsugaya Toushirou's capture is also of high priority.
If he shows signs of resistance, then...
execute him immediately!
Ichigo, it's Renji.
A Gotei Squad order has been issued.
What's that?
An execution order has been issued for Captain Hitsugaya.
An execution order? What the hell?
Looks like there was no time for debate and no chance of pardon.
What?
Rukia, there's more. We found out about Kusaka.
Ichigo.
Yeah, I heard it.
Kisaka Sojiro. He's Captain Hitsugaya's former classmate.
He died before graduating from the Spiritual Arts Academy.
You!
We warned you...
If you interfered, you'd be done for.
Shinigami, huh?
Who's there?
Ichigo, that man is very capable.
That's no ordinary reiatsu.
That's Hyourinmaru!
You have it backwards, Kyouraku...
I'm supposed to be the one that's sick and bedridden.
But now...
There is one thing that still troubles me.
If you compare the time of the attack by Hyourinmaru,
and the time the search crew found Captain Hitsugaya,
no matter what path you take to the Real World...
it should take longer.
Assuming they were both the same Hyourinmaru...
Reign over the frozen sky...
Hyourinmaru!
Why do you...
Because I am the true master of Hyourinmaru!
What did you say?
Twin zanpakutou, you said?
Zanpakutou are born from the shinigami's own soul.
First, the link between zanpakutou and shinigami is a binding contract.
Second, it is impossible to have a zanpakutou with multiple binding contracts.
That's not a zanpakutou.
Can you prove that something of that sort couldn't exist?
That there couldn't have been more than one Hyourinmaru?
Hyourinmaru?
Assuming there were two shinigami, then one of the owners must be...
I see!
Now I understand the reason you've asked me to investigate this...
Hacking into the Great Spiritual Libraries is nothing to me.
You... who the hell are you?
My name? Kusaka Sojiro!
This is...!
The man who, in the Central 46 Chambers of Seireitei,
was murdered by Hitsugaya Toushirou!
Soul Society has declared Hitsugaya Toushirou to be a criminal.
He has no place to return to.
The only remaining wild card is you.
Now you will die, shinigami!
Toushirou!
- Kusaka! Why?
The decision of the Central 46 Chambers is as follows.
It is forbidden for one zanpakutou to belong to two shinigami.
For that reason, today both parties will face each other...
and decide the issue through a duel.
Do you mean for us to kill each other?
One's righteous nature...
One's own abilities...
For its sheer power, you should feel honored to wield Hyourinmaru.
I refuse! If I'm to fight with Kusaka, I'd rather relinquish Hyourinmaru!
Tou...
- Not allowed!
That is forbidden!
Forbidden!
Why can't we have the same zanpakutou?
It is decided.
Because that is the law.
A law that has been in place since the beginning of time.
You cannot go against it.
We won't allow questioning!
We won't allow it!
Fight!
Battle!
Hitsugaya...
Kusaka...
Hey!
Who are you people?
What?
The match has been decided. Hitsugaya Toushirou will wield Hyourinmaru.
This duel isn't finished!
Hyourinmaru is mine!
It's been decided by the Six Scholars.
Please wait! Just once more...
Kusaka!
Why am I...
The one who has to die?
Why?
I... swore my life to Soul Society...
Kusaka!
Hitsugaya is on my side as a friend.
I won't let you get in the way!
Hyourinmaru!
Ichigo!
Hyourinmaru's powers are growing.
It's time. I'll let you two clean up here.
Yes.
Way of Destruction #33: Soukatsui!
Soukatsui (蒼火墜): Blue Fire Crash
Zangetsu!
It's been a while, Ichigo.
What was that just now? A hallucination?
Resonance.
When two zanpakutous clash, as they resonate, they will reveal their past.
Then...
Yeah. It's all true.
So because two Hyourinmarus happened to exist...
Soul Society killed a man?!
Why?!
Because that is the custom.
In Soul Society, the highest and most revered law is to maintain balance.
Those bastards. Don't they care about people's emotions?
You sure say strange things.
The world's fate cannot rely on our feeble sentiments.
No matter how powerful the emotion, there is no comparison.
Is your world any different?
Nevertheless...
Human hearts waver, falter, and inevitably plunge into darkness.
You're wrong.
He...
Toushirou isn't like that.
Why do you believe that?
Because...
Don't, Ichigo!
Because I once suffered the same way.
Not long after my mom died...
A lot of different emotions surfaced within me.
It felt like I was drowning in them.
But, I kept all of those feelings locked up inside.
I thought it was something everyone had to do.
I didn't realize how much you hurt yourself by doing that.
Toushirou had the same expression as I had back then!
He's keeping everything inside!
That's it.
I figured it out...
What he's trying to do.
Thanks.
If you can see the future, don't ever look back.
Strike forward, never hesitate.  Go, Ichigo!
Rukia!
Ichigo... Are you okay?
Yeah, where is Kusaka?
Sorry, he got away.
Alright, then we will have to beat these guys and chase after him.
I figured it out...
What Toushirou wants to do.
He survived Kusaka-sama's attack...
What an annoying little pest.
We must defeat him.
Obviously!
I have to tell him...
...no matter what happens!
You finally found me.
I've been waiting for you.
Kusaka!
I wounded you with Hyourinmaru for a reason.
Do you believe now that I am alive?
It doesn't really matter, does it, Hitsugaya?
We've been trapped at this crossroads long enough, wouldn't you say?
Crossroads?
You've seen what the Gotei 13 Squads are capable of!
Even so, you still stay with them?
Maybe it's because of that girl?
Leave Hinamori out of this, where's the King's Seal?
Right here, where it belongs. This power will make our dreams come true, right?
Dreams...
Of course.
What is the power of the King's Seal?! How do you know about it?!
There is no need to rush, you'll know its power soon enough.
Now, let's go.
What?
Rukia, what is that?
I don't know...
This reiatsu is so powerful and pure, I've never felt anything like it.
It can't be!
That is the King's Seal's true power!
It's begun! The vengeance of Kusaka-sama and Hitsugaya Toushirou against Seireitei!
What? Seireitei?
You are a risk, and thus you must be eliminated at all costs!
We won't let you interfere in Kusaka-sama's plans!
Hollows?!
Hollows, charge!
Excuse me, reiatsu from the King's Seal has appeared above Soukyoku Hill.
Vice-Captain!
Hey, you guys aren't supposed to leave! Got that!?
What the hell is that?!
Captain!
Emergency alert: To all search parties in Soul Society and the Real World,
The reiatsu of both Captain Hitsugaya and the thief of the King's Seal has been detected upon Soukyoku Hill.
Please, return and immediately begin emergency defensive procedures.
I repeat, please return and immediately begin emergency defensive procedures.
For the intruders to have trespassed so easily...
The enemy must have known that the Gotei 13 Squads were in disarray.
The enemy?
He is Captain Hitsugaya.
This is...
Right, this is Soukyoku Hill. This is the power of the King's Seal.
The King's Seal grants the ability to traverse time, space, and the infinite dimensions.
In other words, it makes teleportation into child's play.
I can deflect any attack by merely sending it to another dimension before it arrives.
If I do get injured, I can return my body to any point in time before the injury.
Kusaka, that means...?
Yes, I was transported to Hueco Mondo and reincarnated there.
I have searched for the power of the King's Seal ever since...
In order to exact my revenge on Seireitei!
Toushirou!
Cut it open with your bankai.
Cut it?
The King's Seal?
Yes, and after that, everything will turn to dust!
Looks like we're first.
Looks like it, Ikkaku.
Captain Hitsugaya! Why?
Shut it, Renji.
Talking is useless at this point.
Based on the emergency alert and our own orders,
we are to arrest Hitsugaya Toushirou, and the one who stole the King's Seal.
Madarame Ikkaku.
Among the Gotei 13, you are the most skilled at combining raw power and skillful technique.
Flattery will get you nothing.
However you are not my opponent.
Is that so?!
Even with that wound...
You're still serious about this?
Why are you pushing yourself so far?!
Captain Hitsugaya!
Stay out of my way...
There're so many...!
Kurosaki!
Didn't you say that if anything happened,
you would tell me?!
The Hollows are...!
Damn them!
My Ginrei Kojaku can fire 1200 rounds per second.
Ginrei Kojaku (銀嶺弧雀): Silver Mountain Arcing Sparrow
You can't summon those Hollows anywhere near fast enough!
Are you alright, Kurosaki-kun?
Ishida, you jerk!
You could have hit me!
My aim is better than that.
Anyway,
They're coming.
It's huge.
Ishida, I'll take care of this—
El Directo!
Now's your chance, Ichigo.
Get to Soul Society!
Urahara-san is currently preparing a Senkaimon.
Senkaimon (穿界門): World Penetration Gate
We'll deal with these guys.
Save Toushirou-kun!
You guys...
We're off, Rukia.
Be careful, Inoue.
Yeah.
That's enough!
Captain!
Surrender, Hitsugaya!
And that man behind you.
Ridiculous.
Just who...
Are you?!
Toushirou.
What are you doing?
Unleash your rage!
Show them our grudge...
Show them our suffering!
This will be our revenge!
Cut it, Toushirou!
Seize them!
Getsuga Tenshou!
What?
Stop it!
Can't you guys do anything other than fight?!
You don't know anything about Toushirou!
Just because it's been ordered,
you shouldn't just attack him the first chance you get!
Stay out of this, substitute!
This is part of the squad's duty!
They are following orders from a superior officer. This is the rule we live by, no matter the cost!
I just told you, you don't understand!
There's no use arguing!
If you still oppose us, we will cut you down too!
Wait!
Captain-Commander Yamamoto Genryuusai Shigekuni!
Kyouraku! You're conscious again?
Seems that way.
I can't sleep properly when the innocent are being persecuted.
So you're alive, Kusaka Sojiro!
You thought you had killed me?
The King's Seal gave you life...
...and you were raised in Hueco Mundo.
Yeah.
And so I've returned!
Thanks to the King's Seal, I got my life back,
And I will use the King's Seal to become the King of Soul Society!
Soul Society's King, you say?
How arrogant!
You're the ones who are arrogant.
You should realize this!
Captain!
Stay back, Matsumoto!
This is my battle.
What's the meaning of this, Toushirou?!
I...
I never had any intention of helping you.
He never betrayed the Gotei 13 Squads.
Then why did he point his blade at us?
You're going to cut me down?
You're going to kill me again?!
I am merely atoning for my sin.
And what is your sin?
How can you atone for it by killing me?
I see.
Kusaka originally...
swore his allegiance to Soul Society.
However, just because there were twin zanpakutou,
he was exiled and killed, and couldn't attain honor in Soul Society.
Yes.
And he blames his friend's pain all on himself.
Captain Hitsugaya couldn't bear to kill Kusaka again, not with his current status among the Gotei 13.
Is that what you meant?
To settle this,
he needed to strip himself of his status among the squads.
Even if that meant he would be the one to be executed this time.
So from the very start...!
That's right!
I see.
So I misunderstood you.
Then I will do this on my own!
Answer my call, King's Seal!
Just what...?!
I couldn't get you to release it using your bankai...
But, I can do it now...
Kusaka!!
You're not the only one drowning in pain.
Move, Kurosaki!
You don't have to shoulder this burden alone!
Let the ones around you understand and take some of the pain, and the resolve that goes with it!
I'm not a Captain anymore.
You decided that by yourself!
But have you even considered,
how the people around you feel?!
I once knew someone like you who didn't rely on others,
I understand people like you...
Older brother!
Older brother.
Yuzu, Karin.
Why are you in such a hurry?
Ichi-nii...
Why are you smiling?
"Why"?
Ichigo.
We all understand your feelings,
After all, we're a family, aren't we?
Happy things, sad things.
We share all those things.
Otherwise, won't we get lonely?
But.
In fact, that person was the weakest of them all!
Captain!
Captain Hitsugaya!
Toushirou!
Heads up, Kurosaki.
He's coming.
It's mine at last!
So this is the power of the King's Seal!
Kenpachi!
Over already?
Guess you were all talk—
What?
Your attacks...
are useless against me!
You aren't dead yet?
Interesting!
You're mine!
It's useless!
You're in the way.
Amazing.
This is an amazing power!
What's that?
They're... Kusaka's...!
Why are you in such terrible condition?
Don't tell me you ran away?
We have no excuse.
Well, that's fine.
No!
Is he transforming again?!
Do not be afraid!
Stand your ground!
The criminal, Kusaka Sojiro, must be eliminated!
Yes!
Let's go.
Ichigo!
Captain!
Scatter,
Senbonzakura.
Senbonzakura (千本桜): A Thousand Cherry Blossoms
Howl, Zabimaru!
Zabimaru (蛇尾丸): The Snaketail
You're in the way!
Th-this is...?
Just what is going on?
Did he release the full power of the King's Seal?
Not quite.
The King's Seal is just rampaging.
It's what?
Look,
The reiatsu grows stronger and expands.
If it continues like this,
he'll annihilate all of Seireitei.
Annihilation?
It may be powerful, but isn't that a bit much...
The King's Seal is an weapon from another dimension,
Born in a place with complete dominion over time, space, and the infinite dimensions.
In other words,
in a contained area, the wielder becomes a god, to whom death and rebirth are trivial matters.
But.
Since Kusaka doesn't have control of his Bankai, using it to that extent is impossible.
That is to say...
We are in the most dangerous of situations at the moment.
Matsumoto?
I'm okay.
Matsumoto!
Protecting the Captain's back...
is the Vice-Captain's job.
Ow, ow, ow.
Are you alright, Rukia?
I'm fine.
Hey, Toushirou.
So you guys made it through too?
Rukia, Ichigo!
Renji, what is it?
What's it look like...
Look around.
You could call that Kusaka's castle.
And it looks like we're stuck inside his spirit barrier?
What should we do?
Like I'd know.
Ichigo!
Yoruichi-san!
We don't have much time!
The Captain-Commander is preventing this dimension from expanding any further.
Our job is to defeat Kusaka before that happens.
But, how?
You can climb, can't you?
Eh?
And,
We must cut down the core of that tower.
Now,
We should attack immediately, while he's immobile.
Right.
Wait a sec!
The real party's about to start, eh?
I'd better be invited.
Me too, of course.
It's begun?
Hollows?
Don't bother! Leave this to us!
Yoruichi-san!
Soifon, let's go!
Yes!
Shunkou!
- Shunkou!
We need to reach the pinnacle.
Yeah.
Captain.
Take this.
Matsumoto.
Yes.
Watch my back.
Yes!
We'll split into two groups.
Alright. Let's go, Renji, Rukia!
Alright!
I'm stuck with you two again?
Shut it.
What's that?
That flame is..?
Leave her to me!
Hey!
Howl!
Zabimaru!
Renji!
- Renji!
Bankai.
Baboon King, Zabimaru!
Nothing's gonna happen if you waste your time here!
Use Zabimaru as a ladder and climb up!
Got it.
She's here!
Soifon. Now!
I'll take her down!
Sting all enemies to death! Suzumebachi!
Suzumebachi (雀蜂): Hornet
The second fatal blow!
She did it?
High-speed regeneration?!
Matsumoto!
Is this beast moving?
Nope, not quite.
This reiatsu is...!
Now it's getting interesting!
Captain!
Outta my way!
Hurry upwards!
Now!
Right!
They've even summoned Menos?
Bankai!
Haineko!
Just a bit more!
If we could just break through!
Dance!
Sode no Shirayuki!
Sode no Shirayuki (袖白雪): White Snow on the Sleeves
The next dance...
Hakuren!
Hakuren (白漣): White Ripples
Damn you.
Ichigo.
Ichigo, do you see that tower?
Yeah.
If we open a path for a moment, can you get to the top of that tower with Tensa Zangetsu's speed?
What?
That's the only way!
If Ikkaku, Yumichika, and I join our powers,
We should be able to open up a path, if only for an instant.
But...
I heard that!
But, Matsumoto.
To make a path, I'll be enough.
You're gonna do it, Ikkaku?
Yeah!
Captain Hitsugaya, Matsumoto!
Keep this a secret from everyone else!
Bankai!
Ryuumon Houzukimaru!
Ryuumon Houzukimaru (龍紋鬼灯丸): Dragon-crested Demon Light
The first dance,
Tsukishiro!
Tsukishiro (月白): White Moon
Bastards!
What?
This is bad!
Prepare yourselves.
Byakuya!
The Captain-Commander and the others outside are under pressure.
Kurosaki Ichigo.
Make haste.
Renji!
Yeah.
Senkei Senbonzakura Kageyoshi!
Senkei Senbonzakura Kageyoshi (殲景 千本桜景厳): Annihilate,  Vibrant Display of a Thousand Cherry Blossoms
Hikotsu Taihou!
Hikotsu Taihou (狒骨大砲): Baboon Bone Cannon
Daiguren Hyourinmaru!
Daiguren Hyourinmaru (大紅蓮氷輪丸): The Icy Moon of Mahapadma
Getsuga Tenshou!
Ichigo.
You did it, Ichigo.
Finish this, Toushirou.
Hitsugaya.
Let's end this.
Yes, that's right...
We don't need two shinigami!
We must choose one!
Unnecessary! Unacceptable!
Fight! Fight!
Hitsugaya!
I want Hyourinmaru!
Kusaka, stop!
You truly are a prodigy.
Since you could match and kill me.
But I won't die.
I will, my existence will...
Kusaka...
You'll always...
...be my friend.
If I... can be considered one.
"If"?
Seems like it's over.
Onii-sama.
Hey?
Who won?
You fool.
Can't you tell?
Something this small...
You have my thanks, Kurosaki.
So that guy,
I wonder if he has any regrets?
Since he managed to finally settle this with you.
During life,
unfinished business clouds our purpose.
But it's up to you to peer through the illusion.
You ended up here by your own choosing.
This battle and its purpose were settled by you, and you alone.
Then,
That's good, right?
Though I, for one, could have done without this mess.
Let's go back now.
Yes.
Not Toushirou, it's Captain Hitsugaya.
Let's go.
Kakechigaeta botan dake hazushite mo
Even if we only undo the buttons that are buttoned up wrong,
bokura wa nan ni mo kawaranai daro?
nothing changes for us, right?
Bokura wa zutto koko de yume dake o mite
We’re only dreaming here forever,
nani mo shinai hodo doji ja nai no sa
so clumsy that we don’t do anything, aren’t we?
Ima made nakushita mono to
Things that I have lost up to now and things that you see from this point
kore kara kimi ga miru mono
Subete torikaeta naraba
If everything is replaced,
kawareru no kana
then will we be able to change?
Will we be able to change?
Ima made kimi ga naita koto
Tell me that you have cried until now with bashful words
hanikanda kotoba de hanashite yo
Makkuro na kokoro no yami o
Removing the darkness of my pitch-black heart
nuguisatteku
Itsuka no boku wa sutetai no
I want to throw away the old me, I want to embrace you
anata no koto dakishimetetai no
Yokubou wa kono joumyaku o
My desire flows out from my veins
nagaredashite iku
Sabaku no naka de yume dake mite ite mo
Even if we’re only dreaming within the desert,
yatsura no zurusa wa minukenai daro?
we can’t see through other people’s unfairness, right?
Bokura wa zutto koko de namida o nagashi
We’re crying tears here forever,
jibun o semeru hodo yowakanai no sa
not weak enough to blame ourselves
Ima made kimi ga kiita mono
Things that you have heard up to now;
omoide no ano uta nanka o
if I can sing that song from my recollections
Asa made utaeta naraba
Until morning,
yuruseru no kana yuruseru no kana
can you forgive me? Can you forgive me?
Ima kara boku wa utau kara
Because I’ll sing from now, melt my numbed heart
kajikanda kokoro wa tokashite yo
Makkuro na furueru yoru wa nuguisatteku
Removing the pitch-black, trembling nights
Bokura no yoru wa yogoretara
If our nights are soiled, then we can’t believe in anyone
dare no koto mo shinjirarenai no
Yokubou wa kono seijaku o yaburidashite yuku
My desire breaks out of this silence
Shounen shoujo!!
Boys and girls!!
Seishun bakusou!!
Youth rampages!
Kimi no koto dake kangaesasete okure!
Make me only think about you!
Ima made kimi ga naita koto
Tell me that you have cried until now with bashful words
hanikanda kotoba de hanashite yo
Makkuro na kokoro no yami o
Dyeing the darkness of my pitch-black heart white
shiro ni someteku
Itsuka wa shinu to kimatte mo
Even if I decide to die someday,
anata no koto wasurerarenai no
I won’t be able to forget about you
Yokubou ga kono seijaku o
kuzureochite iku
My desire crumbles this silence
Baby I love you, baby I love you!
kuzureochite iku
My desire crumbles this silence
Namida wo nagasu
Shedding tears
asa made odoru koi wo shiteiku
I'll keep this dancing love alive until dawn
See you.
Matsumoto.
Yes?
Sorry about everything... and thank you.
What did you just say Captain?
I didn't say a thing.
Let's head back now.
Eh? Do we have to?
How about we call it a day instead?
We could go to a really fantastic hot spring near here!
You can go, alone.
I can't go by myself!
Don't say that! Hey, come on!
Stop!
Please rate this subtitle at www.osdb.link/75rfc
Help other users to choose the best subtitles