Hey!
Uh...hi.
What is the status?
The area has been expanding at constant rate.
The Stealth Force is on its way to investigate.
They should be entering shortly.
l've established contact.
They'll be passing by the Dangai Precipice World in ten seconds.
Opening communication lines.
Hey! What–?! The exit!
We have an emergency!
We've failed to infiltrate the area!
Requesting immediate back-up! l repeat!
Research Technology Comm center here. We copy your back-up request.
Requesting emergency opening of Senkaimon.
They have been left behind in the Dangai Precipice World.
Notify Central 46 immediately!
Hey! Can you hear me?
Why can't you infiltrate the area? Tell us!
Get ready!
Right!
Hey!
You're not getting away!
Not so easy!
lchigo.
Yeah?
lt seems that Hollow was after this child.
lt's all right. He only looks scary.
Shut up!
All right then, let's go.
Don't worry. Soul Society is not a scary place.
lt's where all the souls come from.
But...
lf you stay here, another monster like that will come after you.
ls it over already?
Yes.
Thanks.
lchigo.
Huh?
Don't use your Combat Pass so freely.
Huh? Why?
Oww!
What's the big idea?!
You have him.
You keep leaving your body here and there, and thanks to that,
l'm the one who has to deal with the messy aftermath.
Why's that?
For example...
A passerby approaches.
"Excuse me, is something wrong?"
"Oh no, this man isn't breathing!"
"Ambulance. No, if he's dead, l must get a hearse!"
Get the idea?
Like they'd call a hearse!
That's not the point!
ln any case, it's a big hassle if there's a commotion.
Hurry! He's in cardiac arrest!
Too late...
M-My body!
You...!
Uh, hi.
Are you all right?
You still need to lie down!
l'm telling you, l'm fine!
Hey, hold him down! He's delirious!
Stop it!
Really...
Man, that was bad.
That's my line!
You're lucky l had a Memory Replacement to switch everyone's memory.
Kon.
Yes, yes!
Hey...
What's with you?!
There's no point unless you hold him!
Why do l wanna...!
Nee-san, l absolutely...!
Shut up!
What?
S-Stop! l'll get dirty!
Shut up!
There's dog poop over there!
Hope it sticks to you!
What's the meaning of this?
What? Another Hollow?
Take this!
lt got in my mouth!
lchigo.
Serves you right!
You've done it this time!
Hey!
Wait! l'm dealing with him...
The train station!
Hey!
What's with this Spiritual Pressure?
l don't know. l've never experienced this kind of Spiritual Pressure before.
What the hell are they?
White ghosts?!
No one else can see them.
They must be spirit beings.
But they don't have chains on their chests.
What's...
We have no choice.
What? Again?
Use him!
Disgusting...
Kon! Go hide somewhere!
Hey, don't leave me.. !
Hey, what are you doing?!
This is Squad 13's Kuchiki Rukia in World of the Living area 3888!
Rukia!
lchigo, try performing a Konso!
What?! A Konso?!
Unidentified spirit beings...
What the hell... lt's worth a try.
lt's not working on these guys...
Wait!
My connection with Soul Society...
What's going on?!
Stop!
Rukia!
What's this all of a sudden?!
Stop! Stop!
What's the deal with you guys?! Move it!
What'll we do?
Well...
What the–?!
A shinigami?!
What are you doing?!
Hey!
Oww! Oww! Hey, don't step on me!
What's that?
She's going to release her zanpakuto!
What?
Call forth the Twilight...
lchigo!
Stop! What the hell are you doing?!
Those things aren't Hollows!
Shut your mouth, stupid!
Stu...?!
Hey! You stepped on my face...
Call Forth the Twilight!
Mirokumaru!
What?!
Now what?
Huh? What happened to that other guy?
Sorry to keep you waiting!
Wasn't that wind so strong?
What's going on?
They vanished.
Yes! That was awesome!
That felt so good!
Oh, it's you.
YOU!
How'd you change into gigai so quickly?
l dunno.
Just who are you?
l'm a shinigami.
l know that!
lf you want to know someone's name, shouldn't you introduce yourself first?
l'm Kurosaki Ichigo.
Oh, you're pretty obedient.
My name is Senna.
Later!
Don't "Later" me! Why'd you do such a thing?
Why not?
Do you know something about those things?
Hey! What's the matter?
This is bad! l knew it!
What is it?!
Hmm... yellow just isn't my color.
Never mind that. Come!
lchigo, right?
Yeah.
Over there!
There's an unconscious man...
Kon!
Not again!
See, you better hurry!
Not so fast!
Come with me!
Hey!
l just want to ask you some questions!
The fool...
Give up already?
You gotta be kidding!
You really think it's okay for a lieutenant to be drinking in the middle of the day?
What're you saying? This is like drinking water.
Hey! lt's empty already.
What?! Already?!
You drink too much, you shaded geezer!
Shut up, baldie!
What?! Wanna go another round?!
Fine! Whoever loses gets the sake.
Got it ?!
Taking the high ground again?
The quicker one gets it!
Whatever. Here l...
What's the matter?!
What is that thing?
A Ferris wheel! Look!
l didn't know they had one of these here.
Anyway, what were you saying?
What squad do you belong to?!
l don't remember such things.
Hmm... what squad did l belong to?
Listen here. You wield a zanpakuto and know how to release it.
There is no question that you are a shinigami.
And if you are a shinigami, you must belong to a squad!
How can you not remember that?
Question, please!
Why are you here?
Well, that's...
Hey!
l said l forgot!
What does it matter, anyway?
Then do you know what those guys were back there?
Don't know that either.
Oh, he's so cute! Can l pet him?
Sure.
But l thought l should take care of them that way.
lnstinct.
You know what l mean?
What's with her?!
lchigo, l'm going to Soul Society.
l'm having trouble contacting them.
And l'm concerned about the phenomenon earlier, too.
Do not let that girl out of your sight!
Hey you! Trying to dump it on me.. !
Ahhh... nee-san... not again...
l'm counting on you.
Boy, what's she so uptight about?
Hey, lchigo!
Stupid, don't shout like that here!
She's gone!
Damm!
Hey!
Jeez, you're so persistent!
Hey, wait!
Remember when you told me that if l answered your questions, you'd do anything l asked you to?
l never said anything like that!
Let's play tag!
Hey! l told you! l never said such thing.
Wait!
Jeez!
Hey, come on out!
Where'd you go?
Hey, what's with all the fun and games?
Rangiku-san? Toshiro?
lt's been a while...
lt's not Toshiro. It's Captain Hitsugaya!
What're you two doing here anyway?
Wait up!
We need to talk.
Err, well, now's not...
Just come!
Hey!
Hey! Dammit!
l'll come back. You wait!
That man is talking to himself.
l see... Kuchiki-san went to Soul Society?
You just missed her then.
Well, where shall we start?
At 12:50AM today, above the Seireitei suddenly appeared a town from the World of the Living.
We also detected a trail of spiritual waves flowing into this world.
One minute later, we lost all communication between the two worlds.
What're you talking about?
Don't you even understand this much?
Now now...
l'll explain it to you in a simple manner.
First off, there are the World of the Living and the Soul Society.
Between them is the Dangai Precipice World, to keep these worlds from colliding.
You ran through it once. Remember?
However, about three days ago,
a new dimension appeared between the Soul Society and the World of the Living.
lt began to expand, bridging the gap and adhering to both worlds.
At this point, it appears the area that attached itself is acting like a lens
and the World of the Living is being visible
from the Soul Society, which is in a different dimension.
l guess you can say it's like a mirage.
The Stealth Force was sent out to investigate this newly created dimension, but they failed.
Our only choice now is...
to check out the influx of spiritual waves into the World of the Living.
lt was decided that l would head up the operation.
Why you?
The other captains backed out.
Never mind that!
Then it was probably those guys.
You saw something?
Yeah...
hoards of 'em, all white wearing pointy red hats.
Blanks...
As suspected, the Valley of Screams.
All right then. Explanation Number Two. Ready?
As you know, souls migrate between World of the Living and Soul Society.
From time to time however, some may encounter accidents and become detached from this Cycle of Transmigration.
These souls wander aimlessly through the Dangai Precipice World and are slowly drawn together.
As the souls come together, it causes a new dimension.
lt is known as the Valley of Screams.
There, the souls separate into memory and energy in preparation to return to the Cycle of Transmigration.
Are you following me?
l'm following!
Kurosaki-san, the ones you saw were the souls with no memory, Blanks.
What happens to the memories?
The memories merge into one entity and return to the World of the Living.
Hence, it is called a Shinenju.
That is the name for the collective of memories.
The appearance of the Valley of Screams is a natural phenomenon.
And it's existence has been verified a number of times...
But the problem is...
the Valley of Screams has connected World of the Living and Soul Society.
ls it that unnatural?
There's no way a tunnel connecting two stars can be created naturally!
This is the same thing!
There's no doubt that someone is doing this deliberately.
Hey! Speaking of which...!
Huh? What is it?
There were some guys wearing strange armor with those white monsters!
l saw it!
Armor?
Do you remember it in more detail?
Of course, l remember!
Uhh... now let's see.
l remember... l mean...
Let me analyze this.
Yes, please do.
Anyway, if this is being done intentionally, then it is done with a grudge.
What do they want?
Well, l don't know.
lt's just...
l have this feeling...
that they're looking for the Shinenju returned to the World of the Living.
That's my hunch.
We'll try to identify the enemy.
Kurosaki-san, please keep watch over the town.
They are bound to appear again.
And, if possible... find the Shinenju.
Yeah, but... l still have to find that girl, too...
Oh, sorry!
What should l do?
Wow! You really came back?!
Over here! Over here!
Of course! l still have questions l wanna ask.
Fine! Let's pick up where we left off! You're it!
Hey, listen.. !
That little.. !
All right... here goes with the legendary performance!
Take a deep breath...!
Ready, and go!
10, 9, 8, 7, 6, 5, 4, 3, 2, 1!
lt's all gone!
Well done!
Wasn't that too fast?!
No such thing. lt's good!
Over there! Up there!
Senna...!
What's that?
Huh?!
What's she doing?
ls it some kind of act?
This feels so nice.
Where'd she go?
She disappeared!
No, in the back!
How was that, everyone?!
C'mon, join me!
Err... Later.
No fair, they're getting more attention than us!
Achoo!
Itadakimasu!
lf you'd said you were treating, l'd have answered anything!
You didn't have any money?
So what about it?
What about what?
l just explained it to you.
ls there anything you know about the Blanks and the Shinenju?
Nope, l don't know anything.
So someone used those pointy-hat things to look for...
Shinen...what was it?
Shinenju.
Look for that thing, right?
Yeah.
So who is this someone?
We're checking into that, too.
For what?
l dunno.
Have you got any idea what this Shinenju looks like?
Not a clue.
You're no help at all.
You just have to wait until the pointy-hats appear again, right?
Oh well, l'll help.
But in return...
l knew it!
That!
That?
Take me for a ride on that and l'll help you with whatever you want!
l'm not fallin' for that again.
Hey!
You love heights, don't you?
lf you look at things from above,
all the things that seem confusing or messed up... suddenly become clear.
Hey, that ribbon.
Oh, you noticed?
Don't you think red is cuter?
l don't mean that. How'd you get it?
l saw it in some shop, tried it on...
and forgot about it.
lt happens often, doesn't it?
No way! Come with me!
What about the tab here?
l'd like to buy this.
A present for your girlfriend?
No!
l'll gift wrap it for you.
l'll take it as is!
Thank you!
Here.
You're unexpectedly uptight, actually going back to pay for it.
Shut up!
l hate that kind of thing.
Thank you! What about the Ferris wheel?
Absolutely not.
Meany!
High-schoolers don't have that much money.
Hey!
Shut up. l'm just going to the restroom!
He's quite nice.
There! All right!
That river...
Dad!
Welcome home!
Dad..?
Mom, l'm hungry!
l know. Take your seat.
Okay then, cheers!
What's taking so long?!
This place was so crowded a minute ago.
This... is my...
This is my funeral?
Dad? Mom?
Those things from earlier...
What?!
Now what?!
You've got better reflexes than l expected.
What do you want with me?
Come with us.
Our lord, Ganryu-sama, summons you!
Ganryu? Never heard of him.
There's no need for you to know him, since you are the...
Jai!
l told you not to blab.
Jumping out like that...
l'll catch her in an instant.
Oh, that tickles.
Don't crush her.
Hurry it up. Let's go.
Now then, let's go.
Hold it!
Where do you think you're going?
You... where did you come from?!
My arm...my arm!
What's with all the wandering off?
lchigo... That's my own business!
No way. You're gonna keep your promise.
Hey, big guy. Sorry about that.
You won't get away with this! l won't let you!
Jai! Enough.
lt is not yet the time.
Time? What're you talking about?
Dammit!
Hey, hold on!
Hey!
You let someone treat you, then run off?
l didn't run away!
Then what?
My family grave is here.
Cut the crap.
lt's true. l remember it.
lt's hazy, but l remember when l was alive.
That's why l came here for a look.
My house used to be around here, too.
l'll help you tomorrow for sure. l'm not lying.
See you!
You idiot. Like l can abandon someone who was just attacked.
That's fishy.
Bad guys are after her?
Well, at any rate, it's just for one night.
l'm Senna.
l'm Kurosaki Yuzu. Welcome.
Thanks for having me.
Hey Yuzu, let her sleep in your room.
And let her bathe, too.
Okay.
What's the matter, Dad?
Hey! Yuzu, you too?
Come in until your bed's ready.
Hmm... boys' rooms are always so drab and boring.
Don't start.
You seem to have a nice family.
You think?
My dad too. He was...
Hey!
What's the matter?
Oh, nothing.
By the way, why were those guys after you?
Did they say anything?
Hmm... something about Gan-whatever wanted me brought to him.
And?
That's all.
lf you hadn't come by, l might've learned more.
What?! Hey, don't sleep in my bed!
Why? There's nothing wrong with it.
Of course there is!
Hey, don't lift your legs up!
You're such a bother!
No, l'm not!
Stop it!
She says she's gonna sleep in his bed!
Well, lchigo-nii is a man, after all.
Oh, Masaki, it's the day we've been dreading!
What am l to do?
Hey! What's goin' on out here?
See, he's all mad.
The bath is ready.
Cripes!
Hey Senna, take a bath and then go to sleep.
Hey!
Kurosaki-san, it's me Urahara.
Any leads on the Shinenju?
Nope.
But l encountered the enemy Kon was talking about.
Are you hurt?
l'm fine. They took off right away.
l see.
About that, we were able to turn up a few things up on our end.
What?
After analyzing the visual images taken from Kon's memories...
We identified the armor as belonging to the clan
that was banished a long time ago from the Soul Society after their take-over attempt failed.
So we know for sure that they hold a grudge against us.
But we still don't know what they're after.
Urahara-san, can l ask you one thing?
What is it?
Can a shinigami have memories of when they were alive?
Let's see... l doubt that very much.
Why do you ask?
No reason... just curious.
Say, do you really think they'll show up again?
l dunno...
But the only lead we have is that we saw the Blanks here.
Aww, this is boring.
Man, why so many people?
lt's usually less crowded around this time of hour...
Senna, don't go too far from my side.
Hey!
Hey Senna!
Over here!
You were just attacked yesterday!
Don't go wandering off like that!
A soul?
Hey, what's the matter?
You're scaring him.
My name's Senna. What's yours?
Tomoya.
Tomoya-kun, huh?
Will you tell me what's wrong?
Umm... my dad's gone...
You were with your dad?
Uh-huh. We were driving to the festival,
but when l looked, he was gone.
l see...
Well then... your dad is probably in heaven and...
That's not true!
Dad is looking for me!
Okay! Then we'll help you find your dad.
Really?
Really! Really!
Tomoya-kun, which way did you come from?
Over that way!
Then let's go.
Hey!
Hey! Right now, we have to...
But we have no leads, right?
Let's go.
No sense in hanging around here.
Okay!
Hey, how long're you gonna keep at it?
There's no festival around here.
Besides, there's no guarantee that his father is still on this side.
We'll find him.
That boy has to leave this world soon.
And a long journey awaits him...
lt's his last wish. How sad if it doesn't come true.
l can't bring myself to perform a Konso like this.
l want to at least give him...
a good last memory.
Nee-chan!
What is it?
Onee-chan! This way! This way!
Onee-chan... my dad...
Let's find him.
Don't worry.
Okay.
l'm so glad this place is still here.
l came here a lot as a child.
You...
Tomoya.
Tomoya!
Dad!
Dad...
l'm sorry... l'm so sorry.
l don't believe this...
Thank you so much!
l'm happy for you.
Uh-huh.
lt's all thanks to you.
No, l didn't do anything.
l see. Could it be that you haven't noticed?
All these souls gathered around you here.
l was able to find this place thanks to them.
These people...?
Uh-huh...all of them here.
How weird. You're the one who called them here.
Tomoya...
Now we can go on our journey.
Bye bye.
Hey!
Wait a minute.
These guys...?!
Why...
Why do they come around me?
lchigo...
actually...
l'm...
Senna...
Ukitake-san?
What's wrong?
Rukia, what happened?
Well...
This is a Level One order from Central 46.
lchigo, hand over that girl!
What?!
lchigo,
l went through every record of the Thirteen Court Guard Squads,
the Stealth Force, the Kido Force, and the Shinigami Academy...
There is no Senna listed anywhere!
And the zanpakuto the girl uses, Mirokumaru...
lt has been verified that it was swallowed up by the Restrictive Current
in the Dangai Precipice World 100 years ago along with its owner.
ln other words, it cannot possibly exist today.
Wait a minute! What are you saying?
l'm a shinigami...
Then when did you come to the World of the Living?
Well...
Two days ago l woke up by the banks of that river.
But l remember my own name clearly.
And that river... l've known it since l was a child...
But... why?
l'm supposed to be just me...
See? All kinds of memories are mixed up in your head, right?
lt's hard to believe...
But the collective of memories you are searching for, the Shinenju,
is you.
l'm...
The Valley of Screams became visible twenty-four hours ago...
Soul Society has concluded that Ganryu wants to destroy the worlds...
and that a crucial element in his plans is the Shinenju.
The Shinenju Senna!
Soul Society will now take you into custody!
That's ridiculous?!
What are you saying? l'm...
Even l'm...!
Hold it. lt just doesn't sit well with me.
lchigo, what are you..?!
No matter what this girl is, she exists at this moment.
She gets mad, she gets happy, she gets hurt...
she has feelings, doesn't she?
But you're gonna ignore that and take her into custody?!
Then you're no different from them!
l'm not handing Senna over to you.
Sorry, but this is not the time to debate.
Move, lchigo!
Can't do that.
What's that?!
Renji!
Matsumoto!
These guys!
Behind you!
Hey kid... today, you will turn the Shinenju over to us.
Hah! You wanna lose your other arm too?!
lchigo!
Kon, take care of her!
Right!
He has much more power than yesterday!
Protect the Shinenju!
What are these things?!
Sit Upon the Frozen Heavens! Hyorinmaru!
Howl! Zabimaru!
What?!
Sogyo no Kotowari!
Go, Kuchiki!
Yes, sir!
Get outta the way!
Nee-san!
Hado 33: Sokatsui!
You're in my way!
Hey!
l am a shinigami!
Call Forth the Twilight!
Don't!
Mirokumaru!
Senna!
That pattern on the armor belongs to the banished clan...
The once noble House of Ryodoji!
l wouldn't know.
We are from the Clan of Darkness, the Dark One.
What?!
You won't get away!
Let's go.
You've got some nerve!
Hey, let go of me!
Senna!
l'm coming for you!
Senna, l won't hand her over!
You're mine...!
lchigo!
lchigo?
He's okay now.
Thank you. l'm glad you all came to help.
Sheesh, he's hopeless.
No such thing.
lt was a surprise attack, even three squad captains couldn't fend them off.
lt couldn't be helped.
Boss...
What about the squad members?
Unfortunately, they lost track of the enemy.
Have you been able to learn anything else?
lt seems they plan to use the power of the Shinenju
to pull the World of the Living and the Soul Society together
to make them collide.
No way...!
lt's hard to believe.
But that's the only explanation.
What about the Soul Society?
They should be working on the next plan of action. Just...
From the Soul Society it's not possible to access the Valley of Screams.
Without an entryway, it's impossible to enter another world.
lsn't there any other way?
Well, there should be an entrance in the World of the Living, which was created when the Shinenju appeared.
l see.
lchigo!
lf we find the entrance, we can go after them.
Right, Urahara-san?
Yes.
Let's go!
lchigo!
We have no choice. Let's go and search, too.
Right!
There are no traces of any gunpowder or chemical residue.
What is going on here?!
lchigo... l...
It's not really your fault.
She's self-centered and stubborn and a little crazy...
But she was trembling.
Deep down, she was frightened that she didn't know who she really was.
And yet...
And yet, l couldn't protect her.
Oh, you noticed?
Don't you think red is cuter?
lf l answered your questions, you'd do anything l asked you to?
lf you look at things from above,
all the things that seem confusing or messed up suddenly become clear.
Why'd she say that...?
lchigo, what's wrong?
Rukia, come with me.
O-Okay.
l remember when l was alive.
My house used to be around here, too.
There... in the river.
What is that?!
This is the same phenomenon that's visible from the Soul Society!
We can go through it!
Rukia, contact Urahara-san.
W-Wait, lchigo! You can't go alone...
l'm going!
l'm gonna save her no matter what!
lchigo!
What is this place...?
l thought you wanted me to do something for you!
We just need you to be the instrument through which...
...we fulfill our dream.
What are you talking about?!
Lower your voice!
Ganryu-sama is the rightful ruler of Soul Society!
lt's all right. l abandoned such formalities long ago.
One thousand years have passed since my grandfather was banished from Soul Society.
We wandered in exile in this Dangai Precipice World...
and survived by evading the Restrictive Current, which swallows up everything that touches it.
We learned to use the souls who had strayed from the Cycle of Transmigration
and turned into wandering ghosts in the Dangai Precipice World as a source of power.
The number of souls is always constant.
lf these souls, or "Blanks" who have strayed from the Cycle of Transmigration
reach a certain number...
they generate a dimension known as the Valley of Screams.
ln other words, this space was created by countless Blanks.
And at the same time, all the memories of these lost souls merge and return to the World of the Living.
That is the Shinenju...
ln other words... you!
However, the Blanks do not lose their individuality right away.
Even though the Blanks are basically empty vessels,
they still wander for a time, searching for their memories.
This is where the problem begins.
Placing the Shinenju at the center of the Valley of Screams
will activate the Blanks' natural desire to seek their memories...
and will drive them to rush towards the Shinenju, causing the Valley of Screams to contract.
This force will be strong enough to pull the World of the Living
and Soul Society, separated by the Dangai Precipice World, into a collision.
What?!
That's a disturbing thought...
Furthermore, the contraction has already begun.
Never mind all the details.
So what's going to happen?
Who knows...?
But two worlds that must stay apart are going to collide.
If we are lucky only one will be destroyed .
Perhaps, both worlds will be destroyed.
How much time do we have?
l don't have enough data, so l can't say with certainty...
But l'd guess... about one hour.
l'll mobilize the Punishment Force and enter the Valley of Screams immediately!
lt's useless.
There is no Senkaimon that connects the Soul Society to this place,
therefore we have no way to enter.
Any effort will be for naught.
The situation is critical!
Prepare the Kido Cannon!
We must destroy the Valley of Screams and the entire dimension connected to it.
But if we do that, it will cause massive damage to the both worlds!
There is no other choice.
No! Please stand back!
What is the meaning of this?! This is a captains' meeting!
Be gone!
My deepest apologies, sir!
l will gladly accept any punishment later.
However, l have crucial information to report!
Substitute Shinigami Kurosaki Ichigo, has discovered an entryway to the Valley of Screams...
and has gone there in order to rescue Senna the Shinenju!
lchigo...
Please send reinforcements to assist Kurosaki Ichigo!
Well... but...
l cannot allow that.
Why is that?
Mind you, l am not taking the Substitute Shinigami's skills lightly...
However, we have only one hour,
and there is no guarantee that the Thirteen Court Guard Squads
could defeat the enemy and rescue the Shinenju in that time.
Do not think poorly of me.
This meeting is now over.
All Squads will begin emergency procedures.
Prepare the Kido Cannon!
l'm...
going, too!
l'm not about to let him take all the glory.
Ganryu-sama, the Blanks have latched onto the Shinenju.
Yes.
Humph! A small fry...
Senna!
l'm coming!
Have you returned for another beating?
Give Senna back!
Just when we were trying to awaken her as Shinenju...
Because of you,
she will now suffer pain and fear as a human being.
lchigo...
What?!
No... no!
Senna!
Nooo!
You bastards–! Get outta my way!
Maybe we should all go after Kurosaki-kun.
You better not.
The Valley of Screams is somewhat similar to the Soul Society...
lt's a spiritual world where humans cannot go.
Kuchiki-san?
Abarai-kun?
How was it?
No good. Soul Society intends to use the Kido Cannon to destroy the entire Valley of Screams.
lf they do that, Kurosaki-kun will...
l won't let that happen.
Before they fire the Kido Cannon, we'll go and finish the job.
But...
Don't worry.
We'll figure something out.
You wouldn't stand a chance alone.
We've already put the team together.
We'll settle this ourselves!
l'm coming, too!
There's no time. Let's go!
Yes, sir!
Kuchiki-san... please take care of Kurosaki-kun.
l know.
Let go!
Damn!
Kenpachi!
lt's dangerous, over there.
You too...!
What was that?
What's taking you so long?!
You guys!
You're not getting away with this... coming all by yourself!
Thought we'd join in for some fun.
Look how many people volunteered to the call.
Leave this side to us!
Now go, Kurosaki!
l'm counting on you guys!
Let's do it!
Right!
Grow! Hozukimaru!
Growl! Haineko!
Raise Your Head!
Wabisuke!
Take that! You pesky brat!
What's going on?!
Hey!
ls this what you're looking for?
Why you–!
You little–!
lt's too late! There!
Ridiculous...
What?!
but l'm not bad at it!
l don't like playing tag,
Go, Ken-chan!
Can l cut you already?
You might just turn out to be some fun, after all.
Sit Upon the Frozen Heavens!
Hyorinmaru!
Hanging in there, huh, kid?
Let's see who'll last longer, shall we?
Well, l don't mind if this keeps up forever.
Take this!
Looks like it's over–
Bankai!
Daiguren Hyorinmaru!
Dammit! l can't believe he still has that kind of power left!
What's going on?!
What?!
Third chant complete. We are ready to fire.
The target will pass out of critical range in five minutes.
Head Captain!
l understand.
l will wait until the very last second.
However...
l said l won't let you get to the Shinenju!
lchigo, grab on!
Renji!
Go! lchigo!
What?!
You're not going anywhere!
Then we'll finish you two first!
What?!
Senna!
You still believe you can save the Shinenju?
Damn right! l'm gonna save Senna!
lt's too late!
The Shinenju has already begun to merge with the Valley of Screams.
No one can stop it now.
Shaddup!
You just wait, Senna! l'll get you outta here real soon!
You still don't seem to understand.
How useless it is.
Getsuga Tensho!
Why you–!
So you finally showed yourself!
l'll beat you and save Senna!
Go ahead, bring it on!
Let's go!
Ban...kai!
Tensa Zangetsu!
For a millennium, our clan was forced to nest in the crevices of the Dangai Precipice World in disgrace.
We were able to endure that suffering until this day...
because of our hatred...
our desire to destroy Soul Society!
And that moment is about to happen!
l will not let you interfere!
Why are you so determined?
The Shinenju is just a collective of memories.
The mere remains of what used to be alive.
That's not true!
Senna is here and she's alive!
She was confused and afraid, looking for help...
l'm going to protect her...
l swore it on my soul!
l get it now...
All of you are just...
lchigo!
We pass out of critical range in two minutes!
No word yet? What are they doing?!
l can wait no longer!
Sensei!
Fire the Kido Cannon!
Captain!
The cannon's been fired! The entire dimension will collapse!
What?!
My zanpakuto is pretty tough.
That kind of attack won't change a thing!
You're not getting away!
There's no need to run away!
You impudent–!
Dance! Sode no Shirayuki!
lt's useless!
Some no mai.
Tsukishiro!
What?!
Like l said, it's useless!
Take this!
Nii-sama!
Be honored...
that you will perish by my Bankai.
Scatter! Senbonzakura Kageyoshi.
Nii-sama!
Let's go.
Senna!
Here l come!
Come on!
Hey, you're awfully quiet.
What's the matter, cat got your tongue?
Shut up.
They're coming back.
Shinenju has been successfully retrieved!
The Valley of Screams is disintegrating!
Welcome home!
Nee-san!
Kurosaki, you did it!
Well done. You did it!
Quite impressive.
l'm so glad everyone is all right.
Thanks! Rukia! Renji!
Stupid! We didn't do it for you.
l must admit, not bad for the freeloader.
What?!
You can stay and eat.
Senna! l forgot, your ribbon...
lchigo.
What is it? Why won't the alarm stop?
lt's no good! The dimension passed beyond the critical zone!
World of the Living and Soul Society are together on a collision course!
At this rate...!
What's going on?!
lt's not stopping?!
Then what'll happen?
This is not good.
Wait!
Why?!
This is bad.
Damn! ls it too late?
lchigo... l'm scared.
Senna?
But... but...
l won't let it happen. Not when it's such a wonderful world.
Not when... so many people live in it.
Not when...
You live here, lchigo...!
lt's okay. The Blanks are still near me.
lf l release their energy all at once,
the two worlds can probably be returned to normal.
Senna?!
lf there's no world, you'll be gone, too...
l don't want that.
Stop! You still have...
l don't want you to die instead of me!
Senna...
Senna!
Explosions in the Dangai Precipice World have been confirmed!
Both worlds are moving towards their respective stable positions.
The collision has been averted!
lchigo, l have a favor to ask.
l want you to check... my family grave...
Remember yesterday, l told you it was here?
l was alive once... and l lived in this town...
So...
Yeah.
l must've had a family, too.
l... existed.
So there should be a name on the grave...
Was it around here?
The fourth one from the end.
ls there... a name?
I don't know why, but my vision is blurred...
ls it there?
Yeah, it's here.
You did live in this town.
And you had a family, too.
l'm glad...
lt feels so warm.
We'll... meet again, won't we?
What're you saying? Of course...
The energy of the Blanks will soon be depleted...
And everything about Senna...
will fade from our memories.
Memories of those that never existed can't possibly remain...
l know she'll be gone soon, but right now, l can still hear her voice.
l want to be loved, but don't try to love,
repeating and wandering through
The single answer l've found is
no matter how scared, or hurt l become,
l tell the person l love, "l love you"
l don't care
Whether you "do love me, or do not love me"
No matter how hard you wish
ln this world, there are way too many things that cannot be changed,
And the fact
That l love you
ls the truth that cannot be changed by anyone
Crossing over a thousand nights, l want to tell you
l have to tell you
l want to be loved, but don't try to love,
Repeating and wandering
The single answer l've found is
No matter how scared, or hurt l become,
l tell the person l love, "l love you"
lt is scary to put feelings into words,
but l'll tell the person l love, "l love you"
There is no way to express in words,
The joy of coming across each other in this vast world
That is why we smile,
singing the passing colorful autumn in sol-fa,
Facing back against the winter, waiting for the spring sunlight
ln order to be reborn so that we can protect someone
The path l came, and the path l go, whenever l turn back
l had cowardly eyes
l want to face it, but cannot be honest about it
Repeating over the days of
not being able to love the person
But hating to be by myself,
l tried to love someone without getting hurt
Crossing over a thousand nights,
l shall go to you now,
There is something l must tell you
l want to be loved, but don't try to love,
Repeating and wandering
The single answer l've found is
no matter how scared, or hurt l become,
l tell the person l love, "l love you"
Even if that feeling is denied,
Telling the person l love...
ls the most wonderful thing in this world.
Wow, what strong wind!
Oh shut up. Who cares about that, it's the same either way!
No, we'll get scolded!
Yeah yeah, l'm out!
Hey wait!