Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
That's a nice boy.
Go get him, Dulli.
Get in.
- We good?
- Oh, yeah.
Are we good? Yeah, we're good.
We're beautiful.
We're perfect.
This is Grade A, 100-percent pure
Colombian cocaine, ladies and gentlemen.
Disco shit.
Pure as the driven snow.
My name is George Jung...
...federal inmate number 19225004.
I was born in New England.
Massachusetts, actually,
in a town called Weymouth.
That's me.
And that's my best friend, Tuna.
My dad ran a plumbing
and heating company.
He had three trucks, 10 employees
and did big jobs.
- Hey.
He was my hero.
- Did you do it?
- Yeah, I didn't fall once.
Attaboy. See you tonight.
- Can I please come to work with you?
Hey, come on, Fred. Let's go, huh?
Say goodbye to the kid.
Clam it, Bill.
I'll talk to my boy as long as I want to.
You got a problem with that?
You really wanna come?
Oh, what the heck? All right.
- All right, get your boots.
Thanks, Dad. Thanks.
Bill, what's your problem?
Guess who's on cleanup today.
And buying lunch.
Money! M-O-N-E-Y.
Dad was a hard worker,
but didn't make enough to keep Mom happy.
Why do you think I married you?
She'd thought she'd married
above her class.
And he'd promised her the moon
but didn't deliver.
- How we will live?
The truth was...
...business got slow and we were broke.
Don't you touch me!
Look at your hands. You're disgusting.
Please, not in front of the boy.
The boy. What about me, Fred?
Mom, wait, where are you going?
- Go home, George!
Mom, where are you going?
No matter how many times
my mother would leave...
...no matter how many times
she embarrassed him...
Mom!
...he always took her back.
He loved her.
God, he loved her.
Ermine.
Come here.
- Are you okay?
Yeah.
You all right?
Hi, George.
I'm home.
Come on, give me a hug.
Come on, Georgie.
Come to Mommy.
George.
Come give your mother a hug.
For 10 years...
...my father worked his ass off
14 hours a day, seven days a week.
He didn't care,
as long as we were happy.
Okay, well, what do I have to do?
But in the end, he didn't make enough...
...slowly but surely lost everything.
We were bankrupt.
Let's get some ice cream.
No, Dad,
I don't care about ice cream right now.
What are we gonna do?
It'll be all right, George.
It'll work out. It always does.
I'm gonna find another job.
Look, George, this is the way it goes.
Sometimes you're flush
and sometimes you're bust.
And when you're up,
it's never as good as it seems.
And when you're down,
you never think you're gonna be up again.
But life goes on. Remember that.
Money isn't real, George.
It doesn't matter.
It only seems like it does.
Yeah, tell that to Mom.
Yeah. That's gonna be a tricky one.
- Hey, Dad.
- What?
Are we gonna be poor?
Because I don't ever wanna be poor.
Then you won't.
I decided right then and there
I wasn't gonna live like that.
I needed to get as far away as possible.
I moved to California
in the summer of 1968 with the Tuna.
We had $300 and a black TR3.
Sure was nothing like this back home.
It was paradise.
We got a small one-bedroom apartment
right on the beach.
It wasn't much, but it had its perks.
George.
George?
You need some help?
California was like nothing
I'd ever seen before.
Hey, where's the beer?
People were liberated,
independent, full of new ideas.
Hi, George, Tuna.
They used words like
"right on," "groovy," "solid."
The women were beautiful.
And they all seemed
to share the same occupation.
- I'm a stewardess.
Yeah.
On the airplane.
And everyone was getting stoned.
Hi.
- Hello. Hi. Hello.
Hey, Tuna.
Hi.
Oh, my God.
I figured it out.
Figured out what?
You know how we were wondering
what we were gonna do for money...
...being as we don't wanna get jobs?
Yeah.
- Check this out.
Oregano?
- Tuna, this is crap.
Look, we're selling it.
We'll make up three-finger lids
and sell them on the beach.
If we move that, we got, like...
Like, a hundred bucks.
And if we don't, well, we can smoke it.
You got ripped off, pal.
It's not a bad idea, man.
I got the baggies and everything.
Look, if you really wanna score some dope,
I got the guy.
The guy was Derek Foreal,
a Manhattan Beach legend.
He owned three restaurants, two nightclubs,
and chain of Laundromats.
But more importantly, he owned the first
male hair salon in all of southern California.
Barbie.
- Hey.
- Mwah.
Maria.
Mwah, mwah.
Hey.
Hey, Sandy.
Ah, so this is the new man, huh?
He's cute.
George.
Tuna.
Hello, Tuna.
Enchanté, George.
Barbie, he is yummy.
He looks just like a Ken doll.
Huh! Ken and Barbie.
Oh, my God, it is so perfect.
Girls, give me about five minutes.
I wanna talk alone to the boys.
Have fun.
- Gentlemen?
All right, everybody, shoo. Come on.
Chop, chop. Give us a few minutes.
Chop, chop, chop.
Go blond, Ron.
Very nice, Heather.
Now what can I do for you, guys?
We'd like to buy some pot.
I know what you want.
- But first, are you cops?
No.
If you are, you have to tell me.
If not, it's entrapment.
We're not cops.
We're from Massachusetts.
Does he look like a cop?
Actually, no.
You know, it's a good thing
you're friends of Barbie's.
Because if you weren't...
...I would never talk to you.
What the fuck is that?
It's your pot.
Wow.
That's more than we had in mind.
I don't nickel-and-dime.
You want it or not?
We'll take it.
Tuna and I became the kings
of Manhattan Beach.
If you bought grass,
you bought it from us.
The bills were paid and I was making
way more money than I could at a real job.
I built a reputation for myself.
People even started calling me
"Boston George."
It was perfect.
This is it for me.
What is it?
Everything.
You, California, the beach.
This spot right here.
I just finally feel like I belong somewhere,
you know?
I feel right.
You're happy.
Yeah, I am.
You?
Um, mm-hm.
Good.
Look what the cat dragged in.
Holy shit, Dulli.
George.
- Hey.
Man.
- What the fuck are you doing out here?
Man, I'll tell you.
I was walking down the beach.
I was minding my business, right?
Who do I see? This fucking guy.
- I didn't know you were in California.
- What are you doing out here?
On vacation, man.
I'm on my way back to school.
Oh. Well, this calls for a joint.
You wanna do the honors?
No, man.
- I'm too fucked up.
- That's nice weed, huh?
Fuck, yeah.
I've never seen anything like this.
I'm fucking wasted.
Right on.
Man.
I'm fucking stoned.
I'm fucking really stoned.
I'm fucking stoned, man. I'm really...
Stoned?
- Yeah, ha, ha.
- Yeah.
Man, I wish there was stuff like this
back at home.
Yeah?
Fuck, yeah. You know how much money
you can make with this stuff back east?
- Yeah?
No shit, Kev?
- That's right.
Yeah?
When there's stuff to move,
it's too easy not to.
Do you know how many colleges there are
within a 60-mile radius?
- UMASS, Amherst, BU.
Smith, Hampshire.
And Holyoke.
Holyoke.
There's 100,000 rich kids
with their parents' money to spend.
There's never anything around.
Nothing good, anyways.
I'm spending 400 bucks on shit.
Yeah?
The way I figure it...
...Barbara flies back east twice a week.
Two bags per flight.
Twenty-five pounds in each bag.
That's a hundred pounds a week.
I know it's a lot of weight,
but you can't get pot like this back home.
I'm telling you, Derek, it'll sell.
I don't know.
The best pot...
...you can charge 500 a pound.
Come on, George.
No one's gonna pay that.
It's already been negotiated. It's done.
The money's there waiting.
Goodness.
Goodness is right.
Listen...
...I want you to be my partner
on this thing, Derek.
Fifty-fifty.
If you do the math,
that's over 30 grand a week profit.
That's $15,000 a week for you,
my friend.
In your pocket, free and clear.
And I just deal with you.
Barbara and me. No one else.
It's gonna work, Derek.
I don't know. East Coast, airplanes.
I'm paranoid. It seems really risky.
Derek, she's a stewardess.
They don't check her bags.
- Bye, dear.
- Bye.
There she is.
- Hey, Barbara.
- Kevin.
See this suit? Japanese.
See you.
Bye.
Barbara.
- Kevin.
How've you been?
- Hey.
More. I need more.
Bye.
Barbara. Hey.
- Hey, Kevin.
- I need more.
I need more.
What do you want me to do?
I can only carry two bags
and I can't fly back here every day.
I know. I got a feeding frenzy on my hands.
You tell George this is small potatoes.
We're missing out on some serious cash.
You tell George. He'll think of something.
- I will.
- Good.
Ladies and gentlemen, Kevin Dulli.
Twenty, 40, 60, 80, nine...
Twenty, 40, 60, 80. A thousand.
Hundred twenty-eight thousand dollars.
Jesus Christ,
I'm getting a boner just looking at her.
You believe it, George?
What's the matter, George?
Something wrong?
Man, cheer up. I mean, half of this is ours.
We're fucking rich.
- It's not enough.
- What?
The fuck are you talking about?
Setup is wrong.
We're doing all the legwork.
At the end of the day, we're paying retail.
- We're getting fucking middled.
So?
So we need to get to the source.
Source? What about Derek?
He's getting middled too.
And Derek's our partner.
What's good for him is good for us.
So we need a source.
Where do we start?
Either one of you guys speak Spanish?
Tuna! Get the fuck in there!
Go on and play.
Yeah!
Cheers.
Cómo, marijuana?
Smoking? Smoke them?
Do you have some pot?
Dónde estápot?
- Do you know where we can get pot?
- No. No idea.
El weed.
Where we can find some marijuana?
We're looking for marijuana.
Take a little off the top.
You know what I mean?
Smoke, man. Marijuana?
Excuse me, do you smoke?
So you got anything?
I haven't asked.
What?
I didn't ask yet. Go ahead.
Hey, George.
Come on.
We'll be back.
Okay.
Santiago?
George.
Ramon tells me
you're looking for some mota.
Yeah, I am.
For instance, say, something like this, eh?
Ahem. Oh, yeah. Yeah, that'll do it.
I'll take it.
You're funny.
Really.
How much will you be needing?
All of it.
Yeah, I'll come back in a week
with a plane.
Maybe we're going too fast.
You take a little and then come back.
Yeah, but I don't need a little.
I need a lot.
Hang on a minute. Hang on. Hang on.
Listen, señor.
Tell you what, amigo.
What about I come back...
...and I bring you, say...
...fifty thousand dollars?
That alleviate some of your concerns?
Amigo...
...you bring me $50,000
and I have no more concerns.
I can't believe we're stealing a plane.
Don't be such a pussy.
We're not fucking stealing it.
We're borrowing it.
Oops. Be cool, boys.
Got a little company here.
Smoke.
Come on, let's go. Tuna?
Let's go. Tuna.
- Good luck, boys. I'll see you in the desert.
All right.
- You sure you know what you're doing?
Relax, all right?
I've flown with my old man
a million times.
It's not the, ahh, taking-off part
you got to worry about. It's the landing.
Okay.
Hi. How are you?
- Good to see you.
You are a man of your word.
Oh, listen,
you know the 50,000 I promised you?
Couldn't get it.
So I brought you 75 instead.
George! Whoo!
George.
Merry Christmas, Derek.
Merry Christmas.
It's beautiful.
You're a genius, George.
- Merry Christmas.
Merry Christmas.
This would make a fabulous
Christmas card.
Get my camera, Sven.
George!
Did you see the bedroom?
I love it. It's so pretty.
- Did you see it?
- Yeah, I saw it.
Hi.
- Hi.
Oh, my God.
- What do you think?
Are you kidding?
- Yeah, you want it?
- Mm-hm.
- We'll take it.
- All right.
It was a great time in our lives.
The seven of us were like a family.
We worked hard, we played hard,
didn't have a care in the world.
Egg roll!
It was perfect.
I can't get over
the size of that ring. I just love it.
Look at it, Fred.
Tell me you don't love that ring.
I'm happy that George
has found somebody he cares for.
Yes, of course.
But I'm talking about the ring.
It's something else, let me tell you.
George has exquisite taste.
What is it? Two carats?
It's gotta be at least two carats.
I don't know.
- Yes, it's definitely two carats.
Treasure it, darling.
- George, you might wanna get that insured.
- Okay, Mom.
Hard to imagine being able to afford a ring
like that on a construction salary.
Oh, shut up, Fred. Shut your big fat mouth.
You don't buy it all at once.
It's called layaway.
- Layaway, shmayaway.
- Yes, layaway.
Something you wouldn't know
anything about, cheapskate.
Cheapskate, beapskate.
- Yeah, you, you big old tightwad.
He still has his Communion money.
- Don't listen to her.
- George, tell your father...
Yap, yap, yap.
George, you tell your father
about layaway.
- Layaway.
- Okay.
The boy's happy, Fred.
Don't be such a killjoy.
I'm not a killjoy.
Oh, Jesus. Babe.
- Put your head back.
- Ahh!
Put your head back.
- Why, Barbara.
My God.
Here, take my napkin.
Is she all right?
- Yeah.
- I'll get you ice. Irene, we need ice here.
- Yeah, she's all right.
- You know what? You wanna go?
- Yeah, let's go.
- Oh, come on. You haven't had your entrée.
- No, it's okay. It's better.
George...
- I'll leave the tip.
- George, no.
- Hope you feel better.
It was lovely to meet you.
- Give your mother a call in the morning.
Okay, Mom.
What a lovely girl.
- Is that all hundreds?
- Yeah.
Are you sure you're all right?
- Yeah, I'm fine.
- Yeah?
Honey, would you be bummed out
if I didn't go to Chicago with you?
No, not if you don't wanna.
Listen, I gotta apologize about my parents.
That was...
They weren't that bad.
They were kind of cute.
I'm not sure about that.
I want you to promise me something.
I want you to promise me
that we're never gonna be like that.
I don't wanna wind up like them.
We're gonna wind up like us.
- Yeah?
- Mm-hm.
- I love you.
- In the car.
Hurry before they come out.
George Jung,
you stand accused of...
...possession of 660 pounds of marijuana
with intent to distribute.
How do you plead?
Your Honor, I'd like to say a few words
to the court, if I may?
You're gonna have to stop slouching
and stand up to address this court, sir.
All right. Fine.
Well...
...in all honesty...
...I don't feel that what I've done
is a crime.
And I think it's illogical and irresponsible
for you to sentence me to prison.
Because when you think about it,
what did I really do?
I crossed an imaginary line
with a bunch of plants.
I mean, "You say I'm an outlaw.
You say I'm a thief.
But where's the Christmas dinner
for the people on relief, huh?
You say you're looking for someone
who's never weak but always strong...
...to gather flowers constantly,
whether you were right or wrong...
...someone to open each and every door,
but it ain't me, babe, huh?
No, no, no, it ain't me, babe.
It ain't me you're looking for, babe."
You follow?
Yeah.
Gosh, you know, your concepts
are really interesting, Mr. Jung.
Thank you.
Unfortunately for you,
the line you crossed was real...
...and the plants you brought with you
were illegal, so your bail is $20,000.
Next case, Your Honor.
- Number 14173.
- No.
George.
- George.
- Hey, babe.
What are you doing here?
Surprise.
You didn't have to come
all the way out here, babe.
What, and miss all the fun?
Not a chance.
So...
...what's the verdict?
The lawyer says he can, uh...
...plead it down to five years.
I'll serve two.
- Two years.
- Yeah.
Two years.
George, I can't wait that long.
What, are you kidding me?
You're not gonna wait for me? Fuck is that?
I...
I don't have two years.
What?
No.
Losing Barbara to cancer
changed everything.
The old gang broke up.
Tuna stayed in Mexico.
God only knows what happened to him.
Point is, we all lost touch.
I'd skipped bail in Chicago
to take care of Barbara...
...and was now a fugitive on the run.
It'd been almost a year
since I'd seen my parents.
And believe it or not,
I actually missed them.
Hi, Ma.
Surprised to see me?
Take off your boots.
You're tan.
Mexico.
Yeah, I heard about it.
I want you to know...
...I'm deeply sorry about your girlfriend.
- Barbara?
- Yeah, Barbara.
Nice girl.
Thank you.
Have you been getting the money
I send you?
What, you mean the drug money?
Yeah, I got it.
Oh, God.
What are you doing, huh?
What are you doing?
It's okay, Mom.
George?
Georgie.
- Hi, Pop.
George, I thought I heard something.
How are you?
- How are you?
Good.
Oh, son, come on in.
How are you? You look good.
May the wind always be at your back...
...and the sun upon your face.
And may the winds of destiny
carry you aloft...
...to dance with the stars.
- Cheers, Georgie.
- Cheers, Pop.
Are you all right?
Just low, you know?
You really loved her.
Yeah, Dad.
I really did.
Are you mad at me?
Uh-uh. No.
- Yeah, you are.
- No.
- I can tell by the way you're looking at me.
- I'm not mad, George.
I just don't understand
what you're doing.
I don't understand your choices. You know,
the goddamn cops are looking for you.
I know.
I'm great at what I do, Dad.
I mean, I'm really great at what I do.
Let me tell you something, George.
You'd have been great at anything.
Anything.
Fuck. Damn.
George!
Fuck. Oh, fuck. Oh, fuck.
I had no choice.
Don't look at me like that.
Let's go.
- What? What was I supposed to do?
- Jesus Christ, Ermine.
- He's in our house!
- Shut up. Shut up.
What, was I supposed to be
an accomplice?
You don't think people know
you're a drug dealer?
Everyone knows you're a drug dealer.
It's no secret.
How do you think that reflects on me?
Every time I go out, I'm humiliated.
So you go to jail. It's for your own good.
You need to straighten your life out!
What are you looking at, Mrs. Gracie?
Your son's no prize.
Stop.
Open up Cell Number 3!
Prisoner is in.
Close Cell Number 3.
Hello. My name is Diego Delgado.
How do you do?
Okay.
Hey, George.
What?
If you don't mind me asking...
...what is the reason
you are in this place?
I don't wanna talk about it.
Oh, come on, George.
If we are to be friends,
we must trust each other.
- I don't like a lot of conversation, Diego.
Me too, yeah.
Too much blah-blah-blah. You know?
But we are roommates.
And we must talk to each other.
I'm arrested for stealing cars.
For the grand theft auto.
Murder.
What do you got down there, Diego?
Nothing. Just a little project.
What kind of little project?
Never mind.
Not for you to worry.
Come on. I thought you said
we're supposed to be roommates...
...tell each other everything,
all that kind of shit.
Uh-huh.
You have your intrigues, I have mine.
Today is a happy day for me, George.
In nine months from today,
I'll be in Medellin, sipping champagne.
In nine months...
...I'm free.
I'm happy for you.
Yeah.
How much time do you have?
Oh, let's see.
Twenty-six months.
Twenty-six months?
For murder?
I must meet your lawyer.
I gotta get out of here, Diego.
Only two ways I know
to leave here early.
One...
...is to escape.
Okay, what's the other?
Uh...
I guess we ought to open our books.
Man, fuck you.
We ain't opening shit.
That's right.
You're the warden's little bitch.
We're hip to you.
Doing that shit to get some time cut off.
What the fuck? Why not?
Listen, I wanna get out of this shithole
as quickly as fucking possible.
But for me to walk early,
some of you has got to graduate.
You should forget it. You're hopeless.
Go to sleep.
Fuck you. See you in the shower.
Jive-ass turkey.
The rest of you guys
might be able to get diplomas...
...and get jobs when you get back
on the outside.
Shit, I'm in this bitch for life.
Motherfucker, I'm a criminal.
Ain't nobody giving me no fucking job.
Well...
...let's learn some criminal shit too.
Tell you what, I'll make you a deal.
What about half the time I teach you
about this George Washington character...
...the other half...
...I'll teach you how to smuggle drugs.
You don't know dick
about smuggling no drugs.
Oh, no?
I was arrested in Chicago
with 660 pounds of grass.
I think that qualifies me.
How'd the fuck you get
660 pounds of weed?
Flew in from Mexico
on a single-engine Cessna.
So we got a deal or what?
Hey, George.
George.
What?
I listened to what you say
to the class today about the smuggling.
Never believed you were a murderer.
I knew you were a mágico.
I'm tired, Diego. Go to bed.
Do you know in my country
I'm a mágico?
A man with a dream.
A man on the rise.
To take nothing and make it something.
Do you have a dream, George?
Well, I would if I could get
some fucking sleep.
You have a dream.
And maybe you will accomplish it.
But yet you failed.
Why?
- Because I got caught.
- No.
You failed...
...because you had the wrong dream.
George?
What do you know about cocaine?
First of all,
what type of planes do you have?
They're, uh, four-passenger,
single-engine Cessnas.
Four passengers.
So that means...
...how many kilos can we fit
in these planes?
I don't know. Probably, uh, 100, 150...
Danbury wasn't a prison.
It was a crime school.
I went in with a bachelor of marijuana...
...came out with a doctorate of cocaine.
And after 16 months,
I was once again a free man.
Well, not altogether free.
The conditions of my parole...
...were that I had to live
at my parents' house and find a job.
Hello.
- Diego Delgado, please.
- Diego, George.
Boston George.
- Today is the day. Are you out?
- Yeah, I'm out.
Congratulations.
I've been waiting for you.
- How we doing?
Fine.
Everything's perfect down here.
Everything is all set up.
Do we need a plane?
How does this work? When do I see you?
Slow down, Georgie.
You need to come down here.
Everybody meets everybody.
We do one for good faith
and then we talk about airplanes, okay?
- I can't go anyway, Diego.
- Georgie.
- It's nice and cold.
- All right, Pop. One minute.
I'm on parole. I can't leave the state.
But, George, you'll be back
before they know you're gone.
I just got released five minutes ago...
George, are we gonna do this or not?
- My friend.
Hey. How are you?
- Fine.
- Good to see you.
Okay.
Fifteen kilos it is then, okay?
We receive $100,000 upon delivery.
Not so fast. No, no, no.
I would like to go over the details.
What details?
I put the coke in the false bottoms
and I take it through customs.
That's it.
Tell me about the suitcases.
- Will there be clothes in the suitcase?
- What?
Clothes.
In the suitcase.
Yeah, okay.
Okay, yeah.
Let's try it. Why not?
Yeah, whose clothes? Your clothes?
Okay. Ahem. Diego?
What the fuck is going on here?
The guy's talking about clothes.
You pulled me all the way down here
to talk about clothes?
I demand to know everything.
I do not trust $600,000 worth of coca
to someone I don't know.
It's 15 fucking kilos. I piss 15 kilos.
- Hey, hey, hey.
I'm an amateur, huh?
Gentlemen, please, hey.
There's not need to be impolite, okay?
Hey.
Cesar?
George, Cesar is just being thorough.
And that's all, okay?
Okay, very well.
But just remember, Mr. Jung,
I will be with you the whole way...
...and I will be watching.
When you're carrying drugs
across the border...
...the idea is to remain calm.
The way I do it
is to think of something pleasant.
A fun party, a moment of triumph,
sexual encounter.
I actually project myself to that place.
A little transcendental meditation,
if you will.
The trick is to imagine every little detail.
Anything to keep your mind off the fact that
you're going to jail for a very long time...
...if they find the 15 kilos of blow
in your suitcases.
Passport, please?
- Nice flight?
Yeah, it was pretty good. Thanks.
On vacation?
- Yes.
On vacation for only one day.
Oh, yeah. My brother's wedding.
It was a nice ceremony and everything.
It was good.
Open your bag, please?
Sure.
Whose clothes are these?
- Mine.
And these?
Old habits, you know. Hard to break.
Close it up.
Yes, sir.
The trial period was over.
It was time to start moving
some serious weight.
Commercial flights weren't gonna cut it
anymore.
What we needed was a pilot.
I'll fly down on a Friday...
...refuel in the Bahamas
and then onto Medellin.
Please continue.
We make the pickup,
refuel once more in the Bahamas...
...then fly back on Sunday
with the mom-and-pop traffic.
Why are you speaking?
- What?
- You. Your responsibility is over.
You don't fly.
You're not a pilot, not a distributor.
You introduced us to Mr. Stevens
and the use of his plane. That's all.
You make a percentage and a generous one.
And you're lucky to get that.
I see.
Ahem. How much?
Padrino will pay 10,000 per kilo
for everyone. You, you and you.
Three million. That is all.
There is no negotiation.
I want two.
Jack, come on, a million each
had such a nice ring to it.
No way. I'm doing all the work,
I'm taking all the risk and it's my plane.
You guys don't have to do shit.
You just sit back and collect your money.
- You good with this?
- Ahem.
Yeah.
That's enough. That's enough.
No! No!
No!
No! No.
- Do you have pictures of your kids?
- What?
I'll need to see them.
I'll also need their names
and their schools.
We're entrusting you with
millions of dollars' worth of coca.
Without your children, there is no deal.
Fine.
Mr. Stevens?
Don't forget the pictures.
George.
- Huh?
George, come here. I need to talk to you.
George.
- George!
- Yeah, yeah. What? What?
- Come here. What's the matter, George?
Nothing.
I mean...
...beside from the fact
that we're moving 300 fucking kilos...
...and we're making dog shit,
nothing really.
Million dollars for our first run isn't bad,
George.
It's fucking chump change.
We may be hauling suitcases
across the border. We're screwed.
You know, George, this is a very small part
of business. Very small.
Which reminds me,
I need a favor from you.
The favor was to pick up
50 kilos of cocaine. Fifty.
That's 110 pounds.
Not exactly a small favor.
It's not like bumming a cigarette,
for example.
But what the hell, I didn't have
anything better to do that day.
It's not like I was on parole or anything.
How you doing?
I'm George, friend of Diego's.
Where's Diego?
I don't know. He sent me. I'm George.
Oh.
George.
Well, that explains everything.
Open your mouth, George.
Get fucked.
Open your fucking mouth.
Now, you listen to me.
- You hearing me, huh?
- Yeah.
I've been holding 50 keys for Diego
for three weeks.
You tell him I don't appreciate it.
You tell him I want my money by Friday.
Can you do that?
- I think so.
- Heh, heh. "I think so."
- Hello.
Uh, may I speak to George, please?
George, you have a phone call.
Okay, Mom.
Thank you.
- Hello?
Hello. George?
- Diego.
Hey, how are you?
- How are you?
I'm fine.
- Where are you?
Uh, ha, ha.
Uh, bad news, George. I'm in Colombia.
Boy...
...I sure would like to see you.
And so would some of your old friends.
You know, George, it's a little bit hard
to get away right now.
I'm afraid you're on your own.
I'm in jail.
What?
Yeah.
Oh.
What I'm doing here
is measuring the purity.
Pure coke, uh, it melts away
at about 185, 190 degrees.
Cutting the agents,
they melt away at, uh, about 100...
...and quality product,
well, that's, uh, melting at around 140.
Hundred and thirty. Good.
A hundred and forty. Yes.
A hundred and fifty?
Fuck me running!
A hundred and sixty?
Jesus Christ, a hundred and seventy!
Hundred and eighty.
Hundred and...
A hundred and eighty-seven.
Where did you get this stuff?
Colombia.
Oh, uh...
Well, do you mind if I do a line?
Yeah, go ahead.
Fuck it. Let's all do one.
What did I tell you, Derek?
It's great, uh, but what am I
supposed to do with all this?
Sell it.
Jesus Christ.
I don't see you in two years...
...and you show up at my fucking door
with 110 pounds of blow?
Just fucking sell it, Derek.
All right, but it's gonna take me a year.
I can't feel my face.
I mean, I can touch it,
but I can't feel it inside.
Thirty-six hours.
I don't believe we got rid of it in 36 hours.
I think it's fair to say
you underestimated the market, Derek.
Right on. It's gonna take us longer
to count it than it did to sell it.
- Greetings, Mr. George.
- Hola, amigos.
Here you go, 1.35 million.
Any place in particular
you'd like to count?
On the plane.
What fucking plane?
Huh?
Thanks.
- Hey, what the fuck is going on here, huh?
Good to see you.
- I thought you were in jail.
- Pablo used his influence.
Now, George,
watch what you say, okay?
Everybody hears everything.
A lot of things get said and dónde...
- Well, let's say this isn't America, okay?
- All right.
Life is cheap here. No offense,
but you know what I'm saying.
All right, I'll just keep my fucking mouth
shut then.
Now, who's this person in California,
the connection?
- It's a friend.
- Who? I need to know.
It's a friend. A fucking friend, okay?
I'm not telling you.
- Who?
- A friend!
- I ain't telling you no more.
- Okay, we'll talk about it later.
Look, that's Pablo.
Oh.
Oh, shit.
El Padrino was Señor Pablo Escobar.
And for those of you living on the moon
for the last 20 years...
...he was it.
The boss of it all...
...el mágico.
He will see you now.
- Okay, let's go.
- Not you.
Uh...
- What?
- No. You go.
- No. No, fuck, wait.
- Yeah, you go.
Ahh, it's gonna be fine.
You go. You go, George.
What the fuck? I'm not going over there.
- Yeah.
- No, you gotta do the talking.
He says Señor Escobar only wants
to see you. Not me. You go.
This way, please.
- Yeah, yeah, right.
Take it easy. It's gonna be fine.
All right, fuck it.
So you are the man, huh...
...who takes 50 kilos
and made them disappear in one day?
Actually, it was three days.
Greetings, Mr. George.
Welcome to Colombia.
Oh, this man.
He was full of courage.
Informant?
He would have run,
fled the country, gone to the policía...
...but then his wife, his children,
his parents, his friends...
...many people would die.
Well, let me take this opportunity...
...to thank you for inviting me
to your beautiful country.
- Beautiful, yes. But poor.
- Yeah.
Coffee, bananas, these are our main export
along with mota.
We've been overrun by the fucking
comunistas, but that is another story.
Our business here today is cocaine, yes?
Yes, it is.
I need to find an americano
who I can trust.
One with, uh, honor, intelligence...
You need an americano with balls,
Señor Escobar.
Yes.
And balls, Mr. George.
Well, lookit.
I can do several things for you.
I can transport the cocaine
from your ranch here in Colombia...
...to the United States
starting with California.
I got pilots, I got planes standing by.
Good, good.
But I need more details.
What is the cost?
Uh...
Right off the top of my head...
Well, I'd have to talk to Diego...
...but let's just say,
roughly 10,000 per kilo.
Mm-hm.
How much can you transport?
Again, this is the language that I would
have to discuss with my partner...
...but, uh, 300 kilos...
So that's $3 million.
This I understand.
But, please, tú remove.
- Yeah.
- This complications with Diego.
The stolen cars,
getting him released from the cárcel.
This causes me much inconvenience.
The 50 kilos could have been
a big problem, huh?
I don't like problems.
Uh...
With all due respect, El Padrino...
...Diego is my partner.
So I won't negotiate without him.
I won't do business without him.
I just won't.
- You sure?
- I'm sure.
Let us speak no more of this.
Let's go on a drive.
We have many other things
to talk about, yes?
I've made a decision.
We're going into business together
and I want to start right away.
Whoo!
Cocaine exploded upon
the American culture like an atomic bomb.
It started in Hollywood and moved east
in no time.
Everyone was doing it. I mean, everyone.
We invented the marketplace.
In fact, if you snorted cocaine
in the late 1970s or early '80s...
...there was an 85 percent chance
it came from us.
All right, 3 million. I counted it twice.
Two-point-five, 2.5, I'm sure.
I'm calling it 3.
Then we're half a million off, huh?
Well, fuck it. I'm not counting it again.
Weigh it.
If it's 60 pounds, it's 3 million.
Fifty is 2.5.
Well, I don't give a shit.
It's close enough.
Where do I put it?
Try the back bedroom.
No room.
Try the closet.
Uh...
We're gonna need a bigger boat.
The Colombians recommended
Noriega's bank in Panama City.
It was either that or launder it in the States
for a 60 percent surcharge.
What? Keep only 40 percent of my money?
No, thanks.
Congratulations, gentlemen.
Even Pablo kept his money there.
- I love it.
Who'd fuck with us?
I'm sorry.
I give you $30 million...
...and you give me this little book.
- I'm married.
- Yeah, I know it.
- Can you believe I'm married?
- You're a very lucky man.
- I love you.
- I'm proud of you.
- I love you too, my brother. I love you too.
Hello.
Do I know you?
I don't think so.
No?
Why are you smiling?
I don't know.
I'm George.
I know who you are, an americano.
Mr. Jung.
I see you've met my fiancée, Mirtha.
Yeah?
Yeah. Augusto would like
to see you immediately.
- Augusto would like to see you.
- Okay.
Okay.
In a minute.
Okay. Excuse us a minute.
Go ahead.
- Nice to meet you.
George.
- Please, join us. Have a drink.
How you doing? All right, fellas?
You remember Mr. George?
- Mr. George.
Congratulations on your conquest
of the West Coast.
Thank you. Thanks very much.
How much bigger can we get?
Sky's the limit. It's accepted by actors
and musicians, everybody else will follow.
- Actors and musicians.
- And musicians.
- Very good. Very good.
Diego.
We were just discussing George's
West Coast operations.
- Hey.
- Yeah, George's mystery man.
Yes, what is this mystery man?
When do we meet him?
Well, you can't meet him.
George keeps him a secret.
He's here meeting everybody...
...he goes to Colombia, meets Pablo...
...but still he keeps his secret,
even from his brother, huh?
Come on. We're all in this together.
- Yes, George, there's plenty for everybody.
- No.
You know, I think that...
I think that El Padrino's happy
with the current situation, you know?
Don't you? Yeah.
I'll be back. Excuse me.
You go.
Breaking up a Colombian marriage
was a serious thing.
A lot of people were pissed off.
Didn't matter.
I was Escobar's guy.
I was untouchable.
Mirtha became my running partner.
Beautiful, passionate...
...and as crazy as I was.
She could party like a man
and love like a woman.
There was only one problem.
I would always be a gringo
to the cartel.
Mirtha could change all that
with two choice words:
I do.
So do I.
We had the world
by the short and curlies.
We were young, rich and in love.
Nothing could stop us.
It was perfect.
Oh, dear God.
Hey.
Put that shit away.
You're pregnant, for chrissakes.
Ah, don't be such a fucking hypocrite.
I quit smoking, didn't I?
Just put it away.
My fucking parents are here. Come on.
Oh, my...
- It's beautiful, isn't it?
- Oh, God, it's enormous.
You like it?
Just look...
Look at this credenza.
Oh, yes. What, it's Spanish?
If you don't mind,
how much is one of these?
- It's gotta cost a fortune.
It's a family heirloom.
I've seen these in magazines.
- They don't come cheap.
- Mirtha comes from a very wealthy family.
- Oh.
Pappy, do you like it?
- Very nice.
- Nice.
Come, I'll show you the rest of the house.
Oh, great.
George mentioned a Jacuzzi.
I've always wanted a Jacuzzi.
Oh, and one of those bidets.
Cocktail?
Yeah. Business has been pretty good.
I got this little import-export thing
going down in Miami.
And that's been very profitable for me.
I got my investments. I got, uh...
Don't bullshit me, George.
I don't wanna waste the time.
I don't see you that much.
You come from my body, remember?
You're my baby boy.
Same kid who would jump off a mountain
if someone told him he couldn't do it.
You haven't changed that much, heh,
have you?
Wow.
I know what you're up to.
Not everything, but I get the picture.
And I don't care.
I don't like it.
It's not what I would've chosen for you.
But it's your life.
It's got nothing to do with me.
I couldn't stop you if I wanted to,
could I?
- Probably not.
- No.
It's good.
Got a family.
It's good if it makes you happy.
It's nice to have nice things, George.
Phew.
Are you happy?
Yeah.
Yeah, at the moment, I am happy, Dad.
Three years?
How long have we been in business?
Does she get to meet your connection?
Was she good enough?
Shut up, Diego.
Gonna be here any minute.
I'm trying to concentrate.
Okay? I'm very angry with you, George.
Very angry.
You don't take me to California,
but you take your bitch wife? A woman?
It was you and me who started this.
Hey, you and me.
What do you need my connection for?
What are you gonna do with it?
Nothing.
It's for the principle.
It's for peace of mind.
Jesus fucking Christ.
I ain't telling you, it's just business.
- Now shut up. You're driving me crazy.
- I'm driving you fucking crazy?
You're driving me fucking crazy.
We had a dream.
What happened to our dream?
- Go inside.
- Shit.
Go on.
I give you everything.
I give you everybody.
And what do you give me, George, hmm?
What do you give me?
No, no, amigo.
Right?
No problem.
We'll count the shit later.
You embarrassed me, George.
You made me look very bad.
Nothing.
No, everything is not right.
I bring you in and you slap my fucking face.
This is not the fucking time, Diego.
No, no, no.
No, listen.
Okay, you take the keys.
You take them and go.
Whoa!
Oh, fuck.
Okay?
Everything's all right.
There's no problem.
Okay? Never happened.
Nobody has to know anything about this.
Diego, I want you to very calmly tell
these nice gentlemen...
...where the fucking cocaine is, all right?
Do it now.
Okay?
Nice doing business with you gentlemen.
Goodbye.
Derek Foreal.
What?
Derek fucking Foreal, all right?
Answer to all your fucking dreams.
Happy now?
Derek?
Derek Foreal, Diego Delgado.
Good to see you. Thank you.
- Hey.
- Hello.
I'm so happy to see you, to look at you.
You're beautiful. You're about to burst.
I am.
Tell her not to drink too much, please.
- I'm so glad to see you.
- Me too.
- We've a lot to talk about.
- Where's Diego?
He's not here.
Where is he?
And who the fuck is this Norman Cay guy?
Everybody's talking about Norman Cay.
Norman Cay this, Norman Cay that.
You know him?
He's not a person.
Norman's Cay is an island.
In the Bahamas.
From what they say, it's very peaceful
and that's where Diego has his new home.
As I understand it,
he's bought 160 acres.
A hotel, a marina and an airstrip.
He's doing multiple runs right now
using the island as a jump-off point.
- What?
- Yes.
And Jack Stevens
is already a very busy man.
Along with many others.
No shit.
Hello?
Hello, Derek.
George.
Hey, am I wearing lipstick?
I said, am I wearing lipstick?
When I'm getting fucked,
I wanna make sure my face...
Hey, look, I don't wanna be
in the middle of this.
That's between you and Diego.
- I bring you into this... Hang on.
- Happy New Year.
Happy New Year, honey.
I bring you in, this is how you pay back?
Hey, look, George,
it's nothing personal. I love you.
This is business.
I gotta go, George.
- Derek.
Derek.
What's wrong?
- What?
- Nothing.
Happy New Year.
Welcome, my friend.
- It's been a long time.
- Don't touch me.
Hey.
Happy to see you, George. My brother.
No more brothers, Diego.
Why do you say that? Huh?
You heard me, George.
Of course we are brothers.
You fucked me.
I did not.
Yeah, you did.
You went behind my back.
You cut me out. You fucked me.
Me? No.
Never, George.
Never.
Mm-mm.
I talked to Derek.
Well...
...maybe you're right.
Maybe I did betray you...
...a little bit.
Yeah.
Yeah, I stole your California connection.
So what? Hmm?
Who introduced you
to Pablo Escobar, huh?
Me. Me.
Who introduced you
to your fucking Colombian wife, hmm?
Me. Who protect you...
...when my friend, Cesar Rosa,
wanted to slice your fucking throat out?
Huh? Me.
Who made you make millions
and millions of dollars?
Me.
And what do I get in return?
This.
Accusations.
I have always given you
everything, George.
Always.
But...
...that is over now.
Yeah.
You know, this is my operation,
my dream.
So go home.
Go back home.
Go home. Go back
to your stupid little life.
Go back and sell half grams
to your fucking relatives...
...for all I care because you're out...
Because you're out.
And don't be so emotional, George.
We're brothers.
We are brothers.
Next time it's fucking loaded.
Bye. Bye. Bye.
Bye.
Say hello to your pretty wife for me.
Sure.
Hello.
Jesus Christ.
It's all right, honey.
Look at you.
It's okay.
It's okay, baby.
It's over.
I quit the business. I'm out.
It's all over.
And I'm not going back.
It's just you and me...
...and the baby.
And there's nothing else. There's just us.
You know...
...fuck it.
Fuck them.
Come here.
I did.
I quit the business.
Got out completely.
I mean, what the fuck? Why not?
I'd made $60 million
and I was out clean.
Well, maybe I jumped the gun on "clean."
Georgie, let's go. The baby's coming.
Right, right, right.
I'm coming, I'm fucking coming.
Jesus Christ.
George, hurry up.
Georgie, let's go.
Right. Right. Right. What the fuck?
George! George!
George!
George.
I'll be right down.
Watching my baby girl being born
did something to me.
Motherfucker!
They talk about religious experiences.
I didn't believe in religion.
Hell, I didn't even particularly like kids.
But when Kristina Sunshine Jung came
into this world, something in me changed.
I knew what I was put on the planet for.
It was the greatest feeling I ever had.
Followed very abruptly
by the worst feeling I ever had.
George!
Call the cardiologist.
I think he's having a heart attack.
George!
The official toxicity limit for humans...
...is between 1 and 1 and a half grams
of cocaine, depending on body weight.
I was averaging 5 grams a day.
Maybe more.
I snorted 10 grams in 10 minutes once.
I guess I had a high tolerance.
George, look, I'm not here
to give you lectures.
I have no moral interest in what you do
or don't do.
But take it easy, George.
Stay with us a while.
You have a daughter now.
A daughter.
I came home and cleaned up my act.
I didn't do anything.
No drink, no nothing.
Sober as a judge.
My life was all about Kristina.
Being with her, taking care of her.
I wanted to be a father.
A good father,
just like my old man was to me.
After five years of laying low...
...still sober...
...Mirtha needed to have some fun.
- Guys, excuse me.
So on my 38th birthday...
...she threw a little party
and invited some old friends.
Happy birthday, George.
Mirtha invited me.
Yeah, she told me.
Look, I'm sorry about everything.
You were right. I did fuck you.
And Diego fucked me.
Cut me out too.
Well, yeah, I heard about it.
I lost sight of everything, George.
Forgot who my friends were.
Well, fuck it.
It's in the past.
Just forget about it.
I'm out of the business...
...so we'll just move on, eh?
Yeah.
Good to see you, Derek.
You too.
Let's get a drink.
Who's cutting your hair?
Let's fucking party, motherfucker.
Let's have some fucking fun!
- Jesus, is that Mirtha?
- Yeah.
Christ almighty, George.
What does she weigh, 80 pounds?
Yeah, give or take. Come on.
Okay.
Freeze!
Waiters.
So it's George, is it?
I'm the only guy on the planet
gets busted by fucking waiters.
Why the feds decided to bust me
on that particular night, I'll never know.
Maybe it was the Porsches
and the Maseratis in the driveway...
...my Colombian guest list
or the cocaine buffet.
Whatever it was, they were just waiting
for me to slip up.
And I did.
What's this?
This is your statement.
How it was all yours.
The pound of cocaine
was for personal use.
None of the other guests
had any idea it was there.
Yeah, right.
I want my kid out of protective custody.
Now. No fucking around.
My wife and my daughter
on a plane tonight.
I sign this shit when I know
they're safe and sound.
- No fucking way.
- Well, fuck you.
I sign nothing, then.
Do it.
- Oh, you know what, one more thing.
Yeah, what?
Get me a six-pack.
Yeah, right.
There was no way in the world
I was going back to prison.
So I signed the deal, took the rap
and posted bail.
Once again, I would become
a fugitive on the run.
Hi, Dad.
Hello, George.
Ermine, your son is here.
Tell him I don't wanna see him.
- Tell him he's not welcome here.
- Mom...
Don't you dare step foot in this house.
You're not my son, you hear me?
I don't have a son anymore.
She's angry, George.
It's been all over the news.
Yeah.
I just wanted let you guys know...
...that, uh, I'm gonna be going away
for a little while.
You're not gonna go to trial?
No.
Okay.
So this is it.
I hope not, Pop.
Me too.
Okay.
- I gotta go, Pop. I'll see you.
- Yeah.
- You take care of yourself, George.
- You too.
Señor Jung?
- Yeah.
I wish to present Señor Rodriguez.
He's the president of our bank.
Hi.
I am afraid that there is a problem,
Mr. Jung.
The banks have gone through a change.
Nationalization.
I am afraid that, uh,
your funds have been appropriated...
...by the Panamanian government.
Please forgive me.
Someone should have called you
from the bank earlier.
My apologies, please.
What are we going to do?
- What are we going to use for money?
Mirtha, please.
I will talk to Augusto tonight.
I'll start working for him.
Just tell me!
Just answer the fucking question!
What do we spend? What?
How will we live?
Not in front of the kid.
Don't give me that shit.
Just better do something.
Everything's gonna be okay, sweetheart.
Don't be upset.
What's happening to us?
I don't know.
Are we gonna get split up?
No, Jesus. God, don't even say that.
Listen to me. I love your mother.
But she's upset right now.
And you're my heart, kid.
Now, could I live without my heart?
I hope not.
Take it easy. There's a cop back there,
all right? Right behind us.
Just fucking drive.
What is your fucking problem?
We are broke. That's my fucking problem.
- And you are a fucking spy.
- What?
That's right.
- Always spying, always judging.
- Right.
Everyone's laughing at you in your face,
you fucking pussy.
Thanks.
You let Diego fuck you in the ass.
- Right.
- Maybe because you like it.
- Maybe because you are a fucking faggot.
- Right.
That's what I think you are.
I think you're fucking him
because you're not fucking me.
You gotta be fucking somebody else.
- Why's that?
- Come on. Take it easy.
- Why don't you fuck me anymore?
- Take it easy. Take it easy.
- Why? Why don't you fuck me anymore?
- Get over there. Mirtha.
Don't you ever put your hands on me,
motherfucker!
Don't you ever touch me again!
- Asshole!
- Relax!
Get your hands off me!
He's a fugitive
and a fucking cocaine dealer!
He has a kilo in his trunk right now!
Look. Let me see that...
Take this sorry motherfucker to jail.
I'm divorcing you, George.
And I'm getting custody of Kristina.
And when you get out next week,
you're gonna pay support.
And that's the end of it.
Okay?
There is someone else.
I don't think you care...
...but I wanted to tell you.
Say something.
What do you want me to say?
I'm in prison.
- You should know, you put me in here.
- I knew you'd say something like that.
Always thinking about yourself.
Say hello to your father.
- My God.
- No.
Go now. Say hello.
Hello, sweetheart.
I thought you couldn't live
without your heart.
Every single day in the joint...
...I thought of one thing...
...one thing only:
My baby girl.
I needed to get my heart back.
Hi, honey.
What are you doing here?
Well, I just wanted to let you know
that I was out and I wanted to see you.
How you doing?
George, you just can't show
up like this.
Why don't you try calling me Dad?
I don't want to, all right?
- Now leave me alone.
- Wait, honey. Listen, Kristina.
I'm sorry.
I wanna make everything okay.
You know?
What do you want from me, huh?
I wanna be your dad again.
I just wanna walk with you,
if you don't mind.
I wanna make everything okay.
Please, Kristina.
If you could go anywhere in the world,
anywhere...
...where would you wanna go?
I was making headway.
Kristina and I walked
to and from school every day.
- Things were starting to look up.
- Maybe California?
California?
Well, you can go anywhere in the world.
You can go to India, Tibet.
Uh, Israel, France, whatever.
- You'd still choose California?
- Yeah.
Yeah?
Hey, Mom.
All right. Well, look, go on inside.
Okay.
- Bye, Dad. See you in the morning.
- Okay, I'll be here.
- Hey, Mom.
Hi.
I'm gonna go inside
and do my homework.
Okay, honey. I'll be there in a minute.
What do you want?
Truce.
I don't wanna fight with you anymore,
Mirtha.
I just wanna get along with you,
you know?
Be civil.
You know I've been seeing Kristina,
right?
Yeah, she told me.
You walk her to school.
Yeah.
Anyway, I've been thinking, uh...
I love her. You know that.
I was thinking I'd kind of like to have her.
I've been away for such a long time,
you know, I just...
I just wanna be with her.
I haven't seen one dollar from you.
You haven't paid me one cent.
Child support, alimony.
You start helping us...
...we'll see what will happen.
All right. That's it.
That's all I wanted to say.
Take care, yeah?
You too.
George.
Are you okay?
Yeah.
Hello? Derek.
Hey, George.
Lookit.
I need to do something.
I wanna put together a crew, huh?
Know anybody?
It's a four-man operation.
Two on the ground, two in the air.
Who's the copilot?
You're looking at him.
We'll provide the plane,
transportation costs...
...U.S. Landing spot, and we'll take it
wherever you want it to go.
You provide a pickup point
in South America...
...and you're responsible for payment.
You also assume all bust risk.
After that, we take 65 percent
of all transportation fees...
...10 percent of the gross,
plus our expenses.
And this is not a negotiation,
so if it's okay with you, we can talk further.
If not, forget we had this conversation.
No, no, no. Everything sounds good.
Um, I'm gonna need to meet
everybody involved, though.
Right there at the table.
Come on.
Gentlemen, this is George.
- George.
What do you say?
- Georgie.
My God, Dulli.
- Oh, my God.
Dulli.
- Jesus. It's been 14 years, man.
- Oh, man, George.
- You look great.
- Yeah, so do you.
Hey, this is my friend.
I've known this guy for 30 years.
- Ben.
- How do you do?
- Have my seat.
- Nice to see you.
Heard you got married.
Hey, honey, you know what?
What?
I was thinking about getting
out of town this week.
And where are you going?
I don't know.
- Maybe California.
- Liar.
Yeah.
Go out there, check it out,
see what it's like.
I got a few things
I have to take care of first...
...but I was thinking maybe Thursday.
You know, Thursday after school.
You know I can't.
Mom will never let me go.
You let me take care of your mother.
You just pack your bags, okay?
But I've got school.
I know. But a friend of mine told me
that they got schools in California too.
- You swear?
- Yeah.
Three o'clock, Thursday,
at your mother's. You and me, huh?
- It's a date.
- I don't believe you.
I swear on my life, Scout's honor.
Swear on my life.
I swear on your life.
All right.
That's a nice boy.
Go on, get him, Dulli.
Get in.
- Oh, yeah.
- Are we good?
Are we good? Yeah, we're good.
We're fucking beautiful.
We're perfect.
This is Grade A, 100-percent pure
Colombian cocaine, ladies and gentlemen.
Disco shit.
- Pure as the driven snow.
- Oh, yeah.
- Right.
- Good fucking riddance.
- Dulli.
- Yeah.
- You saved my fucking life.
- No, I didn't.
No shit. You'll never know. Really.
All you guys.
Really.
And being as how I'm feeling
so fucking generous tonight...
...you just got a raise.
A raise?
- Yeah.
Instead of 10 percent,
you're gonna get 15.
Jesus, George.
Fifteen percent?
That's an extra 200 grand.
That's right. Fuck it.
Do whatever want with it.
Have a nice life. I'm out.
Last fucking party.
I'm gonna go out to California.
Start a new life with my kid.
Here's to it.
Cheers.
- Here's to you, Georgie.
- Here's to you, George.
Cheers.
All right, fellas.
- Dulli?
- Yeah.
How about another round?
I'm gonna hit the head.
Okay.
I feel like a fucking kid today.
What?
I feel bad.
Me too.
I like him too, but what's done is done.
So let's not get all sentimental about it,
all right?
Hey, Dulli, you know
what I was thinking?
I was... I was remembering that, uh...
That time we flew in to Mexico.
You remember that fucking landing strip?
- Right?
- Hmm, yeah.
Fucking nuts.
You're much better now.
What's going on?
What the fuck? What's, uh...?
What's with the long faces?
Huh?
Where's my fucking knife?
No.
Let's do it.
I was busted.
Set up by the FBI and the DEA.
That didn't bother me.
Set up by Kevin Dulli and Derek Foreal
to save their own asses.
That didn't bother me.
Sentenced to 60 years at Otisville.
I'd broken a promise.
Everything I love in my life goes away.
- Hey, Georgie.
- Hey, Arch.
What's going on?
Well, ahem...
You all right?
I'm good.
Fuck.
What do you got?
Bad news.
Tried to get you furloughed,
but, uh, your mom squashed it.
Said, uh, would only upset him.
So, um, doesn't look good.
How's he doing?
Not good.
He's out of the hospital.
He's home, but, uh...
...I don't think there's anything
anyone can do for him.
It's just a matter of time.
Got you a tape recorder.
I thought, uh...
...you know,
might wanna hear your voice.
If you wanna say something to him.
Right.
I'll give you five.
Hello, Dad.
You know, I remember a lifetime ago...
...I was about 3 and a half feet tall...
...weighing all of 60 pounds,
but every inch your son.
Those Saturday mornings
going to work with my dad...
...and we'd climb into
that big green truck.
I thought that truck was the biggest
truck in the universe, Pop.
I remember how important
the job we did was.
How, if it weren't for us...
...people would freeze to death.
I thought you were the strongest man
in the world.
Remember those home movies...
...when Mom would dress up
like Loretta Young?
Ice creams, football games.
Waino, the Tuna.
Day I left for California only to come
home with the FBI chasing me.
That FBI agent, Trout.
When he had to get on his knees
to put my boots on, you said:
This is where you belong,
you son of a bitch.
Putting on Georgie's boots.
That was a good one, Dad.
That was really something.
You remember that?
And that time you told me
that money wasn't real?
Well, old man...
...I'm 42 years old...
...and I finally realize
what you were trying to tell me...
...so many years ago.
I finally understand.
You're the best, Dad.
I just wish I could've done more for you.
Wish we had more time.
Anyway...
...may the wind always be at your back...
...and the sun always upon your face.
And the winds of destiny
to carry you aloft...
...to dance with the stars.
I love you, Dad.
Love, George.
George.
George, come on. You have a visitor.
Hello, sweetheart.
Hi, Daddy.
God, you're so big.
Daddy's a fuckup.
No.
Come here.
You're the only thing in my life
that ever meant anything.
You swear?
I swear, baby.
I swear.
I love you, Kristina.
You're the only good thing in my life.
You're the only thing
that ever meant anything to me.
I love you.
Come on. Let's go.
So tell me about your life.
What do you wanna know?
Everything. I mean...
...what do you do? You go to school?
You...?
Sometimes.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
- Just like the old man.
George!
Let's go. It's getting dark.
Come on. It's getting late.
Come on, let's go.
Let's go.
I got a visitor.
Not today, George.
Time to go back.
Yeah, but l...
I wanna put her on the list for tomorrow.
My daughter.
Okay, George.
She's gonna visit me.
My daughter's gonna visit me tomorrow.
So in the end, was it worth it?
It's lockdown time.
Jesus Christ.
How irreparably changed
my life has become.
It's always the last day of summer
and I've been left out in the cold...
...with no door to get back in.
I'll grant you, I've had more
than my share of poignant moments.
Life passes most people by
while they're making grand plans for it.
Throughout my lifetime...
...I've left pieces of my heart
here and there.
And now there's almost not enough
to stay alive.
But I force a smile...
...knowing that my ambition
far exceeded my talent.
There are no more white horses...
...or pretty ladies at my door.
Please rate this subtitle at www.osdb.link/eky9
Help other users to choose the best subtitles