Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org
[Hiccup] Remember what life
used to be like on Berk?
- Dragons.
- [roaring]
[Hiccup]
You had to be crazy to live here.
But we're Vikings.
Crazy is what we do best.
And I guess I had enough crazy in me
to do something no Viking
had ever done before.
I trained a dragon.
Life on Berk hasn't been the same since.
And now, my friends and l
have the greatest job in the world.
We're dragon trainers.
Living with dragons, it ain't easy.
It brings a new adventure every day.
And there's so much to learn.
Because if you wanna train dragons,
you have to know dragons.
So, if you hurry, you can join us
in the Great Hall
where we're just about to start
a new class.
- [Astrid] So that's a Gronckle.
- [Hiccup] Correct.
And you cannot tell
its head from its tail.
Right, right!
Gronckles do not like
to be scratched under their chins.
- I found that out the hard way.
- OK.
No scratching under chin. Got it.
What...? Toothless, what's up, bud?
- Oh, hey.
- Whoa! A new dragon trainer!
A new recruit.
Want to train dragons, do you?
- Looks eager enough.
- This one's got potential.
Aye, we'll see about that.
Here it is.
Book of Dragons. Between these two
covers are the most incredible creatures
you'd ever hope to see.
Some you know, but there
are some you've never seen before.
And you won't last a day out there
if you don't learn the facts in here.
[Hiccup] Gobber, you can't scare us.
We've already trained dragons.
[Gobber] This book contains more
than just training.
It's the key to unlocking
a new world of dragons.
And I don't suppose you know
who started it all...
- [grunts] Oh!
- ...do you?
[Astrid] I thought it had something
to do with Bork the Bold.
- Oh.
- [Gobber] Well-spotted, lass.
But before he was bold, he was known
as Bork the Very, Very Unfortunate.
- [Hiccup] That's an... odd nickname.
- [Gobber] Aye, but apt.
It seemed that everything
Bork touched went wrong.
[grunting] Oy!
- [zaps]
- Whoo-hoo!
[Gobber] Bork was my
great-great-great-grandfather.
- But he started out as a shepherd.
- [bleating]
But his flock got very small.
That fact is, Bork and dragons
didn't seem to mix.
- [dragon howling]
- [grunting, muttering]
- So he gave blacksmithing a try...
- Ouch!
...and had a go at farming.
But he settled for the life
of a fisherman.
Yum.
[whimpers]
- [muttering]
- [meows]
[sighs]
[Gobber] And he used to say,
''If you see a dragon, kill on sight.''
You kids taught us that we
could train a dragon.
But it was Bork who had the idea
to classify them.
And what does Bork say
is the first class of dragons?
[Hiccup] Oh, that's easy. Stoker class.
Now according to the book,
these hot-headed dragons
are furious fire-breathers.
And when training a Terror,
start with a very shiny object.
[Astrid] Oh, he's cute.
- [barking]
- [Gobber] Cute?! Maybe on his own.
But Bork says if you get
these little Terrors in a group,
it's no picnic.
You see, Terrors are social creatures.
They love to hunt in packs.
Now, what about this brute?
- [man grunting]
- The Monstrous Nightmare.
You can see how this foul beast
got his name.
Nary a Viking has tamed
this fierce creature.
[squealing]
But you know what Bork used to say?
''You fall down, you get right back
on the dragon.''
[Astrid] l bet he didn't know that the
Nightmare can set itself on fire.
And if there's one thing you don't want,
it's an angry Nightmare.
That's why we tried
a more gentle approach.
[Hiccup] lnstead of wrestling
a Monstrous Nightmare,
just give him a little respect.
A gentle hand on his snout.
[Gobber] Looks like you kids
have made some breakthroughs.
All right, Fishlegs. Why don't
you tell us about your dragon?
[Fishlegs] Meatlug's my Gronckle,
and Gronckles are tough,
rock-eating, Boulder class dragons.
[Astrid] But how do you
train a Gronckle?
[Hiccup] A Gronckle
won't stay mad at you
if you just feed
him a little dragonnip.
[Fishlegs] Yeah, and like all dragons,
Gronckles are rumoured to have
five stages of maturity.
The first stage is the egg.
Then the tiny teeth.
The short wing.
The broad wing. And the last stage
is the titan wing,
which is extremely rare.
[Gobber] Rare, but a sight to behold.
Let's look at another
from the Boulder class.
The Whispering Death.
Just saying its name
gives you the shivers.
Bork says the Whispering Death
knows only one thing: killing!
He burrows through the dirt and rock,
attacking from below.
- [woman screaming]
- [man grunting]
[man screaming]
[roaring]
[Fishlegs] Their rotating teeth
can bore through anything.
And these Boulder class baddies
are so wicked,
they can breathe rings of fire!
But even though these dragons
have a fearsome reputation,
it turns out they just love
to be brushed.
[Hiccup] With patience,
any dragon can be trained.
Even this next batch: Fear class.
These dragons are silent,
they're sneaky,
they turn up when you least expect them.
[Astrid] lf Fear class dragons are so
sneaky, how did Bork find one?
[Gobber] He did better than find one.
He found the lair of a Zippleback.
Well, actually,
it wasn't he who found it.
It was his trusted sheep Willy.
And what do you know of a Zippleback?
[Hiccup] Got two heads.
Twice the danger.
One head releases gas...
...the other ignites it.
[Astrid] And if you feed
both heads at once,
they become
one agreeable dragon.
[Fishlegs] That's right.
lf you want to befriend a dragon,
it's a good idea to start
by feeding it.
And once they're fed,
make sure you play with them.
[Gobber] You kids are full of good tips.
But what happens when you go
from two heads to four?
It's the Venus flytrap of dragons,
the devious Snaptrapper!
[Astrid] The book says that this wild
beast has enticed many a Viking
into its deadly trap,
with its sweet smell of chocolate.
[Fishlegs] And like all dragons,
the Snaptrapper sheds its scales.
- [Astrid] And its claws.
- [screeching]
But they all grow back.
With all those heads, Bork must
have had four times the trouble.
[Gobber] Aye, that's a fact.
Until one day, Bork made
an interesting discovery.
Huh?
- [roaring]
- [whimpering]
[Gobber] Snaptrappers love rain.
And they can't wait
to play in the mud.
[Fishlegs]
Well, the Snaptrapper is incredible,
but let's see what secrets we uncover
with the next class of dragons.
[Astrid] The Sharp class.
These dragons have
a generous dose of vanity,
and spend a lot of time preening.
My personal favourite is
the Deadly Nadder.
Bork says that Nadders have
the hottest fire in the dragon world.
We found the best way to train her
was to approach her carefully,
slowly moving around back
toward her tail.
[Gobber] Her tail? You've gone mad.
It's full of poisonous spikes
that can launch at will.
[whimpering]
[Astrid] Yes, but if you
move slowly enough,
and you show her
you're not a threat,
she'll let you smooth
her tail spikes down.
[Hiccup] There's more
to the Sharp class than just Nadders.
Let's look at what Bork wrote
about the Timberjack.
[Gobber] This dragon attacks
out of the sky with razor-sharp wings...
[roaring]
...and can slice through a forest
of trees like a giant guillotine.
Hmm?
Ow-ee.
[Hiccup] But those long wings of the
Timberjack make it impossible for him
to even scratch his back.
[Fishlegs]
Yep, and if you scratch his itch,
he's your friend forever.
[Gobber] Another brilliant survival tip.
A perfect opportunity to teach our new
trainer about this class of dragons.
The Tidal class.
These beasts live in the watery deep
and they can out-swim the fastest ship.
[Fishlegs] Did Bork even know
that the sea was full of dragons?
[Gobber] Not at first.
But he soon found out
that the open sea was no easier,
because if there's one thing that sea
dragons like to eat more than a fish...
...it's a whole boatload of fish.
[grunting, whimpering]
[Gobber] And after that first sighting,
Bork called it a Scauldron.
As we now know, that sea dragon
fills itself up with water,
then heats it in its giant
cauldron-like stomach.
One blast from that hot water,
and you're finished.
[Hiccup] We found out something
surprising about Scauldrons.
lf you wanna train them,
douse yourself with water.
Turns out they like anything
that reminds them of home.
[laughs nervously]
Stop it! Stop!
[Gobber] Look at what also lurks in
the deep. It's the mighty Thunderdrum.
This beast moves through the water
like a tornado,
and is capable of delivering a sonic
blast of pure dragon power.
The story goes that Bork
got lost ice fishing,
and he stumbled across
a Thunderdrum nest.
That must have been
quite a rude awakening,
because when a Thunderdrum hatches
from its shell,
it makes a sound so loud
it rattles the sky!
[howls, grunts]
[whistling]
[Gobber] Now, here's a class
that might stump you.
[Fishlegs] What symbol is that?
[Gobber] It's a symbol
for the Mystery class.
We don't really know
how these guys work.
That's why they're a mystery.
ls it a tree? ls it a rock?
No, it's the Changewing.
This strange dragon can disappear
into any environment.
[Hiccup] Bork noticed that Changewings
are curious creatures.
And they display mimicking behaviour.
Whatever they see,
they love to copy.
[Gobber] Changewings
are known for their acid breath
and their ability to hypnotise.
But finding one takes a keen eye.
[Astrid] Does being able to change
colour mean their skin is softer?
[Gobber] For some, yes.
And it makes them vulnerable to attack,
so these dragons protect themselves
in a strange way.
Like this beauty:
The BoneKnapper.
This odd creature collects the bones
of dead dragons
and makes itself an unusual
coat of armour.
[chuckles]
[dragon snarling]
[roars]
[Gobber] The best way to deal with this
brutal bag of bones is to subdue it
- with force and fear and firepower!
- [Fishlegs] Sure, right.
- That's what you did, Gobber.
- [Gobber] All right, all right.
You give a BoneKnapper whatever it's
looking for and it's just like
an overgrown puppy dog. Why don't we
go on to the next class of dragons?
[Fishlegs] Finally, Strike class.
[Hiccup] Every dragon in this class
is characterised by blazing speed,
vice-like jaw strength
and extreme intelligence.
l give you the Skrill.
This elusive creature
is highly secretive,
and is known to ride lightning bolts.
Found only during electrical storms,
it can shoot bursts of white fire.
lf you get too close to a Skrill,
your hair will stand on end.
[bleating]
Let's see what else is in the book.
The Night Fury.
Speed, unknown. Size, unknown.
[Gobber] l guess this book
really does need updating.
[Hiccup] The unholy offspring
of lightning and death itself.
[Gobber] So, Hiccup,
how did you train a Night Fury?
[screeching, roaring]
[Hiccup] First l had
to get his attention.
Then l needed to earn his trust.
Everyone wonders what it's like to fly.
And now,
thanks to Toothless, we know.
These islands are full of dragons.
But I've never seen another Night Fury.
I have so many questions about him.
But I do know one thing.
Toothless didn't just become my friend.
He became the friend
who gave me my purpose.
[Gobber] He's quite the dragon,
I'll grant you that.
So, now you see.
Everything we know about dragons
started with one very
unfortunate Viking,
who had a hunger to learn more.
Ha ha!
[Gobber] Over the years,
curious Vikings like yourselves
have updated the pages,
and in time,
Bork of Dragons became
Book of Dragons.
It's now a very big part
of our Viking heritage.
So big, that Bork
the Very, Very Unfortunate
was soon renamed Bork the Bold.
- [Astrid] I bet you wish you knew him.
- [Gobber] Well, I do know him.
The fact is, we all know him.
- Thanks to the Book of Dragons.
- [children cheering]
[Hiccup] And I guess one day,
new kids will know us
by how we trained our dragons.
[Gobber] Aye, that they will.
But in the meantime,
you kids can carry on
where Bork left off.
[Hiccup] Well, then I'd better
finish these Night Fury pages.
- There's still so much to learn.
- [Fishlegs] Yeah!
Like how fast Toothless can go.
Well, to be honest,
I don't know his top speed, but...
Oh! Somebody wants to find out,
does he? OK. Let's find out.
Last one to the peak
has to clean the stables.
Hey, wait up! I gotta see this!
To be young, wild
and haVe most of my limbs again.
Oh, right! Congratulations!
Now you're on your way.
Our newest dragon trainer.
It's time to meet your first batch now.
Ha ha! Good luck!
[screeching, muttering]
[bleating]
Please rate this subtitle at www.osdb.link/59c96
Help other users to choose the best subtitles