Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org
Hey, wake up, asshole.
My father wrote this song
10 years ago, remember?
Yeah, it's really good.
It's going to be in
a Blimpie commercial.
You watch TV, don't' you?
No, no.
Casanova out your call.
Yeah, we say I'm a
real crowd pleaser.
Good times are
guaranteed for all.
I got Nasty Habits.
I keep bad company.
If there's something
I want I just grab it.
You know, he's
driving me crazy.
He's been showing up
at my set every day.
Well, what do you mean?
Well, I figured I would
partial in the slave class.
So he's been coming on the
set and ruining everything.
We're over scheduled,
we're over budgeted.
It's horrible.
If its' a good time,
that's all right though.
Honey, I'm the man to call.
I got nasty habits.
I keep bad company.
If there's something I
want, I just grab it.
He says he's looking
for his girlfriend
but she left him 10 years ago.
Then that would have
to be your mother.
Oh, no.
She left him 20 years ago.
What's he doing now, I mean
besides driving you nuts.
Nothing.
Nothing?
He owns all this land
as far as you can see.
Well then, I think I'm going
to be able to help him out
with his problems and if he's
as rich as you say he is he
can help me out with mine.
It's going to work out
very well, I think.
How did he get so rich?
He got lucky.
He was out looking for
his girlfriend one night
and he got hit by a Rolls Royce.
He was so stoned, he
didn't feel a thing.
But he got tons of money
because they thought
he suffered brain damage.
Good guess.
Why are we stopping?
We'd better put
our seat belts on.
Why is that?
My father says the best
way to take this next part,
is to get it over with fast.
Oh my God!
Oh, Jesus!
Oh!
company.
If there's something I
want, I just grab it.
Honey, I don't set rules.
Yeah, I've got nasty habits.
I keep bad company.
If there's something I
Oh, slow down.
Just slow down a
little bit, please.
Whoa!
What is this?
Hands up there!
Oh, my God.
I've got nasty habits.
I got more than I need.
Nasty habits.
Oh, whew.
Well, we made it.
If I could puke,
I'd feel better.
I just have a thing
against puking.
Ah!
That was something, huh?
Oh,--
- Just get my bag.
I forgot to tell
you something.
Yeah.
My dad's got
weird eating habits.
So don't take food if
he offers it to you.
He's a gourmet?
You'll see.
Dad!
Hi!
Hi, honey!
I have someone here
I want you to meet.
What?
He's here to help you.
I want you to meet
a friend of mine.
Huh?
Could you turn the music down?
I can't hear you because
of the music it's...
I can't hear you.
I have to turn the music down.
OK, OK.
Hey!
Charlie!
Thank you.
Aw, man that's the first
time we came in together.
This is Dr. Liddledick.
Little what?
Um, dick.
But it's pronounced
"Lie-del" dick.
Well, nice to meet
you, Mr. Liddledick.
Um, you know, I'm going
to go after rehearsal.
Oh honey.
Honey, where you rehearsing?
I'll come and see you.
Uh, I don't know.
But I'm late so.
Well, how am I supposed
to get back to town?
Oh he'll give you a ride.
Thank you, darling.
OK.
Bye.
Liddledick, huh?
Well, at least you got one.
Yeah, when the skipper,
you know, he got mad at
Gilligan, remember that?
Oh, that's fine.
Excuse me?
Do you know where
the principal is?
Excuse me?
Tree, did we have
an appointment?
You know how I am about time.
Well, you wanted to
see me about my son.
Oh, Kyle.
I'm afraid I'm
going to have to ask
you to take Kyle out of school
Out of school?
Well, that's a bummer.
Here at
New Age High School,
we have only two rules: no
book reading and no homework.
And Kyle has broken
both of them.
Double bummer.
He just
doesn't seem to understand
our television technique.
The children sit in front
of the television sets
and watch "Gilligan's Island."
Afterwards, we have a little
discussion of the hidden
meanings and life lessons.
Everybody is very
happy except for Kyle.
Oh, he's so weird.
And
I think Kyle needs therapy.
Therapy?
Rock and roll therapy.
Have you ever heard
of "The Farts"?
"The Farts?"
Well, "The Farts"
are the loudest rock
and role group in the world.
I have tickets for
their next concert.
Perhaps if you and the boys
father were to take Kyle.
His father?
I haven't seen his
father in 10 years.
Have you ever
been hypnotized before Mr. Man?
Uh, hypnotized?
Yeah.
Is that like--
Well, you know, I
was in jail once.
And these guys tried, you know,
No, no, no.
That's completely different.
And this is painless.
Well, that's what
they said, man.
It's painless and drug free.
Oh, bummer.
OK, now
watch this very closely.
You're getting sleepy.
Very sleepy.
You will like this film.
You will tell a friend.
Now, I want you to
go back in time.
Way back, further, further.
No, no,
no, not that far back.
Very sleepy.
Good.
OK, now, Mr. Man.
I'm going to say a word, I want
you to give me the first word
that comes into your mind.
Pussy.
No, we haven't started yet.
First word will be, dog.
Tree.
OK, that's excellent.
The next word is, salami.
Tree.
OK, that's good.
Oh, Jesus!
Ouch.
- Tree.
- Shit.
Tree.
No,
no, we are just about--
Tree.
This-- exactly what
kind of tree is
this that we're talking about?
Blonde.
Blue eyes.
Nice personality.
So this
tree is a woman.
Is this-- is this your woman?
She left me.
She left me and took my baby.
Took everything.
Took her Joni Mitchell
record and she split, man.
Why did she leave you?
Now, think back.
Said she couldn't sing, man.
Oh boy, she couldn't sing.
Whoa.
It's a big hassle, man.
I'm a black man.
I'm a
militant black, man.
militant black man.
I'm a
kill you, black man.
kill you black man.
Hey, man.
Hold it, hold it, hold
it, hold it, hold it.
Hey, man.
Hold it, hold it,
hold it, hold it.
Hey man.
Hold it, hold it.
Wait man, wait.
Wait, hold it, hold it.
Come here, let me talk
to you, come here.
Just hold on for a minute.
Come here.
Told you before, man.
The woman can't sing, boy.
You got to get rid of her, Jack.
We have work to do.
And I ain't-- got
to get rid of her.
What are you
talking about, man?
I'm talking about
my blue booty, boy.
You got to get rid of her.
You understand what I mean?
I mean, she can't carry a
tune in a wheelbarrow, man.
You know what I mean?
Get with-- Go on, you
tell her now, man.
You told me you were
going to tell her before.
I told you she couldn't sing.
Got them--
I'll think of something.
That was so groovy.
Oh!
Bunny, let's do it again.
Ah!
Come on, Bunny
I'm still horny.
Let's get it on, again.
Oh, shit I'm late.
Look at the time, man.
Oh, I got to go.
I'm late.
Oh damn.
What do you mean, you're late?
I got to rehearsal, man.
Oh!
We've got a rehearsal?
Oh, honey.
Why didn't you tell me?
I've gt to get ready.
I've got to get a babysitter.
Ah, you don't need
a babysitter, man.
Yeah, cool.
I'll just bring him with me.
Ah, you don't need to come,
man, you're not in the band
anymore.
What do you mean,
I'm not in the band?
Well,
- We had a meeting, man.
And we decided it'd be better
if you were out of the band
until we got a
record contract, man.
Then after that, it'll be cool.
You can come on the road
with us, man, and sing.
You know?
Just like before, with the mic
off and everything, you know?
With the mic off?
Yeah, except for
the other day, man.
Someone left your mic
on by mistake, man.
Wow.
We-- we couldn't
figure out where
that sound is coming from, man.
I thought I blew a
speaker or something.
Oh, Christ.
I got to pick up that girl, too.
Yeah, Bobby met this chick, man.
She's a topless dancer but
she sings her ass off, man.
She looks great.
And I got to go
pick her up, man.
So how do I look?
Huh?
I don't know about
this outfit, man.
Do you-- Do you think
it's cool enough?
You know, I think I'm
ready for a new look.
What do you think?
Hey!
What are you doing, man?
She cut all the patches off
my jeans, man, and left me.
And took the kid and
the patches with her.
OK.
Let's go back to the very,
very beginning with you
and this, this Tree.
When did you meet her?
Think back, now.
What do you see?
Salad.
Whoa.
Lettuce, tomato, salad oil.
Salami, strawberries, pasquedos.
Yeah.
Squishy stuff.
More squishy stuff.
Sourdough bread and
Mexican busboys.
White people, Iranian
cashiers and oh,
waitresses with nice titties.
Oh, sorry, man.
That's all right.
I'll get it, Mr. Man.
How's the breakfast, man?
I'm sorry.
It's a little rubbery.
Hey, I'll make you pancakes--
No, no, no.
That's all right.
Let's just get on
with your therapy.
After your wife and child left
you, then what did you do?
I started Hippyland, man.
When my woman left, I
had a brilliant flash
I started Hippyland, man,
just to raise some cash.
I wanted it to be just
like Disneyland, man.
For all the hippy dippy
people right across this land.
With a big bong ride that
would suck you inside.
Spin you round and round
while everybody got down.
Making love, not war 'til
their bodies got sore.
Then you work out all your
cramps in the lava lamps.
But the baddest
ride of all would
be The Free Fall Balls that
take you way up in the sky.
Groovy way to get high.
But first you stand in
line for this real fun time
and you better not cry
when it's your turn to fly.
And don't look down when
you're way up off the ground.
Oop, I changed my mind,
I don't want to go.
Hey, wait a minute bro.
Can we take this slow?
Say fool, oh, lord,
look out below.
Hey, it's OK.
Now, don't run away because
the next ride you take
will be a piece of cake.
And you don't have to stand
for what we've got planned.
This is going to be fun,
unless you're too dumb to come.
Just hang on tight and we
will make it all right.
Now, blast off time for
a real space flight.
And don't get sick
inside this dick.
We'll spin you round and
round way above the ground.
Are we having fun?
Rides almost done.
Look out below, I think
I'm going to come.
Things are going
fine I was building
the ride when old Bobby came
by and somehow snuck inside.
I didn't know he was there
'til I raised him in the air.
He was screaming
so loud, I didn't
know what was the matter
'til I saw him hanging there
and I ran and got a ladder.
While I was getting him down,
I gave the balls a little touch
and Bobby took off.
He didn't like it very much.
Hey man what are you doing?
Nose bleeds when
I'm in an elevator.
Don't worry about it, man.
I'll fix it I just
gotta get a ladder.
I'll be right up.
Don't go away, OK?
Get me down, fool.
Get me down.
Hey listen, man.
The truck's stuck
in the up position.
But don't worry, man.
I'll have you down
before you know it.
The operating
modes of the sweep delayer
indicated by the LED
lamp located at the right
of the delay slighting switch.
The switch intersects
the light...
OK.
OK, I want you try this on.
- Testing one, two--
- No, no, no.
It goes right on your head.
There you go.
OK.
What kind of tape
recorder is this?
No, it's not a tape recorder.
What I want to do is I'm going
to be testing your brain waves.
You're not a reporter?
No, no, no.
I'm a psychiatrist.
Oh, I thought
you were a reporter
from "High Times," man.
No.
Been waiting for
my little gift.
Well, that's funny.
Let me see something.
Just for a second here.
Yeah, well it's not the hat.
Let me try this.
Try it again.
Amazing.
Just amazing.
Well, according to
your brainwave charts,
your solution is
pretty darn simple.
You need a job.
A blow job?
No, no, no, no.
Money.
- Sure, I'll pay, man.
- No, no, no.
You see, you're getting
way off the track here.
What you need is some sort of
occupation that can just get
your mind right off that Tree.
- Who?
- Tree.
Your woman.
You remember, the one
you're trying to forget?
Yeah right.
According to this, you
are actually well-suited
for four different occupations.
I have to tell you, though,
that you didn't test
too high on the chart here.
You're somewhere between
plankton and toaster.
But that still leaves
four jobs open for you.
Either politician, lawyer,
boat anchor, or roadie.
I'm a roadie, man.
I really am.
I got a truck and everything.
Well, splendid.
Then when I snap my
fingers, you'll be a roadie.
You'll be back on
the road again.
Forgetting all about
this Tree business.
And write me a
check for $10,000.
Cool.
You know what?
Come to think of
it, make it for 20.
Because after all, I
did make a house call.
Which reminds me, I have to
be in Torrance in an hour.
So why don't you call me a cab?
Sorry.
Hey, you're a cab.
I'm a roadie.
I have to been in
Torrance in an hour.
Excuse me, man.
Just a minute.
Let me plug that one in.
OK.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
It's got a short in it, man.
I've got to get
this thing fixed.
Gotta be in Torrance
in an hour, man.
What about my check?
Oh yeah, your check.
And you're a cab.
Thank you.
20.
$20.00!
- OK, Bill.
This is our last supper
for a while, man.
Because I'm on the road.
Here you are.
Seems I forgot
which one's yours.
Well, here.
You choose.
Oh, man.
Well, I'm hungry, Bill.
Yum.
I think you're fooling me, Bill.
Hmm.
Honey.
Kyle.
Always reading.
It's not healthy.
That's why you're having
so much trouble in school.
Mom, that school sucks.
The Principal's a kook.
C. Thomas puts out a lot
of money for that school.
So, he's a kook, too.
C. Thomas is a kook?
How dare you talk
about him like that.
If it wasn't for C. Thomas,
we wouldn't have all of this.
He takes good care of us.
Come on, honey.
You just got to make
more of an effort.
Watch more TV.
When I was your age that's
all I did, was watch TV
and listen to music.
Mom, I do listen to music.
Yeah, but what kind of music?
Beethoven?
So, I like Beethoven.
Well, tonight we're going
to go see "The Farts."
So come on, honey.
Get ready.
Oh baby, are you dirty!
Oh!
I missed you.
Hey, we're back on
the road, though.
Oh, wow , a roach.
Hey!
I'll save this for later.
OK, are you going to
start for me or what?
Check this out, man.
Dude calls up Keith
and says he wants
me to come in and audition.
You know, what does he think,
I'm Rob Lowe or something?
You know, I'm a
professional, man.
I know I get offers on films.
You know, I don't
read for nobody.
I'm C. Thomas Howell.
I don't need this.
I'll go do a film in
the Mediterranean,
with Franco Zepherelli.
With my fine babe
and my kid here, man.
That's what I'll do.
Thank you very much.
- Torrance, man.
Where the hell's Torrance?
Torrance.
I better look at a map.
OK.
Torrance.
Well, here's Venice.
I'd better go ask that dude.
Hey, excuse me, man.
Hey, is this Tampa
City or Almani, man?
I can't figure this map out.
Where you want to go?
I have to be in
Torrance in an hour.
Hey, tell you what, man.
You help me start the
car, I'll take you there.
What's wrong with it, man?
I don't know, it's
my cousin, Julio's.
He;s getting married, man.
I'm late, too.
I think I've got.
Yeah, start it up.
Yeah, hey start it, man.
All right.
Go for it.
Go for it, man.
Hey, hold it, man.
Stop guy.
Stop, stop, stop.
All right.
Por que, man.
I'll follow you.
I ought to kill
you, son of a bitch.
Crazy hippy.
Oh, shit.
My nylon's come undone.
C. Thomas, wait.
Hey, Kyle, you
gotten laid yet?
You're so mean to me.
I'm trying to
help the guy out.
Give him a break.
Only the best, now.
Look, look, grab a couple of
beers and meet us in the back.
Track him down.
Like bursting out of the dark.
Come on.
All I feel is the
pain in my heart.
She's a moving target.
One I've missed before.
Yeah,
Well, we made it.
This is Torrance.
Hey, that must be the gig.
My name's been on your lips.
Wonder who you're kissing now.
Wonder who's next on your list?
Like a gunshot out of the dark.
I'm feeling the
pain in my heart.
She's a moving target.
Cannonball.
Get one more shot to
even up the score.
The guy's a jerk.
Yeah, but he's
great in bed, come on.
Oh, you're still seeing
him or can I get his number?
What, do you got
shit for brains?
Man, I'm sorry.
I'm going to
kick your ass, man.
Oh, shit.
Get him.
You little kid bastard.
You're mine, all mine.
OK, split up.
OK.
Woah!
What the fuck is this?
Sorry I'm late, man.
I had a map and everything, man.
And somehow I
ended up in Almani.
So then I asked
directions, you know?
And then I ended up
in Wilmington, man.
And I asked directions again
and I ended up in Compton.
I didn't ask anybody there, man.
I just drove out of Compton
and ended up in Pasadena.
And finally found
a hitchhiker, man.
And they were coming here,
so I ended up here, man.
I'm sorry I'm late, man.
Where's Dave?
Uh, Dave's not here, man.
I can see, Dave's not here.
But where is he?
He's sick. he's sick.
Sick my dick He's probably
somewhere fucked up.
Little no talking, black
ass, junkie bastard.
Right.
Whoa, Look here, forget that.
The gig is over.
Look, you're headed
for Fresno, now.
Tomorrow, / You
know where that is?
Fresno?
I got the address here.
There you go.
Oh, wrong address.
That's the wrong address.
Not to walk on by, Fresno
is up near San Francisco.
You can't go up there with
your ass hanging out like that.
Did you really
pay for this shit?
God damn, look like your barber
and your tailor are fucking.
Can you beat this?
You got anything better than
this Stevie Wonder outfit?
Yeah, I've got my clothes
with me, man, in the truck.
Well please bring the
mother fuckers with you.
Go on, hippy.
Fresno, right?
Fresno.
Seems like I'm
working for nothing.
That ain't nothing new.
I know my bills are always late.
Car payments six months overdue.
Come on, stay
awake, stay awake.
Sure someday I'll have it all.
Girls and all the
money I spend on you.
Now, I'm going to have
to hawk this new guitar
to pay the rent.
Hey!
Hey, Far Out Man,
what the road, man.
You're going to get
us killed, golly.
Cheech?
Huh?
Hey, man!
I said wake up.
Look you're going to get--
Just stay on the white line.
God damn.
Man, don't you have any
coffee or anything here?
What am I doing in
this movie, man?
I got development
deal all over town.
I'm out of here.
I'm going to do
anything for money.
Whew!
I'll do anything for money.
Oh, shit!
Honey, what can I do for you?
Money is the--
Hey, hey dude, wait!
Wait up!
Hey, stop!
Stop!
Oh, God.
Hey!
Yup, starting to hear things.
Hey, hop in.
Damn, I didn't even see you.
So where are you headed?
Home, I guess.
So where is home?
Palisades.
You're hitchhiking
the wrong way, dude.
I'm heading for Fresno.
Fresno?
I don't want to go to Fresno.
No one wants to
go to Fresno, man.
Hey, listen, my
mom will pay you.
Relax, man.
Relax.
Say, I'll tell you what, dude.
You come to Fresno with me
now, I'll give you a gig.
How long?
You could help me.
How long is it going to be?
Just a night.
Just a day and a night.
OK, just a
day and a night.
I'll have
you home by tomorrow, man.
At the latest.
Kyle!
Honey, where are you?
Homer!
I love a cowboy in
his tight blue jeans.
His boots with the pointed toes.
It's a sexy way to meet
riding ropes at the rodeos.
I love a cowboy.
Can I borrow a
Oh, yeah.
You going to phone your mom?
Yeah.
Good idea.
Operator recording.
How would you like
to direct this call?
Collect call from Kyle.
Oh, hold on.
There's a call on
the other line.
Hello?
I have
a collect call from Kyle.
Will you accept the charges?
Yes.
Kyle?
Oh, honey.
Oh, thank God.
Where have you been?
I'm with this guy.
I think we're in Fresno, now.
You're in Fresno?
OK.
Music.
I love a cowboy in
his tight blue jeans.
His boots with the pointed toes.
It's a sexy way to meet,
riding ropes at the rodeos.
I love
Yeah, I'm with this guy.
What do you mean,
you're this guy?
Too early in the morning to
be listening to this shit, man.
He sweeps me off my feet.
Makes no difference
if you're short
Got nothing but cowboy
music on this thing.
Whoops.
Alabama slammer.
Oh, good.
Here's something.
Oh, man.
Kyle?
Shit.
Come on, hit him.
Let's go.
Go, fight.
Go.
Get him.
Hit him, hard.
Come on, whack him.
Get him, get him again.
Wham.
Come on, man.
What was his problem, man?
I don't know, man.
That
guy was a jerk.
Come on, let's go find
somewhere else, man.
Their too nuts around here.
I mean, did you
see that dude, man?
I mean, let's give taxi
over a rest or what.
Damn, man.
Hey, hey where'd the road go?
Oh, oh, hey.
Your journey is over here.
Hi, this is Holly Turbo, From
KASSTV Here at the famous White
Melon Airport.
Where, world famous Hollywood
stars keep their airplanes.
In fact, here comes
one of them, now.
Tree.
It's in my makeup bag.
Tom is somebody from
the-- from the Rat
Pack or the Brat Pack or some--
Hi there.
I'm Holly Turbo from KASSTV.
Your-- what's your name?
- C. Thomas Howell.
- Oh, that's it.
And what's her name?
- This is Tree.
Oh, she's Tree.
She's one of those players
in those bimbo movies
or something.
- Please, please, please.
This is my fiance.
Oh, is this television?
- Yes, it is.
Are we on?
Oh listen.
Everybody out in TV land--
Now Tree.
Our son has--
- Tree, Tree.
- --disappeared.
And I can't find him--
This is a serious
interview program.
So I was wondering if anybody
could get a hold of him,
could they please connect?
- Later hon.
- We've got to get going.
We've got to get away.
Thank you.
Could you tell us, do
have an airplane here, sir?
Yes, I do actually.
I've got a couple
of them in the back.
Oh, that's wonderful.
C. Thomas, ask her name so
they know who to call for Kyle.
Ask her name.
Come on.
You know, we're--
our child's missing.
Well, what's his name?
Go ahead, what's his name?
His name is Kyle.
And he's about Tree's height.
He's blonde.
- Blonde.
- And--
And he doesn't have
his braces on anymore.
Right, right.
So actually--
I'll tell you what.
I'd love to do an
interview on you.
So anybody who knows--
Well, if you're
back here tomorrow.
Honey, please please.
I'm trying to talk.
OK?
I'll you're back here
tomorrow, I'll give
you a full blown interview.
- Same time?
But right now, we're
in a very big hurry
and I appreciate your time.
- Same time, same station?
- Absolutely
Oh, do you hear him
ladies and gentlemen?
He'll be here.
Tune in.
Oh, I hope we find him.
Hey,
babe, don't worry about it.
I hired the A, number
one detective in Fresno.
(TRUCK HORN
BEEPS)
Oh, what was that?
Damn.
What the shit?
See listen, man.
I'm a little lost.
Do you know where this place is?
Christ, I never been to Fresno.
Sure smells weird here.
Fool, you're here.
The gig is in there.
Can I see some ID, man?
Oh, far out.
No, man.
Get off.
No, off the stage man.
I got the rest of the
stuff in the truck, man.
No, no.
Hey, sorry I'm late, man.
Off the stage, man.
What?
Off.
I can't hear you, man.
Get off the stage.
Off the stage.
Yeah, that's it, man.
Take the guitar.
Backstage, OK, man.
I'm putting all this
stuff backstage.
Hey, let me try that, man.
Let me try it.
Say, anybody seen that Brody?
You know the little
raggedy mother fucker.
Hey, I'm over here, dude.
Over where?
Right here.
God damn, man,
quit fucking around.
Look here this is serious.
That's cool, isn't it?
Yeah, yeah, that's nice.
Look at me, you got any shit?
What kind of shit?
Blow.
You got any?
Blow?
Blow.
Oh, that's funny, man.
I like that.
That's real funny.
I ask for blow, he blows.
Yeah, I don't do
blow any more, man.
What kind of fucking
roadie are you?
You don't do blow, man.
Come on.
You guys always
got the best shit.
It's bad for your, man.
It's ruined all my friends.
Fuck that, man.
- No, you get a habit.
- Hey, man.
Some people can handle
it, some people can't.
Me personally, I handle it.
I've been doing blow for
years, I ain't got no habit.
Come on, now.
Need you to get medicine.
Something.
You know, I don't need.
I just, like it
every now and then.
It wakes me up.
No, I don't want
to do that, man.
You know, like, I got a
lot of work to do here.
I got to help set up the band.
Fuck that.
Forget that roadie shit.
From now on, you're my man.
All right?
You're my man.
Now go get me some blow, OK?
Oh, yes sir.
Can I help you?
Yeah, I need some coke.
Coke?
Certainly.
Would you like a straw with it?
Not that kind of Coke, man.
You know, some coke, some blow.
You know
Isn't that illegal?
Oh, I'm sorry, man.
I need something that
just looks like coke.
Something white?
Right.
White powder.
Yeah.
A little more
Niacin for the rush.
That stuff will really
mess your head up.
Is that the shit?
Here you go, man.
That's a lot for $1500.
Well, I got a real good
connection in Fresno, man.
This is bullshit, man.
This much for $1,500?
From Baltimore to Kokomo
I made my score with blow.
No that's good stuff, man.
It's 100% pure stuff.
Must be stepped on.
It's pure, man.
That's 100% pure.
Well, let's give
it the ultimate test.
Whoo!
Shit!
God damn!
Whoo!
Ow!
God damn!
Pshew!
Man, this is the meanest
shit I ever tooted.
Yeah, it's pure, man.
Here go ahead.
Oh, no thanks, man.
I don't do that shit.
What?
What's wrong with the shit?
What do you mean?
Well, last time
I did some coke,
man, I almost killed the
guy that gave it to me.
Oh, well hey,
don't worry about it.
That leaves more for me.
For operator assistance,
press zero.
Operator, can I help you?
Hello, yeah. collect
call from Kyle.
Lyle?
Kyle.
Hi
this is Tree and you
could leave me a message.
Just wait for the beep.
I'm
sorry, there's no one
there to accept that call.
OK.
Oh, I hope he's all right.
Honey,
I checked him out myself.
I'm talking about Kyle.
Yippee.
Well?
He was here.
Where is he now?
He left.
What do you mean, he left?
Who was he with?
Well, now according
to people here,
he was involved with
some guys in a fight.
I don't know.
He was involved with the
Indian, with the drunk.
They say he was--
Want some coffee?
No, thank you.
Say he was an Indian.
He was riding him, like a horse.
Now, the guy that
Kevin was with--
It's Kyle.
K-Y-L-E.
K-Y-L-E. K-Y-L-E. I've got it.
I've got it.
According to what
people said here,
your son is with an older man.
Probably in his 40s or 50s.
46, 47, 50.
You know, the long
haired, hippy type?
Anyhow, you see what they
did is they had breakfast.
And they had flapjacks and
toast and eggs over easy.
I think it was
three minute eggs.
They didn't
have any breakfast.
Three minute eggs.
They didn't have any breakfast.
Oh, you see?
And then they left together.
Then, they just left.
And then they left.
I don't want to hear this shit.
You're off the case.
Please lady, please.
I'm just a dick
trying to do my job.
Hey!
Uh-oh.
The groupies are in
the middle of the road.
Stop!
Yeah, yeah, we're
with the band.
Jump in.
Hey, you guys with the band?
Yeah, party, man.
Oh, wow party.
Oh, that's great.
Oh, rock.
Hey, there's a party.
Yeah, come on.
Oh, yeah, yeah.
We're with the band.
He's a bass player.
Bye, see ya!
See you down there.
We're going
to have to hitch a ride.
Can't you feel the
fever in the air?
Hear my voice coming out for
you and you can't resist.
When you taste the
passion we both share?
'Cause you know one touch
could make sparks fly,
I've got a secret
that I can't hide.
Hold on baby and you will see.
God, it's so smokey out there.
I can't handle it.
It's all smoke.
Like smoking chimneys
or something.
Ah, sounds like a good
party going on out there.
Oh, that looks so good.
Do you mind if I join you?
Oh no, come on in.
God, that's great.
Pretty relaxing, huh?
Yeah, this is a
honeymoon suite.
I lucked out.
It's killer, man, to sleep in.
Had to move the bed, cause every
time I looked up in the mirror,
I thought someone was
falling on top of me.
Oh, God.
Can I have a hit off that?
Oh.
What's the matter?
I'm just a little bit shy.
Well, just pull up a
dick and have a seat.
Cheap son of a bitch.
Come off the street.
Don't give me no money, snort
up all my drugs and shit.
Now, your ass laying there dead.
Like I give a shit.
You cheap mother fucker.
And to spill my shit all
over them polyester pants.
You didn't even have nothing
in here I could steal.
God damn it, I should have know
your old ass had a week heart.
So tell me, are you married?
Nope, nope, nope.
Not even a little bit.
No.
I'm not married at all.
That guy, that guy Od'ed.
You cocaine stealing bastard.
Look at this, a genuine
cubic zirconium watch.
Why Got all them--
look at it.
Credit cards.
Sammy Smith.
John Johnson.
David Johnson.
Sara Johnson.
You don't look like
no Sara Johnson.
He's got gold.
Come on,
hurry up hurry up.
I need something.
Just give me something,
really quick.
I've got
some pliers, dude.
Pull his teeth out.
Oh, come on baby.
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
Just a minute, man.
Hold it.
This man ain't dead.
He needs some mouth to
mouth resuscitation.
Oh, no, Junior.
You can forget that.
Well?
Do it.
He looks groovy, man.
OK, Kyle.
Hit it.
Yeah, Spider?
This is Lou.
Have you seen that little
no talking faggot, Bobby?
The sucker owes me money, man.
And he sent a little
freaky hippy up here.
Tried to kill me.
(HUMMING ON
BOTTLE)
Yeah, gave me
some bad blow, man.
And then he tried to
kill me, with his guitar.
With a guitar.
Yeah.
So I sent the hippy back to LA.
And I'm on my way back.
Yeah, fuck it.
Bye.
If I could fly like a bird in
the sky, I would find my love.
My love.
If I could sing
like a mockingbird,
I'd sing the words
that mean I love you.
I love you.
Fly away.
'Til we meet the setting sun.
Fly away together.
Free and happy for
heaven and heaven.
OK, we'll drop the trailer here.
You guys stay with
the instruments.
Keep an eye on everything, OK?
I'll go find some place
to park this thing.
Oh, great Ali Pasha, please
free my gypsy lover, Akbar.
I beseech you.
I'll let you ravish my body.
I'll let you pour
honey on my toes
and get in a few
good licks and I--
I hear something.
Oh Jesus, here comes
the geek in the truck, again.
Rae Dawn, I've had it with this.
(TRUCK HORN
BEEPS)
I want this man off the set.
Hi, Daddy.
Hey, honey.
We're filming.
Yeah, I thought that was you.
Hey, guess what?
I'm a roadie, again.
I just got back from Fresno.
That's great.
And I'm over what's her name?
Tree?
Yeah.
Oh, I saw Tree, on TV.
At the White Man Airport.
She's going to be there today.
- You saw Tree?
- Yes.
- Where?
At The White Man Airport.
You might be able to catch her.
You should go there, right now.
Peter, here.
I don't have to work this way.
I won't work this way.
I want you off the
set, right now.
And I want her off
the set, right now.
You get out of here.
Hey, Dawn Dawn, can
I borrow your car?
Isn't
helping the activities.
Making my life a
living hell as if it
wasn't a living hell already.
Hey, I need
a toy for my kid, man.
Oh, how about a a little gun?
Oh, yeah.
Great, man.
We've got a few guns here.
We've got a little
dart gun with handcuffs
and here's a nice little Luger.
Hey, man, you got anything
that looks real, man?
Like an Uzi or something?
I mean, these look
like toys, man.
You want guns?
It's going to be
easier to buy real guns
than it is to find these.
The Law, light
anti-tank weapons.
Great, man.
I'll take them all.
What the hell?
Tower, this is security.
Please come in.
Yes, we have an unauthorized
personnel with weapons
on runway three, please.
Unauthorized--
What
do you mean, unauthorized?
That means that this
mother fucker as got guns
and he's out here
to hurt somebody.
All available units respond
to a crazy motherfucker
with a gun at the White
Man Airport, over.
All available units respond to
a crazy motherfucker with a gun.
Private, don't move.
I got you.
You Yankee dog,
you going to die.
You Yankee pig.
You come to my village,
you steal my wife,
you rape my goat.
Now, you going to make my days.
All right you Yankee pig.
I want you to prepare
to die, right now.
Don't move.
Go for that weapon
and you're dead meat.
I'm going to let you
make a run for it.
Then I'm going to shoot your
balls off, one at a time.
Go ahead, make a run for it.
I'll get you.
Not if I don't get you first.
Oh, C. Thomas,
what are you doing?
Oh, my God.
Relax.
Shut up!
I do this all the time.
Unbelievable.
I can't believe that.
A three pointer backwards, man.
I've never done that before.
That's it.
I'm never flying with you again.
Hey, if we hurry up,
we can make the game.
We are not going home
and watching the game.
I have to find Kyle.
Get in the car.
Now, you have to go.
Just go on.
Get in the car, the place is
surrounded by machine guns.
Machine guns?
They're terrorists
and they have guns.
Oh, God.
Hey you.
Hey.
What's going on, man.
We've got some cars we
got out of here like, now.
Move them.
I'm not the tow
truck driver, man.
Well, you are now.
Come on, move it.
OK, babe.
Don't you fret.
My dad's a stunt man.
I've seen him rig one
of these things before.
We'll be here about one second.
Let me just pop this hood
up we'll be out of here.
Where the hell are we anyway?
Supposed to be
right here, somewhere.
Oh my God.
Over here.
Honey,
check and see if the hood
latch is up there in the front.
What's the problem?
Oh my God.
Oh, I don't believe--
Tree?
I believe it's you.
It's Tree.
Oh my God.
Honey,
I think you better
try and flag somebody down.
Is that my boy?
Honey?
Hey, talk about service, Dad.
This is unbelievable.
A tow truck from nowhere.
Unbelievable.
Great.
Easy easy.
I'll get you an autograph.
Look at you.
Look could you do me a favor.
Oh, man
Could you do a favor?
Could you just get behind
me push me right down there
and I'll give you an
autographed picture?
- Oh, sure, man.
- Thanks a lot.
Thanks a lot.
Come on, come on ride with me.
That's a good idea, honey.
You should probably
ride with him.
OK, honey, I'll ride with him.
OK, you know,
just go really slow.
OK?
Because it's new car, man.
OK.
Unbelievable.
Wait a second.
This isn't going to work, man.
Wait a second, I don't
got any by the brakes.
Wait a minute.
I don't have brakes in here man.
Sorry.
Hey get off your break, man.
This is not
going to work, man.
Roach, man.
He's all grown up.
I thought he was a
little bitty baby, man.
That's C. Thomas Howell.
Slow down!
Slow down.
Honey, that's not our son.
That's C. Thomas
Howell, the actor.
Roach is an actor?
Far out, man.
You don't get it.
I thought he was
a little kid, man.
When I heard you
were coming, man.
I went to the toy store and
bought him some toys, man.
Look at this, I
thought he was a baby.
Oh, fuck!
He's got a gun.
It's all your fault.
See what happens?
What do you mean, my fault?
You left me, man.
Shit!
Your son is missing.
What do you mean missing?
He's-- oh.
Where did he go?
Hey!
Hey, did you see me
back there, buddy?
Huh?
Fabulous.
Oh god.
Oh god, am I glad to see you.
Hey!
Get off me.
All right, you're arrest.
Hey dude.
No, man.
My duty to inform you,
you have the right--
Did you see Soul Man?
I am the black dude in Soul Man.
You have the right
to remain silent.
Aw, fuck.
I'm going to call
my attorney, man.
Patty, Val, Shit.
Why did you come and find me?
Well, you left, man.
You just took off.
What do you mean, find you, man?
I looked all over for you.
Oh, sure you looked.
I looked, man.
No wonder our sons a mess.
But I couldn't find you.
You know why?
Why couldn't you find me?
Because I don't know your
last name, that's why.
Tree.
that's why I couldn-- what
are you going around asking,
hey man have you see Tree?
His legal name is Jimmy
Henry Eric Clapton.
Just a minute.
I named him that.
It's Jimmy-- I named him after
all the guitar players I know.
It's Jimmy Henry
Clapton Berry Chuck--
Chuck?
Yeah, Chuck Richard Page
Hooker Lee John John.
Chuck, C-H-U-C-K.
Here, this is
a picture of him.
Oh, let me see, man.
That's my son.
That's not--
That's Kyle, man.
Yes, his name's Kyle.
That's what he calls himself.
No, that's Kyle.
Honey, show the
man the picture.
Come on, man.
That's Kyle.
This is my son who's missing.
Listen, come on.
What are
you talking about?
Crazies along the way.
Well, I just say that the
judge can take dirty games
that you know that you play.
Whoa, I'm burning for you.
That's what you said, yeah.
If you know those
guys you're crazy,
they haven't eaten for days.
So weird, man, that
that kid's my son.
And he looks just like you.
You think so?
What the fuck, man?
What the fuck?
Hey, hey.
Back off, guys.
I'll handle this, man.
Hey, he didn't mean it.
Bitch, move.
Now, I'm going to
kill this dog face.
Hey, man.
Mellow out, dude.
Get out of my face, asshole.
I'm going to kick
that dork's ass, man.
Hey, you're really tense, man.
You got to change your diet.
I bet you eat meat.
I knew it, man.
Look at your eyes, man.
You need calcium, man.
Listen, I've got some--
Lay off my baby.
Ah!
Mom, are you OK?
OK, listen, man.
Take like two in the morning
and two in the afternoon.
But don't ever take these
on an empty stomach.
OK?
Bunny?
I'm not a hippy anymore.
Because I'm an actress, now.
And Bunny, I'm
living with Tommy,
but, I mean, I don't love him.
Well, I mean, I don't
love him like I love you.
I mean, he's going to
get me a part in a movie.
Bunny, tomorrow I'm going to go
to Italy with him because he's
going to do movies.
Zepherelli promised me a part.
I mean,
he said I was going
to get a part.
Better get that part.
So-- Bunny?
Good night.
I love you.
So what do I do?
You want me to hang out?
No,
sweetie, take it easy.
We got the lawyers
on this thing--
He's in the middle
of this all ready.
You guys are going to have
a serious, serious problem
on your hands.
Well,
sweetie, how are you?
Are you OK?
Emotionally I'm fine.
I can deal with anything.
But this was pretty scary.
Yeah,
well, you're a strong guy.
But not to worry, I
got fabulous news.
You got the Zepherelli film.
It's all set.
You're going to go.
One little hang up, sweetie.
On that other picture--
Wait a second, what
are you saying to me
What did I tell you?
They've decided to
change their minds.
What do you mean, I
didn't get the part?
Keith, the guy said he wrote
the fucking script for me.
What do you mean, I
didn't get that part?
You
just didn't get it.
You've been in
negotiations for two weeks.
I don't want to hear this shit.
Well,
I can't help that.
You gotta--
Keith, I've been banking on
this fucking movie for a month.
Don't
bank on it, sweetie.
Color and go.
- Who's doing the movie?
Who's doing this?
Universal.
It's a Universal-- What
do you mean Universal?
For what?
Who did they go with?
Well, they went with Judd.
They thought Judd was the--
Oh, my God.
He's a nobody.
- He's a nob--
- Did you see "From the Hip?"
- No.
No, i told you--
Judd Nelson.
He's an unknown.
Well,
he's not so unknown he--
No,
I want this, OK?
No, I won't take this.
No, no, no.
I will not take
no for an answer.
No!
Oh, no!
That's it, pal.
No, you don't understand.
I wanted this movie.
Action, Rae Dawn.
Down on your knees Ali Pasha.
Do you think I,
Princess Clitora,
would really let
you lick my toes?
You sartin pig.
I spit on you.
I kill you, prepare to die.
Cut, cut.
Oh Jesus.
Rae Dawn, it's
your father again.
Daddy, what are you doing?
I just came by to
say goodbye, man.
I'm going back on the
road with the guys.
Well, that's great.
Maybe you should get going.
We're filming.
It's drugs.
Oh, sorry.
Well, you better get going.
Before I lose this job.
Tree left me, again.
You're kidding.
Wait, Dad.
Five.
Five,
take 10, take 20.
You're so god damn big.
You know what your
problem is, Daddy?
You're too nice.
You're too 60's.
This is the 80s.
Almost the 90s.
You got to be rotten.
You're not going to let
some wimpy actor with a name
like C. Thomas Howell take
your woman away are you?
That's pathetic.
You got to be tough.
If you want her, Daddy,
you have to go take her.
Go get her.
You've got to nail the bitch.
Get in there with both
feet and jump on it.
Now, let's go,go go.
Oh, Daddy!
Whoa!
Oh, Jesus.
Daddy!
Honey how do
you say make a bag in Spanish?
I can't hear you.
The only thing I can
hear is you getting
ready and getting in a car.
That's all I can hear.
Is you getting the make
up bag, you getting ready,
you getting ready, and
you're getting ready.
Now go.
I don't know bag.
Donde es make
up bag por favor.
Ay!
Que stupida.
Excuse me.
You don't happen to
know who owns the--
Judd? --that's
parked right in the middle
of the street, right there.
Judd?
Judd Nelson.
- Hi.
You're my favorite actor, man.
You're awesome.
Is the car yours?
I fucking love you.
Thank you.
You're out of sight.
Thanks a lot, man.
"From the Hip" is aces, man.
That's my favorite film.
What you did in that courtroom
scene, unbelievable, man.
You know I almost did this gig
you're doing in the Bahamas.
I was this close
from doing it but I'm
doing the Zepherelli thing
in Italy and I got tied up.
I had to turn it down.
Are you an actor?
Am I an actor?
"Soul Man," America's
number one comedy 86'.
Thomas Howell, man.
Sorry, man.
I don't watch, I
don't watch cable.
Well, did you see "The Hitcher?"
I'm sor-- I don't go, I
don't go to the movies much.
If that car is yours--
"The Outsiders" I
was Pony Boy, dude.
I was a Pony Boy, man.
It's probably the beard.
I was much younger, I
was about this tall.
Pony Boy, look check me out.
That's great I'm
sure I know you.
It's a pleasure.
- Honey!
Can you please move the car?
Wait one second.
You have to wait one second.
What are you
yelling about now?
Look who's here.
- Moving it would be great.
- Are you sure?
- If you just please--
- Oh.
Are you sure?
Secret admirer?
Nicolas Cage, oh my god.
I am such a fan of yours.
Thank you.
I love that movie "Moonstruck"
Well, Birdie is my best
work, but thank you anyway.
Red Dawn?
If you could move the car.
Cher was fabulous.
Who did her make up?
I'm not sure, it was really
crowded in the trailer.
Ay!
Charlie Sheen!
La camera.
- We love you.
- I was in "Hitcher."
Excuse me.
Is your name Tree?
Could be the beard,
I didn't have a beard
when I was doing it then.
This is amazing.
I can't believe this.
I just saw this
video at my managers
called "Garage Sale Bimbo's."
That was you, right?
You saw "Garage Sale Bimbo's?"
We have a part for you.
And you never
saw "The Hitcher?"
We have been looking for you.
My manager should
have called by now.
We have a movie for you.
A role opposite me, four
months in the Bahamas.
We think you'd be perfect.
Big bucks.
You saw, you saw "The
Garage Sale Bimbo's"
and you never saw "Red Dawn?"
You can bring any
makeup artist you want
and we're leaving in a week.
- Wait a second.
Wait a second.
I'm talking to you.
"Grandview, U.S.A."
We would love you.
We could bring you down early.
Get a little bit of a tan.
I mean rock my nation, baby.
You'd be per--
Hey, you're on my
dick nerve, boy.
Just--
A star.
I knew I'd be a star one day.
Mom, Dad's hurt.
He's in the hospital.
Dr. Stoner,
report to the administration.
Dr. Stoner.
Dr. Stoner, report
to one of our--
Where is he?
He dead.
He what?
Girl, he died a half hour ago.
Nice man, too.
Oh, oh no.
Bunny.
why did you have to die?
Wait.
I hear his spirit.
Bunny, where are you?
Talk to me.
Hey, hey!
You're alive.
Hey, they serve
Mexican food here, man.
Does he have any insurance?
Him?
Whoa, I can't
believe you're my dad.
You going to come live with us?
I don't know.
Hey.
What?
Are we can be living
together again, man?
Can I be the
singer in your band?
Yeah.
No problem, man.
Yeah, but with the mic on?
With the mic on, man.
Hey listen, you know, your
voice is really in style now.
Now?
OK.
All right!
Hey, hey Kyle.
Hey.
Come on, let's have a race.
OK.
What's the damage?
Watch out, Dad.
Whoa!
That was far out, man.
Yes, it's me and I'm back again.
Yes, I'm back to
where it all began.
Yeah, I'm back to
where I belong.
Having a ball while
I sing this song.
I'm singing the blues
in my orthopedic shoes.
Yes, it's me and I'm back again.
Yeah, I'm back to
where it all began.
Been living high
and feeling good.
I've been treated like
a good girl should.
I can't go back to
that same old stuff.
I need it smooth.
I can't take it rough.
Yes, it's me and I'm back again.
You treat me right,
I'll stay all night.
If you want the best, you've
got to pass that test.
You want it nice, you've
got to pay the price.
I'll be your toy
but I won't be your
Boy.
Yes, it's me and I'm back again.
Yes, I'm back to
where it all began.
I've been away
for too damn long.
It's been years since
I sang this song.
I've been down,
right to the ground.
Now, I'm me and I'm black again.
I'll be your lover but
I won't be your wife.
I could live with you
but I need my own life.
I can be true blue
but I need someone
who will love me and hug
me and talk nice not to me.
Yes, I'm back and
I'm better than ever.
And you find out
whenever we get together.
This is me and I'm back again.
You treat me right and
I'll stay all night.
You want the best, you
have to pass that test.
You want it nice, you've
got to pay the price.
I'll be your toy but
I won't be your boy.
Yes, it's me and I'm back again.
In the land of sky blue
waters, I will fill
my A-frame cabin with a garden.
Living with so fear and Mama
making positive vibrations.
Raise a golden shower on the
never ending hippie nation.
Well I tried and I
tried and I tried.
I tried so hard.
I wander this land with
my home in my hands
seeking hippie mountain.
I share hippie food with
my wandering friends.
We could groove forever.
But hippie nation slipped away.
Left me with a headache
on a cold winter morning.
I got a job, got new clothes.
Put my hippy dreams in the dark.
But now hippie children,
they're everywhere.
Hippie children
love is everywhere.
Hippy children come on.
Hippy children all
over this world
there are young boys and girls
taking care of their mothers.
From every junior high, all the
holes in the sky young girls
are thinking.
And out of this foolish
vacation from learning
come new hippy nations.
Peace and love little
girls talk about
ecology and working together.
Inner city college kids
thinking about someone
besides themselves.
But now hippy children,
they're everywhere.
Hippy children love everywhere.
Hippy children come
on, come on, come on.
Hippy children come on yeah.
Now is the time
for all the hippies
to come to the
aid of the planet.
And the only pragmatic
solutions are dreams about love.
Hippy children
they're everywhere.
Please rate this subtitle at www.osdb.link/an74p
Help other users to choose the best subtitles