Good morning, Mr. Sullivan.
I have a meeting in a few minutes
with some very jittery
stockholders, mattson.
I hope you have good news for me.
Yes, sir. I do, sir.
Every supermarket tabloid in the country
is running headlines about Andy barclay
and his killer good guy doll.
What about his mother and the police
that were on the case?
The police were smart.
They denied everything,
which is fine because
now they can't hurt us.
But the mother's a different matter.
She backed up her boy's story in court,
so now she's under
psychiatric observation.
Jesus. Where's the boy now?
Midtown children's crisis center.
Foster custody is pending.
My stomach hurts, mattson.
Is this what you call good news?
Yes...
No. I'm getting to that, sir.
Our biggest problem
has been the rumors. A lot...
Good morning, Mr. Sullivan.
A lot of people are saying that
some joker here at the company
must have tampered with the doll's
voice cassette, you know?
"Hi. I'm Chucky.
I'm the lakeshore strangler.
"And now I'm gonna kill you."
Something like...
Well, something like that.
But the good news, Mr. Sullivan,
is that now we've got the doll.
We've rebuilt it from head to toe.
A lot of it was burned to a crisp,
but everything checks out,
the voice cassettes,
the servomechanisms.
We've found absolutely nothing.
This is a quality control report.
I'm sure it will make
the stockholders very happy.
I want to see the doll for myself.
Absolutely.
Gentlemen, Mr. Sullivan's here. We ready?
Well, give us a minute. We're not used to
making them manually.
- What's wrong?
- I don't know, it's stuck.
Just"
they'll have this worked out.
0h, Jesus!
Andy, you still
dreaming about Chucky?
Sometimes.
- You want to talk about it?
- No.
Come on, Andy. Remember what I told you?
Talking helps make
- the nightmares go away.
- Nightmares go away.
Well, Chucky was
trying to take over my soul.
Why?
He was this bad man who
got inside my good guy doll,
so he wouldn't have to go to hell.
But then he wanted to get inside me.
Why, Andy?
'Cause if he stayed
inside the doll too long,
he'd be trapped in there.
He needed me 'cause I was the first person
he told his secret to.
What secret?
That his real name was Charles Lee ray.
Boy, that's a scary dream.
It was.
You know, dreams can't hurt you.
Dreams aren't real.
- Right?
- Right.
Here.
In there.
Let's hurry up.
Mattson, I don't care what it takes.
Put a lid on this.
Yes, sir. That's not a problem.
I'll take care of this.
Listen to me.
You smother this or you're out of here
in 24 hours. You got that?
Yes, sir.
Now, if you will excuse me,
I've got a meeting I've got to get to.
As far as the stockholders
and I are concerned,
this matter is finished.
Yes, sir.
Uh, what do you want me to do
with the doll?
Stick it up your ass.
Naturally, he was badly
traumatized by the murders,
but they bounce back
pretty fast at that age.
Poor kid.
What Andy needs now is a normal
family environment, a fresh start
and a chance to forget the past.
Since you two have done so well
with so many kids,
we were hoping you might foster him
until his mother recovers.
- There's always room for one more.
- Mm.
What's that supposed to mean?
Uh, well...
He seems normal enough,
but how has all this affected him?
Well, in order to come to terms with
something he couldn't possibly understand,
he turned it all into
a kind of fairy tale.
He insisted his do" was responsible.
He said it was possessed
by the soul of Charles Lee ray.
Who?
The lakeshore strangler.
He murdered a dozen people
in this series of ritual voodoo killings.
Are we even qualified
to take care of a boy like this?
Well, I understand
your concern, Mr. Simpson,
but I'm sure you can see that
this is just a child's way
of coping with a difficult situation.
Andy's fine now.
He just wants to get on with his life.
So, Andy, what do you like to eat?
All kinds of things.
Well, what's your very favorite food
in the whole wide world?
Chocolate.
Besides chocolate.
Mm. My mom used to fix
me eggs for breakfast. I like eggs.
You got it. We should stop at the store.
- Uh, the one down here?
- Yeah, the organic...
You're in luck, Andy.
Joanne's a terrific cook.
You like Sushi? You know what I mean by...
Phil, look out!
Jesus Christ!
Look out for the car.
Hey, wait up.
Make yourself comfortable, Andy.
Thanks.
Well, I have to get
back to the office this afternoon.
I thought that
you'd done everything.
Ah-ah-ah...
First rule. Don't touch the old stuff.
Sorry.
Well, that's okay. No foul.
It's just that we collect this junk,
and a lot of it's kind of fragile.
- You like it?
- Uh-huh.
It's been in my family
for three generations.
My grandmother gave it to my mother,
and my mother gave it to me.
And who are you gonna give it to?
Why don't you take this upstairs
and explore?
I'll be up there in a minute.
Okay.
What do you think?
0h, I'll get used to him.
Jesus. Did you ever hear of knocking?
Andy, did you find...
What? Are you crazy? Give them to me.
Come on, joanne.
Phil will shoot you
if he catches you again.
Andy, this is Kyle.
She's staying with us, too.
Charmed.
Kyle, what is this?
You've been here three weeks.
Why haven't you unpacked?
What for?
I've never spent more
than a month in any home.
With that attitude, I can see why.
Come on. Put these things away,
and then would you do me a favor
and help me get dinner started?
Can't. Got to work tonight.
Kyle, that's the third night in a row.
I'd really like it if you'd spend
a little time with the family.
I need the money.
I'm gonna be on my own next year.
Yes, well, until then,
you're with us, okay?
- Come along, Andy.
- Bye.
I think you'll be very happy here.
This is your room, right here.
I made those curtains just for you.
I bet blue is your favorite color.
Take a look around. I'll start to unpack.
Wow!
I thought you might like those. Um...
There's more in the closet.
Before dinner,
we'll go explore the backyard.
And, later, I'll read you some stories.
Would you like that?
There are lots of kids your age
in the neighborhood, Andy.
I'm sure you're gonna make
all sorts of new friends.
Hey, hey, hey!
Andy, rule number two,
no running in the house.
It's only a doll.
Andy, are you listening to me?
0h, Andy, I'm so sorry.
I didn't realize that was in there.
We've had so many kids here,
it's hard to keep track of everything.
I'll get rid of it.
Hi, I'm Tommy.
And I'm your friend till the end.
Why don't we get settled in,
and then we'll have some dinner, okay?
Shit.
Hello, Gabriella. Guess who?
That's right.
The vodka? Oh, the vodka.
Of course I remembered
the vodka.
Two-week anniversary.
You think I'd forget the vodka?
I know what that does to you.
Okay, well, wait for me.
On my way. Yeah.
Shit.
I want to play red light.
No, Sammy, I don't want to
play red light now.
I want you to go back to bed right now.
But I'm scared.
There's nothing to be scared of.
It's just a storm.
Grace poole.
Yes, I'm trying to
reach Andy barclay.
Andy no longer lives here. Who is this?
This is his uncle Charles.
Sorry, cash only.
But that's a gold card.
That's just as good as cash.
Not here, it ain't.
We don't accept credit cards.
I don't carry cash, okay?
Oh...
Don't move!
Jesus!
God. Okay. Okay, what do you want?
- No questions. Just drive.
- Okay, okay.
Keep going.
Now, park this piece of shit.
Put your arms behind the seat.
- What?
- Do it!
Okay. Take it easy. Take it easy.
Please, don't, don't shoot.
Look, I... I don't carry cash.
I got... I got a gold card.
I'll give you anything you want.
Tell me what you want.
Freeze, asshole.
Take my... take the car.
And you can drop me off,
but just, please, leave me alone.
Please.
Bang. You're dead.
No! No! No!
"The woodcutter argued
for a long time with his wife,
but she was such a horrid,
frightening woman when she was angry,
that in the end he agreed to her plan.
In the morning,
their stepmother called them.
'I think it would be nice if we all went
into the forest today, ' she said.
Hansel and gretel did not reply,
but followed their parents
into the dark forest."
Where they all lived happily ever after.
- No, they don't.
- Well, they do for now.
We'll finish it tomorrow night, okay?
Don't go.
What's the matter?
I miss my mother.
Oh, honey, I know you do.
Will I ever see her again?
Of course you will. I promise.
Don't worry. I'll stay with you
as long as you want.
My mother used to sing to me.
Will you sing to me?
Shit.
Hi. I'm Tommy.
Shut up, you idiot.
I like to be hugged.
- I like to be hugged.
- Hug this.
I like to be hugged.
I like to be hugged. I like...
- What was that?
- Nothing. Now go to sleep.
Nobody's going to hurt you.
Eat dirt, Tommy.
Do either of you have anything to
say about this?
I think we should talk to a lawyer first.
Kyle, that's not funny.
That statue was very important to me.
I think one of you owes joanne an apology.
I'm innocent.
Andy?
I didn't do it.
All right. You leave me no choice.
Until somebody fesses up,
you're both grounded.
But I have a date tonight.
Sorry.
This is exactly how I wanted
to spend my day off. Thanks a lot.
But I didn't break the statue. Really.
Yeah. Maybe it just fell, huh?
Hey. You want to hear me
say your name backwards?
Kyle.
Hold this.
Jesus. Give me that.
What the hell do you think you're doing?
I wanted to taste it.
Get real. It tastes like shit, okay?
These things are very bad for you.
Then why do you do it?
Because grown-ups are allowed to
do things that are bad for them.
You're not a grown-up.
You're beginning to
get on my nerves, Andy.
Now, why don't you
give me a hand over here?
Mr. Simpson is kind of grouchy, isn't he?
He's not so bad.
I've had fosters that would shoot you
for staring at them cross-eyed.
Really?
Sure.
They figure you're not theirs.
You're just passing through.
The minute you screw up...
Argh! They let you have it.
You know, I got to tell you,
I'm not happy with this whole thing.
Having second thoughts?
Well, you have to admit,
he's a very troubled little boy,
and he obviously has not come to terms
with this whole doll thing.
Look, all I'm saying is that he may need
more attention than we can give him.
Phil, Andy's been through hell.
You have to give him some time.
He'll settle down.
Besides, I like him.
I hate you.
Hi. I'm... Tommy,
and I'm your friend to the end.
Hidey-ho.
Kyle, do you miss your mom and dad?
You can't miss someone you never knew.
Where are they?
I have no idea.
My dad left before I was born.
My mom put me up for adoption
when I was three.
Do you remember her?
I made it a point to forget.
It's easier that way.
Hey. Break time.
Move over.
Want a push?
No, thank you.
Come on. It's fun.
Come on, Andy, please,
I just want to sit here, okay?
Too late. There you go.
Andy, come on. Give me a break. Stop it.
No.
Andy, I'll kill you.
Come on. Let me off!
Andy.
I'll get you.
- Come on, Andy, cut it out.
- Dinner!
- Come and get it.
- Whoa.
Aah!
Mayhem. Come on. I'll race you.
No fair. You got a head start.
Excuses, excuses. Don't forget your doll.
For Kyle. Think she'll like it?
What do I know
about teenage girls?
More than you did three weeks ago.
I'm not so sure.
I was thinking we should
get something for Andy.
Make him feel more settled. Any ideas?
Yeah. How about a valium?
Surprise.
Did you miss me, Andy? I sure missed you.
I told you.
We were gonna be friends to the end.
And now it's time to play.
I got a new game, sport.
It's called hide the soul.
And guess what? You're it.
Give me the power, I beg...
This isn't over, you little shit.
I'm not gonna spend the rest of my life
as a plastic freak.
Next time you're alone, you're mine.
Oh, my god.
It's Chucky. Look out!
- Shut up. You'll wake Phil and joanne.
- Kill him! Kill him!
Andy, stop it, will you?
What the hell is this, now?
It's Chucky. I told you he'd find me.
He tried to take over my soul.
Andy, calm down.
You didn't have to wait up.
Yeah? You know, Kyle, I don't believe you.
You actually tied this child up,
so he wouldn't tell on you.
- Is that it?
- Oh, come on, Phil.
- Chucky did it!
- That's enough now.
Chucky? I... I've had it.
But you've got to kill him.
Andy!
Please, listen to me. I'm not lying.
If you don't kill him, he'll come get me.
Andy, calm down.
I'm going to get rid of it.
There, see? He's gone.
He can't bother you anymore.
I'm turning human again?
If I don't get out
of this body soon, I'm screwed.
Come on, Andy. We're late.
Andy. Don't forget your lunch.
Egg salad.
Mmm, yum!
Now, whatever you do,
don't act nervous, okay?
They'll smell a new kid a mile off.
Just act like you belong.
What are you looking for?
Nothing.
Is it Chucky coming to get you?
Andy, how did you manage
to tie yourself up like that last night?
I already told you.
Get real.
You're just like everybody else.
You don't believe me either.
- Kyle.
- Hey, Autumn.
Hi.
Why'd you have to leave so early
last night? You missed all the fun.
Story of my life.
Come on now.
Where is it?
Ah-ha!
"Pinocchio jumped forjoy, shouting,
'I'm alive! I'm alive!'
then the talking cricket said..."
What'd he say?
"'If you're very, very good,
and promise to tell no lies,
then you will become a real, live boy.'
boys who are bent on
following their caprices
and will have their own way,
sooner or later repent."
Get lost, microchip.
Am I boring you, Andy?
No, miss...
Kettlewell.
I have precious little Patience
for disruptive students.
But he just whacked...
Especially new students,
whose utmost concern
should be getting on my good side.
I want those desks spick
and span before anyone leaves.
Andy! You think this is funny?
I didn't do that.
Go ahead, kids. Don't forget
the spelling test tomorrow.
Not you. Come over here.
Sit down and get comfy.
You're going to be here for a while.
But I didn't do it, I swear.
No? Then who did?
Don't even think about it.
No toys. Head down.
Head down.
Peekaboo!
Please, let me out of here, Andy.
It's dark in here.
I promise I won't kill anyone else. Okay?
Now, open the goddamn door!
Let me out, you little dick!
Let me the fuck out!
Andy, I told you to stay in your seat.
Come out of there.
Open this door right now.
Andy, come out this very second.
Andy! Andy!
Andy?
Andy, this isn't funny.
You've been very naughty, miss kettlewell.
Andy, what's this all about?
Chucky followed me to school.
He tried to get me again, so I ran home.
Do you know what's he talking about?
His teacher called,
said she was keeping him
after school for detention,
said he wrote an obscenity on his paper.
Chucky did it.
All right, Andy. Come on.
This is going to stop,
'cause I will not allow this
foolishness in my house.
Do you understand? Open the door.
- Oh, Phil.
- Joanne, please.
Open the door.
Open it.
Open it!
Now, I want you to look down there
and tell me what you see.
It's Chucky, but...
His name is Tommy,
and he's been there
since last night, hasn't he?
Hasn't he?
For crying out loud, joanne,
the child needs professional help.
Oh, stop pretending
you're worried about Andy.
You never wanted him
here in the first place.
That's not true.
So, what are you
suggesting we do? Send him back?
You don't have to make
it sound so horrible.
Do you have any idea
how traumatic that would be?
Traum... for whom, joanne,
for him or for you?
Look, if that kid stays here,
he's gonna tear this family apart.
Family? Is this what you calla family?
Families don't just
give up on their children.
Joanne, he's not our child.
It's not the end of the world.
But they're gonna send me away.
You'll be okay.
Where will I go?
Andy.
I've lived with dozens
of different families,
and they always seem to send me away
just when I'm getting comfortable,
- but you know what?
- What?
Every time it happens,
it just makes me stronger,
because it reminds me that the only one
I can count on is myself.
Okay? And you have to learn that now.
I know it sounds tough,
but you'll deal with it.
It doesn't matter.
Wherever I go, Chucky will find me.
Advances over the declines
by a seven to six margin.
Decent today, with the...
What's wrong?
I thought I heard something downstairs.
It's one of the children.
That's what I'm afraid of.
Why fight it, Andy?
We're gonna be very close.
In fact, we're gonna be
fucking inseparable.
What the hell's going on down...
Andy...
Put down the knife.
But I need it for...
Just put the knife down,
and we'll talk about it.
Everything is gonna be just fine.
How's it hanging, Phil?
No. Oh, god. Phil. Phil.
I'll call an ambulance.
Phil. Phil.
Oh, god! No!
Oh, god! Oh!
Get away from me!
Oh, god!
No, we didn't
hear anything. Nothing.
I should have listened to him.
He'd have been here now if only
I'd listened to him.
It's not your fault.
I'll take care of this.
Andy, you'll be fine now.
You'll come stay at
the center with us for a few days
until we can find you a new family.
We've placed Kyle with
a number of families.
Things always seem to work out okay.
Don't they?
Yeah.
There's your stuff.
Come on, Andy. Let's go.
He's still in the cellar, Kyle.
Don't let him get you, too.
Andy?
We'll be out of your way
in just a minute here.
Did anyone, besides the boy,
witness the accident?
- Okay.
Let's go.
Joanne!
Joanne?
Bitch. You hurt me.
How much further till we get to the kid?
A ways.
Step on it.
What's the rush?
If I don't get out of this body soon,
I'll be trapped in here!
What are you looking at?
Floor it.
Get real. This is a station wagon.
Shit!
Pull over.
Behave yourself.
I'll kill you if I have to.
Okay, honey, let's see your license.
You were clocking 60 in a 45.
What's your hurry?
I have a date.
You're gonna have
to do better than that.
That's one of those good guys, isn't it?
Yes, it is.
I love these things.
What's your name, buddy?
Chucky.
That's incredible.
I'll say.
What the hell's that?
You've seen dolls that pee?
This one bleeds.
Okay, look,
just slow it down, huh?
And buckle up for safety.
Now, get going.
You okay, honey?
Mmm-hmm.
Don't let the bedbugs bite.
Come on. Step on it.
Fine. We'll just get pulled over again.
Just shut up and drive
before I kick your fucking teeth in.
You goddamn women drivers!
Fuck.
Fucking bastard.
Shit. Andy.
Playtime's over.
Andy, what are you doing?
Come on. We've got to get
out of the building.
Kyle, what's going on here?
You did this, didn't you?
He did it.
Get into my office.
Is this your idea of a joke?
Oh, just give me that.
Amazing, isn't it?
Come on!
Okay, sport, we're gonna have
a little game of Chucky says.
Chucky says, "move your ass."
Snap out of it!
You act like you never seen
a dead body before!
Andy, come on! Open it.
Andy! Open the door!
Come on! Everybody out!
Inside. Hurry.
Stop!
Come on.
Hey, lady, slow down, will you?
J“ passin' by j"
Say your prayers, Andy.
God damn it!
J“ I first saw you I
Pull over!
- What?
- Pull over!
Pull over!
Hey! Just what in the hell
do you think you're doing?
Let me go. Let me go.
What the fuck's wrong with you?
Let go!
Crazy bitch!
We're home.
Close your eyes and count to seven.
When you wake, you'll be in heaven.
This is it, world.
From now on,
no more Mr. Good guy.
Give me the power, I beg of you.
No!
You little shit!
Do you know what you've done?
It's too late! I've spent too much
time in this body.
I'm fucking trapped in here!
What the hell?
Andy, run.
- Andy.
- Kyle!
Are you okay? Come on.
Shit!
Andy! Hurry up!
Let's go. I'll go first.
Stay right behind me.
Come on.
Andy, step on it.
Reach! Give me your hand!
Andy!
Stop yourself. Grab the side.
Andy! Hurry up! He's right behind you.
Little bastard!
Don't look back. Come on. Hurry!
- You can't get away from me!
- Give me your hand!
Reach!
I'm gonna kill you, Andy!
Come on. Go! Go! Go! Run down there.
I'm gonna get you fuckers!
God!
Oh, god!
Come on. Do it!
Come on. Give me your hand.
Don't be afraid. Come on.
Closer. Closer so you can grab my hand.
Andy. Now!
Can't open it.
How will we get out?
We'll have to find another way.
Give me your hand.
I hate kids.
Terrific.
Duck!
Do it!
Andy, please.
I was only playing.
No, please! Oh, please!
God, it hurts!
No! No! God! No! No! No!
Holy shit.
We did it.
Let's get out of here.
- Let's see. Are you okay?
- Yeah.
What's this?
Thanks for coming after me.
Yeah, well, you owe me one, squirt.
Kyle!
I've got you now, Andy,
and you know what I'm gonna do to you?
I'm gonna cut off your legs, too.
Huh?
Kyle! Kyle!
Kyle! Kyle! Kyle, wake up!
Kyle!
Come on. Come on.
Ugh! God. What did you do to him?
All right, Andy.
Kyle! Kyle!
Eat this, you son of a bitch.
Come on.
Where are we going?
Home.
Where's home?
Andy, I have no idea.