This is Andy barclay.
Eight years ago,
he touched off the scandal
that nearly crippled this company,
claiming that his good guy doll, Chucky,
was possessed by Charles Lee ray,
the notorious lakeshore strangler.
Now I ask you, ladies and gentlemen,
after all the lawsuits
and negative publicity,
when the company is finally
getting back on its feet again,
where is the wisdom in putting
the good guy back on the market?
Mr. Sullivan, before any of this happened,
the good guy outsold
all our other toys two-to-one.
Even now, interest in
the marketplace is at its peak.
The factory is up and running again.
We should be in stores by next week.
We cannot let the fantasies
of one disturbed boy
influence company policy.
Well, what if the doll somehow affects
another child in a negative way?
You could have a public relations
nightmare on your hands.
You know, one of the hardest
things about this business
is that it is a business.
It doesn't matter what we're selling.
Whether it's cars, nuclear weapons,
or, yes, even toys.
The bottom line is the bottom line.
And what are children, after all,
but consumer trainees?
Andy barclay is ancient history.
No one remembers him. Nobody cares.
I have made up my mind.
We're moving ahead.
Thank you.
- Okay.
- All right.
Mr. Sullivan.
If there's nothing I can say
to convince you,
then I must go on record with my position.
I'm completely against this.
Your position is crystal clear, miles,
and you can be sure I won't forget.
Just a minute, folks! Please.
Mr. Sullivan, we have
a little surprise for you.
The guys at the factory sent this over.
And we all wanted you to have it.
It's the first one off the assembly line.
The good guy of the '903!
Well, if there's nothing else,
I'm gonna get going.
Fine.
It's just,
my wife's expecting me.
It's our anniversary.
Fine, petzold.
Well, I guess I could review
the larrabee report after dinner.
Good night, Mr. Sullivan.
Good night.
Well, despite a downdraft
in the bond market,
stocks were able to
post a rally on Friday,
thanks to a couple of different factors.
Not only did the stronger-than-expected
employment report
allay some recession fears,
but also there was
a technical rebound in stock,
short covering, program buying,
and the resurgence in the deal stocks
help set the tone for rally on the street.
Here's a look at the numbers now.
For Friday, the dow industrial's
up sixteen and two-thirds.
Of the highs of the day,
the transportation average up
a little better than three.
Utilities bouncing up a point to pass
at 12, at 22, 61, 78.
S&p 500 cash are better than two
with the margin peaking up
almost two and a half
with the premier ending at 1.59.
New York stock exchange index up 1.23,
volume backing off a bit
at 164 million shares.
Advances beat declines just about
nine-to-five on the New York
stock exchange.
The up volume 103 million shares,
the down volume 39...
In just a moment's time...
Well, shit.
And bonds headed south
on the stronger-than-expected
economic data,
which served to bolster the us dollar.
The dollar index up a quarter point.
Hi, my name is Larry.
Hi, my name is pauly.
Hey, wanna play?
I like to be hugged.
Hi, my name is Larry.
Hi, my name is pauly.
Hey, wanna play?
I like to be hugged.
Hi, my name is Larry.
Hi, my name is pauly.
Hey, wanna play?
I like to be...
Don't fuck with the Chuck!
Oh, my god.
Bull's-eye!
Just like the good old days.
Nothing like a strangulation
to get the circulation going.
You're my only ticket out of here, Andy.
I got to get out of this goddamn body.
Where are you, you little shit?
Inward, hut!
Come on.
Come on, yeah! You can do it!
Come on. You can do it, Jackson, hurry up.
Yeah! Move. Yes!
Come on. Let's go. Yeah! Come on.
Get moving! Go to the end of the line!
Isee that
for the past eight years
you've been in one
foster home after another.
Mind if I ask why?
They took me away from my mother.
She's, uh... under special care.
I know that.
I meant how come you never
got settled anywhere?
Adjustment problems.
I can read, barclay.
I'm asking you.
I never felt comfortable
with those people.
They weren't family, they were strangers.
All right, listen up, barclay.
I'm willing to cut you some slack
because you've had it so rough,
but you're a troublemaker.
And I got a real problem
with troublemakers.
They don't fit into the system.
So here's my advice.
Grow up, you're not a kid anymore.
It's time to forget
these fantasies of killer dolls.
Yes, sir.
"When I was a child, I thought as a child.
But when I became a man,
I put away childish things."
First corinthians.
Look alive, barclay, on your feet!
At Kent, we take bedwetters
and turn them into men.
Oh, yes. Yes.
Oh, yes!
We're seeing some skin now, aren't we?
Presto! You're bald.
Always feels a little weird at first.
Next.
Kiss it goodbye.
You know, the romans
invented the military cut.
You know why?
Why?
To keep their hair short
so their enemies couldn't
grab a hold of it in battle
and slit their throat.
Now, hold still.
Oh, shit.
We 're back,
and we 're better than ever.
No one will play with me.
Uh-oh. There's a friend in need.
Hey, cheer up!
Who are you?
I'm a good guy.
Good guy! Good guy!
I've just come from
the good guy clubhouse,
and I'll be your friend till the end.
You will?
Wow!
Sure I will.
Hidey-ho!
So, all aboard for high-flying fun
with me, your friend till the end,
the good guy doll from play pals.
Come on, man!
Are you okay?
The bastards! Fucking bastards!
What happened?
Shelton, that's what happened.
Shelton and his goddamn lackeys.
Thank you. I'm fine.
I'm Andy.
You must be new.
Otherwise you'd know they don't
tolerate any form of individuality here.
Certainly nothing so personal
as the first name.
Yeah, right, I forgot. Barclay.
Whitehurst.
Harold Aubrey, for the record.
So, who's this Shelton?
Cadet lieutenant colonel Brett c. Shelton.
He's god around here.
Don't expect any mercy from him.
Welcome to hell, barclay.
All present and accounted for, sir.
Thank you, major Ellis.
You're the new boy, huh?
Yeah.
How you doing?
Pretty good.
Who said you could look at me?
Do you know who I am?
Shehon?
That's lieutenant colonel
Shelton to you, asshole!
Lieutenant colonel Shelton.
No. Lieutenant colonel Shelton,
sir.
Lieutenant colonel Shelton, sir.
What's your name, dipweed?
Barclay.
Sir.
-Loudel - sir!
Loudel - Sir!
That's much better, new boy.
That's much better.
Shit, whitehurst.
You are without a doubt
the most pathetic thing I have ever seen!
Wouldn't you agree?
I asked you a question, nimrod!
No, sir! I don't agree, sir!
Are you contradicting me,
you sorry-ass sack of shit?
You asshole.
What did you say?
I
You think you're pretty funny,
don't you, de silva?
Yes, I do, sir.
Why don't you drop
and give me 25 right now?
25 what, sir?
25 push-ups, de silva.
One, sir. Two, sir...
Now, you women might think that
because you're so much more delicate,
you deserve some
sort of special treatment...
Nine, sir...
And once a month we're just going to
get on out of your way.
12, sir. 13, sir...
- Well, you can forget it.
- 14, sir...
The same rules apply for everybody.
18, sir. 19, sir...
Only the fittest survive.
21, sir. 22, sir. 23, sir...
One-handed.
24, sir.
25, sir.
Recover.
How you doing, Tyler?
Sorry. Nothing from your dad today.
Maybe tomorrow.
Listen, he's busy flying jets,
defending the country.
He'll write to you
when he gets the chance.
I know.
I got a job for you.
Would you give this to
the new kid for me? Barclay.
Yes, sir.
Attaboy.
Whoa.
Watch it, kid! Anyway,
how could you be so stupid?
Hey, look out!
A good guy.
Who the fuck are you?
I thought you guys
only said three sentences.
I'm new and improved.
I never saw a doll like you before.
All right, kid, fun's over.
Where the hell's Andy?
Andy?
Can't you read?
He was supposed to get this package.
Tampering with the mail
is a federal offense.
Sorry. Is he your best friend?
He's more than that.
He's my new lease on life.
Wait a minute.
I got a new body,
and I ain't told anyone
about my little secret yet.
So, uh, what's your name, kid?
Tyler. What's yours?
Chucky. But, uh,
my real name is Charles Lee ray.
Whitehurst, what am I doing wrong?
Is there anything you can't do?
Yeah. I can't seem
to get thrown out of this place.
Barclay, meet de silva.
So, want to show me?
- Yeah, sure.
- Okay.
No. Put the elbow... yeah, like that.
And like this.
No. Keep both eyes open.
Keep your sights on the target.
Now hold your breath.
Squeeze the trigger, don't pull it.
You're not concentrating.
You know, it was really great what you did
for us back there at formation.
Well, Shelton's a major dick.
Tell me about it.
Couldn't we just
play hide-and-seek?
Ah! Hold still.
What do you call this game anyway?
Hide the soul. Trust me,
you're gonna love it.
Whatever you say, Charles.
Give me the power, I beg of you!
So we divide the troops in half,
- that'll be about 70 on each team.
- Shit!
Charles, stop swearing.
Per soldier, and we're gonna need
- the Springfield 0-3s...
- Yes, sir.
Marked for both the red team
and the blue team.
What are you doing, Tyler?
We're playing hide the soul.
I'll catch up with you.
I'll start loading the paint pellets.
We don't play with dolls,
do we now, Tyler?
Dolls are for girls.
But Charles is my new best friend.
Tyler, you know better than to talk back
to a superior officer.
Yes, sir.
Clean that up.
I'll take care of this.
I'll be back!
Left! Left! Left, right, left!
Left! Left!
Get that weapon up, barclay!
Platoon, halt!
Left face!
New boy, fall out!
Fall out!
Order, hut!
Port, arms!
Right shoulder, arms!
Left shoulder, arms!
Port, arms!
Right shoulder, arms!
Barclay!
It's not a Baton, barclay.
You look like a goddamn
majorette over here.
I'm not used to guns, sir.
Does this look like a gun to you, barclay?
It's a rifle!
- Major Ellis?
- Sir!
Would you please show the new boy
the difference?
This is my rifle, this is my gun.
This is for shooting, and this is for fun.
A soldier's rifle is his best friend.
Remember that.
Stop!
Shit!
Help! Please, mister!
Please, somebody!
Jesus!
I'm stuck! Mister!
I'm in here!
Hold on. I'm coming!
Where are you?
I'm coming.
Yell or something! Make a noise!
Where are you?
What the...
Oh, my god.
No! Stop!
Stop!
Fall out.
You get back there.
Better finish unpacking, barclay.
Shelton's notorious
for surprise inspections.
What are you doing?
What does it look like?
I'm polishing Shelton's shoes.
He makes you Polish his shoes?
No, I offered out of
the kindness of my heart.
Whitehurst, did you see Cochrane
with that doll today?
No. What doll?
He was carrying a good guy doll,
just before the accident
with the garbage truck.
Good guys, I remember those.
Yeah, me, too.
Uh, lights out in a few minutes.
I'm going to go get washed up.
Barclay, I almost forgot.
Sergeant Clark wanted to know
if you got that package.
What package?
He said you got a package in the mail.
That little kid, Tyler,
was supposed to bring it to you.
- Didn't you get it?
- No.
Who would've sent me a package?
Hey, long time no see, pal.
No, you're dead. We killed you!
You know what they say,
you just can't keep a good guy down.
Andy, how you've grown.
You're not gonna kill me. You need me.
You need to transfer your soul
into my body.
Wrong again, wimp.
I got some fresh meat lined up
and I'm not gonna let you spoil it,
not this time.
Tyler.
Yeah, just think. Chucky's gonna be a bro.
I'm not gonna let you get away with this.
I'm not gonna let you near that kid.
What's the matter, barclay, huh?
You homesick?
You miss your mommy?
What the fuck is this?
I'm sorry about your shoe, all right.
I'll Polish it.
Just give me back the doll.
No, no, you listen to me.
You tell whitehurst
he's off the hook, huh?
I got myself another slave.
And clean up this mess.
You got five demerits.
What about the doll?
Ah. My kid sister's birthday is coming up.
I think she's gonna love it, don't you?
Oh, shit.
Andy.
What the fuck?
No, stop!
What the fuck are you doing
in my room, barclay?
You wouldn't believe me.
Where's the doll, barclay?
Where's the fucking doll?
- You took it, didn't you?
- No!
What's going on?
Yeah, well, somebody sure as hell took it.
It's almost midnight, colonel.
Is this really necessary?
I'm trying to weed out a thief, sir.
You've always told me how important it is
to uphold the school's code of honor.
I'm simply trying to impress that
upon the men, sir.
All right, Shelton, make your point.
But I want everybody back inside
at 0100 hours.
Yes, sir.
By the time we get through with barclay,
he's going to be living
in a whole world full of shit.
All right. We've only got an hour,
so let's make it count.
Yes, sir.
All right, ladies,
get those weapons in the air.
I want to see 'em high!
Higher!
I think I'm gonna throw up.
You're dead, new boy.
Fucking geek.
"Dear Charles, you're it.
Come and find me, your best friend."
Shit.
Charles.
Come and find me!
God damn it.
- Platoon!
- Hut!
Double time!
Hut!
Get those knees up, ladies!
Whitehurst, where do the kids sleep?
Above the portico. Why?
You're wearing combat boots,
not ballet slippers.
- Come on, move!
- Barclay!
It's gonna get
a lot worse than this!
Get the lead out. Come on, move it!
Faster, faster. Let's go, Brock!
Get those knees in the sky! Come on!
You son of a bitch!
You got a hell of a punch there, barclay.
Now I'll see what kind of
tough guy you really are.
Get your head around.
Tyler, come out, come out,
wherever you are.
Olly olly oxen free.
Get out here, you little son of a bitch.
- Three!
You're not sounding off.
- Four!
- You're pissing me off!
Five!
All right, barclay, you got me curious.
What are you trying to prove?
Forget it.
No, really, I want to know.
All right.
The doll's alive. He's after Tyler.
You're right, forget it.
I just hope he can take care of himself.
Come on.
Quiet.
Shut up.
Okay, come on.
Come on.
I can't believe
I let you talk me into this.
Okay, just stay here
and keep an eye out, okay?
- Oh, I live for this.
- I know, ivers. Now, go, go!
You know, I don't see
what you see in that guy, anyway.
I don't know, he's... well, he's just
different from everybody else.
Oh, please.
- Oh, he's kind of cute, too.
- Mmm.
Okay.
Foster homes. No wonder he's so quiet.
What was that?
So you took the doll?
Shelton will have you court-martialed
if he finds out.
We're playing hide and seek.
What are you guys doing?
We couldn't sleep.
Oh, he is so cute.
Ivers! Give him back!
You guys, please be quiet.
Can you go stand guard?
Yes, sir.
So what's his name?
- Ask him yourself.
- All right.
What is your name, little doll?
Hi, I'm Chucky.
And I'm your friend to the end.
Hidey-ho!
I love it.
His real name is Charles Lee ray.
Oh, is that so? Give me your lipstick.
- What for?
- Just give it to me.
Oh, no.
What are you doing?
You'll see.
Wait. Stop.
- Here you go, little baby!
- Come on!
You're messing him up.
Oh, you're so cute.
- Aw.
- Don't do that!
Don't. He looks stupid.
You're making him look like a wuss.
- No, he looks sweet.
- What are you doing?
Oh.
You guys, someone's coming.
Come on, let's go.
Come on. Let's go.
Stop! What about Charles?
This means war.
What the hell?
- I like to be hugged.
- Ah! Jeez.
Oh, you gotta be fucking kidding me!
A man lives through two tours in 'nam
and then one night he just drops dead.
Doesn't make any sense.
At ease!
We will now take a moment of silence
to honor colonel Cochrane.
He was a fine man
and he will be sorely missed.
Bow your heads for prayer.
Take seats!
It's getting pretty shaggy, Carlson.
I want to see you on Friday.
Yes, sergeant.
Monday, fabrizio.
Yes, sir.
My man.
Tuesday.
Look at you, whitehurst.
You're a disgrace.
When's the last time you had a trim?
Two weeks ago, sergeant, I think.
You think? You think?
I want to see you right after breakfast.
You got it?
Yes, sir, sergeant botnick, sir.
And what are you looking at, new boy?
Wednesday.
Barclay, what are you doing?
You can't just get up
in the middle of mess.
Major.
At ease!
Tyler.
Hi, barclay. What's up?
I gotta talk to you about Chucky.
You mean Charles.
Have you seen him?
Not since last night.
He's hiding somewhere.
He's gonna lay low
till he knows you're alone,
and then he's gonna come after you.
He just wants to play.
Listen to me, Tyler.
No matter what he says,
no matter what he promises you,
you've gotta stay away from him.
Don't let him fool you. He's bad.
Charles isn't bad. He's a good guy.
- It says so on his shirt.
- He lies, Tyler.
Believe me, he's bad news.
He's hurt a lot of people.
I think colonel Cochrane was one of them.
You're just jealous 'cause he's
my best friend now, instead of yours.
Look, you better keep this.
Whitehurst, you are without a doubt
the sorriest excuse for a soldier
to ever disgrace these walls.
Face it, you're not cut out for this life.
Why don't you do yourself a favor
and get the hell out of Kent?
If I had any choice
in the matter, I would, sir.
Smart-ass.
Presto! You're bald.
Yeah.
What the hell?
How'd you get in there?
That haircut ain't regulation, soldier.
When's the last time you had a trim, huh?
Kiss it goodbye.
Presto! You're dead.
It's definitely you.
I just forgot my... my...
Boo!
The annual war games
have been an unbroken tradition
here at Kent for over 50 years.
Colonel Cochrane was a man who believed
in the value of tradition.
He not only would have wanted us to go on,
he'd have ordered us to go on.
Therefore, the war games
will proceed as scheduled.
Hoo-ah!
Lieutenant colonel Shelton
will command the blue team.
Major rawlings will head up the reds.
The objective is simple.
To capture the other team's flag,
bring it back here safely to base.
Rawlings.
You will pick up your weapons
in the armory before moving out.
You will be using
the standard issue Springfield 0-3.
Your ammo.
Shelton.
If you get hit, you are dead.
Hike back to base.
Commanders, take charge of your teams.
May the best team win.
Good luck, men and women.
Nice of you to join us.
Looks like botnick's
in a pretty bad mood today.
What's wrong?
Nothing. Nothing's wrong.
Nothing's wrong. I'm fine.
Nothing's wrong.
This ought to slow the pricks down.
Left! Left! Left!
J“ here we go again j“
J“ here we go again I
I same old stuff again j“
J“ same old stuff again j“
J“ marching down the Avenue j“
J“ two more miles,
we'll be through j“
J“ I'll be getting rid of you j“
J“ same old ugly stuff j“
J“ here we go again j“
J“ marching down the Avenue j“
J“ one more mile,
we'll be through j“
J“ one more mile, we'll be through j“
J“ I'll be getting rid of you j“
what's going on, whitehurst?
You saw something, didn't you?
You saw Chucky.
Don't wimp out on me now, whitehurst.
I need your help.
That kid needs your help.
I didn't see anything, okay?
I didn't see anything at all.
J“ your left, right, your left j“
J“ your military left j“
Ellis, let's make sure
the perimeters are secured.
Yes, sir.
She checks all the windows,
and then the babysitter
hears this thump, thump,
thumping.
Like something's being dragged
across the floor upstairs.
And suddenly she thinks,
"I haven't checked on the children."
So she hurries to the top of the stairs,
and when she gets there,
she sees her boyfriend,
completely dismembered,
dragging himself
across the floor by his chin.
Thump. Slide.
That is gross.
Hey, you guys,
I got a better story and it's true.
It's about this mental institution,
and it's a few miles away from here.
Hey!
Hope it wasn't something I said.
No. I'm sorry.
De silva, where do you think
the red team's camped out?
Could be anywhere.
Shelton'll find them. He always does.
By the way, you can call me Kristin.
What?
Kristin.
It's my first name. Do you have one?
- Andy.
- Huh.
Come on, Andy,
I want to show you something.
Pretty cool, huh?
Yeah.
I almost forgot there
were places like that.
People just go to have fun.
Listen.
Somebody's out there.
It's probably just a chipmunk
or something.
Nothing scares you, does it?
Man, now I really gotta get out
of this body.
I'm going after Tyler.
Are you crazy? You'll never find them.
Wanna bet?
I swiped this from Shelton's tent.
He sent out a reconnaissance mission
right before we pitched camp.
The red team is somewhere around here.
That kid's a sitting duck, whitehurst.
Now, are you with me or not?
I'm sorry, I can't.
Up and at 'em, ladies,
we're moving out!
I want this camp to be a ghost town
in five minutes!
I thought we weren't
going until dawn, sir.
Someone stole the reconnaissance map
out of the colonel's tent,
so we're making our move now.
Get going, hanley.
Whitehurst.
You wouldn't know anything
about a missing map, would you?
Where the hell's barclay? Whitehurst!
Colonel Shelton, you'd better have
a look in here, sir.
What is it, Ellis?
Barclay's gone awol, sir.
He stole the map.
That little fucking traitor's
doubling for the reds.
Where's Tyler?
He went awol with some guy named Charles.
Where's Andy?
Whitehurst, where is he?
Platoon, halt!
All right. De silva, you're going
to take the right flank.
Siegel, you take the left.
I want you to check in
on the radio every five minutes.
- Yes, sir.
- All right, move it.
The rest of us are gonna spread out
and meet up with Ellis at split rock.
Move out!
Whitehurst, move!
Thanks for coming after me.
What are friends for?
Duck.
That was a close one.
Now, we can play hide the soul.
I'm tired. I don't want to play
that dumb game anymore.
You're a fucking drag, you know that?
Watch your mouth, Charles.
Stop calling me that!
What's the knife for?
A good soldier is always prepared, Tyler.
Barclay was right. You're not a good guy.
Sorry, kid, you got me. I'm bad.
Now, assume the position.
No!
Get back here!
Barclay! Barclay!
Tyler!
Barclay, you fucking traitor,
give me my map!
Listen to me, Shelton!
You got any idea what we do
to traitors, barclay?
Tyler's in trouble.
Come on, whitehurst, back me up.
Major Ellis, call in the flanks.
Yes, sir.
De silva, Siegel, do you copy?
De silva, do you copy?
De silva, come in.
Siegel's on his way back, sir.
No word yet from de silva.
- Well, keep trying.
- Yes, sir.
Help! Help!
Tyler!
Barclay!
Are you okay, Tyler?
Well, looks like we got
ourselves a little pow.
Barclay, you were right. Charles is bad.
He tried to hurt me.
Who the hell's Charles?
Come in, barclay. Come in.
Who the hell is that?
It's Charles.
Who is this?
Put barclay on, jarhead.
It's the reds.
They're up to something.
What do you want?
I want the kid.
Bring him up to the oldjeep
or there 'ii be hell to pay.
- Andy, don't do it!
- De silva!
You hear that, barclay?
Don't touch her,
you son of a bitch.
Now, bring me the kid or I'll waste her.
Red team, red team. Come in, red team.
This is red team. Over.
We got a situation
up here at the old Jeep.
Blue team sighted.
Advise you to move your troops in.
I hope they like the taste of lead.
Now just sit back
and watch the sparks fly.
All right, you two are
gonna go on up ahead, draw 'em out.
- The rest of us are gonna circle around.
- Shelton, this is no game.
I'm telling you, this guy is dangerous.
Relax, barclay. It's only paint.
All right. Let's do it.
I'm scared, barclay.
Yeah, me, too.
All right, kid. Get over here!
Don't fuck with me!
I'll blow all of you to pieces!
Beat it.
Now, just get down and shut up.
Yeah!
Hold your fire!
De silva, where the hell is everybody?
Hi, soldier.
Fuck me.
All right!
- Shit!
- Stay down!
Jesus Christ. They're using live rounds!
Hold your fire! Hold your fire!
Hold your fire!
Oh, god, he's not breathing.
Get away from him!
You did this, didn't you?
You sick son of a bitch!
Now I'm gonna kill you!
Stop it! Get off of him!
- He didn't do it! Stop it!
- Let go of me! Let go of me!
Sayonara, suckers.
No! Get off of him!
Stop it! He didn't do it!
Look out!
No! Oh, my god, what happened?
It's whitehurst.
Oh, my god! Ellis, what happened?
Epstein, what the hell happened?
- I don't know.
- Who fucked with the rifles?!
- I don't know!
- Okay. Okay.
- Get Clark on the radio.
- Yes, sir!
And get me a medic up here
- right now!
- Yes, sir!
All right. Everybody stay calm!
Epstein, I want that radio! Oh, god.
This is the last time
I'm gonna tell you.
Give that thing a rest
or you're out of here, both of you.
Come on, we're not bothering anybody.
You're bothering me. Keep it down.
Jeez!
Mister, mister, you've got to help me.
What's wrong? What's the matter?
Charles! Charles, he's after me.
- Who's Charles?
- He's a good guy!
- He wants to play hide the soul.
- Okay, slow down, slow down!
Have a seat over there. Are you from Kent?
- Yes, sir.
- What's your name, son?
Ronald Tyler. Private first-class, sir.
Have a seat. How about some gum, private?
I know how it must hurt when a friend does
something bad to you.
Sure does.
But I bet your friend...
What's his name, Charles?
I bet you Charles didn't mean it.
I bet you he's really sorry.
No, he isn't. He wants to hurt me.
Nobody's gonna hurt you.
Hey, I know what will cheer you up.
Look what I found.
- Here's your prize.
- Here you go.
Thank you, daddy.
Let's go in the super loop.
Yeah.
Hey. Hey, maybe somebody's seen him.
Oh, god.
- Come on.
- Wait.
Mommy, mommy, I loved it!
- Were you scared?
- No!
Let's have some popcorn
and go on one more ride.
Perfect. In there.
Don't even think about it.
- Come on.
- Okay.
In there!
Time to play.
This looks good. Park it.
Ah!
Kid!
Tyler!
Barclay! Barclay! In here!
He's got a gun!
Kid!
Are you okay? Oh, my god.
Oh, god.
Here. Take it.
You can do it.
I'll be okay.
Help! Help!
- Help! Help!
- Yeah! You're mine now, Tyler!
Tyler!
Barclay!
Tyler, watch out!
Shit!
This is it, kid! End of the line.
Give me the power, I beg of you!
Come on, keep both eyes open.
Hold your breath.
Yeah!
Are you okay?
Yeah.
Come on, let's get out of here.
Hold on, Tyler! Hold on!
Give me the fucking kid!
He's mine!
Barclay, help!
Mine! Give me the fucking kid!
Hold on, Tyler. Hold on.
He's mine!
- Come on, hold on, Tyler.
- Barclay!
Here. Take the knife!
Give him to me!
Take it! Here, take it!
- Barclay!
- Hold on!
- Reach for it!
- He's mine!
Tyler, come on. I got you.
Okay, we're on our way in.
Roger.
You'll have to come with us now, son.
Are you gonna be okay?
Don't worry. I've been here before.
Watch your head.