Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org
(♪♪♪)
FLINT:
My name is
Flint Lockwood. My whole life
I always wanted to be
a great inventor.
Just like my hero.
MAN (ON TV): The Scientifically
Wonderful World of Science.
With your host, Chester V.
Welcome back, science friends.
You know, I have devoted my life
to inventing the future.
But every dream has a beginning.
I still remember my first invention:
The humble Food Bar.
Whoa!
FLINT: It was like Chester V
was speaking directly to me
using the language of science.
Now look at us.
Our new Food Bar XL
with flavor crystals.
Still making people happy
after all these years.
Now, kids, you'll almost
certainly never be me.
But, remember, there's no such thing
as small science.
Only small scientists!
KIDS:
We love you, Chester V!
Speaking of small scientists,
say goodbye, Barb.
Goodbye, Barb.
Ha, ha, ha!
Can your ideas
change the world?
Yes.
FLINT: Just like Chester V, my dream
was to make the world a better place.
Spray-On Shoes!
Voila!
BRENT: How you gonna
get them off, nerd?
(CLASS LAUGHS)
FLINT: Unfortunately, a lot of
people didn't believe in me.
But I never gave up.
And eventually,
I invented this:
A machine that could
turn water into food.
MACHINE:
Cheeseburger.
It's called the Flint Lockwood
Diatonic Super Mutating
Dynamic Food Replicator.
Or, for short:
The FLDSMDFR.
FLINT: Because of my
invention's food weather,
I finally made the
world a better place.
Yeah!
I love it!
Or so I thought.
When the weather evolved into
a disaster of epic portions,
and the machine started
creating dangerous living food
I had to face the truth:
It was time to
put an end
to my FLDSMDFR.
MACHINE:
Chee-- Chee-- Chee-- Chee--
Cheese.
(MACHINE POWERS DOWN)
FLINT: By destroying
my greatest invention,
I made something even better:
Friends!
Wow.
You made me very proud, son.
Unh!
Thank you, Dad.
Sorry.
(♪♪♪)
Sam Sparks, in the eight minutes
since we saved the world,
I've had time to reflect.
And I think you and I
should have a place together.
A Place?
A place where we work.
You think we work together?
I do.
Awesome! Yes!
FLINT: We could build a lab.
SAM: With cool weather
forecasting devices!
We can invent fantastic
machines like the FLDSMDFR.
Yeah!
But not that one.
No.
Not ever.
Never, ever, ever!
What shall we call our lab?
Oh! How about
Sparkswood?
Ooh!
Sparkswood.
Sparkswood is gonna need
some security.
And I can be your mascot!
And I can be your dad.
There are many ways
in which I can help.
Ho, ho! Can't forget you,
lab partner.
Steve!
Where'd he get
the brown crayon?
This
could be our future.
Oh, yeah! Ha, ha!
(AIRCRAFT WHIRRING)
(♪♪♪)
(CROWD GASPS)
Greetings, friends.
And namaste.
Whoa. Is that...?
Chester V?
Mustache.
Please have some humanitarian aid
as a gesture of our goodwill.
Chester V! Whoa!
Your lab vest looks
even cooler in person!
Thank you. The lack of sleeves
frees up my arms to do this.
Whoa!
Ah! Hand, what did you do?
There's nothing wrong with your hand,
young Lockwood.
You see, I am merely a hologram
of the real Chester V.
The United Nations has asked
me and my Thinkquanauts
to assist in the cleanup
and containment
of the leftovers all over the world.
Including your Swallow Falls.
We'll get started on the cleanup
right away.
As soon as you all leave.
What? You need us to leave?
Listen up, ghost man,
you expect us to skedaddle from our
homes because of some nasty leftovers?
Yes. Yes, I do.
Son, you can't argue
with yellow police tape.
Everybody back up!
Listen to ghost man.
But do not fret.
All of you will be
temporarily relocated
to sunny San Franjose,
California!
The home of Live Corp!
On my word as a hologram,
you shall all return home
before you know it.
Except for you,
Flint Lockwood.
Me? Why?
Oh, heh, heh.
You are going--
Wait, wait, wait. No, no, no.
Where am I going?
Oh, please tell me!
Just give it a second.
He's buffering.
You are going to join me
at Live Corp
and help us make the world
a better place.
Sir, that's all I've ever wanted.
But I can't.
On account of making
a promise two minutes ago
to build a lab with my friends, sir.
I understand, Lockwood.
But if you become
a Thinkquanaut like me,
then all your dreams will come true.
You have to do this!
What about our dream?
Flint, this is a once-in-a-lifetime
opportunity.
We're all behind you.
Are you guys sure?
Sure.
(♪♪♪)
This is the best day ever!
Sir, I've taken care of everything.
The locals have been evacuated.
Splendid. And the inventor?
Outstanding!
Oh, he took the job.
Now we can keep an eye on him.
He has no idea of our real plan.
Contact me as soon as Operation
Capture the Invention succeeds.
WOMAN (ON RECORDING):
Live Corp.
MACHINE:
Cheeseburger.
(♪♪♪)
(ALARM BEEPING)
Oh, big day, big day!
Big day, big day,
big day! Yes!
Wake up, Steve!
Steve.
Do I look like a
future Thinkquanaut?
Morning there, skipper.
You want a sardine scramble?
No, thanks!
Can't be late!
Flint! Ask that Chester V when
he thinks we can go home again.
Morning, Sam!
Morning, Flint! Are you ready
for your first day?
Yeah! Are you?
Whoa!
Sam?
Well, this is me. Good luck
with your new jobs, guys.
Good luck, Flint!
Break a leg, Flint!
Bye!
Adios.
(PAUL MCCARTNEY'S "NEW" PLAYING)
♪ Don't look at me
It's way too soon to see ♪
♪ What's gonna be
Don't look of me ♪
♪ All my life
I never knew what I could be ♪
♪ What I could do ♪
♪ Then we were new ♪
♪ Then we were new ♪♪
Wow!
Good morning, Flint
Lockwood and lab partner.
I'm Barb.
FLINT: Eeh!
I know, I'm a huge fan.
Monkey.
Excuse me,
I'm an ape. One of Chester V's
most brilliant innovations.
An orangutan with a human brain
within my ape brain.
Like a turducken.
I'll be your welcome ambassador.
Soy latte?
Okay.
Coffee and milk?
(CHUCKLES)
Are you ready to
live?
Oh, am I!
STEVE:
Monkey.
Ape. Follow me, boys.
BARB:
Welcome to Live Corp.
Wow.
BARB:
There are caffeine stations
every 10 feet.
Soy-free soy latte?
Thanks!
Hot.
Not too bad yourself, monkey.
Caffeine patches
are available 24 hours.
And our mocha-yoga classes
are offered in beginner or grande.
Over here, indoor sports.
Those are encouraged.
Oh, cool!
I've never played volleyball.
Well, neither have they.
You'll fit right in!
Can your ideas
change the world?
Behold, the motivation pod.
Can your ideas...?
I know, right?
Quinoa latte?
Absolutely! Ha, ha, ha!
Can your ideas
change the world?
Yes, Chester V poster, they can!
Mine too!
So can mine!
I have great ideas.
Absolutely! I've got my idea pants on.
Thinkquanauts!
Awesome!
Hey! Excuse me,
I'm so looking forward
to working with you guy-- Uh!
Aww!
That's where we belong, Steve.
Anxious!
Oh, heh, heh.
That's not even a possibility
until our next vesting ceremony.
FLINT: What's that?
BARB: That's where Chester V
handpicks a great inventor and
makes him into a Thinkquanaut.
When? When?
Next one's in six months,
so submit your ideas
and who knows?
He might choose you.
Really?
Hot chocolate with
double-whipped whipped cream?
Thanks.
Happy inventing!
(FLINT SCREAMING)
(♪♪♪)
(FLINT GRUNTS)
We're gonna have to get used
to that landing.
Okay, Steve, we have six months
until the vesting ceremony.
Let's do this thing.
Can.
That's the spirit, Steve!
(♪♪♪)
FLINT (ON VIDEO):
Say goodbye
to ice cubes
with the Re-Freeze-a-Fan!
Can your ideas change the world?
The Forkenknifenspooninator!
Can your ideas
change the world?
The Grocery Deliverator!
Whoa!
Can your ideas change the world?
Invisible coffee table!
Ah!
Flint.
CHESTER:
Can your ideas
change the world?
Flint!
The Celebrationator!
A party in a box
for any occasion.
Okay, Steve,
time to celebrate!
Celebrate!
Flint!
Happy birthday, Tim Lockwood!
Here you go, Dad. Hope you like it.
Steve picked it out.
Steve!
(DISCO MUSIC PLAYING OVER SPEAKERS)
(♪♪♪)
(AUDIENCE APPLAUDING)
Yeah. Yeah!
Okay, like we practiced.
When I'm up on stage getting my vest,
you hit the red button
when I say "celebrate."
Celebrate!
Whoa. Careful, Steve!
This is a loaded party-in-a-box.
CHESTER: Hello, Team Live Corp!
(AUDIENCE CHEERS)
It's a pleasure to welcome you
to our annual Thinkquanaut
vesting ceremony!
Whoo! Chester V!
Ha, ha, ha.
I have built the coolest, hippest
company in the world.
As you all know, the Food Bar
is the lifeblood of this company.
And this year, I've challenged myself
to reinvent taste. Ooh.
So in two short weeks,
we shall release the new
Live Corp Food Bar!
Version 8.0!
Yes!
CHESTER: And now, without
further ado, who will be this year's
newest Live Corp
Thinkquanaut?
Oh, ho, ho! Yeah!
CHESTER: We have received thousands
of invention submissions
and today, one of them
will be deemed
Thinkquanaut-worthy.
Thank you, Barb.
Whoo!
This person comes
from an island.
Ohh. Uh-huh!
He's got a memorable
mop of unruly hair.
Hair. Hair!
Ha, ha, ha! That's me!
Our newest Live Corp
Thinkquanaut is:
Flint--
Yeah!
--ly McCallahan!
No.
Crikey blikey! Yes!
CHESTER:
For inventing
a zero-emission car
that runs on cute.
(PURRS)
(SCREECHES)
This is the greatest
day of my life!
Didgeridoo!
I'm finally a real inventor!
Sorry, Steve.
No reason to celebrate.
Celebrate!
Wait, Steve, no, no, no. No!
(DISCO MUSIC PLAYING
OVER SPEAKERS)
♪ He's a real baboon ♪
♪ He's a real baboon ♪♪
(MAN SCREAMS)
(LAUGHING)
(CODY CAMERON'S "THE INVENTOR SONG"
PLAYING)
♪ The inventor walks home ♪
♪ His confidence shaken ♪
♪ He is sad and alone ♪
♪ So he calls up a friend ♪♪
Hi, Sam, it's Flint.
I see you're live on TV
with a tornado.
Probably why you're not
answering the phone.
Thinkquanaut?
I think not.
Ugh. Please call me back.
Okay. Bye!
(SIGHS)
Bad news!
Sir, we lost contact
with Search Teams X and Y.
What?
Yeah!
The situation is
grim, sir. Still no sign
of the FLDSMDFR.
Should I send in Team Z?
Are you mad, Barb?
We'll be all out of alphabet.
Look, we're running low
on Thinkquanauts. We need
someone expendable.
Someone who knows the island
inside and out.
Someone who's smart, but still naive.
Someone who idolizes me,
has recently hit rock bottom
and will now do
just about anything I ask.
Where are we gonna find
someone so desperate?
I think we already have.
(GROANS)
(♪♪♪)
Sprinkles!
Fire!
Flint, who's number one? Oh.
Ta-da!
(FLINT SOBBING)
Hey, Flint, I got your message.
Oh, no, what happened to you?
(FLINT WAILS)
Flint, everyone gets humiliated
on national television.
It's not that big a deal.
Yeah, but not everyone
gets humiliated
in front of their childhood hero.
I'll never be a real inventor
in Chester's eyes.
Mom gave me this lab coat because
she always dreamed
I'd do great things.
Now I guess I won't.
Now that's a big bucket of churn.
Flint, you don't need
Chester's approval.
You can still make
the world a better place
without an orange vest.
I don't get vests.
Is it winter on your torso
and summer on your arms?
(SIGHS)
For what it's worth, the people
who really care about you
think you look great
in your lab coat.
Good night, Mr. Lockwood.
Good night, my dear.
(DOOR OPENS THEN CLOSES)
Hey, look, son.
This Chester V guy.
He promised us we'd be home
before we know it. Well,
we darn sure know it
and we're not home.
So I say you,
me and your friends,
we take the boat.
We can go fishing every day.
And if there's still a mess on the
island, we can go clean it up ourselves.
Dad, please.
I'm not into fishing.
And cleanup? You're way too old
to be doing that kind of work.
I'm only 49.
(DOORBELL RINGS)
BARB:
Flint Lockwood, please.
Oh, Flint. Um...
There's. Could you
come to the door, please?
I think it's that monkey
in your poster.
What? No!
Ahh!
Barb?
BARB:
Shh.
Good day.
I'm afraid I have something
very important to discuss
with you.
WOMAN (ON RECORDING):
Live Corp.
Chester V wants to see me?
(♪♪♪)
Follow me.
FLINT:
Whoa.
(GASPS)
Ah. Young Lockwood.
Chester V. Sir.
I can explain everything.
I thought I was gonna meet
the real Chester V.
You are.
ALL: Oh, not me.
Him.
CHESTER:
Yes, it's me.
Sorry about that.
My holograms and I were having
an urgent brainstorming session.
Aah! Mr. V!
You're real!
I'm so excited to get this opportunity
to show you my inventions.
Hold on. Hold on. That's not
why I brought you here tonight.
Our cleanup operation
back on Swallow Falls
has met with
unexpected complications.
This is a photograph
before we began our cleanup.
And this was three days ago.
It gets worse, Flint.
There's only two of us left.
We need help.
(SCREAMING)
(CREATURE ROARING)
What is that thing?
Cheesy.
It appears to be
a living cheeseburger
with french fry legs
and sesame seed eyes.
Living food?
Oh, no. This could
only mean one thing.
The FLDSMDFR
survived the explosion,
and it's still operating.
This is what worries me most.
(HOWLS)
They're trying to learn to swim.
If they succeed and
get to the mainland,
they will destroy monuments
all around the world
including the one monument
your food storm didn't destroy.
Not Lady Liberty! I've gotta destroy
the FLDSMDFR. But how?
Well, my Thinkquanauts have invented
this.
The BS-USB.
Or BSUSB.
A Bifurcating Systematic
Universal Stop Button!
Precisely. It would
destroy the machine
and everything it created.
But we cannot find your FLDSMDFR.
We've searched everywhere
and failed.
Chester, I'll find the machine.
I invented it. I can fix this!
Brilliant!
But are you sure you want
to take this on alone?
Yes!
Wait, did you say "alone"?
Alone it is, then.
If you succeed, you'll be more
than just a Thinkquanaut.
You'll be my hero.
Your hero?
Yes, my hero.
Your mission must
be kept a secret.
We don't wanna create
a worldwide panic.
You mustn't tell anyone, not even
your closest friends and family.
Sir, I won't tell a soul.
Sam! Sam, Sam, Sam!
I gotta tell you a secret! Sam!
Big news. I'm going to Swallow Falls
to destroy the FLDSMDFR,
which is creating
deadly food monsters,
which are trying to learn to swim
so they can attack Lady Liberty!
Sam?
Wait, you're doing this alone?
Yeah. Please don't tell Dad. if he finds
out I'm going back to Swallow Falls,
he's gonna wanna come too.
Well, I'm coming.
What? No! I promised Chester V
I would go alone.
There's no talking you out of this?
Nope.
Wait.
Sam, it's gonna be deadly dangerous
with a good chance of death.
And that's why we'll need help.
EARL: Triple decaf
mochaccino-boba-latte
with skim soy and nutmeg sprinkle?
FLINT:
I'd like to order something strong.
Wait your turn, fancy pants.
Flint Lockwood
and Sam Sparks!
And Steve too!
Juicy!
Earl, we need your help.
Swallow Falls is overrun
with deadly food monsters.
MAN:
Hey,
where's my coffee?
Coffee? I'm not a barista,
I'm a polista!
(GROANS)
Let's ride!
Can I come too, Dad?
Son, you are my beautiful,
precious little angel.
But I cannot let you come with me.
Not until you get
your first chest hair.
I have chest hair.
It's just like mine.
Wait a minute.
That's not a chest hair.
That's cupcake frosting.
Tell your mom
I'm getting our home back.
What's up?
Sponge.
Forceps.
A swab.
Manny. We need your help.
I can drop everything.
Camera.
(CALF MOOING)
♪ Chick 'n' sushi
Get it while it's cold ♪♪
Hoo!
Yo, Chicken Brent!
In the flesh.
Ba-gawk-oh!
Swallow Falls is in trouble.
Will you help us?
You bet I will. I just need someone
to cover my shift.
Thanks, tree.
(♪♪♪)
FLINT:
Okay, gang.
We'll be traveling to the island
using my Grocery Deliverator!
All right, who wants to go first?
Hungry.
Yes, Steve, hungry for adventure.
See you on the island,
my brave lab partner.
Afraid!
It worked!
Banana! Banana! Banana! Steve!
I guess it only works on food.
I gotta fix that.
(HORN BLOWS)
Ahoy there,
skipper, my boy.
Dad.
ALL: Mr. Lockwood?
Dad, no. How did you
know we were here?
I could see you
from the apartment.
(SIGHS)
Flint, if you're going home,
so am I.
The island's gonna be
very dangerous--
I was born on the island, and I wanna
die on that island, just like your mom.
Besides, I know that place like
the inside of a tackle box. I wanna help.
No!
Flint, let him help.
The man does have a boat.
Which is twice as many
boats as we have.
(MANNY SPEAKS IN SPANISH)
Fine. But we'll get
there faster
if we use the Grocery
Deliverator.
Steve!
Aah!
Okay, okay,
we'll take the boat!
(WHISTLING)
Shoving off!
♪ Ninety-nine buckets
Of chum on a boat ♪
♪ Ninety-nine buckets ♪
♪ Of chum ♪
(♪♪♪)
♪ Nineteen buckets of chum on a boat ♪
♪ Nineteen buckets of chum ♪
♪ You hold your nose ♪
♪ And out one goes
There's 18 buckets of chum on a boat ♪♪
We'll be there in two flaps
of a sardine's fluke!
Thanks, Dad!
Okay, when we land at Swallow Falls,
our first objective
is to get to my lab.
I can use my old computer to pinpoint
the FLDSMDFR's location.
Once we find it, we can shut it down
with the utterly irreplaceable BS-USB.
What if you don't find it?
I have to. It's my machine.
If the world gets destroyed
by these, it's my fault.
I can't let that happen.
TIM:
Land ho!
If we work together,
this should be easy as--
Pie.
(♪♪♪)
Oh, no! We're--
Toast!
EARL:
French toast!
This is totally--
Bananas!
I was gonna say "nuts,"
but now I'm afraid to.
(STEVE SHRIEKS AND CHITTERS)
Uh-oh.
Whoa, whoa!
STEVE: Home!
FLINT: No! Steve, wait!
The jungle's no place for a monkey.
Home, home, home!
Manny, are you getting this?
MANNY: I certainly am.
SAM: Flint.
Look! The climate
has shifted dramatically
to allow this much vegetation
to grow!
(GROWLING IN DISTANCE)
(STEVE CHITTERS)
Aah! Sam! Ratbirds!
Okay, then. All ashore
that's going ashore.
Dad, this place is really dangerous.
I'd feel better if you stayed here
on the boat where it's safe.
Safe?
I wanna help.
I'd never forgive myself if you
got eaten by a cheespider.
He's right, Tim Lockwood.
Don't worry,
we'll get your home back.
(SIGHS)
Well, fine.
Thanks, Dad. We'll try to be back
before suppertime, okay?
Sure.
(EARL GRUNTING)
Whoa. Look what's
happened to our town.
(♪♪♪)
Look.
There's my angel son
Cal's old preschool.
(MANNY GASPS)
MANNY:
My old van.
Look! An old thing
that I've never seen before!
FLINT:
That's where
the Thinkquanauts were
attacked by a cheespider.
BRENT: It's like a cheesy
spider web, made of
cheese.
Let's get out of here!
No, wait. What if there's
a survivor in there?
Stand back, everybody.
I'm gonna cut the cheese.
(PARTS)
Uh... That was the cheese.
Hello? Anybody in here?
(♪♪♪)
Shh!
(WHISPERS)
Sorry.
(CLATTERING)
Ha!
(GRUNTS)
Wow.
That is the biggest strawberry
I've ever seen in my life.
Is it heavy?
Yeah. But other than that
it looks like a perfectly normal,
fresh, delicious strawberry.
(ALL SCREAM)
N-woo?
(SCREAMS)
It's moving!
Heh, heh.
Oh, that was a close one.
You got a little someone
stuck to your pants.
Ah! Get it off! Get it off me!
Sam! Sam!
Hey, wait, wait. Stop!
Sam, don't touch it!
Put it down! Put it down!
Look at him.
(SCREAMS)
Seriously?
Aww. I think
I'll name him Barry!
Okay, Sam, could you please
put "Barry" down?
Look, we have to get to the FLDSMDFR
so we can shut it down
with this utterly irreplaceable
BS-USB.
Hey! That's not for you!
I need that.
Please?
That BS-USB is really important.
N-woo?
N-woo. Yes.
Hi, N-woo. Hey, you wanna
hand it to me, buddy?
I beg you.
Huh?
Please?
Oh, oh.
N-woo.
N-woo, N-woo. Yes.
Yes. There you go.
No!
Don't let him get away!
Stop!
Gotcha.
N-woo?
Aah! Here, you take it, you take it.
You're gonna have to carry him
until he passes the BS-USB.
And by "pass," you mean...
Yes. Look, we better get a move on
before we run into any more
of these creatures.
(ALL GASPING)
(♪♪♪)
Oh! It's so beautiful.
It's enough to make a
grown man cry.
But not this man.
Get back in there, tear.
Wow, I can't believe
the FLDSMDFR created
all of this.
Ah! Where's Barry?
Whee. Ha, ha, ha!
Uh-oh.
Ah! Ah!
Just a little bit closer.
I can get him.
Come on, Earl, faster.
Look at the mangos.
You mean flamingos.
Flamangos!
There's a bunch of shrimp!
They look like chimpanzees.
Shrimpanzees!
Those are some
tasty-looking jellyfish!
Oh!
What's that one over there?
SAM:
That's just a tomato.
(TOMATO WHIMPERS)
Barry!
Come on!
Chester gave me that BS-USB.
It's really important.
Shrimpanzee.
Steve.
Shove.
There's a leek in the boat!
(YELLS)
EARL:
Hold on, everyone.
This ain't gonna be no picnic.
FLINT:
Stop! Get back here!
Keep it steady, Earl.
SAM:
Watermelophants!
(SCREAMS)
Barry, grab my hand!
Barry!
(SIREN WAILING)
Freeze, berry man.
Thanks, Earl. Ugh.
Okay, come here.
You have caused enough trouble
for one day.
Susheep!
MANNY:
Cantalopes.
SAM:
I can't believe your machine
reprogrammed itself to create
this entire ecosystem
of living food.
How is that even possible?
I have no idea.
Best we don't think about it.
The world should know about this.
Manny, is your camera still working?
MANNY:
Of course. I've been rolling
since we landed.
BARB: So much for
keeping this a secret.
We can't let these friends
tell the world anything.
What we need to do is go there
and separate Flint from his friends
so we can manage
the situation.
Champion!
Brilliant idea.
Way to go, Chester.
Thank you.
Barb, you take care of that weather girl.
But, sir,
I'm a scientist.
That's why I need you.
I want the same brilliant mind
that solved the unified field theory
to help me help Live Corp.
Consider it done, sir.
Good monkey.
To the Helpicopter.
FLINT:
Oh, Earl.
Pull over there.
Duck!
Duck? I love-- Ba-gawk! Ah!
(♪♪♪)
(GROWLS)
Whoo-hoo-hoo!
Yeah!
You guys,
that wasn't so bad.
Yeah, well, be thankful
we didn't run into a--
Cheespider!
EARL:
Run!
Cheesy. Cheesy. Cheesy.
Manny!
BRENT:
Wait for me!
(BRENT SCREAMING)
Ba-gawk-oh!
I'm glad you still wearing
that diaper.
I wish I brought a fresh one!
Hey, guys!
Down this alley!
Oh, no! Dead end.
(CHEESPIDER ROARING)
(SCREAMING)
(ROARS)
(♪♪♪)
(SHRIEKS)
Ghost man?
Greetings, and namaste.
Chester V! You're here!
That's right,
young Lockwood.
And by the looks of things,
just in time.
One minute later, and we would
have been food for that food.
Flint, I thought you said you were
going to complete this mission alone.
Can I say something?
Apparently you can.
This is Barb, my number two.
Why are you carrying
a strawberry in
your backpack, miss?
Stand back, everyone!
Hey, hey, hey, stop.
You're scaring him.
Scaring him?
Oh, please, it's probably
got a mouth full of fangs.
(HISSES)
Now you're scaring me.
I've been carrying him
and he hasn't hurt anyone.
I'm sorry.
Are you a scientist?
Matter of fact, I am.
She's a meteorologist.
Meteorology.
Oh, I love it.
The science of smiling and having
pretty hair while you point at a map.
It's a very important job--
Meteorology is
a comprehensive analysis--
Ladies, ladies. Please.
I'm sure we can all agree
that one of you is a scientist.
Young Lockwood,
why was your lady friend carrying this
rabid little strawberry in her backpack?
Why is the strawberry guy in
the backpack? Well, um, that's funny.
Um... It's... Uh...
You know what he did? Um...
(SIGHS)
He, uh... He ate the BS-USB.
Not the BSUSB.
I'm on it.
She's got a knife!
If you touch a leaf on his head...
Step away from the berry, madam.
(BARRY SQUEAKS)
That orange hairy lady
scared the jam out of him!
N-woo?
Oh, no, it's jammed.
Lick. Lick. Lick.
Oh, thanks, Steve.
Young Lockwood.
The world could've
been destroyed
because of the actions
of one sinister strawberry.
We cannot allow any more
mistakes like this.
Oh...
It won't
be long before
those malicious melons,
pernicious pickles,
and belligerent burgers
learn to swim
and make their way
to the mainland.
What is
your plan?
I need to get back to
my lab so I can
make contact with the FLDSMDFR.
Brilliant!
I'll lead the way.
No, we'll lead the way.
SENTINELS:
Safe, safe, safe.
I believe my Sentinels of Safety
are better equipped to lead us
in their robo-suits.
(EARL GROWLS)
N-woo?
TIM:
"I'll be back
before supper."
What a bunch of baloney.
Just leave me on the boat
without any food.
I know a place where
I can get something to eat.
There she is.
Home sweet home.
(♪♪♪)
What?
There's no sardines?
Had to be looters.
Ah.
Vintage Baby Brent.
(SNIFFS)
Ah.
(DOOR OPENS)
(MUTTERING INDISTINCTLY)
Oh, chum.
No, no!
Uh-huh. Yeah. Heh.
I like them too. I do.
I love them.
Mine. No, no. Mine.
Off. Off. Mine.
No, no, mine. Mine. Off.
Hey, hey, hey. Easy, you guys.
Come on, you could lose an eye.
Look, I tell you what. You want more
sardines? I can get you more sardines.
(BRENT GRUNTING)
Hey, thanks for loaning me
these skinny jeans, Flint.
Those aren't skinny jeans.
Nope.
My feet are turning purple.
Is that bad?
(RUMBLING IN DISTANCE)
Uh-oh.
(CHITTERING)
Bananostrich! Ah!
EARL: Go, go, go!
Come on, Brent!
STEVE: Banana!
Banana! Banana!
That bunch of bananostriches
nearly split us.
Are you okay?
Oh, my gosh.
My house!
STEVE:
Home, home, home!
Oh, my gosh.
Your lab!
Oh, crap balls.
We can't go up there,
Flint Lockwood.
That dangly, upsy-downsy lab's
not to code.
I've got to, if I'm gonna find
the FLDSMDFR.
We can do it. Those
load-bearing vines will be able
to support a small team.
Onwards and upwards!
Right, sir.
To the lab!
(♪♪♪)
Sentinels,
keep the locals safe.
I'll keep them safe.
Hey, guys! Where you going?
Guys! Hey
wait for me!
Uh-oh.
A little help?
STEVE
Spooky.
Spooky is right, Steve.
(YELPS)
I say,
this laboratory of yours
is a wonder of engineering.
Really?
Thank you, sir.
Initiating backup power.
(FLINT IMITATES BEEPING)
COMPUTER:
Welcome, Flint.
FLINT:
Whoa, my computer's dead.
The fate of the world is depending
on us. Think, Lockwood.
Well, if I could pull
the hard drive, there's enough
equipment in this
lab that I could build
a tracking device.
Flint! Whoa!
I say, young Lockwood,
what extraordinary
underpants.
Thank you, sir. They're
my Wedgie-proof underwear.
I invented them when I was 6.
I had no idea we were so alike.
Except I invented mine
when I was 3.
(BOTH CHUCKLE)
You guys have been wearing the same
underwear since you were kids?
Yes!
Excuse me.
How do you expect us
to get the hard drive
with all that electrified water?
(CRACKLING)
We dangle!
Come, Lockwood, give the monkey
your underpants.
What?
CHESTER:
Lay on,
young Lockwood.
(♪♪♪)
Whoa!
Yes! Heh, heh.
SAM:
Whoa!
You know, hanging from
my underpants in this space
brings back so many memories.
I too built my lab up high
to keep the bullies out!
You were--
(SCREAMING)
You were bullied too?
CHESTER:
Absolutely.
People like us
are always bullied.
Sometimes I wish I'd kept
my bullies around.
Really?
So I could crush them
with my success.
Just like you did
with that man-baby.
You mean Brent?
Sure, he used to be a bully,
but he's my friend now.
CHESTER:
Friend?
A bully can never be your friend.
Never?
Remember
the ancient Chinese proverb:
(SPEAKING IN CHINESE)
Huh?
"Stew offered by a bully
is poisoned broth."
Wow, stew.
I have so much to learn.
CHESTER:
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
Mission accomplished!
Indeed, young Lockwood.
Indeed.
(UNDERPANTS SNAP AND BOTH YELP)
BRENT:
Help!
(RATTLING)
(MANNY SPEAKS IN SPANISH)
Help! Come on, guys.
Get me ou--!
(BRENT GRUNTS)
You okay, Earl?
My chest hairs
have been tingling all day.
Don't worry.
Live Corp Sentinels
have danger-sensing fibers
built into their chest plates.
Bravo, Lockwood.
With luck, we'll survive the night.
(♪♪♪)
(BELLOWING)
Hm. Sounds like midnight snacks.
Dr. Manny!
This is delicious!
I call it Manny's Gorilla Stew.
So how do you make a gorilla stew?
You keep it waiting for two hours.
Hey, guys.
Oh, that smells good.
Hey, Flint! Wanna try some of this
special stew? I saved you a bowl.
It's killer.
Killer stew.
(SPEAKING IN CHINESE)
No!
Thank you,
Brent.
Ever since that ghost man
showed up,
Flint Lockwood's been acting--
Jerky.
He rejected my stew.
No one has ever rejected my stew.
I'm gonna go talk to him.
Flint, wait up.
Yeah, Sam?
Is something wrong?
Yeah, we blew a fuse.
You blew a fuse.
Why are you being so weird
to your friends?
What?
I haven't been weird.
You karate-chopped
Manny's stew out of Brent's hands.
You hurt their feelings.
Sam, you wouldn't understand.
(SPEAKING IN CHINESE)
I do understand,
but you're forgetting that:
(SPEAKING IN CHINESE)
Huh?
"A bully turned friend
will be friend to the end."
Listen, Brent came here to help you.
We all did.
(IMITATES WHIRRING)
And you're acting like
we're just in your way.
Remember, we work together.
(♪♪♪)
That weather girl is
ruining our plan.
I just need more time, sir.
We don't have more time.
If we don't get the FLDSMDFR
in the next 48 hours,
we'll miss our deadline
to release Food Bar 8.0.
I'll be a laughingstock!
Sir, let me handle this.
Never send a monkey
to do Chester work.
I'll take care of it.
(SQUAWKS)
(HORN BLOWS)
Okay, guys, we're here.
Hey, hey, hey!
That is not for you.
All right, let's get to it.
(CLAMORING)
Okay.
You got this, right?
Okay. Then you wanna put
one of these on there, like that.
No, no, no.
No, don't eat that. That's bad.
You'll hurt yourself.
Hey, hey, easy! Stop picking
on your brother, will you?
How would you like it
if he was shoving you?
Okay, now watch.
Are you watching?
One and two and three!
Catch the big one!
(♪♪♪)
Yeah, good, huh?
It's called fishing.
(GASP)
(HARMONICA PLAYING)
♪ Out on my boat ♪
♪ With a pickle that likes dill ♪
♪ The frowny one's sour ♪
♪ He's a real bitter pill ♪
♪ She's so sweet ♪
♪ With her onion pet Pearl ♪
♪ Teaching pickles to fish ♪
♪ That's my crazy world ♪♪
(PICKLES HUMMING AND GURGLING)
(WHISTLE BLOWING)
I tell you, if only Flint liked fishing
as much as you guys.
Why am I talking to a pickle?
(SQUAWKS)
Dangerous food creatures detected.
Stay put.
We'll find and destroy them.
(CHUCKLES)
Barry!
You can't be here.
You better hide him.
FLINT:
Okay, gang! Today's the day
We find the FLDSMDFR.
Sam, I was thinking about
what you said last night--
BARRY:
N-woo?
What?
Me too.
Right. Listen, I have
been acting weird, but it's only
because I'm under a lot of pressure.
N-woo?
What?
So true!
FLINT: But I'm also doing this for us.
You see,
I still want Sparkswood
to happen, but it can't.
Not until I become
a great inventor like Chester V.
Flint, you don't have to
prove anything--
Ha, ha. Lockwood!
How goes the inventing?
Very good, sir. I was
up all night making this.
I call it the Flint Lockwood
Food Jungle
Topographical Pointing
Machine.
Or...
The FLFJTPM! Brilliant!
Oh, thank you, sir. Follow
the beam, find the machine.
(SQUAWKING)
All I have to do now
is cut the leg holes.
Ooh.
Huh. Well,
maybe it's better
here.
FLINT:
Great idea, Sam.
And, guys, you can help me by--
Excuse us. Your friends are
distracting you from our mission.
Distracting?
(CHUCKLES)
My chest hairs just
don't trust that Chester.
We should be hunting
the FLDSMDFR, not chitchatting.
But, sir, I--
You're heading into the deepest,
darkest part of the jungle.
You need to focus on
saving the world.
Be a hero.
Okay. You're right, sir.
Excellent! Let's go!
Okay, Barry, time to go home now.
Okay. Okay.
Okay, one more hug, Barry.
Barry?
Right! Barry.
You Barry.
Barry.
And I'm Sam Sparks.
(STAMMERING)
Saspa.
Right! Sam--
FLINT: Come on, Sam!
Coming!
Okay, Barry, time to go home now.
Now go.
Now you go on home.
Buh.
Bye.
Huh?
(OHIO EXPRESS' "YUMMY
YUMMY YUMMY" PLAYING)
Saspa
♪ Yummy, yummy, yummy
I got love in my tummy ♪
♪ And as silly as it may seem ♪
♪ The lovin' that you're givin'
is what keeps me livin' ♪
♪ And your love is like
Peaches and cream ♪
Hot dog. Hot dog.
♪ Kind of like sugar
Kind of like spices ♪
♪ Kind of like, like what you do ♪
♪ Kind of sounds funny ♪
♪ But you love honey ♪
♪ And, honey, I love you ♪♪
(CHITTERING)
(CREATURE SHRIEKS)
(HEAVY FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING)
(LEAVES RUSTLING)
(♪♪♪)
(GROWLING)
Tacodile! Supreme!
(ROARS)
Holy guacamole!
I got this, bro!
I'm okay!
Up there! Hurry, Sam!
(BARB SCREAMING)
Barb!
FLINT:
You okay?
Uh-huh.
Freeze!
Come on, let's go!
Let's get out of here!
(MANNY SPEAKS IN SPANISH)
Bravo, young Lockwood, bravo!
(MURMURING)
(SQUEALING)
(GROWLS)
(GASPS)
A mother?
FLINT:
Sam!
Saspa!
Butter.
Parkay.
Almost there.
The FLDSMDFR
should be just across
this syrup bog.
BRENT: This is syrup?
Syrup is my favorite.
Darn mosquitoasts!
CHESTER:
Don't worry, man-baby.
They, like all the other
abominable food monsters
will soon be no more.
SAM:
Wait, Flint!
What if we're making a big mistake?
Mistake?
About shutting off the FLDSMDFR.
Some of these creatures,
they're incredible.
CHESTER:
Incredibly
dangerous. We were just
attacked by a giant tacodile.
He's right, Sam. I mean, we were
almost eaten by a cheespider.
It doesn't mean we have
to destroy all of them.
Some of the food's
actually been friendly.
It is true. The dessert creatures
are especially sweet.
Okay. Maybe we-- Ah!
BARB:
Mosquitoast!
Was gonna bite you.
See? Even the tiniest creatures
are attacking us.
SAM:
The only reason they're
biting is because of the drop
in barometric pressure.
Bugs do that before a storm. And by
the look of those nimbostratus clouds--
(THUNDER RUMBLING)
CHESTER:
Miss Sparks, we are
not talking about the weather.
We are talking about food here.
Dangerous food that does not
have human emotion.
Food that is not friendly.
Food that cannot love!
SAM: Flint,
we should be studying
the food animals, not killing them.
What if he's wrong?
The choice is yours, son.
Live up to your full potential,
or walk away
and let the food monsters
destroy Lady Liberty.
Sam, finding that FLDSMDFR
and saving the world,
that's what matters.
Really?
Our opinion doesn't matter?
Of course it does!
Yes!
Yes, it matters.
But just not right now.
Uh-oh.
Wrong answer.
STEVE: Toast.
Yeah? Well, I guess
this doesn't matter either,
young Lockwood.
I'll just
see you back on the boat.
(♪♪♪)
Wait! Sam!
Wait, please!
No! No. Sam!
Come back!
Come back, Sam, no!
No, Sam!
Sam! Sam!
Sand!
Hey, Earl,
would you talk to her?
You bet I will.
Hey, Sam! Wait for me!
Adiós.
Sayonara.
Goodbye,
Señor Lockwood.
Bye, Flint.
Steve!
Et tu, Steve?
(♪♪♪)
Oh. What just happened?
CHESTER:
You've made
the right choice, son.
Sentinels! Keep them safe.
Butter.
CHESTER:
Ah, Young Lockwood,
we're getting close.
I feel it in my beard!
(♪♪♪)
FLINT:
Water goes in the top
and food comes out the bottom.
It's gotta be inside that
big rock candy mountain!
This is exactly why I wanted you
on this mission.
Sally forth, Lockwood.
(THUNDER CRASHES)
I can't believe Flint
is still listening to that guy!
Flint is naive. It appears
he is being manipulated
for some nefarious purpose.
Of course he is!
Sam! Freeze!
What?
EARL: Stay calm
and walk toward me
slowly.
Very slowly.
Oh, come on.
Now you're acting weird.
I'm in no mood for this.
(GROWLS)
(SCREAMS)
(ROARING)
Stop right there, cheese monster!
Nobody eats my friends
on my watch!
(EARL GRUNTING)
No, wait!
Chester's been lying to us
about these creatures,
and I am going to prove it.
EARL:
Sam, don't do it!
It's foodicide!
Danger! Danger! Danger!
Nice cheespider.
Ohh. Ugh.
Yellow.
Dude!
You got special-sauced!
(CHUCKLING)
It's Okay, guys.
See?
She's not mean.
She's just
a little beefy.
Whoa.
What's it doing?
I think she wants you
to scratch her buns.
Aw. I like that too.
Who's a good cheespider?
She's cute!
But why did she attack us before?
Because we were dressed
like them.
BRENT:
She doesn't like backpacks?
No. It appears she
doesn't like Live Corp.
The food creatures know something
we do not.
STEVE:
Gasp!
Who's Evel?
Not "Evel." Evil.
I knew it! Chester's
up to something terrible.
We have to warn Flint!
Let's ride!
Run!
SENTINEL:
You're not warning
anyone about anything.
Oh, crap balls.
(GROWLS)
Magnificent.
(♪♪♪)
FLINT:
The FLDSMDFR
must be up there.
(SPLASH)
A very unpleasant fall.
Finish the job, Lockwood.
Yes, sir.
Whoa. Ahh!
(FLINT GRUNTING)
(SIGHS)
Whoa! Oh!
Made it!
(FLINT GASPS)
(GRUNTS)
FLDSMDFR.
Look, I'm sorry
I have to do this to you
again.
But I can't let your swimming
cheespiders destroy Lady Liberty
or the world.
(MACHINE PULSATING)
Whoa.
MACHINE:
Marshmallow.
(BURBLING)
They're like
a family.
Sam was right.
This is a mistake.
(LAUGHING)
Oh, dear!
Sir! Uh, sir?
There it is.
Wait.
In all its glory.
Chester, look, I can't do this.
Oh, okay. I will.
What? Wait.
Chester, wait. We can't destroy it.
Ah!
Let go of me, Lockwood.
No, sir, I can't let you do this.
(BOTH GRUNTING)
No! No! No!
WOMAN (ON RECORDING):
Live Corp.
FLINT:
The BS-USB
reprogrammed it?
It was never gonna
turn off the machine.
A BS-USB?
Hello.
Your machine is what I wanted
all along.
You lied to me.
Of course I lied to you.
I knew you'd eventually fall
for these pathetic creatures.
But you were my idol.
My whole life, I looked up to you.
I wanted to be you!
Oh, Lockwood.
I was just using you
to get your invention.
We're ready.
Launch Operation Slice and Dice.
(CHUCKLING)
(HISSES)
And now that I've got what I want,
I no longer need you.
I'm afraid we're going
to have to let you go.
Wait, wait, wait.
No, no, please.
(SCREAMS)
(♪♪♪)
(HARMONICA PLAYING AND TIM LAUGHING)
(HISSING)
Whoa.
That's not natural.
No, no, no.
Easy, easy, you guys.
Don't cry.
(♪♪♪)
(TRUMPETS)
(YELLING)
Huh?
(SCREAMS)
Okay, Steve. If me and you put
our two brilliant minds together,
we will get out of here.
Steve?
Brent, do you ever get
the feeling that maybe Steve Lockwood
is just a monkey?
Why would you say that
about him, Earl?
Why would you ever say that?
Of course he's just a monkey.
How stupid are you people?
No one should ever put
any trust in a monkey.
Chester thinks
you're a monkey.
Well, I'm an ape.
Chester knows that.
But he calls you a monkey.
Ooh!
It is true, he does.
He's just joking around.
Chester's my best friend.
If Chester was really your friend,
would he still call you a monkey?
(♪♪♪)
MARSHMALLOW:
N-woo! N-woo!
(WHISTLES)
Flint.
Dad.
What's happening, son?
You look terrible.
What's with all of them?
They saved my life.
I let Chester steal the machine and now
he's starting Operation Slice and Dice.
Come on, son. You're really
not making any sense.
Look, Chester's gonna wipe out
all the foodimals.
My friends tried to
tell me they were good,
but I didn't listen.
Everything I touch just gets ruined.
BARRY: N-woo!
Barry?
N-woo!
Barry. I'm so sorry I misjudged you.
I should have listened to Sam.
Saspa. Sam.
What is it? What are you trying to say?
Saspa, Saspa.
Saspa!
Sa--
Saspa.
Sassy pants.
Dad.
Saspa, Saspa!
Sam and the gang?
Uh-huh. Uh-huh.
It looks like a Sentinel of Safety.
Aha! Sassy pants.
Sassy pants? No, Dad. He's saying
Sentinels captured Sam and the gang.
(SPEAKS GIBBERISH)
And they're being held in the factory?
We gotta get them out of there.
But how?
There's just two of us.
N-woo!
(ECHOING)
(RUMBLING)
N-woo!
N-woo! N-woo!
Hey, what's with all the "N-woos"?
Why do they have my TV?
Water goes in the top
and food comes out the bottom.
N-woo! N-woo!
What's it, broken or something?
What's it doing?
N-woo!
Here, you take it,
you take it.
FOODIMALS:
N-woo.
It's saying that I'm N-woo.
FOODIMALS: N-woo.
ALL:
N-woo. N-woo.
N-woo.
Look, Flint, they came here to help.
We all did.
It's time to let us.
Uh-huh.
Okay, I don't know
if you can understand me.
I know you think I'm N-woo.
But the truth
is I'm no N-woo,
I'm just a man.
A man who's made a lot of mistakes
in the last couple of days.
And now my friends are in
a lot of trouble, thanks to me.
(BARRY SPEAKING GIBBERISH)
Someone once told me
that I didn't need friends.
That I could accomplish more
by myself.
I know now more than ever
that he was wrong.
We need all the
friends we can get.
And I need your help.
All of you. Fruits,
vegetables and meat!
I need you to help me
to get into that
factory, save our friends
and get our home back!
(CHEERING)
Okay, now I just gotta figure out
how to get in there.
With the right rod and tackle,
I could cast you up
into that unfinished part
of the factory.
Should be a piece of cake.
Hm?
Dad, let's go fishing.
(TIM MYER'S "ALL OF US TOGETHER"
PLAYING)
♪ Go ♪
Wildebeets!
Meatballrus!
Go, go, go!
Watermelophant, do your thing!
♪ All of us together ♪
FLINT:
Spray-On Shoes.
Hair Un-Balder.
Grocery Deliverator.
Helmet.
♪ Life is so ♪
♪ Much better ♪
Got it.
♪ All of us together ♪
Ready when you are, Dad!
Ready, skipper, my boy.
♪ Go ♪
It's too heavy!
FLINT:
Whoa!
Here comes the cavalry.
FLINT:
No way! Subs!
Subwhales!
(GROANING)
TIM:
Prepare to release lure.
Hit it, Sweet.
♪ All of us together ♪
♪ Life is so much better ♪♪
Catch the big one, buddy.
Yes!
Uhh... We have a problem.
N-woo, in here.
(GROANS)
(♪♪♪)
FLINT:
What's going on?
(BERRIES MURMURING)
Sam's backpack.
They were here!
(CHEESPIDER GROWLING)
(FLINT SCREAMS)
(WHIMPERING)
Good cheespider.
Saspa?
(SPEAKS GIBBERISH)
Got it, Barry.
Thanks, cheespider.
N-woo!
(BERRIES WHIMPERING)
Barry, use the Grocery Deliverator
to save your friends.
I'll go save mine.
Uh-huh.
(SCREAMS)
(SPEAKS GIBBERISH)
Ah!
There's a leek in my boat.
(LEEK YELLS)
Flint!
Go, go, go!
Hey,
freeze!
Uh-oh.
Food fight!
(♪♪♪)
Crab cakes!
Oh!
Run!
Oh! Oh!
I'm all cheesed up.
(SCREAMS)
Retreat!
(2 UNLIMITED'S "GET READY
FOR THIS (YAR REMIX)" PLAYING)
SUIT:
Head scan complete.
♪ Y'all ready for this? ♪♪
(SCREAMS)
(GIGGLING)
Lockwood?
You're still alive?
That's right. Hands up.
Give me back my friends.
Of course!
I have them right here.
Hey, Flint.
Sam! Guys!
Chester, let them go!
Don't worry, Lockwood,
I'll let them go.
Right into my super-sized
Food Bar machine.
ALL:
Food Bars?
Food Bars? You're going
to turn them into Food Bars?
Yes, Food Bars.
The lifeblood of my company.
I learned your FLDSMDFR food
is far more delicious than "food" food.
So using your foodimals
as ingredients
would make my products
super-delicious!
I had to have your invention.
Unfortunately,
I couldn't find it.
Until you helped me.
(GASPS)
FLINT: FLDSMDFR!
MACHINE:
Watermelon!
(WHIMPERING)
You're a monster!
Those are living creatures.
Yes, that's the problem.
Food with legs
is much harder to catch.
They hide, they fight back,
they want to live. Ugh.
But now that I control
your FLDSMDFR,
I can pave your island
and work in complete secrecy.
Live Corp will remain
the coolest, hippest company
in the world
with a new Food Bar version
8.0!
I never should have believed in you.
Yes, that was quite foolish.
Now if you want your friends back,
I suggest you drop your cans.
Don't do it, Flint!
Save the island!
But you are my island.
Ew. Okay, first, shut up.
Then drop the cans
or I drop your friends.
Okay, okay. There.
Oh, no, Flint. This is embarrassing.
I changed my mind.
Please understand
I can't leave any witnesses.
(GROANS)
Barb, grind them.
But, sir, I didn't think we were going to--
This is why I work alone.
Monkey!
You are dismissed.
And now, without
further ado.
Flint, hurry!
Why won't this go faster?
Give me that controller!
Sure, come and get it.
(LAUGHING)
But which one of us has it?
Is it me?
Or me?
FLINT:
Oh!
SAM:
Earl,
can't you break us out of here?
Yellow police tape!
The one thing I can't break.
(GRUNTING)
Forkenknifenspooninator!
Sam, guys, listen.
Invisible coffee table!
I'm sorry I was such an idiot.
Flint, that's true,
but now may not be the time!
Please let me finish.
I took you all for granted.
I should have listened to you.
Okay, go on. But hurry!
The truth is I need each
and every one of you guys.
You're more than my friends.
You're my family. Oh!
How sweet. Note to self:
Put that on their tombstones.
Good one, Chester!
Don't you see, young Lockwood?
These friends are the reason
you keep losing.
Well, it's better than ending up
alone like you.
Ha, ha, I'm not alone!
I've got holograms!
Flint! Why don't you throw him
a party?
ALL:
We love parties.
Party?
Party!
ALL:
Party's over, Lockwood.
FLINT:
No!
Not yet.
I think it's time to celebrate!
(SHRIEKS)
No!
Celebrate!
Yes!
(OVER SPEAKERS)
♪ He's a real baboon ♪
Ow.
Thanks, lab partner.
Helping!
♪ It's time to party now
Party now ♪♪
FLINT:
Guys, I'm
so sorry for being such a--
Chester!
Okay, I guess I deserve that.
No, Flint!
Chester!
(♪♪♪)
I've got what I want.
Enjoy your friends, Lockwood.
FLINT:
No! No!
Don't do this!
Ha, ha. Oh!
Heh, heh. Uh-uh.
Food!
(ROARS)
Anybody gonna be keeping
folks safe in this town, it's me.
Ba-gawk-oh!
Tacodile supreme.
(ROARS)
It's over, Chester.
Mustache!
Now hand over the FLDSMDFR.
No! Never!
FLINT:
Chester,
there's nowhere to go.
That's what you think.
Save me, monkey!
Rm an ape!
Bad monkey! Give that back!
Bad monk--!
(CHESTER YELLING)
My holograms! Save me!
HOLOGRAM 1:
We're here for you.
HOLOGRAM 2: You're going to be fine.
HOLOGRAM 3: We'll save you.
You see, Flint?
With my holograms--
Oh, fudge.
I saved myself.
(BELCHES)
Ugh.
That will leave a bad taste
in your mouth.
Ugh.
BARB: Ahem.
Uh... I believe this belongs to you.
(♪♪♪)
Here you go, pal.
Gosh, I hope this works.
(MACHINE POWERING UP)
MACHINE:
Pickle.
Cheeseburger.
Leek. Strawberry.
Lemon.
Yes! Ha, ha!
Banana.
(♪♪♪)
(SCREAMING)
It's enough to make a
grown man cry.
And that's okay.
You go right ahead, tear.
(GROWLS)
Guys,
do you think we could still
work together?
I think we will work great together.
Come on,
bring it on in, Barb.
(♪♪♪)
(LAUGHING)
Aw, this is nice.
Ape!
Monkey.
I'm proud of you, son.
Thanks, Dad.
But there's one last thing
I need to do.
Okay, now, son.
Now, once you put it on like that,
all you have to do is cast it.
So like this?
Ehh.
No, no, no.
Here, let me show you how.
See, it's all in the wrist.
Like this.
Whoo! Catch
the big one, boy.
Am I fishing?
Yup.
I'm fishing!
Whoa, whoa! You've got a live one.
Now reel him in, Flint.
That's it. Steady, steady.
Oh. He's a fighter!
Ah! I got one!
I got one, Dad!
Okay.
Can we do this again?
Like all the time?
You betcha, skipper.
(LAUGHS)I
Sam, guys, I caught my first fish!
Yay!
Whoo! Way to go, Flint!
EARL:
Flint Lockwood, you are a fisherman.
STEVE:
Happy.
BRENT:
Hey, look, rainbows!
(♪♪♪)
(CODY SIMPSON'S "LA DA DEE" PLAYING)
♪ There's no way to say this song's
About someone else ♪
♪ Every time you're not in my arms
I start to lose myself ♪
♪ Someone please pass me my shades
Don't let them see me down ♪
♪ You have taken over my days ♪
♪ So tonight I'm going out ♪
♪ Yet I'm feeling like ♪
♪ There is no better place
Than right by your side ♪
♪ I had a little taste ♪
MACHINE:
Strawberry.
♪ And I'll only spoil
the party anyway ♪
♪ 'Cause all the girls
are looking fine ♪
♪ But you're the only
one on my mind ♪
♪ La da dee
La da dee doo ♪
♪ La da da me
La da da you ♪
♪ La da dee ♪
♪ La da dee doo ♪
♪ There's only me
There's only you ♪
♪ La da dee
La da dee doo ♪
♪ La da da me
La da da you ♪
♪ La da dee
La da dee doo ♪
♪ When you were gone I think of you ♪
♪ All these places packed with people ♪
♪ But your face is all I see ♪
♪ And the music's way too loud ♪
♪ But your voice won't let me be ♪
♪ So many pretty girls around ♪
♪ They're just dressing to impress ♪
♪ But the thought of you alone
Has got me spun ♪
♪ And I don't know what to say next ♪
♪ Yet I'm feeling like ♪
♪ There is no better place
Than right by your side ♪
♪ I had a little taste ♪
♪ And I'll only spoil
the party anyway ♪
♪ 'Cause all the girls
are looking fine ♪
♪ But you're the only one on my mind ♪
♪ La da dee
La da dee doo ♪
♪ La da da me
La da da you ♪
♪ La da dee
La da dee doo ♪
♪ There's only me
There's only you ♪
♪ La da dee
La da dee doo ♪
♪ La da da me
La da da you ♪
♪ La da dee
La da dee doo ♪
♪ When you were gone I think of you ♪
♪ There's no way to say this song's
About someone else ♪
♪ Every time you're not in my arms ♪
♪ I start to lose myself ♪
♪ Someone please pass me my shades
Don't let 'em see me down ♪
Uh-oh.
♪ You have taken over my days ♪
♪ So tonight I'm going out ♪
♪ Yet I'm feeling like ♪
♪ There is no better place
Than right by your side ♪
♪ I had a little taste ♪
♪ And I'll only spoil
the party anyway ♪
♪ 'Cause all the girls
are looking fine ♪
♪ But you're the only one on my mind ♪
♪ La da dee
La da dee doo ♪
♪ La da da me
La da da you ♪
♪ La da dee
La da dee doo ♪
♪ There's only me
There's only you ♪
♪ La da dee
La da dee doo ♪
♪ La da da me
La da da you ♪
♪ La da dee ♪
♪ La da dee doo ♪
♪ When you were gone I think of you ♪
♪ La da dee ♪
♪ La da dee doo ♪
♪ La da da me
La da da you ♪
♪ La da dee
La da dee doo ♪
♪ There's only me
There's only you ♪
♪ La da dee
La da dee doo ♪
♪ La da da me
La da da you ♪
♪ La da dee
La da dee doo ♪
♪ When you were gone I think of you ♪
♪ I pretend the night is so beautiful ♪
♪ Take a photo with the bros ♪
♪ La dadee La da da doo ♪
♪ They won't see
Through my disguise ♪
♪ Right here behind my eyes ♪
♪ Replaying in my mind ♪
♪ La dee da ♪
♪ Yet I'm feeling like ♪
♪ There is no better place
Than right by your side ♪
♪ I had a little taste ♪
♪ And I'll only spoil
the party anyway ♪
♪ 'Cause all the girls
are looking fine ♪
♪ But you're the only one on my mind ♪
(SPEAKING GIBBERISH)
(AUDIENCE LAUGHING)
♪ La da dee
La da dee doo ♪
♪ La da da me
La da da you ♪
♪ La da dee
La da dee doo ♪
♪ There's only me
There's only you ♪
♪ La da dee
La da dee doo ♪
♪ La da da me
La da da you ♪
♪ La da dee
La da dee doo ♪
♪ When you were gone I think of you ♪
♪ La da dee
La da dee doo ♪
♪ La da da me-- ♪
(♪♪♪)
(SCREAMING)
♪ La da dee
La da dee doo ♪
♪ La da da me
La da da you ♪
♪ La da dee
La da dee doo ♪
♪ When you were gone I think of you ♪
♪ La da dee
La da dee doo ♪
♪ La da da me
La da da you ♪
♪ La da dee
La da dee doo ♪
♪ When you were gone I think of you ♪♪
(STEVE CHITTERING)
(♪♪♪)
Hi, Steve.
Hello, Steven. I'm Barb.
So do you wanna
go get coffee sometime?
Dinner!
Even better!
(BARB GIGGLES AND STEVE SHRIEKS)
(PAUL MCCARTNEY'S "NEW" PLAYING)
♪ Don't look at me
It's way too soon to see ♪
♪ What's gonna be
Don't look at me ♪
♪ All my life
I never knew ♪
♪ What I could be
What I could do ♪
♪ Then we were new ♪
♪ You came along
And made my life a song ♪
♪ One lucky day
You came along ♪
♪ Just in time ♪
♪ Well, I was searching for a rock
You came along ♪
♪ Then we were new ♪
♪ We can do what we want
We can live as we choose ♪
♪ You see there's no guarantee
We got nothing to lose ♪
♪ Don't look at me
I can't deny the truth ♪
♪ It's plain to see
Don't look at me ♪
♪ All my life
I never knew ♪
♪ What I could be
What I could do ♪
♪ Then we were new ♪
♪ We can do what we want
We can live as we choose ♪
♪ You see there's no guarantee
We've got nothing to lose ♪
♪ Don't look at me
It's way too soon to see ♪
♪ What's gonna be
Don't look at me ♪
♪ All my life
I never knew ♪
♪ What I could be
What I could do ♪
♪ Then we were new ♪
♪ Now we are new ♪♪
(♪♪♪)
Please rate this subtitle at www.osdb.link/eu76
Help other users to choose the best subtitles