(BOBINSKY COUNTING IN RUSSIAN)
(CAR HONKING)
(BOBINSKY CURSES IN RUSSIAN)
MOVER: We're here!
Time to muscle up.
(BOTH GRUNT)
(GIGGLES)
(GROANS)
(DOOR CREAKING)
(PEBBLES CLATTERING)
Hello?
CORALINE: Who's there?
(CAT SCREECHES)
(GASPS)
(PANTING)
(MEOWS)
(SCREAMS)
You scared me to death,
you mangy thing.
I'm just looking for
an old well. Know it?
Not talking, huh?
Magic dowser,
magic dowser...
(THUNDER RUMBLING)
Show me the well!
(HONKING)
(SCREAMING)
Get away from me!
(CORALINE GRUNTS)
Ooh.
Let me guess.
You're from Texas or Utah,
someplace dried-out
and barren, right?
I heard about
water witching before,
but it doesn't make sense.
I mean, it's just
an ordinary branch.
It's a dowsing rod.
Ow!
And I don't like
being stalked,
not by psycho nerds
or their cats!
He's not really my cat.
He's kind of feral.
You know, wild.
Of course,
I do feed him every night,
and sometimes
he'll come to my window
and bring me
little dead things.
Look, I'm from Pontiac.
Huh?
Michigan.
And if I'm a water witch,
then where's
the secret well?
You stomp too hard
and you'll fall in it.
Oh!
See?
(HOLLOW THUDDING)
It's supposed to be so deep,
if you fell to the bottom
and looked up,
you'd see a sky full of stars
in the middle of the day.
Ha.
Surprised she
let you move in.
My gramma, she owns
the Pink Palace.
Won't rent to
people with kids.
What do you mean?
(STAMMERING)
I'm not supposed
to talk about it.
I'm Wybie.
Wybie Lovat.
Wybie?
Short for Wyborne.
Not my idea,
of course.
What'd you
get saddled with?
I wasn't saddled
with anything.
It's Coraline.
Caroline what?
Coraline.
Coraline Jones.
(SCOFFS)
It's not
real scientific,
but I heard
an ordinary name
like Caroline
can lead people to have
ordinary expectations
about a person.
(GRUMBLING)
LOVAT: Wyborne!
I think I heard
someone calling you, Wyborne.
What?
I didn't hear anything.
I definitely heard someone,
Why-Were-You-Born.
LOVAT: Wyborne!
Grandma!
(CHUCKLES UNCOMFORTABLY)
Well, great to meet
a Michigan water witch,
but I'd wear
gloves next time.
Why?
'Cause that
dowsing rod of yours,
it's poison oak.
(EXCLAIMS)
(BLOWING RASPBERRY)
(SPLASHING)
I almost fell down
a well yesterday, Mom.
Uh-huh.
I would've died.
That's nice.
Hmm.
So, can I go out?
I think it's perfect
weather for gardening.
No, Coraline.
Rain makes mud.
Mud makes a mess.
But, Mom,
I want stuff growing
when my friends
come to visit.
Isn't that why
we moved here?
Something like that.
But then
we had the accident.
It wasn't my fault
you hit that truck.
I never said it was.
I can't believe it.
You and Dad get paid
to write about plants,
and you hate dirt.
Coraline, I don't have time
for you right now,
and you still
have unpacking to do.
Lots of unpacking.
That sounds exciting!
Oh. Some kid left this
on the front porch.
WYBIE: Hey, Jonesy.
Look what I found
in Gramma's trunk.
Look familiar? Wybie.
(GROANS)
CORALINE: Huh.
A little me? That's weird.
What's his name,
anyway?
Wybie. And I'm way
too old for dolls.
Hey, Dad.
How's the writing going?
Dad!
Hello, Coraline
and Coraline doll.
Do you know where
the garden tools are?
It's... It's pouring
out there, isn't it?
(SCOFFS)
It's just raining.
What'd the boss say?
"Don't even think
about going out,
Coraline Jones!"
Then you won't
need the tools.
(GROANS)
(SQUEAKS)
(SQUEAKING)
(GROANS)
You know, this house
is 150 years old.
So?
So explore it.
Go out and count all
the doors and windows
and write that down on...
List everything
that's blue.
Just let me work.
(TYPING)
Ew!
(EXCLAIMS)
(SQUEAKS)
(SCREAMING)
No. No, no, no. No.
One boring blue boy
in a painfully
boring painting.
Four incredibly
boring windows
and no more doors.
All right, little me.
Where are you hiding?
Huh?
Hey, Mom.
Where does this door go?
I'm really, really busy.
CORALINE: I think it's locked.
CORALINE: Please!
(GROANS)
Will you stop pestering me
if I do this for you?
(WHIMPERING)
Fine.
Bricks?
I don't get it.
They must've closed
this off when they
divided up the house.
You're kidding.
And why is the door so small?
We made a deal!
Zip it!
You didn't lock it.
(MOM EXCLAIMING
IN FRUSTRATION)
(SINGING)
Oh, my twitchy-witchy girl
I think you are so nice
I give you bowls of porridge
And I give you
bowls of ice cream
(GROANS IN DISGUST)
Why don't you
ever cook, Mom?
Coraline, we've been
through this before.
Your dad cooks,
I clean, and you
stay out of the way.
I swear I'll go
food shopping soon as
we finish the catalog.
Try some of the chard.
You need a vegetable.
It looks more
like slime to me.
Well, it's slime
or bedtime, fusspot.
Now what's it gonna be?
Think they're
trying to poison me?
(SIGHS)
Don't forget about me, guys.
Okay?
Good night, little me.
(MOUSE SQUEAKING)
(CONTINUES SQUEAKING)
(CORALINE GASPS)
Whoa!
Huh?
Mmm. Something smells good.
(OTHER MOTHER HUMMING)
Mom? What are you doing here
in the middle of the night?
You're just in time
for supper, dear.
You're not my mother.
My mother doesn't have...
(STAMMERS)
(MIMICS STAMMERING)
Buttons? Do you like them?
I'm your other mother, silly.
Now go tell your other father
that supper's ready.
Well, go on.
He's in his study.
CORALINE: Hello?
Hello, Coraline.
Wanna hear my new song?
My father
can't play piano.
No need to.
This piano plays me.
(EXCLAIMS IN SURPRISE)
(SINGING) Making up
a song about Coraline
She's a peach, she's a doll
She's a pal of mine
She's as cute as a button
in the eyes of everyone
Who ever laid
their eyes on Coraline
When she comes
around exploring
Mom and I will never,
ever make it boring
Our eyes will be on Coraline
I'm sorry,
but she said to tell
you the food's ready.
Mmm.
Who's starving?
Raise your hand.
Whoa!
(CLEARS THROAT)
We give our thanks
and ask to bless
our mother's
golden chicken breast.
(OTHER FATHER LAUGHING)
Mmm!
CORALINE:
This chicken is good.
Hungry, aren't you?
Do you have any gravy?
Well, here comes
the gravy train.
Choo, choo!
Huh.
Another roll? Sweet peas?
Corn on the cob?
I'm real thirsty.
Of course.
Any requests?
Mango milkshake?
Home?
We've been waiting
for you, Coraline.
For me?
OTHER FATHER: Yep.
Wasn't the same here
without you, kiddo.
I didn't know I
had another mother.
Of course you do.
Everyone does.
Really?
OTHER MOTHER: Uh-huh.
And soon as
you're through eating,
I thought we'd play a game.
You mean like hide-and-seek?
Perfect.
Hide-and-seek in the rain.
What rain?
(EXCLAIMS IN SURPRISE)
What about the mud?
We love mud here.
Mud facials,
mud baths, mud pies.
It's great
for poison oak.
How'd you know I...
I... I'd love to play,
but I better get
home to my other mother.
But I'm your other mother.
I mean my other,
other mother.
Mom number one?
(EXCLAIMS)
I think I should
get to bed.
Of course, sweetheart.
It's all made up.
But...
Come along, sleepyhead.
(CORALINE GASPS)
Wow.
DRAGONFLY: Hello, Coraline.
DRAGONFLIES: Hello, hello,
hello, hello.
What's shaking, baby?
Hello.
GIRL: Hey.
How's it going, Loper?
Where's your
swampers and chook?
Cripes almighty!
How are my best trolls?
I can't wait till summer.
You're both coming, right?
We're already here,
Coraline.
Gone to Oregon.
CORALINE: Oh.
The mud.
See you soon.
(YAWNS)
It's gone.
My poison oak! It's gone!
Huh.
(KETTLE WHISTLING)
It was incredibly real, Mom.
Only you weren't
really you.
You were
my other mother.
Buttons for
eyes, huh?
Coraline, you only dreamed
you ate all that chicken.
Take your
multivitamin at least.
You were in
the dream, too, Dad.
You had wild-looking pajamas
and orange monkey slippers.
(LAUGHS)
Orange?
My monkey slippers are blue.
Psst.
Can you get me
some of that magic mud
you were talking about?
Because I have
a terrible case
of writer's rash on my...
(MOM CLEARS THROAT)
If the real Charlie Jones
wants his pages edited,
he better wrap them up ASAP.
Coraline,
why don't you go
visit downstairs?
I bet those actresses
would love to
hear your dream.
Miss Spink and Forcible?
But you said
they're dingbats.
Mmm-hmm.
Bobinsky. Bobinsky. Bobinsky.
(SNIFFS)
(GROANS)
(EXCLAIMS IN DISGUST)
Hello?
I think our mail
got mixed up.
Should I leave
it outside, or...
(EXCLAIMS)
(CLUCKING)
CORALINE: Hmm.
Secret!
(GASPS)
Famous jumping
mouse circus not ready,
little girl.
Circus?
Oh, uh...
I brought this for you.
(SNIFFING)
(SIGHS CONTENTEDLY)
(SPEAKING RUSSIAN)
Huh?
New cheese samples.
(BOBINSKY GRUNTS)
Very clever using this mix-up
to sneak my home
and peek at mooshkas?
Mooshkas?
The mice!
Oh!
Sorry. I'm Coraline Jones.
And I am
the Amazing Bobinsky.
But you call me Mr. B
because amazing I
already know that I am.
(GRUNTS)
(GASPS)
Ha!
You see, Caroline,
the problem is...
My new songs go
oompah, oompah,
but the jumping mice
play only toodle-toot,
like that.
Is nice but not
so much amazing.
So now,
I switch to stronger cheese
and soon, watch out!
Here, have beet.
Make you strong.
Do svidaniya, Caroline.
Coraline.
Oompah, oompah.
Toodle-toot.
Hey, Caroline!
(SPEAKING RUSSIAN)
Wait!
No!
(BOBINSKY GRUNTS)
The mice asked me
to give you message.
The jumping mice?
They are saying
do not go
through little door.
Do you know such a thing?
The one behind the wallpaper?
But it's all bricked up.
Bah.
So sorry. Is nothing.
Sometimes the mice
are little mixed-up.
(GRUNTS)
They even get your
name wrong, you know?
They call you Coraline
instead of Caroline.
Not Caroline at all.
Maybe I work them too hard.
(DOGS BARKING)
Cease your
infernal yapping.
How nice to see you,
Caroline.
Would you like
to come in?
We're playing cards.
Still Coraline,
Miss Spink.
Miriam!
Put the kettle on!
April, I think
you're being followed.
It's the new neighbor,
Miriam. Caroline.
SPINK: She'll be having
the oolong tea.
FORCIBLE: No! Oh, no, no.
I'm sure she'd
prefer jasmine.
No, oolong.
Ah. Jasmine it is, then.
(SIGHS)
Come on, boys.
Are those dogs real?
Our sweet departed angels.
Couldn't bear to
part with them,
so we had them stuffed.
SPINK: Now, there's
Hamish the third...
Go on. Have one.
It's hand-pulled
taffy from Brighton.
Best in the world.
SPINK... the third,
the ninth, yes.
The fourth, I'm right.
And Jock Jr., Jock Sr.,
Jock the third, the fourth,
and that's
Jock's second cousin
thrice removed.
I'll read them
if you like.
Read what?
Your tea leaves, dear.
They'll tell me your future.
Drink up then. Go on.
No, not all of it.
Not all of it.
That's right.
Now hand it over.
Oh!
Oh, Caroline.
Caroline, Caroline, Caroline.
You are in
terrible danger.
Oh, give me
that cup, April.
Your eyes are going.
My eyes?
You're blind as a bat.
Well, not to worry, child.
It's good news.
There's a tall,
handsome beast
in your future.
A what?
Miriam, really.
You're holding it wrong.
See? Danger.
CORALINE: What do you see?
SPINK: I see
a very peculiar hand.
FORCIBLE: I see a giraffe.
Giraffes don't just
fall from the sky, Miriam.
Oh, Lord.
(DOG YIPS)
Well, what should I do?
Never wear green in
your dressing room.
Acquire a very
tall stepladder.
And be very, very careful.
(GASPS)
Now, was there something
you came to tell us?
No. I guess not.
Thanks for the tea, though.
FORCIBLE: Toodle-oo.
SPINK: Cheery-bye.
FORCIBLE: Do you have any
nice queens for Mummy?
(DOG YIPS)
Danger?
(RATTLES)
(EXCLAIMS)
Great! The village stalker.
Ow!
I wasn't stalking you.
We're hunting banana slugs.
What do you mean "we?"
(CAT MEOWS)
Ha! Your cat's not wild.
He's a wuss puss.
What? He hates to
get his feet wet. Jeez.
Wuss puss.
So, that doll.
Did you make it
look like me?
Oh, no. I found it that way.
It's older than Grandma.
Old as this house,
probably.
Come on. Blue hair,
my swampers and raincoat?
Dang! Check out Slugzilla.
You're just like them.
Huh?
I meant my parents.
They don't
listen to me either.
Uh-huh. You mind?
(MIMICS CHOMPING)
(GRUNTS)
(SCREAMS)
Hmm.
Ew!
You know,
I've never been inside
the Pink Palace.
You're kidding.
Grandma'd kill me.
Thinks it's dangerous
or something.
Dangerous?
Well, she had
a twin sister.
So?
When they were kids,
Grandma's sister
disappeared.
She says
she was stolen.
CORALINE: Stolen?
(MEOWS)
Well, what do you think?
I don't know.
Maybe she just ran away.
LOVAT: Wyborne!
Look, I gotta go.
Wait a minute.
(SQUEAKS)
(OTHER MOTHER HUMMING)
Welcome back, darling.
Hi.
So thoughtful of you
to send this nice cheddar,
Coraline.
Cheddar? Oh!
The mice bait.
Would you go
fetch your father?
I bet he's hungry
as a pumpkin by now.
You mean my other father.
Your better father, dear.
He's out in the garden.
But my parents don't
have time to garden.
(SHUSHING)
Mmm!
Go on.
(CORALINE GASPS)
(LAUGHS)
Hey.
I love your garden!
Our garden, Coraline.
(LAUGHING)
Stop tickling me!
Daughter in distress.
Tickle no more,
you dragon snappers.
Well, she says
it's time for dinner,
breakfast, food.
Hop on, kiddo.
I wanna show you something.
CORALINE: I can't believe
you did this.
OTHER FATHER:
Mother said you'd like it.
Boy, she knows you
like the back of her hand.
Mmm. So good.
I love
dinner-breakfast-food.
Coraline,
Mr. Bobinsky
has invited you
to come see
the jumping mice
perform after dinner.
Really?
That know-it-all Wybie
said it was all
in Mr. B's head.
I knew he was wrong.
Well, everything's
right in this world, kiddo.
Your father and
I will clean up
while you and your
friend head upstairs.
My friend?
CORALINE:
Great. Another Wybie.
Hello,
Why-Were-You-Born.
CORALINE: Hello!
I thought you'd like him more
if he spoke a little less.
So I fixed him.
So he can't talk at all?
Nope.
Hmm.
I like it.
Now, run along,
you two, and have fun.
You're awful cheerful
considering you
can't say anything.
It didn't hurt,
did it, when she...
(LAUGHS)
CORALINE: Whoa!
CORALINE: Cool!
(CLUCKING)
(CANNONS BOOMING)
CORALINE: Look at you!
(CORALINE LAUGHS)
OTHER BOBINSKY: Lady
and gentleman, for to
tickle your eyes and ears
and making hearts to thump,
I, Sergei Alexander Bobinsky,
am introducing
my astoundishing,
stupendulous and amazing
jumping mouse circus!
My name!
(FANFARE PLAYING)
(CIRCUS MUSIC PLAYING)
It's wonderful, Wybie.
Wow!
Yahoo!
That was great!
Very, very thank you,
lady and gentleman.
We loved it, Mr. B.
It was so... So...
Ah...
Amazing!
You are very welcome
anytime you like.
You and also your
good friend there.
Do svedaniya, Coraline.
(KISSES)
(GROANS)
(GRUNTS)
CORALINE: There were
garden squash like
balloon animals
and snapdragons.
Oh, and upstairs,
I saw a real mouse circus.
Not pretend like
the crazy man's
in our house.
You sure
you won't come?
Don't fret, Charlie.
They'll love
the new catalog.
At least they'll
love my chapters.
I did not call
him crazy, Coraline.
He's drunk.
Well, I guess I'll see you
around, you dizzy dreamer.
Dad! I'm not five anymore.
(GEARS CRANKING)
(EXCLAIMS IN SURPRISE)
My kingdom for a horse!
(CRASHING)
Put them back.
But, Mom,
the whole school's
gonna wear
boring gray clothes.
No one will have these.
Put them back.
My other mother
would get them.
Maybe she should
buy all your clothes.
CORALINE: So what do you think
is in the other apartment?
I don't know.
Not a family of
Jones imposters.
Then why'd you
lock the door?
I found some rat crap,
and I thought
you'd feel safer.
They're jumping mice, Mom,
and the dreams
aren't dangerous.
They're the most fun
I've had since
we've moved here.
Your school
might be fun.
With those stupid uniforms?
Right.
Had to give it a try.
How do you feel
about a mustard,
ketchup, salsa
wrap for lunch?
Are you kidding me?
Had to go food shopping,
anyway.
Dad's planning
something special.
Grossgusting.
You wanna come along?
You can pick out
something you like.
Oh. Like the gloves.
(SIGHS)
Look, Coraline,
if things go well today,
I promise I'll make it up.
That's what
you always say.
Won't be long.
But I might be.
I knew it was real.
(PURRS)
OTHER MOTHER:
Dearest Coraline,
Miss Spink and Miss Forcible
have invited you
downstairs after lunch.
I hope you like
the new outfit I made you.
Love, Mother.
(BURPS)
(CAT MEOWS)
Wybie's got a cat
like you at home.
(MEOWS)
Not the quiet Wybie.
The one that talks too much.
You must be the other cat.
No, I'm not
the other anything. I'm me.
Um... I can see you
don't have button eyes,
but if you're the same cat,
how can you talk?
I just can.
Cats don't talk at home.
No?
Nope.
Well, you're clearly
the expert on these things.
After all,
I'm just a big fat wuss puss.
Come back. Please?
I'm sorry I called you that.
I really am.
How'd you get here?
I've been coming
here for a while.
It's a game we play.
She hates cats and
tries to keep me out,
but she can't, of course.
I come and go
as I please.
The other mother
hates cats?
Not like any mother
I've ever known.
What do you mean?
She's amazing.
You probably think this world
is a dream come true,
but you're wrong.
The other Wybie told me so.
That's nonsense.
He can't talk.
Perhaps not to you.
We cats, however,
have far superior senses
than humans,
and can see and smell and...
Shh!
I hear something.
Right over...
(MEOWS)
(SNIFFING)
(ORCHESTRA TUNING)
Hey, Wybie.
(MUSIC PLAYING)
She's practically naked!
(SINGING)
I'm known as the siren
of all seven seas
The breaker of
hearts by the bay
So if you go swimming
With bowlegged women
I might steal
your weak heart away
(DOGS BARKING)
Oh, my God.
(SINGING)
A big-bottomed sea witch
May bob through the waves
And hope to
lead sailors astray
But a true ocean goddess
Must fill out her bodice
To present
an alluring display
(DOGS BARKING)
Beware of old oysters
too large in the chest
Let's banish them
from the buffet
I'm far more nutritious
You smell like
the fishes
Did I hear a banshee?
You're sea green
with envy
This mermaid enchantress
No, I, Birth of Venus
BOTH: Will send
sailors swooning...
(SCREAMS IN PAIN)
Will send sailors
swooning all day
(BOTH EXCLAIMING)
(DOGS BARKING)
I can't look.
Ready to break
a leg, Miriam?
Our lives for
the theater, April.
(DOGS BARKING)
OTHER FORCIBLE: "What
a piece of work is man!
"How noble in reason!"
OTHER SPINK:
"How infinite in faculty."
"In form, in moving
how express and admirable!"
"In action
like an angel."
OTHER SPINK:
"In apprehension
how like a god!"
(SCREAMS)
OTHER FORCIBLE:
"The beauty of the world!"
(CORALINE LAUGHING)
OTHER SPINK:
"The paragon of animals!"
Yeah!
(SCREAMING)
(LAUGHING)
(DOGS BARKING)
Hey, there.
Was it wonderful, dear?
Oh, yeah. They swooped down
and pulled me
right out of my seat,
Spink and Forcible,
only they weren't old ladies.
That was
just a disguise.
But then, I was flying
through the air, and it was...
It was magic.
You do like it here,
don't you, Coraline?
Uh-huh.
Good night, Wybie.
You could stay here
forever if you want to.
Really?
Sure.
We'll sing and play games,
and Mother will cook
your favorite meals.
There's one tiny
little thing we need to do.
What's that?
Well, it's a surprise.
For you,
our little doll.
OTHER MOTHER:
Black is traditional.
But if you'd prefer pink
or vermillion
or chartreuse...
OTHER MOTHER: Though you might
make me jealous.
No way!
You're not sewing
buttons in my eyes!
But we need a "yes"
if you want to stay here.
So sharp
you won't feel a...
Ow!
There, now.
It's your decision,
darling.
We only want
what's best for you.
I'm going to bed.
Right now!
Bed?
Before dinner?
I'm really,
really tired. Yeah.
(YAWNING)
I just need to
sleep on things.
Well, of course
you do, darling.
I'll be happy
to tuck you in.
Oh, no, thanks.
You've done so much already.
You're welcome. And I...
We aren't worried
at all, darling.
OTHER MOTHER: Soon you'll
see things our way.
DRAGONFLIES:
What's wrong, Coraline?
Don't you wanna play?
Yeah! I wanna hug your face!
GIRAFFE DOLL:
Get a grip, soldier!
GIRL: Hey!
BOY: Hey!
Where's your buttons,
Loper?
You want to stay,
don't you?
Going home tonight, robots,
and I won't be back.
Go to sleep.
Go to sleep. Go to sleep.
OTHER MOTHER: A tiny
little thing we need to do.
CORALINE: Go to sleep.
Go to sleep. Go to sleep.
OTHER FATHER: So sharp
you won't feel a thing.
CORALINE:
Go to sleep. Go to sleep.
OTHER MOTHER: Soon
you'll see things our way.
Mom! Dad!
(GASPS)
Oh, God. I'm still here?
(PIANO PLAYING)
Hey, you!
CORALINE:
Where's the other mother?
I wanna go home.
All will be swell,
soon as Mother's refreshed.
Her strength is our strength.
Mustn't talk when
Mother's not here.
If you won't even
talk to me,
I'm gonna find
the other Wybie.
He'll help me.
No point.
He pulled a long face,
and Mother didn't like it.
(GRUNTS)
(GASPS)
(CAT MEOWS)
And what do you
think you're doing?
Well, I'm getting
out of here.
That's what I'm doing.
Huh?
Something's wrong.
Shouldn't
the old well be here?
Nothing out here.
It's the empty
part of this world.
She only made
what she knew
would impress you.
But why?
Why does she want me?
She wants
something to love, I think.
Something
that isn't her.
Or maybe she'd just
love something to eat.
Eat? That's ridiculous.
Mothers don't
eat daughters.
I don't know.
How do you taste?
(LAUGHING)
CORALINE: Huh?
But how can you walk
away from something
and still come back to it?
Walk around the world.
Small world.
(FANFARE PLAYING)
Hang on.
(MOUSE SQUEAKING)
Stop!
He's one of the circus mice!
(SQUEAKING)
(GASPS)
I don't like rats
at the best of times,
but this one was
sounding an alarm.
Good kitty.
They say even
the proudest spirit
can be broken with love.
(CHUCKLES)
Of course, chocolate
never hurts. Like one?
They're cocoa beetles
from Zanzibar.
(EXCLAIMS IN DISGUST)
I want to be with
my real mom and dad.
I want you to let me go.
Is that any way to
talk to your mother?
You aren't my mother.
Apologize at once, Coraline!
No!
I'll give you to
the count of three.
One.
Two.
Three!
Ow!
What are you doing?
Ow! That hurts!
You may come out
when you've learned
to be a loving daughter.
(SCREAMS)
(PANTING)
(GHOSTLY MOANING)
(GASPS)
Who's there?
TALL GIRL GHOST: Hush!
And shush.
For the beldam
might be listening.
You... You mean
the other mother?
Who are you?
Don't remember our names,
but I 'member my true mommy.
Why are you all here?
GHOST CHILDREN: The beldam.
She spied on
our lives through
the little doll's eyes.
And saw that
we weren't happy.
So she lured us
away with treasures.
And treats.
SWEET GIRL GHOST:
And games to play.
BOY GHOST:
Gave all that we asked.
SWEET GIRL GHOST:
Yet we still wanted more.
TALL GIRL GHOST: So we
let her sew the buttons.
BOY GHOST:
She said that she loved us.
But she
locked us here.
GHOST CHILDREN:
And ate up our lives.
Well, she can't keep me
in the dark forever.
Not if she wants
to win my life.
Beating her is
my only chance.
Perhaps, if you do
win your escape,
you could find our eyes.
Has she taken those, too?
Yes, miss.
And hidden them.
BOY GHOST: Find our eyes,
mistress, and our souls
will be freed.
I...
I'll try.
(GASPS)
(CORALINE GRUNTING)
Wybie?
(CORALINE GASPS)
Did she do this to you?
I hope that feels...
Shh!
(CORALINE GRUNTS)
OTHER MOTHER:
Coraline? Is that you?
Let's go!
OTHER MOTHER: Coraline!
Come on!
She'll hurt you again.
OTHER MOTHER: Coraline!
How dare you
disobey your mother!
(GASPS)
OTHER MOTHER: Coraline!
(PANTING)
I'm home!
Anybody here?
Hello? Hello, hello!
Real Dad?
Real Mom?
Oh, Mom's groceries!
Ugh!
(FLIES BUZZING)
That's disgusting.
(DOORBELL RINGING)
I missed you guys so much,
you'll never...
Oh. The Wybie that talks.
Huh?
Yeah, so, you know
that old doll I gave you?
Um...
My grandma's real mad.
Says it was her sister's.
The one that disappeared.
You stole that doll,
didn't you?
Well, it looked just
like you, and I figured...
It used to look
like this pioneer girl,
then Huck Finn Jr.,
then it was this
Little Rascals chick
with all these
ribbons and braids and...
Grandma's missing sister.
I think I just met her.
Come on.
Listen, I'm really
not supposed to...
Whoa!
She's in there.
Can you...
Can you unlock it?
Not in a million years.
But it wouldn't matter.
She can't escape
without her eyes.
None of the ghosts can.
(EXCLAIMS IN DISBELIEF)
Yeah. So I really
need to get that doll.
Great! I'd love to
get rid of it.
Where are you hiding,
you little monster?
You and Grandma been talking?
The doll's her spy.
It's how she watches you,
finds out what's wrong
with your life.
The doll is my grandma's spy?
No. The other mother.
She's got this whole world
where everything's better.
The food, the garden,
the neighbors.
But it's all a trap.
Yeah, I think I heard
someone calling me, Jonesy.
Don't believe me?
You can ask the cat.
The cat?
I'll just tell Grandma
that you couldn't
find the doll.
Ow!
You're not listening to me!
That's 'cause you're crazy!
(WYBIE SCREAMING)
(CORALINE SCREAMING
IN FRUSTRATION)
(PANTING)
CORALINE: You creep!
Crazy!
CORALINE: Crazy?
You're the jerk wad
that gave me the doll!
Mom! Dad!
(PHONE RINGING)
Pick it up, Dad. Pick it up.
DAD ON ANSWERING
MACHINE: Hi!
Dad! Where...
I'm digging in
my garden right now,
but leave a message
and I'll get
right back to you.
Where have you gone?
(WHIMPERS)
(SPINK GRUNTS)
Uh... Don't you only
make wings for the dead ones?
Just looking ahead, dear.
Angus hasn't been
feeling very well of late.
FORCIBLE: April?
Aren't you getting ready?
We've lost our ride, Miriam.
Caroline says
her parents have vanished
quite completely.
What?
We've waited months
for those tickets.
I suppose we could walk.
With your gammy legs?
It's nearly two
miles to the theater.
(CLEARS THROAT)
Oh, yes.
Your missing parents.
SPINK: We know
just what you need.
Miriam, get...
That's right.
How is 100-year-old
candy gonna help?
(DOGS WHIMPERING)
(SCREAMING)
There you go, sweetie.
What's it for?
Well, it might help.
They're good for
bad things sometimes.
No. They're good
for lost things.
SPINK: It's
bad things, Miriam.
Lost things, April.
Bad.
Lost.
(WHISPERS) Bad things.
Bad.
Lost!
Good night, Mom.
Good night, Dad.
(SNIFFLES)
(SOBBING)
(CAT PURRING)
CORALINE: Hello.
How did you get in?
Do you know where
Mom and Dad are?
(GASPS)
Mom? Dad!
(GLASS SQUEAKING)
(GASPS)
(GRUNTING)
(SCREAMS)
(PANTING)
(MEOWS)
How did this happen?
(CORALINE GASPS)
She's taken them.
They're not
coming back, are they?
Mom and Dad.
Not on their own.
Only one thing to do.
(CLATTERING)
You know,
you're walking
right into her trap.
I have to go back.
They are my parents.
Challenge her, then.
She may not play fair,
but she won't refuse.
She's got a thing for games.
Hmm.
Okay.
(WIND WHISTLES)
OTHER MOTHER: Coraline?
Mom?
Coraline!
You came back for us.
Mom!
Darling, why would
you run away from me?
(GASPS)
(LAUGHING)
Where are my parents?
Gosh, I have no idea
where your old parents are.
Perhaps they've
grown bored of you
and run away to France.
They weren't bored of me.
You stole them!
Now, don't be
difficult, Coraline.
Have a seat, won't you?
(GARBLED CHATTERING)
(RAT SQUEAKING)
Mmm.
Why don't you
have your own key?
(GARBLED) Only one key.
Shh!
The garden squash
need tending,
don't you think, pumpkin?
(GARBLED) Squish-squash,
pumpkin sauce.
(GLASS SQUEAKING)
Mom?
Dad?
(GLASS SQUEAKING CONTINUES)
Where'd she hide you?
(BELL TINKLING)
OTHER MOTHER: Breakfast time!
CORALINE: Be strong, Coraline.
(OTHER MOTHER HUMMING)
Why don't we play a game?
I know you like them.
Everybody likes games.
Uh-huh.
What kind of
game would it be?
An exploring game.
A finding things game.
And what is it you'd
be finding, Coraline?
My real parents.
Too easy.
And the eyes of
the ghost children.
Huh.
What if you
don't find them?
If I lose, I'll stay
here with you forever
and let you love me.
(CORALINE SIGHS)
And I'll let you sew
buttons into my eyes.
Hmm.
And if you
somehow win this game?
Then you let me go.
You let everyone go.
My real father and mother,
the dead children,
everyone you've trapped here.
(EXCLAIMS)
Deal.
Not till you give me a clue.
Oh, right.
In each of three wonders
I've made just for you,
a ghost's eye is
lost in plain sight.
And for my parents?
(CHUCKLES)
Fine. Don't tell me.
(SIGHS)
It's a deal.
What does she mean,
"wonders?"
Hmm.
(CROAKS)
Ugh!
No!
(GRUNTS)
(BUZZING)
Stop!
Why steal this?
(CORALINE GASPS)
Wow!
That must be it!
(GARBLED) Sorry.
So sorry.
Mother making me.
Don't wanna hurt you!
Take it!
(PANTING)
Bless you, miss.
You found me!
But there's two
eyes still lost.
Don't worry.
I'm getting the hang of it.
(OTHER SPINK SINGING)
(RUSTLING)
(GROWLS)
The pearl.
(SCREAMS)
Thief!
Give it back!
OTHER SPINK: Give it back!
Thief!
Give it back!
Stop! Stop! Thief! Thief!
OTHER FORCIBLE:
Thief! Stop!
Hurry on, girl.
Her web is unwinding.
Oh, Wybie.
Evil witch! I'm not scared!
(CREAKING)
Hello, galoobooshka.
I'm Coraline.
Is this what
you're looking for?
Uh-huh.
You think winning
game is good thing?
You'll just go home and
be bored and neglected,
same as always.
Stay here with us.
We will listen to you
and laugh with you.
If you stay here, you
can have whatever you want.
Always!
You don't get it, do you?
I don't understand.
Of course you
don't understand.
You're just a copy she made
of the real Mr. B.
(DISTORTED)
Not even that anymore.
(SQUEAKS)
(GASPS)
No!
(SCREAMING)
(GRUNTS)
No!
(GROANS)
Oh, God. I've lost the game.
I've lost everything.
(SOBBING)
(CAT MEOWS)
I think I mentioned
that I don't like rats
at the best of times.
I think you might have said
something like that.
It looked like you
needed this one, however.
Thank you.
I'm heading inside.
I still have to
find my parents.
Come on, quickly!
(CAT GROWLS)
So you're back.
And you brought
vermin with you.
(MEOWS)
No. I...
I brought a friend.
You know I love you.
(SIGHS)
You have a very
funny way of showing it.
So where are they?
The ghost eyes?
Hold on. We aren't
finished yet. Are we?
No, I suppose not.
After all,
you still need to find
your old parents, don't you?
Too bad you won't have this.
Be clever, miss.
Even if you win,
she'll never let you go!
I already know where
you've hidden them.
(CHUCKLES)
Well, produce them.
They're behind that door.
Oh, they are, are they?
(GLASS SQUEAKING)
(WHISPERS) There.
Mom. Dad.
(OTHER MOTHER COUGHING)
Go on. Open it.
They'll be there, all right.
You're wrong, Coraline.
They aren't there.
Now you're going to
stay here forever.
No, I'm not!
(CAT SCREECHING)
(OTHER MOTHER SCREAMS)
OTHER MOTHER: No!
(MEOWS)
You horrible cheating girl!
(GASPS)
(SCREAMS)
(OTHER MOTHER CACKLING)
(MEOWING)
No! Where are you?
You selfish brat!
(GRUNTS)
(LAUGHING)
You dare
disobey your mother?
(CORALINE GRUNTS)
(GROWLING)
Please shut it!
(SCREAMING)
(GRUNTING)
(OTHER MOTHER SCREAMING)
OTHER MOTHER: Don't leave me!
Don't leave me!
I'll die without you!
(SCREAMS)
(PANTING)
(EXCLAIMS)
(DOOR OPENING)
MOM: Coraline, we're home.
Mom! Dad!
I missed you so much!
(CHUCKLES)
Missed us?
Oh, no. You broke my
favorite snow globe.
I didn't break it.
It must've broke
when you escaped.
And cut your knee.
Coraline, I asked you
to count all the windows,
not put your knee
through them.
But...
Well, get yourself
cleaned up.
We're going out tonight.
(EXCLAIMS)
We got a lot to celebrate.
You're talking about
your garden catalog?
Of course. What else?
CORALINE: But look at
the snow on your...
What's gotten
into you, Coraline?
(DAD EXCLAIMING)
(CORALINE LAUGHING)
So, gonna
order the tulips?
What's that?
For the garden party?
I have no idea what
you're talking about.
Dad! So, Ma, invitations?
Don't forget
the invitations.
Even Bobinsky?
Mr. B.'s not drunk,
Mom. He's just eccentric.
(LAUGHING)
Good night, Coraline.
(MEOWS)
Oh.
Hello again.
You still mad?
I'm really sorry
I threw you at her,
the other mother.
It was all I could think of.
I think it's time,
don't you?
To set them free?
It's a fine, fine thing
you did for us, miss.
Well, I'm glad
it's finally over.
It is over and
done with for us.
What about me?
You're in
terrible danger, girl!
But how? I locked the door!
It's the key, miss.
There's only one,
and the beldam will find it.
'Tain't all bad, miss.
Thou art alive.
Thou art still living.
(GASPS)
I gotta hide this somewhere,
somewhere she can never...
(MEOWS)
Out of my way!
CORALINE: (SINGING)
Oh, my twitchy-witchy girl
I think you are so nice
I give you bowls of porridge
and I give you
bowls of ice cream
I give you lots of kisses
And I give you lots of hugs
But I never
give you sandwiches
Wth grease and
worms and mung...
(GRUNTS)
...beans
(SCREAMS)
(POUNDING)
(HORN HONKING)
(SHOUTING)
(COUGHING)
(SCREAMING)
(GASPS)
(GRUNTING)
(SCREAMS)
(CORALINE EXCLAIMS)
(PANTING)
(BOTH GRUNT)
(SPLASHING)
(PANTING)
I'm really sorry
I didn't believe you
about all this
evil stuff, Coraline.
Why did you change your mind?
Well, Grandma showed me
this picture after
I called you crazy.
It's her and her sister,
before she disappeared.
The Sweet Ghost Girl.
LOVAT: Wyborne! Come home!
Oh, man.
What am I gonna tell her?
Just bring her by
the house tomorrow.
We can tell her together.
We... We can?
You know, I'm glad
you decided to stalk me.
(CHUCKLES)
(LAUGHS UNCERTAINLY)
It wasn't my idea.
(MEOWS)
CORALINE:
Thanks for helping me,
Miss Spink, Miss Forcible.
Oh, look, April.
Pink ladies!
Actually, it's just lemonade.
How's Angus doing?
Oh, much better, dear,
but he can't duck
his wings forever.
DAD: Here comes a burp.
(DAD BURPS)
MOM: Charlie!
Excusez-moi, but that pizza,
that was delicious.
CORALINE: Cold drinks?
Oh, yeah. Great.
You were right, Coraline.
I really hate dirt!
But the tulips look nice.
CORALINE: Thanks, Mom.
(BOBINSKY MUTTERING)
That is possible.
(CORALINE CLEARS THROAT)
CORALINE: How are
the mooshkas, Mr. B?
They tell me that you
are savior, Caroline.
And soon as they are ready,
they wish to give special
thanks you performance.
LOVAT: Wyborne,
I know where I'm going.
I grew up here.
CORALINE: Welcome, Miss Lovat!
Oh. Hello.
I'm Coraline Jones.
I've got so much to tell you.
MOM: Here.
DAD: Thanks.
SPINK: Do you want to pop
a little gin in it, dear?
FORCIBLE: Of course.
(PURRS)