Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org
[ Train Rattling ]
Why don't you, like,
ever realize the truth, Vince?
I ate nine pies and a meatball hero
in one hour. That's a record.
It wasn't nine pies.
It was eight.
You left two slices of mushroom
on the last tray.
- Violet?
- You guys, it was six pies. No hero.
I had to call the paramedics
to pump your stomach, and it was
three and a half years ago.
When are you guys gonna talk
about something else?
When someone comes through
that door and breaks the record,
then we'll stop talkin'
about the subject.
Enjoy your pie, guys.
- It's the last one I'll ever serve.
- Aren't you forgetting something?
Quit it, Pete.
I'm not doin' that.
It's a tradition.
Sign the card.
I got it, folks.
I got the first autograph.
- Hey, Violet. All right!
- Violet's on her way to the wall.
That's 20 years
of girls leaving town.
That Wallis jinxed.
I won't sit near that wall.
Let's hope you have better luck
than they did.
- [Crowd Shouting]
- Ladies and gentlemen.
As you all know, my best friend,
Violet Sanford,
has decided--
has decided to leave
South Amboy tomorrow...
and travel the 42 miles
to New York City.
So-- Okay, come on.
Bring her up here, girls.
- Come on, Violet.
- [ Crowd Hooting ]
Come on, Vi.
Come on, everyone.
Hey, Violet, come on.
Come up here.
- Come on, honey.
- You guys!
Now, I think it's only fair
that tonight, on her last night
with us in Jersey,
she grace us
with a little tune.
No way!
[ Girls ]
/At first I was afraid
I was petrified /
//Kept thinkin' I could never
live without you by my side//
/Then I spent so many nights
thinking how you did me wrong /
//And I grew strong
and I knew how to get along//
/ No, not I /
/ I will survive /
/ Oh, as long as
I know how to love
I know I'll be alive /
//I got all my life to live
I got all my love to give//
/ I'll survive
I will survive //
[Man Whistles]
Look at this!
Four people killed last night
in New York.
No reason at all.
Police have no leads.
[ Clicks Tongue ]
- Tragic.
- Dad, what're you doin?
I guess four out
of seven million ain't so bad.
Headlines should read,
"" Millions Survive Night in New York.""
Dad, stop. I get the point.
Here. Eat your eggs.
They're not eggs. They're egg whites.
And I'd rather eat the carton.
You've already lost six pounds.
You're staying on this diet.
No fast food. No sausage.
Oh, and I bought you some
of those Lean Cuisine meals,
and I put 'em in the freezer.
- My mouth is watering already.
- And I lined your vitamins up
on the counter.
- I don't take vitamins.
- You do now. Just take them.
Oh, and I put fresh batteries
in the TV remote and set
the V.C.R. timer so--
Excuse me. Excuse me.
Am I missing something here?
I'm the parent. You're the child
running away to live by herself.
I should be tellin' you
how to live.
Fine. How should I live?
- Simple. Don't go.
- [ Sighs ]
I got that Irish Spring you like.
Oh. And Dad, whatever you do--
- Don't do the laundry.
- [ Muttering ] Don't do the laundry.
Just leave it by the dyer and I'll
do it when I come home every Sunday.
Ah, this is interesting.
They say the handrails
on the subway system could one day
lead to an outbreak of plague.
Dad. Look.
You said I could be
whatever I wanna be.
I never said songwriter
in New York City.
That's the exception.
You said anything,
and I believed you, so--
[ Sighs ] I'm not leavin' this house
without your support.
- [Car Horn Honking]
- That's Gloria. What's it gonna be?
[ Sighs ]
Violet, I saw how hard it was
for your mother when she didn't make it.
But if she was here,
she'd tell me to shut up,
wish you luck
and give you a big hug.
I'm not gonna give you a big hug,
and I'm not gonna wish you luck, but...
I am gonna shut up, sit here
with my coffee and pretend to be mad.
Is that okay?
This is the last of it.
- Honey, are you okay with that?
- Yeah, I got it.
I got it. Wait.
All right.
That's everything.
- Let's hit it.
- Good luck.
There, I said it.
- Love you.
- Put some pepper spray in your
purse. Even if you're not sure.
Just start spraying.
You know, you're not alone,
Mr. Sanford.
Hey, you know, me and you
should have dinner sometime.
I'm lockin' the doors.
//At first I was afraid
I was petrified//
//Kept thinkin' I could never
live without you by my side//
// Oh, no, not I//
//I will survive//
//As long as I have love to give
I know I'll be alive//
//I've got all my life to live
I've got all my love
to give//
//I will survive//
//I will survive////
All right.
This is it.
What do you think?
I had a feeling
you were gonna need this.
- What are you doing?
- What? It's just some
emergency cash I saved up.
Honey, from the looks of this place,
I'd say this is our emergency.
Well, I'm not takin' it.
Fine, then.
I'm freezing your assets.
So, thanks
for everything.
- I'll call ya.
- [ Sniffing ]
What is this?
It's just that all our lives,
you know, we always had one thing
in common, you and me.
What are you talking about?
It's like, you know we said
we wouldn't lose our virginity...
until we got married,
and that didn't happen.
And then we said we'd go to
college or junior college...
or dental hygienist school,
you know.
And that didn't happen.
We've never followed through
on a single thing, you know.
And I think that's
what makes us so special.
[ Chuckles ]
And this is why you're crying?
Well...
a long time ago you told me
that you were gonna move to New York.
But everyone thought you'd just
stay in Jersey and get married
like me and Danny are gonna.
You know. And-- And look at you.
No matter what,
you really did it right,
and I'm so proud of you.
[ Sighs ]
// [ Soft Ballad ]
[Pounding]
Enough! You hear me?
[Shouting]
You be quiet!Enough in there!
/ I don't like to be
alone in the night /
/And I don't like to
hear I'm wrong when I'm right /
/And I don't like to /
/ Have the rain on my shoe //
Hi. I'm Violet Sanford.
I just recently moved to New York,
and I was wondering
if you would give my tape
to one of your artists.
Violet, that is so cute.
Now, let me tell you about me.
My name is Wendy,
and I first moved to New York...
when I was 21 to be a dancer,
but I broke my big toe.
And then I got knocked up
by this actor who dumped me
to join the Peace Corps.
So for the last 1 6 years
I been raisin' my daughter
all by myself.
And then two weeks ago
she tells me that she is a bisexual...
and that she hates me more
than any person on this planet.
[Chuckles]
Now, tell me how I can
help you, please,
because I am dying
to make your dreams come true.
You don't take the tape
unless it comes from an agent,
but I can't get an agent
until I get published?
If we were to listen to that tape,
that would give you grounds...
for a copyright
or plagiarism lawsuit.
It's just a little tape.
All I want is someone to sing my songs.
Welcome to the music business.
[Phone Ringing]
- Good evening. I.D., please.
- Hi. Uh, sure.
/ Maybe /
//Find a way to make it
back someday//
- What can I get you?
- Let me ask you something.
I'm a songwriter. Is there someone
here I could talk to about my songs?
I've been a struggling
sax player for 1 2 years.
- What can I get you from the bar?
- Pepsi and some crackers.
////[Continues]
- [ People Chattering ]
- Hey. How are you doing?
/Then I hope there's someone
out there /
Excuse me.
Who's that guy?
That would be Mr. O'Donnell.
Mr. O'Donnell.
He's the manager or something?
Yeah. He's the music manager.
He's in charge of finding bands and...
booking new talent.
//Run away with my heart//
//Run away with my hope////
Hey, where the hell were you,
O'Donnell?
I got 1 5 orders stacked up here
and nobody to run the grill.
Fifteen orders, Walt.
Is that all?
Gimme ten minutes,
I'll catch us up. Go on. Lie down.
Relax. You look tired.
We can talk about
my raise later.
You think this is Australia?
There's no raise. I'm about to fire you.
[Door Opens, People Laughing]
Um, excuse me.
Mr. O'Donnell?
- Yes.
- Mr. O'Donnell.
My name is Violet Sanford.
I'm a songwriter.
I just wanted to give this to you.
I know it's not the most professional
way to submit a tape.
- But this is all pretty new to me.
- It's pretty new to me too.
I just figured as the manager
of a club like this, you must know
every band on the East Coast.
The manager...
of this club.
Um--
- You guys go ahead. I'll catch up.
- Sure thing.
Mr. O'Donnell.
[ Clears Throat ]
I don't usually do this,
Violet.
Um, but I-- I have
a feeling about you.
- So I'm gonna take your tape,
and I'm gonna see what I can do.
- Thank you.
I can't believe
how easy this was.
Neither can I.
Uh, you wanna go for
some coffee or something?
O'Donnell, who do I look like?
Your goddamn maid?
That's Mr. O'Donnell,
but I'll let it slide
this time.
I told you to take your stuff
home and wash it.
You got cow grease
caked on the front.
Walt, I've warned you
about your attitude-- You're fired.
Oh, you better not
push me, kid.
I can find a hundred other
little punks like you,
can burn a turkey burger.
Minimum wage punk.
Maybe we should start over. Uh...
I'm Kevin O'Donnell,
and I work the grill
here at the Fiji Mermaid Club.
I just made a complete
fool of myself.
I was gonna tell you.
I'm almost sure
I would have told you.
I just want you to know
I'm not following you home.
I'm just walking myself26
blocks in the wrong direction.
- I asked you to leave me alone.
- Did I mention how sorry I am?
I mean, not that it's all my fault.
You did throw yourself at me.
I didn't throw myself at you.
I was pretending to be sweet
and innocent so you'd give me a break.
- Can I ask you a question?
- What?
Is there a reason we just walked
in a circle? Are you lost?
I'm not lost.
Somebody just moved my street.
You-- You wanna play a game?
I bet I can guess
where you're from.
I'm about to get out
my pepper spray.
I reckon you're
from a big city.
And there's no sign from here
of a belly button ring...
or a tongue piercing.
- I gotta go with Chicago.
- Okay.
I've never had anyone stare
at my ass for half an hour,
so I'm gonna say good night.
And I'm hoping
you're gonna say it back.
Okay. I can take a hint.
I really do know a lot of people
in the music business.
You just don't give up,
do ya?
- Well, it was the sweet and
innocent thing. It did me in.
- Good night, Kevin.
Just for the record,
I was only staring at your ass
for the first 15 minutes.
-[Man Answering Phone]
William Morris.
- I don't mean to interrupt.
- I just want to leave this--
- I'll transfer.
- William Morris. Please hold.
- It's a demo. I'm a songwriter.
William Morris.
I'll be right with you.
[ Phones Disconnect ]
I just want to leave this
for Whitney and Mariah.
- I'm sure they're
personal friends of yours.
- Look.
I'm sure it sounds great in your shower,
but karaoke ended a half-hour ago.
So if you'd like to get
your songs heard,
you're gonna have to take them...
to an open mic night
just like everyone else.
[ Phones Resume Ringing ]
William Morris.
I'll transfer.
You're not getting validated.
// Caught in a mirror//
-[Pool Balls Clacking]
- / Looking through
sympathetic eyes /
- Can I help you?
- Um--
Yeah, hi. Uh, I'm sure all your spaces
are filled for tonight.
I just wanted to come down
and check out what this whole
open mic thing was about.
I can squeeze you in in ten minutes.
A couple of my regulars,
they called in sick.
So, uh, I've got
some spaces to fill.
I need you to sign your name
in here and get yourself ready.
////[Singer Continues]
Bathroom's around the corner
if you want to throw up.
Next up we have a young lady
named Violet Sanford.
So let's put our hands together
for New Jersey's own Violet Sanford!
Come on up, Violet.
Good! There we go.
Yeah. Whoo!
-[Woman] Yea, Violet!
-[Scattered Applause, Whistles]
Oh, oops.
- I'm a little nervous.
- So are we, honey.
Don't tease me, honey!
Sing!
[Man #@]
Come on, give her a break.
I'm sorry.
Hello?
[ Crying ]
You gotta cheer up. You look like
somebody ran over your dog.
Hey, um, how much
is a slice of pie?
Oh, uh,
we happen to have
the best French apple in town.
And, uh,
it's on the house.
-Shut up.
- You just have to pay attention.
- Okay?
- Twenty.
- Twenty says it's Pretty Woman.
- I will raise you ten,
because it is Home Alone.
- Oh?
- You guys have to read the signs.
I call with
Saving Private Ryan.
- What?
- Let's flip this over,
and Miss Jennifer from Austin...
says her
favorite movie is--
No way. There's no way!
You already saw this one.
Oh, you are such a cheater.
Hello. A naked girl in army boots?
Easy play to call.
- Thank you.
- Those boots are kind of cute.
- I have to get me some of those.
- [ Chuckles ]
Wait, wait, wait. Oh, Romero.
You gotta turn that up, baby.
That is the jam.
- Turn it up!
There you go, there you go.
- Oh, no.
- Girl, what are you doing?
- Remember this? Remember this?
- [Girls Groaning]
- Belly dancing.
[ Hooting ]
- Do you know those girls?
- Oh, yeah. They're here every
morning around this time.
- Winding down.
- Wait, wait.
- They have to, in their line of work.
- Are they hookers?
No.
Coyotes.
[ Laughs ]
All right.
You guys? You guys wanna see
what Al gave me for my birthday?
- This.
- You let him brand you?
- Isn't it cute?
- She let them an brand her.
Hey, check it out, ladies.
We each made 300bucks tonight.
- Mmm.
- You sure you wanna be
goin' off to law school?
Hmm?
- Let's make a toast.
- Yeah.
To Zoe's last week
as a Coyote.
- Oh.
- She's gonna be
impossible to replace.
I just wanna tell you both
that I will never, ever forget you.
[Woman]
Who's up there?
- I'm lookin' for the owner.
- Hey, come on down.
Bring a case with you.
What are you doin' here?
- Uh, I'm gonna drop this case.
Where do you want me to put it?
- That depends. What do ya want?
Well, I heard you might need
a new, uh--
That, uh, there might be
a job opening.
Put it right there.
Let me take a look at ya.
[ Groans ]
Let me guess.
Piedmont, North Dakota.
South Amboy, New Jersey.
Same thing.
You do any drugs?
Just coffee.
That's all I can afford right now.
- Let me see your arms.
- Are you kidding?
Do I look like
I'm kidding?
Ooh, where'd you get
that scar on your wrist?
Pizza oven. It's a permanent
burn from pulling slices for four years.
That could be the saddest thing
I've ever heard.
- Um, what's next?
You want a urine sample?
- Ha, ha.
I prefer blood.
Look, are you really the owner?
'Cause I've had a rough couple of days,
and so the last thing I need
is some waitress on a power trip
wastin' my time.
You start Friday night.
Be there at 11:00.
That's when we get busy.
- You're givin' me a job?
- I'm givin' you an audition.
Don't be late, Jersey girl.
I don't mean to press my luck,
but would you mind telling me
why you're hiring me?
Because the average male...
is walking around with a toddler
inside of his pants.
A two-year old, right there
inside his Dockers.
Men have two-year-old children
in their pants?
That's why you're hiring me?
You look like a kindergarten teacher.
The kids'll love it.
Sorry I asked.
I.D., please.
Oh. I'm supposed to
start work here tonight.
Go ahead. Hey, you picked
a good night to start.
- It's a little slow right now,
but it should pick up.
- Okay.
//Love is like a bomb
Baby, come on get it on//
-//Livin' like a lover
with a radarphone//
- [ Screams ]
//Lookin' like a tramp
Like a video vamp//
//Demolition woman
Can I be your man//
Is this a church meeting
or is this a bar? Make some noise!
[ Whooping, Shouting ]
- Yeah!
-// Come on//
- Want it?
-// Take a bottle//
//Shake it up//
//Break the bubble//
//Break it up//
//Pour some sugar on me//
// Ooh, in the name of love//
//Poor some sugar on me//
// Come on, fire me up//
-//Pour your sugar on me//
- I'm sorry. Sorry!
- I don't think so.
-Just in time.
- Where you goin'?
- Uh, I was-- I was looking for you.
Good. Let's go.
//
//Listen, red light, yellow
light, green light, go//
// Crazy little woman
in a one-manshow//
//Mirrorqueen, mannequin
rhythm of love//
- Really love your top.
- Thanks.
- I got it, um, on sale--
-//Loosen up, uh, loosen up//
// You gotta squeeze a little
squeeze a little
tease a little more//
Okay. Hair.
- Let's see your moves.
- [ Hoots ]
That's Rachel.
You can learn a lot from her.
She just cut some guy's
ponytail off.
Yeah. The court ordered her
to take anger management classes...
after she pummeled a customer
for grabbin' her ass.
- [ Whooping ]
- He pressed charges.
I gave her a raise. Cheers.
//Pour some sugar on me//
- There is only two rules, okay?
What do you want?
- Two beers.
- Don't date the customers.
- Okay.
Second, don't ever bring
your boyfriends into my bar.
As of this moment
you are to appear available,
but never be available.
Break my rules,
I fire you on the spot.
- I-- I understand.
-Jesus.
Hey! Hey, everybody!
Shut up!
I'd like you to meet
my new girl...
- whose name is--
- Violet.
Jersey.
- [ Cheering ]
-Jersey
is an ex-kindergarten teacher...
and a former nun who just escaped
from the convent...
and is tired of being the only virgin
in New York City.
Would anyone like
to buy her a drink? Whoa!
- Come on, move! I'm workin' here.
- Sorry.
- Four margaritas with salt.
- All right.
Got tequila.
No mix, no salt, no blender.
- Okay, how about a black Russian?
- Got vodka, no Kahlua.
- White wine.
- Never carry the stuff.
- So basically you have--
-Jim, Jack, Johnny Red,
Johnny Black and Jose.
All my favorite men.
You can have it anyway you like,
as long as it's in a shot glass.
Okay, I'll take a beer.
- Four dollars.
- I'm Cammie, the Russian tease.
Violet, the Jersey nun.
That one's Rachel,
the New York bitch.
We all play our little parts,
only Rachel really is a bitch.
And I really am a tease.
Cammie, you can only be a tease
if you stop sleepin' around, babe.
Yeah. I keep forgetting that part.
I'll have a shot of tequila, and don't
forget one for your pretty little self.
Oh, thanks, but ever since
I got really drunk on tequila,
I never drink the stuff anymore.
Hey, Lil! Your new girl's refusing
your good booze.
No! I was-- I was suggesting
this gentleman buy me a double.
That's more like it.
- Whoa!
- I need eight shots.
Four Canadian, four South
of the Border, six-pack MGD
and a double-blended back.
- You want eight shots of what?
- I got it.
Forty-six even, honey.
Hey, Lil! Yo!
Your Jersey girl
can't quite keep up.
Hey, gimme
a Scotch and water.
- Okay, you got it.
- Lil, do we serve water
with our whiskey?
Only water I serve's got
barley and hops in it!
Hey, everybody!
Do we serve water in this bar?
[ Crowd Chanting ]
Hell, no. H2O! Hell, no. H2O!
[ Chanting Continues ]
Hell no, H2O!
[ Hooting ]
Sink or swim time, Jersey.
Getup there!
// The devil's in the house
of the rising sun//
I can't do that dance.
// Granny, does your dog bite
No, child, no//
Okay.
//
- Here's some cash.
You did okay for a nun.
- You're firing me?
I told you this was an audition.
Thanks for comin' in.
Now, get outta here.
//Johnny said
Devil, just come on back
if you ever wanna try again//
//I done told you once
you son of a bitch, I'm the
best there's ever been//
//He played fire on the mountain
Run, boy, run//
//Devil's in the house
of the risin' sun//
Please!
-// Chicken in the breadpan
pickin' out dough//
- Hey!
Guys, guys, back off,
back off!.
Look, the way I see it,
you got two choices.
You can start a fight here,
throw some punches, get a bloody
nose, make fools of yourselves,
or you can take this ten bucks
I got right here...
and buy these two pretty ladies
a round at the bar.
- Come on. What do you say?
- Let's go to the bar!
Party!
-////[Continues]
- Hold it, Jersey. I'm just dyin'
to know where that came from.
Try serving a beer and pizza
on Monday nights when the Giants
play the Cowboys in November.
I'm giving you
a second audition.
There's a store at the corner
of Sixth and Hill.
Be there at noon tomorrow.
I'm sending my fashion coordinator there
to take you shopping.
Now go home
before I change my mind.
Hey, andere. I'd be shocked
if you survive another night.
// Granny, will your dog bite
No, child, no////
Here we go!
And left, and right,
clog, clog, clog.
//
Oh, yeah!
So, uh, tell me more
about this bar.
- What kind of place is it?
- I don't know. It's just a bar, Dad.
It's no big deal.
What are you eating?
One of those Lean Cuisine meals.
Rice and vegetables. Delicious.
- Oh! See, they're good. Right?
- Mmm. Yum.
So, well, what's going on
with your songwriting?
Songwriting. Oh!
He still has my tape.
//Dance, dance, dance//
//Dance////
I want my tape.
-////[Continues]
- I had a feeling
you'd be back to see me.
- No dates in the kitchen, O'Donnell.
- I'm not staying.
I-- I just want my tape.
Please.
- Thanks. Bye.
- Did you really write all those songs?
You listened to my tape?
No, of course not.
I mean, that would be
invasion of privacy.
/ Baby, you're the right kind
of love //
Go ahead, laugh it up.
'Cause there's nothing you can
say that's gonna bother me.
I'm just trying to tell you
I like your music.
I mean, do you always
take compliments so well?
- I gotta go.
- Wait! Uh--
I wanna see you again.
Where are you workin'?
- I'm a Coyote.
- [ Howls ]
- Good.
- And what the hell is that?
- If you want to see me again,
you'll figure it out.
That good? Uh-huh.
Sorry I'm late.
Al and I had a big fight.
And then we made up. Twice.
You're the fashion coordinator?
Lil told me to get you something
that would make the kiddies drool.
Trust me, Violet.
I have a serious
shopping problem.
- It has a zipper... in the crotch.
- Yeah.
Who'd wear that in public?
- Actually, I have it in blue.
-// You're unbelievable//
// Oh//
// You burden me
with your problems//
//By telling me more than mine//
//I'm always so concerned//
// With the way you say
you always have to stop//
// To think of us being one//
//Is more than I ever know//
// The things you say//
// You're unbelievable//
// Oh//
Forgive me, Father,
for I have sinned.
//Seemingly lastless
Don't me and you can ask us//
////[Continues]
[Hooting, Cheering]
// You're unbelievable, oh//
Here I am! Yeah, baby!
// You're unbelievable////
Come on! Knock it--
Hey! Knock it off!.
Lil! The ice!
How do you like that, huh?
// There's every good reason////
I don't know how you guys do it.
I can't have another drink.
Next time that guy buys you a shot--
That's on me, honey.
Chase it with a beer.
- I don't get it.
- I don't swallow it.
I just spit the shot
back into the beer bottle.
They'll never know.
You try it.
Hey, just keep an eye
on your spittoon bottle.
Once Rachel served hers to Lou
by accident. Huge drama.
Cammie, I think I just fell
in love with you.
Oh, Violet!
I'm not a lesbian.
I've played in the minors,
but never went pro.
- Th-That's not what I meant.
- What are you doing?
Lil's starin' straight at you.
Come on. Grab this guy.
Make yourself look busy.
- Hi. You look like
you could use a shot.
- No, I'm waiting on Lil.
Sorry. It's a no parking zone.
If you wanna sit here,
you gotta order a drink.
- Okay. Gimme a glass of water.
- Okay.
- He just ordered water.
- Yeah.
You know what to do.
Um--
Testing. Um, hey, everybody,
this guy just ordered water.
Do we serve water in our bar?
[Everyone]
Hell, no!H20!
Jersey! No!
It's okay, Lil!
Nobody orders water in your bar!
He can order whatever he wants.
He's the fire marshal.
Hey, Mike, I'm so sorry.
She's new.
I'm okay.
Let's step outside.
-//Party//
- Nice knowing you, Jersey.
-// Get naked////
- Come on, you guys!
Let me hear you!
You okay?
Who am I kidding?
I can't do this.
Ofcourse you can.
Now cheer up,
because there's a really
cute guy at the bar asking for you.
Somebody's asking for me?
He says his name
is Mr. O'Donnell.
He's hot.
Jersey. The fire marshal
threatened to shut me down.
- He let me go with a $250 fine.
- Lil, I'm really sorry--
I'll make you a deal.
You figure out a way
to make me 250 tonight,
I'll let you
come back tomorrow.
Great.
So much for
sweet and innocent.
- So, you found me.
- Some guys at work told me
where I could look for Coyotes.
Well, take a good look,
because tonight's my last night.
I think I'm gonna get fired.
- Why?
- I have to make $250 in two hours.
It's completely impossible.
Here's nine dollars,
just to get you started. Okay?
I always like to help
a friend in need.
Why are you looking at me
like that?
Kevin, I don't want
your money.
All right, uh, listen up.
Ladies.
The bidding will start
at $25...
for one night only.
You get this:
purebred, housebroken,
fully trained,
yowling stud.
- No way.
- That's pretty cheap.
Violet, what are you doing?
You said you wanted to help,
so... turn around, sir,
let 'em take a look at ya.
Why are you doing this to me?
It's payback time,
Mr. O'Donnell.
Now, turn around.
No, God, no.
Don't do this.
Go on, show 'em
what you've got.
Are you in?
Do you wanna do this?
- All right, ladies.
What'll you give me?
- I've got twenty bucks.
[ Women Hooting ]
I've got $25 right here.
Make it 35!
Thirty-five dollars!
- Forty dollars!
- Get-- What are you doing?
- Come on, girls, fifty?
- Fifty!
- Sixty-one dollars.
- I've got 70.
- Come on, girls. Seventy-five?
- Seventy-five dollars!
Eighty dollars!
Come on, girls. Do Ihear85?
Ninety! Ninety-five dollars!
One hundred dollars!
//
- That's it.
- You wanna come home with Mama?
[Bidder]
Whoa!Nice!
Oh, yeah!
That's my boy.
- Oh, yeah. Shake it, shake it.
- $1 25 back here!
$1 40, right here.
Come on, come on.
//
My goodness, girls, come on.
One fifty and you'll see the butt.
Come on, girls.
You can do better than this.
One seventy-five.
Yeah!
There we go.
Two hundred dollars!
- You've got215righthere!
- Two hundred and fifty dollars.
Sold, for $250!
- No!
- Come on up, honey. He's yours.
Damn you!
The blonde would have gone 275.
Come with me.
You're gonna owe me
big-time for this one.
That's 250 even.
Mmm. Mmm! Oh.
//I'm gonna see ya
I'm gonna meet ya, meet ya
meet ya one day//
/ Maybe next week
I'm gonna meet ya /
//I'll meet ya
I'll meet ya//
[Lil]
Better close out, girls.
- Can I ask you something?
- What?
What-- What does
""Coyote Ugly"" mean?
Did you ever wake up sober
after a one night stand...
and the person you're next
tois layin' on your arm,
and they're so ugly...
you'd rather chew off
your arm than risk wakin' them?
- That's coyote ugly.
- Let's go, ladies.
Well, why would you name
your bar after something like that?
Well, because ""Cheers""
was taken.
Cabs are out front.
- You're rich, Jersey.
- See ya.
Yeah. Good night.
The woman who purchased me
is named Sandy Rosenfeld,
a divorcee with three grown kids,
a passion for long walks
and short-haired hunting dogs
and Italian opera.
Her ex-husband is a C.P.A.
Her favorite artist is Van Gogh,
and her New Year's resolution
is to lose 1 5 pounds--
and to see Barbra in concert.
Okay. I owe you.
[ Chuckles ]
What do you want?
Well, it's 3:30 in the morning.
I want what every man wants.
Breakfast.
And that's it? I go to breakfast
with you, and we're even?
No. We're not even close to even,
because I danced on a bar,
I took off my shirt,
and I unzipped my pants.
Okay. Let's make a deal.
Breakfast and lunch.
- Breakfast, lunch and two dinners.
- That's four dates!
Yep. Which would make it
the second longest relationship
I've ever had.
- Get in the car.
- [ Laughs ]
Oh, I hate to spoil
your evening, but it looks like
we're not gonna go anywhere.
Oh, my God.
It's hard to find parking
in New York.
You ever eaten Turkish?
This is the place.
- Hey. How you doin'?
- Hi, Kevin.
- Four of the regular?
- Sure, yeah. Hey.
- Hey, Kevin. How are you, man?
- How you doin', man? Good.
Here it is, man.
Flown in from Miami.
- Check out the merchandise.
- Hey, man, no. I trust you.
All right, all right.
Look, uh, I don't know
what you're into, but--
The Amazing Spider-Man,
number 1 29, mint condition.
- Worth a thousand bucks.
- A comic book.
No, it's not just a comic book.
This is the first appearance
of the Punisher.
This is the holy grail
of comic books.
- You collect comic books.
That's so cute.
- Yeah.
It's not cute.
It's very rugged and manly.
- It's just a bit kinky. Huh?
- I think it's sweet.
So, do you always eatbreakfast
on the hood of your car?
What can I say?
I'm a romantic.
You think this
is romantic?
Well, you may not be feeling it now,
but I think one day...
-you'll be on stage singing
a song about this very night.
- Mmm.
""When We Were Downwind
From a Trash Barge.""
Yeah. Catchy title.
Hum a few bars.
Sorry to disappoint you,
but I'm a songwriter, not a singer.
When I get on stage,
I freeze.
What if the fate of the free world
rested on your voice?
Okay. If the fate of the free
world depended on me singing,
maybe.
All I ever really wanted
is to sit in the dark...
and hear someone great
singing my songs.
I wanna be the one
who writes the music.
I remember the first time
my mother played me
"" Bridge Over Troubled Water""...
by Simon and Garfunkel.
I remember exactly
what she was wearing.
I remember exactly how her hair smelled.
I remember exactly how I felt.
And every time
I hear that song,
I remember exactly
what she was wearing...
and exactly
how her hair smelled...
and exactly how I felt.
'Cause the great songs
last forever.
- So, what's the problem?
- Well...
now they're telling me the only
way to get my songs heard...
is to go out there
and sing 'em myself.
So we're gonna have to try fix this
little problem straight away.
Hmm. And how do you propose
we do that?
Well, is there any place
you feel comfortable singing?
- The shower.
- We'll start there.
I mean, I don't care how long
it takes, how many hours
we have to spend in that shower.
- Let's get to it.
- Okay. Before we hit the showers,
maybe you could tell me
a little something about yourself.
Oh, really?
What do you wanna know?
What part of Australia
are you from?
I'm from all over.
My family moved around a lot.
So the rest of your family
doesn't live in New York?
Do you always ask
this many questions?
Do you always dodge
You can at least tell me
where you got all the moves
you pulled on the bar tonight.
Well, if I told you,
I'd have to kill you.
- [ Scoffs ] That's original.
- Oh.
The sun's coming up.
We're gonna be late.
Late? Late for what?
This is incredible.
- Look at that fish!
- All right. Put this on.
You're gonna need it.
Why? What are you
talking about?
You're gonna help me
unload the next bin.
- You're joking, right?
- No. It's not that bad, Vi.
- I do it all the time.
- Exactly how many jobs do you have?
Tuesday through Saturday,
I'm at the club.
Sunday and Monday
I park cars at the plaza.
I've been a telemarketer.
Would you like to switch to AT&T?
And for six terrifying hours
I delivered phonebooks in Queens.
Don't forget your
extensive work in fish.
This is an expensive city,
and these guys pay cash.
I don't care if they pay in lobster.
I'm not sticking my hands
in that fishy bin.
I was gonna split the money
with you.
-A hundred bucks apiece.
- A hundred bucks?
- Wait, wait. Why didn't you say so?
- Thanks, Dan.
-You're not ready, are you? Fifty bucks.
-Wait. No.
- Twenty-five, ten. Ready?
- Okay. Uh-huh.
Ooh! That's disgusting.
Hey, you'll hurt their feelings. Okay.
Just on top of the other fish.
So, I know I just met you
a few days ago.
There's something I have to tell you.
You smell really bad.
Well, so do you. I mean,
I was gonna kiss you good-bye,
but, um, I thought I might gag.
You're a real charmer.
Okay. Good night.
Good morning.
Don't look at me like that.
Spend it.
- What are you doing here?
- I changed my mind about this kiss.
I think we should give it a shot.
Well, have a nice day.
"" Have a nice day""?
Yeah. I panicked.
I didn't know what else to say.
Have a nice day.
All right. Back of the line over here.
Back of the line.
Yeah! Whoa!
[ Both Hooting ]
Whoa!
[ Shouting Continues ]
- Yeah, I like it!
- Yeah!
- Hey, baby!
- Make a hole. Make a hole!
- Shit, the cops are here.
- Nobody else gets in here.
Look at this place.
Hey, Lil. I'm sorry.
There's nothing we can do here.
You're 50 people over max.
They're trying to shut us down.
Let's go outside and talk.
I'll take care of it.
Hey! Hey!
- This is not a gas pump, son!
- [ Shouts ]
Wait your turn!
[ Shouting, Arguing ]
- Hey, no pictures, man!
- Hey, I'm a reporter from The Voice.
Yeah!
Whoa!
What are you doing? Hey!
- Put me down!
- Hey!
- Cammie!
- Help!
- Come on! Let her go!
Rachel, help!
Come on!Breakitup!
- Lou, where's Rachel and Cammie?
- I don't know!
[ Shouting, Grunting ]
Let me go!
[ Shouting, Grunting Continue ]
-////[Rock]
-Jersey, they're tearing
this place apart!
- Rachel! Rachel!
-// One way or another
I'm gonna find ya//
-//I'm gonna get ya, get ya
get ya, get ya//
- Let me go!
/ One way or another
I'm gonna get ya /
/ I'm gonna get ya, get ya
get ya, get ya /
/ One way or another
I'm gonna see ya /
/ I'm gonna meet ya, meet ya
meet ya, meet ya, one day/
-//Maybe next week
I'm gonna meet ya//
- [ Shouting, Grunting Continue ]
- / I'll meet ya, I'll meet ya /
-[Whistling]
//I will//
/ Drive past your house /
/And if the lights
are all out /
- / I'll see who's around /
- Ooh!
/ One way or another/
//I'm gonna find ya//
//I'm gonna get ya, get ya
get ya, get ya, one way//
- I'm talking about that!
- / Or another I'm gonna win ya /
- / I'm gonna get ya
I'll get ya /
-[Cheering, Hooting]
/ One way or another
I'm gonna see ya /
- Yeah!
- / I'm gonna meet ya, meet ya
meet ya, meet ya /
// One day, maybe next week//
- / I'm gonna meet ya
I'll meet ya /
-[Woman] Yeah!
- Great. Yeah.
- Last call, Lil.
-Start clearin' 'em out.
- You got it.
Let's go.
/ One way or another
I'm gonna lose ya /
- Yeah.
- / I'm gonna give you the slip
A slip of the hip /
- / Or another, I'm gonna lose ya
I'm gonna trick ya /
- [ Whistling, Hooting ]
/ One way or another/
/ I'm gonna lose ya
I'm gonna trick ya, trick ya
trick ya, trick ya //
[Cheering, Singing Fade]
Did you see their faces?
I mean, wow.
They all wanted you, honey.
Even the girls.
Not a duty seat in the house.
- You guys, that was, like,
a one-time performance--
-[Rachel Sighs]
- Hmm?
- That I have to repeat,
like, every night.
Yahoo!
She sang along with a jukebox.
Let's not start polishing a Grammy.
Oh, come on, Rach.
She saved your butt. Admit it.
No. She saved me
from kicking the shit
out of a couple of drunks.
- That's it. Ooh.
- Ooh, that was good.
- Where you goin'?
- I don't know.
I gotta walk or celebrate or--
Ugh, pass out or something.
[ Chuckles ]
Hey, ladies and gents,
how about a big round
of applause for the singing
Coyote from Jersey!
- So I'm a Coyote?
- Five nights a week.
Hey, what is it?
What's wrong?
Why would anything
be wrong?
Um, you called me
in the middle of the night
and said there was an emergency.
What was that for?
I had a good night.
I wanted a good-night kiss.
Well, wait a second.
Where are you going?
Have a nice day,
Mr. O'Donnell.
"" Have a nice day""?
/ Right kind of wrong /
- / Right kind of wrong /
-////[Rap Blaring]
// We likes to party
La-la-di-da-di//
////[Continues]
// On the East Coast
is the place tube//
////[Continues]
// We likes to party
La-la-di-da-di//
[ Matching Rap Rhythm ]
/ Lovin' you /
//Isn't really something
I should do//
/ I should try to be strong /
/ Isn't really something
I should do /
//Shouldn't want to spend
my time with you//
/ I should try to be strong /
/ But, baby, you're the right
kind of wrong /
/ Baby, you're the right kind
of wrong //
What's going on?
Why do we need my guitar?
You'll find out soon enough.
No. This way.
Okay, now there's a seat.
- [ Giggling ]
-Just there.
Uh-huh? Okay?
Take a look.
Your fans wanna hear you sing.
I told you. I-I can't sing my own songs.
I never could.
Well, that's too bad,
because they've requested
to hear your songs.
Be gentle on the keyboard.
I borrowed it from the club.
You did all this
just to help me sing?
I thought maybe we could cure
that stage fright I've heard
so much about.
Kevin, I wish you could.
Come on, let me try.
Tell me what it feels like.
You really wanna know?
Yeah.
You asked for it.
What are you doing?
The only way I can show you...
is to make you...
really... nervous.
The first thing that happens...
is my heart starts to race.
Good.
Racing heart. Yep.
- Got it.
-And then...
my entire body starts shaking.
Shaking body.
I'm-- I'm getting that. Yeah.
And...
then everything gets... a bit...
cloudy.
Clouds are definitely
rolling in.
Then I start...
losing control.
Well, how long
does this usually last?
Oh, it's been known
to last all night.
- That must be horrible.
- It's excruciating.
[ Giggles ]
////[Drum Machine Plays Beat]
[ Moans ]
[ Music Stops ]
I think that audience got more
than they paid for, really.
[Laughs]
What's ""L.M.S. ""stand for?
Lynn Marie Sanford.
It was my mom's guitar.
She died five years ago.
She moved to New York to be
a singer when she was my age.
She came pretty close
to the big time.
Well, what happened?
She hated the stage.
She said it was the scariest
place in the world.
Sounds familiar.
You really want me to sing?
Just tell me
what I have to do.
[ Scoffs ]
[ Sighs ]
Disappear.
All right. No problem.
/ I don't like to /
/ Be alone in the night /
//I don't like to//
/ Hear I'm wrong
when I'm right /
/And I don't like to /
/ Have the rain on my shoes /
/ But I do love you /
/ But I do love /
/You /
////[Beat Plays]
/ I don't like to /
/ See a sky painted grey/
- /And I don't like when /
- [ Bottles Breaks ]
-//Nothing's going my way//
- [ Laughing ]
//And I don't like to
be the one with the blues but I do//
If you wanna write a song.
If you want to be like
a serious songwriter,
you simply gotta go
with the Mac.
Laptop. You can lay your tracks down
on a blank CD, and you're done.
Do you--
Do you have a payment plan?
-// The way you lay
your head upon//
-[Bottles Breaking]
- Play ball! Let's go!
-//My shoulder when you sleep//
- [Cheering]
- Come on, Cammie!
// Oh, I do//
//And I don't like to//
- [ Laughing ]
-//Hear I'm wrong when I'm right//
- [ Cheering ]
-//And I don't like to//
//Have the rain on my shoes//
//But I do love you////
- [ Tires Screeching ]
- Hey!
- [ Horn Honks ]
What are you doing?
What are you,
brain damaged?
You know what kind of maniacs
we got driving through here?
They don't stop for nothin'.
- Whose boat?
- I borrowed it from a friend.
Yeah?
Looks like a guy's car to me.
- How can you tell?
- I've been staring at cars
every day for the last 1 6 years.
- Who is he?
- He's a friend.
Look, I brought you
a turkey sandwich,
no mayo, extra sprouts.
Thank you. Great.
I'm starvin'.
Now tell me about this bar.
Is it a bunch of bankers
havin' martinis after work?
I gotta go. Look.
I love you.
- I love you too. Be careful.
-[Car Horn Honking]
Hey, do I come to your office
and honk? Come on!
I got you a gig. There's this
club where a lot of music people
hang out called the Elbow Room.
My friend's the manager.
He owes mea favor,
and you're it, next Thursday night.
Are you forgetting
about the stage fright?
Uh, what about the bar?
Come on, Kevin.
All I do is sing along
with the jukebox.
See? You're making progress.
A few more nights at my place,
and you'll be cured.
I hate to burst your bubble,
but I'll never be cured. It's genetic.
Stage fright DNA.
Yes, I saw that on E.R. last week.
Okay. Laugh all you want,
but my mom couldn't do it,
and neither can I.
So was your mother afraid
to try?
Look, I just wanna be a songwriter.
Why won't you give up on this?
Because I've been giving up
on people my entire life,
and it's a nasty little habit.
So, you're gonna sing
at the club, or I'll--
Or you'll what?
I'll never kiss you again.
That sounds like a threat,
Mr. O'Donnell.
Well, let's just say...
it's gonna be quite a long,
cold winter.
That's supposed to convince me?
It's working, isn't it?
Your knees are getting weak.
- I'll think about it.
- Try again.
Uh, I'll see
if I can get off work.
You're gettin' warmer.
All right. You win. I'll do it.
Oh, I love winning.
- [ Shouting, Cheering ]
-//Pour some sugar on me//
-//Pour your sugar on me//
- Hey, we have a special treat...
for you tonight,
boys and girls.
- Look who dropped by for a visit.
-//Pour some sugar on me//
- [ Cheering ]
- [ Shouts ]
- No!
I'm a paying customer tonight.
I have class in the morning.
What are you doing?
- Come on, Zoe!
- No!
Zoe! Zoe! Zoe! Zoe!
[ Shouting ]
Time to get wet, girls. Whoa!
-// Well, I'm packing up my game
and I'm gonna head out West//
- [ Hooting, Cheering Continue ]
// Where real women come equipped
with scripts and fake breasts//
//Find a nest in the hills
Chill like Flynt//
//Buy an old drop top
Find a spot to pimp//
-// Well, I'm a real kid
and I'm a real McCoy//
- Who wants some of this?
//And I'm headed out West
sucker, because I wannabe
a cowboy, baby//
// With the top let back
and the sun shine shining//
// Cowboy, baby//
//Ridin' at night
'cause I sleep all day//
- Excuse me,
does Violet Sanford work here?
- Yeah, she's on the bar.
- She's on what?
- She's on the bar.
- What do you guys say?
- [ Together] Yeah!
[ Cheering, Hooting Continue ]
// Yeah, Kid Rock
You can call me Tex//
//Rollin' sunset woman
with a bottle of Becks//
//Seen a slimmyin a 'vette
Rolled down my glass//
//And said, ""Yeah, this dick's
fittin' right in your ass ""//
//I'm flickin' my Bic
up and down that coast and//
-//Keep on truckin'
till it falls into motion//
- Dad! Wait!
-// Cowboy//
- Dad, it's not as bad as it looks.
-//And the sun shine shining//
- Daddy, it's not as bad as it looks.
I just sing here every night.
- People come here to see me.
- Cowboy!
- Say something!
- The guys are putting your
picture up in their booths!
- I gotta go, get up early.
- Dad, it's just a bar.
- You can trust me.
- But you're my daughter.
//I can smell a pig
from a mile away//
// Cowboy//
// With the top let back
and the sun shine shining//
// Cowboy//
// Cowboy////
[Bill's Voice On Machine]
Hi, you've reached Bill Sanford.
- Please leave a message
when you hear the beep.
- [ Machine Beeping ]
[ Violet On Machine ]
Dad, you can't avoid me
for the rest of your life.
I have to come over and do your laundry.
We both know you're
running out of clean shirts.
- I bet the one you're wearing
stinks pretty bad.
- [ Sniffs ]
I'm not gonna apologize
because that would mean
I'm doing something wrong.
And I'm not sure I am, so--
I'm playing at a club tonight.
A real club.
Someone important could hear my song,
and next month somebody
might be singing it on the radio.
-So wish me good luck.
- Good luck.
Anyway, um, I'll call you
and tell you how it goes.
Take care of yourself, old man.
-[Phone Hangs Up]
-[Machine Beeps]
Old man.
All right.
You should be dancing on the floor!
I wanna see your bras!
Ow!
-// Well, my baby and me
went out late Saturday night//
- All right.
//I had my hair piled high and
my baby she looked so right//
// Well, pick you up at 10:00
Got tohaveyouhomeby2:00//
-//Mama, don't know
what I catched off of you//
- [ Yelling ]
-//But that's all right, we're
looking as cool as can be//
- [ Shouting, Indistinct ]
- Is this the greatest party
we've ever been to or what, man?
- [ Shouting ]
Lil, I can only stay two hours.
- What are you talking about?
- I gotta leave early tonight, remember?
- Bourbon.
- Why?
Maybe you haven't noticed all
the bodies you had to crawl over
to get in here tonight.
- Lil, I told you I gotta leave
by 1 0:30 no matter what.
- Four!
- Here.
- Got it. I got it.
Seven.
- /That I love you, yeah /
-[Deejay Scratching Record]
//Hit me//
- Here you go.
- What are you doing?
I gotta go. It's half past.
Can you have Lou call me a cab?
Listen, Jersey. You're not
going anywhere. Not tonight.
This place us out of control.
But, Lil, I told you.
I'm only working two hours--
You wanna sing?
Sing for them.
These people dragged
their asses out here to see us.
This is New York,
and there's a line halfway
around the block.
That's something, Jersey,
whether you believe it or not.
-//Last night a little dancer
came dancing to my door//
- And if I go?
- If you were going,
you would have left by now.
-//Last night a little angel//
//And tonight//
- Where are you?
- Lil won't let me go.
Violet, just walk out.
She doesn't own you.
You can still make it here.
I'm-- I'm sorry.
- I'll call you tomorrow.
- Tomorrow?
Violet.
- What's the story?
- She's not coming.
So what am I supposed to do, Kevin?
I got a whole spot to fill.
I'm sorry, Richie.
I made a mistake.
Whoa, this doesn't change
anything with us, Kevin.
A deal's a deal.
Am I right?
//All she wants to do
is dance, dance, dance//
// Wild-eyed pistol wavers
who ain't afraid to die//
//And all she wants to do is//
/All she wants to do
is dance and make romance /
//She can't feel the heat
Comin' off the street//
- / She wants to party/
- / Ooh /
- / She wants to get down /
//All she wants to do is//
//All she wants to do
is dance//
//And make romance//
- I'm the guy! Me!
- [ Cheering ]
//All she wants to do
is dance//
[ Laughing ]
Zach, who said
you could be up here?
You're not supposed
to be up here.
All right.
Take it easy, Zach.
Zach, take it easy.
-// We barely made the airport
for the last plane out//
- Hey! Hey!
- Hey, hey, knock it off!.
- Kevin!
- [Rachel]Lil!
- Hey!
- [ Grunts ]
- Break it up!
- Kevin, that's enough!
-// 'Cause all she wants to do
is dance//
-[Man]Help! Stop!
- Lou!
- [ Yelling ]
- [ Music Stops ]
- [ Grunting ]
- Kevin, that's enough!
Kevin, that's enough!
- Get off me!
- [Lou]Stop it!
- Kevin, Zach's a regular,
and he was just having fun.
- Having fun with my girlfriend!
- Lou, get him out of here.
- You're gonna chill outside,
or I'm calling the cops.
Out of my way! Move!
[ Kevin ]
Let me go!
- Get the hell out of here!
- Hey, everybody,
free drinks on the house.
I'm paying. Get up here.
Kevin. Kevin.
What is your problem?
Look, I'm sorry about tonight,
but look at this. There was
no way Lil was gonna let me out.
This is not about Lil.
This is about you and this place.
- There is my job.
- It's a goddamn sandbox for
you to stick your head in.
- What is that supposed to mean?
- The place is a joke.
All right?
They don't come to watch you sing.
- They come to watch girls
shaking it on a bar!
- And what would you have me do?
- Sing for quarters in the park?
- Well, at least you'd be
singing your own songs.
I told you I can't do that,
so stop pushing!
I'm just asking you to try,
but I guess that's asking
a bit too much.
Right. It's so easy to be you,
isn't it?
You have no dreams, no hopes,
no chance of getting hurt.
When was the last time
you took a chance on something?
- Some of us don't have that luxury.
- Why is that?
Oh, right. We don't talk about you,
right? It's a big secret.
Come on, Kevin.
Let's play a game.
I'm gonna guess why
you left Australia.
- Doesn't matter.
- You... were in jail.
No, that's not it.
You have a wife and four kids in Sydney.
Come on. Am I getting warm?
Come on, Kevin.
I don't have a lot of time.
Why'd you run away from home?
I didn't have a home.
Is that what you wanted to hear?
I don't have a family.
I mean, that's the big secret.
Are you happy?
Huh? Are you gonna
feel sorry for me now?
You gonna hold me close
while I tell you I had to change
homes every two years?
I had a bad childhood.
Big deal.
I don't need your sympathy,
'cause I'm here,
and I'm living on my two feet
like I wanted to.
That was my dream.
And at least I did it
with a little bit of dignity.
And I didn't.
That's it?
Well, just unbutton the blouse
a little and unzip the pants,
show a little bit offish,
I think you can figure it out.
[Car Door Opens, Closes]
Go on in. Your fans are waitin' for ya
to crawl on a bar.
[Engine Starts]
[Tires Screeching]
I told you not to break the rules.
What are you talking about?
I'm talking about you and your boyfriend
making a scene in my bar.
I'm talking about a friend of mine
inside with a broken nose.
The rules were simple, Jersey.
I've fired girls for a lot less.
What, so I can't have a boyfriend now?
What kind of stupid shit is that?
Hey! This place is my home,
and I'm not willing
to risk everything I have
on your personal life.
It's business,
plain and simple.
This is not business.
I worked my ass off for you,
and you're supposed to be my friend.
I never said I was your friend.
I'm your boss, and you knew
the rules like everybody else.
Will you stop... with ""the rules""?
It's a bar, for Christ's sake!
Then what are you
so upset about?
[ Sniffles ]
/ Please remember/
/ How we laughed
How we cried /
/ How this world
was yours and mine /
/And how no dream
was out of reach /
/ I stood by you
You stood by me /
// We took each day
and made it shine//
// We wrote our names
across the sky//
// We ran so fast
We ran so free//
//And I had you//
//And you had me//
//Please remember////
- // [ Dance ]
- [ Cheering ]
-//I'm just a love machine//
- Oh, my God. Give me a bite.
I'm starving.
-////[Singer Vocalizing]
- Mmm!
- Mmm, thank you.
- How does it feel
to be Mrs. Molinaro?
You know, I think he was a perfect
choice for my first marriage.
[ Both Laughing ]
- [Gloria]Mmm.
- [Bill]Hey, Gloria.
- Oh!
- Thanks for inviting me, uh--
I gotta go to work.
I'm on graveyard tonight.
- Thank you, Mr. Sanford.
- Yeah, well,
it's not worth a hug, dear.
- It's only 50 bucks.
- Aw.
- Your old man's a ten, Vi.
- Eleven, some days a twelve.
Well, it's a beautiful wedding.
No, you can't go. I just want
one picture of you and Violet
dancing together. Come on.
-// Wise men say//
- [ Stammers ]
- Okay. Come on. Smile.
-// Only fools//
//Rushing//
//But I can't//
-//Help//
- Are you really working, or
are you leaving because of me?
-//Falling in love//
- You know I don't like to wear a tie.
// With you//
-////[Continues]
- Ha, ha.
So this is how it's gonna be?
You're not gonna return
my phone calls?
If you needed money,
you should have come to me.
I would have found a way
to take care of you.
Dad, you can't even
take care of yourself.
Hey, I am doing just fine
on my own, thank you very much.
Oh, really? So how come
you're not wearing any socks?
//Falling in love//
-// With you//
- I had a minor disagreement
with a clothes dryer.
//Like a river flows//
-Just face it, Dad. You need me.
-//Surely to the sea//
- And I moved out,
and that's what bothers you.
-//Darling, so it goes//
//Some things//
- No. No.
-//Are meant to be//
What bothers me...
-// Take my hand//
- is, for the first time
in my life,
I was ashamed of you.
-// Take my whole//
- I would have never thought that
would ever have been possible.
//Life too//
//For I can't//
-//Help////
-[Phone Ringing]
////[Music Fades]
[Violet's Voice On Machine]
Hey, it's me.
Leave a message after the beep.
-[Machine Beeps]
-[Kevin] Violet?
I've just finished work,
and in a few hours...
I'm going to unload
three disgusting fish trucks.
I thought maybe you'd like
to come and give me a hand.
- But you're not in.
- Okay, okay, okay.
I'm coming. I'm coming.
Or you're not picking up,
so I'll call back...
because I'm hoping
one day you... will wanna talk.
- [ Dial Tone ]
- Kevin? Hello?
[ Sighs ]
[Thunder Rumbling]
[Phone Ringing]
Kevin? Hello? It's me.
- I'm here.
- [ Woman ] Is this Violet Sanford?
- Yes.
- I'm calling from
Riverview Medical Center.
We have a patient here by the
name of William James Sanford.
Is that your father?
Violet Sanford?
- Yeah?
- Your dad's in recovery right now.
The car struck him
on his right side when
he was walking to the booth.
His right leg is broken,
and there was some arterial damage
we had to go in and repair.
But other than that,
it's just a lot of bumps and bruises.
I'd say he's a pretty lucky guy.
Violet?
I told you, don't come down here.
It's your wedding night.
Oh, are you kidding? Danny's been
in my family for five minutes.
You've been in my family
my whole life.
[ Crying ]
[ Sighs ]
[Monitor Beeping]
[ Moans ]
Mmm, I'm sorry.
I love you... so much.
I never did thank you
for the dance.
That's okay.
That's all right.
[ Labored Breathing ]
[ Crying ]
My tapes. [ Sighs ]
Come on. Just call him.
Just pick up the phone and call him.
[ Scoffs ]
Don't call him.
Told you.
This place is a palace.
It's pretty late.
Are you sure you wanna do this now?
Well, here's my door.
No turning back now. Come on in.
Oh, you're so right.
This place is a palace.
- Would I lie to you?
- This is a great idea. I'm so glad--
- Nice strong pulse.
- Mmm.
Don't look at me like that.
I'm a sick man.
You can eat whatever you want
now, but when we go back home,
it's egg whites
and Lean Cuisines.
- I'll see you later, Bill.
- W-Wait a minute.
What do you mean,
""until we go home""?
- I'm moving back.
- [ Sighs ]
I couldn't do it.
I couldn't sing my songs.
- I was afraid.
- [ Sighs ]
Do you know why Mommy quit?
Yeah, she told me--
'cause she couldn't do it.
No, that's not it.
She wasn't afraid, Vi.
Your mother on stage--
Oh, she was amazing.
Then why did she quit?
Because of me.
Right after you were born,
she told me she wanted to quit,
and I let her.
See, I knew how good she was,
but I never told her.
I loved her...
more than anything.
And I just went on and pretended
that there was no other choice.
- Dad, it's okay.
- No, it's not okay.
I'm not gonna make the same
mistake twice. You're not
goin' back to work for Pete.
I don't care what it takes.
I don't care how many bars
you have to stand on.
You are not comin' home.
I'm not letting you back in the house.
Forget it.
[ Sniffes ]
Are you wearing cologne?
Hmm? No!
Oh, well, it's just a...
splash of Old Spice.
Where did you get Old Spice?
That nice redheaded nurse
gave it to me as a gift.
Then she asked me out
for coffee.
I'm scared.
Are you gonna go on a date?
God, a date.
I better buy a pair of socks.
[ Giggles ]
[ Drum Machine Plays Beat ]
[Neighbor Pounding On Wall]
[ Groaning ]
Okay. Come on in here.
Watch out for the-- Okay. Okay.
[Bill Screaming]
// Try to resist//
Try to hide from my kiss//
// Can't fight the moonlight//
[Pitch Changes]
// You can't fight
the moonlight//
[ Laughing ]
// You'll surrender your heart//
//But you know
But you know that you////
Okay if I eat here at the bar?
- Do you have a reservation?
- Uh, yeah.
It's under, um,
""cast-iron heartless bitch.""
Could it be under
""stubborn and pigheaded""?
Yes. That's the one.
I'll have a double
water on the rocks, please.
- How'd you find me?
- Cammie.
She told me about your pop.
I'm sorry to hear about that.
He's okay.
Good.
- So am I.
- Yeah. Yeah, I can see that.
What's good to eat here?
Lil, you didn't come here to eat.
What do you want?
'Kay.
I just wanted to let you know
you can come back to the bar
whenever you want.
- I appreciate the offer,
but I'm okay here.
- I figured that.
You were never a lifer.
I'm married to that bar.
Hell, I'd, uh--
I'd sleep there if I had the guts
to walk around barefoot.
- [ Laughs ]
- But that's me, you know?
I'm the original Coyote--
just a small town gal trying
to make it in the big bad city.
""Small town gal""?
Piedmont, North Dakota.
You ever tell anyone that,
I'll kill ya.
Take care, Jersey.
[ Machine Beeps ]
You have one new message.
- [ Sighs ]
- [ Cat Meows ]
I have one message in eight hours.
How pathetic am I?
[ Woman ] Violet, this is Lyndsey Morgan
from the Bowety Ballroom.
Listen, we loved your CD,
and we want you to play
in our songwriter's showcase
next Sunday night.
You're on at 10:00 sharp.
So drop your music by the club,
and the house band
can learn your song.
Now if you have any questions,
don't be afraid to give me a shout.
See ya Sunday.
- Here are the keys to the apartment.
It's all yours.
- Thank you.
I can't thank you enough for
subleasing me this place.
You don't know how long I looked.
And when is your boyfriend moving in?
He's actually coming in
tomorrow from Boston.
It's historic, guys.
This is the first night
I've closed early in three years.
Ta-da. Will you hang that
outside for me?
- Hey, Lou, you got that number
I asked you about?
- Yep.
So why are you moving
to Chicago?
[ Sighs ] I'll figure that out
when I get there.
-[Phone Ringing]
- Um, oh.
- Hello.
- Hey, do yourself a favor and
look at page 1 37 of The Voice.
I can't believe
your name is in the paper.
I'm gettin' this framed.
Dad, if you're not ready
in five minutes,
I'm gonna leave without you.
Keep your pants on, will ya?
I'm physically challenged.
[ Muttering ]
I only got three rolls of them.
I hope that's enough.
Dad, I'm only singing
one song.
Right. Better go get
another one.
[ Man Laughing ]
Hey, Bill.
My kid's singing tonight
at some club in the city.
She's a little nervous.
Hey, maybe you can give us
a one, two, three for luck.
You got it. All right, let's give it up
for Bill Sanford's daughter.
- Light 'me up. One, two, three.
- [ Bells Ringing ]
[ Ringing Continues ]
Oh, look, Vi.
- I can't do this.
- [ Tires Screeching ]
- [ Horn Honking ]
-Jesus!
- [ Honking, Screeching Continue ]
Did I mention to you
that I was recently
in a horrific car accident?
I-- I can't do this.
I gotta go back.
- Violet, listen to me.
Are you listening?
- Yes.
You have nothing to be afraid of.
You're already a star.
- Dad, what are you talking about?
I'm a nobody.
- If you're such anybody,
then why did I buy this off Pete
for 20 bucks?
- Why do you have that?
- I saw it on the wall, decided
I wanted the first autograph.
I figured it'd be
a damn good investment.
Now what are you waiting for?
I didn't spend three months
in physical therapy...
just to take a ride
to the state line, you got me?
- Yeah, I got ya.
- So what do you say, Vi?
How about another U-ey?
[ Tires Screeching ]
You guys call in a one, two, three!
Now, let's do it again.
- This time I wanna feel chills!
- [ Bells Ringing ]
There goes Bill again. He's
back for seconds. Come on now!
Let's give him all we got!
- [ Ringing Continues ]
- [ Hooting ] Let's go!
The only reason why I came down
here tonight is to see her fall
on her face.
Oh, take it easy, Rachel.
It's supposed to be a nice night out.
- Excuse me.
- I'm cool. Don't worry about me.
- Hi. Good evening, ladies.
Can I help you?
- [ Together] No.
It's packed, Lyndsey.
The house band has been on
for 15minutes.
If she's not here in five,
she's bumped.
- [ Tires Screeching ]
- [ Man ]Jesus!
Uh, now that we're here,
I'm feeling a little nervous.
Thank you, Mr. Sanford.
Oh, oh, probably just carsick.
Forget I mentioned it.
I'm fine. Have a great show.
Vi.
Get your but in there.
Come on. We're right behind you.
Break a leg, sweetie.
[Announcer]
Ladies and gentlemen,
making her Bowery Ballroom debut,
Miss Violet Sanford!
// [ Rock]
////[Keyboard]
I'm sorry.
[ Chattering ]
/ Under a lovers' sky /
// Gonna be with you//
//And no one's gonna be around//
//If you think
that you won't fall//
/We'll just wait until /
// Till the sun goes down//
/ Underneath
the starlight, starlight /
// There's a magical feelin'
so right//
/ It will take you in tonight /
- /You can try to resist /
- Whoa! Violet!
/Try to hide from my kiss
but you know /
/ But you know that you
can't fight the moonlight /
/ Deep in the dark
you'll surrender your heart /
/ But you know, but you know /
/That you can't fight
the moonlight, no /
/You can't fight it /
/ It's gonna get to your heart /
/There's no escape from love /
/ Once the gentle breeze /
// Weaves its spell
upon your heart//
/ No matter what you think/
//It won't be too long
till you're in my arms//
- Come on, baby. Shake it!
-// Underneath//
- Hey, pinhead.
- /The starlight, starlight /
- That's not long enough, baby!
Now shake it!
Come on. Don't do it, Rach.
He's a big guy, and you're still
on probation.
Don't worry. Those classes
are really paying off.
-//It'll steal your heart tonight//
- [ Grunts ]
// You can try to resist//
/Try to hide from my kiss /
/ But you know, but you know /
/That you can't fight
the moonlight /
/ Deep in the dark
soul surrender your heart /
/ But you know, but you know /
/That you can't fight
the zonlicht /
Okay. Let's give a big Coyote welcome
to LeAnn Rimes.
/You can try to resist /
// Try to hide from my kiss//
//But you know, but you know//
So tell me, what do you do
when you realize that all
your dreams have come true?
You pay off old debts.
/ But you know, but you know
that you can't /
-// Can't fight the moonlight//
- Volume 1 29.
The original appearance
of the Punisher--
the one I cost you.
- Thank you.
-//It will fill
your heart tonight//
- /You can try/
-// You can try to resist//
// Try to hide from my kiss//
//But you know, but you know//
-////[Continues]
- Lil, don't think
your new girl's gonna hack it.
-//But you know, but you know//
-[Crowd Chanting]
Jersey! Jersey! Jersey!
- /That you can't fight
the moonlight /
-[Chanting Continues]
Jersey! Jersey!
/You can try to resist
my kiss /
- / But you know, but you know /
- / Don't you know /
/That you can't fight
the moonlight /
/ Oh, no
You can't fight it /
/ It's gonna get
to your heart //
////[Rock]
Okay. In true Coyote tradition,
I'm gonna make every woman's night...
and auction off the most
handsome little hot tie in the place.
Violet, come on.
You can't do this to me again.
- Here he is, girls.
- [ Cheering ]
- Come on, Dad!
-//All you got is this moment//
Okay, ladies.
The bidding will start at $25.
-//21stcentury'syesterday//
- See, nobody wants to do this.
What are getting me into?
- $25!
- [ Laughing ]
You said you wanted
a more active social life.
Come on, girls.
There's a lot of miles
left on these tires.
- $50!
- Come on, Dad. Strut your stuff.
-//And give me a moment//
- Seventy-five!
// Your moves are so raw//
//I've got to let you know//
-//I've got to let you know//
- Whoa!
[Crowd Shouting, Cheering]
Take-- Take some of it off!.
-// 'Cause I'm not sleepin'//
- Okay, put-- put some of it on.
-// There's something about you girl//
- Yeah, baby!
-// That makes me sweat//
- I'm going 80!
- Ninety-five!
-//How do you feel//
- [ Laughing ]
-//I'm lonely//
- Yeah! All right, Jersey!
-// Can't take it all//
- [Woman]$98.50!
-// What ya gonna do
Gonna live my life//
- A hundred!
//So slide overhear//
-//And give me a moment//
- $1 50!
- Sold!
// Your moves are so raw
I've got to let you know//
- Whoa!
-//I've got to let you know//
- Hey, I'm a Coyote!
-//So slide over here//
- Well, your father has no problem
with stage fright.
-// Your moves are so raw//
- [ Both Howling ]
-//I've got to let you know//
- So tell me,
- what do you do when you realize
all your dreams have come true?
-// You're one of my kind////
////[Piano]
// Time//
//Sometimes the time
just slips away//
//And you're left
with yesterday//
//Left with the memories//
//I//
//I'll always think of you
and smile//
//And be happy for the time//
//I had you with me//
// Though we go
our separate ways//
//I won't forget
so don't forget//
// The memories we've made//
//Please remember//
//I was there for you//
//And you were there for me//
//And  remember//
//Please remember//
//Me//
//I was there for you//
//And you were there for me//
//And remember//
//Please remember me//
//And how we laughed//
//And how we smiled//
//And how this world
was yours and mine//
//And how no dream
was out of reach//
//I stood by you
you stood by me//
// We took each day
and made it shine//
// We wrote our names
across the sky//
// We ran so fast
We ran so free//
//I had you and you had me////
//Knew all about//
// Your bad reputation//
//And now it's bound to be
a heart break situation//
//But I can't help it
If I'm helpless every time//
// That I'm where you are//
// You walk in and my strength
walks out the door//
//Say my name
and I can't fight it anymore//
// Oh, I know I should go//
//But I need your touch
just too damn much//
// Yeah, yeah//
//Lovin'you, yeah//
//Isn't really something
I should do//
//I shouldn't want to spend
my time with you, yeah//
// Well, I should try
to be strong//
-//I should try to be strong//
-//But, baby, you're the right
kind of wrong//
//Right kind of wrong//
//Baby, you're the right kind
of wrong//
//Now, baby, you're the right
kind of wrong////
//I don't like to//
//Be alone at night//
//And I don't like to//
//Hear I'm wrong
when I'm right//
//And I don't like to
Have the rain on my shoes//
//But I do love you//
//I don't like to//
//See the sky painted grey//
//And I don't like to
be the one with the blues//
//But I do love you//
//Love everything about//
// The way you're loving me//
// The way you lay your head
upon my shoulder//
// When you sleep//
//And I love to kiss you
in the rain//
//I love everything you do//
// Oh, I do//
//And I don't like to//
//Be alone in the night//
//Hear I'm wrong
when I'm right//
//And I don't like to//
//Have the rain on my shoes//
//But I do love you//
//But I do love you////
Please rate this subtitle at www.osdb.link/fk3d
Help other users to choose the best subtitles