Downloaded from
YTS.MX
Official YIFY movies site:
DEAD SNOW
Hey... Hey...
Listen to this.
It says that a man was
skiing in the mountain wilds.
It actually says "mountain wilds".
In the middle of two mountain tops,
he starts yelling for his dog.
- Avalanche!
- Not very clever...
When he was found two days later he
had dug himself six meters... Downwards.
What?
That's pretty normal actually,
because if you're taken by
an avalanche you get so...
disoriented that you
won't know which way is up.
So many start to dig the wrong way.
- I would easily find the right way.
- You should just spit!
- Haven't you been in the military?
- No, why?
If you're stuck under the
snow after an avalanche,
- you should spit to find out which way to dig.
- Just lie there and slobber on yourself?
- Slobber?
- It means drooling.
- Dribble.
You owe me a coke.
The spit will run downwards, so you
just dig the opposite way.
- Gravity, as easy as that.
- Can you remember stuff from the military?
I can only remember my duty number...
69...
- Speaking of 69 Martin...
- No thanks. Not interested.
Oh, darn it.
- Of course I mean with Hanna's cousin.
- Kris?
- Yeah, is she single?
- She is very single.
I don't know her, but
Hanna says she is...
...Very single.
Do you think there's any chance
to slam it in her number two?
If you spit first.
- Where do you think Sara is now?
- I don't know...
She'll probably be there
tonight or tomorrow.
I don't understand why she bothers
taking the trip over those mountains.
So, tell me about the
boys that are coming.
Ok. Martin, which is
the best looking one...
- Is mine.
- How did it turn out with him?
- Will he finish the studies?
- I'm not sure. Don't think he is either.
It's not exactly good to be a medical
student and be afraid of blood.
- Poor Martin.
- Martin is scared of blood,
and wants to be a doctor?
- Seriously?
- Yes.
Then there's Vegard, who's with Sara.
- And then there's Erlend.
- The worlds biggest movie geek.
And Roy...
...the horniest boy
north of the polar circle.
- He's single, you can have him.
- Thanks... Nice.
How does it feel to
be on the losing team?
That overtaking earlier...
Ok...
Just follow the scooter trail.
It will only take 45 minutes.
When you arrive, I will have unpacked
most of the luggage and heated the cabin.
- Is there cell phone reception there?
- No, we lost that half an hour ago.
Then how am I supposed to make
heavy-breathing phone calls?
The emergency number.
Take care.
Mile after mile, after mile!
Hold on a second...
I have a question.
How many movies begin
with a group of friends
going on a trip without cell phone reception?
- Friday the 13th.
They don't have reception, because
they don't have cell phones.
Evil Dead 1 and 2.
Yes, sort of... Except
that also counts the sequel
as a remake with higher budget.
- Ok, Ok...New rule.
- No movie talk for an hour.
- Good suggestion.
It's for your own good Erlend.
If you want to dip your balls this weekend,
you should stop the nerd alert.
And then you have April Fool's
Day from... 1984 I think.
Now that's a classic.
- Don't you agree?
- Yes.
Let's go.
- Damn, I'm so warm now.
- It's beautiful here.
- So, what should we do?
- Watch a movie?
- We unpack and get acquainted.
- I have a better idea...
Left foot on green.
...Already is.
Why do we even play this game?
Because Hollywood told
us it is great fun.
- Right foot on red.
- It has to be the most boring game...
That... ever...
- No joking?
- Of course.
One more time?
Lie down and let me show you
sedation from the Middle Ages.
- What are you doing?
- Like that. Put your arms behind... There.
- You're sitting on my hands.
- It's how it works.
- Now close your eyes.
- No.
- Close your eyes.
- No, I'm not closing them.
Don't... Martin, Stop.
Quit it...
Just relax.
- Martin!
- Cut it out!
I was only kidding.
Why do you do that? I get
claustrophobic and I can't breathe.
- Sorry. Look now.
- No.
- How does that work?
- Get some beer.
- What?
- Beer. Beer, beer.
Beer, beer, beer.
Hello?
There's someone out there.
I saw someone.
It's probably Sara.
- Not Sara...
- Are you sure it wasn't an elk?
I can damn well tell the difference
between a human and an elk!
I don't see anything.
There's nothing here. Vegard was right,
it was probably just an animal.
Typical women. They get
frightened by everything.
Is it possible to get
a cup of coffee here?
Who made the coffee?
Ecological...
- Didn't it taste good?
- No, it didn't.
What are you nice kids
doing at a place like this?
Easter vacation.
- Is it your cabin?
- No, my girlfriend's.
And who's the lucky one?
She's not here right now
- she's skiing across Istind.
- Across Istind?
She's a bit more athletic
than the rest of us.
Is the...
Is the terrain dangerous?
The terrain is the least of your
problems up there, put it that way.
I presume you spoiled little shit-heads didn't
bother to check out the local history
before you came waltzing in on that
bloody snow tractor of yours.
Things have happened here...
Things that people
don't like to talk about.
During World War II, Øksfjord was an
important location for the Germans. It was...
Almost like a middle station
for German destroyers.
It was an important link to stop
convoys between Britain and Russia.
"Einsatz"
That was the name of the forces
that were stationed there.
In contrast to most places where...
the Germans got along with the civilians,
but that was not the case here.
It was under the leadership of...
Colonel Herzog.
So the civilians went through hell.
The people were tortured, beaten
and maltreated every day.
Trust me when I tell you...
These were evil hellish bastards.
It was towards the end of the war
when they stepped over the line.
The Germans started to realize they were
beaten, and the Russians were on their way.
So the Germans went into
every house and stole all
gold, silver and shiny
items they could find.
Those who protested...
got a bullet between their eyes.
But they got one hell
of a surprise afterwards.
The citizens had secretly teamed up.
And decided that enough was enough.
All the anger and rage the
3,000 citizens had built up
during the last three years
needed to be unleashed.
So they had started gathering
all the weapons they could find.
That was basically scythes,
axes, knives, shovels...
Everything that could break a skull.
So...
they ambushed the bastards
in the middle of the night.
The soldiers didn't have a chance,
and they knew it. Several got killed.
But the devil himself...
Colonel Herzog with several
of his men managed to escape.
They ran up in the mountains.
And took with them lots of the stolen goods,
the greedy pigs that they were.
Several civilians followed them, but
they lost the tracks up in the mountains.
In these exact mountains...
Where they most likely froze to death.
Because of that...
people tread lightly up here.
There's an evil presence here.
An evil you wouldn't want to wake.
Yeah, we have to be careful
so we don't wake up the evil.
I should get moving.
Remember what I told you.
We're actually all medical students,
so I think we'll do fine.
Unfortunately we haven't learnt to banish
evil yet, but I think that's on next semester.
But what if you're holding your own
intestines in your hands. What do you do then?
Or if you get your arms and legs torn off.
What do you do then?
Have you learned that yet?
Thanks for the coffee.
Sara?
Sara...
Hello?
Is there anybody there?
I have a weapon.
Are you sure we shouldn't
wait till tomorrow?
She'll probably be here during the day.
It's no problem.
You're probably right...
I just have a bad feeling.
She'll probably be here soon.
Listen...
If I'm not back tomorrow...
Just listen!
Follow the scooter trails
back down to the car...
And get help, ok?
- Ok.
I'll go find her.
- See you later.
- Drive carefully.
Ok boys, we want a clean race.
You'll start at my signal,
and no dirty tricks.
- Please, just one dirty trick.
- Not even one.
Are the drivers ready?
On your marks... Get set... Go!
Erlend!
Hello?
Hi.
Ah, fuck!
Calling Doctor Hovden...
Dr. Hovden to the emergency room.
I see you're not exactly rid
of that little problem of yours.
I assume there's not much
action when Aunt Flow visits.
God damn, you're so childish.
How the hell are you going to manage?
Six years of medical studies
and you still almost vomit from a tiny cut.
You can be a baker perhaps?
- Does anyone want a beer?
- Are you ok?
- Yeah...
- Sorry.
Cunt bag!
Check this out.
It says 1942.
- 1942?
- Hey, hey, it's mine.
Let's wait till Sara and Vegard return.
We won't touch it before then.
SARA!
Sara!
We are two small pretty ladies.
Hey, hey. Let's not get crazy here.
- We don't know who it belongs to.
- That box has been here for 50 years.
We just take what we want, cash in,
and pay down our student loans.
It hasn't been there for 50 years,
without anyone noticing it.
50 years? It's 100, I promise you that.
- People have seen it, and it's just flemflams.
- Huh? Fle...?
Flemsflams? Flemsflams…? Flemsflams!
- No, I'm going to take a shit.
- Godspeed.
Good luck. Name him after me.
Ok. A joke...
This one is good. It contains
both poo, pee and sperm.
Once upon a time there was a poo...
There are no good jokes that don't
contain poo, pee or sperm.
Kris?
No, don't...
- And you think that is a joke?
- It's a good joke.
You took a long time.
Did you see Kris?
Yes.
Fuck.
Erlend?
Err... Erlend, is that you?
Oh shit.
Erlend, stop that shit.
Erlend?
Help... Help!
Help! Help!
- What the hell? It's in the middle of the song.
- Shut up!
I thought I heard something.
Kris?
Kris!
She's not answering. I've yelled
several times, she doesn't reply.
She's probably fucking with you.
Don't talk to me like
I'm five years old, Martin.
Hanna. She's wasted,
she probably fell asleep in the john.
I'll go look for her, ok?
Clever, we'll shoot her.
Take it with you.
It's that maniac from earlier.
We'll go look for her, ok?
Someone checks the outhouse, and
someone checks around the cabin...
Shotgun!
Martin, can't I try it? Let me hold it.
- No.
- Yes, come on.
- Not now.
- Come on, just let me hold it.
No...
- Is it heavy?
- A little.
- Let me check it out.
- Later perhaps.
Can you see anything?
- I have a shotgun here. I have a shotgun!
- Sorry, sorry.
Martin?
Check this.
What a nice trip... Fantastic...
Kris? Are you taking a shit?
Have you dozed off?
- She wasn't there.
- Stop it.
She wasn't there.
What does that mean?
She wasn't at the outhouse
or around the cabin.
We found this though.
- Let's see. Maybe she's inside it.
- Stop fucking around.
- It's Sara's.
- Sara's?
- Where did you find it?
- Just behind the cabin.
I get a bad feeling from this.
We have to go find her,
she could freeze to death.
- Ok, we get dressed and go look for her.
- So we'll just trudge around in the forest?
Where did we just come from Martin?
We've just been outside.
Oh, thank God.
I can't see anything.
Pull!
Fuck! Move the sofa
in front of the door.
And stay away from the windows!
Get it out!
Come on and twist.
Leave the cushions!
Stay calm!
They can't get in here.
The table!
Martin! Martin!
Einsatz...
Zomb... Zombies...
Don't get bitten! Don't get bitten, ok?!
Stop that rubbish,
what the hell are we going to do?
We have to get to the car.
Help me!
I said we should have
gone to a Sunny Beach!
Martin...
Martin, don't bite.
Now it's suddenly totally quiet.
Stay here and become
lunch for the rest of...
- We have to do something.
- Like what?
We can't just sit here.
We must try to find the car.
We find the road back and get help.
Only Vegard knows the way, and
the tracks are covered with snow.
I know...
We have to do something...
We can't just sit here and wait for...
Wait for it to fix itself,
we have to do something.
What if we split up?
Two can look for the car, while
two waits here for Vegard.
Those who eventually leave will most
likely get those bloody bastards after them.
If two go outside and make a noise,
it will attract... Those creatures.
At the same time the two
others run into the woods.
Then we'll just run towards the fjord.
There are people down by the fjord,
we will have to get help.
Who will get to be those
lucky bastards acting as bait?
You do something too!
Where are you, you cowardly bastards?!
Are you afraid to come out in daylight?!
Fuck, was that too much?
Do you think they'll get pissed?
Come on.
Fuck...
Sara?
Come on!
Cowardly bastard.
Ok...
Do you recognize any of this?
Not a chance.
Everything looks the same...
- Which way?
- If we both go downhill...
- We have to split up.
- What?
One of us have to get down
to the damn car and get help.
- We go to that car together!
- Liv, listen to me.
We don't stand a chance on our own,
we have to go together.
- One of us have to get to the car...
- Please, we can't! I don't want to go by myself!
Liv, listen to me!
You saw what happened to Erlend.
We don't stand a chance on our own.
We have to go together...
- We run together.
Are you sure that thing will work?!
Have you ever tasted
moonshine from Finnmark?
Throw!
Hi. My name is Martin Hovden, and we're
staying at a cabin in Øksfjord... And...
Just up in the mountains. We're under
attack by something that looks like...
German soldiers from WWII.
And now we managed to set the
cabin on fire, and... Hello?
Hello!
- That fucking cunt hung up on me!
- Of course she did, what you said sounds -
- insanely absurd!
- Then what the fuck should I say?
Say that we are under
attack by terrorists!
Say that they have missiles. They will
bring helicopters and all that shit.
Brilliant.
Fucking cunt, it's out of battery!
Come!
- We have to get over to that shack!
- The shack? What the hell are we doing there?
We don't have time for that now.
- I can't see anyone.
- I'll look for some light.
You know what we have to do, right?
- Right?
- Yes.
A little more.
Duck!
Where have you been?
Where the hell did
you get a machine gun?
I've kept myself busy.
Where are the others?
Hanna and Liv are looking
for the car to get some help.
The others...
They...?
Behind you!
No, no, no, no, no, no...
What is it?
Do you remember what
Erlend said. Do you?
Don't get bitten. No matter
what you do; Don't get bitten.
- Then you turn into...
- Isn't your grandfather half Jewish?
You don't think they would
recruit someone half Jewish?
You'll get infected if you...
You'll be like them.
You saw what they did to Vegard. It didn't
exactly look like they wanted team mates.
Do you think I'm willing
to gamble on that?
- What are you doing?
- We had...
We learned about amputation, remember?
What the fuck are you doing?
No, no, no, no, no!
Let's sledge that fucker
and get out of here.
Run, for fuck's sake!
Oh, fuck...