Someone needs to stop Clearway Law.
Public shouldn't leave reviews for lawyers.
Stop!
Fuck you.
Hibisawa!
Stop!
No way.
"Wanted: Yusuke Hibisawa"
You bastard!
YUSUKE HIBISAWA
Help!
Don't!
YUSUKE HIBISAWA
I'll kill her.
Let her go!
"Foreign Ministry,
Deputy Director: Katsuya Seta"
Any comment on the testimony?
You must have something to say.
KATSUYA SETA
Have you received money?
from the Mafia?
KATSUYA SETA
No comment.
You used ODA as a cover.
KATSUYA SETA
I don't know. Out of my way.
The lives of innocent children
are being taken!
Mr. Seta, give us your statement.
"The Municipal Court"
It's Maruo!
Here he comes.
You bastard!
Murderer!
Any word of apology?
TAKESHI MARUO
Congressman Maruo,
is your son really innocent?
TAKESHI MARUO
He was falsely accused.
It's over anyway!
Another Criminal Dies"
"Mysterious Deaths"
"Series of Deaths"
"Heart Attack"
"Sudden Deaths"
Yet another criminal has died.
They all died of heart attacks
without any history of illness.
Police are looking for a connection
between these mysterious deaths.
What is it?
Hey!
"Killers Found Dead"
A follow-up report.
The Ministry of Health, Labor
and Welfare have announced...
that these deaths may have been
caused by an unknown pathogen.
The victims so far,
are all criminals or suspects...
and those wanted by the police.
They are working on a solution as
it is becoming a worldwide phenomenon.
The strange deaths that are
happening is God's work.
God has sent the sinners to hell.
He has raged against
the evil of mankind.
Let Him light our way!
"Savior Kira"
Kira's awesome.
Who is he anyway?
Don't you know? He's our savior.
"Praise Kira"
"Please kill more criminals
and make this a better world."
"The thought of them in fear
makes me smile."
Kira's just a murderer.
"He's an angel of the Underworld."
"Criminals deserve to die."
"I want the lot dead."
Got it?
No, not yet.
"Trash to trash can,
criminals to Kira"
"Kira is a devil.
He's the one who should be punished!"
"No one bullies me anymore
at school."
"Thanks to Kira."
He's the talk of the net.
I think it's very likely that Kira exists.
He definitely exists.
They're all criminals, right?
I think it's way too extreme.
Criminals should die anyway.
Kill my parents, too.
Just kidding!
We interrupt our program
for this news.
The suspect who broke into
a consumer finance company in Tokyo...
has been identified.
His name is Hiromichi Imaizumi,
age 45.
The police say
that he is deeply in debt...
which could be the motive for
this armed robbery.
We give you live report
from the scene.
"HIROMICHI IMAI..."
Live from Shinjuku.
Three employees have been killed,
and five hostages remain.
We can hear the suspect shouting.
Five hours have passed since
the holdup began, but still no sign of...
I see people coming out.
A riot squad is
entering the building.
The suspect is still inside.
The hostages are coming out.
They're all safe!
We've just received news
that the suspect is dead.
According to the employees
held hostage...
Imaizumi suddenly
clutched his chest and collapsed.
Another mysterious death.
Is that it?
I can't think of anything else.
It's Kira. He did it.
Unbelievable!
Here.
Up the middle.
Yeah!
Excellent!
Show off.
It's your fault.
You're impossible.
You thief.
Future Superintendent, betting?
I'll buy you lunch.
That money's not clean.
I worked hard for it.
I wanted to celebrate.
Celebrate what?
The notice board.
You've passed the Bar Exam.
I'm the one who wanted
to be a district attorney.
You don't have to rush it, Shiori.
I just want to catch up with you.
I support Kira.
He's our savior.
But he just ignores civil rights
and false charges.
I can't approve of him.
Does studying law help?
Kira helps.
Hear hear!
Let's do a research on Kira.
They're all talking about Kira.
He's the god of justice.
That sounds too arrogant.
Oh really?
All criminals should be
punished by the law.
I might do the same
if I had his special powers.
Never.
You have your own way of
changing the world with law.
The law has its limits.
There are limits to everything.
Last month, I hacked into the database
of the Police Agency.
I needed to find out...
whether the criminals were
receiving adequate punishment.
But what I saw was the limit
to the justice I believed in.
This can't be...
"Wanted"
"Case Dropped"
"Unsolved"
Many criminals were
never captured for some reason.
The secret data showed
they were free from punishment.
"Takuo Shibuimaru"
"Case Dropped"
We were kept in the dark about that
to avoid confusion.
Is that really... possible?
I couldn't believe it, either.
A MONTH AGO
That's why I needed to
see for myself.
You got away with murder.
Is that fair?
I get carried away sometimes.
And then...
I hear this voice.
What does it say?
"Kill him!"
Just kidding.
You've taken years off my life.
Did you hear it?
The cry of the parent whose kid I killed
when they heard the verdict.
"Bring back my child!"
What're you looking at?
A relative of the kid?
This reminds me.
How it felt as the knife
slipped into the flesh...
and cut through his heart.
Why am I here?
I don't remember.
No one can put me behind bars.
Why did you go there?
It's dangerous.
Shiori, do you still
disapprove of Kira?
Do you honestly believe
they'll be punished by the law?
I will not tell her the rest.
No one will know my secret.
"The Compendium of Laws"
"Whoever's name is written on
this notebook will die".
The trial of the high school girl
murder case was held today.
The alleged killer, Kaonuma
showed no sign of remorse...
making the victim's family
even angrier.
Yosuke Kaonuma allegedly kidnapped
Tae Taeyama in Nagano...
and dragged her into a public toilet
where he stabbed her to death.
"KAONUMA"
He sent a letter to the papers
admitting his deeds.
The police are searching thoroughly
for other charges.
Don't forget your handkerchief.
Got it.
Then off you go.
You're up at last.
I envy college students.
Be careful of strangers.
I will. Bye.
Bye.
Light, hurry and eat up your breakfast.
Okay.
"A Sudden Death in Jail"
"Yosuke Kaonuma"
"YOSUKE KAONUMA"
Aren't you having breakfast?
Remember him?
"TAKUO SHIBUIMARU"
What is it?
Are you alright?
Help!
Hey!
What's wrong?
Wake up.
Takuo!
He's dead.
What's happening?
Shit!
Glad you like it.
What's the matter?
Can't you believe your eyes?
So, the god of death pays me a visit.
I dropped the notebook.
Are you taking it away from me?
Finders keepers. It's all yours.
Do I have to give you my life
in return?
Don't worry. If you don't want it
pass it on to someone else.
In which case, I'll erase
your memory of the "Death Note".
Is that all?
You may experience agony and fear
that only the user will come to know.
Well, that might not concern you.
Can other people... see you, too?
Only the people
who touch the "Death Note".
Tell me your name.
Curious?
Call me "Ryuk".
Ryuk...
FOUR MONTHS LATER
THE METROPOLITAN POLICE DEPARTMENT
It's impossible.
We can't make this case.
The victims are criminals and
are scattered all over the world.
We see no connection whatsoever.
Chief.
This may be caused by
some unknown virus after all.
Want to throw it over to
the Ministry of Health?
I'm convinced
that this is a massacre.
I will not tolerate it;
the way he carries out his crimes.
We must get the bastard.
We're with you all the way, Chief.
I have to see the Commissioner.
THE NATIONAL POLICE AGENCY
I'm here, Sir.
Matsubara, when did you come back?
Yesterday.
The ICPO have concluded
that the culprit is in Japan.
How did they conclude that?
The first death occurred in Japan.
So the culprit must be here.
That's what "L" says.
"L"?
Oh him.
He's cracked many unsolved cases
all over the world.
He's our last chance.
Watari.
We can contact "L"
only through Watari.
I've been asked to present
this message from "L".
Hello everyone. I am L.
The unexplainable deaths that
have occurred around the world...
is most likely caused by a single genius;
a slaughter by a vicious human being.
This data shows the deaths in Asia
caused by the Micrwa virus...
along with the distinctions of sex
age and nationality of the deceased.
A distribution chart.
A natural occurrence would show
a gentle slope like this.
Now, this is the chart of
the unexplainable deaths.
I see.
Are you suggesting that
the deaths are unnatural?
Yes.
I will call the culprit,
"Kira" for now.
But that doesn't necessarily mean
that he did it alone.
This shows the number of people
and the success rates of the crime.
Group crimes are much less
successful.
If we assume
that this is a group crime...
he would have to have at least
80 accomplices around the world.
With 80 accomplices,
the success rate would drop enormously.
This indicates that it is being done
by an individual.
Then how do you explain
all the killings at the same time?
Your theory won't work.
I could narrow the profile down and
prove to you, how he executes his plan.
How?
This is all for now.
Until then, good-bye.
You don't agree with him?
It's not a matter of agreeing,
we have no other choice.
I will make Yagami the leader of
the Investigation Team.
Yes, Sir.
"Kira"
Look Ryuk.
They're all talking about him
on the net.
The world can feel
that justice indeed exists.
"Kira", that's me.
Feeling good, huh?
They all know that the bad guys
are being eliminated.
The good will rejoice
and the bad will tremble in fear.
History is about to change.
"Death Note" will help make
a crime-free world.
The future is in my hands.
What a hero!
They've sent me news about Kira.
"A news flash"
We bring you live report...
Who's he?
From the International
Criminal Police Organization.
"My name is Lind L. Tailor,
known as L."
"I have been asked by the ICPO
to help find the serial killer."
"This is one of the most
brutal crimes in history."
"The mastermind behind this,
known as Kira..."
"has an extraordinary ego,
and is a vile and immature criminal."
"Immature" is right.
"I, L will assure you that
Kira will be arrested at all cost."
Be my guest.
"Kira, I can easily read
your moves..."
"because of your immaturity."
"You are not allowed
to exist in this world."
"You are far lower than
the criminals you've eliminated."
You are, too.
I'll let the world know.
"However, there are many
who support Kira."
"He has taken the law
into his hands."
It's a pity I can't play games
with you anymore.
"But if we allow people
to be judged this way..."
"our civilization will revert to
a world of brutality."
40 seconds...
Call an ambulance!
Impressive.
So, Kira...
you can kill people
without lifting a finger.
Hear this, Kira.
The man you've just killed
is a convict on death row.
It was hidden from the media, and
his arrest was strictly confidential.
We made him appear as me.
The real L is still alive.
Kill me if you dare!
You can't, can you?
And Kira...
I have new piece of information.
You are now around Tokyo area.
We've made you think it was worldwide
but the broadcast was restricted.
The first crime occurred in Japan,
so we knew you were here somewhere.
But now, we're sure.
Awesome!
This isn't a game!
Watch your mouth.
Sorry.
The police are right behind you.
Kira.
We will solve every mystery
and hunt you down without fail.
Your penalty is death!
My penalty?
I am justice!
No, I am justice.
Savior of the weak
and god of the new world.
The ones who disobey are evil.
You kill in the name of justice.
Humans are fun!
I've gotta see who wins.
Right.
Chief, I've confirmed.
The fake L on TV has actually died.
L actually narrowed the culprit down.
They've sacrificed the life of a convict.
That makes them no different
from Kira.
"L Vs Kira"
"Convict Killed On Air"
"Kira, the Killer"
"A Full Investigation"
"Detective L Vs Kira"
"Heart Attack, Lind L. Tailor"
"Kira Kills Convict"
At first I thought it was
"Candid Camera".
What do you think of Kira?
He should leave it to the police.
And the court.
What?
Did you see the news?
Oh that.
Come in.
Sayu!
They let a person die on TV.
I thought it was a dirty trick
using a convict.
I knew you'd be on Kira's side.
He's far better than L.
Kira is a murderer.
What he's doing isn't justice.
But the crime rate is dropping.
He's just holding us down with fear.
Think of it as a revolution.
Revolutions have betrayed us.
What a fighter!
Shut up.
Huh?
Nothing. Let's go outside.
Wanna try it, too?
Why not.
I can't... with people around.
Not unless it were our last kiss.
What if she were to discover
that you are Kira?
I believe Shiori would understand
someday.
L, here's a report from
the Investigation Team.
Please begin.
This chart as requested by L,
shows the victims' times of deaths.
I see nothing special here.
Have you heard of?
The Law of Large Numbers?
Large Numbers?
It's a theorem Bernoulli created
in observing nature.
Is L watching this?
It's connected to L's computer.
We split this seemingly random data
into seven sections.
Is L doing that?
I guess.
What is that?
It looks familiar.
A timetable.
A college students' schedule.
Mondays start from third period.
Tuesdays have early starts.
College student Kira,
who doesn't kill during class.
You're in a good mood.
Huh, am I?
You've promised to tell me
how things are going with Shiori.
No, I haven't.
I'm curious, too.
What's going on with you and her?
Father's home.
Don't run away from me!
You're back.
Welcome home.
Light and Shiori are...
Blabbermouth.
What about him?
Here you are.
It's nice drinking at home.
I knew you were exhausted.
Why?
You're in charge of Kira's case.
Why would I be?
Seems like there's a lot on your mind.
Father, I want to help you.
Light.
I know you've helped us
several times before.
You have a sharp mind.
And I'm very proud of you.
I'm proud, too.
That's right.
But this time, we're dealing with
a dangerous killer.
He's a devil that kills
without doing anything himself.
I can't have you involved.
But I could...
No.
This is my case.
Your time will come
5 or 10 years from now.
Save your strength for then.
Don't rush it.
I understand.
I'll go study.
For 10 years from now.
Father.
But if something were to
happen to you...
I'd send Kira to the gallows.
Can you believe that your father
was in charge of the case?
Police's database?
This is today's report on
the investigation.
They know Kira is a student.
24 criminals are dying per day!
Precisely one per hour.
What does this mean?
Kira isn't a student after all
That's not what he's telling us.
Then what?
He can manipulate the times of death.
Manipulate the times of death?
And one more thing.
Our information has been
leaking out to Kira.
It was three days ago
that we discovered he was a student.
From the next day,
the time became irregular.
Which means...
Kira is telling the police
that he is amongst us.
Don't you think it's a quiet afternoon
for a revolution?
The crime rate is dropping
thanks to Kira.
We're getting closer to
a crime-free world.
Who could have imagined
such a future was possible?
What's the matter, Ryuk?
Tired of apples?
There's no one...
I'm being followed. Since when?
The day before yesterday.
Why didn't you tell me?
I'm not on your side nor L's.
Police, right?
No, they can't be onto me yet.
Who can he be?
Light.
We, gods of death survive on
the years of human lives.
What do you mean?
People who die because of the book,
leave behind the years...
You take away the years
they were supposed to live, right?
How do you think
we've come to know your names?
You can see them.
Uh-huh.
Your names and the years you'll live.
You can see the years I have left
and his name, too?
Don't you want to see like me?
I might.
What do I give you in return?
Half the years of your life.
No way.
Then how will you get his name?
Chief, three others died in jail.
Shirami cut his fingers
and drew a large star on the wall.
Yadanaka left a suicide note.
And Tobe escaped from his cell
and ran into the lavatory...
where he died of heart attack.
Mr. Yagami.
Tell the press that it was
nothing more than a heart attack.
Why?
It seems like Kira is trying to
test something with these deaths.
See?
It's all here; the information
they didn't give in their statement.
The killings were carried out
just as I'd written.
What a surprise!
Today in Kanagawa?
at 2:40 in the afternoon...
here was a robbery at Teikai Bank
which left three employees dead.
Three men disappeared with
5 million yen.
Later, two of them were captured,
but one is still on the run.
He is Kiichiro Osoreda, age 36.
His past convictions were...
Ryuk.
Huh?
People who touch the "Death Note"
can see you, right?
So what?
The bus is starting.
The bus is a nice change.
There's someone following me
for the past three days.
Why are you following me?
Are you someone from
the inquiry agency?
I don't know
what you're talking about.
What is this?
If you wanna live, do as I say.
Shut up! Be quiet!
Light...
Call the company.
This is Sasaki on bus 124.
This bus is mine!
If you want the hostages alive,
get me 100 million.
"I'll find a chance and grab him."
Don't. It's too risky.
You must leave it to me.
How could I trust you?
I am the son of a cop.
Let me go.
Wait.
I can save you from him.
How will I know
that you're not an accomplice?
Accomplice?
In most cases, they team up
and one of them works as a lookout.
Alright
The FBI?
His name... Raye Iwamatsu.
Hey!
What're you up to?
Kid, you have some nerve.
What in the hell are you?
Can you see me?
Where did you come from?
I see. A piece of the "Death Note".
You monster!
Get down!
Too bad.
I'm the god of death
so I don't die easily.
Stop!
Stop the bus!
Kiichiro Osoreda, car accident.
On March 29th, 2006...
he gets on the 10:12 Kyonan bus
bound for the Okukawa Garage.
He carries a gun with 8 bullets,
and tries to rob the bus...
but sees a horrifying phantom
and starts to fire at it.
With no bullets left,
he hurries off the bus and...
You.
If you have questions,
come to me directly.
I won't run or hide.
Let's go.
Your mother's coming.
And the busjacker?
Died instantly.
Serves him right.
The police are all over the place.
We should...
It's okay.
I've already told the police
about what we saw.
So lie down and rest.
Promise me you'll never
do it again.
If something were to happen to you,
I don't know what I'd do.
Shiori...
You're back.
Hi.
Is something the matter?
It's nothing.
"He which made them at the beginning
made them male and female."
"A man shall leave father and mother,
and cleave to his wife."
"And they twain shall be one flesh."
The Bible.
When are we going to church
to meet with the priest?
Is Saturday okay?
Fine.
Raye, you must be very careful.
You're dealing with Kira.
Who used to go on
dangerous missions for L?
You've changed me.
The new victim left a note.
"L, DID YOU KNOW?"
"THE GOD OF DEATH, EATS..."
"NOTHING BUT APPLES"!
Sorry.
There can't be only one FBI agent.
Suspecting that Kira was someone
within the authority...
L must have had the FBI
secretly follow me.
That would mean he's not
the only agent in Japan.
If I kill him, I'll be suspected.
But what if all the FBI agents
on this case were to die?
Hey, Light.
The FBI aren't criminals.
Killing them anyway?
"Minami-Aoyama Catholic Church"
Raye.
I'm sorry, Naomi.
I just got a call.
I'll join you later.
But Father made time for us.
Patch things up for me.
"Raye Iwamatsu. I am Kira.
Use the transceiver inside."
"I will talk to you directly."
Hello, I am Kira.
I am watching your every move.
Do not look around. Face forward.
Remember, I can always kill you.
How will I know you're not a fake?
I'll show you.
See the man sitting next to you
His name is Taruhito Ozaki,
arrested for rape two years ago.
But the victims feared revenge,
and did not press charges against him.
He deserves to be punished.
Taruhito Ozaki heart attack
Taruhito Ozaki sits on
the right hand side of the train.
After it leaves Akasakabashi Station,
he will die quietly from a heart attack.
Stay calm.
Now quietly, see if he's dead and
make him look like he's sleeping.
Do you believe I'm Kira now?
You killed him just to prove that?
Just answer my questions.
Tell me how many people from the FBI
are here in Japan.
If you refuse, I'll start killing
the passengers one by one.
There are 11 people besides myself.
Do you know
all their names and faces?
No.
I'm telling you the truth.
But surely, you must know
who your leader is, don't you?
I do.
You'll find five pieces of paper.
Write down the name of your leader
inside the blank of the first page.
Accurately.
If you make it up,
I'll know immediately.
I wouldn't dare if I were you.
Cut on the computer.
You'll soon get all 12 IDs of
the FBI from your leader.
"Free Access Available"
I've got it.
Open it.
Look at the pictures of the agents
attached to their IDs...
and fill in their names accurately
inside the rest of the blanks.
Done.
Now, put them back in the envelope,
and place it on the rack.
Get off at Shinagawa Park Station.
And leave the transceiver behind.
Raye.
Naomi?
Raye!
Raye...
Raye Iwamatsu, heart attack.
Cancels all schedule, and
rides the train from Akasakabashi.
Gets on the 10:14 train
from the last door of the fourth car.
He takes the manila envelope...
and dies three seconds after
getting off.
Five in Tokyo, three in Kanagawa,
and four others.
They all died of heart attacks.
Their leader in Washington is said
to have died at the same hour.
FBI agents?
They were instructed by L
to secretly investigate the case.
By L? Did you know about this?
It's all out of the blue.
"A Report on FBI Activities"
The FBI agents that were
investigating the case died.
All heart attacks.
Kira is now killing people
besides criminals.
It is possible that
we may all become targets.
You should think carefully...
about your families
and your loved ones.
You are free to drop out of
this investigation.
I guarantee that you will not
be demoted or punished for doing so.
Those of you who are not afraid to
risk everything can stay.
Lastly, I thank those
who fought with us till this day.
There's only six of us.
Watari and I are with you.
I have faith in people who have
a strong sense of justice.
L.
I'm sorry but
it's getting hard to trust you.
You give us orders from a safe place,
keeping yourself hidden at all times.
How can you expect us to trust you?
We can't have you working with us.
He's right.
To tell the truth,
I've also had doubts about you.
You tend to take drastic measures.
However, your cooperation is
essential to finding Kira.
If you want to work with us,
why don't you show yourself?
And then we could fight together.
Fine.
Watari.
I will take you to L.
How do you do, I'm L.
I am Yagami.
Ukita.
Aizawa.
Mogi.
Sanami.
Matsuda.
Hey you!
If I were Kira, you'd be dead by now.
What do you mean?
From what we know so far...
Kira needs the names and features
of the targets in order to kill them.
From now on, do not
give out your real names.
As for myself, call me Ryuzaki.
Alright.
Kira can also manipulate
one's behavior before death.
The suicide notes written in jail
were probably Kira's experiment.
Experiment?
He tested them to see how accurately
he could kill the FBI agents.
He's sent a message to me
through their suicide notes.
Did Kira do that, too?
The agents died eight days after
this experiment.
During that time, he somehow got
the names from one particular agent.
Kira is someone
within the authority...
marked by the FBI,
before the experiment.
Exactly.
That should be easy to narrow down.
Sure.
Gathering from Kira's behavior,
he is very immature and hates to lose.
Just like me.
I've been losing up till now
but things are going to change.
Let's win this together.
Ryuzaki.
This isn't a game,
this is an investigation.
Our purpose is no different.
"Busjacker Killed in Accident"
"11 a.m. Kyonan Bus"
"Investigation Closed"
I've collected all the tapes.
The ones from the security camera.
Thanks for the trouble.
This is him.
Oh yes, he was sitting at the back.
I remember.
He was quarreling with a young man
when the robber came on the bus.
What did this young man look like?
Handsome.
Not that I have a thing for boys.
Brave too. He didn't seem afraid
when the gun was pointed at him.
Was he questioned by the police?
No. Actually, he disappeared.
Maybe he didn't want to be involved, either.
Here.
And this...
You've narrowed down the list?
Yes.
Who's on it?
The Chief's and Deputy Chief's families.
Why don't you explain?
This is the moment of
Agent Iwamatsu's death.
As you can see,
he is pointing towards the train.
Someone was on it?
Presumably Kira.
Who is she?
Iwamatsu's fiancé.
She was a talented FBI agent
who used to work under me.
She probably noticed something unusual
and decided to follow him.
Let's contact her right away.
She's disappeared since his death.
He must have been onto somebody.
And we are one of them.
With a probability of
less than three percent.
Questioning us?
No.
We'll set up cameras and bugs
in both your houses.
We cannot allow
this kind of outrage!
If this comes out, we're all fired.
I thought we weren't afraid
to risk everything.
Fine. Let's do it.
Chief!
Check for any blind spots,
and do it thoroughly.
What about your wife and daughter?
I'm aware!
But we'll never clear ourselves
if we avoid this.
We'll set the cameras and bugs for,
shall we say, seven days.
Why don't we have Chief
watch his own family then?
Alright.
Mr. Yagami and I will watch his house.
Rest of you take turns
and watch Mr. Kitamura's.
This man...
Recognize him?
He was following Light.
Something the matter?
He died.
He was killed by Kira
while investigating the case.
Hey, Light.
Why are you scheduling deaths
for weeks ahead?
So as not to be suspected, in case
I'm hospitalized or tied up somehow.
You think of everything.
Welcome to my show...
"Misamisa's Happy Sweets"
Here's what I'm making today.
Can't wait!
Fatten your friends with
croissant-pudding!
What is it?
Nothing.
You can fatten your rival in love
as much as five kilos.
My rival would be?
the pop star, Ai Otsuka.
But I ended up getting fat instead!
Now who's the devil?
Croissant-pudding completed.
Let's make pigs out of our rivals in love!
Excellent!
Who do you respect the most?
Kira.
A follower of Kira, too?
He's so cool being
the executioner and all.
The youngsters should agree.
Actually, Kira saved me.
What do you mean?
Misa, I've told you
not to talk about Kira.
Why can't I?
Please cut the bit about Kira.
Where's my freedom?
I can't ask about her private life?
You can, but not on this subject.
Everyone's talking about Kira.
Thank you all!
Bye!
Light.
This is Ms. Maki.
She wants to ask you something.
How do you do?
Hello.
I'm doing an article on Kira's case.
I've heard you met Raye Iwamatsu.
Remember the man on the bus
from the FBI?
Oh him.
He was killed by Kira
while investigating the case.
I didn't know.
You didn't?
He was the one following Light.
That's right.
Because he suspected you were Kira.
Are you trying to say I killed him?
Kira can kill with a name.
You've used the busjack to
find out Raye's name.
That's funny.
Did Raye die immediately afterwards?
Three days later.
If I were Kira, I would've killed him
as soon as I discovered his name.
Light can't be Kira.
You're wrong.
And rude.
I may sue you
so I'm putting down your words.
Other agents died, too.
But if you killed Raye first,
you thought you would be suspected.
That's why he wasn't killed
right away.
Am I wrong?
All the agents died?
I never heard that on the news.
It was kept a secret.
You're making it up.
I didn't know she was such a person.
On the subway...
you somehow found out the names
of the agents and killed them all.
This is a waste of time. Let's go.
Light Yagami.
You can't kill me.
I've given you my false name.
Go away.
Raye was my fiancé.
I'll hunt Kira down and won't stop
till I put him behind bars.
What was that?
She's crazy.
False name, huh?
Another one's on your tail.
Sure you don't want my eyes?
You're in deep shit.
The people who set-up the cameras told me
that Light checked for signs of entry.
Other than that, we found
nothing suspicious in his room.
Were all those cameras necessary?
Light's characteristics,
his IQ and lifestyle...
they all fit the profile.
This is a waste of time.
If there's even a speck of doubt,
we must continue.
Without that determination,
we'll never catch Kira.
Hey Light, talk to me.
No one's watching.
Give me an apple.
I demand one!
Come on!
Apples?
What's wrong?
L's onto me completely.
Someone's been in my room.
I smell it.
There are cameras and bugs
hidden everywhere.
L wasn't so easy to deal with after all.
As long as I'm being watched,
there are no apples for you.
What?!
Let's look for the cameras
and find a blind spot.
Your son is a hard worker.
You must be very proud.
He wishes to join the Police Agency.
How will my son be cleared?
If he does nothing suspicious,
and there's a murder by Kira.
You want us to wait for a murder?
It seems so.
Have one.
DAY THREE
It's dinnertime!
I'm taking a break.
Chief, you must rest.
You haven't slept in three days.
How could I,
when my family are being suspected.
Yes? Understood.
We have confirmed the deaths of...
three killers that were on the run,
and two convicts on death row.
Is that so?
Not too fast.
Have you forgotten
that Kira can manipulate time?
We won't know for sure
until a new crime is reported.
DAY FIVE
DAY SEVEN
Aren't you worried?
Dad hasn't come home in a week.
I'm used to it.
Father's hard at work.
You should be, too.
Okay.
Eating chips after dinner
You're gonna get fat.
I'll be up all night studying.
I need my strength.
Thanks for dinner.
Wow!
Trading ended
with a recovery of 10,800 dollars.
This morning, crude oil price
had declined to...
60 dollars per barrel.
We have just received
new information.
The suspect accused of kidnapping
a five-year-old girl in Edogawa...
has been arrested.
Toru Kashimayama, age 29,
allegedly kidnapped Kasumi Miuchizawa.
Her body was found buried
under the floor of his apartment.
On the 28th of last month, Kasumi was
playing in a park near her home...
where she was last seen
climbing into a red car.
He's not watching the news.
Something seems to have happened
at the scene.
Mr. Murai
Live from Funabori.
Kashimayama has just died.
According to information...
Kashimayama was said to have been
in the middle of an interrogation...
when he suddenly died of
heart attack.
Mr. Murai?
Do you suspect Kira?
The cause of death is still unknown,
but there is that possibility.
This is Kira's latest crime.
Light is no longer under suspicion.
Isn't that enough?
Ryuzaki!
"TORU KASHIMAYAMA"
The Chief's and Deputy Chief's families
are cleared.
Ryuzaki, aren't you satisfied?
Watari.
Recover all the bugs and cameras
from their houses.
Understood.
You must be relieved, Chief.
It'll be a fresh start.
Light, the cameras are all gone.
There's nothing like
eating apples...
free from the public eye.
But Light.
What if your sister had taken
that bag of chips?
I'm the only one
who likes consommé flavor.
A phone call from Naomi Misora.
It's been a while.
L.
As of now, I will prove to you
that Light Yagami is Kira...
by risking my life.
"Shiori"
Hello?
Can we meet?
Where?
The art gallery.
I was just thinking about you.
When can you come?
I can leave right now so...
in 30 minutes.
Light...
You sound strange.
Shiori?
We're monitoring the art gallery.
Let me see it.
I'm at the entrance.
Come inside.
I'll be by Ekusuhso Kenak's
"Mask and Death".
Alright.
We can see how Kira kills?
What do you mean by that?
Light?
I knew it. Kira is Light.
Is my son still a suspect?
Shiori.
Light!
Forgive me.
Light Yagami.
If you want to see her alive,
confess right now.
That you've killed Raye.
And that you are Kira!
Get some cops in there!
You've got it all wrong.
I'm not Kira.
If you keep on lying...
I'll kill her.
No!
Even if I were,
she has nothing to do with it.
Kill me instead!
I'll teach you the pain of
losing your loved one.
Don't do it!
Please, not Shiori.
Light...
How miserable you are!
The almighty Kira,
begging for his girlfriend's life.
I'm telling you, I'm not Kira!
You can't kill without a name.
I'll tell you mine.
Naomi Misora.
Naomi is in katakana characters,
and Misora, Chinese ones.
Now that you know my name,
go ahead and kill me!
Naomi Misora...
The police?
They're almost there.
No, hold them back a little longer.
What?
Here's the good part.
How dare you! This isn't a show.
You want to save her?
Then kill me.
Like you did Raye.
Like all the criminals
you've executed.
Go on and kill
without laying a hand on me!
But I'm not Kira!
Shiori!
Please... no.
Shiori...
This can't be happening!
Shiori?
She's armed.
Shiori, hang in there.
Shiori.
Light...
Shiori...
That was... our last kiss.
Why?!
Why did you shoot her?
Tell me!
Stop!
This was a miscalculation.
Naomi Misora's miscalculation was
that I saw her.
She also shouldn't have told me
she was Raye's fiancé.
Nobody uses false names on weddings.
The church is open to everyone,
so it was easy to find out her name.
Naomi Misora, suicide.
Arranges to meet with
her fiancé's killer.
Takes his girlfriend hostage
at the Omei Art Gallery.
She makes the girlfriend call him
on April 15th, 14:15.
She then contacts a third party;
the Investigation Team...
and tries to make the killer confess
as they watch.
At 14:55, she stops
the hostage from running away...
but in a moment of madness,
ends up shooting herself.
I'm sorry.
If only we'd gotten here earlier.
I'll send for a car.
Didn't expect Shiori to die,
did you?
I'm the one who killed Shiori.
Huh?
With the help of "Death Note".
But how?
Naomi ended up killing Shiori,
but you can't make people kill.
If you write their names,
they'd all die of heart attacks.
I know.
That's why I wrote Shiori's name
on the page next to Naomi's.
Shiori Akino,
killed by a third person.
Get's kidnapped
at the Omei Art Gallery.
On April 15th, 14:15, she is
forced to call up her boyfriend.
She gets away
as the police break in.
But at 14:55,
a warning shot hits her...
and she dies trying to protect
her boyfriend.
It didn't have to say anything about
Naomi shooting Shiori or vice versa.
Does that mean,
Naomi just happened to kill Shiori?
A coincidence?
That's hardly a perfect scheme
for killing Shiori.
It was no coincidence.
I planned everything.
All I wrote was that
Shiori would be killed by a gunshot.
And that Naomi would carry a gun
in order to shoot herself.
No one carries a gun around
in Japan...
which means that the gun Naomi has,
would be shot at Shiori.
Hear this.
"Death Note" changes our destinies
in the most natural way.
So even though it wasn't written,
everything went according to my plan.
You're a devil in disguise.
My girlfriend was killed
before my eyes.
If I tell them I want to
join the team and capture Kira...
everyone would sympathize and
believe me without a doubt.
Light, you know what?
You're far worse than god of death.
Shiori truly loved you.
Didn't you love her at all?
I don't know.
Misa, I know you're lonely.
Don't come close to me!
You're the one who said
you wanted to die.
I didn't say such a thing.
Let's go to heaven.
Your parents are waiting.
We'll go together.
You're an assistant director.
I'll tell, and you'll lose
your job forever!
I've been watching you
at the studio, in the hallway.
We'll die together.
I'm giving you my life.
That's my destiny.
Moron!
Who said I want to go to heaven
or to hell?
Don't worry. It won't hurt a bit.
No...
Somebody! Help me!
Light, your car's here.
Let's get you home.
Father, I have a request.
What is it?
Let me on the team.
Shiori was killed because of Kira.
I'll never forgive him.
So please put me on the team.
We welcome you!
We meet at last.
I am L.
Lend us your brain.
We'll capture Kira together.
First, apologize.
Watch Movies, TV Series and Live Sports
Signup Here -> WWW.ADMITME.APP