Watch Movies, TV Series and Live Sports
Signup Here -> WWW.ADMITME.APP
Don't! Don't come!
Death, that's what you want, isn't it?
No! I don't want to die!
You're my assistant aren't you?
I'll die with you!
Let's go to heaven
where your mom and dad
are waiting for you
"Sakajo Ryotarou"
Amane Misa
Your life's been extended
Are you an ... angel?
No, I'm the Reaper
The Reaper£¿
Cool!
The human whose name is written in the note shall...
die.
Akino SHiori was shot and killed by a woman at the museum
Misora Naomi, the murderer, also killed herself there
Did they know each other?
I don't know
Yagami Light, the boy who saw it, was Shiori's boyfriend, wasn't he?
Were they involved in a love triangle?
That's enough! Where do you think you are!
Are you from their college? Can I ask you couple questions?
No, we're not!
Ah, you're detectives! Then I want to ask some...
Get out of here!
The Police...?
I feel sorry for both Shiori and Light
Who said that Misora was an excellent FBI agent?
She was too obsessed with catching the one who killed her fiance
I don't understand why she suspected Light
They're here
Yagami Light
the hero of this tragedy who lost his girlfriend
His father is the director of the detective team
And his sister... must still be in high school
I heard Kira has something to do with this case
Don't say such nonsense
Kira didn't kill her
Light must be hurt by such a heartless rumor
You're right..
Everyone feels sorry for you, Light
Dad, I will avenge Shiori
Sorry, I didn't want you involved
I'll definitely make Kira pay
You ARE the Kira, aren't you?
5 seconds!
Opening!
Good evening
Welcome to Evening Spot, I'm Nishiyama Saeko
Nakayama Kiyohiko, who murdered a girl, just died of heart attack
Nakayama was wanted for murder
But today in Shibuya he suddenly fell
and died of heart attack
Today was the 10th birthday of Aoki Takuma, the victim's brother
My sister asked Kira-sama from heaven to do this
I think this was a gift from her
Currently, L, the mysterious detective ICPO invited to investigate
has concluded that Kira lives in Kanto, Japan, but has not achieved any further result
This is Kira's handy work
The police has not admitted though
You must leave everything communication device, including mobile phone here
Ryuzaki, here is Mr. Yagami Light
Ryuzaki£¿
I see, a false name to protect you from Kira
You're so sharp. How did you see it?
You can see it easily if you think of the cases logically
I've heard about your extraordinary ability
Not sure if they were being sarcastic..
I suspect you to be Kira
Are you joking?
I don't like to joke
Then why did you invite such a dangerous person?
Because if I die, you'll be suspected the most
You mean, if you die, I'm Kira
How did you came up with that?
Our investigation status has leaked out to Kira
so I had the FBI team investigate our members and their family
including you, Light
I felt like someone's been following me
As a result, we've lost
Every member of the team was killed. This is a shame
But we succeeded in profiling the most suspicious person
out of the people we have investigated
You mean me?
Yes, and we set cameras and taps in your room
That's illegal...!
Did my father agree too?
It was a special case
If so, it must've proved that I'm innocent
I bet you can outwit them easily
Besides, Misora Naomi reached you although we didn't give her any information
Hey, Wait!
You're too mean... Light just lost his grilfriend!
because Misora Naomi killed her!
Kira can control the dying situations
You think that I controlled Shiori and Misora and killed them...
What for£¿
To make people feel sorry for you and to join our team
to approach me and...
to kill me
You bastard!
You may have a superior intelligence, but you don't have a heart!
Mr. Matsuda, I can prove my innocence on my own
So, how do you thik I killed those people?
That's the only think I want to know
It will give the answer to every mystery
If all the mysteries were solved and it told that I'm Kira...
Unfortunately, death penalty
Checkmate
bravo
We don't suspect you Light
Ryuzaki too. He examined you just to know the probability
You need to suspect, when you're investigating
But the more important thing is to stop Kira from killing people as soon as possible
I also hope...
that you're not Kira
If you get the Reaper's eye, you can see his real name
by giving me half of your lifetime
You can kill him when you want!
The Diet has stopped the regular council by the speech from the PM
that crime rate is decreasing because of Kira
but many of the citizens and the young members of the Diet
rather seem to support his opinion
Killing is bad, but
a nation often kills criminals under the law
The matter is whether it is a "right killing" or not
from this point of view, Kira's killing seems to be justified
Who? Who made this idiot in charge of the government?
We must not allow this situation to happen, sir
Yagami, what are you thinking?
Where and what is your team doing?
Everything we do is based on L's directions
What kind of person is L?
Is he American?
I can't tell you, sir
You!
L is risking his own life
We believe his will and follow him
I understand
You can have request money or staff as much as you need, so...
catch Kira right away!
Nothing exciting at the Sakura TV festival
Isn't there any entertainment?
TV stars for example?
That'll cause a riot!
No, I don't think it's gonna happen
I beg you Mr. Demegawa! We might lose Saeko's life
You must leave it to me as I've been doing research on Kira
I understand him the most
You are kind of..
unattractive
Morning!
Not attractive?
-Saeko, this is our chance!
-I'm so excited
Are you sure it's ok to broadcast it without boss's permission?
Protect me even it gets you fired!
If we can get the ratings, they'll put hundreds of testimonials on the wall!
It's going to be the true Sakura TV festival
News isn't a comedy show!
Who do you think you are?
Your head and here should both be a little softer
Save the sexual harassment..
This is a case of kill or cure
What?
Director
We've got information that Sakurat TV
will broadcast a message from Kira
3 days ago
We received two videotapes from somone who called himself the Second Kira
The Second Kira?
In the first videotape
there was a notice that the murderer who was arrested recently would die
and yesterday, he did die of heart attack
Ms. Sagami, confirm it please
Yes
Also, the Second Kira
requested us to broadcast the other video from 2:59 pm today
We have not watched this video
As I said in the beginning
the Second Kira demanded us to broadcast the video
or he would kill all of our staff from the top
Please understand that we are hostages of Kira
As journalists, we risk our lives to broadcast this
Everyone should stay calm
Is this.. really happening here?
I don't want to goto Sakura TV festival anymore
It's now 2:59. Please watch this video
Here it is
I am the Second Kira
Just like Kira, I also hate evil
and I want to create an ideal world where there's no crime
Anyone who opposes Kira is my enemy
Anyone who disturbes Kira is letting brutal criminals go free
so they must die so the society can become peaceful
Hibima Kazuhiko, one of the opposers who's now appearing on Taiyo TV
Will die of heart attack
Kira's judgement is autocratic.
He is just a cruel murderer.
But..
What's wrong with Taiyo TV?
-Hurry!
He certainly is an autocrat
We might be slaves of Kira
Mr. Hibima?
Somebody.. Help
Someone please help
You alright¡­
Can you hear me
Still breathing?
Mr. Hibima unfairly insisted that Kira was evil and criticized him
He deserves death
Stop it!
You must accept Kira so we can create a future together
What are you doing?
Make them stop showing it now!
The producer of the program doesn't answer the phone
They just want the audience rating
Mr. Mogi arrived at the scene?
The furture is with Kira
If you agree with Kira's justice, gather in from of Sakura TV
Let's raise our voices for Kira
Only Kira can purify this unclean world
He's right!
Kira is doing the right thing!
Crime is decreasing thanks to Kira
That critic sure deserves it!
Today's the Kira festival!
I'm scared! Let's go!
Come one, let's see what'll happen.
I'm actually a Kira supporter
What?
Kira¡­
I won't let anyone interfer with what Kira's doing
Anyone does will die
Police!
Mr. Mogi
Stop!
Don't support Kira's justice
Do you defend the cruel mass murderer?
Don't forgive him!
Get away from here now!
What are you talking about? The police is totally useless
ya¡­
Kira is now protecting the world
No, Kira is a cruel murderer!
Wake up and disperse!
Kira taught us...
Disperse¡­
You are in danger too!
.... that the laws never help us
Do you hear the cries of the people?
People who lose their love can never be healed
Stop it
Mr. Mogi!
Mr. Mogi¡­
Do you hear the murderer's laugh?
Who took lives of innocent people, and live without being punished
You're in danger!
Get away from here!
Step aside!
Let me through
Disperse¡­
Get back
What are you doing?
You must stay away from here
Kira has begun to act
for a bright, ideal world
Camera no. 1, zoom in on the fallen policemen
Great! He's dead!
You'll be dead if you go there
We can't just sit here and watch TV!
This Kira might be able to kill just by seeing the faces
The the policemen near the scene to keep away
Yes
Ryuzaki...!
We must fight with Kira
But
We must rescue Sayu!
This Kira's targets
are people who interrupt the broadcasting
Sayu should be safe
And Kira, if you're watching TV,
Come here now
I promise I will help you
As you see, I have the eye
Let me see your Reaper, then I'll show you mine
Reaper£¿
Do you expect me to believe that such things really exist?
It must mean the ability of killing
And let's create a new world together!
What do you mean by the new world!
You murderer!
How can you kill people so easily?
What did they do to you£¿
Murderer!
Sayu...! Don't upset him!
Murderer
Murderer¡­
Murderer!
What are you doing!
A car just crashed into the station
We don't know yet what exactly happened
Is that..
really?
Sayu!
Dad?
Cover your face with this
go inside
Mogi..
We'll inform you as soon as we find out what is happening at the entrance
Alright, cut to commercials
The ratings will be 30... no, 40 at least
L's message earned 35%
You can't go in
Step aside
Is that you?
You're the producer£¿
You can't enter without...
The police£¿Stop broadcasting now!
If we do that, we're gonna die
You want to see innocent people...
forced to get involved and killed?
I got it!
Calm down¡­
Got it..
Hello?
Thank you
Ryuzaki, I told them to stop broadcasting
I go the videotapes too
This is as I thought
It was Mr. yagami!
I can't do this in such as way
Dad, where is Sayu? Is she alright?
Light..
Yes, we're both fine
Mr. Yagami, are you still wearing a helmet?
No, I took it off
I'll go pick them up
Please arrange for the permission to enter the studio
You'll be Kira's target!
Dad and Sayu will not be harmed inside the studio
The Second Kira surely has the Reaper's eye
You've got a nice buddy huh?
No
There's no proof that he's not my enemy
Then isn't it dangerous to go?
If he truely supports me, he'll be a strong weapon to wipe out L
I must find him before L does
Move out
Sakura TV has stopped broadcasting, following the order from the police
Taiyo TV
is protesting against Sakura TV
According to Taiyo TV
Mr. Hibima died because of Sakura TV
Misa, the recording is cancelled
yeah, alright
It can't be helped
I need to change clothes
The Kira didn't show up
-Sayu
-Light
I was worried about you
Mr. Mogi..
He was killed¡­
Yes, I will report it
Excuse me
Kira...?
I found you
I knew he'd come to me
Yagami...
Tsuki?
The videotapes were dispatched
at a post office in Kita-ku Osaka
The fingerprints are so small
so 'he' might be 'she'
Are you sure that these are from the Second Kira?
It may be a fake
You mean, this might be a fake by Kira that there are more Kiras?
Light, what do you think?
That's impossible
And this Kira can kill only by seeing the faces
The video images were childish,
trying to use the media slyly
This Kira is way stupid and different from the first Kira
Besides, the first Kira doesn't kill innocent people
You're right
If I were Kira, I'd get angry
This Kira tried to make us believe that he was outside the studio
Had the studio on surveillance
He could be hidden inside the studio
Check everyone in the studio
If the first Kira joins the second Kira
It will be a huge threat
We must prevent it. Mr Yagami..
Is it possible to send Kira a message through TV?
What kind of message?
Nishiyama Saeko is the No. 1 anchorwoman in Japan
Thank you so much
That's clever... You're the man, Demegawa
How can they be so blind?
The Second Kira trusted and sent the tapes to us
because you've been reporting on the First Kira's activities
They should appreciate you
Irritating¡­
Why didn't you become an anchor?
See how Saeko behaves?
To be an anchor, you have to sell youself as a 'female'
I can't stand it
You're prettier than her
Give me a break
Demegawa!
Did you survive the torture by the police?
Yeah, and more than that
I got a sweet gift from them
What's that?
That's a message from the police to the Second Kira
We can expect high ratings
Great job!
This is a message for the Second Kira
Stop trying to approach the First Kira
It's not too late if you haven't met him
You must never get involved in Kira just because you're curious
You'll be used
and definitely killed by Kira
Yagami Light....
It's written "Moon"
but read "Light"
"...please provide us with any information regarding Kira"
"... save those living under Kira's terrorist acts"
"... and save the world"
Reating the message...
Here is the data for every staff at Sakura TV
and the list of people who entered the studio that day
What a huge amount
That total...
8000 people. approximately.
Let's start
Oh, good evening!
Nice to meet you, I'm Amane Misa
You're a friend of Sayu?
Oh, no
I was watching TV and... I thought you must be worried.
I couldn't help come to see you
to show you this notebook
Here, touch it
Light, you're back!
She's my friend.
She'll come to my room for a while
Hello
Light, did you invite a friend?
Nice to meet you
Her face looks familiar...
She's Misa-misa! of the Happy Sweets!
Yeah! Amane Misa!
How did you know it?
Ah, that's what I thought!
You haven't done 'the deal'
You know, you can see people's names and their lifespan
but you can't see the lifespan of a person who has the notebook
I couldn't answer unless you ask me
Are you... working in the studio or something?
um... I... I think I'm kind of famous..
A singer?
Oh, actually, this is my first CD.
I also appear on magazine and TV.
Oh, there's a new movie too
How did you find out where I live?
From the internet,
You gave a speech at the entrance ceremony of college
I found a photo of you there
If you were arrested,
Kira's secrets would come out!
I'm sorry!
But I haven't been arrested
and I won't be if I follow your orders from now on
Right?
I can find out L's name
I'll be your eyes. So...
So what?
Let me be your girlfriend
I can't
Why not?
There are your fingerprints on the tapes
If the police take fingerprints directly from you,
they'll find out you're the Second Kira.
Those weren't mine!
I'm not that stupid
I have a friend in Osaka who's into the occult
and I showed her fake pictures of ghosts
and asked her to send videos to TV stations together...
And what is she doing now?
If you want, I'll kill her right now
No, The police'll easily link her to you
If you don't believe me...
You can keep my Death Note
I'm still the owner of the notebook even if you keep it.
So I can still work my eyes for you.
Right Remu?
Yes, you're right
Now, I can't kill you
and you can kill me if you don't need me
I'm happy...
...even if you're just going to use me
Trust me
Why are you doing this?
Misa lost all of her family members 3 years ago
They were killed by a burglar
Since Misa had seen his face
The suspect was soon arrested
But Misa was the only witness so it wasn't enough to convict him
Tamura Yoichi, the suspect was soon released
She was caught in a deep empty darkness in her mind
Everyone gave up on Misa's future
But one day,
Something happened
"Tamura Yoichi Found Dead"
"Is This Kira?"
Kira punished him
Misa was grateful to the God named Kira
Please
Trust me
You are everything to me
But you killed innocent policemen
Don't you think it's the same as the burglar who killed your family?
Don't say such things to me?
You also think that..
...sacrifices for the good of all can't be helped
It was the only thing I could do
I really wanted to see you
I understand
For me...
You shortened your own life...
Your eyes became my weapon
Thank you...
I'll do my best
to be loved by you..
I'll arrange a chance for you to see L.
And you'll see L's real name
Can you do it?
You don't have to ask me, just say "do it"
I'll do anything you want me to
If one of us gets arrested
we'll never talk about the other one and the Death Note
Can you swear?
Yes, I swear
Good
Then... It's my turn
We're gonna date at least once a week
You don't understand what I said
But once L dies,
There won't be no difficulty between us, right?
You underestimate L
Besides L is already...
Suspecting that I am Kira
What?
L is so smart
Everybody says L hasn't figured out anything yet...
Now I've reached a position where I can contact him directly,
L and Kira are getting closer...?
I'm impressed by both!
It's so exciting
And of course, I need you to kill L.
So I wanted to contact you as quickly as possible
If so, why just can't we date?
If you want to date once a week
I'll have to date other girls
to avoid being suspected that we have a special relationship
You can't do that
If I see you dating other girl..
I'll kill her!
I'm the only one who'll date you!
If you don't obey me, I have to kill you
I won't let you kill her, Yagami Light!
If you harm this girl,
I won't forgive you
I see her lifespan
If she dies, I'll think it's because you killed her. I'll have to kill you
If I find you trying to kill her..
I'll kill you before that happens
Ryuzaki...?
Since that, there's no new action by the Second Kira
I'm afriad the FIrst and the Second Kira have made contact already
Isn't it careless to expose your face?
Yes, it's dangerous if you're Kira
You're the only one outside who knows that I'm L, so
If you told the Second Kira about me, it's "the end." To avoid it,
I brought this
That'll work
Did you come to watch over me?
You think Kira is a college student. don't you?
I have an important job here
About Kira?
Light
I had a recording nearby so I came to see you
Here I am
You
Oh?
Are you Light's friend?
Yeah
His name is Ryuzaki
Why're you wearing such as stupid mask?
Why don't you take it off?
Hi there!
Are you... Ryuzaki...?
Nice to meet you.
I'm Amane Misa
Um... Light?
Your friend is a little weird
He's just shy
I envy you Light
I listen to your Heaven's Door!
Really?
I'm so glad!
Light, why can you date with such a cute pop star?
I approached him first
Misa!
Look, isn't that Misa-Misa?
She really is!
Why! Why is she here?
This is great
It's real
You're the most intelligent students in Japan, right?
Please shake hands with me
Oh! Someone touched my bottom!
Can't forgive him!
I, the greatest detective, will definitely catch the pervert!
Here you go
Ryuzaki, you're funny
Then, don't you want to date with me?
Too bad, here's my only sweet heart
Whaaat?
I have a class, so go back to your work
Right
Sorry, but I'm glad to see you
See you soon, Light
It's good...
She's so cute
Ryuzaki
She's my girlfriend
bye
It was lucky to see Misa-Misa.
I'll go back to the office
Take care
I won...!
"Misa"
Hello
What are you doing?
Someone dropped this cell phone and I picked it up
It belongs to Misa
Give it to me
Calling her just after you said goodbye?
You really are in love with her
Or,
Was there anything you had to ask her immediately
Hello
We have the target.
It wasn't the place we expected
since she moved around so much
We'll send her to the office
I got it
Thank you for the hard work
Just now
We arrested Amane Misa for the suspicion to be the Second Kira
What?
She is an enthusiastic supporter of Kira and she was in the studio that day
From her room,
We found material evidences such as a cosmetic powder
and fibers matching her clothes
We're not going to announce so please cooperate for awhile
You have to stay away from the office
What are you going to do to her?
I can't tell you.
Can I take her phone too?
I can't believe she's the Kira
It can't be
Awwww, Light
The goddess of the luck is gone
See you
Ryuzaki
Do we really have to do this?
Second Kira can kill by seeing the face
It's reasonable to restrain her with a 24 hour surveillance
If she isn't Kira...
This will violate human rights
We've got the evidence!
Besides she stays silent even in this situation
If she's innocent, why doesn't she just say so
Tell her agent to announce
that she's in hospital
It's already done
Mr. Yagami
Amane and Light have a close relationship
What?
She's even visited your home, Mr. Yagami
Light...
I have to contact Rem
before Misa talks them about the secrets...
It's gonna get worse
We can't part from the owner of the Death Note
Unless the owner abandons the right of possession or...
dies
She hasn't eaten anything in 2 days
She has a lot of guts..
She doesn't even complain
I'm... becoming a fan of her
I'm going to buy her CD
Idiot!
Toilet...
I want to use the toilet
Even after she got caught,
Kira hasn't stopped punishing
Here
Misa
Please...
Say something...
We don't want to..
make you suffer anymore
What do you...
know about Kira?
I can't stand this anymore
kill me
We must release her!
Amane Misa, do you hear me?
Please
kill me
Do you mean that you admit you're the Second Kira?
It doesn't matter if I'm Kira or not
If I have to live like this...
I'd rather die
Hey!
kill me now
You're able to kill me easily!
I should have died that time anyway
I'm happy even if I die now
kill me before I get old and lose my beauty
kill me right now
Rem..
Misa abandoned the possessive right of the Death Note
She asked me to kill her
because she didn't want you to get in trouble
Do you understand, Yagami Light?
Everything she did was to be loved by you
Did she...
lose all the memory about the Death Note?
Of course
She forgot that she has killed people
or that you are Kira
I told her that she'd never see me anymore
and all she'd remember is that she loves Yagami Light
Misa answered it would be fine
Save her at all cost!
If you don't, I'll kill you
With a Death God being so nice to her..
Misa must be very happy
I am just trying to keep the promise with Jealous
Jealous£¿
Jealous was always looking down on Misa
He had a father-like sympathy towards the girl who lost her parents
However, when the time comes when Misa would die
Eventually, he broke the rules of the Death Gods
He wrote the name of the man
and extended Misa's lifespan
The Death Gods exist only to take lives of humans
It's a serious taboo to save a human
and extend her lifespan
Jealous fell to pieces and died
asking me to take care of her
Therefore
Jealous's Death Note was given to Misa
A Death God who falls in love with a human shall die...
a great story, indeed
If you won't save Misa,
I will kill you
Don't give me the same phrase over and over again, Rem
Imagine how she feels if I die
She'll definitely kill herself
Can't you even imagine that?
There's a way
It needs a lot of work though..
Are you really sure that it will save Misa
if only I follow your direction
Can't you trust me even a little?
He's smarter than you think
Ok, I trust you
Yagami Light
I leave Misa to you
What are you doing with my Death Note?
I'm just hiding it
When I discard its possession, I'll say...
"I discard it"
"I discard it"...
hum....
Hey stalker
If you quit now,
I won't accuse you!
I'll give you my autograph and a kiss!
Oh please!
Let me out of here!
What happened to her during the blackout
She kept repeating..
We are not stalkers.
We are the police
The police can't do such a thing!
Pop stars are wiser than you think!
If you think we are stalkers,
why did you keep silent?
I don't know!
You suddenly caught me
when I was just going to have lunch with Light
Do you admit the relationship between Yagmai Light?
Of course...
Of course I do. He's my boyfriend.
Is she really the same person?
Then how, did you and Light know each other?
I fell in love with him at first sight at Sakura TV station
I found his address and went to his home
Anything wrong?
You know how she acted before
Now she frankly admitted about Light
I'm confused
Who said that we can't bring cellphones into the office?
ya..
Hello
I got it, please come in
Keep recording and shut down the screen
Yes
Is someone coming?
Light!
I've told Ryuzaki but...
As L said, I might be the Kira
What on earth are you talking about?
I've been thinking that..
It may be better if people who committed serious crimes die
So it's possible that I may become Kira
You're not the only one who thinks so!
Are you trying to cover Misa?
I don't know much about her yet since we've just started dating
I can't believe that she's Kira
Of course, I'm not conscious of Kira in me
but,
I might have a multiple personality
I want you to figure it out
We investigated you, but couldn't find anything suspicious
But we watched over him only when he was home
We don't know exactly what he did outside
Then tie his arms and legs and keep him under surveillance
This time
It's an around-the-clock surveillance
That'll be fine with me
But if,
new crimes are committed while I'm under surveillance...
and Kira punishes the criminals
When it happens
We'll certainly free you
Thank you
Light...
Do you really mean it?
Where's Light?
What happened to our son?
Dad, why don't you say something?
Dear
"Celebrating LIght's 18th birthday"
"This is a rulebook which was based on human wisdom"
"which still struggles to answer what justice is"
"Thanks, dad!"
"I want to study and think about what justice is"
Amane Misa: Surveillance Day 8
Yagami Light: Surveillance Day 3
How is it, Ryuzaki?
Has kira killed anyone yet?
There's no activities so far
No criminals have been killed
Is that so...
Then I'm getting even more suspicious.
I'm soooo bored!
I can't eat apples
and I can't even talk with you.
I wonder how Rem's doing now
Where's my ID card?
Does anyone know?
Don't make a sound
I brought a little gift for you
Misa. Day 12
Light: Day 7
I want to see Light
I want to see Light, stalkers!
Dad, mom
Light,
You look exhausted
Are you okay?
Yeah, I know I look so miserable right now
But I don't care about such as useless pride..
"I discard it"
You "discard" it?
You'll lose your memory
Alright, Light.
Goodbye
Ryuzaki...
What's wrong?
I know I asked you to do this to me
But now I surely know..
This is a waste of time
I'm not Kira
I'll be the judge of that, not you
It's totally impossible to do such cruel things
without being conscious
Don't you think so?
It was you who said that you might be Kira
without being conscious
While I'm here, I clearly saw my goal
I won't let Kira go free, he drove me into a corner
Ryuzaki!
Let's cooperate and find a way to reach Kira!
We can get him!
Light...
suddenly became so positive
Misa: Day 19
Light: Day 14
Since he offered to do it, but
I'm worried about Misa
She's a tough kid
If I were her, I'd go insane
Ryuzaki!
Kira is back!
Criminals are dying of heart attack one after another
Light!
There's been no action from Kira for 2 weeks.
It's time you admit that you're Kira
Hey!
If you see only the current situation, I'm guilty. But this is a trap...
I said I'm not Kira!
Believe me!
Why did Kira... choose me as his replacement?
You often predicted who'll be the next target of Kira
You must have noticed the reason through your reports
Kira's punishment...
...is nearly the same as my view on justice
That's what I thought
Kira is just trying to make the world a better place
It's my mission to tell the people that he's doing the right thing
If I were Kira, I would use the media more efficiently!
That makes you the most suitable person as Kira's partner
That is the reason
Kira chose me as his partner...
Misa: Day 23
Light: Day 18
Criminals are constantly being killed
Even the ones they never knew
It's impossible to kill them in this situation
For example,
if the Kira's ability has been transferred to another person
and the person has become the Third Kira
and they've lost their memories
It explains everything
Even if you were right,
there's no way to prove it
Ryuzaki
Why don't we try a different approach?
How do you feel?
Good, thanks
I'm impressed with your courage
Still, we have the evidence found in Amane's room
You can't go outside until we solve the case
If I have to stay here anyway
Let me go back to the team and help you find Kira
Yes, I was thinking about the exact same thing
You have to stay with me all day and assist me
Thanks, Ryuzaki
Let's find Kira together
I love you...
Light
Ms Wakita!
Are you okay?
What happened to you?
Get an ambulance!
She's dead
Her name is Wakita Masako and she was wanted for
killing her colleague when she was working in a nightclub
Is this another case
of punishment from Kira?
We found Wakita's address and tried to interview her
but she died in front of us
Ms. Takada, you must be shocked
She did not have any health problem
so it is natural to think that she was killed by Kira
Now please look at this graph
This is the result of a poll taken from 1000 people in Japan
According to the result,
60% of them are supporting Kira
This is surprising isn't it?
I don't think so
Considering that the crime rate has been decreasing
by the appearance of Kira, this result is expected
Not bad
This is a fact that Kira is fighting against evil
What is the true justice?
Does the police, or L, really can help us?
Kira is trying to make us thing.
She's good
We can't blame her because
We haven't found any clues to go on
What's wrong Ryuzaki?
It's not like you
Oh, great work!
Thank you for supervising
Your comments were witty
Thank you so much!
The director said that...
you'd be a good anchor
Really?
for being critical towards the society through Kira's case...
Your brave, intelligent attitude has attracted the viewers.
You're becoming more attractive
Mr. Demegawa!
Could you ask your boss?
to spray pesticide in the studio
since a noisy bug's flying around here
Saeko!
Let's go have dinner?
Kiyomi
You know, each employee has an appropriate role, right?
What is your role, then?
No one's listening to your trashy comments!
Let's go
I say she's too fugly to be the anchor for our show!
Oh, come on
We employees can't say no to your boss, you know.
Are you kidding me?
You're the one who said no to your boss and showed Kira's video!
You slept with her, didn't you?
There's nobody but you who got a job by sleeping with me
Stop the car
Huh?
Stop the car now!
I'll never forgive her!
Hey, wait!
Calm down!
What's the matter with you!
You can't catch a taxi here!
Good evening
Welcome to Evening Spot,
I'm Takada Kiyomi, the new anchor
First of all,
I have to announce a sad news
Last night, Nishiyama Saeko, our excellent former anchor,
died of a car accident
She was, for me..
a few years senior than me
and one of the person I respected the most
It is very sad that...
my first job as an anchor is
to announce about Saeko's death
This feels like being on a honeymoon!
If I can always spend my time with you like this
I won't want to go back to work
But, if they lock me up again, I'll die!
Oh, sorry!
Light
Are you studying?
Sorry Misa, can you please leave me alone for a while?
I'll go downstairs
Dont leave me alone
Light, come back soon, okay?
I'm sorry, but I'll set you free soon
Ryuzaki is a little depressed
Yeah, because he lost all his clues...
You're too loud
Ryuzaki!
Please be honest
What is the percentage that I'm Kira?
The percentage that you are Kira is...
nearly zero
I see
Great
I'm so happy
I'm also happy that you don't seem to be Kira, but
at the same time I lost all the clues
There's a vital clue
What if I said so?
When will you come back?
Are you serious?
Look at this
The red one is Kira's action before I was confined
and the blue one is his new action.
I profiled them statistically
Are these the same person?
No
They have some differences
Oh, they really do!
Even if you try to imitate someone's movement
you can't hide your habits or personality
They appear to be a remarkable tendency
Ryuzaki...
He's got the energy again!
I bet you know it
If Kira before and after the restraint were the same person
THe distribution wouldn't be so different
It means that they are different person and
we can see the distinct characterists that show their tendencies
How is it , Ryuzaki?
Doesn't it give you some motivation?
Yes Light, that you so much
By the way, what are the characteristics?
Well, the first characteristic is publicity
I mean, the new Kira cares slightly more about cases featured by the media
And the second factor is
gender
The new one focuses on more cases related to women
This Kira may be a woman
And the third factor is...
which might be the answer already
What? Oh come one Light, tell us
frequency of the cases reported by one broadcasting company
Which company?
It's Sakura TV
To sum up
compared to the First Kira, this new Kira is
more media-oriented, feminine, and Sakura TV...
The anchor died of accident and the new one is female!
Does she keep a diary in such an old notebook?
That's not snobbish people do
She must have a lot of money
I don't think it's a diary. SHe's copying down from the PC screen
Can you zoom in the surface of the notebook?
Okay, wait a second
What are these£¿
Names of the criminals who've just been killed by Kira
Ms. Sagami, capture them and confirm that they are
Yes
Killing one after another everyday
Are there any left to kill?
It tells you how sinful human beings are
Look who's talking
I know
Punishing the sinful people, I'm even more sinful
But even those sins burden me for my entire life
I have to fulfill my duty
Is she talking to herself?
No,
She's definitely talking to someone else
It's confirmed
Names of the left page belong to the criminals
who died of heart attack yesterday
Accurate details of when and how they died..
including the unannounced cases
We got it!
Boss! Let me arrest her!
She can make an excuse that she was just researching their deaths
You're right...
One more thing
What she's writing down on the right page now..
are also names of the criminals
but they are still alive
They must be the next targets
If they really die tomorrow, we can conclude that she's Kira
or she has some kind of relationship with Kira
We can't just wait until those people die!
Damn it, what should we do!
We can use Kira's cruelty
Hello, Ms. Takada
You keep getting scoops about Kira as a supporter
I found out the reasons
What do you mean?
I peeked in your room
It's illegal!
Every secret is hidden in your black notebook, right?
I want you to buy the tapes
for 5 million yen
All the names she wrote down yesterday...
matches the criminals who died today.
Takada Kiyomi is the Kira!
She definitely is!
I'm the one who called you
"Miatsuo Yosuke"
If I die, the tapes will automatically go public
Are you doing this with someone else?
No, I'm alone
There's my account number on the back of the card
Transfer 5 million yen to my account
Once payment is confirmed
I'll give you the tapes
Thank you
It's me. Kiyomi. turn on the TV
Sakura TV
Why?
No reason, just turn on the TV
Kira is a woman?
Wow, I couldn't think of it
"Special Program: Chasing Kira's Identity"
I have the tapes as evidence
Wait, It's too soon to show them
We'll show you the videos at the end of the program
You'll see Kira's identity
1 hour 25 minutes and 40 seconds left
until then, we'll ask our guests some more questions
We were scooped by other guys
I'm sorry...
I'll call you back
"that female..."
I did it as you said
You're a good actor
Now, what do we do next?
"Matsuo Yosuke suicide"
22:36, refuses to appear on the program
after cleaning out all the evidences he has
jumps from the roof of the building
she's writing down how he's going to die
Kira can control the action of the people she's going to kill!
It's safe, Rem
"Now it's safe"
what is she talking about?
Does she really believe that Matsuda will act according to what she's written?
Are you for or against Kira's actions?
Don't you see?
If I supported Kira, I wouldn't appear on TV like this
Don't you think it's dangerous?
It's a minute past the time....
Rem, what's going on?
"Rem.."
What is "Rem"?
Who is she talking to?
A Death God?
"Matsuo Yosuke"
It must be a false name!
Rem! You must've known it since you're the Death God!
You didn't tell me!
She often says "Death God"
Is it a code or something?
The most logical way is to think that
the Death God exists
What?
Okay
Let's make a deal
Give me the Death God's eyes!
The Death God's eyes...?
The Second Kira said the same thing
The Second Kira has the ability to kill only by the faces
That's "the Death God's eye"
Roll down the window
Show me your ID
You don't have it?
Don't look at me like that, the rule is the rule
Shidohara Genta
How did you know my name?
Wait!
Do you appear on TV?
Something TV...
You're an anchor, right?
What are you doing?
Wait!
A policeman fell down, but I can't help him!
Got it
Did she use "the eye"?
It's too dangerous to let her go any further
We don't know how she did it, but it's better to catch her
Freeze!
Let me go!
We have watched every single action you made
The TV program was a fake
It was a trap!
Takada Kiyomi!
How did you do that?
Are you a detective?
As Kira..
How did you kill those people?
You wrote the names on the notebook
After writing them down.. what did you do?
I just write them down
I said what did you do after!
Then why don't you try it?
You write names down and...
the person whose name is written dies
The notebook of the Death God
What the...
Dad, what's wrong?
When you touch it, you can see the Death God?
Ryuzaki, let me touch it!
Light... are you okay?
yeah
I won!
Everything's under control
If only I touch the Death Note, my memory will come back
Is this really true?
Yes, but
you can remember it only when you touch the Death Note
if the Note wasn't the one you used before
But if I keep the ownership, the memory won't be lost right?
How can I keep the ownership?
While you have the memory, kill the former owner
Good.
That explanation is enough
Rem
Give this to the Third Kira
If you're the Death God, you can find a suitable one
And after 13 days, let that person resume Kira's job
I can choose anyone?
As you won't remember, you can't reach the new owner
I know about my ability more than anyone else
I will definitely try hard to find the new Kira
and catch the person!
I'll touch the Note before L, or at the same time
And one more thing
I have something I want you to write down on the Note
What is it?
I've made up
a false rule of the Death Note
The Death God exists
That explains everything
Now I know how they kill
If you write down a person's name on the notebook
that person dies!
Is this correct. Takada Kiyomi?
The Death God...
The killer notebook...
Who will believe this?
We can't judge her with the current laws!
That's right
I didn't kill anybody
I just wrote down the names
No
If we can prove that the notebook kills people
You'll be guilty
Death Penalty
Humans, listen!
I'm the Death God, Rem
Only the humans who touched the Death Note can see me
I can see your lifespan
And I can take your lives away
So you'd better not make me angry
The Death Note has the power of the Death God
That woman is correct
the humans whose name is written on the Death Note shall die
"Takada Kiyomi"
With so called Death Note you can control the dying situations, can't you?
Why don't you try it yourself
by writing her name on the Note?
Rem, what do you...
Takada!
She's dead...
Light, hand me the notebook
Overall
Why did Takada Kiyomi die?
Accidental heart attack or...
suicide...?
Killed by other Kira?
What do you think, Death God?
Don't ask me
The name on the notebook and the dead criminals are the same, but
there's no name before Light's confinement
What do you think?
The owner of the Note might die when the ownership moves to the other
The First and the Second Kira might have already...
I see. Now Takada has died
and the ownership of this notebook has transferred to someone else
What do you think, Death God?
Don't ask me
Who owns the Note now?
I cannot answer
Is that the only thing you can say?
By the way
about the last rule of this Death Note
"If the owner does not write any name for 13 days"
"the owner shall die"
Considering this rule, the former Kiras have died
Then Light, who was under surveillance for 18 days?
and Amane, which was 23 days, are completely innocent
Death God!
Are all the rules on this notebook true?
Yes, they are
I got it, Light and Misa are free now
Light, call your mother and go home
Dad!
I'd like to stay here and continue working..
I think I have to
Ryuzaki
You need me, don't you?
I got it.
Light, stay here and help us
This looks like a common notebook
I can't believe this thing can kill people
What?
Why don't you come with me?
You can come whenever you want
Ryuzaki will allow us
to just talk at the entrance
Right, I'll come see you everyday
Be prepared!
Misa...
Listen quietly
Will you do me a favor?
What is it?
It's here!
Light is the Kira...
He's my God!
So happy
My Light is the Kira...!
I'm back at last!
Ryuk!
Why are you here?
That Death Note is mine
So this time I'll follow you
Don't worry, your memory won't be gone
If you become the owner of this Note
Okay, I'll be the owner
Oh, I almost forgot!
Here
A gift from Light!
App.. Apple
Oh Light... !
He's more generous than he looks!
"Dear Misa"
"When you read this letter, you must've remembered everything."
"To create an ideal world together."
"You must resume punishing instead of me."
"And one more thing."
"do you remember the guy named Ryuzaki I introduced you at my college?"
"He's our enemy, L"
That guy is L?
"You must've seen his real name with your Death God's eye."
"Write down the name on the Death Note"
"and eliminate L."
Elminate L...
Damn it!
I can't remember it!
I saw names of hundreds of people everyday
Once you discard the ownership, you lose the ability of "the eye"
I'm sorry, Misa
Ryuk
Make the eye-deal again
Are you sure?
You've already lost half of your lifespan
You'll lose the half of if
I know!
I don't want to lose my face!
Face....
but you have the face.
Don't take it literally!
Well, I don't understand human mind really...
You want the Death God's eye
I have to obey Light...
Just one week after Takada's death...
The new Kira has appeared!
Criminals are being killed again
It means there are more notebooks
Just after,
Amane Misa was freed
Ryuzaki!
Don't give me that again!
Don't you remember the 13 day rule?
Mr Yagami
What?
Let's inspect this notebook
I'll ask FBI and have them provide us with two prisoners from the death row
We'll make the prisoners A write the name of the B
to see if B will die
then leave A from the Note for 13 days to see if A will die
I can't believe you treat human lives like bugs
It can't be helped
It's to protect thousands of people's lives
Isn't there any other way?
Today, again!
A numerous number of criminals are killed
Ryuzaki
You may be right to stop Kira from killing people
I'll take responsibility for the experiment
I'll supervise
Dad..
Thank you for understanding
I'll goto the States
Are you going alone?
Let me go with you
No, you can't
Stay here with Ryuzaki and wait until I contact you
I'll be fine
Others will come with me, little to worry
Wait, am I worrying?
How about here?
Yes, it is worrying
First, goto the Tokyo Bay heliport by car
Then fly to the Yokota Camp. The US army will carry you by plane to Washington D.C.
Watari has arranged for everything
I got it
See you later
Now, we're all alone
What are you thinking about?
Right now
Watari is coming here Amane
It was your plan!
Why Misa?
For some reason, the 13 day rule didn't work for Amane
Amane is the Second Kira
And she has another Death Note
This is what I'm thinking about
Then why she didn't write your name when she was freed?
Probably, she forgot my name she saw at the college
while she was restrained
Forgetting things is a girl's nature
I am going to
show my face to Amane
What?
If you do that, she'll...
Yes, she'll definitely write my name..
We can catch her when she's done it
Let's get her Note
We never know when and when she'll write
There are millions of cameras in this building
What if she didn't bring the Note?
She'll definitely bring it. This is a huge chance
to kill me
All right!
Then we'll catch her, and restrain her again
until she tells us about the First Kira
Is that alright?
We can definitely make her confess
as we have the evidence
You shut out the crew to do this, didn't you?
If she'll be tied like that again
She may die this time
I know I feel sorry, but it can't be helped
What's the matter Death God?
Ryuzaki asked me to come
does it mean he doesn't suspect me as Kira anymore?
Of course, he doesn't
But if...
I couldn't save your life...
If my heart stops
this sensor will automatically alert Mr. Yagami
I've asked him to burn the Death Note
to never be used again
Misa's lifespan has been shortened again
Lifespan?
What do you mean?
Ryuzaki
If you risk your life I'm prepared too
Let's catch Amane Misa
...the Second Kira in the act!
Here she comes
Yagami Light....
You've known that this would happen
Since when I told you that if a Death God expands lifespan of a human
the Death God will die
You drove her intoa a corner
to make me save her
It will expand her lifespan
and I will die instead
That's been your plan from that day
You'll succeed in killing a Death God!
You are the true devil
But still, Misa loves you
Yagami Light!
I'll never let you use my Note!
Misa...
Even if a short while...
be happy...
Watari...!
Checkmate..!
Did you use...
that Death God...?
Rem has a gentle heart
Yagami Light...
I knew it...
You are the Kira
I wanted to know your name
Loser
I am
not a...
Goodbye, L
You were the best rival
of me, Kira, the God of the new world.
If I made a single mistake
I might've been dead too
It was a high risk to release Misa
and let her use Death Note instead of me
Keep watching me achieving the revolution
Farewell, L.
I see...
She burnt the Note with her
Light!
You made it!
Misa, where's the Note?
So, you killed L!
Ryuk! How have you been?
I won, L is dead
But I still have a job
"Yagami Soichiro"
"Heart attack"
That's your own father's name, Light!
To create the new world
But
He's your father!
Why!
Just shut up!
No matter how you love something,
there's the time you have make sacrifices
I cannot be what I used to be
"Comes back with the Death Note, gives it to Light and dies"
Dad...
Give the Death Note back to me
Dad
Since we were young
You don't forgive even the most insignificant injustice
and try to be our model father
I respect you so much
So I'm sure you'll understand
What I'm going to do
What I will achieve
Dad...
I'm sorry
It's your time
Where's the Death Note?
Light
I saw everything
I watched you through the cameras
and I heard your voice
What?
Light!
You're...
under arrest
Light,
I'm so sad
we couldn't be friends
Ryuzaki...?
You...
Why...
A fake notebook!
Misa, you betrayed me!
No, I didn't
How can I betray you?
No matter how evil you are
I love you!
She didn't betray you
It was unexpected that the Death God acted that way
This is the real one
Amane Misa digged out
And this
is my real name, which you wanted to know
You can't change what is written in the Death Note
which means you won't die until the day written first
I'll die 20 days later
so you can't kill me now
when did you switch them?
The criminals I punished died as planned
Yes, on the first day
Then I concluded that you are the Second Kira
The 13 day rule is also false
From the second day, Watari switched it into the fake one
We were watching it
and told you a false information
as if the criminals were killed by Kira
The biggest goal was, Light
to confirm that you're Kira
You're a smart boy
You didn't give me any clue
So I decided
to give up my own life
This plan couldn't succeed without Mr. Yagami's cooperation
He is a very sincere person. At first he refused to do it
But when I showed him my name written in the Note
I think he understood that I was serious
Then he finally said yes
to cooperate with my plan
He said
you're not Kira
he would believe so
until the last moment
The cars didn't go to the heliport
and everyone was watching
what was happening here
The saddest thing is
Watari's death
I couldn't predict that the Death God would write his name
That was my last mistake
Light
I will understand
what you are going to do
you said so
I'm sorry
I cannot understand at all
This isn't justice at all
Before I got the Death Note
the world was dead, with tons of criminals that current laws can't punish!
It was so unreasonable!
You know what happened
After Kira appeared, the crime rate decreased 70%
Isn't that what you want?
to live in such a peaceful world?
Light!
A sheet of the Death Note
I knew you have it
You killed Takada with that
At last,
I found the last piece
You're right, I'm the Kira
I'm God of the new world
No, you're not
You are just a murderer
And this notebook is
The most horrible lethal weapon ever
L...
You don't know, since you don't go out of your cozy room
You don't know that good people are suffering because of evil people in the world!
There are tons of evil human beings
who should disappear for the rest of the people!
It's impossible to save them with the power of the laws
Yes, it's impossible
Laws aren't perfect
because humans, who created laws that aren't perfect
It's impossible to be perfect
However,
the lawas are evidence of human's struggle to be righteous
You are egotistical
It must never be allowed to rob someone's life based on ego!
It's wasteful to talk with you!
Ryuk!
Ryuk, where are you
Hi there
Oh, another Death God
Can everyone see it, as you all have touched the Note?
Ryuk...
I'll show you something fun
Kill them all
Kill them all right now!
Light!
What are you waiting for?
Write their names, hurry
All right, I'll write it down
Don't!
Stop!
It's no use...
Ryuk...
Are you done yet?
yep
Show me
See
"Yagami Light"
Too bad!
You've been too much
dependent on me
Wait...
I said...
I'd show you something fun!
You've shown me enough
You've enjoyed enough too
What are you talking about!
Nothing has started yet!
Oh, I almost forgot to say
A human who used the Death Note
cannot goto heaven nor hell
After you die, you'll see
nought!
Light!
Why, Ryuk, why?
I can't die here!
Light!
Why?
I was always trying to do the right thing
You tought me what justice is, Dad
Why do I have to die like this!
Kira is, the justice...
Dad..
Please understand me...
Light?
You idiot..
I will clean out
every Death Note
You don't want to use it?
Oh, I'm soooo bored!
I reported the eveen to the superiors
I couldn't say anything about the Death Note though
I reported everything to ICPO
They couldn't understand
Kira's death won't be announced
Light was killed by Kira...
It's the truth
I told Sachiko and Sayu
Amane has lost her memory about the Death Note again
Because we burned both notebooks
Ryuzaki
I can't say a word for you
I'm sorry
It's me
who has to apologize
I couldn't even save Light
Ryuzaki,
I'm happy to fight along with you
I"m proud of you
It's my time, let me be alone
I don't know
What kind of people my parents are
But I know, Mr. Yagami
You are a great father
also to me
Ryuzaki...
Goodbye, Mr. Yagami
And thank you
One year later
It's the first time we baked a birthday cake for Light
after he graduated kindergarten
After he entered elementary school, I started buying it every year
I remembe that I blew out the candles
I asked him right?
Your brother let you do it
even though it was his birthday
He was so kind to you
Mom, look!
It's snowing
Sayu, bring an umbrella to the station for Dad
Dad!
Oh, thanks
Shall we share it?
After Kira disappeared, is the crime rate increasing?
Do you think the world still needs Kira?
No, I don't
Kira... killed my...
Light fought against Kira, until the very last moment
I know...
I know, Dad
Happy birthday
I feel like I...
forgot something very important
But...
I can't remember anything!
Light....
Watch Movies, TV Series and Live Sports
Signup Here -> WWW.ADMITME.APP