Allen, Bomb Squad,
Special Services...
State Police and the FBI!
Lieutenant Jurgenson, Upummer! I want
you to go to St. John's Emergency...
in case we got any walk-ins
from the street.
- Take that down there and get it faxed.
- Kramer, get the city engineer!
I gotta find out a damage report.
It's very important.
Bonwit Teller. Who the hell would want
to blow up a department store?
Did you ever see a woman
miss a shoe sale?
Connie, I want you to get started
on the witness sheet.
Ricky, you and Joe, you make sure
the uniforms got it cordoned off there.
And you don't let
the damn TV crews in. Benson!
- Inspector, phone.
- Not now. Benson! Traffic!
We get Fifth Avenue cleared up by 3:00,
or we got the traffic jam from hell!
- Walter!
- Yeah?
I think you'd better take this.
Major Case Unit,
Inspector Cobb.
Said Simple Simon to the pie man
going to the fair...
"Give me your pies...
or I'll cave your head in."
You see, Bonwit's was just
to make sure I had your attention.
Is there a detective
named McClane there?
- He's on suspension.
- No, Walter, he's not. Not today.
- Who is this?
- Call me Simon.
- What do you want?
- I want to play a game.
- What kind of game?
- "Simon says."
Simon's going to tell
Lt McClane what to do...
and Lt McClane is going to do it.
Noncompliance will result
in a penalty.
What penalty?
Another big bang
in a very public place.
What is it that you want
Lt McClane to do?
Simon says Lt McClane
is to go to the corner...
of 138th Street und Amsterdam...
which is in Harlem
if I'm not mistaken.
Kowalski! Lambert!
Do you know where to find McClane?
Well, I kinda doubt
you're gonna find him in church.
Well, you better find out
what rock he's under...
and kick it over.
- John.
- Thanks.
Gimme some more. Come on.
Jesus, John.
You look like shit.
Where did we leave off
with that roster?
We got three killings in Red Hook
the past two nights.
Put Miner on it.
And Genetti.
The mayor's office will call
before the day's out.
Next, 14 dump trucks stolen
from a yard in Staten Island.
Fourteen! Jesus! Is somebody
starting a construction company?
Nah, it was John's landlady
going to clean his apartment.
Insurance fraud.
That's a priority
out in California.
The contractor splits the money
with the thieves.
We had that out in Jersey
a couple years ago, Joe. Remember?
See what Kelly can do with it.
Hey, what was the lottery number
last night?
- 4667.
You still bettin' your badge, Rick?
Yeah, 6991 every week.
6991, lucky number.
Half the cops in New York
play their badges.
How're the kids, John?
I hear they're okay.
Did you talk with Holly?
- No, I didn't talk to Holly.
- Coming up on it, Inspector.
Is it hot in here,
or am I just scared to death?
You wanna make sure
the gun's secure?
Yeah, it's good.
You know, you're the first woman
since Holly who's seen me do this.
- I'm honoured.
- Yeah, so was she.
So, where's the backup gonna be?
We're gonna drop back
to 128th Street.
What?
Ten blocks?
Are you fucking kidding me?
Oh, man, that's just great! Hey, Walter,
what is all this about, huh?
- If we don't do it, this guy says he's
gonna blow up another public place.
- Well, why me?
- What does it got to do with me?
- I have no idea. He just said
it had to be you.
It's nice to be needed.
- Frankly, John, you haven't been...
- Hey, Walter, how 'bout you mind your
fucking business about Holly, huh?
Between you and Simon, you're
fucking up a perfectly good hangover.
Okay.
We'll be back to pick you up
in 15 minutes.
Take your time.
I expect to be dead in four.
Let's go, Billy!
Oh, man.
- Hey, yo, Uncle.
- Come look at this.
It's ten after 9:00.
Why aren't you in school?
- Tony wants to sell you this.
- Tony? That no-neck dude
they call Bad T?
He says he found it
in a Dumpster.
He keeps stealing from people,
they're gonna find him in a Dumpster.
No, he didn't steal it.
He says his uncle gave it to him.
Mm-hmm. Hand me
that newspaper over there.
Don't ever let people use you.
You're runnin' all over town
with stolen property.
If you get caught,
you get in trouble...
while he gets to deny
the whole thing and walk away.
You... You mean you want us
to take it back to Tony?
No, I'll take it back to Tony,
with a message.
- Now, where you goin'?
- School.
- Why?
- To get educated?
- So we can go to college.
- And why is that important?
- To get "espect."
"Respect."
And who's the bad guys?
- Guys who sell drugs.
- Guys who have guns.
- And who's the good guys?
- We're the good guys.
- Who's gonna help you?
- Nobody.
- So who's gonna help you?
- We're gonna help ourselves.
- And who do we not want to help us?
- White people.
That's right.
Now, get on outta here.
Go to school.
- Uncle, you better come look at this.
- What?
There's a white man
standing in the street.
- I seen one.
- Not like this.
Dial 9-1-1. Tell the police
to get up here quick.
Somebody's about to get killed. And get
your butts to school. You hear me?
- Yeah.
- All right.
- I paid 500 bucks...
- You better back off, man.
- Hey, man!
- He ain't so big.
- Morning.
- Good morning.
You having a nice day, sir?
You feeling all right?
Not to get too personal...
but a white man standin'
in the middle of Harlem...
wearin' a sign that says
"I hate niggers"...
has either got some serious
personal issues...
or not all his dogs are barkin'.
Hey, I'm talkin' to you!
Now, you got about ten seconds
before those guys see you.
When they do, they will kill you.
You understand?
You are about to have
a very bad day.
Tell me about it.
Sir, this is a police matter.
- For your own safety, I'm gonna
ask you to step across the street.
- You damn right it's a police matter!
For your own safety, I suggest
you hide your butt in my shop
till the police get here.
What the fuck?
Aw, shit.
- Listen, I'm a cop. I'm on a case.
- What?
Somebody blew up
Bonwit Teller's an hour ago.
Did you hear about that on the news?
- Yeah.
- The same asshole that did that said...
I gotta come to Harlem and do this
or he's gonna blow up something else.
- Do you understand?
- Shit, shit, shit.
- Listen, I got a gun.
You should get across the street.
- They got ten guns.
- You should get across the street!
- Look, start acting crazy, all right?
- What?
- Like Looney Tunes.
You know, like Bellevue?
- Hey, Zeus, this a friend of yours?
- He look like a friend of mine?
I think the dude just escaped from
some hospital. You know, like Bellevue?
I am the voice of my own god.
And my god did...
I told the librarian that I had a bad
headache, but she didn't believe me.
I really do have a bad headache, though.
I have a very bad headache!
- And my head does not feel...
- Oh, man, shut the fuck...
- Who in the fuck...
- You've made a very bad mistake.
- Kick his ass.
- Put it through his head.
- Bust his head.
Cut this shit off!
Fellas! Fellas!
Nature boy here hates niggers.
Now, what are we gonna do about that?
- Fight him!
- Yo, yo, yo, yo!
Hold up! Hold up! Hold up!
- Oh, shit!
- Yeah!
Get him! Get him!
- Back! Back up!
- Hey, what you trippin' on?
- Back the fuck up! Now!
- Hey, you better quit that, boy!
Come on, man, get up.
Get up! Get outta here!
Stop the c...
Stop the goddam cab!
- Don't shoot!
No, don't shoot me! Don't shoot!
- Don't move that cab! Get up!
- Come on, get up!
- Yo, you sayin' you gonna kill us?
I mean it! I don't want to, but I will!
You know I will! Come on. Drive! Drive!
- Drive! Go! Go! Go! Drive, goddam it!
-  Get the fuck outta here!
Drive! Drive!
Don't stop! Don't stop!
- Just keep driving!
Run the red light! Drive!
- Don't shoot me, man! That's all I got!
- That's all I got.
- Man, put that fuckin' money away!
- Nobody's robbing you, asshole!
- Don't kill me!
- Nobody's gonna kill you!
- Shit!
- Just run all the lights! Drive!
- Oh, man! Damn!
- We got a bus.
- That cut deep?
- How the hell would I know?
Just keep pressure on it.
Oh, fuck!
- Jesus, right? John McClane.
I owe you one.
- Damn right, you owe me!
- You got any idea what those guys
are doin' to my shop right now?
- Chill out, Jesus!
- We'll send a car for...
- "Chill out"? What the fuck?
Are you tryin' to relate to me?
- Talk like a white man!
- Okay. Jesus, I'm sorry
you got involved, all right?
Why do you keep calling me Jesus?
I look Puerto Rican to you?
- Guy back there
called you Jesus, didn't he?
- He didn't say Jesus!
- He said, "Hey, Zeus." My name is Zeus.
- Zeus?
Yeah, Zeus! As in father of Apollo!
Mount Olympus!
"Don't fuck with me, or I'll shove
a lightning bolt up your ass!"
Zeus! You got a problem with that?
- No, I don't have a problem with that.
- Shit!
- Downtown. Police Plaza.
- That's just great.
Get a record of all his collars,
recent releases...
and a list of anybody else
he might have looked at sideways.
It's probably as long as your arm,
so I'm gonna need some help with it.
It's textbook megalomania.
It's a pathological state...
in which fantasies of control
or omnipotence predominate.
He wants control over him.
He wants control over his actions,
over his thoughts, even his emotions.
- Sounds like you got
a secret admirer, John.
- Yeah, maybe he'll send me some flowers.
- Everybody knows you like pansies.
- It's not tha0 kind o- emotion.
- This guy is ugly.
- How is that?
Nothin' wrong with him
a shower wouldn't cure.
Beer is normally taken
internally, John.
- Just get me some aspirins, will ya?
- Yeah, okay. Hold this here.
This is Fred Schiller, John,
and he's a...
- A shrink. Yeah, I got it.
- Yes. I was saying that we're dealing...
with a megalomaniacal personality
with possible paranoid schizophrenia.
Hey, hey, how about we just skip down
to the part where you tell me what
the fuck this has to do with me, huh?
I don't know. I mean,
what I do know is it does have
specifically to do with you.
This guy wants to pound on you
till you crumble.
He wants you to dance
to his tune and then...
Put on a dress and fuck me?
I was going to say kill you.
- Pick up five, goddam it!
- He's sitting on an awful lot of rage...
and it could be manifested physically
if he's stressed.
Somebody he arrested?
Somebody he pissed off?
- That could be one hell of a long list.
- Fuck you, Joe.
See, these people don't like
to work anonymously.
They want you to know
who's doing it to you.
So this name "Simon"
is probably not an alias.
It's probably "Simon"
or some variation.
"Simon, Robert E. Busted in '86,
extortion, kidnapping, ten to fifteen.
Did seven years for good behaviour.
Released on a state work-furlough
two months ago."
- Check it.
- Thanks, Rick.
Bob Simons was a bankrupt businessman
who kidnapped his partner's daughter.
He's a fuckup, not a psycho.
The guy we're lookin' for is nuts.
A nut who knows a lot about bombs.
We found this in a playground.
Professional!
Very cool stuff.
You know, boom!
- You think you should
slam it around like that, Charlie?
- When it's unmixed, you can't hurt it.
This stuff is cutting edge.
It's a binary liquid.
- A what?
- Like epoxy.
Two liquids.
Either one by itself...
you got nothin', but mix 'em...
Ricky.
Charlie, you're gonna be wearing
that shirt up your ass!
- Christ Almighty, Charlie!
- Like I said, very cool stuff.
Now, with a package like this,
you get a warning.
Now, the bomb has to arm itself.
You'll see the red liquid
pump into the clear before it detonates.
- How long before?
- Ten seconds, two minutes.
Could be anything.
But once it's mixed,
be somewhere else.
This stuff has gotta be pretty rare.
We oughta be able to find out
if any of it's missin' somewhere.
I already did. Livermore Labs
theft over the weekend.
He got enough to make
another one, Joe?
- About 2,000 pounds.
- Of that?
Well, the detonating mechanism
could be anything... radio, electrical.
Hell, you could use a beeper
and phone it in.
- Inspector? Inspector, it's him.
- He's got a double Alberti
feedback loop on it.
- A nasty little trick
I believe once used in Lebanon.
- Charlie. Charlie!
- Charlie, shh!
- What?
Wanna start the trace?
Simon.
He wore the board,
walked the street and survived.
- Where are my pigeons now?
- Pigeons?
I had two pigeons, bright and gay,
fly from me the other day.
Why was it they did go?
You cannot tell. You do not know.
- You mean McClane?
- No, I mean Santa Claus.
- Yeah, I'm here.
- Ah, there after all. And your friend?
Carver! Carver! Come on.
We need you in the other room.
- Let's go! Come on!
- They need you. Go.
- Yeah, he's here too.
- And may I speak with him?
Well, is the ebony
Samaritan there now?
- You got a problem with ebony?
- No, no.
My only problem is that I went to some
trouble preparing that game for McClane.
You interfered
with a well-laid plan.
Yeah? Well, you can stick your
well-laid plan up your well-laid ass.
That was not smart.
There are lives at stake here!
- Not enough time, Inspector.
- You better hope he calls back.
He will.
Ricky, you wanna tell those people
to shut the hell up out there!
Hey, keep it down here!
Simon, he wasn't speaking
for all of us.
That was unpleasant.
Don't let it happen again.
- So, what's your name, boy?
- Don't call me "boy."
I'm sorry.
It was a poor attempt at humour.
I was going to send you home
with a chiding...
- but now I think perhaps
you should join the game.
- We got him!
It's a pay phone in Oslo.
- No, w-wait, they say
it's Juarez, Mexico.
- Norway?
No, wait. No, wait. N-Now
they're saying it's Juarez, Mexico.
Forget it! Australia?
He's scrambling up their system.
They don't know where he is.
Having fun with
the phone company, are we?
Simon says,
McClane and the Samaritan...
will go to the subway station
at 72nd and Broadway.
I will call you in 15 minutes
on the pay phone outside the station.
No police. Failure to answer
will constitute noncompliance.
Do you understand me, John?
Oh, yes, I understand. I understand
that you're a fuckin' wacko...
that likes to play kids games,
that's what I understand.
- Hardly.
- Hardly?
Well, then, who are you?
Somebody I sent up? What'd you do?
Shoplifting? Purse snatching?
Cross dressing? What?
You c-c-couldn't catch me if I stole
your ch-chair with you in it.
My ch-ch-ch-chair with me in it?
Ooh-hoo! That's very exciting.
Let me ask you a question, bonehead.
Why are you trying to k-k-k-kill me?
- John, John, calm yourself.
- Why don't you come on
down here to Police Plaza...
and we'll figure this out
like a couple of men, huh?
- Just come on down here.
- If killing you was all I wanted...
- Simon, this is Inspector Cobb.
- you'd be dead by now.
I can appreciate your feelings
for McClane...
but believe me,
the jerk isn't worth it.
He's stepped on so many toes
in this department...
by this time next month
he's gonna be a security guard.
His own wife wants
nothing to do with him...
and he's about two steps shy
of becoming a full-blown alcoholic.
One step. One step.
Now listen to me.
You sound like a real smart guy.
What is it that you want?
Are you talking about money?
Well, whatever, whatever.
McClane is a toilet bug.
Now what would it take just to forget
him and live happily ever after?
You know, money is shit to me.
I would not give up McClane
for all the gold in your Fort Knox.
72nd Street subway,
pay phone, 15 minutes.
McClane and the Samaritan.
If you're competent in the least,
you've found the briefcase...
so you know what I mean by penalty.
I wanna thank you for that vote
of confidence, Walter.
Well, I thought it was worth a try.
This guy's a raving maniac.
Well, he-he couldn't be any clearer
if he got it from a case history.
He gave you clues
to his identity.
He spoke German.
He called it "your Fort Knox."
And he stammered
when McClane pushed him.
Now, you believe this guy
really can't be bought?
There's no chance. The very mention
of money only enraged him further.
- What's that?
- It's your shield.
- You askin' me to be
a cop again, Walter?
- Ricky, get him his gun, all right?
- You didn't answer my question. Hey!
- Joe, this time they...
- You didn't answer my question, Walter.
- Are you done, Lieutenant?
Now, you two better get going if you're
going to get up to 72nd Street on time.
- Joe, this time they go with backup.
- You got it.
- Come on, you guys!
- I'm not goin' anywhere.
- Simon says you gotta go!
- I'm not jumpin' through hoops
for some psycho!
That's a white man with white problems.
You deal with him.
- Call me when he crosses 110th Street.
- Hey! Why'd you save my ass?
I didn't. I stopped a white cop
from gettin' killed in Harlem.
One white cop gets killed today...
tomorrow we got a thousand white cops,
all of 'em with itchy trigger fingers.
- Got it?
- Get him back.
- Charlie, where'd you find that bomb?
- Chinatown.
Shit.
Zeus! Yo, partner! Wait up!
Hey, hey, hey, hey!
I ain't your partner.
I ain't your neighbour, your brother
or your friend. I'm your total stranger.
Okay, stranger...
you know where that park is
at 115th Street and St Nicholas?
- Yeah, it's in Harlem.
- Where do you think
we found that bomb?
Listen, this guy doesn't care
about skin colour, even if you do.
- What am I doin'?
- Cheer up. Things could be worse.
I was workin'
on a nice, fat suspension...
smokin' cigarettes
and watchin' Captain Kangaroo.
Come on.
Is that the phone?
Okay, they made it to the phone,
but there's a problem.
Well, what do you mean?
How big a problem?
Oh, about 300 pounds.
- And they're probably going to end up
having to get an operation.
- Ma'am? Excuse me, ma'am.
- We need this phone
for official police business.
- Do you mind!
- Honey, I'm a cop.
I need the phone right now.
- I'm sorry, but I can no...
Get off the damn phone, lady!
Police business!
- Well, I never!
- I can get used to this.
I'm sure you can find a phone
across the street, ma'am.
Let's get something straight.
I'm the only one here
on official police business.
- Don't ever do that shit again.
- Let's get somethin' else straight.
You need me
a lot more than I need you.
You don't like the way
I do things, fine. I quit.
I don't know.
All right, I need you.
All right, I need you
more than you need me.
- Hello!
- Birds of a feather flock together.
So do pigs and swine.
Rats and mice have their chance,
as will I have mine.
Nice. Rhymes.
- Why was the phone busy?
Who were you calling?
- The Psychic Hotline.
I'd advise you to take this
more seriously.
Look, it's a public phone!
What do you want me to say?
You can simply say
there was a fat woman on it, and it
took you a minute to get her off!
Now, John, there's a significant
amount of explosive...
in the trash receptacle next to you.
Try to run,
and it goes up now.
Nobody's gonna run, but I got
a hundred people out here!
That's the point.
Now, do I have your attention?
As I was going to St Ives,
I met a man with seven wives.
Every wife had seven sacks.
Every sack had seven cats.
Every cat had seven kittens.
Kittens, cats, sacks and wives.
How many were going to St Ives?
My phone number is 555...
- No, no, no! Wait! I didn't
get all that! Say it again!
- Not a chance.
- My phone number is 555 and the answer.
- But I didn't...
Call me in 30 seconds or die.
- All right,
seven guys with seven wives makes...
- Shut up, McClane. I'm good at this.
- Seven guys with seven wives makes...
- Shut the fuck up, McClane!
He said seven wives with seven sacks.
- Seven times seven is 49.
Now tell me the rest.
- Seven wives?
- A sack with...
s-seven sacks with seven...
- Weren't you listening?
- Yeah, I was listening.
I didn't hear every fuckin' thing...
- What the heck is wrong with you?
- Well, I... Besides having
a bad fuckin' hangover, for one thing!
- All right, all right, all right.
Seven wives times seven, 49.
With seven cats.
Seven times 49 is 343, right?
- What, are you asking me or telling me?
- I'm telling you. 343 times seven is...
One, zero, 24. 2,401.
That's what you got, right?
Yeah, that's what I got.
Is that it, 2,401?
- That's it. Dial. 555-2401.
- 555-2401.
- No, wait, wait!
It's a trick. It's a trick.
- What? What? What do you mean?
- I forgot about the man.
- What man? Fuck the man!
We got ten seconds left!
He said how many were going
to St Ives, right?
The riddle begins: As I was going to
St Ives, I met a man with seven wives.
- The guy and his wives
aren't goin' anywhere.
- What are they doing?
Sittin' in the fuckin' road
waitin' on a mo...
How the hell should I know, McClane?
- Well, who's going to St Ives then?
- The guy. Just the guy.
- Just one guy? Just one guy.
- The answer's one.
- How do you dial one?
- 555-0001.
- Zero, zero, one. Just one guy's going?
- Hello, John.
Yeah, piece of cake.
Give us somethin' harder next time.
- But you're ten seconds late.
- No, no! The answer is one! The...
- Boom!
- There's a bomb in the trash! Get down!
- Everybody, get down!
Get down! There's a bomb!
Everybody, get down!
There's a bomb!
Get down! There's a bomb!
- Welcome to New York.
- Really.
They were just talking.
Here, you can have it. Come on.
- Come on, let's go.
- I'm getting outta here right now.
- I told you it wasn't a bomb.
- I thought there was a bomb!
No bomb.
- Yeah.
- I didn't say "Simon says."
It's 9:50,John.
The number 3 train is arriving now.
I left something provocative
on that train, John.
Simon says,
get to the pay phone...
next to the news kiosk
in Wall Street Station by 10:20...
- Half an hour.
- or the number 3 train
and its passengers vaporize.
Use any means of travel
other than civilian, I blow the train.
Attempt to evacuate the subway,
I blow the train.
I'll call you in 30 minutes.
Be there.
- We're fucked.
- Ninety blocks in 30 minutes?
In New York traffic?
It could be double that.
We don't even have a car!
Hey! Hey! Sir! Sir!
I'm a cop! I'm a cop!
- I am requisitioning this car
for official police business.
- Hey, what are you doing?
- Thank you very much. Get in! Get in!
- What the fuck you doing to my car?
- Pretty slick.
Listen, I used to drive a cab.
The fastest way south is...
What the fuck are you doing?
- What were you sayin'?
- I was saying I used to drive a cab.
Ninth Avenue is the fastest way south.
But we seem to be going east.
Where the hell are you going, McClane?
I told you Ninth Avenue
was the quickest way south!
- Stop with that goddam yelling!
I know what I'm doing!
- Not even God knows what you're doing!
They're headed east on 72nd
towards the park.
- But Wall Street is south!
- Man, stop yelling at me!
I got a bad headache!
And the best way south is not
Ninth Avenue, it's through the park.
Oh, dear.
I told you the park drive
is always jammed.
I didn't say park drive.
I said through the park.
Shit! We lost 'em.
They're in the park headed south.
- Get outta here!
- Fucking prick!
I got him, Connie.
He's taking the scenic route.
- Outta the way!
- Oh, man.
Get out! Get outta there!
Watch it, watch it, watch it,
watch it! Oh, my God!
Are you... Are you aiming
for these people?
No. Well, maybe that mime.
Tree! Tree! Tree!
What's goin' on here?
Look out!
- Tree! Tree!
- Just hang on.
Rock! Rock! Rock!
Hey, look out down there!
McClane! McClane, watch it.
McClane!
Come on! Outta the way!
- How do Catholics do their thing?
- North, south, west, east.
- How much time?
- Twenty-seven minutes.
Ha! 72nd and Broadway
to Central Park South in three minutes!
That's gotta be a fuckin' record.
Come on, get out...
Yeah. Now what?
- We need a fire truck.
- What?
To follow.
- 9-1-1.
- Lt John McClane, NYPD.
Access number 7479.
Calling from a civilian transmitter.
- Get me an emergency
dispatcher right away.
- Dispatch. Go ahead.
I got two officers down at the corner
of 14th Street and Ninth Avenue!
Need an ambulance! Over!
Emergency calls on the west side
go to Roosevelt Hospital.
That's two blocks from here.
- Slow the fuck down, McClane!
- Kinda like football, isn't it?
- What?
- Get yourself a blocker
and head for the end zone!
If you'd said Wall Street,
we could've followed him all the way.
Wrong! South of 14th Street's
a different hospital!
St Luke's. Hang on.
- Time?
- 10:02.
We're halfway there
with 18 minutes to go.
Fuck this! Hang on.
Hang on. Get outta there!
Slide over and take the wheel.
- Where you goin'?
- We should be ahead
of that train, right?
- You're not gonna get on that train...
- I'm gonna get on that train! You gotta
get to that pay phone by 10:20!
- What are you gonna do?
- I'm gonna get that bomb.
Listen, you fail, I cover your ass.
I fail, you cover my ass.
- And if we both fail?
- Then we're both fucked.
Go now! Drive! Get to that
phone booth by 10:20! Go!
My lucky fuckin' day.
Shit! Look out, ma'am!
Look out! Look out! Look out!
Get outta the way!
This is a bad idea!
Excuse me! Excuse me!
Just get outta the way, please!
- 112 Wall Street.
- Wait. This isn't a taxi.
You don't understand.
Your light's on.
I'll make it simple.
112 Wall Street, or I'll have
your medallion suspended.
What, you don't like
white people?
112 Wall Street?
You got it.
Come on.
Fuck!
Move your legs, sir.
Get your legs outta the way!
Sorry. Sorry.
- Hey! Excuse me!
- 1823405...
Hey!
Shit!
Excuse me! Watch out!
Excuse me, sir.
Pardon me, please. Excu...
- Will you step outta here for a minute.
- What?
I'm a cop. Step out of here
for a minute, please. Will ya?
Excuse me, please!
Let me get through here, please!
- It's him.
- Excuse me. Excuse me, please. Pardon.
Excuse me, sir, but I'm expecting
a call. I need that phone.
Why don't you use
the other phone?
Sir, please.
I need to use that phone.
Hey, listen, bro,
I was here first.
"Bro"? Get away
from the goddam phone!
Put your hands up!
- I have to answer that phone.
- Just shut up and get 'em in the air!
Watch it! Excuse me! Pardon me!
Watch, watch your back! Watch it!
Ladies and gentlemen,
I'm a New York police officer.
I'm gonna ask you to calmly
and quietly start moving towards
the other end of the car.
Go now, please! Go now!
Fuck! Let's go!
Watch it! Watch out!
Watch... Watch it! Go!
I have to answer that phone.
Get 'em up!
Look, if you have to shoot me...
then you go ahead
and you shoot me!
But I have to answer this phone,
all right?
- I'm here.
- And McClane?
He's on his way. Uh, you know, he's
a little slow. He's kinda out of shape.
The rules applied to both of you.
I'm afraid this is noncompliance.
Goodbye.
Trust me, guys. Duck.
Hey, get outta there!
Get outta there! Duck, asshole!
Oh, my God!
McClane?
What?
- You can see right down into the subway.
- How many fire trucks do you count?
- You guys! You guys!
- How can you see it from up here?
Damn! Get in there.
Officer, tell those people
to get the hell back, will ya?
We got a shitload of cuts and bruises,
a couple concussions...
some old guy's pacemaker stopped,
and a pregnant girl's water broke.
And that's all.
How're you doin', John?
Still can't hear too good.
Well, it's a miracle you're still alive.
It's a goddam miracle.
- Yeah, that's the problem, Joe.
- What?
The miracle part. What are the odds
of us makin' it down here on time?
- Zip.
- That bomb was gonna go off
no matter what.
He wanted it to go off
right down here.
Take this off me, Dave.
Well, what's so special
about this place?
- I don't know.
Something just doesn't add up.
- Lt McClane?
They're asking for you and a Mr Carver.
- Where?
- John?
John, this is Andy Cross
with the FBI.
- This is Mr Jarvis. He's...
- I'm, uh, with another agency.
- It's good to meet you.
- This is Lt McClane.
This is Mr Carver.
We've got
a couple of questions first.
Do you recognize this guy?
- No.
- How about this one?
How about you?
Did you recognize
the voice on the phone?
No.
Did you, uh, notice
any cars following you?
- No.
- Anybody following you at all?
Any kind of surveillance?
Telephone? House?
Anything unusual at all?
Well, now that you mention it,
I have experienced a...
you know, like a burning sensation
between my toes.
I thought it was just some athlete's
foot or something. I don't know.
We read your jacket, Lieutenant.
We were told you would be cooperative.
- Cooperate with what?
What do you mean cooperate?
- Hey, now wait a minute. He will be.
- We're wasting time
here in this goddam van.
- You wanna share information...
how about sending
a little our way as well?
- Look, we wanna hear
what he knows first.
- What the hell?
- You give us pictures, and then you...
- Look, we want to hear
what he knows first.
Hey, I know as much as you know.
All right?
There's a guy out there
settin' off bombs.
He calls himself Simon.
He speaks with a German accent.
And, for some reason,
he's very angry with me.
Now, maybe you can tell me
why, fellas.
The first man there is Methias Targo.
Was Hungarian army.
Explosives expert. Now we believe
he's working for the Iranians.
- Working?
- Freelance terrorism, by contract.
- Who's the girl?
- Targo's other half.
Rumour is the Israelis slipped a bomb
in between their sheets.
Uh, he wasn't at home,
but they think maybe they got her.
The second man was an obscure colonel
in the East German army.
He ran an infiltration unit.
The kind of thing the Nazis did
at the Battle of the Bulge.
- English-speaking troops...
- Yeah, yeah, I saw the movie.
All we know of him is the G.D.R. medical
records show he suffers from migraines.
His name is Peter Krieg.
Well, that is
an exceptional report, fellas.
Now do you wanna tell me
what the hell this has to do with me?
The name Gruber mean anything
to you, Lieutenant?
- It rings a bell, yeah.
- LA.
- What?
- That thing in the building in LA.
Peter Krieg was born...
Simon Peter Gruber.
He's Hans Gruber's brother.
- Oh, shit.
- Yeah, it's that thing in LA.
We figure he's got you
fitted up for a toe tag...
and he's gonna do anything
to get it tied.
Inspector!
Inspector, it's him!
Don't let him know we're here.
- Simon.
- Inspector.
Now, who from the FBI
is in the van, I wonder?
Let's see.
Almost certainly Cross.
- Come on, Andrew. Say hello.
- Hello.
And I know you never run alone,
so say hello, Bill.
Still trying to butch up
by chewing on your glasses, huh?
This, gentlemen, as they say,
is where the plot thickens.
I have put 2,400 pounds of explosive...
in one of the 1,446 schools
in greater New York.
It is fitted with a timer
set to explode at exactly 3:00 pm.
Thank you.
Your silence says I'm understood.
Did you say 2,400 pounds?
Yes, but please
don't interrupt again.
Simon says, if you attempt
to evacuate schools...
the bomb will be detonated
by radio.
And, gentlemen,
someone will be watching.
Repeat, one school will be dismissed
at 3:00 pm, permanently.
- Unless...
- Unless what?
Unless John McClane and his new best
friend complete the tasks I set them.
John, are you listening?
Yeah.
The pay phone beyond Hope,
Tomkins Square Park.
Twenty minutes.
Go by foot. No rush.
If you're really clever,
you'll learn the location of the bomb
and the code to disarm it.
Oh, and by the way, gentlemen...
we got something of a bargain
on radio detonators.
The only problem is
the darn things seem to respond...
to police and FBI frequencies.
So, if I were you,
I'd keep off your radios.
Simon, wait.
Twenty-four hundred pounds
of that liquid stuff.
My God.
Get me the commissioner.
He's doing a press conference. He's
supposed to be here in half an hour.
All right, Ricky, get
every senior officer on the site
and get 'em here right away.
You're not gonna give me
any jurisdictional nonsense on this?
I got two kids
in the school on 64th Street.
- What can I do to help you?
- How many men have you got?
Seventy-five. But if I push the panic
button, I can get 500 from Washington.
- When?
- 2:30, 3:00.
Between now and then...
We're gonna have to do this
all by ourselves. Let's go.
And Tomkins Square Park
is more than two miles away,
so you guys better get running.
No radios.
You take my telephone.
You get anything, you call me
through the switchboard. Good luck.
Thanks.
Find that bomb.
- Ricky, where are they?
- Right over here.
- The senior man present is Chief Allen.
- Chief of what?
- Transit.
- Okay, thanks, Ricky.
Gentlemen, we have a decision to make.
Chief Allen.
The man who has done this
has told us that he has planted...
another very large bomb in a school
here in the New York area.
And he has told us that we cannot
evacuate, but he has not said
that we cannot search.
Now, I recommend we get everybody,
and I mean everybody...
I'm talking about police,
transit, sanitation, fire...
even the goddam librarians...
and we start searching schools,
and I mean right now.
I'm talking about a thousand buildings
within the city limits...
and we have three hours
and 15 minutes to do it in.
Now, I'd like to keep the media
out of this as long as possible...
because if they get in,
we've got a panic.
Are we in agreement?
Come on, guys. Let's go!
Move it out! Move it out!
No radio contact. No radio contact.
They bought it.
You can begin.
Hook, line...
and sinker.
All right now, men.
Let's go! Let's go!
Let's go!
- Hey, hold on. Let me go over there.
- I gotta get through!
Sergeant Turley!
In the last five minutes, the volume
of calls in here has tripled!
- What the hell is goin' on?
- Stop. Let me explain.
For the rest of the day,
we're supposed to handle
the department's communications.
What do you mean "handle"?
They're shutting down the police band.
All calls will be coming
through this switchboard.
And I'm gonna marry Donald Trump!
Walsh, what's going on?
Why'd everybody tear out of here?
Come on, Pamela. Look at your watch!
It's comin' up on shift change.
The bean counters are worried
about overtime...
so we sent everybody back
to the precinct to punch out.
- The next shift
is gonna be here in a minute.
- You are so full of shit, Walsh!
Thank you.
What the hell?
Detective, Bob Thompson,
city engineer's office.
We'd like to get an idea
of the damage.
Man, you guys really
got here fast.
Well, it's Wall Street, sir.
A lot of money here.
A lot of opinion makers the mayor
doesn't wanna piss off, you know?
Is this it?
Holy Toledo!
Somebody had fun.
I'd appreciate it if you'd show
my associates the way down.
Yeah. Yeah, sure. Jimmy!
You got the flashlight?
Murphy, come on, you too!
- Rick Walsh.
- John Gunther.
Come on, gentlemen. Let's go!
You were probably at the World Trades.
You know what that mess was.
Please inform Mr Little
that Mr Vanderfloog is here.
Mr Vanderfloog?
There's a Mr Vanderfloog
for Mr Little.
Go down 20 metres! Come on!
- A lot of steam down here.
- Yeah, yeah. We snapped
a couple of the steam pipes.
It's like a sauna. We got the subway
guys to shut down the third rail.
- It's on emergency lighting.
- Yeah, emergency lights, and
there's still some light... Hey!
No shooting!
Speak English!
Otto doesn't speak English,
do you, Otto?
- Where the hell did we get this guy?
- He's one of Targo's thugs.
Pull all the way up!
Pull all the way! Pull all the way!
So what's up with this LA thing?
You famous or somethin'?
Yeah, for about five minutes.
- Don't tell me. Rodney King, right?
- Fuck you.
- You know this guy Simon
we're talking to?
- Yeah.
I threw his little brother off the 32nd
floor of Nakatomi Towers out in LA.
I guess he's a little
pissed off about it.
Wait a minute.
You mean to tell me I'm in this shit...
'cause some white cop threw some
white asshole's brother off a roof?
Mr Vanderfloog?
Felix Little, corporate relations.
Sorry you had to wait, but apparently
there was an explosion in the subway.
It's played hell
with our alarms, I'm afraid.
- I trust there's nothing wrong.
- Oh, no. Good Lord, no. Safe and secure.
Now, you were concerned
about a currency exchange?
W-We are not a commercial bank,
in the normal sense.
We're... We're primarily...
governments, central banks,
that sort of thing.
- Apart from the depository, of course.
- Of course.
Yeah. And you are in the flower
business, Mr Vanderfloog?
Back! Back! Come on!
Come on!
Oh, no, Mr Vanderfloog,
that's the vault elevator.
I'm sorry. Our alarms
are sonic and seismic...
two things which, I'm afraid,
do not react well to explosions.
You know, th-this subway business
has knocked all our systems
into a cocked hat.
In fact, we've had to give up
and pull the plug on the whole thing.
- The repair people are downstairs now.
- Good Lord!
Yes, yes. Heavens to Betsy!
If anyone knew!
But I thought this was
a currency exchange.
Oh, I think we'll go straight
to the withdrawal.
Hey, Captain, you wanna come down here
and take a look at this?
Somethin's going on.
What do you think, guys?
You'll be able to fix that?
Just a minute now.
Okay, I'll be right back. Down!
Stay back!
Come on. Come on. Shit.
- Come on.
- Front desk.
Yes. Call the police. Get your ass
down here right now! I'm under attack!
Hey, just relax, mate.
Maybe you'll live through this.
Shit!
I think he's dead, my dear.
All right.
Let's see to the office work.
God! It's Fort Knox!
$140 billion.
Ten times what's in Kentucky.
Fort Knox. Ha!
It's for tourists.
Yeah. McClane.
John, you're out of shape?
You barely made it.
Yeah, well, we all barely make it.
What do you want us to do?
What has four legs
and is always ready to travel?
- What?
- What did he say?
What has four legs
and is always ready to travel?
What's the matter with you? Don't you
have kids? That's an elephant joke.
That a bomb?
- Yeah. Go, go ahead and grab it.
- No. You're the cop.
- Man, Simon said you're supposed to be
helpin' with this.
- I'm helpin'.
- Well, when're you gonna start helpin'?
- After you get the bomb.
- Careful.
- I'm being careful.
- Don't open it.
- What?
I gotta open it.
Uh, it's gonna be all right.
Shit! Shit!
I told you not to open it!
I trust you see the message.
It has a proximity circuit,
so, please, don't run.
Yeah, I got it. We're not gonna run.
How do we turn this thing off?
On the fountain there should be
two jugs. Do you see them?
A five-gallon and a three-gallon.
Fill one of the jugs
with exactly four gallons of water...
and place it on the scale
and the timer will stop.
You must be precise. One ounce more
or less will result in detonation.
If you're still alive in five minutes,
we'll speak then.
Wait! Wait a sec...
- I don't get it. Do you get it?
- No.
Get the jugs.
Obviously, we can't fill
the three-gallon jug with
four gallons of water, right?
- Obviously.
- All right. I know. Here we go.
We fill the three-gallon jug
exactly to the top, right?
Okay. Now, we pour that three gallons
into the five-gallon jug...
giving us exactly three gallons
in the five-gallon jug, right?
- Right. Then what?
- Okay. Now, take the three-gallon jug,
fill that a third of the way up...
- No, no, no. He said be precise.
Exactly four gallons.
- Shit!
Every cop in 50 miles is runnin'
his ass off, and I'm out here
playin' kids games in a park.
You wanna focus
on the problem at hand?
I thought you said you knew! You said
don't say anything if you don't know!
I thought you said... Gimme the fuckin'
jug. We're startin' over.
- No! We can't start over!
We can't start over!
- Pour that out! We're startin' over!
- We can't start over.
- Gimme the fuckin' jug, or I'm gonna put
my foot up your ass, you dumb mother...
- Say it! Say it!
- What?
- You were gonna call me
a nigger, weren't you?
- No, I wasn't!
- Yes, you were.
What were you gonna call me?
- Asshole!
How's that, asshole?
You got some fuckin' problem
with me 'cause I'm white, Zeus?
Is that it? Have I oppressed you?
Have I oppressed your people somehow?
I'll tell you what your problem is. You
don't like me 'cause you're a racist!
- What?
- You're a racist.
You don't like me 'cause I'm white.
I don't like you
because you're gonna get me killed!
How much time?
Aw, shit!
We got less than a minute.
Throw this thing away.
No, we can't take it off of there.
It'll detonate. Just, wait.
Wait a second. Wait a second.
I got it! I got it!
Exactly two gallons in here, right?
- Right.
- Leaving exactly one gallon
of empty space, right?
- Yeah.
- A full five gallons here, right?
- Right.
- If you pour one gallon out of the five
gallons into there we have exactly...
- Four gallons in there!
- Yes!
- Pour it in there! Come on!
Come on!
Don't spill. Don't spill it!
- Good, good, good! Exactly four gallons.
- You did it, McClane.
- Put it on the thing!
Get it down there!
- Oh, shit.
Congratulations.
You're still alive.
- Yeah, we did it.
- You surprise me again, John.
This is becoming an ugly habit.
Yeah, well, I don't have the time
right now, Simon. Listen.
Deal's a deal.
Where's the school bomb?
On the contrary,
you have lots of time.
You have...
two hours and 47 minutes precisely.
Plenty of time
to test those wits of yours.
Hey! Hey! Hey, listen, jerk-off!
Let me tell you somethin'!
I got a bad fuckin' hangover, all right?
And I'm a little sick of these fuckin'
riddles! Now, where is the school bomb?
Temper, John.
The road to truth has many turns.
You will find an envelope
under the rim of the fountain.
When you undertake the trip it suggests,
ask yourself this question:
What is 21 out of 42?
We're behind.
We should abandon the rest and go.
Relax, Targo.
There's not a cop for 20 blocks.
He's sending us to the home team dugout
at Yankee Stadium. Why?
Well, we're the home team. Are we
supposed to find something there?
What's 21 out of 42?
Twenty-one again.
Half of 42. Forty-two what?
- How many players
are on the Yankees ball club?
- Twenty-five.
- What else is 21? Blackjack.
- It's a club.
It's a wild goose chase,
is what it is.
Where's the nearest "A" train?
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
You know,
some kid might find that.
You're right.
Come back here!
You little sons of bitches!
Hey, you! I remember you!
Hey, hey, hey. Where're you going?
Come here. What are you doin'?
- What are you doin'?
- Let me go! Let me go, dick-head.
Watch your mouth.
You wanna go down to juvenile hall
for a Butterfinger? Is that it?
Look around, man.
All the cops are into somethin'.
It's Christmas.
You could steal City Hall.
- Come on. Let's go. Come on.
- My bike.
- Yo, that's my bike!
- Yeah. It's Christmas.
- Hey, hey, hey! Where're you going?
Yankee Stadium's that way!
- That's my bike, you asshole!
Why don't you just run over everybody
in the whole street?
McClane, what the fuck
are we doin' back down here?
Let me ask you somethin'. What is it
that Wall Street doesn't have?
What, is this stuff catchin'?
You're talkin' in riddles.
- No, no. Stay with me. What is it
that Wall Street does not have?
- What?
Schools. And what is it
they have a shitload of?
What?
- I'll be back in a minute.
- What am I supposed to do with this?
Give it to those guys over there.
He's here.
Perhaps you could be
a little more specific.
McClane is here.
He's walking toward the bank.
And the black man
is coming toward me.
Oh, now that's a pity.
And after we've gone to all
that trouble at the stadium.
Simon, kill him.
Stop toying with him
and kill him now.
Okay. So be it.
May he rest in peace.
I'll inform Karl in the lobby.
- You pack up your team
and get out of there.
- And this one?
Officer.
Yeah, I'm, I'm, I'm afraid
I'm gonna need an answer on that issue.
- Let him go.
- Understood. Yes, sir?
John McClane says to give you this.
Wait, wait. Jesus, don't open it.
It's a bomb.
- Another?
- Yeah.
Oh, I see. Um, oh,
we'll take care of that.
We better move now. Sir,
thank you so much for your assistance.
We really appreciate it.
Thank you.
What are you doing?
- I don't want to ride with it.
- Some kid could...
Put it in the back.
Hey! Y-You, you,
leavin' this place unguarded?
I understand.
- How ya doin'?
- All right.
John McClane. NYPD.
- Are you all right?
- Yeah. It's laundry day.
What can I do for you, Lieutenant?
Has it been quiet like this
all morning here?
- Well...
- Except for that big explosion
a couple of hours ago.
I mean, have you seen anything strange
happen in the last hour or so?
No. And we've had cops in here
pretty steady since the subway thing.
Yeah.
We were just gonna make a round on
the vault floor, if you wanna tag along.
Sure. Yeah. I think I will.
Now, what do you think of this heat
this late in the year?
Eh, Indian summer, huh?
Yeah, it feels like it's gonna rain
like dogs and cats later.
- Here's one of your guys.
- Detective, uh, Otto, isn't it?
John McClane.
Hey, Mike. How ya doin'?
I keep tellin' myself I'm gonna
take the stairs just for the exercise.
And on a hot day like this.
But it seems like I always end up
riding the lift.
Hey, what was the lottery number
last night?
Any of you guys
play the lottery? No?
Ah, my wife buys me two tickets
every week.
For the last ten years,
plays the same two numbers all the time.
I said, "Honey, why don't you play
a different number?"
She goes,
"Well, those are my lucky numbers."
I got the tickets right here.
Put that fuckin' gun down!
Put that fuckin' gun down now!
Put it down!
Hello!
Anybody down here?
- Put your hands up!
Put your fuckin' hands up now!
- No, no, no!
John, no!
No! God, it's me! It's me!
- Jesus Christ,
you almost gave me a heart attack.
- You all right?
You all right?
- Yeah, yeah. It's not my blood.
- What the hell's goin' on down here?
Go take a look in there.
Hey, McClane.
Where the hell is everybody?
Simon fuckin' says!
I should've seen it comin' a mile away.
This was never about revenge.
- It's about a goddam heist.
- Wh-Wh-What was in the room?
- This.
- What is this?
- Oh, shit! Is this gold?
- Yeah, it's gold.
Damn, this is heavy!
They cleaned out a whole room of this?
- Yeah.
- You know, that would've taken
like a, a, a, a tank, or a, or a, a...
A dump truck.
Fourteen great big dump trucks.
- We almost got hit by a dump truck.
- Shit!
- Damn. Slow down! Shit!
- Put that shit down.
- No fuckin' way.
- They ain't gonna let you keep it.
- Yeah, yeah, we'll see.
- We're gonna need a car.
A car?
- You know how to hot-wire this thing?
- Of course I can. I'm an electrician.
Only problem is...
takes too fuckin' long.
- Not on the bridge!
- Down there, McClane. The FDR.
Let's go, let's go. Come on!
- Oh, shit!
- What?
- They shot the phone.
- Oh, too bad.
- Come on. What's 21 out of 42?
- I don't have a clue.
- Well, what about Yankee stadium?
- We'll get there, but that son of
a bitch is not gettin' off of Manhattan.
- Move!
- Jesus Christ!
Who do you think you are, lady,
Hillary Clinton?
- That's it! Hillary Clinton.
- What?
- The 42nd president.
- No. She'd be the 43rd president.
- All right, all right.
But who's the 21 st?
- I don't know.
- You don't know?
- No, I don't know! Do you know?
- No!
- Well?
What kind of engine does this piece
of shit have? Come on, step on it!
It's a Yugo. It's built
for economy, not speed.
- What are you doin'?
- I'm gonna get us another phone.
Wait, wait, wait!
- Hey, who was the 21 st president?
- Go fuck yourself!
- That guy was pissed.
- He'll feel better
when he looks in the back seat.
Oh, shit.
That was my gold bar!
This is McClane.
Get me Inspector Walter Cobb.
- John, where the hell are you?
- Walter, it's not a revenge.
It's a heist.
- What?
- There's gold in the Federal Reserve,
and they took a shitload of it.
- They're headed north in dump trucks.
- Have you been drinking, McClane?
No, not since this morning.
Listen. There's a line of dump trucks
northbound on the FDR at about 70th.
You gotta close the bridge and get some
helicopters over there right away.
I couldn't close a hot dog stand
right now.
I'm spread all over hell.
What about this damn bomb?
Find out who the 21 st president was.
It's got somethin' to do with this.
John! John, the 21 st what?
Walter! Shit!
Goddam cellular fuckin' phones!
- Get hold of Munson in Triborough.
- Inspector.
Tell him to close all the East River
bridges north of 59th Street.
- Lookin' for dump trucks.
- Dump trucks?
McClane says there are dump trucks
headed up the FDR loaded with gold.
Walter, they don't allow
dump trucks on the FDR!
- Connie!
- All right.
You don't want I should argue.
I won't argue,
no matter how stupid it is.
K-9, bring it around to the back.
Check out the boiler room.
Find anything, Charlie?
I could spend a week in here with
an X-ray machine and still not find it.
You don't have a week, Charlie.
You got five more minutes. Then
we're movin' up to 86th Street.
We're goin' as fast as we can.
What's up?
McClane was mentioning something
about the Federal Reserve Building.
- Isn't that right near that Wall Street
bomb site we just left?
- Yeah.
How long do you want us
to stay here?
The men at the stadium.
Stay or go?
Karl should have checked in by now.
Moment.
Come on. Come on.
Stay where you are.
McClane may still turn up.
Relax, Targo.
If he is still alive...
he won't be talking to anyone.
It's the next turn-off.
Hi. It's Elvis Duran.
You're on the air. What's up?
First of all, I just wanna tell you
what a great show you got.
- I listen to you all the time.
- Thank you. Thank you.
What do you wanna talk about?
Well, you know all those cop cars
screamin'around everywhere?
You know what they're up to?
There's a bomb in a school.
- My cousin's a cop.
- Here you go, my dear.
Somebody put a big bomb
in a school somewhere.
- Seven. Five.
- Only they don't know which one.
- 207...
- So they're searching all of them.
- Shh. Shh.
- Every school in the metropolitan area.
Holy shit.
- Doris!
- Annie?
Doris, can you get ahold
of my wife?
Turley! Half the goddam city
just called 9-1-1!
- They're gone.
- What?
- They're gone!
- Who is this guy, Houdini?
Shit! Down there! Down there!
- This thing got air bags?
- Your side does. I don't know about my...
McClane!
In the truck,
let me see the hands.
Put 'em on the door!
Don't kill me! Don't shoot me!
- You a truck driver?
- No, I'm a beautician.
Of course I'm a truck driver!
- Where are you takin' this truck?
- The aqueduct.
What are you takin' a dump truck
to the race track for?
- No, the aqueduct. The aque...
The water aqueduct!
- Aqueduct?
See? Goes from here all the way up
to the Catskill Mountains.
- What does?
- That! The water pipe!
Goes for about 60 miles.
- Hey, you the foreman?
- Yeah.
NYPD. You had any, like,
extra dump trucks come through here
in the last couple of minutes?
I'm gonna write
those fuckin' clowns up.
They better start
payin' attention to work orders,
or we're gonna kick some butt.
- Who? Who are you talkin' about?
- Ah, the dozen idiots
who tore ass up the tube!
We're not loadin' up there any more.
We're loadin' over here.
So much for bridges and helicopters.
You got a map that shows me
where this tunnel goes?
Yeah. Right here.
We run pretty much up
under the Saw Mill
till you get up to the Coffer Dam.
From there on, we've already brought
the water down from the reservoir.
- Anybody get in or outta there?
- Yeah. There's a vent shaft
every two miles.
- No. I mean with a truck.
- At the Coffer Dam.
You can get a truck in there.
You can get there on the surface.
Just follow the Saw Mill River Parkway
up there. It's about 20 miles.
All right. I'm gonna meet you
right there, all right?
Wait, wait!
Wh-What am I supposed to do?
- You're gonna go up to Yankee Stadium.
- McClane!
Go! Get outta here.
We got less than two hours.
Goddam it!
Hey! Is somethin' wrong?
480 yards of rock moved so far.
Now, that's ten times
the Hoover Dam.
Right now, there's 516 feet of rock
above our heads.
This part is phase three
of tunnel three.
Planning for it began
back in 1954...
but construction didn't begin
till June of 1970.
You know what the most interesting part
of tunnel three is?
- What's that, Jerry?
- The valves. Each one...
A big departure
from tunnels one and two.
Come on! What a hell of a place
to break down.
Hold it a minute, Jerry.
Let me have your hard hat.
- You got a jacket?
- Yeah, yeah, yeah. Here.
Wait here a minute.
Wait until he gets
alongside the door.
Hey, fellas.
Mickey O'Brian, aqueduct security.
Hey, listen. We got a report of a guy
comin' through here with eight reindeer.
Yeah, they said he was a jolly, old,
fat guy with a snowy-white beard.
Cute little red and white suit.
I'm surprised you didn't see him.
What is it with you guys
and these phones?
This'll give me somethin'.
Holy shit! Is that guy dead?
- Yes, Jerry. I'm afraid he is.
- Jesus Christ.
Yeah. I want you to get ahold
of a guy named Cobb.
Walter Cobb. C-O-B-B.
He's the head of my police unit.
Get him down here. Find him.
Tell him you were with John McClane.
- Tell him to find out
who the 21 st president was.
- Chester A. Arthur.
- What?
- Chester A. Arthur. 1881 to 1885.
Nominated vice president in 1880.
Did you know he was the collector
of customs right here in New York?
No, I didn't know that, Jerry.
Take care of yourself.
Now?
No, there's only one of them.
Yes or no?
No.
We need the other one too.
TV's got us. TV's got us.
We gotta release these traffic guys.
No. Traffic jams
we can take care of later.
- You find out what the hell
is wrong with this thing!
- Frequencies are jammed.
- What about Ricky?
- I don't know.
I can't get ahold of him.
- But, Walter, Federal Reserve.
- Yeah?
Biggest gold storage
in the world.
You get a unit back down there.
Find Ricky. Find out what the hell
is goin' on.
- Walter!
- Yeah?
You gotta hear this.
Christ, I thought we were
going in the back way.
This is the back way, Walter.
In half an hour, you're gonna have
a riot at every school in this city.
We'll start at the top floor.
Put 20 men on each floor.
Send the other 50 men
down to the basement with us.
- What about McClane?
- Not a word. I'm gettin' nothin'.
- Busy signals.
- Westchester's probably worse
than we are.
This is kinda puttin' all our eggs
in one basket, isn't it?
- I mean, what if McClane's wrong?
- Walter?
- Yeah?
This is Principal Martinez.
Principal Martinez, Inspector Cobb.
- How do you do, Inspector?
- How do you do, Principal Martinez?
I don't want to alarm your children.
I wonder if you could move them all
into the auditorium and keep them calm.
We are coming to the dam.
You can call the rear guard.
Rear guard, you can close up now.
We've reached the dam.
You can come up now.
Nils, you can close in now.
- Nils!
- Attention, attention. Nils is dead.
I repeat, Nils is dead, fuck-head.
So is his pal.
And those four guys
from the East German all-stars...
your boys down at the bank...
they're gonna be a little late.
John.
In the back of the truck you're driving,
there's $13 billion worth
in gold bullion.
- I wonder, would a deal
be out of the question?
- Yeah, I got a deal for ya.
Crawl out from under that rock
you're hidin' under, and I'll drive
this truck up your ass.
How colourful.
I told you not to toy with him.
Thank you. That's very helpful.
You've jeopardized the mission
and the contract.
We are vulnerable
till we reach the ship.
I'm going to put an end to this.
Stop!
Targo! Targo!
Here! Come here!
- We blow the dam.
- What?
We drown him.
Walter!
Take a look at this. The janitor said
this one was delivered this morning.
About 10:30, right?
Not hooked up.
- Yeah?
- Okay. Now take a look at the front.
We drill the hinges.
Get everybody out.
McClane!
- McClane!
- Where are you?
Over here!
You got a hell of a way
of flaggin' somebody down!
- You all right?
- Did you go to Yankee Stadium?
- Yeah! There's nobody there!
- You didn't see nobody?
- No!
- Nobody was followin' you?
I'm tellin' you.
He's jerkin' us around.
Oh, shit! Jesus!
Come on! Come on!
"Oh, no! I didn't see nobody.
Nobody's following us."
Go, go, go!
It's not rigged. Pull it.
Well, I'd say you could
call off your search.
- Can you stop it?
- I shouldn't even touch it.
Who knows what kind of booby traps
this thing's got. What about the code?
No word.
- When do we evacuate?
- Simon says he sees one kid
leave the building, boom!
Fine. There's a chance
that somebody's still watchin',
but we can't stand here...
with our thumb up our ass waitin'
for this freakin' thing to blow up!
Okay.
- Shit! Shit!
- Get your head down!
Come on, Zeus, hold it steady!
Hold it steady!
- Go! Go!
- Outta the way!
Go around him!
- I found out who's the 21 st president.
- Who?
Some guy named Arthur.
- Chester A. Arthur?
- Chester A. Arthur. That's it. Yeah.
- Chester A. Arthur Elementary School?
- Yeah. That's it.
Gently down the stream
Merrily, merrily, merrily, merrily
- Life is but a dream
- Merrily, merrily, merrily, merrily
- Row, row, row your boat
- Gently down the stream
- Life is but a dream
- Merrily, merrily, merrily, merrily
- Row, row, row your boat
- Gently down the stream
- Merrily, merrily, merrily...
- Gently down the...
- Hi, kids!
I know you usually have assembly
on Fridays, but today is special.
Mr Lambert here
is from the fire department...
and today he wants us to practice
a brand-new fire drill.
So, I want you to divide in half,
and I want half of you to go over here...
- teachers will help them...
and line up against the wall.
- Open the door.
The other half will go in this
direction. Please do it very quietly
and very quickly.
All right? Everybody up, please.
Teachers, please help them.
Fire drill, my ass.
That guy ain't from the fire department.
Maybe it's 'cause of the radio.
You mean, like, they're after us? Nah.
- Tony squealed on us.
- No, he didn't.
- Come on.
- Well, where you goin'?
- Let me drive! Let me drive!
- Go, go, go!
Goddam it!
Why the hell didn't you tell me before?
Of course he put the bomb up
in that school.
- Why would he do that?
- Make sure he got
your complete attention.
- Jesus! Jesus!
- Find the fuse panel.
- What?
- The fuse panel.
- Where's the fuse panel to this car?
- It's right here! It's right here!
- Pull out the anti-lock brakes fuse.
- Shit, I don't know which one it is.
Well, then yank 'em all out then.
- There.
- Put your head down.
Put your head fuckin' down.
This is gonna be really bad.
Listen to me.
Hang the fuck on, all right?
- Oh! Oh! What the fuck happened?
- You got a triple-A card?
- Keep moving. Keep moving.
- Excuse me.
I got the janitors making a last sweep
of the building right now.
Thank you, Miss Martinez.
Come on.
All right, five stud,
three nines, one...
Stay down! Stay low!
Oh, man!
- What the fuck are you doin'?
- Interrogatin' him.
Well, what's he gonna tell you,
"I'm dead"?
Well, I ain't gonna know
till I ask him, am I?
Go around and see if there's
any aspirins in that glove box.
No way. You do it.
Ten quarters.
The guy in the dump truck
had ten quarters. Exactly ten quarters.
Well, maybe they were makin'
long distance phone calls.
No. For the bridge.
- What?
- It's for the toll on the bridge.
There! There! Down on the wharf.
Dump trucks.
Right there! Right there!
Christ, they got it loaded
on a ship already.
Shit! How about the Coast Guard?
- It'd take 'em an hour to get here.
- Shit!
Shit! We can jump.
- What?
- We can jump.
Outta your fuckin' mind!
It's 100 feet down to the deck!
- But not to the crane, it isn't.
- The cables would cut you in half.
- I can make it.
- Bullshit. Get down.
Get down. Look in the back
of that car for some gloves.
Six booby traps, four dead ends...
And a partridge in a pear tree
Okay, honey.
Let's dance.
We're gonna have sort of a race.
So when I say go, I want you all
to run like crazy.
All of you. You follow
the police officer and the fireman.
You guys are my front runners, okay?
Walter, think we're cuttin' this
a little thin?
No, Joe. We're gonna wait.
McClane still may get the code.
- Line me up with that crane!
- There. There. Right there. Right there.
- All right.
I see it now. I see it.
- Right there. You're okay.
- Shit. This is gonna take a miracle.
- Keep your fingers crossed.
Swing it. Swing it.
Come on. Come on. You almost got it.
Almost. Almost. Yeah! All right.
Where are you goin'?
What, are you in a hurry?
I'm goin' first this time,
all right?
We have the intercom rigged, sir.
Walter, the kids may be fine,
but you wait much longer and
I'm gonna pee in my pants.
We're gonna wait, Connie.
Six more minutes.
- Yo, McClane.
- What?
Down there.
Oh, shit. Go, go, man!
Go, go, go!
Oh, boy.
Am I glad you talked me
outta jumpin'.
Fuck.
Get his feet.
There's something you should see.
Later.
- It's important.
- Later.
Now.
This was in a container.
We go find Simon
and drag him to the ship-to-shore radio
and beat that fuckin' code out of him.
- Here. Take this.
- How's it work?
- You don't know how to shoot a gun?
- Look, all brothers don't know how
to shoot guns, you racist motherfucker.
Sue me. Just yank back on that
and pull the trigger. That's it.
- That's it?
- That's it. Just don't shoot yourself.
Hey, don't be no hero.
You find him, you come get me.
Hey, Katya!
Stupid. Stupid.
- You have the autopilot set?
- Yes, sir.
Good.
Don't fuckin' move.
Oh, the Samaritan.
- Gimme the goddam code.
- Code?
You mean for the school.
I'm sorry. I can't do that.
You call in that code right now...
or I blow your sick ass
into the next world.
If that's what you gotta do.
- You gotta take the safety catch off.
- Oh, goddam!
See. That works.
Now where's McClane?
What was that?
He said, "Don't shoot."
Okay, Charlie. We're gonna
have to go with the evacuation.
- We're gonna go.
- All right. You heard the man.
Let's go! Let's go!
- Move! Move! Move!
- We're gonna go!
- Let's go, men!
- On my mark.
Five, four, three, two, one, go!
- Let's go! Go!
Go! Go! Go! Go! Go! Go!
Let's do it!
Okay, gang. Let's go!
Go! Go! Go! Hip-hop! Hip-hop!
Come on. Everybody! Let's go!
- Run! Run! Run! Run! Run! Run!
- Keep moving.
- We're gonna win! We're gonna win!
- Go! Go! Go! Go! Go! Go!
Keep moving!
To your left! To your left!
What are they doin'?
Yo, where you goin'?
- Hey, where you goin'?
- What's goin' on?
I see you all day, little man.
Policeman.
And you don't go away.
Yeah, I'm that fuckin'
Energizer bunny.
Where are you going now, huh?
Going to arrest me, "bunny"?
No.
I don't think
I'm gonna arrest you.
I'm gonna fuckin'...
I knew it was bullshit.
There's nobody watchin'.
Time to get Charlie out.
- Let's move, Charles. Time's up.
- Give me another 30 seconds.
Takes a minute-15
if you're a kid, Charlie.
And last I looked, you weren't too light
on your feet. Now move!
- Up here!
- Help us!
- Oh, my God!
- Come on!
- Look over here!
- Christ, get 'em outta there!
- Rooms are locked!
- The rooms are locked!
- Get outta the way!
Hey! Any one marked four!
What's goin' on, Walter?
We still have kids
in the building.
- I'm stayin'.
- No, Charlie. Get outta there.
You ever see that show
called The Addams Family?
They got a motherfucker on there
called Lurch.
You don't think I'm gonna let you
get to that gun, do you?
Fuck!
Help! Help! Help!
Four! Fuck it!
Get outta the way!
- Where are they, Walter?
- Still in.
No guts, no glory.
If we get to the roof,
we can jump to the next building!
- Shit!
- Outta the way.
Okay. Come on.
Get him up here. Get him up here!
Come on! Come on!
Mayday, mayday. Bridgeport Coast Guard.
Bridgeport Coast Guard, come in.
Come on, kids.
- Shit, it's too far!
- Over here. Down.
No guts, no glory.
There's a big black-and-white fuckin'
boat in the middle of the harbour.
- Please stay on the line.
- Yeah, sure. I'll stay on the line.
Pancake syrup?
Hello, John McClane.
There was never any bomb
in the school, was there?
Of course not.
I'm a soldier, not a monster...
even though I sometimes work
for monsters.
No. The real bomb is on this ship.
Coast Guard.
I was tellin' 'em where the boat was.
Game over, huh?
Not quite over.
Bridgeport Coast Guard.
Come in, please.
They put you on hold?
She told me to stay on the line.
- Oh, God, I love this country.
- You know, your brother was an asshole.
- You know, he really was an asshole.
- He was... He was an asshole.
You, you got his number, yeah?
Yeah, okay.
Forgive me.
Would you help Mr McClane below?
Careful now.
Now, do you have the communique?
Bridgeport radio,
come in, please. Bridgeport.
- Coast Guard.
- Are you there, dear?
- Yes, we're here.
- Do you have the ability
to record a message?
- Yes.
- Then please begin now.
Right.
This is a communique
from the CRF.
For too long, the West has conspired
to steal the wealth of the world...
consigning the balance of humanity
to economic starvation.
Today, we will level
the playing field.
In a few minutes, the contents
of the Federal Reserve Bank...
the gold your economies
are built on...
will be redistributed by explosive...
across the bottom
of the Long Island Sound.
If you are not in gridlock,
I invite you to come and watch.
- You're gonna blow it all up?
- That's the idea.
There are some gentlemen
in the Middle East...
who seem to think that they'll make
a great deal of money.
See the men safely off the ship, and
I'll see you in the port-side launch.
The hell's all this
got to do with killin' McClane?
Life has its little bonuses.
Didn't I hear you say
you didn't even like your brother?
There's a difference, you know,
between not liking one's brother...
and not caring when some dumb Irish
flatfoot drops him out of a window.
Hey, I didn't even know
that motherfucker!
Yes, and I never invited you
aboard this ship.
No riddle is gonna stop
this motherfucker?
No code, no riddle,
no fancy little countdown.
Hey, fuck-head.
Yeah, you. Fuck-head.
There's just one thing
I gotta know.
You got any aspirins? I've had
a bad fuckin' headache all day long.
Must be your lucky day.
Keep the bottle.
Where is the gold?
He's betrayed us.
The containers
are filled with that.
If I hadn't have saved your fuckin' ass,
I wouldn't be sittin' here with you...
about to blow up with $100 billion
in fuckin' gold!
Yeah, well, I got some bad news.
You're only gonna blow up with me.
- What?
- There's no gold on this boat.
- How do you know that?
- 'Cause I know the man.
I know the family.
The only thing better than blowin' up
$100 billion worth of gold is makin'
people think you did.
- Yeah? Well, where is it?
- I don't know. He must have switched it
back on the dock somewhere.
Oh, yeah. That's supposed
to make me feel better?
No. You're wrong about the other thing,
though. You're not gonna die.
Yeah? You know
some cop trick about handcuffs
that's gonna get us outta this?
Yeah. Use a key.
- You know how to pick this lock?
- Is this some black shit again?
Will you stop with that racial shit?
Are you a fuckin' locksmith or not?
Yeah, yeah, yeah. I can do it
if I had somethin' to do it with.
- How about a splinter
of that cable I slid down?
- That might work.
- Hold on.
- Fuck are you doin'?
Oh, fuck! Shit!
How's that? That big enough?
Shit. Yeah.
Yeah, that might work.
All right. Then I'm gonna drop it
in your hands. Cup your hands.
Don't drop this motherfucker,
all right?
- Get, get it right. Come on. One...
- You ready? Ready?
Two... Spit it.
- Yeah! Get it?
- Come on. Come on. Move your hands.
All right. Okay.
Damn, McClane. You know,
I was just startin' to like you.
- Yeah? Well, don't. I'm an asshole.
- What are you talkin' about now?
- I lied to you, Zeus.
- About what?
You remember I said
Weiss found that bomb up in Harlem?
- Yeah.
- They found it down in Chinatown.
Oh, now that's low...
even for a white motherfucker like you.
I told you I was an asshole.
What the fuck was that?
I don't know.
Look, it was the only way
I could get you to come with me.
You got a wife, McClane?
- Yeah.
- I'm surprised anybody'd stay with you
long enough to be married.
Yeah. Well, she didn't stick around
too long. We're sorta separated.
What the fuck is "sorta separated"?
Well, she was in LA,
I was in New York.
Had a fight on the phone. She hung up.
I didn't call her back.
- How long ago was that?
- About a year ago now.
About a yea...
What the fuck
are you laughin' about?
You threw away your marriage
because you were too fuckin' stupid
to pick up the phone?
What, you think that's funny, huh?
You laugh at other people's misfortunes?
I bet you blame that shit
on your wife too, right?
Well, my wife
is a very stubborn woman, yes.
You better stop fuckin' laughin'
and undo these cuffs.
I'm almost there!
There! How's that for concentration?
Oh, shit!
- What?
- Fuck! I dropped the thing!
- Dropped the fucking thing?
- Goddam it!
- Shit! Where is it? Where did it go?
- Find it. Find it, all right?
I don't fuckin' see it.
What the fuck is that?
I think I made it mad.
Just go, McClane.
Get the fuck out of here.
- Gotta fuckin' do somethin'!
- Goddam it, McClane! Listen to me!
Just go.
Have a hard enough time gettin' through
the day without havin' your death
on my conscience, man.
- Shut the fuck up and think, all right?
- Okay, okay.
- Tools. Tools. Check the engine room.
- There's no time!
- What the hell's it doin' now?
- It's mixin'.
Shit!
- What the hell are you doin'?
- Get ready. Lean forward.
- What?
- Lean forward, goddam it!
What? The fuck you doin'?
Now it's gonna go fast.
Lean forward.
- Oh, no, no!
- Lean forward! Get ready!
Move your hands!
Damn! Motherfuckin' shit!
- Come on. Let's go!
- Oh, goddam! Goddam!
- Come on! Come on!
- Oh, fuck! My leg! Ow!
Get upstairs! Come on!
Go! Go! Go! Go! Go! Go! Get upstairs!
Oh, shit! Ow! Damn it! My foot!
- Let's go! Let's go!
- Down there at the back of the boat.
Come on!
- No, damn it!
- Run, goddam it!
- I am, you...
- Come on!
- All right? Watch! Watch! Watch!
- Yeah.
Let's go! Down here!
The back of the...
How's he doin'?
I got shot in the leg.
How do ya think I'm doin'?
- He's gonna be just fine.
- How about you?
I'm all right.
Did ya get Ricky out of there?
Yeah, they found him.
- Are you gonna be all right?
- Got a bad headache.
- Think they're mad at me?
- I wouldn't worry about them.
They'll get to you eventually,
but right now they're busy with
this salvage operation, I guess.
No! Dre-Dredges! Dredges!
They're just wastin' their time.
There's no gold out there.
- What do you mean?
- He took it with him.
- He beat me.
- John, he beat all of us.
- He wasn't playin' against you.
- Fuck that, McClane.
You're still alive, aren't ya?
- Well, aren't ya?
- Yeah.
So he lost. Lambert.
Would you give him a quarter?
Asshole.
- Take it easy.
- I got him.
- That's it.
- Easy.
- Yeah, this is collect from John.
Thanks, guys. Appreciate this.
Yeah, uh, Carmine, just tell him
you'll accept the charges.
Son of a bitch had aspirin.
Yeah, it's John.
Yeah, I'm hangin' in there.
Is Holly there?
Yeah, I'll hold on.
Zeus, hold up!
John? John? John?
Goddam it, you son of a...
Yesterday...
Yesterday we were an army
with no country.
Tomorrow, we have to decide...
which country we want to buy.
And remember,
this is all due...
to the g-g-g-g-g-g-g-g-gullibility
of the New York Police Department.
To fallen comrades.
Leutnant, take over.
All right. Listen up!
First squad...
you muster up in half an hour
in the school bus!
You'll be the lacrosse team!
The plane's in Nova Scotia.
We can leave in twenty minutes.
No rush.
And, Jurgen,
you'll be the Padre!
Padre?
Lights! Douse those lights!
Hey, dick-head!
Did I come at a bad time?
I think
she's pissed at you, McClane!
Go! Go!
He's under us right now. Come on
back around. Come on back around.
- That's right. Run, motherfuckers.
- Zeus, what've we got on your side?
Look like roaches
with the lights comin' on.
- Are we going to Nova Scotia?
- You go with the trucks!
I have something personal
to finish.
Let's go to work!
Come on! Move it!
That's right. Run, motherfuckers!
The exterminators are here!
What the fuck? Oh, shit!
What the fuck is this smoke back here?
We got a chopper behind us.
You got a gun on board?
What is this?
Can't see a goddam thing. Hold it
still. I can't see a goddam thing.
- Oh, shit!
What do you mean, "Oh, shit"?
All right. Hang on. Hang on.
We're goin' down.
Between those high tension wires?
See this wire?
Hey, McClane! What the fuck?
Hey, we got smoke! We got fuckin' smoke
and shit flyin' on me here!
- Truck! Truck!
- Hold on. Here we go!
Come on. We gotta get outta here! He's
gonna start shootin' at us any second!
- Get him out of here.
- Shit! The belt's stuck!
I can't get it off!
Look out! Here he comes!
Can't get out, McClane!
- Get him outta here.
- Where're you goin'?
I'm gonna try
and get his attention.
Oh, shit! It just keeps
gettin' better and better.
I had no idea Canada
could be this much fun.
Just give me somethin' to shoot at.
Come on, hotshot.
Show me that smilin' face.
Say hello to your brother.
Get outta here!
Yippee-ki-ay, motherfucker.
- Looks like you got his attention.
- Yeah. It looks like it.
- Think we should call a fire truck?
- Aw, fuck 'em. Let 'em cook.
- Oh, shit!
- What?
What?
- I left Holly hangin' on hold.
- Aw, call her back.
I don't know.
She's gonna be pissed.
She'll get over it.
I don't know, Zeus.
Like I said...
she's a very stubborn woman.
Well, she'd have to be
to stay married to you.