Subtitles downloaded from www.OpenSubtitles.org
You don't like flyin', do you?
What gives you that idea?
You wanna know the secret
to surviving air travel?
After you get where you're going,
take off your shoes and your socks.
Then you walk around on the rug barefoot
and make fists with your toes.
Fists with your toes?
I know, I know. It sounds crazy.
Trust me. I've been doin' it
for nine years.
Yes, sir. Better than a shower
and a hot cup of coffee.
Okay.
It's okay.
I'm a cop.
Trust me. I've been
doin' this for 11 years.
On behalf of your captain and crew...
we'd like to welcome you
to Los Angeles.
Have a very Merry Christmas.
Flight 247 to Tucson now boarding at Gate 14.
Flight 247 to Tucson
now boarding at Gate 14.
Mr. Edward Machowski,
please report to the white courtesy phone.
Ah.
How do you do?
Ladies and gentlemen!
I want to congratulate
each and every one of you...
for making this one of the greatest years
in the history of the Nakatomi Corporation.
On behalf of the chief executive officer,
Mr. Ozu, and the board of directors...
we thank you, one and all, and wish you
a Merry Christmas and a happy New Year!
Hey, Holly, what about
dinner tonight, huh?
Harry, it's Christmas Eve.
Families, stockings.
Chestnuts.
Rudolph and Frosty.
Any of these things ring a bell?
Actually, I was thinkin' more of
mulled wine, a nice aged Brie...
and a roaring fireplace.
You know what I'm sayin'?
Ginny, it's 5:40. Go join the party.
Have some champagne.
You're makin' me feel
like Ebenezer Scrooge.
Thanks a lot, Ms. Gennero.
Do you think the baby can handle a little sip?
That baby's ready to tend bar.
Last chance.
Bye.
McClane residence.
Lucy McClane speaking.
Hello, Lucy McClane.
This is your mother speaking.
Mommy! When are you coming home?
Pretty soon. Pretty soon.
You'll be in bed when I get there though.
Let me talk to Paulina, okay, hon?
And no snoopin' around the house
looking for presents.
Is Daddy coming home with you?
Well, we'll see what
Santa and Mommy can do, okay?
Put Paulina on.
Bye, honey.
Paulina!
Hola, Mrs. Holly.
Um, did Mr. McClane call?
No, Mrs. Holly.
No telefonó.
Well, he probably just didn't
have time before his flight.
Um, it might be a good idea
to make up the spare bedroom just in case.
Sí, Mrs. Holly.
I do that already.
What would I do
without you, Paulina?
California.
Excuse me.
Hey, I'm John McClane.
Argyle. I'm your limo driver.
Nice bear.
Okay, Argyle.
What do we do now?
I was, uh, hopin' you could tell me.
It's my first time drivin' a limo.
Oh, that's okay. It's my
first time ridin' in one.
Relax. We got everything
in this mug, man.
Look at this -  CD, C.B., TV...
telephone, full bar, VHS.
if your friend's hot to trot,
I know a few mama bears we can hook up with.
- Or is he married?
- He's married.
Okay.
Oh, sorry about that.
It's the girl's day off.
I didn't know you were
gonna sit up front.
So, uh, your lady live out here?
About the past six months.
Meaning you still live in New York.
- You always ask this many questions, Argyle?
Sorry, man. I used to drive a cab, and, uh,
people would expect a little chitchat.
- So, you divorced?
- Just drive the car, man.
Hey, come on. You divorced?
You separated? She beat you up?
He had a good job.
Turned into a great career.
Ah, that meant she had to move here.
You're very fast, Argyle.
So why didn't you come?
Well, why didn't you come
with her, man? What's up?
'Cause I'm a New York cop.
l got a six-month backlog of New York
scumbags I'm still trying to put behind bars.
I can't just pick up
and go that easy.
In other words, you thought
she wasn't gonna make it out here...
and she'd come crawling
on back to you...
so why bother to pack, right?
Like I said,
you're very fast, Argyle.
You mind if we hear some tunes?
Hey, that'll work.
Don't you got any Christmas music?
This is Christmas music.
So your lady sees you, you run
into each other's arms, the music comes up...
and you live happily
ever after, right?
I can live with that.
So if it doesn't work out, man,
you got a place to stay?
- I'll find a place.
- I tell you what.
I'm gonna pull in
the parking garage and I'll wait.
You score, you give me a call
on the car phone.
I'll take your bags to the desk.
You strike out,
I'll get you a hotel.
You're all right, Argyle.
Just remember that
when you sign for the tip.
Hi.
- Good evening.
- I'm here to see Holly McClane.
Just type it in there.
Cute toy.
Yeah. You have to take a leak,
it'll even help you find your zipper.
Christ.
13th floor.
The party. They're the only ones
left in the building.
Take the express elevator.
Get off where you hear the noise.
Thanks.
- Champagne, sir?
- Yeah. Thanks.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Hey! Merry Christmas!
Jesus.
Fuckin' California.
I couldn't agree with you more.
Why don't I talk to him right now?
Hi. I'm looking for, uh -
- Holly Gennero.
- Yeah.
- Then you must be John McClane. Joe Takagi.
- Hi.
- How was your ride in?
- Nice.
- l have you to thank for that?
- It seemed the least we could do.
It's quite a place you have here.
It will be
if we ever get it finished.
There are still several
floors under construction.
Holly went to the vault room to fax some
documents. She should be back any minute.
In the meanwhile,
her office is right back here.
Ellis.
l was just makin' a call,
and this was, uh, the nearest phone.
I want you to meet
John McClane, Holly's husband.
Holly's policeman. Ellis is in charge
of international development.
Heard a heck of a lot about you.
Missed some.
Uh, could I get you anything?
Food, cake, uh, some watered-down champagne?
No, thank you.
I'm fine.
You throw quite a party.
l didn't realize they
celebrated Christmas in Japan.
Hey, we're flexible. Pearl Harbor didn't
work out, so we got you with tape decks.
Actually, it's kind of sort of a double
celebration. We, uh, closed a pretty big deal today.
And a lot of it was due to Holly.
- Am I right, Jo-Jo?
- Go ahead without me.
I'll be about 4 minutes.
John.
Have you met everyone?
No, we've been sticking him
with spears.
of course he has.
She was made for the business.
Tough as nails.
- Yeah.
- I was hoping you made that flight.
Show him the watch.
- Later.
- Well, go on. Show him.
What, are you embarrassed?
It's just a small token
of appreciation for all her hard work.
It's a Rolex.
I'm sure I'll see it later.
Is there a place
where l could wash up?
Sure.
You'll have to forgive Ellis.
He gets very depressed this time of year.
He thought he was
God's greatest gift, you know?
Yeah, l know the type.
I think he's got his eye on you.
It's okay. I have my eye
on his private bathroom.
Where you staying?
Things happened so fast, I didn't get a chance
to ask you on the phone.
- Cappy Roberts retired out here.
- Oh, yeah?
- Told me I could bunk in with him.
- Cappy retired, huh?
- Where's he live?
- "Ramona."
Pomona.
- Huh?
- Pomona.
- Yeah.
God, you'll be in the car
half the time.
Why don't we make it easy?
I have a spare bedroom.
I mean, it's not huge
or anything, but...
the kids would love
to have you at the house.
They would, huh?
I would too.
Oh! Ooh!
Sorry.
I missed you.
I guess you didn't miss
my name, though, huh?
Except maybe when
you're signing checks?
Since when did you
start using "Ms. Gennero"?
This is a Japanese company.
They figure a married woman's got one foot -
You are a married woman, Holly.
You're married to me.
Are we gonna have this conversation again?
We did this in July.
- We never finished this conversation in July.
- I had an opportunity.
- l had to take it.
- Right. No matter what the consequences...
no matter what it did to our marriage,
you had to.
It didn't do anything except maybe change
your idea of what our marriage should be.
I don't think you have a clue what my idea
of our marriage should be.
- I know exactly what your idea
Ms. Gennero, I -
- Excuse me.
- Hi.
Um, Mr. Takagi is looking for you.
- He- He wants you to say something to the troops.
- Thank you.
Speech time.
Be back in a few minutes.
That's great, John.
Good job.
Very mature.
So Kareem rebounds, right?
Feeds Worthy on the break.
Over to A.C., to Magic,
then back to Worthy, right?
Boom! Two points.
We're in.
Left.
Right, and again left.
Son of a bitch.
Fists with your toes.
Yeah, Argyle.
- Hey, Mac! How's it goin' up there?
- Oh, all right. Where are you?
I'm kickin' it in the garage.
What's the word with you and your lady, man?
Uh, the vote's not in yet.
- Hey Brother.
- Just a moment.
- No, no ... not yet, just wait ...
Argyle?
Mac, you there? Hello?
You know the number.
Use it!
Stay calm. Everything's gonna be fine.
Everything's gonna be fine.
Shit!
Think. Think.
Ladies and gentlemen.
"Due to the Nakatomi
Corporation's legacy of greed around the globe...
"they're about to be taught a lesson
in the real use of power.
You will be witnesses."
Now...
where is Mr. Takagi?
Joseph Yoshinobu Takagi.
Born, Kyoto, 1937.
Don't move.
Family emigrated
to San Pedro, California, 1939.
Interned at Manzanar, 1942 to '43.
Scholarship student,
University of California...
1955.
Law degree, Stanford, 1962.
M.B.A., Harvard, 1970.
President, Nakatomi Trading.
Vice Chairman,
Nakatomi Investment Group.
Enough.
And father of five.
I am Takagi.
How do you do?
It's a pleasure to meet you.
Computers. 32, construction.
33, computers.
Nice suit.
John Philips, London.
I have two myself.
Rumor has it Arafat buys his there.
- In there?
- On the left. On the left.
"And when Alexander saw the
breadth of his domain, he wept...
for there were no more
worlds to conquer."
Benefits of a classical education.
Oh, that's beautiful.
I always enjoyed to make models
when I was a boy.
The exactness, the attention
to every conceivable detail.
It's beautiful.
Is this what this is all about?
Our project in Indonesia?
Contrary to what you people may think...
we're going to develop that region,
not exploit it.
I believe you.
I read the article in Forbes.
Mr. Takagi.
I could talk about industrialization
and men's fashions all day...
but I'm afraid work must intrude...
and my associate, Theo,
has some questions for you.
Sort of fill-in-the-blanks
questions, actually.
I don't have that code.
You broke in here
to access our computer?
Any information you could get, when they
wake up in Tokyo in the morning, they'll change it.
You won't be able to blackmail
our executives, threaten our profit -
Sit down!
Mr. Takagi, I'm really
not interested in your computer.
But I need the code key
because I am interested...
in the $640 million
in negotiable bearer bonds...
that you have locked in your vault.
And the computer controls the vault.
You want money?
What kind of terrorists are you?
Who said we were terrorists?
Mr. Takagi, I sympathize
with your reluctance...
but I'm sure you realize you're not dealing
with anything significant here.
It's not as if it's
the education of your children.
The bonds represent, at most...
10 days operating capital
for your parent organization.
It's really no more than
a temporary inconvenience.
Now...
the code, please.
It's useless to you.
There are seven safeguards on our vault,
and the code key is only one of them.
- You'll never get it open.
- Then there's no reason not to tell it to us.
I told you.
It's not over yet.
That's a very nice suit, Mr. Takagi.
It would be a shame to ruin it.
I'm going to count to three.
There will not be a four.
Give me the code.
One.
Two.
- Three.
- I don't know it, I'm telling you.
Get on a jet to Tokyo
and ask the chairman.
I'm telling you, you're just gonna
have to kill me.
Okay.
We'll do it the hard way.
Tony, see if you can dispose of that.
Karl, you'd better go and check on Heinrich's
work up on the machine floor.
Nothing.
See to Heinrich.
Now, you can break the code?
You didn't bring me along
for my charming personality.
Argyle, tell me you heard the shots
and you're callin' the police right now.
Of course I'm still comin' by later.
Sweetheart, have l ever lied to you?
My boss? He thinks
I'm on my way to Vegas.
Uli, get up on the pipes.
Marco, you go through here.
I'll throw you the cord.
Yeah.
Hans, we're on the roof.
Here.
Uli!
Thirty minutes to break the code.
Two hours - two and a half hours...
for the five mechanicals,
at the minimum.
The seventh lock, however,
is out of my hands.
- I'm sorry.
- The 7th lock.
The electromagnetic seal. You do understand
the circuits cannot be cut locally.
Trust me.
Why the fuck didn't you
stop 'em, John?
'Cause then you'd be
dead too, asshole.
Think, goddamn it.
Think!
We've got a fire alarm.
Call 911.
Give them the guard's name, the building code
number and cancel the alarm.
Then disable the system.
Eddie, on what floor
did the alarm go off?
Now? Should we go?
Nein.
Yes. Oh, baby,
come to papa. Come on.
Ah!
Baby. Come on, baby.
Come on, baby.
Come to papa.
I'll kiss your fuckin' dalmatian.
Oh, you stupid motherfuckers!
No! No!
Turn the fuckin' truck around!
The fire has been
called off, my friend.
No one is coming to help you.
You might as well come out
and join the others.
I promise l won't hurt you.
Drop it, dickhead.
It's the police.
- You won't hurt me.
- Oh, yeah? Why not?
Because you're a policeman.
There are rules for policemen.
Yeah. That's what
my captain keeps tellin' me.
Drop that, motherfucker!
I'll fuckin' kill you!
Come on! Come on!
I'll fuckin' rip your head off?
You bet your ass I wish to proceed.
Nine million terrorists in the world, and I gotta
kill one with feet smaller than my sister.
I wanted this to be professional, efficient,
adult, cooperative.
Not a lot to ask. Alas, your Mr. Takagi
did not see it that way...
so he won't bejoining us
for the rest of his life.
So we can go any way you want us.
You can walk out of here
or be carried out.
But have no illusions.
We are in charge.
So, decide now, each of you.
And, please remember...
we have left nothing to chance.
Get them back!
"Now I have a machine gun.
Ho-ho-ho."
A security guard we missed?
They're usually tired old policemen
growing fat on a pension.
No, no.
This is something else.
Oh, they're gonna kill us!
What did I tell you?
- We have to do something, Hans.
- Yes, we do.
We have to tell Karl his brother is dead.
Tell him to come down.
- Karl?
- Yeah?
Karl, come down right away!
Franco, you and Fritz take
the body upstairs and out of sight.
I don't want the hostages
to think too much.
... come down right now ... quickly ...
- I want blood!
- You'll have it.
But let Heinrich plant the detonators
and Theo prepare the vault.
After we call the police,
they'll waste hours trying to negotiate...
and then you can tear the building apart
looking for this man.
But until then,
we do not alter the plan.
And if he alters it?
What do ya think?
Something's wrong.
Cops?
John.
John? Aw, Christ.
He could fuck this whole thing up.
What does he think he's doin'?
- His job.
- Bullshit.
His job's 3,000 miles away.
Without him, we still have a chance.
We might be able to get outta here.
Tell that to Takagi.
Mayday! Mayday!
Anyone copying? Channel 9.
Terrorists have seized
the Nakatomi building...
and are holding at least
30 people hostage.
I repeat, unknown number
of terrorists, six or more...
armed with automatic weapons
at Nakatomi Plaza, Century City.
- Where's the best place to transmit?
- Somebody answer me, goddamn it!
The roof! Go! Go!
It's the same address as that fire signal.
I'll handle it.
Attention, whoever you are. This channel's
reserved for emergency calls only.
No fuckin' shit, lady.
Do I sound like I'm orderin' a pizza?
No one kills him but me.
They have already
killed one hostage.
They are fortifying their positions
while you're jerkin' me off on the radio!
Now, send a police backup A.S.A.P.!
Sir, I've already told you,
this is a reserved channel.
If this is an emergency call,
dial 911on your telephone.
Otherwise, I'll have to report
this as an F.C.C. violation.
Fine, report me!
Come the fuck down here and arrest me!
Just send the police now!
Ow!
Whoa!
See if there's a black-and-white
that can do a drive-by.
I thought you guys
just ate doughnuts.
They're for my wife.
Yeah.
- She's pregnant.
- Yeah.
Bag it.
Big time.
Thanks.
Dispatch to 8-Lincoln-30, over.
This is 8-Lincoln-30.
Come on in, over.
Investigate a code 2
at Nakatomi Plaza, Century City.
8-Lincoln-30 to Dispatch.
I'm on my way.
Christ!
Girls.
... in the attic ...
Shit. Where the fuck is it?
Oh, my God.
- Hans, we have a machine gun ...
- Have you found him?
- ... he's in the furnace area of the roof ...
- He's in the furnace area of the roof ...
- Where is Karl?
- He's in the elevator shaft.
- Did you hear that?
Perfect. The elevators are
locked off. He can't escape.
Just shut him in and come back down.
Oh, fuck.
Karl, the police are probably
on their way already. Karl!
Christ.
I can stall them,
but not if they hear gunshots.
lf you lock him in, he'll be neutralized
"Come out to the coast.
We'll get together, have a few laughs."
Now l know what
a TV dinner feels like.
Karl, come!
Police! Hurry ...
It's about time.
No signs of disturbance, Dispatch.
8-L-30, roger. Possible crank call.
Check the area again and confirm.
Who's driving this car,
Stevie Wonder?
I do see a guard inside.
I'm gonna go in for a closer look.
8-L-30, Roger. Use caution.
- Eddie?
- I had a feeling you'd be callin'.
Good evenin', officer.
What can I do for you?
- How many are there?
- Just one man.
- Someone is "jumping the gun".
We had that false alarm, you know?
Ask me, that god-damn computer
sent you out on another wild goose chase.
They've been chasing bugs
in this system ever since they installed it.
- Notre Dame on top of USC.
- Aw, shit!
Come on. l got 50 bucks
bet on them assholes.
Come on. Come on.
Where's the fucking cavalry?
He's on the 34th floor. Go, hurry.
It was good for 52 yards.
You don't mind if I take
a look around, do you?
No, help yourself.
Seven to nothing, Notre Dame.
The Irish driving 74 yards in eight plays-
This fucking -
Freeze, motherfucker! Drop it!
- Don't! Don't!
- Put that fucking gun down! Put the gun down!
- Okay! Don't shoot!
- Drop the fucking gun!
Marco, duck!
Aw, the hell with this.
You are done!
No more table.
Where are you going, pal?
Next time you have
a chance to kill someone, don't hesitate.
Thanks for the advice.
Sorry to waste your time.
No problem at all.
- Merry Christmas.
- Merry Christmas to you.
Oh, for the love of -
- 8-Lincoln-30 to Dispatch.
- 8-L-30, go ahead.
Yeah, that's a wild goose chase
over here at Nakatomi Plaza.
Everything here's okay.
Over.
Damn! Goddamn it!
Jesus H. Christ!
Welcome to the party, pal!
Goddamn it!
Now means now, goddamn it!
Policeman under automatic
rifle fire at Nakatomi!
I need backup assistance now!
Now, goddamn it! Now!
Monica, I can get us a table.
Wolfgang and l
are very close friends.
Officer in need of assistance.
- l interviewed him.
- Reports of shots fired at Nakatomi.
2000 block, Avenue of the Stars.
Repeat, officer
needs assistance at -
I'm in Nakatomi Plaza.
They're turning my car into Swiss cheese!
I need backup assistance now!
Now, goddamn it! Now!
I never thought I'd love
to hear that sound.
All of you, relax. This is a matter
of inconvenient timing, that's all.
Police action was inevitable...
and, as it happens, necessary.
So let them
fumble about outside, and stay calm.
This is simply the beginning.
I thought I told all of you
I want radio silence until further-
Oh, I'm very sorry, Hans.
I didn't get that message.
Maybe you should have
put it on the bulletin board.
I figured since I waxed Tony and Marco
and his friend here...
I figured you and Karl and Franco
might be a little lonely.
So I wanted to give you a call.
How does he know so much about -
That's very kind of you.
I assume you are
our mysterious party crasher.
You are most troublesome
for a security guard.
Sorry, Hans. Wrong guess.
Would you like to go for "Double Jeopardy"
where the scores can really change?
Hmm. These are very bad for you.
Who are you then?
Just a fly in the ointment, Hans.
A monkey in the wrench.
A pain in the ass.
Whoa.
Check on all the others.
Don't use the radio.
See if he's lying about Marco,
and find out if anyone else is missing.
Mr. Mystery Guest...
are you still there?
Yeah, I'm still here.
Unless you wanna open the front door for me.
No, I'm afraid not.
But you have me at a loss.
You know my name, but who are you?
Just another American who saw
too many movies as a child?
Another orphan of a bankrupt culture
who thinks he's John Wayne?
Rambo? Marshal Dillon?
I was always kind of partial
to Roy Rogers actually.
I really liked those sequin shirts.
Do you really think you have
a chance against us, Mr. Cowboy?
Yippee-ki-yea, motherfucker.
- I can get the jump on everybody if I get a remote.
- I don't have the new pages.
- Where's the Gladden report?
- Harvey, keep your pants on, will you?
- Sam, look, I'm begging you.
- Simon's at a remote thing
with that Santa sing-along.
- I'll tell him to swing by.
- I'm not sitting on this for Simon!
- I don't wanna hear it!
- This is my story!
- I can't hear you.
- All right, look. Sam, I tell you what.
You don't wanna give me a truck,
I'll go and I'll steal a truck.
- Give us a break, Thornburg.
- Eat it, Harvey!
Four, three, two, one.
Harvey, we're on the air.
Good evening.
This is Harvey Johnson.
And I'm Gail Wallens, and this is
Nightline News at 10:00.
Our top stories
on this Christmas Eve-
Take truck number five
and get out of here.
He wasn't lying about Marco.
He's down on the street.
And the other man was Heinrich.
And his bag is missing.
But he had the detonators.
Theo.
- Theo.
- Yo!
We may have some problems.
How's our schedule?
- Three down, four to go.
- Then don't waste time talking to me.
This is Sergeant Al Powell
of the Los Angeles Police Department.
if the person who radioed for help
can hear me on this channel...
acknowledge this transmission.
I say again, if the person who radioed for help
on this channel can hear me...
acknowledge this transmission.
I read you, Powell.
You the guy in the car?
What's left of him.
- Can you identify yourself?
- Not now. Maybe later.
Listen fast. This is a party line,
and the neighbors got itchy trigger fingers.
All right, here's the deal.
You got 30 or so hostages on the 30th floor.
- The leader, his name is Hans.
- We have to find him and shut him up.
- He's telling them everything!
- Let him. I'm waiting for the F.B.I. to arrive.
Until then, he can waste as much time as he likes,
but we must find the bag.
- Fritz, go help Uli. We must have the detonators.
- They got an arsenal up here.
They got missiles, automatic weapons...
and enough plastic explosives
to orbit Arnold Schwarzenegger.
They're down to nine now,
countin' the skydiver you met.
These guys are mostly European,
judging by their clothing labels and...
cigarettes.
They're well-financed
and very slick.
- How do you know that?
- I've seen enough phony I.D.'s in my time...
to recognize that the ones they got
must've cost a fortune.
Add all that up, l don't know
what the fuck it means.
But you got some badass perpetrators,
and they're here to stay.
I hear you, partner.
L.A.'s finest are on it.
- So light 'em if you got 'em.
- Way ahead of you, partner.
So what do I call you?
Call me... Roy.
Well, listen up, Roy.
if you think of anything else
you think we need to know, don't be shy, okay?
In the meantime, find a safe place to hole up
and let us do our job.
- Understand?
- They're all yours, Al.
All right, who's talking to 'em?
I am, sir.
Sergeant Powell. Al Powell.
Dwayne Robinson, Powell.
What's the deal here? What do these pricks want?
Well, if you mean the terrorists, sir,
we don't exactly know.
We haven't heard a peep from them.
Well, who in the hell
have you been talking to?
We don't know that either, sir.
He won't give us his name.
But he appears to be the one
who phoned in the report.
He's killed one terrorist for sure,
and he claims he's capped off two others.
He claims?
Has it occurred to you he could
be one of the terrorists pulling your chain?
Or some nutcase in there?
I don't think so, sir.
In fact, I think he's a cop.
- Maybe not L.A.P.D., but he's definitely a badge.
- How do you know that?
A hunch.
Things he said...
like being able to spot a phony l.D.
Jesus Christ, Powell!
He could be a fucking bartender for all we know.
- TV's here.
- Oh, shit.
I'm not gonna warn you again.
I have a request.
- What idiot put you in charge?
- You did...
when you murdered my boss.
Now everybody's looking to me.
Personally, l'd pass on the job.
I don't enjoy being this close to you.
Go on.
We have a pregnant woman out there.
Relax. She's not due
for a couple of weeks.
But sitting on that rock
isn't doing her back any good.
So I would like permission to move her
to one of the offices where there's a sofa.
No, but I'll have a sofa
brought out to you. Good enough?
Good enough.
And unless you like it messy,
I'd start bringing us in groups to the bathroom.
Yes, you're right.
It will be done.
Was there something else?
No. Thank you.
Mr. Takagi chose
his people well, Mrs. -
Gennero.
Miss Gennero.
We interrupt this program
for a special news bulletin.
This is Richard Thornburg,
live from Century City.
Tonight, Los Angeles has joined...
the sad and worldwide
fraternity of cities...
whose only membership requirement...
is to suffer the anguish
of international terrorism.
Approximately two hours ago,
an unidentified group of men...
seized control
of the Nakatomi building...
sealing off all entrances and exits.
All telephone lines have been cut.
And the only communication
now possible...
has been through the use
of C.B. communicators...
which the group
apparently brought with them.
According to official sources,
the perpetrators-
Unit Five, hold your
position at the main entrance.
All right, guys, we got Charlie Unit
in position by the parking structure.
Let me ask you something.
Does this stairway go up to the escalator?
- Yeah. That's where they're going.
- Tell them to go ahead.
- Through the lobby up there
and try and draw some fire.
- What's going on?
What's it look like?
We're going in.
Goin' in?
Man, that's crazy!
There could be over 30 hostages in there
for all we know.
We don't know shit, Powell.
If there's hostages...
how come nobody's come to us
with ransom demands?
If there's terrorists in there,
where's their list of demands?
All we know is that
somebody shot your car up.
It's probably the same silly son of a bitch
you've been talking to on that radio.
Excuse me, sir, but what about the body
that fell out the window?
Well, who knows? It was probably
some stockbroker who got depressed.
- We're ready for you, Chief.
- All right, light 'em up. Let's go.
- All right, hit your lights.
- Blue Unit, go.
- We got approval, Chief.
- Lights on!
Down a little.
Al.
Al, you still with me, babe?
What's going on?
Yo, Al?
I'm here, Roy. I'm kind of busy right now.
I'll talk to you later.
- What's wrong? What's going on?
- I said I'll talk to you later.
If you are what I think you are, then you'll know
when to listen, when to shut up...
and -  and when to pray.
Jesus Christ. You're coming in.
That's it, isn't it?
Christ, Powell, I told you what kind of people
you're dealing with here.
- All right, let's load 'em up.
- Blue, go.
So, they'll be coming.
Everyone get ready.
Theo, you are the eyes now.
- Rivers!
- Yo!
Begin your reconnoiter.
Let's go!
Shit!
Hey, come on.
Let's go!
Ow! Jesus.
All right, spread out.
Shut up.
Let's go!
You macho assholes.
No! No!
All right. Listen up, guys.
'Twas the night before Christmas,
and all through the house...
not a creature was stirring,
except...
the four assholes
coming in the rear...
in standard two-by-two
cover formation.
Okay, we're all set.
We're ready.
- Kick ass.
- Go!
Right. Let's do it.
- Take cover!
- They're shootin' at 'em!
It's panic fire.
They can't see anything.
They're shootin' at the lights.
They're going after the lights.
Pull 'em back.
- It's not happening.
- Mike, burn it.
Don't be impatient.
Just wound them.
- Get 'em back. They're sittin' ducks
up there without lights.
- No, they're almost in.
- Get 'em back!
- They're almost in. Send in the car.
Send in the car.
Jesus Christ!
Rivers, Rodriguez, report.
Whoa! Wait a minute. Wait a minute.
What have we here, gentlemen?
The police have themselves an R.V.
Southeast corner.
Hurry ...
Oh, Jesus Christ.
Out of here! Get back!
Get the fuck back!
- Get over there!
- Hurry.
- Shit
- Leave it. Move on.
I see him!
- Ready?
- Just a moment.
Oh, my God!
The quarterback is toast.
- All right, all right!
- Get them out of the car. Let's go!
- Hang on, Rivers. That's an order.
- Hit it again.
Hans, you motherfucker, you made your point!
Let 'em pull back!
Thank you, Mr. Cowboy.
I'll take it under advisement.
Hit it again.
Fire.
Fuck me.
Let's go! Get 'em out of the car.
Don't you know they're burning?
Fuck it.
Bring the other one over here.
Hurry.
Let's see you take this
under advisement, jerk-weed.
Geronimo, motherfucker!
Oh, shit!
They're using artillery on us!
You idiot.
It's not the police. It's him.
Holy shit.
My God.
- Tell me you got that.
- I got it. I got it.
Eat your heart out, Channel Five.
We've had an update on the
terrorist takeover of the Nakatomi building.
Sources say the terrorist leader, Hans,
may be this man, Hans Gruber...
a member of the radical
West German Volksfrei movement.
Strangely, the Volksfrei leadership
issued a communiqué an hour ago...
stating that Gruber had been
expelled from that organization.
- Al, do you copy?
- Are you all right?
Yeah, I'm fine.
What-What was that?
- Remember that plastic explosive I told you about?
- Yeah.
There you go.
Is the building on fire?
No, but it's gonna need a paint job
and a shitload of screen doors.
Our spotters say
you got two with that blast.
Is that him?
- Yes, sir.
- Give me that.
You listen to me, mister. l don't know
who in the hell you think you are...
or what you're doing,
but you just destroyed a building!
Now, we do not want your help.
Is that clear? We don't want your help.
I've got 100 people down here,
and they're covered with glass.
Glass? Who gives a shit about glass?
Who the fuck is this?
This is Deputy Chief of Police
Dwayne T. Robinson...
and I am in charge
of this situation.
Oh, you're in charge? Well, l got some
bad news for you, Dwayne.
From up here it doesn't look like
you're in charge of jack shit.
- You listen to me, you little asshole. I'm -
- Asshole?
I'm not the one who just got butt-fucked
on national TV, Dwayne.
Now, you listen to me, jerk-off.
If you're not part of the solution,
you're part of the problem.
Quit being part of the fucking problem
and put the other guy back on!
Hey, Roy.
How you feelin'?
Pretty fuckin' unappreciated, Al.
Hey, look. l love you.
So do a lot of the other guys.
So you hang in there, man.
You hear me? You hang in there.
Yeah, thanks, partner.
What are you doing?
I'm tired of sitting here waiting to see
who gets us killed first -
them or your husband.
What are you going to do?
Hey, babe, I negotiate
million-dollar deals for breakfast.
I think I can handle
this Euro-trash. Hey.
Sprechen sie talk?
Huh?
If you listened to me,
he would be neutralized already.
I don't want neutral. I want dead.
- Hope I'm not interrupting.
- What does he want?
It's not what I want.
It's what I can give you.
Look, let's be straight, okay?
It's obvious you're not some dumb schmuck
up here to snatch a few purses. Am I right?
- You're very perceptive.
- I watch 60 Minutes.
I say to myself, "These guys are professional,
they're motivated...
they're happening,
i.e. they want something."
Now, personally, I couldn't care less
about your politics.
Maybe you're pissed off
at the camel jockeys.
Maybe it's the Hebes, Northern Ireland.
lt's none of my business.
I figure you're here to negotiate.
Am I right?
You're amazing.
You figured this all out already?
Hey, business is business.
You use a gun. I use a fountain pen.
What's the difference?
Let's put it in my terms.
You're here in a hostile takeover,
you grab us for some greenmail...
but you didn't expect some poison pill
was gonna be running around in the building.
Am I right?
Hans, Bubbe, I'm your white knight.
I must have missed 60 Minutes.
What are you saying?
The guy upstairs
who's fucking things up? Huh?
I can give him to you.
Oh, God!
Roy!
Roy, you all right?
Just trying to fire down
a thousand-year-old Twinkie
What do they put
in these things, anyway?
Sugar-enriched flour,
partially hydrogenated vegetable oil...
polysorbate 60
and yellow dye number five.
Just everything a growing boy needs.
How many kids you got, Al?
Well, as a matter of fact,
my wife is working on our first.
How about you, cowboy?
You got any kids back on your ranch?
Yeah. Two.
I sure hope I can see 'em swinging
on a jungle gym with Al Jr. someday.
Well, now, that's a date.
But, uh, you're gonna have
to bring the ice cream.
Touching, cowboy. Touching.
Or should I call you Mr. McClane?
Mr. Officer John McClane...
of the New York Police Department.
- Get on the phone to Harry in New York.
- Got it.
Better get ahold
of somebody at Dispatch.
Sister Theresa called me
Mr. McClane in third grade.
My friends call me John.
You're neither, shithead.
l have someone
who wants to talk to you -
a very special friend...
who was with you
at the party tonight.
Hey, John Boy.
- Ellis?
- Yeah. Now, listen, John.
They're givin' me a few minutes
to try to talk some sense into you.
I know you think you're doing your job,
and l can appreciate that...
but you're just
dragging this thing out.
Now, look, no one gets out of here
until these guys...
can talk to the L.A. police...
and that just ain't gonna happen until you stop
messing up the works, capisce?
Ellis, what have you told them?
I told them we were old friends,
and you were my guest at the party.
Ellis, you shouldn't be doing this.
Tell me about it.
All right, John, listen.
They want you to tell them
where the detonators are.
They know people are listening.
They want the detonators
or they're gonna kill me.
John, didn't you hear me?
Yeah, l hear you.
John, I think you could get
with the program a little, huh?
The police are here now.
It's their problem.
Now tell these guys where the detonators
are so no one else gets hurt.
I'm putting my life
on the line for you, pal.
- Ellis, listen to me very carefully.
- John -
Shut up, Ellis! Just shut your mouth!
Put Hans back on the line.
Hans, this shithead does not know
what kind of man you are, but I do. Listen -
Good. Then you'll give us what we want
and save your friend's life.
You're not part of this equation.
It's time you realized that.
Hey, what am l,
a method actor, Hans?
Babe, put away the gun.
This is radio, not television.
Hans, this asshole is not my friend.
l just met him tonight.
I don't know him. Jesus Christ, Ellis,
these people are gonna kill you!
Tell them you don't know me!
John, how can you say that
after all these years?
John? John?
Do you hear that?
Talk to me!
Where are my detonators?
Where are they,
or shall I shoot another one?
Sooner or later, I might get to someone
you do care about.
Go fuck yourself, Hans.
Did you hear that?
He just let the guy die, man.
He just gave him up.
Give me that headset.
- That's like pulling the trigger yourself.
- Christ, man.
Can't you see what's happening?
Can't you read between the lines?
- Is this on the right channel?
- Yes, sir.
He did everything he could to save him.
If he gave himself up,
they'd both be dead right now.
No way, man. No way.
They'd be talking to us.
Listen, you tell this partner of yours to stay
the hell out of this from now on.
Because if he doesn't, I'm gonna nail him.
I'm really gonna nail his ass now. Believe me.
The man is hurtin'.
He is alone, tired...
and he hasn't seen diddly-squat
from anybody down here.
Now, you're gonna
stand there and tell me...
he's gonna give a damn about what you'll do
to him if he makes it out of there alive?
Why don't you wake up
and smell what you're shoveling?
You listen to me, Sergeant.
Anytime you wanna go home,
you consider yourself dismissed.
No, sir.
You couldn't drag me away.
Attention, police.
- This is Sergeant Al Powell -
- Give me that.
This is, uh -  This is, uh,
Deputy Chief Dwayne Robinson. Who is this?
This is Hans Gruber.
I assume you realize the futility
of direct action against me.
We have no wish
for further loss of life.
Well, uh, what is it you do wish for,
Mr. Gruber?
I have comrades-in-arms
around the world languishing in prison.
The American State Department
enjoys rattling its saber for its own ends.
Now it can rattle it for me.
The following people
are to be released from their captors.
ln Northern Ireland,
the seven members of the New Provo Front.
In Canada, the five imprisoned leaders
of Liberté de Québec.
- In Sri Lanka, the nine members
of the Asian Dawn movement.
- What the fuck?
I read about them in Time magazine.
When these revolutionary
brothers and sisters are free...
the hostages in this building
will be taken to the roof...
and they will accompany us in helicopters
to the Los Angeles International Airport...
where they will be given
further instructions.
You have two hours to comply.
Wait a minute.
Mr. Gruber, this is crazy.
I-l-I don't have the authority.
I can't authorize - Two hours is not enough.
H-Hello?
Hello?
Danny, did you get all that?
Let's go. We gotta make some calls.
Do you think they'll
even try to do it?
Who cares?
Theo, are we on schedule?
One more to go, then it's up to you.
And you better be right...
because it looks like
this last one's gonna take a miracle.
It's Christmas, Theo.
It's the time of miracles.
So be of good cheer and call me
when you hit the last lock.
Karl, hunt that little shit down
and get those detonators.
Fritz is checking the explosives.
I'll check the explosives.
You just get the detonators.
Hey, Powell, you out there?
I'm here, John.
I'm here.
You gotta believe me.
There was nothing I could do.
Well, it's gonna be both
our asses if you're wrong.
I hear you.
Did you catch that bullshit
Hans was running?
It doesn't make sense, man.
Don't ask me, man. I'm just a desk jockey
who was on my way home when you rang.
The way you drove that car,
I figured you for the street, Al.
In my youth.
And author of Hostage Terrorist,
Terrorist Hostage: A Study in Duality.
Dr. Hasseldorf, what can we expect
in the next few hours?
Well, Gail, by this time the hostages
should be going through...
the early stages
of the "Helsinki Syndrome."
- As in Helsinki, Sweden.
- Finland.
Basically, it's when the hostages
and the terrorists go through...
a sort of psychological transference
and a projection of dependency.
A strange sort of trust
and bond develops.
We've had situations
where the hostages...
have embraced their captors
after their release...
and even corresponded
with them in prison.
No, no.
No, darling. "Asian Dawn."
Dawn.
D-A-W-N.
- Sir?
- I -  Yeah?
- The F.B.I. is here.
- Oh. The F.B.I. is here now?
Yes, sir, right over there.
- Hold this.
- You want a breath mint?
Uh, yeah. We got it.
Hey!
How you doing, man?
I'm Agent Johnson.
This is Special Agent Johnson.
- Oh. How you doing?
- No relation.
I'm, uh -
I'm Dwayne Robinson, L.A.P.D.
I'm in charge here.
Not anymore.
Hi, there.
How you doing?
Oh!
Please, God, no. You're one of them,
aren't you? You're one of them.
Don't -  Don't kill me.
Please, don't. Please!
- Don't kill me. Don't kill me, please.
- Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Relax. Relax. I'm not gonna hurt you.
I'm not gonna hurt you!
Oh, God.
What the fuck are you doing up here?
What were you looking for?
I managed to get out of there,
and, uh -
Well, I was just trying
to get up on the roof...
and see if l could
signal for help, you know.
It's just through here.
Why don't you come and help -
- Whoa, whoa, whoa. Forget the roof.
- Come on. Come on.
I said forget the roof.
They got people all over it.
Come on. You wanna stay alive,
you stay with me.
Well, the best way
we can figure it is...
we've got maybe
30 or 35 hostages up there...
probably on the 30th floor...
and maybe, l don't know,
seven or eight terrorists up there.
Sounds like an A-7 scenario.
Thank you.
We'll handle it from here.
When we commandeer your men,
we'll try and let you know.
- Aren't you forgetting something?
- Such as?
What about John McClane?
He's the reason why we have
the information we have up until now.
He's also the reason why you're facing
seven terrorists instead of 12.
He's inside?
Who is he?
Well, he might be a cop.
I don't know. We're checking on that.
- One of yours?
- No. No way.
Do you smoke?
Yeah.
Thanks.
You don't work for Nakatomi.
And if you're not
one of them -
I'm a cop from New York.
New York?
Yeah.
Got invited to the Christmas party by mistake.
Who knew?
Yeah.
It's better than being caught
with your pants down, huh?
I'm John McClane.
You're, uh -
Clay.
Bill Clay.
You know how to use a handgun, Bill?
I spent a weekend at a combat ranch.
You know that game
with the guns that shoot red paint?
Probably seems
kind of stupid to you.
Well...
time for the real thing, Bill.
All you gotta do
is pull the trigger. Come on.
33rd. floor. Come right away.
Put down the gun...
and give me my detonators.
Well, well, well.
Hans.
Put it down now.
That's pretty tricky
with that accent.
You oughta be on fucking TV
But what do you want
with the detonators, Hans?
I already used all the explosives.
Or did I?
- I'm going to count to three.
- Yeah.
Like you did with Takagi?
Oops.
No bullets. You think
I'm fucking stupid, Hans?
You were saying?
Karl.
Shoot the Windows!
Shoot the glass.
Jesus Christ!
Smile, Karl.
We're back in business.
...is the last resort of diplomacy.
Then couldn't we just as well say...
that terrorism has an equal claim
on being that too?
You got something.
Tell me you got something.
Just McClane's name, badge number,
employment record...
vital statistics
and his family's home address...
right here in L.A.
Whoa!
Go to work.
Got it.
God, that man looks really pissed.
- He's still alive.
- What?
Only John can drive
somebody that crazy.
Hans.
You better heat up that miracle,
because we just broke through on number six...
and the electromagnetic
came down like a fucking anvil.
Have a look at what our friends outside
are doing, and I'll be right up.
Hey, John?
John McClane, you still with us?
Yeah.
But all things being equal,
I'd rather be in Philadelphia.
Chalk up two more bad guys.
Well, the boys down here
will be glad to hear that.
You know, we got
a pool going on you.
- What kind of odds am I gettin'?
- You don't want to know.
Put me down for 20.
I'm good for it.
Hey, Powell, you got flat feet?
What the hell
you talking about, man?
Something had to
get you off the street.
What's the matter? You don't think
jockeying papers across a desk...
is a noble effort for a cop?
No.
- I had an accident.
- The way you drive, I can see why.
What'd you do, run over
your captain's foot with a car?
I shot a kid.
He was 13 years old.
It was dark. I couldn't see him.
He had a ray gun.
It looked real enough.
You know, when you're a rookie, they can
teach you everything about being a cop...
except how to live with a mistake.
Anyway, I just couldn't bring myself
to draw my gun on anybody again.
Sorry, man.
Hey, man, how could you know?
I feel like shit anyway.
Well, then this won't matter.
The L.A.P.D. is not calling
the shots down here anymore.
- Feds?
- You got it.
All right, those
are the city engineers.
They're going into
the street circuits.
- Those guys in the suits -
I don't know who they are.
- That's the F.B.I.
They're ordering the others
to cut the building's power.
Regular as clockwork.
- Or a time lock.
- Precisely.
The circuits that cannot be cut
are cut automatically...
in response to a terrorist incident.
You asked for miracles, Theo.
I give you...
the F.B.I.
- I said I want the friggin' building shut down.
- I got a problem.
- I got a switch here -
- I don't give two shits about your switch!
- I want the building out. Dark. D-A-R-K!
- Hold on! You don't understand.
- You can't do it from here.
- Yeah, you could.
It can't be done from here.
- I could just - I got the radio.
- You can't do it from down here I'm telling you.
It's gotta be done from downtown.
They've gotta take out
a whole city grid.
- We're talking 10 square blocks.
- Ten blocks?
Johnson, that's crazy.
It's Christmas Eve, man.
- There's thousands of people.
- You have to go wider.
- I need authorization.
- Authorization?
- How about the United States
fucking government?
- Hey.
Lose the grid or you lose your job.
- Yeah, Central?
- Yeah?
This is Walt down at Nakatomi.
Say, listen.
Would it be possible
for you to turn off grid 212?
- Are you crazy?
- Maybe I should call the mayor.
No shit, it's my ass. I got a big problem
down here. Shut it down.
Shut it down now.
Emergency lighting activated.
- Powell. Powell, talk to me.
What's going on here?
- Ask the F.B.I.
They got the universal
terrorist playbook...
and they're running it step by step.
It's gonna go.
It's gonna go!
Yes!
Merry Christmas.
Those bastards are probably
pissing in their pants right now.
The mayor's gonna have my ass.
Whoo!
Well, what are we gonna do now?
Arrest them for not
paying their electric bill?
We've shut them down. We let 'em sweat
for a while, then we give 'em helicopters.
Right up the ass.
This is Agent Johnson.
No, the other one.
I want that air support
ready to lift off in five minutes.
Damn right. Fully armed.
We're on the way.
Oh, yeah!
I wish to talk to the F.B.I.
This is Special Agent Johnson
of the F.B.I.
The State Department has arranged
for the return of your comrades.
Helicopters are en route
as you requested.
I hear you.
We'll be ready.
By the time he figures out
what hit him, he'll be in a body bag.
When they touch down,
we'll blow the roof.
They'll spend a month
sifting through the rubble.
And by the time they figure out
what went wrong...
we'll be sitting on a beach
earning 20%.
Powell.
Yo, Powell, you got a minute?
I'm here, John.
Listen, man, I'm starting
to get a bad feeling up here.
I want you to do something for me.
Um -
I want you to find my wife.
Don't ask me how. By then, you'll know how.
Uh, I want you
to tell her something.
I want you to tell her that...
um -
Tell her it took me
a while to figure out...
what a jerk I've been,
but, um -
but that -
that when things
started to pan out for her...
I should've been
more supportive, and, uh -
and I just should've been
behind her more.
Oh, shit.
Tell her that, um -
that she's the best thing that
ever happened to a bum like me.
She's heard me say "I love you"
a thousand times.
She never heard me say, "I'm sorry."
And I want you to tell her that.
I want you to tell her that...
John said that he was sorry.
Okay?
- You got that, man?
- Yeah, I got it, John.
But you can tell her that yourself.
You just watch your ass
and you'll make it out of there. You hear me?
Well, I guess that's up
to the man upstairs.
John? John?
What the fuck were
you doing upstairs, Hans?
- John?
- No, Al, listen. Listen, just lay off for a while.
I gotta go check on something.
One minute.
That's all I'm asking.
One minute just to speak to you.
All right. All right.
All right. Get back.
Get back. Off. Off. All right.
Look, you let me in right now,
or I call the I.N.S.
Comprende?
Look, this is the last time these kids are gonna
have to speak to their parents.
All right? All right.
Come on. Come on.
What were you doing, Hans?
What were you doing?
Jesus, Mary, mother of God.
Powell, listen to me!
It's a double cross!
The whole roof
of the building's wired to -
John.
John, come in.
Did you get that?
No. Something about a double cross.
Tell me about it.
We are both professionals.
This is personal.
Oh.
They're coming.
- Choppers are coming.
- Okay.
Time to gather your flock,
Miss Gennero.
You know, your mom
and dad are very important people.
They're very brave people.
So is there something you would like
to say to them if they're watching?
Come home.
Mrs. McClane.
How nice to make your acquaintance.
On your feet, everyone!
To the roof!
Lock them up there
and come right back.
Move! Come on! Let's move!
You should've heard your brother squeal
when I broke his fucking neck!
What do you figure the breakage?
Figure we take out the terrorists...
lose 20 -  25%
of the hostages... tops.
I can live with that.
Keep this thing on the deck.
They're expecting transports, not gunships.
Move it! Come on! Move!
Come on! Come on!
Move it!
Let's go! Move!
Theo.
A little bonus for us.
- Please, sit down. Sit down.
- Hey!
A policeman's wife
might come in handy.
McClane, l have some news for you.
McClane.
Come on!
Move, move!
Motherfucker, l'll kill you!
Armed. The truck?
The truck.
After all your posturing,
all your little speeches...
you're nothing but a common thief.
I am an exceptional thief,
Mrs. McClane.
And since I'm moving up to kidnapping,
you should be more polite.
Motherfucker, I'm gonna kill you!
I'm gonna fucking cook you,
and I'm gonna fucking eat you!
I don't like this, Sarge.
Just like fuckin' Saigon, eh, slick?
I was in junior high, dickhead.
Where's Holly?
Where's Holly Gennero?
Holly Gennero! Where's Holly?
Where's Holly? Where is she?
- They took her!
- Where?
- The vault!
- Where is the vault?
The 30th floor. Up the stairs.
They just took her!
Get downstairs, all of you!
The whole fuckin' roof is wired to blow. Get down!
Get down! Get the fuck downstairs!
- They made us, Bureau.
You got a terrorist shooting hostages.
- l see it. Bank left.
Nail that sucker!
I'm on your side, you assholes!
Shit. Swing around again!
I'll bag this little bastard.
What the fuck -
Jesus!
Oh, John, what the fuck
are you doing?
How the fuck
did you get into this shit?
There's something wrong.
They're coming back down.
- Blow the roof.
- But Karl's up there!
Blow the roof!
I promise l will never even think...
about going up
in a tall building again.
Oh, God.
Please don't let me die.
Holy shit!
Holy Christ!
We're gonna need some more
F.B.I. guys, I guess.
Jesus fucking Christ!
What the fuck is going on?
What are you gonna do, sit here while
the building falls down around your ears?
Shit!
Hey! All right!
Hang on, baby.
Hang on, honey. Oh, God.
Hans!
Jesus.
Hi, honey.
So that's what this was all about?
- A fucking robbery?
- Put down the gun.
Why did you have to nuke
the whole building, Hans?
When you steal $600,
you can just disappear.
When you steal 600 million,
they will find you...
unless they think
you're already dead.
Put down the gun.
Nein (No)! This is mine.
You got me.
Still the cowboy, Mr. McClane.
Americans, all alike.
Well, this time...
John Wayne does not
walk off into the sunset with Grace Kelly.
That's Gary Cooper, asshole.
Enough jokes.
You'd have made a pretty good
cowboy yourself, Hans.
Oh, yes.
What was it you said to me before?
Yippee-ki-yea, motherfucker.
Holly!
Happy trails, Hans.
I hope that's not a hostage.
Give me water hook-ups
for engine companies five, three, nine, six.
Over here. It's a better angle.
Let's give 'em a hand over there.
Keep it going now.
Keep it going.
Come on. Come on!
We're gonna miss it.
- Okay, hand me my notes.
- Come on!
Keep that water on there.
What was it like in there? How did they
treat you? Did they frighten you at all?
- Any comment?
- It was terrible. We don't wanna talk about it.
How does it feel to be outside?
Al, this is my wife Holly.
Holly Gennero.
- Holly McClane.
- Hello, Holly.
You got yourself a good man.
You take good care of him.
- McClane?
- Yeah, it's okay. Let him through.
McClane, I wanna debrief.
I want a debriefing.
You got some things to answer for, mister.
Ellis's murder, for one thing.
Property damage.
Interfering with police business.
All right, I want two of you
to go inside and see if there's anybody else.
Yes, sir.
I'll take the left.
- Watch it!
- Whoa. This one's with me.
Five, four, three, two.
Mr. McClane. Mr. McClane,
now that it's all over...
after this incredible ordeal,
what are your feelings?
Well, well, well.
- Merry Christmas, Argyle.
- Merry Christmas.
Did you get that?
Let me through.
Let me through. Thank you.
If this is their idea of Christmas,
I gotta be here for New Year's.
Best watched using Open Subtitles MKV Player