-== [ www.OpenSubtitles.com ] ==-
In ages past,
the dragons and their crystals of power
came to this barbaric land
through the portal from Dragon World.
The crystals brought strength and wisdom,
especially the great Aurathon,
the mighty crystal
with powers so vast it could only be wielded
by the Dragon King himself.
But though the dragons wanted only peace,
their human allies wanted war.
The kingdoms of Norvagen and Draigar
misused the knowledge
brought by the dragons,
and battles erupted.
Seeking to end the wars,
the Dragon King
made the wizard, Xenoz,
ambassador between the dragons
and the two kingdoms.
He was given dragon-gifts
and immortality.
And for a time, Xenoz
and the Dragon King
forced peace upon the land.
But peace imposed by
others cannot last.
Then came the great betrayal.
Evil forces arose,
and the Dragon Queen was slain.
In his anguish,
the Dragon King and many of his followers
returned to Dragon World,
closing the portal.
The great Aurathon,
the receptacle of all dragon knowledge
and the only crystal whose powers
could open the portal itself,
went with them.
That's what it looked like.
'Course, no one's seen it for a thousand years.
But... but we still have dragons, Dad.
Eh? Oh, yes, Targon is
an old friend of the family,
so he stayed behind.
You ready?
You always tell me never to let myself
get distracted by an opponent!
Right you are, lad.
Help me up.
What else do I always say?
Never trust a soul...
- except a dragon's.
So how many dragons are left?
Targon there is all
we Norvagen have these days.
Although the legend says
they may return
when the war is over,
I doubt it.
Not if the Draigar keep hunting them.
Those rotten Draigar!
I like the attitude, son,
but you swung
before you were ready.
Think, lad. Plan.
You're too impulsive.
But other than that,
an excellent practice.
I do believe you're ready.
For what?
Ah, Xenoz!
Thank you for coming.
I have a surprise for you, my boy.
We are in harmony.
Let your senses seek
the wisdom of the ancients.
I feel you, Father.
When you are ready...
you may... strike!
Your skills have grown impressive.
I have a good teacher.
Aurora!
Hey, no fair!
That's cheating!
That is battle, Kyra.
Norvagen do not fight by the rules.
You assumed we were
finished and we were not.
You think too much.
Sometimes a soldier
must simply act.
Don't think I'm going
to forgive you, Aurora.
Even if you are
the last dragon we have.
Oh, I think you shall.
After all, someone must stand against
those dragon-hunting Norvagen.
Is that not right, Xenoz?
Oh, absolutely.
I have come as you requested, King Siddari.
Although sometimes I wonder.
As the dragons vanish, the need for
a dragon ambassador
grows questionable.
I could retire...
Looks like Aurora doesn't
like that idea, Xenoz!
How complimentary.
I understand you have
a special surprise
for your daughter?
Indeed I do.
Father!
You mean my first dragon flight?
Well, perhaps not?
As I recall, you are upset with Aurora
at the moment...
With Aurora?
No way!
We're best friends!
Tell him, Aurora!
Well, what do you think, Xenoz...
Great dragons, sir!
Are you sweating again?
As always, Your Highness, I find it
too warm here after
the chill of my ice palace.
But as for your daughter,
I think she is ready.
Then will you
give her your blessing?
By the powers bestowed
upon me by the dragons,
may these two fly together as one.
Can I go? Can I?
She's all yours, but be careful.
Then come on, Aurora!
Let's fly!
Have you ever seen Aurora accept
a rider so completely, Xenoz?
Xenoz?
Aye, the boy was
born for that dragon!
What?
Aurora!
Where are you going?
Stop!
Something's wrong! Soldiers!
To me!
No! Turn!
I said turn!
If this is the doing
of that Draigar, Siddari...
You!
Stay back!
Norvagen!
Over here! This way!
Draigar!
I knew they were behind this!
Attack!
Warriors!
So... it begins again.
You are troubled, son.
Yeah, you could tell?
The wind speaks your mood.
It always has.
I sometimes wonder
if it is affecting you
or whether you affect it.
That's absurd!
Sure it is.
And yet the wind is angry,
and so are you.
Why shouldn't I be!
I mean, this latest
skirmish with the Draigar
has lasted eight years!
That's half my life!
What's eight years
when the war itself
has lasted a thousand?
When you reach my age...
When I reach your age,
I want peace!
And the sky...
I want to see the sky
filled with dragons again!
You know the legend says they'll return
when the war is over!
Wishful thinking.
This war has sapped our land,
our people, our energy.
But tomorrow's battle...
Will be the same! Again!
Let me end this... tonight!
What!
Let me take Targon.
I'll come in fast and hard,
right into the Draigar castle itself.
I can capture the princess
and be gone before those
Draigar can even respond!
And with her as our captive,
they'll be forced to surrender on our terms!
What?
The princess is a respected fighter, son.
- She's a girl! I can do this!
- No!
Wars are won by armies,
not individuals.
Besides, we need you
for tomorrow's battle.
No.
This has to end.
Tonight.
I'm serious, Father!
Too many Draigar
soldiers have fallen
in this battle.
It's time to end it!
By sacrificing you?
No. Out of the question.
It's not a sacrifice!
How do you do that?
Sorry, you know I can't control it.
But this I can!
Issue a challenge!
The Norvagen prince against me!
One-on-one!
To end the war once and for all!
The risk is too high.
I can take him, Father!
He's a clumsy brawler. A Norvagen.
I'm the best fighter you have,
you've said so yourself.
And you can prove that
tomorrow, in battle,
with soldiers beside you.
As it should be.
What are you saying?
That you want another
thousand years of war?
I tried, Aurora.
I didn't even mention the legend.
But I know you want your kind
to return as much as I do.
This has to happen.
The Norvagen and I have
to face each other,
I can feel it.
So if my father won't
issue the challenge...
Then I'll challenge the prince myself!
Let's go, Aurora!
Fly!
Remember, Targon!
Fast and hard!
Something is happening.
Something... momentous.
My crystal of scrying!
Well, this is interesting.
The two royals.
You! Draigar!
What are you doing here?
I was coming to offer
you a challenge! One on one!
I had plans of my own,
but this'll do.
Go, Targon!
Aurora! Attack!
Apparently we're in this alone.
See you on the ground?
After you.
Winner takes all?
Can't speak for my father,
but that's fine by me!
Good move. But you should have
finished me while I was down.
Wouldn't have been fair.
Whatever.
Fair's fair. As you said.
Let me know when
you're ready to start again.
Where is Prince Dev?
Sire, the lookout reported him flying
out on Targon before dawn.
Well, then. He shall miss
our triumph, hey men?
Let the wisdom of the ancients
guide our weapons!
And may the Norvagen
fall beneath them!
Forward, men!
For the riches of victory!
Something familiar... about this place.
There... there should be.
It's where... you and I first met...
eight years ago.
I remember... the ball
of flame... from the sky.
Yeah.
I always...
sort of wondered where that went.
I see... it scarred your face as well.
Have you noticed... anything else?
Like what?
Unusual things.
Things nobody can seem to explain.
You mean...
like that?
Or like that.
How do you like that, men?
My son was so eager for battle
he started without us!
Princess Kyra has joined
us for our victory!
Let us not disappoint her!
Attack all sides!
Target kings!
What is this?
The Draigar hire mercenaries
to do their fighting now?
They're not ours,
I assure you! Look!
Father!
Kyra!
Well, I'm sold.
These guys are not your buddies!
Quickly! Come with me
if you want to save your fathers!
Targon!
Aurora!
We have to go back! Now!
My dragon, my father,
Have no chance
if you don't come with me.
What were those creatures?
Vorgons.
The servants of a rogue dragon.
They ride Nogards, swamp dragons.
Well, they've got my father!
You have to go after them!
You have a more important
task ahead of you.
What's more important
than rescuing my father?
Hang on!
This is my home,
here on Dragon Mountain.
You made this?
Yeah, he's a wizard. Duh!
Ice is one of my
greatest powers.
A gift from the Queen Dragon.
All dragons have powers,
contained in those crystals
they wear around their necks.
The site where I just found you
was once the congress
for dragons and humans.
It was there they decided
how best to use these powers.
Each crystal has its own power.
This dragon's crystal, for instance,
allows me to see
into another's mind.
Looking into his
mind won't take long.
If it's a dragon's crystal,
how come you have it?
Many dragons entrusted me
with their crystals when they...
left this world.
As dragon ambassador,
I can use them as well.
Interesting.
I see that you are concerned
about your father and Targon.
Yeah, obviously. So can we...
That you intended
to kidnap princess Kyra
to force an end to the war.
Why, you cowardly creep!
Because you secretly long
for the war to be over,
so that the dragons will return.
Oh...
We're wasting time.
What I need is a crystal that will
help me rescue my father.
There is one.
The Aurathon.
The Aurathon?
Of legend?
It's powers are immense.
But right now the rogue has it.
This rogue.
You say he was the giant
fireball that knocked us
from the sky when we were kids?
By the time I arrived
on the scene he had vanished.
I've been looking
for him ever since.
And you think he was behind the attack?
Not think.
Know.
I recognize his tactics.
But where did he come from? And why?
He must have stolen the Aurathon
and used it to open the portal
from Dragon World.
But he was badly
injured in the process.
He's been in hiding ever since,
trying to heal before I find him.
Sounds like you two have issues.
We do.
Targon is injured!
Those ugly brutes
captured both the kings!
That a girl, Aurora.
The warm oil will speed the healing.
I still don't see why
you can't come with us.
The rogue knows that
my strength is ice.
He has taken refuge
in a cavern of fire.
With this and the Aurathon,
I cannot stand against him.
And we can?
You two are the best
warriors in your kingdoms.
Apparently that's not
what my father thinks.
Mine either.
Then do this!
Prove yourselves!
I don't know.
I've fought against plenty of Draigar.
But I've never fought
alongside one before.
I'd rather do this alone.
Afraid I'll show you up?
Now listen, stork...
Save it for the dragon, please.
And take these.
What are they?
Have you ever seen what happens
to a container full
of water in the snow?
Yeah.
It freezes... and explodes.
Exactly.
I have extracted that
explosive quality of ice
and filled these harpoons with it.
Really?
Cool!
Guys.
My scrying crystal
indicates that crevice
is your way in.
You'll have to get
past the Vorgan guards.
No problem.
Huh, lets go!
Remember!
Don't try to defeat the dragon!
Just get the Aurathon and get out!
Something about this feels bad.
These are starting to drip.
And I suspect we don't want
to be around when they melt.
Here, you get his attention.
I'll grab the Aurathon.
Hey, who said you're
giving the orders?
All right!
Where is he, anyway?
Consider his attention gotten!
Think fast!
One more!
I'm almost there!
The Aurathon!
It's not here!
No.
But you are!
Where are we?
I am not certain, but judging from
the temperature, I can guess.
Ah, yes?
And what does your
so-called Draigar wisdom tell you?
That I have been an even
bigger fool than you have!
We... we can hear you?
Of course.
Humans are not the only
ones who can communicate.
But Xenoz never
said anything about...
Xenoz!
That treacherous wizard's
words are nothing
but betrayal and deceit.
Is that why he sent you two
rather than his Vorgans?
His Vorgans?
He said they were yours!
You shall see soon enough
where their true allegiance lies.
But they have my father!
And mine!
That's why we were
after the Aurathon.
Xenoz told us...
Xenoz knew I had hidden it.
That's why he sent you
on this fool's errand.
He knew you would be captured...
he hoped that I would reveal
its hiding place to you.
Of course!
The scrying crystal!
Blast!
Gortaz! Attack!
So what... what are you
going to do with us?
Nothing... here.
We're about to have company.
These guys are definitely
not your buddies.
Release us! We can help you!
Nice work.
You mean, "for a Norvagen?"
What else would I mean?
Listen, lanky...
Stop it, both of you.
We are approaching
a sacred place.
Here?
Doesn't look like much.
It is the Ring of Oroborus.
Most sacred of all
the dragon temples.
Impossible!
The ring of Oroborus has been
abandoned for a thousand years!
The legends say it was magical,
that only the Dragon King
could open it.
Indeed?
I am the Dragon King.
And it is time you
faced your destiny!
You traitorous wizard!
These are dragon bones!
You are the one who has been
killing the remaining dragons!
Their crystals add to my power,
and besides, Vorgans need to eat.
That is inhuman!
I've done worse.
Of course, the Aurathon would be
the mightiest crystal of all.
Only Thoron knows where it is.
But since your blasted children
fought off my Vorgans,
I'm having a little
trouble locating him.
Well, good for them!
Both of them!
May our children bring you
a well-deserved defeat!
Oh, shut up.
When we gave Xenoz the power
to utilize the dragon crystals,
it was only because we felt
it would help bring
peace, shared wisdom
and knowledge between our worlds.
Little did we know how
such power would corrupt him.
Xenoz conspired with Stendahl,
an evil dragon whose
power was strength,
to slay my queen and
take her ice crystal.
This was the horrific
sight that greeted my eyes
when I arrived.
In my fury, I flamed them,
but it was not enough.
No wonder you went
back to the Dragon World.
Stendahl was imprisoned
for a thousand years.
But the vengeance in his
evil heart only grew.
When he was
finally released,
his first act was
to attack me again.
He and I almost
destroyed each other.
But in the battle,
the Aurathon was activated,
opening the portal
to this world.
I stopped him, but I was
hurled through myself.
And then you
bumped into us.
Literally.
And it was well that I did.
For I learned that
the traitor Xenoz still lived,
protected by the gift of immortality
we dragons bestowed upon him.
It was known he would
seek the Aurathon,
and I was too injured to fight him.
Into myself I absorbed the crystal,
and there divided it.
And thus, the great gem was hidden...
in two vessels,
which would soon be miles apart.
You mean the Aurathon's in us?
But how could you do such a thing?
I had little choice.
If Xenoz obtains the Aurathon,
he can open the portal.
Combined with his other
crystals of power,
no dragon or human will be
able to stand against him.
It would mean doom
for both our worlds.
So that explains these strange abilities of ours!
The Aurathon's powers are elemental.
Earth, wind, fire, water.
I gave you each the ability for one,
in the hopes it might help you survive.
It has, but we can't
really control them.
That is the role of Oroborus!
To unlock and
focus these powers!
Behold!
Yes!
Now this has potential...
You need to concentrate.
And as for you...
- relax.
The power is part of you.
Feel it, don't try to command it.
So... what made you choose us?
Targon and Aurora.
They saw in you
a unity of purpose...
a desire for peace,
even at the cost of yourselves.
This is greatness...
a greatness that may yet
save your kingdoms.
Or may not.
Oops.
The Ring of Oroborus!
They must be within! Gortaz!
Launch your squadron.
And take these.
Aurora? What is it, girl?
Aurora? Hey!
Ahh, that should do it, boy.
In a few weeks,
you'll be good as new.
No! Hold still!
You're not well yet
No!
I still don't see
what you're worried about.
You've got your strength back,
we can control our powers,
and Xenoz may not even
know we're here!
Well, two out of three, ain't bad!
Quickly! On my back!
I've got this!
We have to get
out of here, now!
Look! It's Targon!
And Aurora!
Kill the dragons!
Thank you!
Thank you, both of you!
We'll take it from here!
Temper your confidence.
Xenoz is certain to have
prepared for our arrival.
What? Your foolhardy children
think to challenge me?
Our children?
Both of them?
- Together!
What a team they'll make!
A short-lived one, I promise you.
To your posts!
Ice!
Hear me!
Rise and do my bidding!
Ice dragons.
Can you take them?
Not with you two on my back.
Then just get us over the castle!
We'll take it from there!
What do ya say, Draigar,
are you ready?
After you, Norvagen!
Feel the icy rage of
my wrath, Dragon King!
I shall...
Destroy them!
What?
How do you have such powers?
That's for us to know...
And you to find out!
And find out I shall!
Now, let us see what
is in your minds...
Of course!
The Aurathon!
Divided in two,
and under my nose this whole time!
Very clever, Thoron...
but not clever enough!
You monster!
The Aurathon.
Greatest of all the dragon crystals!
And it is mine!
Xenoz?
My queen...
Gortaz,
thanks...
for the hand...
What the?
That's right, this is
the work of Thoron!
The dragons gave me immortality,
but I could not heal,
and for this,
I shall have my revenge!
Let the portal to the
Dragon World be opened!
No!
Too late, Thoron!
You were a fool to let these children
retain the Aurathon!
Now you cannot defeat me
and they are helpless!
Are they?
You question me?
I, who for a thousand years
have manipulated their
ancestors like puppets?
I took their dragons
and they blamed each
other, as I intended.
I know how they think,
I know how they feel,
I know what they can do.
They are but weak humans
and they can do nothing!
I beg to differ, traitor.
They are Prince Dev
and Princess Kyra
and they have been chosen
by the dragons themselves!
Behold!
What?
No! Give it to me!
You got it!
The ice castle!
It's coming down!
Then lets get off of here.
Now!
May the peace and
trust they brought us
last a thousand years and more!
To Prince Dev and princess Kyra!
Hail Princess Kyra!
Well, what are we gonna do now?
My whole life has been
fighting the Draigar.
Is there anything else?
I guess that's what
we're going to find out.
Still, Xenoz told the
truth about one thing...
Your wish
about the legend?
Laugh if you want,
but I always dreamed that someday,
if the dragons came back,
this is the place
where I'd see it.
You mean like that?
The dragons are
returning! The legend!
It's true!
To peace!
To us!
To dragons forever!
This is not over!
Please rate this subtitle at www.osdb.link/ck75
Help other users to choose the best subtitles