Once upon a time,
in an obscure corner of the earth,
there was a teeny-tiny encounter.
And so began the long, long
adventure and days spent in combat
involving Son Goku and his friends,
and revolving around the Dragon Balls.
Battles against foes who
were mesmerized by Shen Long,
who would grant any wish...
Hit the mark!
A furious fight against Piccolo,
which ended in vengeance...
You lose!
The matchup against Vegeta,
with the survival of humanity at stake...
You dumb-ass!
The battle with Freeza on Planet Namek...
The Artificial Humans and the Cell Games...
See you in hell!
Now!
The final showdown with Majin Boo...
As one after another powerful enemies appear,
the Super Saiyan Goku,
together with his growing sons,
Gohan and Goten, and his other friends,
save the earth from its tight spots,
and before anyone knows it,
peace returns to earth.
However...
Have you sensed it, too, Kaioshin?
Yes. He certainly is
awake early this time, isn't he?
My word, peace truly is short-lived.
And after they just created the world anew, too.
I would think that Kaio
and the others sense it, too,
but tell him to be on the lookout, just in case.
Mm-hmm. All right.
Yes, Kaioshin-sama.
Yes, yes...
Yes, I have noticed it, too.
Hey! Be quiet, Goku! I'm trying to talk here!
Goku? Do you mean, Son Goku-san is there?
Y-Yes.
He is here on my world to train.
We cannot allow him to become aware of this.
He is sure to take an interest.
Yes, of course, where Beers-sama is concerned...
G-Goodbye, then...
What about Beers-sama?
G-Goku!
Huh? Is that the name of some candy?
Y-You found me out, huh?
It is a most delicious candy.
Well of course it ain't!
Kaio-sama, you were talking
like you were pretty freaked out.
It's something you don't need to know about.
Oh, if you tell me that,
I'm just gonna ask you even more!
There's no way I'm telling.
You were speaking to Kaioshin-sama, right?
Maybe I'll go ask him directly.
All right! All right! Don't go
using your Instantaneous Movement!
Don't tell Kaioshin-sama
that you heard this from me.
There are deities in this
world that create planets and life,
such as Kaioshin-sama.
And, conversely,
there are also deities
who destroy planets and life.
So then,
this Beers-sama is one of them?
That is correct. Beers the Destroyer.
Huh? He's a deity, but he's still a destroyer?
Birth and destruction.
They're needed in order to
maintain balance in the world.
I wonder how many worlds
will fall victim this time.
My goodness...
...Beers the Destroyer is awakening, is he?
We won't know peace for some time, huh?
Why have you changed into your gi?
This Beers-sama guy is pretty strong, right?
Don't tell me you're...
I can't wait to see how strong he is!
Y-You idiot!
What?!
You just don't get it! Beers-sama's strength
is on a completely different level than you are!
He's Beers-sama, the
greatest destroyer in the world!
He's such a capricious
destroyer that even Kaioshin-sama
would be scared to come face-to-face with him,
and maybe pee his pants
a little bit, he's so terrifying!
The part where he's the strongest
in the world has me fascinated!
Please wake up, Beers-sama.
You must not fall back asleep again.
You are the one who set your
alarm bomb yourself, aren't you?
If you don't get up soon,
your backup alarms will--
All right... all right.
I won't have you sleeping in
for 15 years, like you did last time.
If you insist on not getting up...
...would you like me to perform
my waking-up song for you again?
Well then...
A-All right!
All right.
I only slept 39 years this time.
That's no more than a catnap.
Beers-sama, you are the
one who set your wake-up time.
Incidentally, why did you choose this time?
There's something that I was curious about.
Well, I have prepared your bath.
Please go take it.
No way. I hate baths.
You are covered in bomb soot.
It could contain mold.
Come on!
What if I say no?
Someone will say "Beers the Destroyer
is amazing, but pee-yew!"
and word will spread around.
Whis, I'm tired of your unfunny jokes.
I'll destroy you.
By the way, Whis, while I was asleep,
did Freeza leave Planet Vegeta destroyed for me?
Yes, without a trace.
Oh, yeah? I could have given
the folks on that planet an eternity,
but they'd still be nothing but trouble.
And that King Vegeta was especially hard-fisted.
I would have been happy to destroy them, too,
but their world is so far away,
you know? It was too much trouble.
I have to admit, though,
Freeza is a bad apple, too.
He's so self-important. The next time I see him,
I think I might destroy him, too.
There won't be any need for that.
Freeza has been defeated.
Eh?
You mean there's someone that can defeat Freeza?
One moment, please.
Huh? It seems like I've
seen this somewhere before.
Who is this guy?
A Saiyan.
He appears to be called
both Son Goku and Kakarrot.
I thought all the Saiyans died in
the destruction of Planet Vegeta.
Most of them did perish,
but some who happened to
be on other worlds were spared.
And by the way, Prince Vegeta was one of them.
Isn't Saiyan hair supposed to be black?
I have to say, I'm surprised
a Saiyan could defeat Freeza.
At this point, the Saiyans
have acquired a technique
whereby they become
what they call "Super Saiyans."
What's that?
Super Saiyan? Super Saiyan?
Super Saiyan?!
That's it.
That's what it was!
What what was?
Let's see... Super Saiyan... Super Saiyan...
n-God!
I dreamed about it!
A dream where I fought against
a Super Saiyan God, like this guy!
Uh-huh.
You still don't get it?
It was a premonition. Premonition!
You mean, your dream?
Beers-sama, your premonitions
don't have all that high
an accuracy rate, do they?
That dream you had earlier
about that idol moving here
didn't come true, did it?
You're making fun of me, huh?
All right, come with me, Whis.
Seer! Seer, are you here?
I was taking a walk. What is it?
You told me 39 years ago, didn't you,
that in 39 years, an arch-rival would appear?
Did I say that?
You said so, didn't you?
Okay, I did.
See?
The Seer's prophecy and my premonition--
An arch-rival of mine is going to appear.
A Super Saiyan God!
It sounds entirely questionable to me.
It's hard to imagine an arch-rival
for you to begin with, Beers-sama.
Well, even if the arch-rival that the
Seer mentioned is an exaggeration,
someone fascinating is bound to appear, right?
That's why I woke up early this time.
I see. So that's why.
So, are you going to go see the Saiyans?
Of course I am.
I have to find this "Super Saiyan God."
Super Saiyan God, you say?
Such over-the-top naming.
It ends up sounding tawdry.
I found them. Most of the surviving Saiyans,
five of them, are in 4032 Green, on
Planet 877, living on a world called "earth."
Earth? I'm sure I've been
to that planet once, long ago.
That's the planet which
had something called dinosaurs,
which took a rude attitude toward me,
so I exterminated them, right?
However, one of them,
the Saiyan that defeated Freeza,
currently appears to be
on Kaio of the North's world.
A Saiyan at a Kaio's place?
That sounds suspicious.
Whis, how long will it take to get there?
Roughly 26 minutes.
About the length of an episode of TV anime, huh?
Sure is far!
Well, what choice is there?
I'll suck it up and go.
All right, then, let's be off!
To the Kaio of the North's world!
Yeah!
Bulma-san, happy---
...birthday!
Eh?! He's not coming?!
Why is he training at
Kaio-sama's place at a time like this?
That's the kind of guy he is.
Geez, I told him about this over six months ago!
Huh? Where's Vegeta-san?
Looks like he's training.
Honest to goodness, you Saiyans...
He)', you there!
Eh?
Don't just sit around, bring me another drink.
I'll give you an autograph afterward.
All right, what kind of drink would you like?
Mister Satan, this gentleman
is Bulma-san's father, Dr. Briefs.
Th-The greatest genius in the world?
Not to mention the richest man in the world.
Oh, sweetheart, you're
the richest man in the world?
Huh, I'm not too sure of that, myself.
H-How terribly rude of me!
By the way, what kind of drink would you like?
D-Don't be absurd!
I will bring you something to drink!
What can I get for you?
Huh? I'm fine right now.
Oh, not at all! What would you like to drink?
Okay, a cola.
A cola! Right, as you wish!
I will bring you a whole case, right now!
Ah, geez, Papa. How embarrassing.
I put it on to look dashin' comin'
to Bulma-san's birthday party.
By the way, Bulma-san, just how
old have you turned this birthday?
How rude! As though I'd tell you!
It's true that the prizes
for the bingo tournament
include a castle and an airplane, right?
That's right. If that's too much
trouble, I can convert it to cash.
That's the richest person in the world for you!
I wonder if Goku-sa will drop in
for at least the bingo tournament.
Bulma, are there any
X-rated DVDs among the prizes?
No!
O-Oh, no!
Wh-What is it, Goku?!
Today is Bulma's birthday party!
This ain't good! She'll be mad at me!
Oh. Don't startle me over something like that!
She's scary. Probably...
It would be a close contest
between her and this Destroyer guy.
Kaio-sama?
Goku!
Th-This is serious! Here! Right here!
Huh?! Bulma is coming here?!
No!
Beers-sama is!
Beers the Destroyer is on his way here!
Huh? Eh?
I ain't sensing anything.
You can't sense the presence of deities!
Remember, whatever you do,
refrain from doing anything stupid.
It will be fine, I tell you.
All right!
You worry me.
Goku, go hide inside the house!
Huh? What for?
Quickly!
And quickly, too. Geez...
Hurry!
Okay, O kaY!
Why, though? Why is Beers-sama coming here?
Why, indeed?
Wh-Why, Beers-sama...
Him, huh?
He sure looks like he
ain't just anyone, all right?
...w-welcome to my...
...humble place. Thank you
for coming... all this way...
Long time no see, huh?
Kaio of the North...
Huh? Oh! That guy's the
one they call Beers-sama?
I must say... your world...
...is small, huh?
Eh? Y-Yes... I'm terribly sorry.
Please excuse the cramped fit.
Long ago, Beers-sama
destroyed it, making it smaller--
taking it out after losing at hide-and-seek.
Oh, did I?
However, considering that
you restored your world earlier,
and you did not bring
it back to its original size,
you must prefer it to be this size, don't you?
Anyhow...
Beers-sama, what brings you here?
Ah, I have a little business
with the Saiyan inside.
Yikes!
Come on out here!
H-How terribly impolite of me!
Goku! Come say hello to Beers-sama!
Heya! I'm Go--
I was certain you were going to say that!
You're old enough to know better!
At least offer a proper greeting!
Uh, wh-why, hello there. I'm... I mean...
My name is Son Goku.
It's honorable to meet you, Sir.
Good morning. Now then,
I have something I want to ask you.
Let's see... Super...
Super Saiyan God.
Yes, yes.
Do you know of the existence
of this "Super Saiyan God"?
Super Saiyan God?
I know of just plain "Super Saiyans,"
but I ain't ever heard of that "God" business.
I haven't heard of it, Sir.
This is the first time I have heard
the term "Super Saiyan God," myself.
Ah, I see.
I heard from Whis, here, that
you're the one who defeated Freeza?
Freeza? Yeah, I defeated him, all right. Sir.
It doesn't appear to me like
you could defeat him as you are,
but I understand you transform and power up--
into what's called a Super Saiyan.
That is correct. You are well informed.
But you don't know about the God thing.
Whis...
...is Prince Vegeta, on the planet
called earth, also a Super Saiyan?
Yes. And each of the three others
also seem to be able to transform.
You know that much, as well?
All of them, huh?
That seems suspicious. Well then...
I wonder if I can find
anything by going to earth.
B-Beers-sama, I do not think
the other Saiyans know, either.
I won't know unless I ask them, will I?
Whis, how long to reach earth?
Roughly three minutes.
Three minutes? All right, then.
Well, I think I'm going to go see this "earth."
Um...
You're not going to destroy it,
or anything, right?
As long as nothing happens to annoy me.
Hey, listen!
Ain't you--I mean, Beers-sama,
I heard you were ridiculously strong.
Would you mind showing
me just a little of it? Sir?
You want to see my power? How?
I'd like to have a sparring
match with you, if only for a minute!
Goku! That's enough!
I have lived a long time,
but I've never heard a
request as unique as that one.
You certainly seem sure of yourself.
Or could it be that you're simply
just a big dummy, instead?
Yes, he's a big dummy!
He is just a big dummy, you see!
Sure.
Okay, come at me with your full power.
Thank you! I mean, thank you very much!
But are you sure you want my
full power right from the start?
If you get hurt, don't go getting
upset and destroying this planet.
You have my promise.
Well, go ahead.
Okay -
First, this is "Super Saiyan."
And this is "Super Saiyan 2."
And this is the mighty "Super Saiyan 3"!
Run for it, Bubbles!
Well, well, this is a surprise.
It appears that this isn't
just a bunch of hot air, after all.
Heh-heh, you see?
If you want, I can go back to "2" for you.
No, no, as you are will be fine.
Okay, begin.
You're looking down on me. All right...!
Well then, let's be off.
Okay -
See you later, Kaio of the North.
Are you still alive, you big dummy?
Oh, right! I can't just sit around.
I have to contact Vegeta as soon as possible!
Vegeta! It's Kaio!
What do you want with me, Kaio?
Listen closely to what I'm about to say.
Beers the Destroyer will be there very soon.
The Destroyer?
I've heard that name before.
In any case, once Beers-sama arrives there,
do absolutely, absolutely nothing to engage him!
Otherwise, it will mean the
annihilation of the earth itself.
The earth will be annihilated?
Goku couldn't leave well
enough alone, and was easily beaten.
He was what?! Kakarrot?!
Super Saiyan 3 Goku was left
barely breathing after just two blows.
Just two blows, you say?
I'm begging you.
The fate of the earth rests with you.
That really was awesome.
Imagine, there being someone like that...
I warned you, over and over!
Just be grateful you weren't killed!
To get any stronger,
there ain't no choice but to
merge with Vegeta, is there? No...
...even at that, I doubt I could beat him.
Let's hope the people on
earth don't do anything foolish.
He said something about
"Super Saiyan God," didn't he?
Is that something I can arrive at with training?
Or is it the name of a Saiyan
called "God"? ls there another...?
A senzu bean?
I'm better!
Kaio-sama, we have to
let everyone on earth know!
I've already told Vegeta.
He's the one most likely
to step over the line, after all.
Things ain't looking good.
I'd better get back to earth right away.
Or maybe I should train a bit first.
You're finally here, huh, Vegeta?
Oh, and why are you wearing your combat gear
to your own wife's birthday party?
What's wrong? You seem unusually blue.
A-ha, could it be that you're in shock over
your beloved wife turning another year older?
It sure is nice for you Saiyans,
not having to grow older.
Silence!
What do you mean, "silence"?! Hmph!
What is this? I've got a knot in my stomach.
Is the great Vegeta-sama trembling with fear?
What is with you?
Beers the Destroyer...
Without a doubt, I know
I've met him somewhere before...
Hey, Prince Vegeta, right?
You're all grown up now, aren't you?
It looks like this "Ki" that you
all use doesn't work on deities.
Ah, yes, well...
Something's come over Vegeta.
Do you remember me now?
I remember!
When we previously met,
you were still just a little boy, huh?
Don't you remember? Your father, King Vegeta,
put on quite a spread for me.
The Destroyer, Beers...
...-sama...
What Kaio said was no exaggeration.
This guy is trouble. He's way beyond trouble!
It looks to me like you're up
to something enjoyable here.
What's more, I smell something very good.
A-Ah, this? My wife is having a birthday party.
Your wife? Well, I'll have
to go pay my respects.
Beers-sama...
Oh, right. The point of my visit...
Have you ever heard the term "Super Saiyan God"?
Super Saiyan God?
You don't know it, then?
Are you sure your premonition wasn't wrong?
I'm never wrong!
But you are, quite often.
I'm starting to get annoyed.
Oh, Vegeta, the man who
tells his wife to be silent...
Who have we here?
O-Oh, th-this is...
...Beers-san and...
The name is Whis.
Oh, friends of yours?
Hello. I'm Bulma, Vegeta's...
...beautiful wife.
--Hello, Bulma-san.
Oh, my! For being friends of yours,
they have fine manners.
But you don't appear to be from earth.
You're aliens, right? Aliens?
Th-That's enough!
We just happened to drop by earth,
and spotted Vegeta-kun here.
Sightseeing? If you'd like,
why not come party with us, first?
You're quite welcome.
H-Hey!
Well, I do hate to intrude...
...but the truth is, I spotted some of the most
delicious-looking food when I first got here.
Go ahead, go ahead.
C-Come, let's go down there.
Hey! You there, the cat monster!
How'd you like a match with me?
A match?
Th-That idiot!
I'm pretty good!
Oh, Dad, you're embarrassing us!
I apologize for his rudeness.
Where are the Dragon Balls?!
You idiots! If you make any
loud noises, they'll hear us!
R-Right!
All right...
This house is ridiculously huge,
for crying out loud!
Pesky fools!
We' re sorry.
Sheesh!
Just where are the Dragon Balls, anyway?
All seven of them are
supposed to be together here.
I don't know why I can't get my wish granted,
but right now, we're in luck!
My next goal is to be hugely wealthy!
Huh?
L-it's not world domination?
Getting a great deal of money comes first.
I've had enough of living the poor life.
We couldn't even get hired for part-time work
in these child-like bodies we have, you know!
--Y-Yes...
--Well...
I am Great King Pilaf!
Earlier, when we were
finally about to get Shen Long
to grant our wish, Pilaf-sama,
you said "Make us young again!"
Y-Yeah, but...
...there's no point in dominating
the world when we're old,
if we're going to drop dead right away.
Maybe so, but we're too young like this!
It was a relief for me.
My life has been greatly extended, in dog years.
Stop your griping and hurry up
and find the Dragon Balls!
And if worse comes to worst,
let's just grab anything of value!
--Yes, Sir!
Okay!
"Prizes"
O-Over here...
What is it?
"Bingo Tournament Prizes-Keep Out!"
You don't suppose...
...all of these...
...are prizes?!
That castle is a prize!
--Wow!
--Damn it, what a ritzy bunch!
I'll spray graffiti on them!
"Stupid"
Take that! And that! And that!
I.
That's quite sordid.
--Come on!
--Let's hurry!
Yeah! The Dragon Balls must be
hidden here someplace! Find them!
--Yes, sir!
You don't think they're
inside the castle, do you?
Pilaf-sama!
Did you find them?!
The participation prize is a
ten-year assortment of fine hams!
Get two or three boxes!
Yahoo!
The second-place prize is...
What a ridiculously huge diamond!
Be sure to take it!
But if this is the second-place prize...
First-place must be...
We sure found them easily enough.
Pilaf-sama!
Th-There really are all seven of them here!
--Yahoo! Yahoo!
--Banzai! Banzai!
Pilaf-sama, let's get our
wish granted right now!
You fool!
If we summon Shen Long in here,
the ceiling will collapse on us!
Hey, you guys!
What are you doing in there?
W-We're friends of the boy who lives here.
Huh? My friends?
Y-You're the boy who lives here?!
That monkey is talking!
--Mon--
Who are you calling a monkey?!
I am Great King Pilaf!
We came here to burgle the place!
What's the big idea, giving them your real name?
Hey, Goten! Come over here and
see this! There's a funny monkey!
I'm not a monkey!
Hmm?
Hey, boy! Be quiet! Do you want to get hurt?!
What?
Look.
Th-That distinctive hairstyle...
It looks extremely familiar...
Those blank eyes that reveal such innocence!
They look extremely familiar...
H-He's that...
"Genuine great ape!
Clear out!
Right!
You can have this.
Pilaf-sama! Wait for me!
Wow, that really was one
strange monkey and dog, huh?
Mm-hmm.
Hey, who was that girl who gave
you the pretty rock as a present?
Is she your friend, Trunks-kun?
She's... my girlfriend.
What do you think? Amazing, huh?
You mean, you're going out with her?
W-Well, yeah. We've even held hands.
That's amazing!
Y-Yeah, I guess.
Amazing.
Damn! What is he doing here?!
He's still a child, too!
And thanks to him, we didn't
get the Dragon Balls, did we?!
What?! You're creeping me out!
Prepare to feast your eyes... on this!
I used the diamond to distract their gaze.
They haven't realized that the
Si Xing Qiu ball has been stolen.
You've outdone yourself, Mai!
Yes!
Just a minute! We can't grant
our wish with just one of them.
Don't you worry about that, Pilaf-sama.
We'll say, "if you want this back,
hand over one million zeni,"
and demand their money!
Oh, I get it!
Mai, you're a genius! You big-time rascal!
Oh, no, not as much as you are, Pilaf-sama.
But that diamond was worth
more than ten billion zeni, wasn't it?
U-Um...
Y-You idiot! That huge
amount of money just means
that much more stress, doesn't it?
Y-Yeah! If we get so
nervous that we pee our pants,
are you offering to wash them for us?!
Huh?
Eh?
Ahem...
I'm not so sure about that example.
It seemed to be a little bit off-color.
I beg your pardon.
Hmm? Isn't that...?!
It's him! What is he saying?!
That girl over there is your girlfriend, Trunks?
I don't know who you take after,
but you're quite the stud,
aren't you? Nice going!
Amazing, huh?
Y-Yeah, I guess.
Call her over here for me.
Yo'.!
My good lad! You just flew
through the air to get here!
Never mind about that, I...
...was trying to act cool, and
said that you were my girlfriend.
You said I was...?
N“ you'.!
Then, me?
Why would I?! This girl here!
Who, me?! Me, with a little boy like you...?
You're a little girl, yourself, aren't you?
Oh, right.
I hate to ask, but pretend
to be my girlfriend for a while.
P-Pretend to be your girlfriend?
What do I have to do?
Well, we hold hands... and stuff...
H-Hands?!
The children these days are so depraved!
You're free to eat all the food you want, too.
Food?!
And there's a bingo tournament, too!
Absolutely!
Come on!
Just a moment.
Pilaf-sama, I know he is a child,
but holding hands with a boy
on the very same day
I met him is something I can't...
You're actually more than
old enough for this, aren't you?
Pilaf-sama, there are some things
you can say, and some you can't!
Do it, Mai! For the food and
the bingo tournament! As well as...
...the Dragon Balls it comes with.
I've seen that older lady somewhere before...
I-it was back then!
Yes, that is her, all right!
That kid earlier and the one
who was with them back then...
I'm getting nothing but bad feelings about this!
Come on, let's go.
R-Right!
These "takoyaki" balls are fascinating.
They are quite delicious.
Both the sauce flavor and
soy sauce flavors are fantastic.
So your name is Mai-chan?
Mai-chan, how old are you?
41.
You shouldn't tease the grown-ups!
Ka...
...ha...
Please don't wreck anything else.
Hal!
This is crazy!
It's no use. I can't beat
the Destroyer like this.
Beers-sama was much, much stronger.
Hey, Kaio-sama!
It looks like a quick bit of
training ain't gonna be enough
to reach this Super Saiyan God thing.
I have to admit, I'm not seeing
any sign of this Super Saiyan God.
I was kind of looking forward to it.
From what I hear, as far as the Saiyans go,
aside from Son Goku and Vegeta,
the others are all half-earthling.
And two of them are still just children.
Okay, next up is everyone's
favorite, the bingo tournament!
While the castle and the
airplane are both terrific prizes,
the main attraction has to be...
Look at this! All seven Dragon Balls together!
If you win, you can have
whatever wish you want granted!
Oh? Those balls are a lot like
Planet Namek's wish orbs, huh?
--Earth's Kami does appear to be a
Namekian, after all. --All right!
As I recall, a dragon
appears from the wish orbs,
and grants any wish they want, right?
H-Hey, just a minute!
Aren't you one Dragon Ball short?
The Si Xing Qiu ball is gone!
No way! They were all there a little while ago!
Hey, are you leaving already?
Mai-chan, tell me what
your cell phone number is!
I don't have anything so fancy!
Hold on!
You idiot!
O-Oh, no, I fell into their trap.
You're the one who cried out, you know.
At this point, there's little choice left.
Damn it!
P-Pilaf-sama!
H-Hey, all of you! If you
don't want this kid to get killed,
you'll hand over one million zeni!
Well, 100,000 zeni will be okay, too.
Wh-What's so funny? I really will kill him!
That child says she will kill him,
yet the others are laughing.
Maybe they need some punishment.
N-No! That girl is apparently
my son's girlfriend, after all!
This is just a silly game.
I really, really, really mean it!
U-Um, Mai-chan...
No talking, hostage!
Your chest is touching me.
Oh, this is an entertaining side show, isn't it?
All right, I'll play along!
You adorable little villains!
The Great Saiyaman does not stand for bad guys!
--Yeah! Yeah!
--Way to go!
Seems fishy. By any chance,
is that the Super Saiyan God?
P-Please, do not get the wrong idea!
That is just Kakarrot's son,
dressed up in a disguise!
Young lady, go ahead and try to shoot me!
Th-That's crazy!
S-Stay back!
It really is okay for you to shoot me.
I think that will liven things up a bit more.
I know! While you're at it,
shoot all your bullets at once at me!
Mm-hmm, that will be great!
A-All of them?
It's no problem.
He can deflect all of them away.
But don't shoot at my feet or anything.
Let's keep it simple.
Aim right for the face, okay?
Okay, villains! Shoot as much as you like!
Okay, but you asked for it!
How do you like that, you villains?!
Do you now realize the
power of the Great Saiyaman?!
That's not like him. He's not
accustomed to drinking so much.
You guys, I thought that was just a toy,
but it's a real gun, isn't it?
You children shouldn't be
carrying something like that.
If it hadn't been me, this
could have been really serious.
Ee-yow!
Videl! Videl, are you okay?
Videl-san!
Gohan! What's the big idea,
hittin' your own wife?
L-I'm so sorry!
Here, let me have a look.
Can you heal her, Turtle Hermit-san?
I'll give her mouth-to-mouth--
That has nothing to do with an injured leg!
You haven't changed at all, you dirty old man!
N-Neither have you! How could
you do that to a great sage?!
Allow me to heal her.
Wh-What do you think you're doing?
You should watch what you say.
This person is Kami-sama.
K-Kami-sama? You don't mean, for real?
Are you really Kami-sama?
It's better.
Thank you very much, Kami-sama.
Um, your tummy is carrying...
Shh! It's still a secret.
Oh, it is?
Gohan, no more drinkin'
alcohol for you for a while! Got it?!
Y-Yes. Thank you, Dende--I mean, Kami-sama.
This is a dream, right? A dream.
But I thought we were
dreaming before, and it was all real.
By any chance, can you deflect bullets, too?
Of course I can. You knew that
when you started the act, right?
And you there, the dog,
you can't just stand there in a daze.
You have to hurry up and come slashing at me!
S-Sorry.
And monkey, your intensity
leaves a lot to be desired!
What a shame. It could have gone over better.
We'll try harder next time.
Wh-What did you think?
That was an entertaining show, right?
One of them came flying at me, too.
It feels a bit itchy.
Unpleasant. Very unpleasant.
So then, will you destroy the earth?
It might be best to renew
the whole planet at once.
Before Creation cometh Destruction.
Hey, come on, you guys!
That's all for the side show!
Now, let the fun of the bingo tournament begin!
P Bingo! P
What's come over Vegeta?
P Fun time bingo! P
P Earth is a fun place to be! P
P The food 'vs good there, too'. P
P Fun time bingo! P
P Fun time bingo! Yeah! P
That was somewhat engaging, huh?
Yeah. I never figured him to
be such a poor singer and dancer.
He could give your songs
a run for their money, Whis.
I'm sorry to hear that.
Well, let's collect ourselves
by getting some more food.
Yeah, all right.
Okay, that was good.
All right, children, that Ball isn't a toy.
You can't go carrying it
around without asking first.
But your little skit was
kind of entertaining. Thank you.
Okay, the Dragon Balls are all back together,
so let's start playing bingo!
I sacrificed my pride to preserve
Beers' mood, so things managed to work out.
But it shouldn't be an issue anymore.
All that's left now is to get him to
leave earth while he's still in a good mood.
Is anyone one spot away from bingo yet?
Beers-sama...
Have you tried that
dessert they call "pudding" yet?
It truly is velvety-smooth and delicious.
What's that? Pudding, you say?
Where exactly is it?
Over there.
Oh my, it was here just a moment ago.
Don't tell me you ate them all, Whis.
Indeed not!
You there, is there any more pudding?
L-I'm sorry, but the pudding
over there is the last of it.
You there... Would you mind
sharing one of those with me?
Make that two--one for me.
If not, at least let us have one, for me.
Beers-sama, that's not fair.
You've already had one, right?
Hand it over.
Boo! No way!
What?!
I'm eating them all myself!
But there are so many of them!
All of them are mine!
Give me one!
No!
Give me one, you dummy!
You called me a dummy.
I'm gonna turn you to candy and eat'cha!
Oh, no! I look away for one second, and...!
Now I'm completely upset!
Hey!
What did you do that for?!
Beers-sama! Please stop!
S-Stop him!
Ten-san'.!
He's out of this world!
Kuririn-san, get the others out of here!
Y-Yeah...
Are you all right?
Goten! Get her two friends!
Uh-huh!
You wouldn't give me any pudding,
so I'm gonna hurt you some more.
Stop!
Damn it! It doesn't matter anymore!
This way, Beers!
Thanks for waiting.
Ho! This tastes absolutely delicious!
What do you call this food?
Huh? O-Oh, it's called sushi.
Oh, yum.
He beat Vegeta in the blink of an eye!
Mai, wait here a minute.
Goten!
I know!
Fu--
--$ion! Ha!
Yay!
G-Goten has gone and turned delinquent again!
His fighting senses, at least, are pretty good.
Hey, you! The cat-person!
Cause a big ruckus over pudding, will you?!
Anyone who has manners that
bad gets their butt kicked by Gotenks!
What did you say?
You earthlings are probably
accustomed to eating it,
but for me, it's an unknown food,
whose flavor I can't even guess!
Pudding! Even the naming
makes it sound delicious, doesn't it?!
Y-You hush!
Don't! You're no match for him!
Ow! Ow!
I'm sorry'.
I imagined that you'd be beyond the pale,
but I never thought our
levels would be this far removed.
Damn, the end is finally here.
You run out of pudding,
and the Super Saiyan God isn't here.
I guess it's time for destruction.
Hmph, it might be an honor to be
eliminated by Beers the Destroyer.
Oh, well isn't that a nice thing to say?
All right then, as you wish...
Hey, that's enough of that already!
I don't care if you're a
friend of Vegeta's or not,
but you've turned my 38th
birthday upside-down, you know!
38th, is it?
H-How dare you... hit my... Bulma!!
You filthy bastard!
This is incredible!
I think Vegeta has finally
surpassed Goku, hasn't he?
Take this!
Wh-What's that?
Are they launching off extra-large
fireworks at the Capsule Corporation again?
Well?
Sure enough, that doesn't seem
to be Super Saiyan God, either.
Enough, already. I'm going to
destroy the earth and head back.
Whis!
Just a moment!
So it's a sea urchin battleship roll?
This is quite delicious, too.
L-I won't let you do it!
You're always "destroy this," "destroy that"!
Let it go. I told you, it's already over.
Vegeta!
Whis, I say!
You called, Beers-sama?
It looks like this Super Saiyan
God is just a pointless dream,
like you said it was.
And I'll say it again! I'm gonna
destroy the earth and head back!
As you wish. But could you
please wait a little while longer?
H-How is the tuna roll?
Fantastic!
Incidentally, I don't seem
to have very much time.
Could you wrap some of this up to go?
Um, the earth is, I suppose,
enjoyable in some aspects,
so I will give you one last chance.
You, over there!
Yes, you there! You!
M-Me?
Yes. You, the tasty-looking one.
H-He's gonna eat me!
Come over here.
L-I'm yucky! I taste incredibly yucky!
Rock-paper-scissors with me,
and if you win, I will leave.
But if I win, I will destroy the earth.
R-Rock-paper-scissors?
Destroy the earth?
No way! I'm lousy at rock-paper-scissors!
The fate of the earth has been entrusted to you!
This is your first big role, isn't it?
If you lose, you're to blame.
P-Pu-erh, I'll get you!
Ah! So that's it! Hey, I get it!
I know why you're the one he picked, Oolong!
He thinks that you're just an ordinary pig!
And as a pig, he thinks
you can only throw scissors!
However, you're a pig-man!
He doesn't realize you can
also throw rock and paper!
He's sure to throw rock,
so Oolong, if you throw paper, you'll win!
L-I get it! A-All right! L-Let's do this!
Are you ready yet?
Y-Yeah!
All right...
--Rock-paper-scissors!
Fools! I heard your whole strategy.
Wait!
Goku!
Goku-sa!
Son-kun'.!
You, again? What do you want?
Did you get a handle on
what this "God" thing is?
That's still a mystery,
but don't destroy this planet.
I am a god of destruction.
I know that, Beers-sama.
But just this once, give us a pass.
And do what? Are you going to fight me again?
I'd like to say I will,
but you've got me in a bind.
To be honest, no matter what I do,
I ain't gonna be able to beat--
That's it!
Beers-sama, is it okay if
I try my luck at something?
For what?
You know, that Super Saiyan God thing.
There just might be a chance of getting one!
How so?
Would you give me just a little
bit of time? Just a little? Okay?
Please!
Very well. But just a little.
Thank you!
Bulma! I'm gonna have to use the Dragon Balls!
That's fine. If it's going to put
that dumb rude jerk in his place,
then use them all you want!
That's a spiteful thing to say.
The man is a deity!
Huh? A deity?
Yeah.
So? If you're a deity,
then don't go pitching fits
over something like pudding, you dummy!
He's no ordinary deity.
He's a god of destruction,
the most terrible kind in the world.
His name is Beers-sama.
He's the strongest guy in the universe.
Strong enough that he scares the
crap out of Kaio-sama and Kaioshin-sama.
Everyone, please mind your manner of speech.
If you happen to offend Beers-sama,
you will be destroyed, along
with the entire solar system.
B-Beers-sama!
S-Stop that! It has the opposite
effect with middle-aged women!
“Shut up!
“OW!
Goku, what are you going
to do with the Dragon Balls?!
Come forth, Shen Long! And grant me my wish!
So that's it! You're thinking
of having Shen Long
put a stop to the destruction of the earth!
Nope.
That would be too much for him.
The Capsule Corporation, huh?
Rich people have the wildest attractions, huh?
I shall grant thee any wish. Now, speak!
Listen, Shen Long...
Um... do you know what a Super Saiyan God is?
Huh? What's that?
Ho, that's the same
question that I was going to ask.
Yeah, I do know.
Huh? You know it? Really?
Really. ls your wish
whether or not I really know?
No. no, no, no, no.
If you know, then could
you bring one here for us?
I cannot bring one, for one does not exist.
Super Saiyan God is a deity
that can only be formed by Saiyans temporarily.
What do you mean by that?
You are asking many questions.
What exactly is your wish?
Beers-sama says to produce a Super Saiyan God.
Hm? Ah, B-Beers-sama?!
Why, it is Beers-sama! Pleased to meet you!
Tell them how to form a Super Saiyan God.
Er, right!
I've never seen Shen Long like this.
A Super Saiyan God is a savior,
created by chance by a
handful of righteous Saiyans,
who long ago questioned the
evil acts of their fellow Saiyans,
and led a revolt against them.
This savior had immense power,
and dispatched the evil
Saiyans in no time at all,
but shortly thereafter, they returned to normal,
with their power apparently used up.
Once again, Planet Vegeta
became a world of evil Saiyans,
and the savior was also
eliminated from their legends.
This vanished legend goes...
This story sure is long, huh?
Are you getting this, Vegeta?
Shh! Keep quiet!
..."Five Saiyans who possess
righteous hearts join hands,
and by instilling light into
another righteous Saiyan,
they will become a Saiyan god."
I have now told you the method. Farewell.
Please excuse me.
Five Saiyans who possess righteous hearts?
Hmph, that's impossible.
The only two Saiyans like
that are Gohan and Goten.
How rude of you! While we may
not be able to say much about Vegeta,
Trunks has a righteous heart, doesn't he?
Ha! Any kid his age that
already has a girlfriend is impure.
My, you sound like an old fogey!
Are you sure you're not just jealous?
Yeah, Piccolo-san! Are you
sayin' Goku-sa is impure, too?
Hmm, it's true that Goku may be pure,
but he's purely a fool for fighting.
Whether that counts as a
pure heart is a subtle distinction.
Shut your mouth, you dirty old geezer!
Wh-What did you call me?!
Such a thing to call a sage!
Hurry up and give rise to a Super Saiyan God!
Um, broadly speaking,
don't all five of the Saiyans here
possess hearts that are righteous?
Hmm? Even Vegeta?
Don't you judge me!
Vegeta-san may have been evil a long time ago,
but I'm not so sure about now. Is he evil?
Now that you mention it, you're right.
He hasn't done anything
bad for a good while now.
Stop insulting me!
You're saying the great
Vegeta-sama has a righteous heart?!
It doesn't matter,
just hurry up and give it a try!
Why does Kakarrot get to be the main one?
Quit complaining!
Father, h-has there been any change?
W-Well, I ain't sure.
There, thanks for waiting.
These are called tempura prawns, are they?
That's good, too.
Oh, they did m.
Well, Kakarrot?
Father, you have an outstanding battle power.
Goku has finally gone and become a god!
Son-kun! Go ahead and show him!
Don't bother, Goku!
It won't do any good to fight him.
That was not godly.
B-But...
The reason your battle power went up
is due to nothing more than
collecting energy from the others.
He's correct in saying so.
If all you have is battle power
that appears superficially,
you can't call it godly.
Ah, that makes sense.
Yeah, you're right. I don't feel
like I could beat you, Beers-sama.
Oh, no...
Listen closely, everyone.
Please remember what he said.
The light from five of you
is instilled into one other.
The total number of Saiyans
you need is six, is it not?
Oh, so that's it! We goofed up!
Six? Then, one other... one other...
That's it!
Vegeta, you've got an on-the-level
younger brother, don't you?
On a faraway planet. What's worse,
I don't even know where it is.
You didn't even get his cell phone number?
Enough! I was looking forward
to an interesting development,
but you've disappointed me.
I'm starting to get drowsy,
so I'll destroy the earth
right now, and head home.
E-Excuse me! There is one other!
Videl-san? What other one?
Um, not quite another one,
but soon to be another one, you might say.
But it definitely has Saiyan blood.
What are you talking about, Videl?
Your papa may be a great man,
but I'm a full-blooded earthling!
I'm not talking about you, Papa!
Um, Videl-san has a baby inside her tummy.
D-Do you mean it?!
I do.
I didn't say anything, because
I wanted to surprise you, Gohan-kun.
Hooray!
--Wow!
--Congratulations!
Are you turning God, or not?
C-Come on, let's add
Videl-san, and try it again!
Mm-hmm!
Will this even work?
It hasn't even been born yet.
We've got nothing to
lose, so let's just try it!
Right.
Maybe it's not going to work after all...
Hey, that's the same
old Goku as always, right?
But look at him. His hair is red!
You're right. He also looks a bit thinner.
I can't tell what Goku's battle power is.
Congratulations.
It appears they were successful.
It was worth waiting so very patiently.
Really? Have I become a Super Saiyan God?
We should know once we start fighting.
Now, come and fight me.
All right! Well, here I come!
Sure. If you're the stronger one,
I won't destroy the earth for you.
Huh? You mean it? Thanks so much!
Okay, everyone, this will be dangerous,
so please give them a little more room.
Well? What are your
impressions on being a god?
I'm stunned.
I see. You're surprised.
That's the same impression I had.
Good. Keep that up.
What's wrong? You seem dissatisfied.
A little.
You don't care to be a god?
Nope. I never knew there was a world like this.
What do you mean?
A world that I couldn't come to by myself.
And you're unhappy with that?
Yeah. I ain't happy!
Hmm? What's that?
An earthquake?
You say such interesting things.
You don't like working with
your friends to become a god?!
Oh, I'm happy. I'm happy,
but without using everyone else's power,
I couldn't fight with
you like this, Beers-sama!
That frustrates me!
Then why did you turn God?
Because I wanted to fight you, Beers-sama.
You really are a fool for fighting, huh?
I get that a lot.
Let's follow them!
Right!
Here we go!
They're ramping it up!
Excuse me.
I beg your pardon.
What is this mysterious, delicious item?
Huh? Oh, it's ice cream.
Ice cream? How novel!
Imagine, making food this cold!
Exactly how does one make it?
L-I don't know.
Oh, my. A reply as cold as this ice cream.
Well? That was a pretty good one, wasn't it?
It looks like they're having
a pretty wicked fight, huh?
Th-That bastard! He always snaps up
the best of things for himself!
But still...
Wh-What?
I'm glad that's not me.
Huh?
Are you still unhappy with being a god?
A bit!
That pride will prove to be a weakness!
Good-for-nothing pride!
It's rare that a Saiyan
would be so hung up on it.
Wh-What power!
That ain't true. Vegeta has
far more pride than even I do.
Hmph, now that you mention it,
he forsook his pride earlier,
to protect the others.
I know. He forsook even
his pride as the prince.
Ain't that amazing?
I kind of respect him for that.
And that's why you also forsook
your pride to turn God, right?
That's right.
I wonder what those two are talking about.
It's almost as though
Goku were receiving training.
I should also say that there's
something I'm dissatisfied with.
Huh? What's that?
I still haven't even come
close to fighting all-out.
Oh, really? I was going at
about 80 percent of all-out.
Huh? 80 percent?
Then let's see if you can
keep up with this speed!
What's the matter?
Do you mean business yet?
Yeah! I mean business!
What's this? Using blasts now?!
Ha! This isn't some sporting event!
Stop enjoying destroying things!
He's not God!
He's reverted to a mere Super Saiyan!
C-Can you see them, Kuririn?
No, I can't.
If you're gonna start
using blasts against me...
...then I...
...have one for you!
Go ahead. Feel free.
Hal!
That's Goku's Kamehame-Ha!
Hmm? What's that?
I'll return the favor!
I'll take it, just like this!
Wh-What is that?
Beers' attack! Th-This is bad!
Damn it...!
Apparently, you haven't realized it, yourself.
Wh-What?
Your Super Saiyan God
time ran out a good while ago.
R-Really?
B-But...
It seems as though while you
had turned God and were fighting me,
you absorbed that world into your body.
Which is why, even though
you've returned to normal,
you haven't powered down all
that much. You're something else.
I might even say you're one
of those rarely-seen prodigies.
If that's true, then I'm glad...
Then openly recognize that joy.
That's what you wanted, isn't it?
I can't do that. The first
matter at hand right now...
...is still how huge the
difference in our powers is!
Then give up and bow out!
What is going on?
Damn it...!
Goku-sa!
--Goku!
--Kakarrot!
--Father!
Hey, what did you just do?
L-I don't know.
You don't know?
You are a fascinating one.
What? Why did you stop?
I wanted to get you to say "I give up."
I give up. I give "P!
Beers-same, you sure are strong.
There ain't no way I could stand up to you.
You're the strongest
in the universe, all right.
It looks like you finally realize
the terror of Beers the Destroyer.
However, you are definitely strong, yourself.
In the long, long history
of fights I've been through,
you are the second-strongest.
Huh? Wh-What, only second place?
All right, let me tell you one last thing...
What? That you've
decided not to destroy earth?
No, I can't do that.
I make it a rule not to
change my mind once it's made up.
Then, wh-what...?
My attendant, a man named
Whis, is over there, right?
Huh? Y-Yeah...
While he may be my
attendant, he is also my teacher.
Eh? T-Teacher?! Then, the
strongest one in the universe is...
This world is the "7th Universe."
I am the Destroyer for the 7th Universe.
There are 12 universes in all, you see.
Don't you expect that there are
even more fantastic guys out there?
Goku-sa!
--Goku!
--Son-kun!
L-I'm all right. I'm still alive.
Well then, as promised,
I will now destroy earth.
Oh my, Beers-sama, you destroyed
just a small piece of earth, huh?
Hmph, that's too bad. I guess
I don't have enough strength left.
I'll have to destroy it
completely some other time.
Beers-sama...
You there, when Beers-sama passes away,
would you be the next Destroyer?
Hey!
I'm afraid not.
That's too bad.
Mrs. Vegeta...
Huh? Me? Wh-What?
I'm sorry for all the commotion.
Never mind that, apologize for hitting me!
S-Sorry.
Hey, what are you, dim?!
If you don't mind, please
invite us to your next party.
If you promise not to act up.
Agreed. And this time, I'm going
to have some of that pudding.
I'll have the whole pool
filled and ready for you.
However, don't go telling me
you don't like it after you eat it.
If I don't like it, I really will
destroy the earth this time.
Then we'll get to fight
again, right, Beers-sama?
Farewell.
Unbelievable.
Absolutely right.
Beers the Destroyer did not destroy them.
Could it be because of the
marvelous character of Son Goku?
He keeps making more and more friends...
...until now, at last, even Beers-sama...
No,
we can't say it was
entirely because of Son Goku.
It's that whole group--
no, it may even be because of the whole earth.
Son Goku, who was supposed
to have been a savage Saiyan,
to say nothing of Vegeta,
changed after coming to earth.
Humankind aside, it really
is a wonderful planet, isn't it?
Those people have all sorts of problems,
but they are brimming with a wondrous charm.
I guess that was kind of fun.
I have to admit, his latent
ability is something unfathomable.
Although, I wouldn't call him an arch-rival.
Even so, it's been a long
time since I've seen you
have to use nearly 70 percent
of your power, Beers-sama.
What was his name again?
Son Goku.
Between him and Vegeta,
they really might become my
arch-rivals before too long, huh?
You seem pleased by that.
As are you, aren't you, Whis?
It can become dull when we both live so long.
Besides which, I do not sleep.
Well, I'm a bit tired,
so I think I'll take a three-year nap.
Three years? That is a
fairly brief snooze, isn't it?
There appear to be many more
delicious things on earth, after all.
Sure enough, you did not
feel like destroying earth
after finding how delicious the food is.
Oh, I don't know about that.
Ah, come to think of it...
I had them pack us something
absolutely delicious, called sushi,
for us to bring back with us.
Beers-sama, would you like some?
Or would you rather sleep?
Ha! I'll have some, of course!
It looks like you sampled
quite a bit of tasty food
while I was off fighting, huh, Whis?
Oh, this is some beautiful food, isn't it?
You apply a little of this fluid,
called soy sauce, and eat it.
What is this little green lump here?
That? Ah, now that you mention it,
the chef said "Use it as you like,"
and that it was called "wasabi."
Ah, come to think of it,
I did hear you talking about that.
While I was fighting.
Let me go get us something to drink.
Let's see, here...
That won't do!
Yow-w-w... That was mean of you.
Beers-sama, you do take out your
temper on innocent worlds, after all.
Hmph. This is all earth's fault.
All right, let's head back to
earth right now, and destroy it!
My word, after I said "Use it as you like,"
you are the one who gulped
it down, right, Beers-sama?
Well then, let's make it
"if I don't like the taste of sushi,
it means destruction!" instead.
Now then, please wake me in another three years.
It was good, wasn't it?
Okay, good night.
Ah, Beers-sama, be sure to
brush before you go to sleep.
Huh? Yeah... all right, all right...
Okay, one more time, then!
Bulma-san, happy---
...birthday!
Yeah! 38 years old!
Shut up!
Let's drink!
When you're backed into a corner,
you may be more fearsome than anything.
Hey, Kakarrot, next time,
I'm the one who gets to turn God!
You be sure to cooperate with me.
Yeah, of course! But when you
overexert yourself to get stronger,
it leaves you all worn out afterward!
Oh, come to think of it, Vegeta,
when Bulma got hit, you were all,
"My Bulma!", got angry, and turned
into an awesome Super Saiyan, huh?
I felt so loved!
L-I don't remember saying that!
J-Just that, at the time,
I definitely think I surpassed you!
Yeah, you sure did.
Next time, when we fight
someone who gives us trouble,
have him slap Bulma for us.
Hey!
I thought you weren't here
when Vegeta went off like that.
You arrived long before that,
using your Instantaneous Movement,
to see how things played out, didn't you?
Uh, well...
Son-kun'.!
Is that true, you jerk?!
While everyone else was getting beat up?!
Sorry! Sorry! I was watching
the enemy's movement,
trying to put together a strategy,
but well, I didn't come up with anything.
Bulma! Smack him two or three more times!
Yes, Sir!
Whoa, I'm sorry! I know I made a mistake!