Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
This is Berk, boasting the
kind of balmy, fun-in-the-sun climate
that will give you frostbite
on your spleen.
The one upside is our
annual holiday.
We call it Snoggletog.
Why we chose such a stupid name
remains a mystery.
But with the war long over...
and dragons living amongst us,
this year's Snoggletog...
promises to be one to remember.
OK, OK! I'm coming!
- Good morning, Mr. Bossy.
Do you always have to wake me up
so early to go flying...?
Stupid leg.
Thanks, buddy. I'm OK.
- Yeah, we can go flying now.
Eww! Eww!
What?! Eww!
Toothless!
Come on!
Let's see what you got today!
Yeah! OK, you ready?
Easy...
Yes! Finally!
Yes, yes... No, no!
That one a wee bit higher!
- Here?
- There! That's the spot!
Roar!
Attaboy, Meatlug.
Are you ready, girl?
By Odin's beard, Gobber,
Vikings spending the winter holiday
with dragons!
- What would the fathers say?
- They'd think we'd lost our minds.
Well done! Well done. All of you!
I never thought I'd live to see this
peace on the island of Berk.
This will surely be the greatest holiday
we've ever seen.
What the...?
What in Thor's name?
Come back! What are you doing?
Meatlug!
- What's going on?
- What's happening?
Where's Hiccup?
What do you say, bud?
Wanna go again?
- Whoa!
Whoa!
Whoa! Whoa! Whoa!
Oh, no, my helmet!
Whoa!
Toothless! No, no, no, no!
No, no, no!
Whoa, whoa, wait! Toothless! Stop!
We'll get it later, buddy.
We need to get back
and find out what's going on.
What's the matter?
Where are you going?
No, no, no, don't leave, Stormfly!
Don't go! Please?
- Astrid!
- Hiccup! What's going on?
Where are they going?
- Why did they leave?
- What's happening?!
What if they never come back?!
- Stop, please!
- Calm down!
Give him a chance to speak!
Hiccup, where are all the dragons going?
Dad, I don't know.
Where'd they go?
Snoggletog is ruined!
It's not ruined!
We're Vikings!
We've been perfectly happy celebrating
without dragons for generations.
And there's no reason
we can't do it again.
Now, we don't know
where they've gone off to.
But we have to have faith
that they'll be back again soon.
- Am I right?
- You're right! We are Vikings!
- We're tough... most of the time.
Let's sing
some Snoggletog songs.
- That was depressing.
- I know.
I was looking forward to spending
the holiday with Stormfly.
What are you so happy about?
Don't you miss Meatlug?
Me?
Oh, yeah.
I miss him so much!
Well, good night.
I've got an idea. Let's come up
with a bunch of new holiday traditions.
- You know, to bury the sadness.
Actually, Astrid might
be onto something.
Easy for you to say. Your dragon
can't go anywhere without you.
Must be nice.
Yak nog! Get your yak nog!
Come on! Get a frothy, delicious
cup of cheer!
Hey, you guys, try this tasty new
beverage I made for the holiday.
- What's the smell? Is that you?
- It's yak nog!
If I drink that,
I'm gonna yak nog all over the place.
Maybe you'd rather taste
a punch in the face?
Astrid, it sounds delightful.
I'd love a mug.
You can really taste the yak.
- Yum! What is that?
- You wanna try some?
It's my new traditional drink.
Oh, you know...
suddenly and inexplicably
changed my mind.
Well, you don't know
what you're missing.
I bet Hiccup will love this.
Are you crying?
- Hiccup?
- Yeah, I'm over here, Astrid. Coming.
Here. Happy holidays.
From me to you.
- Thank you, milady.
- What are you up to?
OK, you're gonna think I'm crazy,
but I just couldn't stop thinking
about what Tuff nut said last night.
Toothless can't come and go
like the other dragons,
and that's just not fair.
I was up all night,
and I think I found a way to fix that.
No way! You built him a new tail?
So he's gonna be able
to fly without you!
Mm-hmm.
Wow! What a great gift.
What if he never comes back?
- What am I saying? Of course he will.
- Mm-hmm.
Well, I'm gonna go spread some more
holiday cheer. You're amazing!
Toothless! Come on down, bud!
I got something for you.
What do you think of that? Yeah.
Would you just settle down!
Toothless, come on, bud.
Let me get this on you.
Yeah. You are going to love this.
OK.
No, no, no! Toothless, stop!
Please, wait! Toothless, please!
There you go. See? Got it?
Toothless... Whoa!
Toothless!
I knew you'd come back!
Whoa!
Morning, son.
Hey, Dad.
Glad you're up.
I was looking for your helmet.
My... my helmet?
Odin needs a place to put your goodies.
Yeah, right, I'll... get on that.
Great.
Hold on.
Hold on. All right, come on.
What's on your mind? Out with it.
It's been three days, Dad.
I just thought Toothless
would be back by now.
- I'm sure he's with the other dragons.
- Yeah? I wish I could be that sure.
Listen, I know what it's like to miss
someone you love this time of year.
But what do we do when they can't
be here for the holiday?
We celebrate them.
And I imagine that's exactly what
Toothless would want you to do.
- Right?
- You're right.
Good. Now go get that helmet.
We've had enough disappointment
around here.
Oh, Fishlegs, you hungry? There's
enough fish there to feed a dragon.
A dragon! That's...
Meatlug!
Whoa!
Hiccup? Where are you going?
I have no idea!
Meatlug! What about presents?
Hey!
- I can't believe him.
- You can't believe him?!
- You kidnapped your dragon!
- That makes it sound mean.
- Hey, guys...
- He flew away the second
- he was unleashed!
- I'm 72 per cent sure
he wanted to stay.
- Guys!
- Whoa!
Meatlug barfed up a pile of rocks.
You're such an idiot. Those aren't
rocks. Your dragon laid eggs!
Hey, wait. I bet that's
why the dragons left.
- To lay their eggs.
- But boy dragons don't lay eggs.
Yeah, your boy dragon
is a girl dragon.
OK! That actually explains a few things.
Hey! Everyone's missing their dragons,
right?
- Here it comes.
- I've got an idea.
It'll be another new
Snoggletog tradition.
This is gonna be so good!
Meatlug, where are you taking me?
You guys come here to have babies.
Whoa.
Hmm.
- Wow!
Hey, look over here. You missed one.
Whoa!
Man, it's a good things
don't hatch on Berk.
- Wasn't this a great idea?
- Uh-huh!
Everyone is gonna be
so surprised!
Ow!
Surprise!
Aww!
The eggs explode?
The eggs explode!
Sorry!
Save us!
- Awesome!
- Wow!
This is your best idea yet.
What in Thor's name is going on?!
The eggs explode.
Toothless!
Toothless?
Come on, Toothless, where are you?
Hookfang!
Stormfly.
You have no idea how happy I am
to see you guys.
And you have... babies?
Look at you guys, all happy together.
Who knew you were leaving to celebrate
your own sort of... holiday?
I should get back to my holiday.
So, what do you say there, Hookfang?
Think you can give me
a ride back home?
I'll see you all back on Berk
when you're good and ready. OK, gang?
No, no! No, no, no! I... think
I just started the return migration.
Well, if you insist.
Come on!
Boy, this is never gonna work.
Hold on. I've got just the thing
Gobber, this is a disaster.
- It's not so bad.
- Not that bad?
The village is destroyed,
the dragons have gone and left us...
Let's face it.
This holiday is a complete...
What are these people looking at?
What is that?
It's Hiccup!
And our dragons!
- Welcome back, laddie!
- Good job!
Yeah! Whoo-hoo!
Meatlug!
Stormfly! You're back! Oh!
And there are babies!
- Well done, son.
- Thanks, Dad.
Everyone, grab your dragons!
To the Great Hall!
We finally have something to celebrate.
This the best holiday ever!
Who's a baby? Who's a cutie baby?
Hiccup, I know this must
be really hard for you,
seeing everyone with their dragons.
But you really did a wonderful thing!
Thank you.
Astrid, where did Toothless go?
- I don't know.
Wow. Man!
Wouldn't wanna be you right now.
I mean, you brought back
everyone's dragon except yours.
Yeah, you know,
this is not helping at all.
Toothless! Hey, bud!
- Stoick.
Bad dragon! Very bad dragon!
You scared me to death!
Don't ever stay away that long again!
And what is in your mouth?
Eww! Eww!
Yeah, you found my helmet.
Hey! You found my helmet!
That's where you've been?
Buddy, thank you.
You are amazing.
Happy Snoggletog!
I'm coming, Toothless!
All right, bud, come on down.
I was just...
Toothless, what'd you pull this out for?
You don't need this any more.
Come on, let's get going.
Would you quit fooling around?
You have your new tail now.
Toothless!
Toothless! Stop! What are you doing?!
Winter in Berk lasts
most of the year.
It hangs on with both hands
and won't let go.
And the only real comforts
against the cold
are those you keep
close to your heart.
OK, bud, you ready?
Yee-haw!
Turns out that was
the best Snoggletog ever.
That year, I gave my best friend
a pretty great gift.
Whoo-hoo!
He gave me a better one.
Please rate this subtitle at www.osdb.link/3umx
Help other users to choose the best subtitles