What's up?
Animal Planet.
Man, I just had the craziest dream.
-About what?
-I don't remember.
Yeah. Yeah.
Morning, guys.
Morning, Gene.
What did we do last night?
I don't know.
Wait. Didn't the twins have a party?
Yeah, that's it. Twins had a party.
-Right.
Were we there?
I'm assuming we were.
What kind of boyfriends
would we be if we weren't?
Did I get any messages?
Nope.
See you tomorrow, Gene.
Shibby.
How do you know Gene?
Oh, I thought he was your friend.
No, no, I don't know him.
I'm starving.
-It's pudding.
-I always wondered what a fridge...
...full of pudding would look like.
Is it possible that we got
so wasted last night...
...we bought a lifetime supply
of pudding and then forgot about it?
I'd say it's entirely possible.
-Jesse.
-And Chester are shibby right now.
Please leave your shibby at the beep.
Shibby.
What happened last night?
You show up with a bunch of people,
pizzas and a keg. Our house is trashed.
You're sucky boyfriends.
Always disappointing us.
Now you're probably on the couch
in your underwear.
Playing thumb wars.
Wearing those Army helmets.
And if you are, you've probably
forgotten our anniversary.
Which is today.
You don't get the special treats
we had for you.
Just wanted to thank you guys
for trashing our house.
Bye!
Twins sound pissed.
-Good thing we already got them gifts.
-Yeah.
So where are the gifts?
-They must be in your car.
-They're in the car.
So we'll just take the gifts
to the twins' house...
...get our special treats.
Hey, what do you think they mean
by special treats?
We've been going out with them
for a year now.
And we still haven't had sex.
"Special treats" is code for sex.
Of course.
-Special treats!
-Sex.
Open up, you slackers!
Mr. Pizzacoli!
You left work last night...
...with 30 pizzas
that didn't get delivered!
I want some answers!
Open up this damn door!
It's open.
-Moron!
-What? I'm sorry.
Mr. Pizzacoli.
-Hi, how you doing?
-30 pizzas didn't get delivered!
If I found out you was taking
my pizza home to eat yourselves...
...I will crush you like a doodlebug!
-Look, it's an elephant!
-What?
-Guess it was just a mailman.
-You two are the most irresponsible...
...and disappointing employees
ever to work...
...at Mr. Pizzacoli's
Pronto Pizza Delivery!
A trained dolphin could do
a better job than you!
Well, sure, but then the pizzas
would get all wet.
Look, a unicorn!
A unicorn?
Sorry, I guess it was just
a regular horse. Weird!
You've been embezzling my pizza.
And I will catch you eventually.
And when I do, I swear to God,
you will never deliver pizzas...
...in this town again!
-Close one.
-Yeah.
We'll go to the twins' house.
We'll give them their gifts
and apologize for trashing the house.
And then we get our special treats.
Dude, where's my car?
Where's your car, dude?
-Did I drive last night?
-Yeah, I think so.
-Really?
-I'm not sure.
-Dude, where's your car?
-Dude, it's not funny. It's gone.
-Yeah.
-Dude, where's my car?
Shut up, dude!
Okay. Okay, look.
You're right.
What we need to do is...
...get into the state of mind
we were in last night.
That way, we can retrace our steps.
-Yeah.
-Sense Memory Simulated Perception...
...Altered Consciousness
Memory Retrieval.
Discovery Channel.
Nice.
-Nelson's?
-Shibby.
-I'm sick of walking, dude.
-Me too.
Hey, it's Mrs. Crabbleman.
She'll give us a ride.
Hey, Mrs. Crabbleman!
Hey! Hey!
Mrs. Crabbleman.
Fucking stoners.
She must not have recognized you.
-It's the Binglemans.
-Oh, hey.
Mr. Bingleman!
Hey, Mr. Bingleman.
-Maybe we should just walk.
-Yeah.
Listen, Nelson, the car is gone...
...and we need to do
this sense memory thing...
...so we can get back in the state
of mind we were in last night.
Deep in your consciousness,
you must look.
Concentrate on the knowledge inside,
you must.
Your eyes, you must close.
And you take it to the mo.
Whoops.
Concentrating, you're not.
Sorry.
-Is your dog dead?
-He's not dead.
Come here, Jackal. Come here, boy.
-I don't think he's coming.
-Maybe he's deaf.
Deaf, he is not, dude.
Come here, Jackal.
-Come here, Jackal.
-Does he know any other tricks...
...besides not moving?
All right, you want
to see a trick, man?
Hey, Jackal.
Bite down, killer.
Here comes the fun. All right.
Good boy, Jackal.
Good boy.
Breathe deep. There you go.
-Dude, your dog's a stoner.
-Can he also bong a beer?
Nah, pretty much all he does is...
...lie around and smoke his pipe.
Jackal, can I see your pipe?
Oh, no, don't!
Very protective, he is of his pipe.
When other people touch it,
he does not like.
Sorry, Jackal.
Yeah, see? He's sorry.
Holy crap.
-That's one psycho dog, dude.
-You know what we should do now?
-Eat?
-No. Eat.
Choice excellent, my friend.
I'll get the keys.
Hey, Nelson. Let me order.
"Chinese Foooood. " May I help you?
-I'd like to place an order.
-What you like?
Yeah, I'd like three orders
of garlic chicken.
-And then?
-And then three orders of white rice.
-And then....
-Hey, you guys want soup?
-Sure.
-Yeah. Three orders of won ton soup.
-And then?
-Oh, some fortune cookies too.
That's about it.
And then?
No, that's it.
-And then?
-No "and then."
I-- That's all I want.
And then?
And then-- And then nothing else,
because I'm done ordering. Okay?
And then?
See, all I want is the three orders
of the garlic chicken...
...and the white rice.
And then?
-And the soup, dude.
-Oh, and the won ton soup.
-And then?
-And the cookies, fortune.
And the fortune cookies.
So it's just the chicken, the rice...
...the soup and the fortune cookies,
and that's it.
And then?
And then you can put it
in a brown paper bag...
...and put it in my hand,
because I'm ready to eat.
And then?
I refuse to play
your Chinese food mind games.
-And then?
-No! No "and then"!
-No "and then"!
-And then?
-No! No "and then"!
-You're starting to piss me off, lady.
-And then?
-And then...
...I'm gonna come in there
and put my foot in your ass...
...if you say "and then" again!
And then and then
and then and then and then....
And then?
Come on, Nelson,
just help us find my car.
You didn't have to go all "egg roll"
on that speaker box.
I'm not the one that called
the Dalai Lama a fag.
-I was just kidding around.
-Well, Nelson didn't appreciate it.
Look, it's Christie Boner.
Wow! The hottest of the hot.
El fuego of all that is el fuego.
-Did she just wave at us?
-No way. She would never wave at us.
Then why did she just wave at us?
I don't know. Maybe she thinks
we're other people.
People she waves to.
Hi, Chester.
Hi.
Hi, Jesse. I had a really
good time with you last night.
-Me too.
-That was some crazy party.
-Hey, have you seen my car?
-Well, I saw it last night.
I mean, I saw the back seat.
-I mean the whole thing.
-Get another one with all the money...
-...you were throwing around.
-Money?
Yeah. You had that really nice
suitcase full of money.
-A suitcase full of money?
-Don't you remember giving me $500...
...to show you my hoo-hoos?
-$500?
-Hoo-hoos?
You mean, you don't remember anything?
How about now?
No.
I'm a little bit fuzzy too.
Maybe if I could get
a little refresher course.
-All right.
-Go.
-Are these losers bothering you?
-No, Tommy.
Guys like you could never score
with a chick like this.
-Stick to your own kind.
-Don't be such a jerk.
Next time you guys
bother my girlfriend...
-...stoner-bashing time.
-Oh, yeah?
Yeah.
-Okay.
-Consider this your warning.
Later, dudes!
Dude, you touched
Christie Boner's hoo-hoo.
Shibby!
Low-five.
-Yeah.
-Let's get out of here.
Chester!
Dude, that Christie Boner
is super hot.
Where did we get a suitcase
full of money?
Why don't we have it now?
Maybe we deposited it
in a Swiss bank account.
Now, if we had a ridiculous
sum of money, where would we go?
Dude.
Sweet!
No way we were here last night.
We'd never fit in
at a place like this.
Look everyone!
It's Mr. Jesse and Mr. Chester!
Look at the toggles on that kitten.
Good afternoon, Jesse, Chester.
How are we feeling today?
A little fuzzy.
Hi, Chester. Hi, Jesse.
Did you guys enjoy
yourselves last night?
-Have we met?
-It's me, Tania.
Remember last night
when I gave you...
...that super-special,
slippery-wet lap dance?
Of course. How can I forget?
You want to do it again?
This time, it's on me.
If you say so.
Didn't I get a special lap dance?
Did you ever.
Sweet!
So...
...just how super-special
can a slippery lap dance be?
What the hell were you thinking,
throwing around my money like that?
-You're a....
-I'm a gender-challenged male.
What does that mean?
Oh, dude, you're a dude! That's--
You....
Last night, I had you sneak a suitcase
of stolen money out of here.
-Stolen money?
-$200,000.
$200,000!
I gave you the case and left.
We were supposed to meet.
But you never showed up!
Where's that suitcase?
-I don't know.
-You don't know?
-Where's that suitcase?
-It's in my car.
Then get it. Fast.
Or else you'll be singing soprano.
Dude. Dude, dude!
-We gotta go.
-Are you crazy?
I'm with breakdancing strippers.
Seriously, dude, this is an emergency.
So is this, dude.
It's a breakdancing
stripper emergency.
-Goodbye!
-Bye, Chester!
I love you!
We were supposed to meet her with
the suitcase, but we didn't show up.
Sounds like us.
How wasted were we last night?
I touched Christie's hoo-hoo,
we're on the hook for $200,000...
...that belongs to a transsexual
stripper, and my car's gone.
-I'd say we were pretty wasted.
-We really need to find your car.
Okay, let's see. The last place
we remember being last night was....
The twins'. But we can't show up
without the anniversary gifts.
I got it! We'll get them
a little something for now.
When we find the car, we'll give them
the real gifts. That's a dollar...
...thirty-nine.
-I don't know.
-Trust me.
-It'll be totally cool. Let's go.
-Okay.
We are so dead.
I roger that.
-We've been cleaning all day.
-What do you guys have to say?
Happy anniversary.
We ate the dark ones.
We know you guys don't like those.
Dark ones are the only ones
we do like.
Oh, yeah.
But you could use the box to keep....
You keep...
...ribbons.
-You guys forgot our anniversary.
-No, of course not.
No, we got you guys great gifts.
We just had some car trouble.
We came over here
as soon as we could...
...to help you guys clean up but....
Oh, no.
It looks like you're already done.
All we have to do is
take out the trash.
Guess they haven't been outside yet.
You know what?
We'll take out the trash.
You guys go and take a nice hot bath.
Yeah. You deserve it
after all this hard work.
Pamper yourselves.
-Just....
-Don't make a mess.
Slow and steady, good buddy.
10-4.
-You're tilting.
-Sorry.
-Why are you tilting?
-You gave me the heavy end.
-Let it go, man.
-No, we can get it.
No. Let it go.
We're not leaving it behind.
Okay.
-I'll take my shoe off.
-Okay.
Watch it. Stop pushing!
Watch it! Careful. Careful.
-Are we cool? Are we cool?
-We're still cool.
Now, take your shoe off,
and you get it.
-Okay.
-Get it. That's it, that's it.
I got it!
Oh, my God!
You can't do anything right.
Why do you have to mess everything up?
-I got three words: anger management.
-Yeah!
Dude, we really need
to find your car.
Sorry about yanking you
off the street like that.
-We really need to talk to you.
-Who are you guys?
My name is Zarnoff. This is Zabu,
Zellner, Zilbor, Zelmina...
-...and Jeff.
-Hey.
More specifically, we are
the recipients of instructions...
...from extraterrestrials regarding
the interstellar path to outer space.
Go ahead and laugh.
We are used to being mocked.
Okay.
We have been sent
by our wise and powerful leader...
...Zoltan...
...to find you and recover
the continuum transfunctioner.
Hey, have you guys
ever been to Uranus?
It's supposed to be
nice this time of year.
This is important. We intercepted
an interstellar message...
...that leads us to believe
that last night...
...you were in possession
of the continuum transfunctioner.
Where is it now?
-The who what?
-The continuum transfunctioner...
...is a very mysterious
and powerful device.
-And?
-And its mystery...
...is exceeded only by its power.
Sorry, we don't remember
a thing about last night.
You must be careful.
Danger follows the continuum
transfunctioner. So says....
-Zoltan.
I'll tell you what.
We'll keep our eyes out for the
continual trans-ding-a-ling thing...
...and if we see it,
we'll give you a call.
Yes. You must.
But remember,
you are in great danger.
Trust no one.
Except for us.
Thank you, Jeff. Good point.
Trust no one, except for us.
Zoltan.
Wait a second. Let's recap.
Last night, we lost my car...
...we accepted stolen money
from a transsexual stripper...
...and now some space nerds want us
to find something we can't pronounce.
Maybe we should cut back
on the shibbying.
-Thanks, dude.
-Oh, good!
You're right on time.
You pick up special suits.
Mr. Lee, tailor, make special
suits for you. Come on.
-Dude, you got a tattoo!
-What?
-So did you, dude.
-Naw.
-Dude, what does my tattoo say?
-"Sweet"!
-What about mine?
-"Dude." What does mine say?
"Sweet."
-What about mine?
-"Dude."
-What does mine say?
-"Sweet"!
-What about mine?
-"Dude." And mine?
"Sweet." What about mine?
"Dude." What does mine say?
"Sweet"! What about mine?
"Dude"! What does mine say?
"Sweet"!
Idiots!
Your tattoo says "dude,"
your tattoo says "sweet."
Got it?
Sorry.
-Hey.
-Sorry.
-Shibby.
-Very sharp, very sharp.
You two number one, extra-special
good-looking guys.
-We got these last night?
-You were pretty--
-How much are these?
-You already pay for.
I just do some minor alterations.
Add the secret pockets you order.
Maybe we got
the continual trans-sphincter.
What's--?
Oh, dude!
Dude!
Sweet!
Cool!
-How did we pay for these suits?
-Oh, you pay cash.
Cold hard cash,
crispy new hundred-dollar bills.
Hey, did you see
what car we were driving?
Me? No, I don't see no car.
Hello?
Dude, we bought cell phones.
That's not all we bought, dude.
Shibby!
Man, I cannot believe
we leased a car last night. God!
-But who's Johnny Potsmoker?
-That's my alter ego.
I thought that was my alter ego.
No, that's my alter ego.
-Your alter ego is Smokey McPot.
-Oh, yeah.
You're never gonna figure that out.
Okay, dude.
There it is. Break time's over.
Time to find my car.
This is impossible.
Are you Jesse and Chester?
I don't know. Why?
If you are Jesse and Chester...
...perhaps we will give you
erotic pleasure.
-That's us.
-Right here.
We are looking
for the continuum transfunctioner.
-Who are you guys?
-We are not guys. We are hot chicks.
She's totally right.
The continuum transfunctioner...
...is a very mysterious
and powerful device.
-And?
-And its mystery...
...is only exceeded by its power.
That doesn't really help.
We will give you pleasure now, if you
give us the continuum transfunctioner.
Let me get your proposition straight.
First you give us...
...the pleasure, then we give
you the continuum transfunctioner?
No. First you give us
the continuum transfunctioner...
...then we give you the pleasure.
I've heard that one before.
Okay, look. How about this?
You give me pleasure...
...then we'll give you
the continuum transfunctioner.
-If there's time, you do him.
-Dude--
-Deal.
-Sweet!
-Wait a second.
-Thank you.
Come here. Those space nerds
told us not to trust anybody.
Yeah, but for the love of God,
they're offering us oral pleasure!
What--?
-Okay.
Hey. Where did the hot chicks go?
Where's my money, boys?
We were just going to get it.
You picked the wrong
transsexual stripper to screw with.
You're pinching me.
Well, let's see what the cops
have to say about this.
-You're busted.
-Busted.
-B-U-S-T, busted.
-This one.
-These guys.
-Chester! I saw this on COPS!
-Kick hard and hit back!
-Bye-bye, boys.
Put on the siren.
You're sticking to the
"I don't remember" crap.
Yeah. We don't remember.
Last night, your car
was spotted leaving...
-...the scene of a major drug deal.
-You found my car.
You guys got more important things
to worry about right now.
Where were you between
midnight and 2 a.m. last night?
I told you, okay?
We don't remember anything.
I see we're gonna have to do
this the hard way.
Where were you last night between
the hours of midnight and 2 a.m.?
We don't know.
What the--?
-Now do you remember?
-No.
-How about now?
Hey, leave him alone!
He doesn't know anything!
-Now are you ready to talk?
-Dude, we don't remember!
Okay, here are the whips
you guys wanted.
Hey, it's the donut guys.
These two were at
the Donut House last night.
We started talking and they bought
donuts for the whole precinct.
What time did all this happen?
Let's see. Must've been
between midnight and 2 a.m.
Damn!
You can't be the guys
we're looking for. Sorry.
Hang in there, bro.
-Come on, Kojak.
-All right.
I'm really sorry about all this.
Looks like it was a case
of mistaken identity.
Actually, those are
the real criminals over there.
One of our officers...
-...made a wrong identification.
-Yeah, that was me.
I'm sorry about that, fellas.
Rick will tell you exactly
where your car is.
-We found the car.
We found the car!
-Yeah, we found the car.
-Found my car.
Now we get the gifts, go to the twins'
house, and get our special treats.
Sweet!
Give us the keys
and we're out of here.
You got it.
Oh, boy. Oh, boy.
What's the problem, Rick?
Nothing, I just-- Boy.
Okay. Jeez.
Did you say you wanted your car back,
or you wanted it impounded?
We want the car back, please.
Oh, I see. That's kind of funny,
because what happened was...
...I accidentally sent your car
to the impound.
-Rick.
-I know.
I can definitely tell you this.
You guys...
...can get the car back in a few days.
We don't have a few days, Rick.
We need the car back now.
Say, how about a treat?
There's Bavarian cream.
-Yeah.
-That's a good one there.
-It's good.
-It's great. I have a lot of them.
-You know what? Forget about it.
-Okay.
-Psych!
-Oh, jeez. You got me.
Hey, fellows, who's the goose? Me.
You're such a joker.
One.
-Damn!
-Have you seen Jesse and Chester?
-What?
-We're looking for Jesse and Chester.
I don't know where they are...
...but I bet those punks
over there do.
So then, remember?
I said, "Later, dudes."
-Why were you with those jerks anyway?
-They were just being nice...
...unlike someone I know.
Maybe it's time I find someone
with a sensitive side.
Someone who respects me as a person.
Maybe somebody like Jesse or Chester.
Okay, listen up.
We're gonna find Jesse and Chester.
And when we do, stoner-bashing time!
-Do you know Jesse and Chester?
-Who are you?
-We are hot chicks.
-Yes, you are.
We believe they have
the continuum transfunctioner.
However, if you recover the continuum
transfunctioner from them...
...and bring it to us,
we will give you erotic pleasure.
You've got yourselves a deal.
Okay, guys. Okay, guys, new plan.
First, we find those stoners,
get the continuum transfunctioner...
-...then, it's jerk-bashing time.
-Yeah!
Oh, yeah.
I just remembered where
you might be able to find them.
Send those chicks to meet the twins.
That'll put those dudes
in some hot water.
Try it again. Okay?
Just knock it out of the park.
All right, give it a shot.
Okay, you almost got it.
Now just concentrate on the beep,
swing as hard as you can...
...and keep your ear on the ball.
Okay?
All right, little buddy,
you can do it!
I did it! I did it!
I hit it! I did it!
-Do you know Jesse and Chester?
-Pardon me?
-We're looking for Jesse and Chester.
-Who are you?
We're extremely hot chicks
with big breasts.
Really?
Can I touch your face?
It's the only way I can see...
-...who I'm talking to.
-Okay.
Wow! You are hot.
Is this normal?
Oh, yeah. This is how
blind people shake hands.
-Sammy, you're up next.
-Okay--
-Come on.
-What the--? Sis!
Excuse me, a little help.
Wanda. Wilma.
-Anthony?
-Anthony, what is going on?
Nothing. I was just reading.
Bye, ladies, I need to be alone now.
-We're looking for Jesse and Chester.
-Who are you guys?
We are not guys. We are hot chicks.
We're supposed to meet them later,
but we can't wait.
-We don't know where they are.
-And frankly, we don't care.
-Dude, let's call Nelson.
-Yeah. See if he's home.
-Hello?
-Hey, Nelson, it's Chester.
Hey, Chester! No, it's me, Tommy.
Your buddy Nelson is busy
at the moment.
This is bad karma, boys.
Hey, tell me where
that continuum transfunctioner is.
No hablo English.
Your friend's dead meat unless
I get that continuum transfunctioner.
Jackal! Get your pipe!
-My balls!
-What was that?
Tommy's gotten to Nelson! He knows
about the continuum transfunctioner.
Those double-crossing
sexy, sexy sluts!
I am so sick of hearing about
this continuum transfunctioner thing.
-If one more person asks--
-You got the continuum transfunctioner?
Who are you guys?
We are the keepers
of the continuum transfunctioner.
It is all that stands between
the universe and destruction.
It is a mysterious
and powerful device.
And its mystery
is only exceeded by its power.
-We know.
-We don't have it.
But the universe?
Screw the universe.
Screw the universe?
Chimpanzees often use sticks
as crude tools.
That is one smart primate.
-Hey.
What are you doing here?
We just wanted to see
how that car trouble thing was going.
Oh, the car. It's in the shop.
Really?
The shop run by beautiful women
in black jumpsuits?
The ones you were
hanging with earlier?
-Well, you see, Jesse thought--
-Today's our anniversary.
-Not only do you not have gifts.
-But you guys ditch us...
...for some big-breasted bimbos...
-...while we're cleaning our house....
-Which you trashed.
Twice.
-You're sucky boyfriends.
-But--
We just wanted to come
and tell you in person that it's over.
-Wilma?
-Thank you, Wanda.
-They're totally right.
-Yeah.
We are sucky boyfriends.
Do you even remember
what kind of gifts we got them?
-I bet we got them sucky gifts.
-Yeah.
We suck.
Wait, I just got a really bad feeling
in the pit of my stomach.
You should go sit on the toilet.
No, no.
You know what the feeling is?
It's love.
-Is that what that is?
-Yeah.
I'm in love with Wanda.
And you're in love with Wilma.
But see, now that we know...
...that we've been sucky boyfriends,
we can change.
-We can?
-Yeah. And you know what else?
I'll bet you that we did buy them
super-cool anniversary gifts.
You know why? Because we love them.
Are they wrapped in cool paper?
Yeah. I'll tell you what we'll do.
We'll go to the impound lot, get the car,
which has the gifts in it...
...and then go to the twins' house,
and beg for them to take us back!
Yeah! Let's do it.
No, hold on. I gotta take a crap.
-Told you.
-I know.
I know your body.
Boys, I got some good news.
We just got your car in this morning.
All right!
But the bad news is...
...not only did Officer Boyer
send your car to the impound...
...he tagged it for auction
and it was sold this afternoon.
Rick.
-Do you know who bought the car?
-I have the address right here.
All right.
But it'd be against Regulation...
...457XY2-665 to give it to you.
Come on. Just--
Reaching onto this side
of the counter isn't allowed.
The last guy who tried it ended up
with three broken fingers.
-Reach it.
-You can reach it!
No, I got--
One of these has carpal tunnel.
What if I further injure myself?
I have to do everything.
I'm a better lookout.
My vision's better. You know that.
That's it, that's it.
-Got it!
-We're good, we're good.
-What are you doing?
-Dude, I'm stuck!
-Come on. I'm stuck.
-You seriously stuck?
Don't!
Dude, here she comes! Help!
Get it!
Hold on, hold on. I gotta get--
Okay, okay.
-I got it, I got it.
-Help me!
We'll spit on it.
You know, lubrication.
-That's gross, dude!
-Okay, fine.
-Here she comes.
-Spit! Spit!
Good news. I talked to my supervisor
and he said I could give you...
-...the address after all.
-That's great.
But the bad news is...
...I'm gonna have to
confiscate your pinky.
-All right, next stop, find my car.
-Good.
Hey, check it out.
Totally gay Nordic dudes at 3:00.
Wait. I got an idea.
We just ask for
the continuum transfunctioner?
-Yeah. It's that easy.
-Thank you both very much.
-Hey, don't mention it.
-See you around the galaxy, dudes.
Time to get your car.
The creepy space nerds are back, dude.
Dude, do not worry about them.
Yeah, they're totally harmless.
Now may I have
the continuum transfunctioner?
Not quite yet.
Would you consider giving it to me
while I continue to give you pleasure?
Okay.
-Wake up, dude.
-Oral pleasure?
What?
Nothing.
Get dressed.
We're going to the big house.
Nice outfits.
They're not outfits.
They're interstellar jumpsuits.
-Hey. Nice interstellar jumpsuits.
-Yeah.
Wow! Nice place.
Is this where Zoltan--?
-Is this where Zoltan hangs out?
-No.
This is his parents' house.
We're going over there.
-A barn?
-Is it red?
-No.
-Then it's not a barn!
-This is creepy.
-It's like a country music video.
All right, that's far enough.
You, there. You, over there.
No messing around.
Okay, do you remember which one it is?
-Here, let me show you.
-I'll do it.
-It's that one.
-Hey, grab the--
Keys.
Grab the fire extinguisher
and bonk those dudes on the head.
You want the fire extinguisher?
-Enough!
-No, no, it's that one.
Fudge!
Cool.
What, are you deaf?
Hey, you don't have to be mean.
How are we gonna get out of here?
Your attention, please.
Our imperial commander, Zoltan...
...requests your presence
in the officentary rec room...
...for a Level 7 meeting. Over.
It is now my great pleasure...
...to present to you
our wise and powerful leader...
-...Zoltan.
-Zoltan.
Zoltan.
The time has come, you guys.
We are finally going to fulfill...
...our prophecy of outer space travel.
Zoltan.
They laughed at us
when we said aliens existed.
They mocked us when we wore
bubble-wrap jumpsuits.
But who's laughing now, huh?
I'll tell you who's laughing.
We are!
Zoltan.
Soon we will leave this lame planet...
...and fly through outer space...
...with cool aliens who like us.
It is going to be awesome!
Zoltan!
That's them! They knocked us out
and stole our space suits!
-No, we didn't.
-Yeah, you did!
-Yes, you did!
-No, we didn't.
Hey, who you gonna believe,
us or them?
So you're Jesse and Chester.
I've been looking forward
to meeting you guys...
...although, sorry
it had to be like this.
-Chester!
-Jesse!
-Wanda.
-Wilma!
Normally, we wouldn't
resort to violence...
...but we are dealing with
the continuum transfunctioner.
If you don't deliver it to us,
your girlfriends are history.
Don't worry, girls. We'll save you.
Yeah, you can depend on us.
Enough.
Go now, and bring us
the continuum transfunctioner.
And be quiet on your way out.
My parents are taking a nap.
And then tell us where...
-...the continuum transfunctioner is.
-And then?
-And then we'll be able to go get it.
Can I get an order
of shrimp fried rice?
-I don't see the car.
-It better be in there.
I almost lost my pinky for it.
Oh, man, I'm sensing something
very Canadian about this place.
Plan B.
All right.
Are you ready?
Let's do this.
One, two, three.
I'm okay. You okay?
Shibby.
Dude, it's a llama.
It's not a llama. It's an ostrich.
Okay, okay, okay...
...very slowly, let's turn around...
-...and go back the other way.
-Okay.
New plan.
We turn around again, very slowly...
-...and go back the other way.
-Okay.
They're everywhere.
What now?
Hey, I saw this thing
about ostriches on Animal Planet.
-They're llamas, dude.
-No.
What you're supposed to do
is stand very still...
...and eventually,
they'll get bored and go away.
I think it's working.
Stupid llamas!
Chester!
Just get in this car!
Go, go!
What do ostriches eat?
-Why?
-Well...
...if they eat peanuts...
...we can just throw a peanut
and they'll go away.
-We don't have any peanuts.
-Weak! We're screwed!
They're leaving. It worked.
What worked?
Whatever we did!
Now may I have
the continuum transfunctioner?
Not quite yet.
Please?
Scary dream, huh?
What's up? My name is Mark.
-Where are we?
-You're in the punishment room.
This is where he likes to keep
the ostrich poachers.
-Poachers?
-Yeah, that's right.
I've been in this cage for three
years, five months, and 17 days...
...but who's counting?
How's my breath?
That bad, huh?
Where you guys from?
I'm from Connecticut. Hi. Mark.
There we go.
Chester! Get him off!
Pierre!
No, that's not what it looks like.
Maybe a little bit.
-How was your nap?
-Shut up!
Okay. Well, somebody
sure is a Grumpy Gus today.
In France, when a man is caught
poaching ostriches...
...we shave his head, and we make him
run through the fields.
Oh, God, that's the good part.
Once you have seen this...
...you are never quite the same.
-Okay.
-Tell me about it. I used to model.
Lucky for you, I am an honorable man.
A what? I'm sorry?
I said, "I am an honorable man."
I'm sorry, I-- "Honorgable"?
-Honorable.
-"Honorgable."
-What are you saying?
-Honorable.
I think you're trying
to say honorable.
-Shut up!
-Hey! I'm sorry.
All right, here it is.
I am going to ask you a question.
If you get it right,
I will set you free.
If you get it wrong, well,
you will be spending a lot of time...
...with the ever-popular Mark.
I can be very nice.
All right. Here it is.
What is the average running speed...
...of a full-grown male
African ostrich?
Pass.
-Pass to me. I know it.
-Pass to Mark.
You cannot pass! Shut up!
Do I have to hose you down again?
Don't hose me!
Maybe later.
-Dude, we're dead.
-Hey, not so fast.
The full-grown male African ostrich
or the Latin Struthio camelus...
...can grow to an average size
of 6 feet, 6 inches...
...and weigh from 225 to 350 pounds...
...and can get up to an average speed
of 27 miles per hour.
This is absolutely correct!
Animal Planet.
Well, I said, "Brown."
Here, let me get you out
of this stinking cage.
Oh, please forgive me.
Can I get you guys some beers?
I'd like a near beer, please.
Shut up!
We just came about the car
you bought today.
We wanted to get some stuff out.
No problem. Right this way.
-It was nice meeting you guys.
-Good luck with the modeling thing.
You e-mail me, okay? FreakInCage.com.
Sacre bleu, the car was here
this afternoon. It-- It--
It just disappear!
-How do you just lose a car?
-I'm so sorry, you guys.
-I feel terrible.
-All right, Pierre, just focus here.
Was there anything in the car?
No, nothing.
Except, of course, for this.
Dude!
Dude, I'm having my next
birthday party here for sure.
Yeah, me too.
Cool.
Excuse me. Can you tell me
where locker 206 is?
Yeah, it's right over there.
It's you guys!
Dude, you guys played...
...an amazing round
of putt-putt last night.
-We did?
-Oh, yeah.
-Thanks, dude.
-Shibby.
Here it is.
-I sure hope my money's in there.
-Yep.
-Who are you?
-This is my boyfriend, Patty.
Nice to meet you.
How do you keep popping up?
Less questions,
more giving me my money.
Well, I guess this is it.
Yep. The moment of truth.
It's been a long, strange trip, dude.
It sure has, Jesse.
Hey! I've got a plane to catch.
Okay, okay, okay.
Oh, my suitcase!
Oh, my God! You guys are the best.
Thank you so much.
Thanks for your help, fella.
Good work.
Are we supposed to be
grossed out by this, or...?
I don't know.
Bye.
Look at this stuff.
Captain Stu tickets.
Awesome!
Oh, jellybeans.
No jellybeans.
Cool straw.
-I'm gonna keep this.
-Yeah.
I don't see a
continuum transfunctioner.
Wait a second. What do we know
about the continuum transfunctioner?
It's a very mysterious
and powerful device.
And?
And its mystery
is only exceeded by its power.
But has anyone ever said
what it looks like?
No.
They haven't.
That was Jesse and Chester.
They've got
the continuum transfunctioner!
Quick! To my mother's minivan!
That was Jesse and Chester.
They've got
the continuum transfunctioner.
Quick! To my step dad's pickup truck!
I'm getting the hang
of this thing, dude.
Yes!
Oh, yes! I finally beat you!
You. You're a competitor.
Oh, boy. You got me the first nine,
but not number 10.
Not gonna happen.
-Final showdown time.
-Chester.
-Jesse.
-Don't worry, girls.
We're here to save the day.
Quit it. These things are expensive.
Enough! Do you have
the continuum transfunctioner or not?
Right here.
-Now release the girls.
-First give up the transfunctioner.
-First release the girls.
-First give us the transfunctioner.
Same time.
Yes!
There they are.
Okay, stoners, where's
the continuum transfunctioner?
Release dodo bird.
-Tommy, you're such a jerk.
-Yeah.
-That's our continuum transfunctioner.
-Well, now it's mine.
Nerd.
-Dude, let's get out of here.
-Yeah.
Where is the
continuum transfunctioner?
We don't have it.
But we'd like you to meet
our girlfriends, Wanda and Wilma.
We've already met.
-Stay away from our boyfriends.
-You fake-breasted sluts.
Okay, let's go this way.
Halt. Where is the
continuum transfunctioner?
You want to go talk
to that guy over there.
Let the pleasure begin.
That's not the
continuum transfunctioner.
Of course, it is.
Follow the kids.
Come on, follow them.
Go, go, go.
Nerd-bashing time.
It's not our fault.
It was them.
Looking for a Smokey McPot.
I have a delivery
for a Smokey McPot.
-You ordered pizza?
-I figured we'd get hungry.
Oh, no, it's you two!
Look, I almost got it.
You're really starting to irk me
with your Rubik's Cube fixation!
Sweet!
No wonder they're so impossible.
You've activated the
continuum transfunctioner.
What's going on?
Once all five of the
dirugian crystals stop flashing...
...the universe will be destroyed.
How do you know?
We intercepted
interstellar transmissions.
-Zoltan.
-Nerds.
Way to go, Chester.
Sorry.
You must give it to us
to deactivate it.
We are the keepers
of the transfunctioner.
They will use it
to destroy the universe.
No, we are the keepers
of the continuum transfunctioner.
-They want to destroy the universe.
-Stop copying us.
-Bitch.
Don't you guys remember?
We came to this planet last night...
...to escape the clutches
of those evil space sluts.
-We met you here.
-You gave us a ride to our spaceship.
And we realized we'd lost
the continuum transfunctioner.
Hurry, there's only three
blinking lights left.
Bye-bye, universe.
He's right, dude.
We're gonna make the wrong decision.
You know what, dude? I refuse
to let us go down in history...
...as the dudes
who destroyed the universe.
How do we find out
which ones are the true keepers?
It's simple. We ask them
a question about last night...
...that only the ones that are
telling the truth would know.
But we can't remember a thing.
-You gotta hurry.
-Not now, Jeff.
Zip it.
If we really did give one of you guys
a ride last night...
...then you'll know
the answer to this.
Hurry!
What score did we get
on the 18th hole...
...of the miniature golf course
last night?
You got a hole in one.
That is...
...correct!
Deactivation complete.
Wait. If you guys don't remember
a thing about last night....
-How do you know they told the truth?
-It's simple.
The pudding!
-You guys had a plan!
-And it actually worked.
For the love of God!
Wow! Morphing is cool!
Whoa! That is one
super hot giant alien!
Just go!
-Chester!
-Jesse!
That is amazing!
Yeah. Those are the biggest
hoo-hoos I have ever seen.
Do you spit or swallow?
Swallow!
We will now use the power
of the continuum transfunctioner...
...to banish you
to Hoboken, New Jersey.
-What are we supposed to do now?
-I think we run, dude!
Boy, those guys are in a hurry.
-I want to go on that ride, Daddy.
-Me too, son. Me too.
-What do we do with this?
-You've gotta activate...
...the photon accelerator
annihilation beam!
-The what?
-They said, "the photon accelerator...
...annihilation beam," you fool!
Hurry, activate it, dude!
-This is it!
-Thanks, Captain Obvious!
I can't reach it!
Deep in your consciousness,
you must look!
Concentrate on
the knowledge inside, you must!
Does he have to talk like that?
I like the way he talks.
Chimpanzees often use sticks
as crude tools.
I've got it!
Oh, boy!
We saved the universe!
The big bitch is dead!
Damn! Now those are
some big-ass panties.
-Honey, could you give me a hand?
-No, Tommy. I've found somebody else.
Jesse and Chester saved us.
You'll still take us
to outer space with you, right?
There is a party in the Crab Nebula.
You can come too.
Crab Nebula!
-Here you go.
-Thanks for your help.
-Jesse and Chester.
-You've ensured the universe's safety.
Well, that's cool and all...
...but, dude, where's my car?
You mean you guys don't remember?
-Damn, you were wasted last night.
-Now, we must eliminate...
...knowledge of this encounter.
No. We have so many questions...
...we want to ask you
about the universe.
-Like what?
-Well....
Have you guys
ever been to Uranus?
Nice!
-Morning, guys.
-Morning, Gene.
We'll go to the twins'.
-And then?
-Then we'll give them their gifts.
-We'll apologize for the house.
-And then?
-We get our special treats.
-Dude, that's really annoying.
Sorry.
Dude, where's my car?
Where's your car, dude?
Dude, there's your car.
"I heart you."
You guys are great boyfriends.
-And we have something for you too.
-A very special treat.
Shibby!
Ta-da!
We sewed the names on ourselves.
Wow.
Put them on.
You guys look great.
In berets?
What are these?
More gifts.
-They're beautiful.
-Where did you guys get these?
This...
...place.
-Wow.
-Me first.
"Thanks for helping
to save the universe.
Hope your girls like these gifts.
You will. "
How wasted were we last night?
-Sweet!
-Dude!
-Is anyone hungry?
-Yeah.
-I could go for Chinese food.
-Sounds great.
Sweet!
-My back itches, dude.
-Jesse, you got a tattoo.
Oh, my God. So do you, Chester.
-No way. What's mine say?
-"Dude."
-What about mine?
-"Sweet."
-Yeah, but what does mine say?
-"Dude"!
-What about mine?
-"Sweet."
I know, they're sweet,
but, dude, what's mine say?
"Dude"!
-What about mine?
-"Sweet"!
I can do sexy.
How do you keep popping up like this?
Come on, this isn't fair.
They're mooning us.
Sweet, dude.
It's good, right?
-Sweet!
-Dude!
-I am fun-loving. I like charades.
-Shut up!
Go ahead and laugh.
Hold on a second.
Zoltan!
That's a keeper.
Fingers crossed.
I got it!
You want a piece of this?
-Dude!
-Sweet!
-And then?
-And then we went and--
-Got those sweet jumpsuits so we--
-And then?
-Then we went and-- I'm losing it.
I am fun-loving, without my clothes.
The platonic--
The gray thing, dummy!
-Dude!
-Sweet!
Can we cut?
We gotta cut. We have to.
You have to cut.
You guys have to cut.
Cut!
Punk-ass kids!
And then?