MK: Somebody told me once...
that if you stand still
in the forest long enough...
you'll see signs of
a hidden struggle.
Raging between
forces of life and decay.
That the survival
of the forest itself
depends on the outcome.
And that the good guys need
all the help they can get.
And that if you
don't believe it,
take a close look.
And if you still don't,
look closer.
(SQUAWKING)
(DEVICE BEEPING)
BOMBA: Oh! Oh!
Mmm-hmm. (HUMMING)
(GROANING)
Ah! Oh, oh, oh!
Whoa! I... (PANTING)
(GROANS)
(CHUCKLES)
(SQUAWKING CONTINUES)
(BOMBA PANTING)
(GASPING)
Oh!
(GASPS)
(SCREECHING)
(GROANS)
(CHIRPS)
(GASPS)
(CAWING)
(GRUNTING)
(GASPS)
(GROANS)
(SCREAMING)
(WAVERING GROANS)
Whoa!
Need a lift?
I don't need your help!
You're running out of
branch there, buddy.
Still don't need
your help. (GASPS)
(SCREAMS)
Whoa! Oh!
(SCREECHING)
(ROARS)
(GRUNTING)
Why aren't you
with your group?
What? I fly
faster alone!
How do you
not get this?
You're not the only one
on this team, you know.
So yell at one of them
for a change.
You hear that?
What am I supposed
to do with this kid?
(GROWLS)
Ah, you're right. (GRUNTING)
You've got
your own problems.
(SCREAMING)
You're a Leafman.
You know how
important today is.
You know what? I'm
thinking maybe I'm just
not cut out for this.
That's the problem.
You are cut out for it.
But I'm tired of
waiting for you
to prove it.
Get a bird and get
back to Moonhaven,
or you're done.
What, you're not
going to help me now?
I just did.
That's cool!
I could probably
just jump from here!
Just follow
that last guy down!
Whoa! Incoming.
(LAUGHING)
Bet they didn't
have bugs like that
in the city.
Yeah. I miss it already.
She talks!
Something on
your mind, kid?
(SIGHS)
What do you say to
a total stranger?
Stranger?
You and I go
back twenty minutes.
Not you... Larry.
I mean the person
I'm visiting.
I'm leaving you
out here with someone
you don't know?
(CHUCKLES) It's okay, Lar.
We weren't always strangers.
Maybe now things
will be different.
WOMAN: (SINGING)
♪ And everyone says
♪ This love will change you
♪ Well, I ask
♪ Does anything ever
stay the same?
♪ No, no, no
♪ It's strange changes
That's not a house,
that's termites
holding hands. No offense.
Don't worry, Lar.
I'll be--
(TIRES SCREECHING)
Call if you need
a quick getaway, kid!
Fine.
(SIGHS)
Hello?
Anyone home?
(FAINT BEEPING)
Hello?
(DOOR CLOSING)
Okay. No, actually,
you know what?
I should check this bee.
No, that's (CHUCKLES)
right there. Uh...
Do we have-- I had it
we-- Oh, no, it's over here.
Okay. Yeah.
Uh, let's see.
Uh...
Made of--
Oh, gosh!
I don't know,
polished acorn shell
and thin leather?
Perhaps mouse hide.
Pardon me,
excuse me, sorry.
Correction:
not mouse hide.
Shrew, perhaps.
Or, you know what,
actually, it could be vole.
Hi, Dad.
Oh!
Mary Katherine!
Yeah.
You're here! Mmm!
I didn't realize
today was today.
It always is.
Hey, let me
look at you! Oh...
You look just
like your mother.
Like she did.
(STAMMERING)
You would, if you
know what I mean...
Dad.
Do you want to talk
about it, if that's--
Thanks,
but I've been reading up
on the five stages of grief.
I'm working
through them myself.
I'm good like that.
(SIGHS)
There actually
are a few things
I would like
to talk about.
(DOG BARKS)
Oh, oh, oh! Ozzy!
Look who's back!
Ozzy? (GASPS)
He's still alive?
Well, you know,
most of him.
He may be down to
three legs, but he'll
make a break for it...
the first chance
he gets. (LAUGHS)
Ozzy, go say hi.
(BARKING)
Here, boy!
BOMBA:
Ah, there he goes.
His depth perception's
a little off...
and he has
a tendency to
run in circles.
Hey, but that was closer
than usual, you know?
(LAUGHS)
He remembers you!
(GLASS SHATTERING)
(OZZY BARKING)
So, I have
a little surprise
for you up here.
Just follow me,
take a look.
Ozzy! No. No kisses.
Well, here we are.
Welcome home.
It's like
I never left.
All your things are here,
you got your dolls and...
your pictures,
your turtle.
Oh, dear.
(STAMMERS) Well,
it's good to have you
back, Mary Katherine.
Actually,
I go by MK now.
Oh! MK.
I like that.
It's more grown-up.
(DEVICE BEEPING)
Oh! Um... Hmm.
Do you have
to get that?
Oh, no. No. That was just
one of my sensors.
I got a lot
going on right now.
Today is actually
a highly unusual day.
There is both
a full moon tonight
and the summer solstice...
which only coincide
every hundred years or so.
You can imagine,
it's just crazy
over here.
Hey! Uh...
You probably want
some time to settle in.
I'm just going to let you
make yourself at home,
Mary Kather--
Oh! No, who's
Mary Katherine?
MK, I mean.
(FOOTSTEPS DESCENDING STAIRS)
(SIGHS)
Okay, Mom, I'm trying.
That was the deal.
(WHIMPERS)
Oh, my.
(GASPS)
(ALL GASPING)
Oh!
Come on, Mom,
you're going to
miss them.
Hey, Leafmen!
Huh? What?
Queen Tara,
we need to discuss
today's ceremony.
The Boggans have
crossed our border again.
You're not getting
enough sunshine.
Yes, it's Ronin.
Well, I think he looks
silly kneeling, too,
but I can't get him
to stop doing it.
I think the Boggans
are scouting our defenses.
You know they'd do
anything to stop you
from choosing an heir.
But don't worry,
I've got a plan.
When we were kids
he wasn't so serious.
Would you like
to hear my plan?
And he had
the sweetest smile.
Look, instead of
a public ceremony,
I go in with
a small platoon...
pretend we're
stopping for a drink.
We grab a pod,
bring it back to you.
It blooms, the life of
the forest continues.
We're in, we're out.
(LAUGHING)
It doesn't work
that way.
I can't choose
unless I'm there.
It's about the feeling.
I get it
from the pods...
from the forest...
I get it
from all of us.
There we are.
Don't you have
feelings, Ronin?
Yes, I feel this is
a bad idea.
The Boggans have never
been this aggressive.
I'm not completely
helpless, you know.
I am aware.
But you're
the life of the forest.
Looking after you
is my duty.
Is that the only
reason you do it?
Isn't that
reason enough?
If that's the only
reason there is.
Your Majesty.
Yes?
I'm not ticklish.
(LAUGHS) Oh!
You used to be! (SIGHS)
Very well.
I understand
your concern...
but this is the one day
in a hundred years
I can choose an heir.
If I don't
do this today...
there won't be
a future to protect.
(PANTING)
(CHUCKLES)
I don't think I saw
a salute, Boggan! (LAUGHS)
(GRUMBLES)
(LAUGHS)
(GASPS)
(GROWLS)
(YELPS)
We had a little
skirmish with some
Leafmen this morning.
A rat got caught
in the crossfire...
so I got a new coat.
(LAUGHS NERVOUSLY)
It's, uh, just like yours!
Did you find the location
of their ceremony?
Uh...
Yes, sir!
It's way outside
of our borders.
You mean their borders?
The Leafmen think they can
keep us contained...
surround our
beautiful island of rot...
with their
hideous green forest.
So arrogant!
All in the name
of balance.
I'm sick of balance.
No matter how
much of the forest
we destroy...
the queen regrows it
with one wave of her hand.
She needs to be cut down!
At the root!
Exactly.
Today we'll show them
you just can't stop the rot.
If the queen dies
without an heir...
the Leafmen can't
regrow anything.
The balance swings
in our favor forever.
Leaving you and me...
rulers of a desperate,
desiccated kingdom.
I won't let you down...
Dad.
I know you won't.
You look good in rat.
It's slimming.
(CHUCKLES)
ALL: Yeah!
(CHILDREN GIGGLING)
NOD: Look out,
look out!
Here comes
your star pupil.
Oh, oh, oh!
(SIGHS)
Where have you been?
Wait, you're mad?
You told me to
get back and I'm back.
On this!
(COUGHS)
And you want
credit for that?
You're late.
Find a real bird and
get back to your group.
You know what? No.
What did you say?
I'm not doing it.
I'm not a kid anymore
and I'm tired of you
treating me like one.
I'm trying to help you,
I'm trying to
look out for you.
I never asked you
to do that.
Your father did.
Well, you can stop.
I absolve you of all
further responsibility
in the raising of young Nod.
Don't walk away from me.
(STAMMERS) I'm
your commanding officer!
Not anymore!
I quit! Hyah!
Whoa! Thatta girl.
Easy, easy!
What are you looking at?
Nothing. I have
no opinion on this.
Everyone, mount up!
(CROWD CHEERING)
(ALL CHEERING)
Parade! Fun! Smiling!
MK: Dad!
Dad!
Is this a good time
to talk?
Ow. Hold on,
I'll be right down!
Ow! (GRUNTING)
(BOMBA YELPS)
(GLASS SHATTERS)
BOMBA: Ozzy!
Ozzy, stop! (LAUGHS)
Fetch the camera!
(PANTING)
(GROANING)
Why do you have
security cameras, anyway?
Do people around here
steal old newspapers?
Oh, no, no. They're not
security cameras. (GRUNTS)
No, I have an extensive
network all through
the forest, yeah.
(STAMMERS) I don't know
how much your mother
told you about my work.
Um... nothing.
Just that you have
a delusional belief...
in an advanced society
of tiny people
living in the woods...
and it ruined
your career...
not to mention
your marriage.
Or something?
(LAUGHS) Well...
your mother
had a wonderful
sense of humor.
But I'm not delusional.
I know they're out there.
It's intuition,
like scientists
intuited the atom.
These little guys
are a big part of
the ecosystem...
the engine, if you will,
and I will prove it. Here.
(BATS SCREECHING ON RECORDING)
You have bat sounds
on your iPod? Why?
To study them.
They don't really
fly in your hair.
That's a myth.
But I was
trying to identify...
the frequencies that
draw bats to gather
with their own kind.
So I slowed
the sounds down...
and I put them through
some proprietary filters...
and guess what I heard.
(SIGHS) Voices?
Yes!
(INDISTINCT CHATTERING)
(GROWLING)
Isn't that cool?
Okay...
if tiny men are flying
around in the forest...
how come I've
never seen them?
No, that's easy.
(LAUGHS)
It's the same reason
we can't hear them.
They just move too fast,
like insects.
(FLY BUZZING)
Didn't you ever wonder
why it was so
hard to swat a fly?
My theory is they're
actually living faster.
Like in
a different dimension.
So, no matter how fast
we think we are...
to them we're just
big and dumb and...
(SLOWLY)
slow.
(FLY CONTINUES BUZZING)
Have you ever seen one?
Well, you know, uh...
You know what?
Just because you haven't
seen something...
doesn't mean
it's not there.
I, you know, that's...
Come on.
(GROWLS)
Okay, we need to talk.
I know it's a lot
to take in.
I mean about us.
Oh, no! No,
we'll do it together!
Yeah, both of us.
Here, I made this
for you.
Dad, look...
I am almost old enough
to be on my own anyway...
so I think it would
be better if I just...
Um...
You don't want
to live here?
That's what you want?
No, it's not
what I want.
I want you to stop!
All this!
And be normal. I just,
I want a dad who's not--
(BEEPING)
(ALARM RINGING)
Oh, um, okay.
This is big.
This is a big thing
going on right now.
Let me just find--
Where are you going?
I'm just going to
investigate, rather--
Okay, something
must be happening.
(MONITORS BEEPING)
Ooh! Uh... Let's see.
Where's my camera?
Are you serious?
You have to
catch these things
in the moment...
while they're happening...
otherwise you miss
a chance that could be
gone forever.
You're missing
a chance right now!
Are you even listening?
Look, you've got
to believe me.
I am so close.
All I need is one
little breakthrough.
This could be it!
I will clear this
all up when I get back!
I promise!
Sure, Dad.
I'll be here.
In reality.
(SUITCASE THUDDING)
Bye, Ozzy.
It's not you.
(WHIMPERING)
Uh, Larry? I need
that getaway cab.
I said, pick me up
by the-- Hello?
Ugh! No bars! (GASPS)
(OZZY BARKING)
Ozzy! Heel!
Stop! Play dead!
How are you so fast
on three legs?
Ozzy!
Isn't she pretty?
She's awesome!
She moved those trees
with her mind!
Mom, can I be queen
when I grow up?
Oh, honey, it doesn't
work that way.
Today, Queen Tara
gives her power to
a special Pod...
so the life of
the forest will continue.
It's all
very mysterious, and--
Sweetie,
what are you doing?
(GRUNTING)
(GASPS) Mom!
I did it!
Did what?
Aw!
She's coming!
Don't do anything
to embarrass me...
or it could ruin
my chances of being
a Leafman.
Why do you want
to be a Leafman?
They gotta
wear uniforms.
Me? I like to let
it all hang free.
You see this,
you see that?
Yeah, don't do that.
That's vile.
Come on, I know you
got a little belly, too.
(LAUGHING)
QUEEN TARA:
Gentlemen.
Hey. Your Majesty.
Hello.
It's all right.
Relax, it's just me.
Mub, Grub, it's
a very nice-looking
group of Pods.
I might have
a hard time picking one.
Do you have a favorite?
Well, Your Majesty,
we have had quite
the debate.
Really gone
back and forth.
You'll note
the carefully curated
selection of sizes,
densities, color.
With so many variables,
you can't be too hasty.
Boom! Right here.
Biggest
in the bunch.
Hmm.
Well, that's
one way to go.
How about that one?
What? That one?
For real?
But it's so--
Perfect!
It's perfect.
Excellent choice,
Your Majesty.
Sometimes the biggest one
isn't the best one.
Ow!
(WHISPERING) I told you,
she doesn't like gaudy, Mub.
Unlike you, she's got class.
This is it.
This is the one.
BOTH: Aw!
(DISTANT CAWING)
Boggans.
(GROANS)
Your Majesty!
Get to the barge!
(BOGGAN SCREECHING)
I told you
she was awesome!
LEAFMAN:
Hold the formation!
This is it, Mub!
My chance to be a Leaf--
(GROANING)
What? Your chance
to be a what?
Ronin!
(GRUNTS)
(WIND HOWLING)
Ozzy?
Oh, come on, Ozzy.
(TREE THUDDING)
(GROANS)
We had numbers,
and we had
the surprise part!
How are we losing?
Patience, son.
The forest wasn't
grown in a day.
But we can destroy it
in one. Right?
Ha! That's the spirit!
You take the Pod,
I'll take the queen.
(GASPS)
(GRUNTS)
(BOTH LAUGHING)
Nice one!
You're stealing
my moves, kid!
Your Majesty,
come with me!
Take her to safety!
I have to lead them
away from the crowd!
You're totally my hero!
(GASPS)
(WHISTLING)
Okay...
so maybe
you were right.
Remind me to gloat later.
(LAUGHS)
(GROANS)
Son! No!
(THUNDER RUMBLING)
Ozzy!
(LIGHTNING CRASHES)
(GASPS)
(GRUNTING)
Ah!
Oh! (PANTING)
Ah! Ah, ah!
Ahhh!
(GROANING)
Huh?
(GASPS)
Are you okay?
Are you all right? (GASPS)
Oh, my gosh,
that's an arrow.
(STAMMERING)
Should I pull it out?
I don't know what to do.
Take the Pod
to Nim Galuu.
Nim what?
You need a doctor.
Somebody call--
What is this thing?
It's the life
of the forest.
(LEAVES RUSTLING)
Tara!
So serious.
(EXHALES SOFTLY)
(GASPS)
(SIGHS)
I'm so sorry.
What did she
say to you?
Something about glue?
Or a canoe.
Nim Galuu.
The scroll keeper.
We don't know
anything about the Pod
without Tara.
Maybe he does.
Take the Leafmen
to Moonhaven.
Fortify it.
Keep everyone safe.
What about you?
Mandrake will be
looking for this Pod...
but he won't be
looking for a Leafman
traveling alone.
That's not
what I meant.
I know what you meant.
I'll send word
when I reach Nim's.
Who are you people?
Is this some
sort of reenactment?
(BUZZING)
That's a big bug.
No, it's about
average, actually.
(GIGGLES)
Then what? I'm tiny?
(GASPS)
Oh, no.
No.
No, no, no.
I'm not sure
why the queen brought
you here either...
but she gave you that Pod,
so you have to come with me.
Make me big!
Excuse me?
I'm not going
anywhere until you
make me big again!
Uh... You know what?
I don't do magic.
You can talk to
Nim Galuu about that,
he might know something.
Might?
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
Not so fast, soldier boy.
You do not yank
on a Pod, okay?
Especially when
it's attached to
something so lovely.
Talking snails.
Actually, he's a snail.
I'm a slug.
No shell over here, baby.
It just slows me down.
Ronin, right?
Head of the Leafmen?
Big fan.
I just love what
you do with your jaw.
Yes, that!
We are the official
Pod caretakers, sir.
It can't survive
without us.
We keep it moist.
Moist is what we do.
You're kidding.
You're not kidding. Fine.
(GRUNTING) Word of
the queen's passing
will travel fast...
we have to
travel faster.
With all this extra
weight we're going to
need another bird.
Bird. Of course.
By any chance...
you don't happen
to be part of an
advanced society...
of tiny people living
in the woods, do you?
(BOTH LAUGHING)
RONIN: Some are more
advanced than others.
(CROWD CHEERING)
ANNOUNCER: And that's
another lap down. These
racers are in it to win...
and they'd better be,
we've got some
heavy betting
in the crowd today.
They're clustering
together--
I'm telling you,
this is where I belong!
You belong in
the back of the pack!
I mean racing!
The best man wins.
No other rules,
nobody telling you
what to do.
You talk too much!
And you ain't
winning this race!
Sorry, can't hear you!
Going too fast!
Hey. (LAUGHS) Nice old
fleabag you got there.
It's not the bird,
it's how you ride it.
Yeah? Prove it.
Fetch!
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
ANNOUNCER:
That's a dirty trick,
which, let's face it,
is exactly what we've
come to see.
Final lap!
This is bird racing,
folks, it's not a parade.
Looks like Nod's
out of the race.
(GASPS)
(GRUNTS)
Wait a minute,
is that--
Nod is down
but not out!
Don't let his
old bird fool you!
The kid's on
the comeback trail!
You know what
we'll do if you win?
I don't know, lose?
ANNOUNCER:
It's the final lap.
They're beak to beak,
wing to wing...
and it's Nod by
a tail feather!
The odds-on
favorite takes it home.
(ALL CHEERING)
I bet there's
a lot of happy faces
in the crowd right now.
(GROANING)
Is that the best
you've got?
(NOD GROANS)
GOON 2: How was that?
NOD: (GRUNTS) Better.
Nod, you know
I like you.
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
Yeah, I like you, too,
Mr. Bufo.
And yet,
you don't do
what we agreed.
We agreed that
you would lose,
but then you win.
Now, I can't help it
if I'm fast.
You want me to lose,
you gotta give me
some better competition.
It's called teamwork.
Maybe if you
understood that...
the Leafmen wouldn't
have kicked you out.
They did not
kick me out. I quit.
(LAUGHS)
I admire your
independent spirit, Nod,
I'll miss that.
Feed him to something.
A snake would be good.
No, snakes just
swallow you whole.
Now, if you put him
in a hornets' nest,
that's a show.
Ah, look, it's Ronin,
defender of the weak...
pooper of parties,
here to ruin the fun.
I didn't ruin all of it.
I let you hit him.
Twice.
Hop along now,
little froggy.
Easy, Ronin,
it's a big forest
out there.
Even Leafmen gotta sleep.
You're wasting your time.
I'm not coming back.
I'm not asking.
Oh, I see. The old
reverse psychology.
Make me feel guilty,
get me to beg you.
I didn't come for you.
The queen is dead.
What? How?
Boggan ambush.
(STAMMERING) Ronin,
I don't know what to say.
She was your...
I'm sorry.
What's going to
happen to us,
to the forest?
If we don't get
the Pod to Nim Galuu's,
the forest will die.
NOD: Let me grab my saddle.
(LAUGHS) What?
No. I didn't ask
for your help.
Really? Because it
sounds like you could use
a rider with my--
Ability to
absorb punches?
The situation's desperate.
Let's not make it hopeless.
All right, well,
who's with you?
Who's riding point?
(ALL LAUGHING)
MUB: Uh-oh.
Get your saddle.
I'll get my saddle.
(CHUCKLES NERVOUSLY)
(LAUGHING)
This doesn't make any--
I mean, it makes sense.
(LAUGHING)
Mary Katherine,
you're not gonna believe
these readings...
they are off
the charts!
The wind,
and the rain
and lightning!
And the birds
were flying!
In a storm!
Okay, and that's
not normal.
Which would prove--
(STAMMERING)
Actually, you know what?
(MUFFLED) I'm going to
make some lunch...
and I'll tell
you all about it.
(MUFFLED BARKING)
Ozzy, what are you
doing outside?
Did you see it, too?
Tell me you saw it.
Hey, Mary Katheri--
Or, no, MK! (LAUGHS)
MK, what did you
want to talk about?
What?
What is it, Ozzy?
(YELPS)
(OZZY PANTING)
Hey, I'm Nod,
by the way.
Hi. MK. Yeah.
Could you just
face the way
the bird's driving?
No, don't worry.
She practically
flies herself.
Great, because
this whole bird-riding
thing's new to me.
Are you serious?
We gotta fix that.
Here, put your
arms around me.
I just met you.
(CHUCKLES) Okay,
but you're gonna want to
hold on to something.
(MK SCREAMING)
What is wrong with you?
Do you know how hard it is
to do that without falling?
I do now!
Nod, perch your bird.
Hey, I'm just trying
to keep things...
light.
MK: What did that?
RONIN: Mandrake.
Tara's power always
kept him in check.
Now nothing can heal
what he destroys.
Except that Pod.
We have to go around.
Just for one scout?
Ever see
just one Boggan?
Hold on to me. Hyah!
Still barely know you.
(MK SCREAMING)
Nod, wait!
(CROWS SQUAWKING)
Whoa!
Get to the ground!
(GRUNTING)
This way!
(BOTH SCREAMING)
Other way!
(YELPS)
(BOTH GRUNTING)
(CROW CAWS)
(PANTING)
What was that thing?
What, you've never
seen a Boggan?
Someone had
a happy childhood.
Come on,
let's regroup.
You mean up there
with those things?
They almost killed us.
Don't turn around.
(GASPS)
Is it a Boogie?
Walk towards me slowly.
(GASPS)
(SNIFFING)
Oh, it's a mouse.
(IN CHILDISH VOICE)
Hi, mousie! I was gonna
scare it away.
What are you doing?
Look at its
little hands and its
little whiskers. Oh!
(GASPS)
(SNARLING)
(SCREAMS)
(GROWLS)
(GRUNTS)
Hello! Other person!
Jump!
I can't jump that high!
(SCREAMS)
Ohh! Ah! (SIGHS)
(GASPS) Did you see
what I just did?
Out! Jump out!
(GROANS)
(SNIFFING)
Oh, great.
Hey, over here!
Over here!
(GROANS)
Whoa, whoa!
Fuzzy mousie.
Ahh!
Nice tail.
It's flexible.
(GROANS)
Ah! Ah! Help!
(GROWLS)
(SQUEALS)
They have very
sensitive whiskers.
You know,
I had this.
Uh-huh.
Are you all right?
Dad? I had the most
messed-up dream.
There were talking slugs
and tiny little soldiers
and-- (GASPS)
Hello!
Ah, man!
Now let's move.
Where there's mice
there's bound to be
chipmunks.
New seating arrangement.
(WHISTLES)
You're riding with me.
(SIGHS)
Thank you.
You're with the slugs.
Ugh! Disgusting.
Do you and me
have a problem?
Uh, I don't think so.
What was that
over there?
A little chit-chat?
That's real cute.
You trying to jump in?
What are
we talking about?
There's a code
amongst men.
It goes something
like this.
I saw her first.
(YELPS) Ow!
You're a slug.
So? You think
she'd want you?
Look at yourself!
Oh, that's right,
you can't...
because your eyeballs
are stuck all the way
inside your head.
What's wrong, flatface?
Are you gonna cry?
Do you want me to call
your flatface mommy?
You know you're not
insulting me, right?
You're just grossing me out.
You've been warned.
Ow!
Hey, if this is
a bad time...
I can come back
when you're done
gardening.
Oh! Hey!
I imagine
you're wondering why
I invited you here.
I was frog-marched
here at spearpoint. Ah!
How is that invited?
I let you
keep your legs.
(CHUCKLES)
Comedy. Terrific.
Funny psychopath.
There are rumors
that the Leafman Ronin
was at your
place of business...
and that he may
have rescued
a Royal Pod.
(LAUGHS)
Real smooth.
You got rid of the queen,
but let her Pod get away.
Plus your idiot general
gets himself mulched.
That idiot general...
was my son!
(GASPS)
(WHIMPERS)
(STAMMERS)
Of course he was.
He had your good looks.
And your healthy
gray complexion.
And forgiving nature.
Shut up!
What's it gonna be,
Bufo?
Are you gonna talk?
Or are you gonna croak?
(WHIMPERING)
Where are they
taking the Pod?
It's clear. Hyah!
(NOD GRUNTING)
Why is he even with us?
He's not helping.
Well, when he's
not being an idiot...
he's a pretty
decent flier.
Could be one of the best.
(GRUNTS IN FRUSTRATION)
Plus his father
was my friend,
so I do what I can.
"Many leaves, one tree."
What does that mean?
RONIN: We're all individuals,
but we're still connected.
It's what
we live by.
Hyah!
Maybe you're connected,
but I'm kind of on my own.
No one's on their own.
Not even him.
Hey, Nod,
how's the view?
(MUB AND GRUB LAUGHING)
RONIN: Well...
here we are.
I thought
this was a secret
Leafmen mission.
How many people
did the queen
tell about this?
RONIN: They're here
looking for answers.
Nobody knows that
the queen is gone...
only that the blight
is spreading.
So, this Nim guy
can tell them?
He's the keeper
of our history...
but even
he may not know
about the queen.
He's not always
up to speed.
But he'll help, right?
He's, like, the wise
old man of the forest.
Uh, he's more like
the crazy uncle.
(INDISTINCT CHATTERING)
The whole meadow
just died.
Everything was green,
and now it's gone.
I grew up
in that meadow.
CONCERNED JINN:
Why isn't the queen
doing anything?
DANDELION JINN:
If anything happened to her,
everything's going to rot!
We're doomed!
Get a hold of yourself!
Oops. Sorry.
NIM: Friends!
(ALL SHUSHING)
Neighbors!
(DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING)
Prepare to see
your worries...
disappear.
(ALL GASPING IN AWE)
BOTH: Ooh!
I know rumors
have been flying...
(GASPING CONTINUES)
but the truth is
never as bad
as it seems.
I have just
returned from deep
inside this tree...
from the Rings
of Knowledge...
where every memory...
every event that
ever happens
in the forest...
is recorded
in these scrolls.
(SINGING)
♪ Listen, party poopers,
I've got something to say
♪ Dry your weeping eyes,
we're gonna be okay
♪ So you don't have to worry
about a dog gone thing
♪ The Rings of Knowledge
know everything
♪ The scrolls never lie and,
honey, neither does Nim
♪ It's right here in my hands,
all six of them
♪ So tuck your little fears
and put them right into bed
♪ It says right here
that the queen--
(STAMMERING)
That the queen is--
Uh...
What?
(STAMMERING)
Just tell us
what it says!
What's it say?
CROWD: He doesn't know
anything! Boo!
Fraud!
ALL:
♪ Dry your weeping eyes,
we're gonna be fine
♪ Everything is
really gonna be all right ♪
(GASPS) Ronin!
Did you hear
about the queen?
This is terrible!
I know, but--
We gotta do something!
We gotta keep everyone
from freaking out!
Yes, that's why we--
And the Pod!
We gotta make sure
the Royal Pod is
safely hidden...
far away. And--
(SCREAMS)
What'd you
bring it here for?
The queen's last words were
"Bring the Pod to Nim Galuu."
She say anything else?
Specific instructions?
Maybe a note?
Those were her last words.
I thought you were magic.
Magic might be
stretching it.
I'm charismatic.
Possibly charming.
Do you know
what to do with
the Pod or not?
Not a clue,
but I do know where
to look it up.
Follow me!
CROWD: There he is!
Phony! (BOOING)
Um, no, it's this way.
GRUB: The Rings
of Knowledge!
Is everything that happens
really recorded right here?
NIM: Oh, yeah.
MK: And you've read
all these scrolls?
Ah, I've skimmed them.
So, is this event
being recorded?
Right now?
Of course.
(GRUNTS) Is this?
Yes.
How about this?
BOTH: What about this?
Yep.
That should be it
right here.
Thanks, Marty.
BOTH: Aw!
Okay. Blooming a Pod.
Gotta go
way back for that.
Here we go.
Let's see.
Pod, care of.
Must keep moist.
Well, good news is,
once the queen chooses it...
it's going to
bloom no matter what.
But it has to
open tonight...
in the light of
the full moon when
it's at its highest peak.
Yep, solstice...
full moon, highest peak,
mentions it a bunch of times.
What happens
if it blooms out of
the moonlight?
Unclear.
The last part's missing.
I gotta be honest,
termites have been
a problem.
So here I thought
we were doomed.
This calls for
a celebration!
I suppose
we've earned it.
Wait...
this is gonna
sound weird, but...
I'm not from this world.
(CHUCKLES)
And I thought maybe
something in these scrolls
could tell me...
if there's a way
for me to get home.
The scrolls don't
tell the future...
they only guide us
with the knowledge
of the past.
Hey, that's
a great line!
You guys got that,
right?
So you can't help me?
I didn't say that.
I can't read this.
It's just dusty.
Blow it off.
(GASPS)
It's you.
But I saw you
turn into moss.
Come closer.
Oh, this is perfect!
You can make me big again.
Closer.
(GASPS)
It's a memory.
If you can
hear me now...
it means
you got to Nim's.
The Pod needs you.
I can't be
around for it anymore.
No, don't do that!
Why would you
give that to me?
You don't understand,
I have to get home...
this has nothing
to do with me.
You're here
for a reason.
Maybe you don't see
the connections yet.
But just because
you don't see them
doesn't mean
they're not there.
I know you're scared.
Just stay with the Pod...
be with it
when it blooms...
and then
you'll get back
what you've given.
You'll get back.
(GASPS)
Well, that was intense.
I gotta read
more of these.
That means
I can get home!
Well, if you want
to go home so bad,
then why did you leave?
(CROWD CHATTERING)
Lose the sword, Ronin,
we're done.
We're not done
until the Pod blooms.
We're bringing it
home to Moonhaven.
I need you to
watch it while I tell
the rest of the Leafmen
to expect us.
Hey, I helped you get here,
but I haven't changed my mind.
Do you think
just because you're not
a Leafman anymore...
you're not
a part of this?
Well, the fate of that Pod
affects all of us.
The queen is gone.
(CROWD GASPING)
But, as always,
she looked out for us...
even in her
final moments.
Tonight,
when this Pod blooms,
a new queen will rise!
I know you're sad.
I am, too.
But Tara wouldn't
want us to mourn!
She'd want us to
celebrate her life!
And the life
of the forest!
(CROWD CHEERING)
So, stay with it.
And don't lose
the sword.
(GROANS)
(CROWD CHATTERING)
Look, I'm thinking
that I didn't make
the best first impression.
It's okay. I've never
had a guy fight
a mouse for me before.
(CHUCKLES)
You're not from
around here, are you?
What makes you
say that?
If you were,
I would remember you.
CROWD: To Queen Tara!
To the queen!
You wanna go
somewhere quieter?
Will that be okay
with Ronin?
Yeah, he said to
watch the Pod...
but there's nowhere
safer than Nim's tree.
I think he's
just pretty upset
about the queen.
Here, let me
show you something.
(GASPS)
What?
(SCREAMING)
(GRUNTS) Huh.
That actually
gets easier.
What is--
(RUMBLING)
(GASPS)
Wow.
(DEER SNUFFLES)
NOD: Grab on!
What?
Put your arms around me.
But I barely know you.
Do you want to
ride him or not?
NIM: The scroll said
there was nothing
you could do to
save her, Ronin.
You have to know that.
Send a code
to the Leafmen.
Let them know
the Pod is safe and
we're bringing it home.
You heard him.
Go tell them, boys!
And it's happy hour
at Nim's!
Or just do
the first part.
MK: I gotta admit,
flying is nice, but
this is riding in style.
(CHUCKLES) Yeah.
Not everyone can do it.
You have to be
gentle to ride a deer.
My dad taught me how.
It's one of my
best memories of him.
You must
really miss him.
I know how that feels.
(UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING)
Fruit fly, huh?
So, what's it like,
having such
a short life cycle?
(BOY'S VOICE)
It's great, mister!
When I grow up...
(MAN'S VOICE)
I'm going to...
(OLD MAN'S VOICE)
wish I had done more
with my life, sonny.
(GASPING)
(RUMBLING)
The forest trembles
at the passing of
the humble fruit fly.
(SNARLING)
(PEOPLE SCREAMING)
Excuse me, but I've lost
something very dear to me.
It was left by a friend
who's no longer with us.
(ROARING)
BOTH: Ah!
(GASPS)
You found it!
If you want to take
this Pod, you're gonna
have to go through us!
Relax. I'm not
going to hurt it.
I need it alive.
Well, we're the only ones
that know how to
keep it that way.
Thanks for the tip.
(BOTH SCREAM)
Stay with the Pod,
that's all you had to do.
Yeah, but I just thought--
Do you ever
think about anyone
besides yourself?
It wasn't
all his fault!
And you. I expected
as much from him.
But I thought you
would know better.
We're really sorry,
okay?
I don't want to
hear it.
That was the last
part of the queen
that I-- (SIGHS)
That any of us
will ever have.
The queen gave it to me.
I should have
been here with it.
I'll do whatever it takes
to help you get it back.
I appreciate the offer,
but Wrathwood
is too dangerous.
But you can't go alone.
What about the whole
leaves-tree thing
that you said?
Nim, tell him.
Look, kid,
the moon's coming up.
That's bloom-or-die time.
So if no one has
a better plan--
Why don't we sneak in,
in disguise?
Great idea.
I'll go as a grasshopper
and you can be
my cricket ladyfriend.
It's dangerous,
I might get killed.
I thought you'd like that.
I don't have any
Boggan armor handy.
Do you?
I know where
we can get some.
Well?
I gotta say,
six hands are
better than two.
That's been
my experience.
You might want to
hang on. Hyah!
Whoa!
(NOD SCREAMING)
MUB AND GRUB:
Stop! Please!
My son was born on
a night like this.
These were
his baby fangs.
And here's
the first skin
he ever molted.
He was big
for a larva.
He took
after his mother.
(WEEPING)
Your stories are boring
and torturous!
And the Leafmen
took him from me.
So I took
something of theirs.
It's basic etiquette.
An eye for an eye.
BOTH: Ow!
Jerk!
Tonight your Pod
will bloom here.
And when a Pod
blooms in darkness,
it belongs...
to the darkness.
It will become
my little dark prince.
I'll destroy
the forest with
the very thing you
hoped would save it.
(BOTH SCOFFING)
I hate to break it to you,
but it doesn't say
that in the scrolls.
It does in
the part I have.
BOTH: D'oh!
NOD: Hey,
the Boggan armor...
where is it?
(MK GRUNTS)
Over there.
RONIN:
Let's make this quick.
Come on.
(YELPS)
Ow!
(SCREAMING)
Oh!
(GRUNTS) Ow!
That was awesome. Here.
(COUGHING)
(LAUGHING)
Up we go.
Ugh! That is
some static cling.
No, that's metal,
don't touch that!
Whoo! (GROANS)
Ow!
(WHISPERING)
Knock it off.
Ow. Quit it.
Ow! No, you quit.
I'm not doing it.
Stop!
Ow. I'm not doing--
RONIN: Now!
Come on.
(GRUNTS)
You know...
some of this
stuff looks familiar.
Hey, that's my saddle!
Where are we?
(RUMBLING)
(GASPS)
Oh, it's where
this guy lives.
(NOD CHUCKLES)
I can't believe it.
He's been crashing
around the forest
like a bear for years.
Most stompers
just come and go,
but this guy's relentless.
MK: Wait. Stompers?
NOD: Yeah.
Like us,
but big and dumb
and slow...
always stomping
on things. Stompers.
And this one
is obsessed
with finding us.
Obviously that's
a security risk.
Can't have one of
his big fat feet
stepping on Moonhaven.
One of his ginormous,
flabby, dirty, stinky--
Okay, I got it.
So we've been
throwing him
off the trail.
So you're just
messing with him?
But he's found
all this stuff.
He only finds what
we want him to find.
Look at his map.
We've got him
looking everywhere
but where we are.
(CHUCKLES)
I love how
this guy talks.
(SLOWLY)
"Look at this flower."
(LAUGHS)
(SLOWLY)
"I hurt my elbow."
(LAUGHING)
I think that's
kind of mean.
"Who said that?"
It's his life's work.
He's my dad!
He what?
I'm a stomper.
What happened?
You got shrunk?
Yes! Which he knows.
Seriously?
It's been a weird day
for everybody.
You got a problem
with stompers?
A stomper
squashed my uncle.
(GASPS)
Oh, my gosh. Really?
No. I'm messing with you.
(LAUGHS)
(GRUNTS)
Too far?
Try it again,
maybe she'll
punch you harder.
BOMBA: (SLOWLY)
I'm sorry.
(NORMAL VOICE)
I guess she's right
about me, huh, Ozzy?
All I seem to be
able to do is...
(SLOWLY)
drive people away.
No, Dad,
you didn't! I'm here!
And you're right
about all of it.
Don't stop looking.
Not now.
(CHIRPING)
(PANTING)
Dad! Dad,
just turn around!
(SNIFFING)
Uh-oh.
Ozzy...
no kisses.
(SCREAMING)
(BARKING)
Ozzy!
(PANTING)
Hey, how do I look?
Scary as ever.
(MK SCREAMING)
Are you okay?
Run!
Ozzy, will you
please stop?
(GASPS)
Oh! Oh!
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah!
They're here!
They're in my house!
(GRUNTING)
(VACUUM SUCKING)
(BOTH SCREAM)
(BARKS SLOWLY)
No!
(SLOWLY) Ow!
I hurt my elbow!
Did you hear that?
He said it! (LAUGHING)
Whoa!
Oh, oh, oh, oh!
(MK YELPING)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
No! Don't let go!
Don't let go! No!
(SCREAMING)
(GROANS)
Oh, oh!
Hello there,
my little friend!
Dad! Dad!
(GASPS)
Oh!
Dad! Dad!
(SWOONS SLOWLY)
(MK SCREAMING)
(GRUNTING SOFTLY)
RONIN: Let's go.
You can't stay.
You're with us now!
I'll come home soon, Dad.
I promise.
Come on, MK,
we gotta go.
(SIGHS)
You think he's okay?
Yeah, he'll be fine,
their heads are like rocks.
Uh, smart rocks.
That's a whole
lot of ugly.
Ugh! It smells like
something died in here.
Something did.
NOD: How do we
know where to go?
RONIN:
I've been here before...
with your father.
He never told me
about this.
He never got
the chance.
(BOTH GRUNT)
How's my dark prince?
It's fine!
Good. Because
if it dies, you die.
We know. You said.
Ugly says "what"?
What?
Nothing.
(LAUGHING)
(GASPS)
Shh!
(BATS SQUEAKING)
There's our exit.
Meet me back here
when you've got
the Pod and the slugs.
How are we supposed
to find them?
Follow the slime.
(GROANS)
Aren't you
coming with us?
I'm gonna make sure
nobody follows you.
Don't worry,
you get the easy part...
I get the fun part.
Hey, look!
It's a Leafman!
I'll keep this simple.
I run...
you try to catch me.
Let's go.
(BOTH GASP)
When I get big again,
I am so coming
back here with
a can of bug spray.
Mub. Grub.
We're down here!
I told you
she'd come for me.
(LAUGHS)
This girl is smitten.
Mmm... (GASPS)
Hand me the Pod!
Oh, come on,
you should work on
your grip, my dude.
It's a bit womanly.
(GRUNTING)
(YELPS)
No, no, no!
Whoa, whoa!
(LAUGHING)
Hurry, before
the guards come back!
GRUB: Too late!
I have a plan!
Quick!
Everybody hide
in your shells!
Oh. I have
another plan!
(MUB AND GRUB GRUNTING)
NOD: Go! Go!
MUB: Ow! That hurts!
Those are my eyes!
Can you go
any faster?
It's kind of hard
when you're
pulling on my brain!
MANDRAKE: Ronin!
What a surprise.
I get so few guests.
Could be the stench
of death. Some people
don't care for it.
It's all right.
Ronin's an old--
What do you call someone
you've known a long time...
and always wanted
to destroy?
I expected you
to come.
But I didn't think
you'd come alone.
Who said I'm alone?
(MUB AND GRUB GRUNTING LOUDLY)
(GASPS)
MK: Whoa.
(BOTH SNARLING)
Ow!
Ooh! So, what's
the plan here?
A hundred Leafmen?
A thousand?
Don't flatter yourself.
(GRUNTING)
(BOTH GROANING)
(ALL GRUNTING)
Well, now
I'm just embarrassed.
I completely
over-prepared.
(YELLING)
(ECHOING)
Go, go, go!
(GASPS)
I'm afraid you'll
find getting out...
is a lot harder
than getting in.
(SCREAMING)
NOD: Ronin!
Hang on!
Go! Take the Pod
to Moonhaven!
I'm not leaving
without you!
Now you're starting
to sound (GROANING)
like a Leafman!
Ronin!
Come on!
(WHISTLES)
Hyah!
We've been
waiting for you.
Where's Ronin?
He gave us
a head start.
But the Boggans
aren't far behind.
(CROWD CHEERING)
You guys made it!
I knew you would.
You got that
from the scrolls?
Some things
you just know.
Hmm.
Let's see.
Moonlight comes in here,
moves along here...
reaches the Pod here.
At the moon's
highest peak.
Only time
it can bloom.
Do you know
what this means?
We single-handedly
saved the forest!
Eye five! Down low.
Too slow. (LAUGHING)
So, when the Pod opens,
what happens to you?
I think I go home.
Well, I guess
this is--
Yeah, I guess it is.
Mandrake's bats!
(YELLING)
They're not attacking,
they're just
blocking out the moon.
Are you ready
for this?
(CHUCKLES)
Are you kidding?
We're outnumbered,
out of time and the fate of
the world is at stake.
Why did I quit again?
See you up there.
As soon as I can
find my helmet.
Thank you.
Hey, guys!
I'm going to
need a uniform!
And a bird!
Oh, that's...
You...
That's all right.
I'll find them myself.
A Leafman makes do.
(BATS SCREECHING)
(LEAFMEN ROARING)
(ROARS)
(MK GRUNTING)
What are you doing?
I'm going to help.
Whoa, whoa.
You heard the queen!
If you want to get home...
you have to be
here with the Pod
when it blooms.
Isn't that
what you want?
So I should
just sit here?
I didn't say that.
Then I'm going up there.
I didn't say
that either.
You don't even know
what you're saying.
I'm saying,
who gives up
everything...
for a world that's
not even theirs?
Dad. My dad does!
I have to
get my dad!
Where do you think
you're going?
The queen said
I was here for
a reason.
This must be it.
That's my girl.
Hyah!
(GASPS)
Oh, come on!
(CROW CAWING)
Mandrake!
He's headed
for Moonhaven!
Grub! The Pod!
It's blooming
in darkness!
Whoa! Hyah!
Hey, Dad!
Come on,
I need your help!
(BEEPING)
Whoa, whoa!
(GROANING)
(BARKING)
(BEEPING CONTINUES)
(BEEPING STOPS)
(GROANS) They're all
right about me, Ozzy.
All these years
just chasing things
that aren't even there.
I actually thought
I saw my daughter,
two inches tall,
stuck in a bug jar.
I've lost my mind.
And I am
talking to a dog.
(SNEEZES)
Hey, Dad!
Come on,
I need your help, Dad!
What? No! No!
Dad, look at me!
I'm right here!
Just check your cameras!
(OZZY WHIMPERS)
Ozzy, please.
I've made up
my mind, okay?
(BARKS)
Quiet!
(STAMMERING)
I don't care anymore.
All I want now,
is to find my daughter!
Dad, please!
Please, I need you.
(GASPS)
MK!
(SCREAMING)
Oh! (SIGHS IN RELIEF)
(GRUNTING)
I am so over Boggans.
Ah!
(GASPS)
Ozzy!
Dad!
Don't faint!
(SLOWLY) I won't!
How did you find me?
I got your message.
You were right.
About what?
About everything.
I'm sorry.
(NORMAL VOICE)
Me, too.
(SLOWLY) How did
you get so small?
Dad, it was amazing!
They're real!
(BATS SCREECHING)
And they need
your help.
Follow me!
(CAWING)
Missed me.
I wasn't
aiming for you.
(GASPS)
(SCREAMING)
(GROANING)
Ooh! This must be
the delivery room.
Whoa! Boy,
are you lost!
Down the hall...
make a left, and then
when you see the janitor
with a weird eye--
Shut up!
(GROANING)
(BOTH GRUNTING)
My dark prince.
Come to Daddy.
I don't think
it likes you.
Ronin!
You know how many Boggans
I had to fight to get here?
Seriously,
I lost count.
Well, what's one more?
(GASPS)
It's all real!
It's really here!
Dad, the bats!
We have to get them
away from the moon.
(SLOWLY)
It's so beautiful.
There's no time!
But what
matters most is--
Not now!
(GRUNTS)
Oh!
(NORMAL VOICE)
Oh, you want me to play
the frequencies that...
(SLOWLY) attract the--
(GRUNTS)
(BAT SCREECHES
PLAYING LOUDLY)
(GROANS)
Run!
I'll find you, Dad!
I just have to
get back before--
Oh! Oh!
Ow, ow, ow!
They really do
go in your hair!
(GROANS)
(SCREAMS)
(BATS SCREECHING)
MANDRAKE: This time,
when I leave you
for dead...
you'll stay that way!
(GROANS)
What's that
little saying
you people have?
"Lots of leaves,
something-something"?
Very inspiring.
But in the end
every leaf falls
and dies alone.
No one is alone.
Not even him.
(YELLS)
(ALL GRUNTING)
(SCREAMING)
(THUNDER RUMBLING)
(RAIN PATTERING)
(CROWD MURMURING)
(ALL GASPING)
Look after them
for me.
There's that smile.
(GASPS)
Your Majesty.
You look terrible.
Hey, did you see
how many times
I got hit?
I learned that
from you.
(CHUCKLES)
You're not
going to make me say
all the stuff...
I learned from
you now, are you?
Well, you'd have
learned a heck of a lot
more from your dad.
I was a pretty
poor substitute.
Don't beat yourself up.
Lately you've shown
some real promise.
Oh, please.
Just say
you love each other.
I thought
we just did.
Hey, you're still here.
Yeah.
I guess
I missed my chance.
I'm sorry.
But not
completely sorry.
Wow! Strong grip!
What's happening?
A queen brought you here.
How about a queen
sends you back?
(GRUNTING)
It's working!
We have to
say goodbye!
RONIN: What for?
You're part of us.
Many leaves,
I always say.
I mean,
the Leafmen say.
Not that
I'm a Leafman.
Says who?
(GASPS)
MUB: We'll find each other!
Just follow the slime!
I will, Mub.
You're really leaving.
Put your arms around me.
(EXHALES)
(GASPS)
I always hoped
if I, uh...
if I proved it
to her...
she'd, uh...
you know.
BOMBA: Well,
what do you think?
It's perfect, Dad.
Except, the boots are
higher and the sleeves
are longer.
And they wear
actual helmets,
not acorns.
Really?
(CHUCKLES)
They should seriously
consider the potential.
(BARKING)
Ozzy!
Here you go, boy.
(GROWLING)
(GLASS SHATTERING)
(BEEPING)
Um...
(CHUCKLES) Go.
It's always for you,
anyway.
(VIDEO REWINDING)
Hey.
Hey!
How's work?
No, it's not work
when you love your job.
"Many leaves, one tree,"
that's what I always say.
Uh-huh.
What do you think
you're doing, Leafboy?
Leafman. You know
it's Leafman.
Is it?
I wasn't sure.
Hey, MK!
What's going on,
baby girl?
Hi, Mub.
We were talking.
There's a big sack of
"shut your flat face"
over there
by that tree.
Why don't you go
pick it up?
Listen, slick.
Guys, don't fight.
Oh, it won't be a fight.
I could whip him with
both eyes behind my back.
(LAUGHS)
I'd like to see
you try, jelly butt.
I didn't want to
have to do this!
(GASPS)
Ew!
Mub, get him
out of your mouth!
Dad, I gotta go
Heimlich my friend
out of a slug.
Yeah, that looks
pretty weird.
Here don't forget this.
(SLOWLY)
Tell them about
the acorn helmets.
Or you could
tell them yourself.
Oh!
(LAUGHING EXCITEDLY)
Come on, Ozzy!
(BARKING SLOWLY)
(BOTH LAUGHING)
(RISE UP PLAYING)
♪ I'm the matriarch
of your land
♪ When you need to,
take my hand
♪ Come into my arms
I'll keep you safe from harm
♪ I'll keep
your precious heart
♪ Some people try
to drag you down
♪ They can't harm me
Stand and be proud
♪ You're a warrior
You're my warrior
♪ Be who you are
♪ Know that life holds
more than what you see
♪ Rise up and win
Rise up and win
♪ Fight for you and me
♪ Look into my eyes
and believe
♪ Little woman,
we will fight, we will fight
we will fight
♪ We will rise
♪ I see you and me
♪ Take my hand
and we
♪ We will stand,
we will fight, we will fight
♪ We will stand
and together we will rise
♪ They'll burn you
at the stake
♪ If you don't act
like they want you to
♪ Oh, baby, be yourself
♪ Do good and help the world
♪ Be who you are
♪ Know that life holds
more than what you see
♪ Rise up and win
Rise up and win
♪ Fight for you and me
♪ Look into my eyes
and believe
♪ Little woman,
we will fight, we will fight
we will fight
♪ We will rise
♪ I see you and me
♪ Take my hand
and we
♪ We will stand,
we will fight, we will fight
♪ We will stand
and together we will rise
♪ Rise up
Rise up little man
♪ Don't be scared,
I'm holding your hand
♪ Know that life
holds more than
♪ What we see
and what we get
♪ Be who you are
♪ Rise up
Rise up, little woman
♪ Don't be afraid
to risk it all
♪ Know that life
holds more than
♪ What we see
and what we get
♪ I will
fight for you and me
♪ Look into my eyes
and believe
♪ Little woman,
we will fight, we will fight
we will fight
♪ We will rise
♪ I see you and me
♪ Take my hand
and we
♪ We will stand,
we will fight, we will fight
♪ We will stand
and together we will rise ♪