Provided by explosiveskull
https://twitter.com/kaboomskull
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org
It is time.
It's beautiful, isn't it?
I'm Ikaris.
I'm Sersi.
It's coming! Run!
Father!
Run!
Good fight.
You, too.
Thank you, Ajak.
Shit.
Excuse me. Excuse me.
I know I'm late, Charlie.
"In this broad Earth of ours,
"Amid the measureless
grossness and the slag,
"Enclosed and safe
within its central heart,"
"Nestles the seed Perfection."
The poet's hope and optimism in humanity
echoes our recent universal victory,
the return of half our population...
And, thank God, there she is.
Our brilliant museum scientist, Ms. Sersi,
the person who will be
and was always supposed to be
giving you your presentation today.
Thank you, Mr. Whitman.
Sorry I'm late, everyone.
Today, we'll be learning
about the importance
of apex predators in a balanced ecosystem.
Poetry?
I completely
ran out of things to say,
and these kids make me nervous.
Well, I thought you were
very charming, Professor.
See you tonight.
Ooh! "See you tonight."
All right, settle down.
So...
who can tell me
what an apex predator is?
Animals that hunt their prey for food.
Very good.
Apex predators do hunt
their prey for food,
like all predators.
But one thing that sets them apart
is that there are no other
animals in their habitat
strong enough to hunt them.
Who can give me an example?
Lions.
- Wolves.
- Correct.
Earthquake.
Get down. Get down!
It's an earthquake, everyone.
Get down! Under the tables!
Let me help you.
Don't worry, it'll pass soon.
It's all right. Come here.
You're all right. You're all right.
I like this song.
Me, too.
Do you wanna dance?
Wait, what the hell?
Your hand!
You've had too much to drink. I gotta go.
♪ Happy birthday to you ♪
♪ Happy birthday, dear Dane ♪
- Hip, hip!
- Hooray!
Is this from the Middle Ages?
It has your family crest.
It must have cost a fortune.
I'm a good eBay bidder.
Thank you.
Happy birthday.
So, have you given any more thought
to us moving in together?
Yeah, I... I thought about it.
I can't move in with you.
Yeah. Mm-hmm.
Thought you'd say that.
I'm sorry.
And I think I know why.
Are you a wizard?
What?
Yeah, like Doctor Strange.
No. I'm...
I've noticed some unusual things happen
when I'm around you.
Like our water always turns to coffee
whenever the waiter ignores us.
That's your caffeine addiction talking.
- And Sprite says things...
- Mm.
like you and your ex-boyfriend
broke up a century ago.
She said that?
And he can fly.
He's a pilot.
Get a room, you two.
Can we go now? It's past my bedtime.
Are you really in love?
What if I am?
You better tell him
the truth, then.
I'm working on it.
You guys wanna get pizza?
No, thank you!
He won't live forever, you know.
Move in with him.
I live with you.
Dane.
Shit! Is that a Deviant?
Dane, run!
- Sersi?
- Let's go.
- What is that thing?
- A Deviant!
You said you killed them all!
You told him that?
- You believed me?
- I do now!
What are you doing?
Keep Dane safe!
Sersi, wait! What?
You're fine, dude.
Sprite!
No. Stairs.
Run! Go! Go!
- Go!
- Come on!
It knows where we are!
How?
I don't know!
Sprite!
Ikaris!
Evening, ladies.
Watch out!
Wizard.
Sorry.
Did it just heal itself?
Ikaris.
It's good to see you.
It's good to see you, too, Sprite.
I'm Dane.
Hello, Dane.
Well, I guess you must be the pilot.
We're Eternals,
from a planet called Olympia.
We came here 7,000 years ago on the Domo,
our starship, to protect
humans from the Deviants.
We thought we killed them all
five centuries ago,
but now they're back.
Look, if you don't
want to move in with me,
you could just say.
Dane, this is serious.
Oh, I know. I'm just still getting
over the fact you're not a wizard.
I was hoping you could
change me into a giraffe.
I always wanted to be
a giraffe when I was a kid.
It's too bad I can't change
sentient beings.
You would have made a very cute giraffe.
Why didn't you guys help fight Thanos?
Or any war?
Or all the other terrible things
throughout history?
We were instructed
not to interfere in any human conflicts
unless Deviants were involved.
Why?
If we'd protected humanity
from everything
for 7,000 years,
you'd never have had
the chance to develop
in the way you were meant to.
But if the Deviants were
eradicated a long time ago,
why are you still here?
We've been waiting...
to be told we can go home.
So...
Ikaris.
The boy who flew too close to the sun.
Sprite made that story up
when we lived in Athens.
In the fifth century BC?
How long were you two together?
5,000 years.
I guess you can call that long-term.
What happened?
He left.
I always thought he'd come back, but...
he never did.
So, I moved on.
I'm glad you did.
I'm sorry.
I have to go.
This morning,
an unprecedented global earthquake
swept nation-states across the world,
causing damage and panic.
Many have speculated
its connection with the Blip.
The UN has called
for an emergency meeting...
That Deviant healed itself.
They could never do that before.
And it was coming after us
instead of humans.
What's going on?
I came to check on you
because of the earthquake.
That Deviant is news to me.
Something's happening to Earth.
Can't be a coincidence.
We need to find the others.
I haven't seen
some of them for centuries.
I doubt much has changed.
I'm sorry I hurt you, Sersi.
But we need to stick together.
And once I know you're safe,
I'll leave you alone.
Let's go to Ajak first.
She'll know what to do.
You hear that, Sprite?
Family reunion.
It's about time.
Hey, that one was mine!
Oh, never mind.
Do not fear.
Quickly, inside the gate!
Ajak.
Arishem.
We continue to keep Babylon
safe from the Deviants.
More people have come to seek refuge.
It is now the largest city on Earth.
The Eternals serving their missions
across the galaxies
will learn from your success.
Thank you.
I respect your grand design, Arishem.
But I have noticed something
special about this planet.
And I fear that maybe
this time the cost may...
Do not become
attached to this planet.
You must focus on the true purpose
of your mission.
I understand.
I will not let you down.
Phastos.
Did you go to the party
last night like I told you to?
The party, yeah.
- Yeah, it was...
- He worked all night.
Who was talking to you?
Get a life.
- And where is Sersi?
- Late as usual.
I'm sorry, but I have something
very exciting to show you, okay?
Wait till you see this.
What is it?
It's an engine.
It moves steam from
high pressure to low pressure.
Uh, it'll help them till their fields
at an incredibly fast rate.
It's gonna freak them out.
I mean, they only have had
the wheel 1,000 years, so...
You know, we could do that thing
where you use your mind to control them
and then they could do it quicker.
Ajak, you listening to this?
Phastos, this steam...
- Engine. It's a steam engine.
- It's too soon.
And there she is.
What did I miss?
Nothing. Just the screams
of my deep disappointment.
I am sure
you have something simpler.
Simple.
Okay, let's see. Uh...
Ladies and gentlemen, I present to you
the plow.
'Cause that's what it does.
Plows dirt.
I met another group of settlers
who are building their homes
in the northern fields.
They'll need to plant
their own crops.
- Thanks, Sersi.
- Listen,
humanity may be coming along
slower than some of us want.
But there is no telling what wonders
they will discover as they advance.
The wonders of the world await you.
Follow Gilgamesh and Enkidu into battle.
Be forever inspired
by their bravery and strength.
You and your fellow man...
will go on great adventures.
And become legends of your own!
I just saw that.
There's so many other chairs, man.
You know,
I could use my powers...
Come and have a drink with me.
No.
I can't let you go and fight
Deviants on your own.
- We need to guard the city.
- Get out of my way.
I didn't come to this planet
to cower behind walls.
We need to trust Arishem's design
for this planet.
- Hmm.
- Thena.
It's an honor to fight alongside you.
And you.
My beautiful Makkari.
You're late.
I needed to get
enough artifacts to make a good trade.
Just lie to her.
I can sense vibrations.
Even the tiniest movement.
Including your voices when you speak.
Did you two just waste my time?
The Emerald Tablet you're searching for...
is a myth!
When humans have conflict,
Ajak tells us not to interfere.
Well, she also says
that stealing is very, very bad.
If you don't tell,
I won't tell.
Deal.
I promise I won't
let my feelings for Sersi
distract me from my mission.
Humans are far from being able
to protect themselves from the Deviants.
We still have much to do.
Your faith in Arishem is strong.
I can feel it.
But you are allowed
to live a life, you know?
Go tell Sersi how you feel.
Try.
Sorry.
I'm making a mess.
Well, not bad.
See you.
Let me help you.
It matches your eyes.
You are very kind.
You're learning
their language now?
If I want to spend more time with you,
I need to get to know them.
I am very beautiful.
Wait, what did I say?
You said, "I am very beautiful."
You...
You are very beautiful, Sersi.
I'm yours, Sersi,
if you'll have me.
I love you, Ikaris.
I love you, Sersi.
May the gods hereby bond you in matrimony.
Congratulations.
Hello?
Ajak?
Ajak!
It was a Deviant.
♪ Our love ♪
♪ And our devotion ♪
♪ Were as deep as any ocean ♪
It was the last time I saw her.
Ajak asked me to check on Sersi,
so I went to London.
Turned out, both of us were lonely
and we needed each other.
I guess, in her way,
Ajak never stopped
trying to take care of us.
Bye, Ajak.
It's the first time in 7,000 years
one of us has died.
I think the Deviant
that attacked us in London
killed Ajak and absorbed her power.
Deviants have never
done that in the past.
It healed itself just like Ajak.
I swear, I almost heard it speak.
- Arishem.
- Sersi.
It is almost time.
Sersi! Sersi! Are you okay?
What happened, Sersi?
The sphere that Ajak used
to talk with Arishem,
it came out of her body
and went inside me.
Did you talk with Arishem?
Yes. He said
it's almost time.
Can you try talking to him again?
I don't know how.
But she chose you to replace her.
And she gave you the sphere.
Hold on, Sprite.
Are you sure
you talked with Arishem?
What else would it be?
Mahd Wy'ry.
Where are the others?
We had to split up.
There were more Deviants
than you said.
Well, I'm sure
that was a lot of fun for you.
It was.
Once the others
kill these last Deviants,
we will have eliminated them
all from the planet.
Don't.
We don't interfere in their wars.
This isn't war.
It's genocide.
Their weapons have become too deadly.
Maybe it wasn't such a good idea
helping them advance, Phastos.
Technology is a part of
their evolutionary process, Druig.
It's not exactly something
that I can stop.
No, you can't. But I can.
Stay strong.
It's too late.
- Thena?
- Everyone is going to die.
Are you okay?
Thena?
- Thena? Thena, no!
- Thena!
Don't listen to your head, Thena.
Listen to my voice.
You are safe.
You are loved.
You're our Thena.
Hey, Thena!
Hey! Stop, stop, stop!
- Is she okay?
- Yeah.
Sersi.
Thena, please.
Come back to us.
Okay.
I thought Mahd Wy'ry was a myth.
There is no cure...
so no one really talks about it.
What happened?
Thena.
You attacked everyone.
Wounded Sersi, Phastos,
you nearly killed Makkari.
I don't remember.
You have Mahd Wy'ry.
Your mind is fracturing
under the weight of your memories.
And all I can do is erase them
so that you can start over.
I will have to inform Arishem
and take you back to the ship
where we have the technology
to help you.
But she won't be Thena anymore.
What if it happens again?
She could've killed you.
She could have killed all of us.
Please.
Please, I... I want to remember.
I want to remember my life.
Thena, I love you.
But listen to me.
It's not important
if you remember or not.
Your spirit will remain.
You will always be Thena deep inside.
Trust me.
Why should she trust you?
You're asking her
to let you erase who she is.
Druig, I know you're upset, but...
Upset?
We've trusted you for 7,000 years,
and look where you've gotten us.
I've watched humans
destroy each other
when I could stop it all in a heartbeat.
Do you know what that does
to someone after centuries?
Could our mission have been a mistake?
Are we really helping these people
build a better world, huh?
We're just like the soldiers down there.
Pawns to their leaders.
Blinded by loyalty.
It ends now.
Let them go.
You're gonna have to make me.
Stop.
If you wanna stop me,
you're gonna have to kill me.
I'll watch over Thena.
Let her keep her memories.
One day, when she attacks you,
you might have to kill her.
We'll take that chance.
You may all go.
The Deviants are gone.
There is no reason
for you to stay with me.
Shouldn't you ask Arishem first?
We're a team,
we should stay together.
I didn't ask you for your advice, Ikaris.
Do not forget your place.
This is where we say goodbye.
You are free to go.
I want you to go out there.
And live a life for yourselves.
Not as soldiers.
Not with the purpose you were given.
Find your own purpose.
And one day,
when we see each other again,
I want you to tell me what you found.
♪ Come my way
Nach, mera hero ♪
♪ Get the evil away ♪
♪ Nach, mera hero ♪
♪ You came to save ♪
♪ And now you're here ♪
♪ Nach, mera hero, oh ♪
♪ Now you have come home
Give it all to me ♪
♪ You would risk it all
For the victory ♪
♪ Waiting for you
Scarcely can I ♪
Welcome.
I am Karun Patel.
Kingo's valet.
It's truly an honor
to be in the presence
of the great Eternals.
♪ Like the fire
Like the sun ♪
♪ You have risen,
Mighty one ♪
Cut! Okay, everyone,
that was good.
But we could do 10% better.
That was beautiful. Very, very good.
Really, so good.
My friends
from college are here.
Hello, boss!
Perfect timing!
Welcome to the set of...
Legend of Ikaris.
I'm playing you!
- You like the costume?
- We need to talk.
Tell the director
I have some notes for him...
We need to talk to you in private.
Oh, Karun, he's worked
with me for 50 years.
I trust him completely.
Actually, when we first met,
he thought I was a vampire,
and he tried to stake me
through the heart.
I have apologized so many times.
Not quite enough times.
Very close, though. I'll let you know.
Oh, I have to get ready
for the next scene.
Come to my tent, we'll talk there.
You guys are gonna love
the next scene.
I come in on a wire
'cause, you know, I can't fly.
Wait, are we getting back together?
We need to talk.
I've been waiting for the day
the world learns the true identity
of the Shadow Warrior.
Ajak's dead.
She was killed.
It was a Deviant.
The Deviants are back.
We don't know how many there are.
You need to come with us.
I can't just go. I mean,
all these people depend on me.
We just started shooting this movie.
It's the first of a trilogy.
We just got BTS to do a cameo...
Sir,
- may I say something?
- Please don't say anything.
I think you should go.
I just said don't say anything.
"Life affords no greater duty
than to protect one's family!"
Remember? It's your favorite line
from The Shadow Warrior 2:
Voyage of Time.
Your family needs you.
Seven thousand years.
That's how long
the battle between Eternals
and Deviants has raged for.
You think I'm a movie star.
Well, I am. But I am also...
an Eternal.
Kingo, what are you doing?
I think we should be
remembered, so...
I am making a documentary about us.
You are about to meet
my fellow Eternal, Sprite.
Sprite, tell them about yourself.
Oh, wait.
Okay, well, we'll circle back to her.
This is Sersi.
Sersi,
tell them about yourself.
- Uh...
- We're rolling.
Well, uh...
I can change a rock into water.
Uh, I could turn a rock into wood.
Or a rock into metal.
Actually, one time,
I turned a rock into air.
Cut.
Um, you know what?
Why don't you think about it,
and we'll get back to you, okay?
Let's go.
Sprite says
you're addicted to this thing.
Oh, this?
Look at this.
Whoa.
You know,
seeing as we don't age.
I think you look quite good.
Don't you?
Nobody ever wonders
how you managed
to be the leading man for over 100 years?
Oh, I don't know
what you're talking about.
That is my great-great-grandfather,
that is my great-grandfather,
grandfather,
father, and me.
I'm part of the greatest dynasty
in the history of Bollywood.
Pretty impressive, right?
You abandoned me in Macedonia.
Okay, I got sick
of moving every five years.
People freak out
when they notice that you don't...
age.
I thought we were friends.
Do you know why I love movies?
Because of you.
I missed sitting in the audience,
listening to your stories,
watching your illusions.
We should've all stayed together.
Ajak would still be alive.
She should have never let us go.
This is the Deviant you fought in London?
It's different.
There must be more out there
than we thought.
Oh.
Is... Is this a Deviant, sir?
Yep.
It's a beautiful creature.
What? This? This? No. It's hideous.
You've never had one try
to bite your head off. Roll.
Oh.
You're about to meet
two of the greatest warriors
the world has ever known.
Thena, legendary, deadly, fashionable.
And her trusty friend...
Door.
a mighty powerhouse of strength,
the fearsome Gilgamesh!
Gilgamesh!
What took you so long?
You look younger today, Sprite.
I have the same apron.
Who the hell are you?
I'm Karun. Kingo's valet.
Oh, valet. Like Alfred in Batman.
Gilgamesh. The Deviants are back.
No shit.
I could have used some help.
We were attacked
by a Deviant in London, too.
Even Ikaris couldn't kill it.
You couldn't?
I was distracted.
Sure, man.
Hey, you guys wanna try my pie?
I'm sorry, Gil.
Ajak's dead.
It's true, buddy.
We lost her.
Sersi.
The attack triggered her.
She's no fun to be around right now.
Hey, Thena.
Look who's here.
Give me your hand.
Thena.
Everyone in Centuri-6
is going to die.
Give me your hand.
It's too late. We can't save them.
Thena.
We came to Earth
together on our ship.
You're an Eternal.
The greatest warrior of Olympia.
The legendary protector of Athens.
The goddess of war.
Remember who you are.
Remember.
- Thena.
- Hi.
Hello.
Hey, who's your gardener?
This is just what you guys
eat every day?
- Yeah, this is amazing.
- Every day.
- Thank you for this.
- Oh, you're welcome.
Help yourself.
This one is a trio of wine,
beer, and mead.
Made for all the soldiers
in the battle of Troy.
That's so thoughtful.
Should she be drinking?
No, hers is
non-alcoholic. For kids.
I gave you the same thing, Sprite.
For kids.
I was just kidding.
Yours is a secret brew
Odin taught me as a thank-you
after we helped defeat
Laufey's army in Tonsberg.
What? Oh.
I'm a big baby.
Very mature. Can you stop?
- Stop.
- Speaking of Odin...
Thor used to follow me around
when he was a little kid.
Now he's a famous Avenger
and won't return my calls.
So, now that Captain Rogers
and Iron Man are both gone,
who do you think
is gonna lead the Avengers?
I could lead them.
- I figure I'd be good at that.
- Yeah, you would.
Ajak didn't even choose you
to lead us.
- Whoa.
- Ouch, Gil. Ouch.
- Harsh.
- I'm gonna let that one slide
because, you know,
you've always been bitter
that I can fly and you can't.
Oh, so what, you can fly.
I'm better-looking,
everybody knows that.
Where you going?
I'm just gonna get some air.
Mmm. This is really good, Gil.
You know, I could sell this.
Put my face on it,
move some units.
I made it from corn.
I chew each kernel myself
and ferment it in my spit.
Is this the Centuri-6
Thena was talking about?
Yeah, it's a planet.
She thinks she used to live there
until it was destroyed.
Always talks about massive
quakes ripping it apart.
Everyone died, including herself.
We had an unprecedented global
earthquake three days ago.
Oh, that's what that was.
I thought I was drunk.
Ajak chose me to lead us, but...
I can't even figure out
how to speak to Arishem.
I've tried so many times.
Maybe you're trying too hard.
Sometimes, you just have to listen.
Sersi.
Arishem.
Ajak was killed by a Deviant.
We think it absorbed her power.
And something unusual
is happening to Earth.
It is a side effect
of the emergence.
The emergence?
It is time for you to learn
the true purpose of your mission.
You were sent to Earth
to bring forth the Celestial Tiamut.
Every billion years,
new Celestials must be born.
I plant Celestial seeds into host planets
across the universe.
The planet Earth was chosen
to host the Celestial Tiamut.
In order to grow,
Tiamut needs vast amounts of energy
from intelligent life.
The Deviants prevented this
by consuming humans
until the Eternals eliminated them.
Now, the human population of this planet
has reached the required amount.
It is time for the emergence to begin.
But...
everyone on Earth will die.
The end of one life, Sersi,
is the beginning of another.
Our universe is a constant
exchange of energy.
An infinite cycle of creation
and destruction.
Celestials use energy
gathered from host planets to create suns,
generating gravity, heat, and light
for new galaxies to form.
Without us,
our universe will fall into darkness.
All life will die.
Ajak knew the truth?
She has helped many Celestials
to emerge over millions of years.
So have you.
Earth was my first mission.
I was home, on Olympia.
There is no Olympia.
This is your true home, Sersi.
The World Forge.
It is here that I built
and programmed the Eternals.
Everything dies except us
because we were never alive.
Why don't I remember any of this?
Because your memories
are erased and reset
after each emergence.
They are stored here.
Why do you keep them?
I keep them in order
to study the Deviants.
I created the Deviants, Sersi,
for the same purpose I created you.
Every Celestial host planet
has its own predators.
I first sent the Deviants
to exterminate them
so intelligent life could grow.
But there was a flaw in their design.
They evolved.
Became predators themselves.
And I lost control of them.
I built and programmed you,
Eternals,
to be synthetic beings
and incapable of evolution,
to correct my mistake.
Sersi, Ajak has chosen you
to take her place
as the Prime Eternal.
Do not fail me.
So, you're saying
we're basically fancy robots?
And our past memories
are stored somewhere
in space?
And Arishem made the Deviants.
I'm sorry, Thena.
You tried to warn us.
The last time
Arishem reset your memories,
something must have gone wrong.
What do you mean?
Well, that's what
Mahd Wy'ry is, isn't it?
All this time,
Thena was remembering
all the other planets we were sent to
and everyone dying
during the emergence.
I thought we were heroes.
Turns out we're the bad guys.
We're not the bad guys, okay?
We've helped the Celestials
expand life across the universe.
That's not what bad guys do.
That's what good guys do.
Every time innocent lives
have been sacrificed for the greater good,
it turns out to be a mistake.
We have to stop the emergence.
Sersi, we have no right to
stop the birth of a Celestial.
There has to be a way
Tiamut can emerge
without destroying the Earth.
We just have to delay it
until we figure out how.
Could Druig control its mind?
Maybe put it to sleep?
"Put it to sleep"?
Are you serious?
Gilgamesh asked Druig
to put me to sleep once.
So I could take a vacation
to Fiji, you know?
We're talking about a Celestial, okay?
We have to try.
Come on, we're not gonna let
everyone on Earth die, right?
Right.
I'm human. I'm a little biased.
The world is ending.
You need to go home.
And do what?
Watch TV?
When I could be with the
Earth's original superheroes
as they try to save the world?
Fine.
If you want to, stay.
Thank you very much, sir.
Gilgamesh,
could you please
get rid of the saliva beer?
I thought you like it, man.
We need to go. Now.
Find the others.
Once we're all together,
we'll decide what to do
about the emergence.
Good afternoon.
It's very nice here, sir.
Don't be fooled.
Ignorance is bliss.
Hey. We're looking for Druig.
Is he here?
Yes.
How do you know Druig?
We're friends...
from college.
Hello, Sprite.
I missed all of you.
Please, make yourselves at home.
You've given me a lot of bad news
in one go, my lady.
Will you help us?
I am glad that...
Hey, what's your service?
I'm not getting any bars.
Do you all remember
this forest? Beautiful.
It was the last place
we all lived together.
I've protected these people
for 20 generations now
from the outside world
and from themselves.
Your kind, my friend,
you will be responsible
for your own extinction one day.
Don't you think?
I think we must learn from our mistakes
and do better, sir.
You must not give up hope.
Oh, no, you didn't.
Okay, new rule, no more
possessing people's valets.
Oh, where is your sense of humor, Kingo?
I'm sorry, sir.
Don't apologize, it's not your fault.
You are not a God.
You know that, right?
How ironic. Kingo, the movie star.
I've directed some things, too.
Oh, yeah? Like what?
Some Internet content.
How many views?
I don't do it for the views.
Let's go. He's wasting our time.
- We need him.
- Ikaris.
I missed you.
Are you gonna charm me
or threaten me?
I mean, there's a third option,
if you prefer that.
It must be heartbreaking to find out
that you're not Mother's favorite.
And I'm sure she'd be real proud
- of what you've been up to.
- Druig, this is serious.
I'll tell you what's serious.
I've just been told I've been
sent on a suicide mission
for the past 7,000 years,
and that my entire existence is a lie.
So, excuse me for not giving a shit
about your plan right now.
Druig sucks.
He does, sir.
I don't like this place.
Druig needs to think,
and Sersi wants us to wait, so...
- we wait.
- Mm.
I couldn't recognize myself
in Sprite's illusions.
Those were the good old days.
What if I can't fight anymore?
- Of course you can.
- Mm.
What if I hurt you again?
Come on. You know who you are.
You're Thena, goddess of war.
Thank you.
For what?
- For always taking care of me.
- Oh.
I'd do it again.
On any planet.
I like watching him, too.
Jeez.
I don't think it's creepy at all.
Have you read Peter Pan?
Okay, so, to me, Ikaris is Peter,
Sersi is Wendy,
you are Tinker Bell, for obvious reasons,
and the rest of us are the Lost Boys.
What's your point?
Tinker Bell's always been
in love with Peter.
And it's hard for her
'cause she can never be with him.
I'm sorry, Sprite.
Kingo...
why did Arishem
make me this way?
I don't know.
I thought you broke it.
Always bring backups.
You have a very angry family, sir.
Yeah, it's a big issue.
What about King Midas?
Everything he touched turned to gold.
- Was that you?
- Dane.
- Confucius? Aristotle?
- Call your uncle.
What? My uncle? No.
You've always wanted to make
amends with him, right?
Now is the time. Trust me.
Sersi, you're so weird.
Dane? Dane?
You're breaking up.
You're breaking up?
How did he take the news?
Couldn't bring myself to tell him
it was the end of the world.
There's nothing he could do.
Sersi.
I'm worried about you.
If Arishem finds out
you're trying to stop the emergence...
I'm not powerful enough
to protect you from him.
I'm not afraid.
This violent cycle has to end.
Hey, stop worrying about me.
Old habit.
Why did you leave?
I told myself
something must have happened to you.
So, I waited.
Days became years,
and you never came back.
Sersi,
oh, I've missed you.
I didn't want to leave.
There's something
I have to tell...
Ikaris!
Miss?
You're ok?
Watch out!
Clear the camp!
Get behind me!
One of them took Ikaris.
It's an ambush!
Very nice, sir!
Are you mental? Hide!
We need action sequences.
Sir!
Sprite, get Karun out of here.
How many cameras
did you bring, young man?
Kingo!
Come on!
This way!
Quickly! Come on!
Get in! Get in!
Ikaris!
I've fought that one before.
It's stronger than the others.
No.
Terrible timing, Thena.
Thena!
Stop, Thena!
Druig!
Let them go.
Now is not the time, Sersi.
Please. I know
you're better than this.
Druig.
What's happening?
Go! Get to the river!
Gilgamesh.
A little help here?
Stay here.
Say it.
Good. You're okay.
They're headed for the camp.
Go. They need you.
Go, Ikaris.
Sprite, buy me some time!
Whoa. Whoa!
Can you hurry up?
Now!
Dishoom.
Karun! Did you get that?
I did, sir!
- Kingo!
- Just go.
I'm not leaving you.
Sprite!
Ikaris!
Sersi! Are you all right?
How did you do that?
I don't know.
Stop, stop, stop.
Thena.
No. Gilgamesh.
Stay back.
Ajak...
Her memories...
I understand now.
I can see what she saw.
So many planets.
So much life destroyed
every time a Celestial is born.
Arishem used us
and left us to die
with each emergence.
We just wanted to survive.
And then he sent you.
I will kill you all
for what you have done to my kind.
You are not saviors, Eternals.
You are murderers.
Ikaris!
Thena.
Hey.
Remember.
No.
I'll remember.
When I left,
I thought about taking over the minds
of every human on this planet.
Violence, fear, greed,
all gone.
Why didn't you?
Because without their flaws,
they wouldn't be human.
Please, Druig.
You can't stay here anymore.
These Deviants are trying to keep us
from killing their own kind.
They have a conscience now.
That makes them more dangerous.
No, Sersi.
That makes them us.
Eternals and Deviants.
Arishem's children.
But you are asking me to take control
of a mind of a Celestial.
I do not have that kind of power.
We'll need Phastos.
Well, good luck.
He gave up on humans
a long time ago.
I did this.
If my technology
hadn't helped them advance...
Druig was right.
Our mission was a mistake.
These people...
they're not worth saving.
Oh, Phastos.
They're not worth saving.
- Thanks.
- Give me a good one.
- All right.
- Over here.
And...
Oh, that's great, man!
- Yeah!
- Oh, yeah!
- Nice.
Good one.
All right, ready? Throw!
Oh, so close.
- Daddy, Daddy, watch this.
- Yeah, okay.
- Watch this.
- Let me see. Let me see it.
Dad. I'm only a starter.
Hi.
- Hello. Can we help you?
- Throw it again.
Hey, Jack. Ben.
Hey, guys.
These are my friends from college.
Uh, this is Sylvia
and, uh, Isaac. That's Isaac.
- Isaac.
- Dad, that's Superman.
Dad, that's Superman!
Jack... That's really funny, Jack.
No, no! He is Superman.
That is definitely not Superman.
I saw him on TV.
He was in London, fighting a monster.
And you were with a cape
and you were shooting
laser beams out of your eyes.
- I don't wear a cape.
- Oh, sorry.
Okay, well, we should
just go inside, right?
Can I call you Clark?
Is that what you go by now?
Because, you know...
You've called me worse.
- You got it, Jack?
- Mm-hmm.
- Way to go.
- Yes.
All right.
Show me how it's done.
Round and round and round
and round and round.
- Yep, you got it. Keep going.
- Come on.
Yeah.
Incredibly natural, guys.
So, after all these years,
even you fell for Ajak's lies.
- No need to rub it in.
- Mm.
It all makes sense
why she wouldn't let us interfere
with human conflicts.
Conflicts lead to war,
and war actually leads to advancement
in lifesaving technology and medicine.
So our mission was never to
make a peaceful or harmonious world,
but to increase the population
at all costs.
Just farming humans as food
for the Celestials, right?
That's bleak.
Well, so is telling
your husband and your child
that they could be dead within a few days.
Thought you'd given up on humans.
I got lucky. Okay?
I have a family now.
They give me faith again.
And I see the good
in humanity in them
every single day.
So, look, I cannot help you.
- I am never leaving them.
- Phastos...
I'm sorry, Sersi.
It was wrong for me to use my powers
without thinking about the consequences
in the first place.
So, now, I choose to use my hands
to fix my child's bicycle, okay?
Do you?
I don't use my powers anymore.
You sure?
What are you...
What the hell is wrong with you?
My child is right down the hallway!
That looks like someone's
been using his powers.
- Oh, my God.
- I bet you've built
the perfect safe house.
What is this even made of?
- Vibranium?
- Don't!
Fall collection.
IKEA.
Ass.
How did you even
deal with this guy
for over 5,000 years?
If you stay here, you might as well
invite the Deviants to dinner.
Never mind waiting
for the end of the world.
He has a point.
No, I'm sorry. You can't just show up
in my life and expect me to go with you.
- I'm not gonna...
- You should go, habibi.
You want me to go?
You know what my mom
would say to you right now,
right?
Quit procrastinating, Phil,
and take care of your business.
He's a chronic procrastinator.
I'm not leaving you two. No way.
I'm not happy about it,
but if there's a chance for us to watch
Jack grow up to live a life of his own,
we should take it.
Why does my heart Go on beating?
Why do these eyes of mine cry?
Don't they know
It's the end of the world?
♪ It ended when you said goodbye ♪
♪ Why does my heart
Go on beating? ♪
♪ Why do these eyes of mine cry? ♪
♪ Don't they know ♪
♪ It's the end of the world? ♪
♪ It ended when you said goodbye ♪
The Domo.
Wow.
A foreboding atmosphere fills the air.
An eerie stillness chokes our lungs.
What are you doing?
You know you're creeping us out.
You know that, right?
Oh! Oh, God!
Stay calm, T, please!
Chips. It's just chips.
As you can see, being an Eternal
does not preclude you
from having human emotions
such as cowardice.
What has she done?
Is that... a sarcophagus in my lab?
This is Makkari.
Or should I say Miss Havisham?
None of us have seen her
for centuries.
Ready to go home?
Hmm.
Is that the Ebony Blade?
Excalibur.
Arthur always did have a crush on you.
So you mean...
I've been waiting for centuries
to go back to Olympia,
and now you're telling me...
it doesn't exist?
That, and the world is ending.
At last my boredom is ending.
Have you seen my movies?
I don't have a DVD player.
DVD?
It's all about streaming now.
You know, what you need is a Kindle.
Do you know what that is?
It's like a...
You know, I just realized
that if you don't know what an iPad is,
there's almost no way
to explain it.
So, how did you end up scoring
this Emerald Tablet,
my beautiful, beautiful Makkari?
Miss me?
I'm sorry, what are we watching?
Because this...
- Is this new?
- Are you two...
Because I hate it.
Phastos,
I need to control
the mind of a Celestial.
Okay, get ready for it.
Bracelets?
You made us bracelets?
So, here's a little Celestial 101.
Celestials are the most powerful
energy generators in the universe.
When Arishem made us,
he imbued us with infinite cosmic energy
to keep our bodies regenerating.
The bracelets, in theory,
shut down our regeneration process.
And once that happens,
our bodies accumulate extra cosmic energy.
What for?
Well, if the Deviants
can absorb our energy,
what if we can absorb
each other's energy as well?
If I can find a way to connect us all,
one of us could become immensely powerful,
pulling the accumulated energy
from the rest,
forming...
a Uni-Mind.
"Uni" meaning "one,"
"mind" meaning "mind."
Oh, no,
we heard you the first time.
- Terrible name.
- We'll brainstorm...
"Brainstorm"!
- That's a way better name!
- No, I invented it,
so I'm calling it whatever I want.
So suppose Druig can,
say... put Tiamut to sleep...
Then what?
We find humans a new home
on another planet.
Are we building a big ship, too?
Take a pair of each animal?
Well, you know
what's never saved the planet?
Your sarcasm.
Space colonization
could take decades.
It can happen quickly with our help.
What if we end up
accidentally killing Tiamut?
We could be responsible
for billions of lives
not being created across the universe.
Boss, am I right?
Say something, Ikaris.
You don't think
we should be doing this.
Ajak chose Sersi to lead us.
Sersi should decide.
Forget who Ajak chose.
You're the strongest.
You should be making this decision.
Fine. Just keep lying to yourself.
Sprite.
Okay, this is not...
- Ikaris.
- Don't run after him.
Kingo, I... You guys.
Hey. Don't sweat it.
Sprite's always cranky.
I used to hear her complaining
even when she wasn't there.
I'm okay, Kingo.
If you think we should
do this, I trust you.
I will follow you to the end,
like I always have.
What did you say?
I will follow you to the end,
like I always have.
I'm not who you think I am.
How long do we have?
Seven days.
Good.
We completed our mission.
Where is she?
London.
She has a good life there.
I'm sure she's missed you.
If I'd gone back to her,
I would only have told her the truth.
She would've suffered
knowing this world she loves
would end one day.
Ikaris.
We have to tell them the truth.
What?
- Why?
- Because together
we might be able to stop the emergence.
"Stop the emergence"?
Listen...
Ajak, I know it's hard at the end...
Listen to me, Ikaris.
I have followed Arishem
for millions of years.
And I have never doubted him.
- Until now.
- Why now?
Why now?
Five years ago, Thanos erased
half of the population of the universe.
Delayed the emergence.
But the people of this planet
brought everyone back
with the snap of a finger.
You know, after I let you all go,
I traveled the world, living among them.
I have seen them fight and lie and kill,
but I have also seen them
laugh and love.
I've seen them create and dream.
This planet
and these people...
have changed me.
The cost of Arishem's design,
it's not worth it.
Not this time.
I trust you, Ajak.
I'll follow you to the end,
as I always have.
Thank you.
We have to bring
everyone back together.
There's something
I have to show you first.
It's just up ahead.
They must have been trapped
in the ice for centuries
and broke free last week
when the glacier started to melt
as the Earth's core heats up
for the emergence.
They killed an entire company
of oil workers.
I tracked them here.
I suspected you might
have changed your mind.
I can't let you betray Arishem.
Why don't you just kill me yourself?
When the others realize
something is happening to the Earth,
they'll come to you.
When they find your body,
they'll know the Deviants are back.
It'll keep them busy until the emergence.
I've been loyal to you, Ajak.
Kept your secret for centuries,
lied to everyone I cared about,
but never have I doubted my purpose
to serve the Celestials.
Oh, Ikaris.
I've led you down the wrong path.
It's the only path I know.
Thought I'd find you here.
I've thought about this place a lot.
Amazing how things change over time.
Maybe we're the ones
who've changed.
I know you don't agree with our plan.
I've always thought of the Celestials
like the ocean.
They give life and they take life away
without bias.
If they were gone,
this universe would eventually end.
What you're trying to do
is free humanity from the natural order.
It's not natural to allow all life
on an entire planet to be destroyed.
Arishem's way is archaic and violent.
I don't want to fight, Sersi.
It'll all end soon.
Except there is no end, is there?
We'd carry on without our memories
or free will
for eternity.
You're afraid.
I wouldn't mind leaving this world.
I only wish that when we do,
I would be able to remember you.
I'm in love with you, Sersi.
I'm grateful for the life
I've lived with you.
Ikaris.
Sersi?
It's started.
Oh, no. My God.
What about the Uni-Mind?
I haven't figured out a way
to connect us, but I'm close.
- I'm very, very close.
- How much longer?
I don't know, Sersi!
Find the point of emergence.
You always knew
the end was coming.
It must be a relief.
That Deviant is still tracking us.
Revenge won't bring peace
for you, Thena.
But killing it might.
Ikaris?
What are you doing?
I wanted you to leave
this world in peace.
Without knowing
about the emergence.
But I failed.
I wish Ajak hadn't chosen you.
I'm close to figuring it out.
Boss, what are you doing?
I've let this go on long enough.
Don't hurt him!
He lied to us.
He already knew about the emergence.
No, he didn't.
Ajak told me everything
when we left Babylon.
What?
You were never gonna let us
stop the emergence.
No.
I only wanted to protect you
from the Deviants.
If Ajak wanted you to take her place,
why did she choose me?
What have you done?
He killed her.
I had to.
She loved you.
- Did she?
- She loved you.
Do you think it was easy
to live with the truth?
To know that one day all this would end?
To keep on lying to you?
If we gave humanity the choice,
how many of them would be willing to die
so that billions more could be born?
We're not giving them a choice.
Is this why you're willing to kill?
You are so pathetic!
I'm an Eternal, Phastos.
I exist for Arishem.
As do you.
It's who you are.
I wouldn't change a single thing
about who I am.
Born or made.
But I do not exist for Arishem,
I exist for my family!
Then you are making
the same mistake Ajak did.
I found Tiamut.
- No!
- Makkari!
Get out of here!
Kingo.
You do not turn against your family.
Gilgamesh died because of you.
You won't succeed against me.
And I will kill every one of you
if I have to.
Wait.
I'm going with you.
Sprite...
What is this?
Why did Sprite go with Ikaris?
Because she loves him.
Oh, you guys didn't pick up on that?
He really fooled us, didn't he?
Karun, let's go.
Wait, where the hell are you going?
I can't help you guys.
I still think Ikaris is right.
So, that's it, huh?
Just gonna follow him?
I love the people of this planet.
But if you stop this emergence,
you are preventing so many
other worlds like this one
from being created.
I still have faith in Arishem.
But I refuse to hurt any of you
for my beliefs.
We need you.
Even with my help, we're no match.
It's Ikaris.
But...
I hope to see you on the next planet.
Thank you for all you've done...
for humanity.
It's been a great honor.
I will miss you all.
Look,
if I'm gonna get myself killed
going up against Ikaris,
we'll need to have a backup plan.
All of our powers,
even if they're amplified,
are not enough to kill a Celestial, so...
Well, Sersi did turn
a Deviant into a tree.
I'm sorry, what?
You didn't wanna tell me that?
You've never been able to do it before.
I don't know how it happened, okay?
And I'm pretty sure
I couldn't do it again.
Well, now is the time
to try, don't you think?
Phastos, that Deviant is dead.
Our plan is to put Tiamut to sleep,
not to kill it.
I can't kill a Celestial.
Sersi. Sersi.
We can't!
We can't.
It's okay, Sersi.
I got this.
There's no time for that.
I didn't see the lies
right in front of me.
I'm not even sure
why Ajak chose me to lead.
I asked Gilgamesh once
why he chose to protect me.
He said,
"When you love something,
you protect it."
"It is the most natural thing
in the world."
You have loved these people
since the day we arrived.
So, there is no one better
to lead us now than you.
Sersi.
Get up.
Ajak chose you for a reason.
Sersi!
Oh, Sersi. We need you!
I already gave that speech.
What?
You did... What...
Sersi, the sphere inside of you,
it creates a connection
between you and Arishem.
Maybe I can repurpose it
and create a connection between, uh,
well, all of us.
And that can activate the Uni-Mind.
- Great.
- Yeah.
But, um...
I have to take it out of you.
Okay.
Do it.
Don't kill her.
Thena...
Do it.
Will it work?
It has to.
I'm glad you're here.
Thank you, Sprite.
Protect the emergence.
You're really gonna kill them?
Where's Druig?
He's busy.
Thena, play nice.
You've never had to fight me.
But I've always wanted to.
It's time to put a god to sleep.
I should've done this
five centuries ago.
Druig's gone.
It's over.
Phastos.
I have to try and stop this.
I need to get closer to Tiamut.
- Keep Ikaris busy.
- We've got you.
Go.
Enough.
Thena, stop!
Why are you helping Ikaris?
We can't
let it absorb our powers.
Too late.
Thena, he's trying
to goad you. Don't...
Makkari!
Where's Sersi?
You always did
underestimate her.
Oh, no.
Not so fast.
Boss.
I don't know about you,
but this is really satisfying, right?
Let me go, Phastos!
I can't let her do this!
I don't think so.
I've been wanting to clip your wings
for a long time, Ikaris!
Thena.
Oh, you've changed.
You're broken.
Damaged.
Useless.
You can't protect any of them.
Sersi.
You're not powerful enough
to do this.
And you won't.
You're not a killer.
Maybe I've changed.
And is this really who you are, Sprite?
Are you really willing to let
everyone on this planet die?
I'm sorry, Sersi.
I've always envied you, Sersi.
'Cause you get to live
as one of them.
And I never could.
You know why I hated
living with humans?
Because they reminded me of things
I didn't even know I wanted.
Because of them, now I wanna know
what it feels like to grow up.
To fall in love.
To have a family.
And to know, in the end, I've lived.
It's all over now.
We get to start over somewhere new.
Well, that was very moving.
Druig.
I can't do this.
This is your fight now.
Thena.
It's me.
Gilgamesh.
Look at me.
Gilgamesh?
Stay here.
Say it.
You'll be okay.
Give me your hand.
Ah, it's a shame.
You and I,
we're just tools of a god.
Built to kill.
Thena.
Remember.
I remember.
Come on, Sersi.
Come on.
It's beautiful, isn't it?
I'm sorry.
I know.
How?
How did you do it?
When I touched Tiamut's palm,
I felt energy surging into me.
Tiamut joined our Uni-Mind.
I always wondered how we survived
the destruction of other planets
that we were on.
By being connected to
the Celestial as it emerged.
We became one...
even Ikaris and Sprite
all because of Tiamut.
Is he gone?
Sprite.
I still have energy from the Uni-Mind.
I think I can make you human.
All the things you said you wanted,
you can have them.
But your time will be fleeting
and you'll die one day.
Are you ready for that?
I am.
The sudden appearance
of an enormous stone figure
in the Indian Ocean
has left more questions
than answers for authorities.
U.S. and Australian naval ships
are maintaining defensive positions,
but at this...
You guys did that?
I love you so much.
Are you okay?
I get confused sometimes.
Yeah. Me, too.
So, Dad said
you're the goddess Athena.
"Thena." Drop the "A."
- Oh.
- Hmm.
What's your superpower?
Um, can you just...
Look... One second.
Okay. All right.
See, that thing is... Okay.
Almost gave you a shave
and a haircut, didn't she?
Stand behind me, actually.
Um, you remember earmuffs?
Remember how we practiced earmuffs?
Thank you so much.
You know that your babysitting privileges
are completely revoked, right?
Like, it's done.
Thank you.
Violence... Hey.
Violence is never the answer.
- Right, T?
- Hmm.
You gotta always use
your brain, hmm?
Like you did fighting on the beach?
Your dad
spoke calmly and firmly to the bad guy
and he had no choice but to
listen to me, so no violence.
The kid is ten...
not stupid!
When are you guys leaving?
When is that happening?
That's happening soon, right?
Ah, yes, there's Druig.
- Don't go anywhere near him.
- Oh!
Yeah!
Okay, that's far enough, Jack.
Wow, Dad, the Domo's so cool.
Your dad fixed that
with his bare hands.
Can we go to space, too, one day?
Let's wait till you get
your learner's permit, okay?
Hey, Phastos.
Take care.
This world is lucky to have you.
Thank you.
I know you're not a hugger, so...
Okay.
You think when we find
the other Eternals out there,
that they'll accept the truth
the way we did?
because the truth will set them free.
Told you that thing
was addictive.
Please visit?
I'll try.
When I get time off from school.
Oh, wow. Listen,
it's gonna be good for you
to be in a human environment.
You'll pick up some social skills.
Oh, you didn't think you needed those?
That explains so much.
Gonna miss you.
Me, too.
Madam.
Thanks, Karun.
Sometimes I wonder
if we did the right thing.
Killing Tiamut.
It's too late for that.
But you followed your heart.
We all did.
Even Ikaris.
Looks like someone's waiting for you.
He's a lot cuter in person.
So, after all that,
you still can't change me into a giraffe?
Well, I could next time
I'm connected to a Celestial
during an emergence
whilst performing a Uni-Mind.
Yeah. That sounds like a "no" to me.
What'll you do now?
Not sure.
This planet's my home, but...
I can't pretend to be human anymore.
I love you, Sersi.
I don't care what you are.
Remember when we talked about
no more secrets?
I have no more secrets, I promise.
Actually,
I have one I want to tell you.
What is it?
It turns out my family history is...
complicated.
Sersi?
Sersi, what's wrong?
Sersi!
You have chosen
to sacrifice a Celestial
for the people of this planet.
I will spare them,
but your memories will show
if they are worthy to live.
And I will return for judgment.
You all right, Ted?
Did you see that?
Provided by Synchronized
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org