300MB UNiTED TEAM - sunmenghao
¶ "my generation" plays
[sung in french]¶
[yelling]
[man] congratulations,
hudson high class of 2004.
[cheering, screaming]
There she is.
Fiona!
Bye.
- Hey.
- Hey!
- [giggling]
- hey, you.
- Congratulations, graduate.
- Thanks, baby.
And congratulations
to you, cooper.
Aww. Thanks, baby!
Nice try.
All right. See you at
wade's party tonight?
See you then.
So, it's just you and me
for the entire summer.
Next year you graduate,
join me at college.
Just like we planned.
- Scott, we need to talk.
- Yeah? About what?
About me dumping you.
Huh?
[man] there he is!
The graduate and his
beautiful girlfriend. Ok?
Smile, you two!
- Action!
- Dad, mom, grandma...
Uncle moke... Uh...
I'm gonna need
a minute here, ok?
What do you mean,
you're dumping me?
Scott, I just can't take
All the lying and cheating
on each other anymore.
What are you talking about?
Sweetie, I never cheated on you.
I know. That's what
makes this so hard.
You're looking good,
you guys.
Scotty, it's not you.
It's me.
There I go, lying again.
No, it was you.
You're just so...
- Predictable.
- Smile!
So, that's it.
Here's your
letter jacket back.
Goodbye.
This isn't mine.
She's a keeper, huh?
Oh, wow.
Oh, my god.
[shouting] fiona!
[scott crying]
[cooper] let's see that again.
Fiona!
- This is just so brutal.
- [laughing]
And yet I can't look away.
Bert, play it again. Come on.
- Fiona!
- Bert, get out of here.
[chuckling] ok. See you.
All right.
Stay black, bert.
[laughing] "fiona!"
[computer]
mail, motherfucker!
Hey, I got one
from mieke.
"happy herzlichen."
You still writing that guy?
I thought that was just
for german class.
It was at first, but we're
actually becoming good friends.
He's a really cool guy.
"dear mieke, greetings from
your american pen pal."
Scotty, girl scouts
have penpals.
Listen to yourself,
all right?
You met a "cool guy"
on the "internet."
This is how these
sexual predators work.
Next thing you know,
he'll want to
"arrange a meeting"
Where he will gas you,
stuff you in the back
of his van,
And make a windchime
out of your genitals.
- Come on, let's go to wade's.
- [chuckling] all right.
Screw it.
Let's go.
I'm not gonna let fiona
ruin my graduation night.
Auf wiedersehen, mieke.
[transmission beeping]
[crowd roaring]
- What's up, losers?
- What's up, jenny?
What's up, dude?
Sorry to hear about fiona.
She's a whore.
That's very sweet of you.
Thanks.
Enough fiona talk.
Look around. There's
gotta be 100 drunk girls.
We should try to have sex
with every one of 'e
Hello?
Mixed company?
What?
- I'm a girl!
- No, you're not.
You're just a cool guy
with long hair.
So, where's your
evil twin brother?
Jenny!
There he is.
Hey, jamie.
In fine form, I see.
[grimacing] why'd you
get me gin and tonic?
- I hate gin.
- You do?
You guys are
the worst twins ever!
[crowd chanting]
[crowd] chug! Chug!
[moaning]
- When are you guys taking off?
- Tomorrow morning.
Hey, wade!
Great party, bud.
[muffled screaming]
Man, I am so excited!
A whole summer,
backpacking around europe.
You should've come with us
Instead of working
for dr. Dad, scotty!
It's gonna be
so awesome!
Yeah. I planned every
detail of the trip
to maximize the fun!
You brought a guidebook
to a party?
- Do you wanna see my itinerary?
- Do you wanna see my balls?
You guys decide where
you're gonna go first?
Paris!
I can't wait.
Two years ago nicky jager's
sister, debbie,
Met a wealthy french g,
And spent a month sailing
the meditteranean on his yacht.
Isn't that the most romantic
thing you've ever heard?
Stuck on a boat
with a weird french guy?
That sounds a little gay.
It's not gay.
I'm a girl.
- Kinda gay.
- A little gay.
I gotta piss
like a pregnant woman.
[feedback]
Hey, listen up, everybody.
Gotta a little special thing
I'd like to do tonight.
Going to play
a little song for you
About the nastiest, freakiest
little sex puppet I know...
Fiona.
[cheering]
This one's for you, baby.
Happy anniversary.
[¶ instrumental rock ¶]
¶ scotty doesn't know
that fiona and me ¶
¶ do it in my van
every Sunday ¶
¶ she tells him she's in church
but she doesn't go ¶
¶ still she's on her knees
and scotty doesn't know ¶
¶ oh, scotty doesn't know ¶
¶ so don't tell scotty
scotty doesn't know ¶
¶ scotty doesn't know ¶
[girl] I hope we're just
as popular in college
As we were in high school.
- [girl #2] we will be.
- [girl] I know.
[girl #2] who needs
more chablis?
- [girl] candy, wanna come with?
- No, I'll stay here.
[cooper]
hello, candy!
[glasses clinking]
- Whoops!
- [gasps]
[laughing] holy cow!
Oh, this isn't where
I parked my car!
¶ I can't believe
he's so trusting ¶
¶ while I'm right
behind you thrusting ¶
¶ 'cause scotty doesn't know
scotty doesn't know ¶
Cooper harris, you're a pig!
Uh... Candy,
before you go...
You might wanna
clean that off.
Clean what off?
It's like dirt, or something.
Go like this.
Well, no... It's kinda under,
and to the side,
And under...
- Is it off?
- No.
I think your top
is getting in the way.
- Really?
- Trust me.
That's better.
But keep rubbing it.
¶ I did it with her
on his birthday ¶
¶ scotty doesn't know
scotty doesn't know ¶
¶ don't tell scotty
[cooper] mmm-hmm...
Mmm-hmm...
No, it's just
not coming off.
What is it?
Fine, I'll do it.
Come here.
Oh, my god! Candy!
[gasping] cooper!
[nervous laugh] hey...
This isn't where
I parked my car.
[cooper screams, groans]
¶ scotty doesn't know ¶
[yelling]
[¶ music continues ¶]
Hey.
[crowd] scotty doesn't know!
Scotty doesn't know!
This band rocks!
- Yeah!
- [crowd chants]
[urinating]
[computer beeps]
mail, motherfucker!
Hey, mieke.
"dear scott,
"I was very sad to hear
"about your lady woman
fiona dumping you.
"since you no longer
have a girlfriend,
"maybe I could come
to america
"and we could get to know
each other better."
"perhaps we could..."
"zussamen."
What the fuck is "zussamen"?
"arrange a meeting."
No, no, no! Come on!
Cooper was right.
This guy wants
to have sex with me.
"listen, mieke...
"I don't want to arrange
any meetings with you,
"you sick, german freak.
"so please keep your hands
off my genitals,
"and never write to me again,
"and don't come to america."
"goodbye."
[computer beeping]
[falling]
Oww.
[dog barking in distance]
I'm never drinking again.
Oh, that's nice.
[typing]
Bert, what are you doing?
Reading your email.
Don't do that.
Why are you wearing
my bathrobe?
Oh, I'm sorry...
But somebody pissed
all over mine last night.
Wow. I can't believe
this german chick
Wants to come here
and hook up with you.
I don't think so, buddy.
Mieke's a guy.
No, it says right here,
"trauriges m dchen."
"I was a sad girl
to hear about fiona."
I'm taking "intro to german,"
and even I know that.
Come here.
He sent me a picture,
retardo.
See? That's a picture of mieke
and his cute cousin, jan.
No, retardo.
That's jan, a man's name,
And that's not "mike,"
It's "mieke," a common
german girl's name,
Similar to our michelle.
I hope you wrote her back
and told her to come visit.
You didn't?
You thought she was a guy!
I'm getting
the video camera! Ha!
[bert laughing]
what an asshole!
[scott] no.
No.
[screaming] no!!
[screaming continues]
[scott] "address blocked"?
"email not delivered."
No... Come on!
Hey, mom made waffles.
- What's going on?
- I'm in love with my pen pal.
I'm in love with mieke.
Ok... Ok.
You know what?
I was actually
expecting this.
Frankly, I'm flattered
You picked me
to come out to first.
And don't worry about
telling your folks, 'cause...
- I think they already know.
- No, you idiot. Mike is a girl.
No, no, I get it.
Yeah.
He's the girl,
and you're the girl,
And sometimes
you're both the girl.
Right?
That's hot.
But whatever works for you.
I'm not gonna judge it.
Will you stop?
Look, come here.
Look at this picture.
Wow. Who's the hot chick?
That's "mike."
I mean, mieke.
That's mieke? That's who you've
been writing to all this time?
Until last night,
when I took your advice
And told her to keep her
"hands off my genitals."
Given what we know now,
that seems like the exact
opposite of what you want.
[sighing]
This is a total disaster.
Oh, come on.
It's not that bad.
Though she is really hot.
You're not listening.
I don't even care
what she looks like.
Mieke and I had
this incredible bond.
I told her things
I couldn't even tell you.
Like what?
Nothing. It's a figure
of speech, coop.
- No, seriously. What?
- Nothing. The point...
- You like me better, right?
- Listen...
This girl is not only
smart and funny,
and stunningly beautiful,
But until I screwed up,
she wanted to come
All the way to america,
just to be with me.
- So do something about it.
- What can I do?
She blocked her email account,
her phone number's not listed.
The only thing I know
is she lives in berlin.
So go to berlin.
I can't just go
to berlin, coop.
- Why not?
- Because...
I just can't, ok?
I'm supposed to work
for my dad this summer.
It looks good on
my med school application.
Oh, jesus, scotty!
Man, fiona was right.
You're so predictable.
- I'm going to germany.
- No...
We're going to germany.
[scott] how are we going
to get to germany?
Don't worry.
I've got it covered.
[scott] we're going
to be couriers?
It's the best way
to get a cheap flight.
All we have to do
is carry their packages,
And then drop them off
when we get there.
My cousin did it
when he went to india.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
Of course, he ended up using
a public restroom in new delhi
And they had to
cut off his leg.
You know...
But he got there cheap,
is what I'm saying.
Ok, I don't have anything
to germany for a week.
But I can get you both
to london today for $118.
- Anything else?
- Europe is like the size
of the eastwood mall.
We can walk to berlin
from there.
Cooper, England's an island.
Ok, swim. Whatever.
We'll take it.
- Hey.
- Hmm?
Thanks for coming with me.
I know you had that internship
at the law firm this summer.
Well, forget about
the law firm.
And don't thank me.
I should be thanking you.
This trip is a
once-in-a-lifetime
opportunity for me
To broaden
my sexual horizons.
[laughing] what are you
talking about?
I'm talking about
crazy european sex.
[scoffs] ah.
You know america
was founded by prudes.
Prudes who left europe,
because they hated
All the kinky, steamy
european sex that was going on.
And now I,
cooper harris,
Will return to the land
of my perverted forefathers
And claim my birthright,
which is a series
Of erotic and sexually
challenging adventures.
You've really thought a lot
about this, haven't you?
It's my passion.
[¶ uptempo rock music ¶]
[scott] come on, come on!
The adventure begins.
Welcome to jolly
old England.
Yeah, breathe that sweet,
sexy, european air.
[cell phone rings]
- Oh.
- What is that?
It's the phone they gave me
at the law firm.
Yeah, it's
pretty neat, huh?
- Works anywhere.
- Yeah?
Excuse me.
Cooper here.
Hello, mr. Walters.
Yes, sir, I'm down
in file storage.
Um, hang on one second.
No, sir, I can't find
the gutterman file anywhere.
Yes, sir,
I'll keep looking.
I don't rest
until I find it.
Didn't tell your boss
you were leaving the country?
They would've
stopped paying me.
It seemed easier.
- So, where to?
- I don't know.
First bus to berlin doesn't
leave till tomorrow morning.
What do you wanna do?
Got the tower of london...
There's buckingham palace.
- Uh...
- There's no drinking age.
- There you go!
- Come on.
- Hey! "the fiesty goat."
- [laughing]
[loud chattering]
All right!
What do you wanna...
Soccer hooligans.
[sizzling]
Hey, this isn't where
I parked my car!
Oy!
Who the bloody hell are you?
This is a private members bar,
Exclusively
for the supporters
Of the greatest football
team in the world...
Manchester united.
Now please, enlighten me.
Who the fuck are you?!
That is a good question,
And... Scotty?
Huh?
We're the manchester
united fan club...
From ohio.
If you're manchester united
supporters...
Sing the manchester united song.
Excuse me, I'm sorry...
[scott] I'm not much
of a singer...
- Sing!!
- ¶ my baby takes ¶
¶ the morning train ¶
¶ he works from 9 to 5
and then ¶
¶ he takes another
home again ¶
¶ to find me... ¶
Watching the manchester
united football team!
Eh?
The best freakin' team
in all the land! Whoo-hoo!
Pretty good.
- Pretty dang good, lads!
- Yeah!
[men cheering]
[yelling]
[clinking]
¶ my baby takes
the morning train ¶
¶ he works from 9 to 5
and then ¶
¶ he takes another home again ¶
[men] ¶ to find me
waiting for him ¶
[woman] ¶ he's always on
that morning train ¶
[man] I've unblocked
your email address,
But this scott
is not responding.
He was the one.
I was going to
give myself to him.
Perhaps you should give
yourself to someone else...
Fr ulein.
[giggling]
I'm never drinking again.
Coop, wake up.
Oh, man, that was
a wild night.
You think?
¶ [rock music plays] ¶
Scotty, where the hell
are we going?
[scott] don't worry.
If anything bad happens,
My parents will find us.
Honey, where's scotty?
Cooper said they were
going camping.
Oh, that's nice.
And where's bert?
Fuck if I know.
¶ [music continues] ¶
[talking, bottles clinking]
[screaming] hey!
How are you, you scalawag!
Look, given the current
geopolitical climate,
All european countries should
have a seat at the table.
- Right.
- Except those fucking ities.
I hate them
italian bastards.
- You know what I mean?
- Excuse me.
Hello, boyo!
What the hell happened
last night?
You got steamed up,
pissed as a fart.
Too much sauce, son.
Don't worry.
We come and got ya so
you wouldn't miss the trip.
What trip?
Where are we going?
What do you mean,
where are we going?
We're going to see the mighty
reds do the frogs in paris.
Aren't we, boys?
[men cheer] yeah!
Why are you
yelling at me?
So I tell the swamp donkey
to sock it
Before I give her a trunky
in the tradesman's entrance
And have her lick
me yardballs!
Wow.
You guys are on like
a completely different level
of swearing over here.
Coop? Cooper,
we're going to paris.
I know.
Cecil told me.
Mieke's in berlin.
We're not going to berlin.
What are we gonna do?
We need a plan.
See what I'm talking about?
This is predictable
scotty talking.
Relax. Paris is practically
a suburb of berlin.
It's a nothing commute.
This is why France and germany
have always been allies.
Allies.
The twins. The twins
were in paris, right?
We could give them a call.
They could help us out.
Let me see your phone.
All right, but I'm really
only supposed to use this
for business calls.
[cooper] hey, don't...
[belching]
¶ [ rock music plays] ¶
[horn beeping, cheering]
You're on the wrong side
of the road,
You snail-eating puffs.
Fuck off! Go on, you gaelic
fucking garlic-breath tossers!
Piss off!
Get in here and say that,
You froggy itie shities!
- [horn beeping]
- [mad maynard] fucking beep!
We'll beep, you bastard,
all over your fucking nose!
Get out of the way!
Piss off!
Hey, lads!
[maynard] that wanker's got
a frog football shirt on!
Let's give this nancy
a fucking good kicking!
Come on, lads,
he's going off!
[screaming]
All right. Twins said
they'd meet us here.
Look at that!
There they are.
Come on. Jenny!
- Jamie!
- Hey!
Come here!
No, no.
No, no, no!
- Scott, bienvenu   paris.
- Thank you.
- Is that a new camera?
- It isn't just a camera,
This is a leica m7.
Uber-sensitive
exposure settings,
Legendary cloth
shutter system.
- Let me see that thing.
- No can do.
I spent the last four years
tutoring lacrosse players
to pay for it,
So nobody touches
my camera but me.
- So it's like your weiner.
- No, it's not like...
- Jenny...
- Cooper, leave him alone.
Wow, I can't believe
you came all the way
to europe for a girl.
Wait, not just any girl.
Show her the picture,
scotty.
She makes every girl in our
high school look like a walrus.
I'm a girl
from your high school.
No, I mean "girl" girls.
Guys, we're wasting
the whole day here.
We're in paris!
Let's go to the louvre!
[all] to the louvre!
So, you guys
wanna stay here,
Or should we check out
the huge line
at the eiffel tower?
Here's a fun fact.
Voltaire contracted syphillis
just two blocks from here.
- Should we go?
- Can we please get out of here?
- This guy's really
creeping me out.
- Who, robot man?
He's just trying to feed
his robot family.
- I really don't like him.
- Why?
Because he's doing this?
[making robot noises]
Ok, seriously,
don't do that.
[robot voice] cooper.
Do not hate me.
I am familiar with
over 600 dance moves
And I am programmed
to get...
[imitating robot]
Freaky.
[surprised noise]
[both making noises]
You're just upset because
people like me better.
It's okay.
[buzzing]
[both buzzing]
[gasping] oh!
¶ "two tribes" plays ¶
Fight! Fight!
Break the leg shot!
[gagging]
Ha! Ha! Ha!
Don't look in his eyes, scotty.
- Ohhh!
- That was not cool.
[laughing]
[growling]
[cracking]
[warrior screams]
- [groaning]
- [wincing] oh!
[scott] guys, let's go.
Come on.
[moaning]
Error! Error! Error!
[scott] how cool is this?
It's a shame we only get
to spend one day together.
- Why don't you come to berlin?
- Umm, no.
Jamie, come on.
In a few months, we all
go to different colleges.
This could be the last
chance the four of us
are together like this.
Plus, we're in europe. Huh?
This should be
the trip of a lifetime.
There's no way
we suld split up.
All right, this table
is now europe, ok?
Excuse me.
We are right here,
in paris,
And I have got
to get to mieke,
Who is over here,
in berlin.
If you come with us,
I'm sure there's a ton
Of great stuff to see
along the way.
- We can go to denmark.
- I love denmark.
- We gotta hit amsterdam.
- Definitely.
And the cathedral
at cameret!
- Yeah...
- Maybe. We'll see.
- [cooper] whatever.
- If there's time.
Come on! I really want you
to be there when I meet mieke.
Fine.
- Excellent!
- All right!
- A toast!
- Yes!
- To mieke!
- To europe!
[all] to europe!
Merci.
- Berlin, here we come!
- All right.
Better let me
hold on to those.
- What the hell is that?
- It's a traveler's money belt.
Frommer's says as long
as you have one of these,
No o can rob you
of anything.
Except your dignity.
No, you just put that
in your...
Wait... What?
Come on, guidebook.
Let's go.
[cooper] check it out.
European ass.
What's up?
Jesus, jenny.
I thought you were some...
...Girl. Come on.
Platform 4.
Thanks.
Damn!
[french accent]
I believe this is yours.
Pleased to meet you.
My name is christoph.
- [scott] jenny, let's go!
- [cooper] move it!
Those are my friends.
We're supposed to get
on a train to berlin...
- Jenny!
- I'm coming!!
So, it was really nice
to meet you.
The pleasure was all mine...
Jennifer.
¶ [french rock music plays] ¶
¶ [ music continues] ¶
¶ scotty doesn't know
that fiona and me ¶
[cooper] ¶ do it
in my van on sundays ¶
¶ tells him she's-- ¶
what?
You gotta admit,
it's a really catchy tune.
¶ tells him she's in church
but she doesn't go ¶
[all] ¶ still she's on her knees
and scotty doesn't know ¶
¶ scotty doesn't know ¶
- [all] ¶ scotty doesn't-- ¶
- bonjourno.
Bonjourno.
You know, there are a lot
of other empty compartments.
Huh?
Ah! Si...
[man] si.
Pardon me.
Eh?
Ohhh...
Scusi.
Mi scusi.
[screaming]
Hi.
Bonjourno.
- What the hell are you doing?
- Mi scusi, mi scusi.
No! No, no, no!
- Uh-oh.
- What?
Big tunnel.
[jamie] who's touching me?
Scotty, is that you?
Who's touching me?!
Scotty!
[screaming] oh!
Scusi.
[scott] crans sur mer.
We change trains here.
Well, we got a couple
of hours to kill.
What's there to see
in this town?
Hello? The monument
des poissoni res.
It's a monument to all
the local fishermen
who were lost at sea.
Frommer's says it's supposed
to be... "quite moving."
What the hell is wrong
with you, c-3po?
We're here to see europe,
not some crappy statue.
I'm taking a nap.
Wake me up when
the train gets here.
Hmm. Says here this town
has a famous nude beach.
All right, we can't all
just lie around all day.
We gotta get out there
and experience the culture
firsthand.
Let's go exploring!
So, what's the etiquette
on boners?
Do I roll over and dig out
a hole for it,
Or is it cool to just
let my flag fly?
Wait, wait.
Does "nude beach" mean
we have to get naked, too?
Of course.
Do you think you
can go an hour
Without your currency
colostomy bag?
As long as this thing has
our money and passports in it,
It's not coming off, and my
trunks won't come off, either.
Come on.
You came all the way
to europe.
Can't wimp out now.
Ok.
All right,
on the count of three.
Here we go.
3, 2, 1...
[cooper laughing]
look at jamie's penis!
Very funny.
All right.
Let the crazy ropean
sex odyssey begin.
- Here we go.
- Really?
- Yes.
- Mm-hmm.
- [cheering]
- [cooper] hello, ladies!
- Ladies?
- Bitches?
[scott] eww! What a rip!
There's no nude girls here,
Just guys like us
looking for nude girls.
I don't understand.
"crans sur mer has one
of the best nude beaches
on the continent.
"however...
"during the summer,
the european women
"are chased away
by gawking male tourists,
"so europe's most
nubile exhibitionists
"head to the deserted beach
"next to the monument
des poissoni res."
[girls squeal, giggle]
There's so many penises.
Frommer's tried to tell you,
but you just didn't listen.
This is the biggest
sausage fest on earth.
It's the international
house of sausage.
[jenny] hey!
- Thanks for waiting.
- You're not missing anything.
It's all guys.
At least the sun's out.
[¶ trance synthesizer ¶]
[man] ¶ dreams come true ¶
¶ I made my dreams come true ¶
¶ my dreams come true ¶
Holy crap!
What? I thought this
was a nude beach.
No!!!
- [men] huh?
- [jamie] no, no...
- What? What are you doing?
- Jenny, you gotta cover up.
[all] girl?
Girl!
[chanting] ooh, girl.
Girl... Girl.
Girl... Girl...
Run!
[jenny screams]
- [men chanting]
- I'm not gonna make it.
- Go on without me.
- All right. See ya.
Chica! Chica!
¶ [soft french music plays] ¶
Are you reading mieke's
old emails again?
Yeah.
I have no idea what I'm going to
say to that girl when I see her.
You know, she said
I might be the one?
That's huge.
I've never been
"the one" before.
Thought I was "the one"
with fiona, but turns out
I was, what, 101?
- 200.
- 200!
Look, you got nothing
to worry about.
You'll show up and sweep her
off her german feet.
Thanks.
Yeah.
I will, won't I?
I'm so sad and lonely.
I just wish someone
would show up
And sweep me off
my german feet.
Mieke! I'm here.
Scotty!
About that last email.
I'm so sorry...
The past is the past.
You're here now.
I've been saving myself for you.
Let us make love
for one whole month.
Touch me, scotty.
Ok.
¶ [ romantic german
pop song plays] ¶
¶ [song continues] ¶
Oh, scott...
- Mi bello.
- [sighing]
Mi bello.
[man] mi bello.
[slurping]
Mi scusi.
[all screaming]
Mi scusi!
¶ hot stuff baby
this evening ¶
¶ gotta have some hot stuff ¶
¶ gotta have some
love tonight ¶
[chorus] ¶ hot stuff ¶
[scott] guys, our train
doesn't leave till morning.
Where will we sleep tonight?
[cooper] what do you
mean, sleep?
We can sleep
on the train tomorrow.
This is the best thing
that could've happened.
We're in amsterdam!
This is the drug and
sex capital of europe!
Take a look at this.
"club vandersexxx."
"the red light district's
hottest sex club."
We have to check it out.
Who's with me?
I'll go.
Fine. Since no one else
is willing to go,
I'll just go myself.
¶ I see ¶
¶ you're waiting for me ¶
This is definitely where
I parked my car.
[woman] hello there.
Welcome to club vandersexxx...
Amsterdam's most erotic club,
Where your every fantasy
will be fulfilled.
Also says I get a free
t-shirt with flyer.
He's american.
How sad for you to grow up
in a country founded by prudes.
A country overrun
with crime and illiteracy.
A country where a man
is forced to make sex
To only one woman
at a time,
And one must learn
the woman's name beforehand.
- It was horrible.
- I know.
But you can come with me...
And let the vandersexxx begin.
[gasping]
¶ marijuana in my soul ¶
¶ your iguana in my hall ¶
[scott] I can't believe
we're doing this.
[jenny] don't worry.
Hash brownies are
totally legal here.
You're gonna enjoy these, man.
These are magical.
¶ I like to smoke marijuana ¶
- You wanna do this?
- Yeah.
[bell ringing]
- Hi.
I need a new battery
for my camera...
And while you're at it,
it could use a cleaning.
Wow.
Is that a leica m6?
Actually, it's an m7.
It's got the built-in
light meter.
It's so beautiful.
So sleek, so powerful.
How's the new lens system?
[scoffing] makes the nikon
look like a disposable.
You really know your cameras.
And you're very cute.
Me? Really?
I'm going on break.
I was going to step out back
and have a cigarette.
Would you like to join me?
[wavering] I don't smoke.
Neither do I.
Hold on, hold on.
What is it?
This is great!
You're so innocent.
Let's change that...
Shall we?
What would you
like me to do?
Well...
I don't really know...
I guess I really
haven't done that much.
I haven't really found the time,
with all my extracurriculars,
And model u.N.,
advanced placement classes,
after-school tutor...
- [unzipping]
- ...Ing! Ah!
Gosh, you really
like cameras!
Sometimes, we find our
clients are so overwhelmed
with the pleasure,
That they sometimes
scream out, "no,"
When really
they mean "yes."
And this is why
we have the safe word.
The "safe word"?
If at any time the ecstasy
gets too great,
You just use the safe word.
Until we hear the safe word,
we will not stop.
Yeah, right. Stop.
All right.
[laughing] we're going
to start slowly,
Teasing you with a little
light erotic foreplay.
[giggling] whee!
Oh, yes, ladies!
[barking] on, on,
vandersexxx!
[electric crackle, sizzle]
Hans! Gruber!
¶ [pounding rock music plays] ¶
Hi.
So, are the girls
coming back?
Administer the testicle clamps!
- Huh? What? Hey!
- [fabric ripping]
¶ [ music continues] ¶
Safe word!
What is that?!
That's not a word, it's a...
[stuttering]
"fluggen-kliggin-kien?"
- [zapping]
- [agonizing screams]
Fluggen!!!
[moaning]
- Ok, mister, don't move.
- Excuse me?
[brandishing knife]
shut the hell up!
Oh, brother!
Please don't hurt me.
Oh, no... You're fine.
That's good. You're fine.
Give me cash?
You got cash?
Take it all,
you dirty girl.
What?
Your wallet!
Focus!
- Give it to me.
- [loud groaning] oh!
Oh, I love you!
[jamie] I love you!
I love you!
I looove you!
[both giggling]
[high-pitched giggle]
[giggling]
What's so funny?
[distorted sound]
I'm really hungry.
I think I've got the munchies.
- Excuse me.
- Huh?
It's hot in here. You hot?
'cause I'm really hot.
- So good.
- Ok, I can't breathe! God!
I'm freaking out!
I think we got a bad batch
'cause I'm freaking out.
I can't...
I can't do this.
I saw a gay porno once.
I didn't know until halfway in.
The girls never came.
The girls never came!
[hyperventilating]
I am freaking out!!
- Everything all right with you?
- No, nothing's all right.
You sold us a bad batch
of hash brownies.
You're a bad rastafarian.
These are not hash brownies.
Hmm?
- What was that?
- We do not sell hash brownies.
We're a simple dutch bakery!
Now put your clothes
back on, white boy!
[screaming] ow! Ow! Ow!
"fluggengegeholen!"
[cymbals ring]
Did you say fluggegecheimen?
Yes! Yes!
For the love ogod,
fluggengecheimen!
Are you sure?
Yes, please.
As you wish.
[barking] bring on
the fluggegecheimen!
Wait... What?
Uh-oh.
[cooper] no, no, no!
I didn't say fluggegecheimen,
I said, uh...
[frantically mispronouncing]
[rapid buzzing]
What'd you do last night?
I don't want to
talk about it.
What did you guys do?
[both] don't want
to talk about it.
- What is that?
- Free t-shirt.
Hey, guys.
What happened to you?
I got robbed.
It was awesome!
[jenny] all our money,
our passports, our tickets...
Everything, gone!
How the hell
could this happen?
We all go to amsterdam, and
jamie's the one who hooks up!
For shame!
[cell phone rings]
Oh, that's me.
Coop here. Sorry.
Hello, mr. Walters.
You never got
the gutterman file?
I told humphrey
to give it to you.
That's hogwash. I handed it
to him myself yesterday.
Yes, sir, I will tell
humphrey to report to
your office immediately.
Bye.
- This job's killing me.
- [honking]
[speaks rapid german]
- Uh...
- Let me handle this.
I speak bad german.
- What did he say?
- He said he's driving.
- Oh.
- Something.
Jah.
Berlin?
- Berlin?
- Berlin!
- He's going to berlin!
- Awesome!
- All right! Berlin!
- Come on, let's go!
Next stop, berlin!
[tires screech]
¶ [german rock music plays] ¶
¶ [music continues] ¶
Beautiful!
We made it to berlin.
Jah. Berlin!
- Bratislava?
- Yeah.
Bratislava!
[tires screeching]
[scott] dear sweet
mother of god.
We're in eastern europe.
¶ [chorus sings] ¶
[jamie] eww!
[snarling]
Excuse me.
Do you speak any english?
You are americans?
Yeah.
I love america.
We just get "miami vice"
on television.
"miami vice" is number one
new show.
Yeah.
Listen, we're trying
to get to berlin, germany.
Do you know if there's
a train coming anytime soon?
Oh, yes, very soon.
They are building it now.
Stop! Hammer time!
[man] enjoy bratislava!
It's good you came in summer.
In winter, it can get
very depressing.
[jenny] we gotta
figure something out.
How much money do we have?
[coins jingling]
Frommer's travel tip.
I don't have anything.
What? I got noth...
Fine.
$1.83 american.
What are we gonna
get with that?
Gotta love that exchange rate!
T .
[waiter] dinner is served.
Would the masters care
for anything else?
Think we're good.
Thanks.
Ah! A nickel!
You see this?
- I quit!
- [grimacing]
I open my own hotel!
[scott] so, we got
27 cents left.
What is there to do
in this town?
[¶ throbbing techno music ¶]
- [girl] ¶ my scotty ¶
- [chorus] ¶ scotty, scotty ¶
[girl] ¶ scotty doesn't know ¶
¶ don't tell scotty ¶
- ¶ scotty doesn't know ¶
- [laughing]
This song
sounds familiar.
Jenny, lemme check
your coat.
- Hey!
- Jenny!
That outfit is horrible!
Just take it off... Now!
[giggling]
No, but I will let you
buy me a drink.
[man] excuse me!
You are the woman from the paris
train station, aren't you?
- My name is...
- Christoph.
[laughing] yes.
What are you doing here?
This is my place.
My family owns many like
these throughout europe.
I'd be honored if you'd
join me in my v.I.P. Room
for a drink.
Mmm-kay.
Bye, cooper.
- What's that?
- It's absinthe.
Frommer's says it's
illegal in the states
Because it makes you
hallucinate and go crazy.
They call it
"the green fairy."
My family has a yacht
in the aegean.
Come with me, jennifer.
We will sail away together.
Oh, my god!
We will swim with dolphins,
and sip champagne by moonlight.
Oh, my god!
We will spend the day
sunbathing, drinking wine.
My wife makes
the best sangria.
Wait... What?
Sangria.
You take a good
spanish rioja,
And you put in slices
of orange, and...
No, wait.
You said you were married?
You just go around
europe, sleeping with
every woman you meet?
No, please, jennifer.
It is not like that.
I also sleep with men.
I gotta say,
I'm not feeling anything.
Me neither.
Sober as a judge.
How 'bout you?
I'm not feeling
a goddamn thing.
This absinthe is bullshit!
I hear you, my brother.
I'm outta here.
Excuse me.
- Hey, so where's christoff?
- Shut up.
[cheering, screaming]
- [scott] europe!
- [cooper] europe!
- [all] whoo!
- [jenny] europe!
So, tomorrow, berlin.
Tomorrow, mieke!
Check it out.
[cooper] no way!
Jamie's hooking up
with another girl?
Goddamn it!
It's just so unfair.
I've been all over,
Looking for crazy european sex,
and he's the one who ends up...
- [moaning]
- [both] oh, my god!
That is some pretty
fucked-up shit.
[screaming]
They really are
the worst twins ever.
[screaming]
That was a pretty
wild night, eh?
Yep. Pretty wild,
pretty wild.
I know I was out of control.
How about you guys?
Did you...?
All right, look.
We were really drunk,
Things got a little crazy,
and jamie...
...Kissed me.
Let's just forget
about it, kay?
Ok, fine.
I'll give it a rest.
Jamie, could I borrow
your frommer's?
Oh, here it is.
Bratislava.
Hmm. Capital of slovakia.
Oh, here's a fun fact.
You made out with
your sister, man!
- Shut up! Shut up! Shut up!
- Like two dogs in heat.
- [screaming]
- [¶ car horn playing dixie ¶]
My friends, where is the beef?
[laughing]
You go to berlin?
I'm your ride.
Hop in.
¶ "99 red balloons" plays ¶
[scott] this is mieke's
apartment building.
Wish me all sorts
of luck, guys.
You'll do great,
scotty.
Thanks.
I came all this way.
I'm not gonna miss this.
[doorbell ringing]
- Dude, mieke's hideous! Run!
- Stop.
[speaking german]
Hi, my name
is scott thomas.
I'm from america,
and I'm here to see mieke.
I'm sorry, but
mieke's not here.
Do you know where she is?
She's gone for the summer.
[speaking german]
My daughter had intended to
spend the summer in america,
Looking at colleges
and visiting some friends.
But several days ago,
she suddenly changed her mind.
She would not tell me why.
I think I know why.
[speaking german]
This is heinrich.
He's mieke's stepbrother.
As I was saying, she packed
up her bag and left.
- It was all very sudden.
- Do you know where she is now?
[father] as you know,
she's always been very
interested in the classics,
Greek and roman literature
and history,
And she's always
enjoyed the ocean,
So she found a program that
combines all her interests.
Do you know where she is?
She enrolled in a summer at sea
program, based in rome.
Rome.
Ok, then I guess
we'll go to rome, then.
Unfortunately, mieke's only
in rome for orientation.
Tomorrow her group boards
a boat and she'll be
gone for the summmer.
She'll be quite unreachable.
Unreachable.
Mieke's tour group goes
to the vatican tomorrow,
Then she gets on that boat
and she's gone.
So, it's over?
Thanks for sticking with me
through this, guys, but...
You should probably call
your parents,
Have them wire you
some money and go home.
What are you gonna do?
I'm going to rome.
I'll walk, I'll hitchhike,
I'll swim if I have to,
but I'll get to mieke somehow.
Maybe that'll help.
Where'd you get
all that?
Wait. Where's your leica?
Sold it.
What?
You sold your leica?
But you loved that thing.
What about your
photo tour of europe?
What about the chateaus?
Chateaus have been there
for 300 years.
Mieke's gone in 12 hours.
Let's go!
Frommer's says to check in
Three hours before
any international flight.
Come here, guidebook!
Whoo! We're going to rome.
We're going to rome!
¶ be my girl ¶
¶ are you gonna be my ¶
¶ girl, yeah ¶
¶ be my girl ¶
¶ are you gonna be my girl ¶
All right,
summer at sea group.
Our tour begins
in the vatican museum.
This way, please.
There it is.
[speaking italian]
This entrance is for
private tour groups only.
Oh... But we are
a private tour group.
We've come all the way
from america.
That guy in the orange jacket
is mentally retarded.
Si, I can tell.
How very, very sad.
Yes, it is.
But if you are a tour,
where is your guide?
We've got a fantastic
tour guide.
- Right here.
- What? No...
The vatican has been used
as a papal residence
Ever since the time of
constantine the great
Of the 5th century a.D.!
- [speaking italian]
- oh.
Ok... Um... If you'll
all follow me, please.
[speaks slowly]
have a very special day
For a very special
little man.
Ok.
I can't believe
that guy let us in.
What a retard!
- Let's find mieke.
- Scuzzate.
One of our english-speaking
tour guides has called in sick.
Could you please take
these peoples also?
- How big is vatican city?
- .5 square kilometers.
- Who built the colonnades?
- Gianlorenzo bernini, 1656.
- Where are the bathrooms?
- Floors 2, 6 and 7.
Next I'll take you to where
the college of cardinals
elects a new pope.
When this happens, white smoke
is sent up from the vatican.
Here's a fun fact...
Mieke's gotta be
around here somewhere.
Let's go.
Behind me is the
appartamento papale,
Or "papal apartment."
we're obviously not permitted.
Excuse me, miss.
What is this?
That is the bell of san marco.
When the pope dies,
the cardinal vicar of rome
Rings this bell to notify
the people of rome.
Next we will view
the sistine chapel.
Follow me, please.
Come on.
I think I hear them.
Which way did they go?
That way. I'd stake
my reputation on it.
Good enough for me.
Hey, check it out!
I wonder what this does.
It doesn't do anything,
it's a rope. Come on, let's go.
[cooper] they got a lot
of old stuff here.
[bell ringing]
Dio mio!
The bell of san marco!
The pope is dead!
[murmuring]
Whoa.
She's not in here.
Let's go.
We're definitely not
supposed to be in here.
Hey, check this out!
- I'm the pope!
- Cooper...
Take off the pope hat.
- Oh, no. It's ok. I'm catholic.
- Take it off, goddamnit!
Oh, you took the
lord's name in vain!
Only I can forgive
you now, my son.
Take that fudging thing off!
The pope breaks
an open-field tackle.
It's a hail mary,
he catches at the 40...
The 30, the 20, the 10...
Touchdown, pope!
The pope makes
a two-point conversion.
And oh, my lord!
It's the pope, eight,
And the heathens, nothing!
[laughing]
How's you, sucka?
[making noises]
Cooper, the hat!
The hat!
The hat is on fire!
¶ we don't need no water
let the m... ¶
I'm not kidding! Look!
Oh, holy shit!
I don't want this!
Fireplace! Fireplace!
Go, go!
[both] whoa!
[man] white smoke!
They've elected the new pope!
I'm coming to you live
from vatican square
Where the college of cardinals,
in a surprise move,
Has just elected a new pope.
The crowd is very excited.
This is so strange.
Usually they wait 15 days
to elect a new pope.
We could be seeing
history in the making!
We could be seeing an arrest
in the making.
[coughing]
There she is.
Mieke!
Hey! Stupid curtain!
Let me out!
Mieke!
It's the new pope!
[cheering]
What the hell...?
Mieke!
[crowd gasps]
[scott] hold on!
This is one crazy pope.
[yelling]
[gasping]
[man] you!
Ferma! Stop! You!
You... And your
retarded friend,
You're in big, big trouble.
[man] oy!
¶ [rock music plays] ¶
Take your mitts
off them boys!
They're with me!
I've just about had enough
of you fuckin' ities!
But I am swiss!
Them, too!
Now, bud...
You get in there, and you
say what you got to say.
Mieke. I'm here.
I made it.
Who are you?
[crowd moans]
[bert laughing]
What a fucking loser!
I'm gonna videotape this.
I'm scott.
From ohio?
Scott?
Scott thomas?
- Yes.
- From ohio?
- What are you doing in rome?
- I came here to be with you.
Listen, I just traveled
all the way across europe.
I got chased by naked men.
I ate brownies with absolutely
no drugs in them.
I watched a brother
and sister make out.
I kicked a robot in the balls,
but I did it all so that...
...So I could tell you
one thing.
I love you, mieke.
[crowd] aww...
We're perfect for each other.
What do you think?
I think...
Oh, mike...
Mieke!
[moaning, gasping]
[woman] forgive me, father,
for I have sinned.
I have cheated on my husband.
Do you think god
will ever forgive me?
[moaning] oh, yes!
- [mieke moaning]
- father?
- [banging]
- [woman screams]
This sucks.
I can't believe I'm
the only one who didn't
hook up while we were here.
Europe is officially
the worst country on earth.
I know.
I thought I'd at least get to
have some crazy european sex.
What?
[giggling]
- Scott, I have to go.
- Ok.
My boat is leaving.
I still can't believe
you came all the way here,
Just for me.
What can I say?
I'm very unpredictable.
Keep writing to me,
scott, ok?
Yeah, I will.
Yes! Yes! Yes!
[scott] whoo-hoo!
Hey, guys, I'm so glad we got
to take this trip together.
This was the best time
of my life.
[man] excuse me.
You're the young man who
gave me that tour of
the vatican, aren't you?
- Listen, I'm very sorry...
- I just wanted to thank you.
You were the most knowledgeable,
albeit idiosyncratic,
Tour guide I've ever had.
Thanks.
But I'm not actually
a tour guide.
I've just read frommer's
enough to have it memorized.
Although I threw in a few things
frommer's didn't know about.
How would you like to add them?
Excuse me?
That's my guidebook.
I'm arthur frommer.
It's amazing!
Frommer's is going to
pay me to see every museum
and cathedral in europe.
- [laughing]
- that sounds so exciting...
For you.
I figured, since you're
going to be staying,
You might need this.
- A disposable camera.
- That's right.
Thanks, scotty.
That's from both of us.
[cell phone plays
"scotty doesn't know"]
Hello, mr. Walters.
I see.
Fired? Well, I...
Well, if that's what you want,
I understand. I just...
Goodbye, sir.
They had to catch you
eventually, right?
- No, they fired humphrey.
- Shut up!
I got his office and a raise.
- No!
- [laughing]
[announcer] flight 341
from rome to cleveland...
That's you guys.
- Have a good flight, everybody.
- Come here.
Be good.
- Oh! Ok...
- [grunting]
- Cooper, have a good flight.
- [grunting] be good.
Thanks.
I'm on it.
- [gasping]
- [bell tone]
[cooper] this still
counts as europe, right?
[scott] "dear mieke,
"greece sounds incredible.
"I just moved into
my dorm room today,
"but I can't wait to see you
over christmas break.
"this time I think I'll fly
to berlin direct."
[phone ringing]
- Hello?
- Hey buddy, how's college?
I just got here. My roommate
hasn't even showed up yet.
Do they room all you
pre-med geeks together?
I'm not sure
I'm going pre-med.
I'm thinking about
majoring in german.
German?
I've got a better idea.
Why don't you major in
not being such a woman?
So, how's jenny?
Jenny...
Jenny who?
I know a lot of ladies
named jenny, they're all...
Ow!
Hey, scotty,
what's up?
Hi, jenny!
How's jamie doing
with frommer?
Oh, no.
[robotic noises]
Hold on.
Come here, robot!
Cooper, not again!
[knocking]
Hold on, this could be
my new roommate.
[cooper] what's the freak
look like?
Is he a dork or is he cool?
Better not be cooler than me.
[cooper] is he bigger than me?
I just got your last email.
What are you doing here?
Going to college.
You're going to college here?
- What dorm?
- This one.
Room 214.
How is this possible?
I guess they thought
I was a guy.
Now who would be dumb enough
to make a mistake like that?
[cooper] do I hear kissing?
Are you making out with
your new roommate, scotty?
[giggling]
[cooper] scotty?
Scotty? Scotty!
¶ scotty doesn't know
that fiona and me ¶
This happy ending
is bullshit.
When does the fairy get laid?
I'm outta here.
¶ still she's on her knees
and scotty doesn't know ¶
¶ oh, scotty doesn't know ¶
- Catchy tune.
- Fuckin'-a, man.
¶ fiona says
she's out shopping ¶
¶ but she's under me
and I'm not stopping ¶
[chanting] scotty doesn't know!
Scotty doesn't know!
Hello, and welcome to
Amsterdam's finest and most
luxurious youth hostel.
Sounds great.
There is no bathroom,
nor is there one nearby.
[donny] ¶ I can't believe
he's so trusting ¶
[giggles] soy.
¶ while I'm right
behind you thrusting ¶
- Get it?
- She got it.
If you do not wish to have
your valuables stolen,
I suggest destroying them
or discarding them right now.
You can also try
hiding your valuables...
In your anus.
Drink?
I'm gonna rip away his pants
and look at his dick, ok?
- [laughing]
- ready? Quit. Shut up.
Sorry. I know I fucked it up.
Yes! You take her hair...
And one strand at a time,
pull it out!
Use her like a humping post!
Jenny, this is europe.
They have orange juice ads
with lesbians and dildos.
[announcer] "happy juice."
Show them something
they haven't seen.
¶ fiona's got him
on the phone ¶
¶ and she's trying
not to moan ¶
¶ it's a three-way call
and he knows nothing ¶
¶ nothing
scotty doesn't know ¶
¶ scotty doesn't know
Should a fire occur,
due to our faulty wiring,
Or the fireworks
factory upstairs,
you will be incinerated,
Along with the valuables
you have hidden in your anus.
¶ so don't tell scotty
scotty doesn't know ¶
¶ really want to go ¶
¶ scotty doesn't know
scotty doesn't know ¶
¶ scotty doesn't know ¶
¶ the parking lot
why not? ¶
¶ it's so cool
when you're on top ¶
- [bubbling]
- [giggling]
¶ life is so hard
'cause scotty doesn't know ¶
¶ scotty doesn't know ¶
Fuck off!
Get out of it, you wankers!
Go on, you gaelic fucking
garlic-breath tossers!
Piss off! Get in here
and say that, mate!
Come on! Fucking come
and have it!
You fucking beep?!
We'll beep, you bastard,
all over your fucking nose!
Fuck off!
Go on, you french bastards!
Get on the other side
of the road, you pricks!
Go on out of it!
Fuck off!
I'm nackered.
- [laughing]
- league supporters.
¶ scotty doesn't know
scotty doesn't know ¶
- [laughing]
- no, wait...
Hey! Check these out!
I'm 18 years old.
¶ gonna tell scotty
gonna tell myself ¶
¶ scotty has to know
scotty has to know ¶
¶ scotty has to
scotty has to go ¶
¶ scotty doesn' know
scotty doesn't know ¶
¶ scotty doesn't know
Scotty doesn't know!
- [crowd] scotty doesn't know!
- [yelling]
[crew member] scotty's gotta go!
¶ "get loose" plays ¶
300MB UNiTED TEAM - sunmenghao
300mbunited.com | rapidpremium.net
Is it off yet?
No, keep rubbing it.