Downloaded from
YTS.MX
[grand orchestral fanfare
playing]
Official YIFY movies site:
YTS.MX
-[quiet panting]
-[engines revving faintly]
[engines growing louder]
[engines roaring]
[tires screeching]
ANNOUNCER [over P.A.]:
That's the cleanup crew
up on the track,
and that's a lot of racers
-involved there, folks.
-[crowd cheering]
♪
[grunts] Jack, you realize
you got this in the bag, right?
Season's wrapped up, man.
Doesn't matter where you place.
I'm telling you,
I got intermittent miss.
-Last two laps.
-On it!
Get those plug wires!
Jakob! Now.
Hey, Pop.
Tell me what you see, Dom.
Got an oil spill
going into turn two.
Bell's driving safe.
Corbin's got a sponsor in
the stands, so he's pushing it.
MAN [in distance]:
Talking about me?
You got a real problem
with car 23.
-Linder. -MAN: About to
whip your ass, Toretto!
-MAN 2: Settle down,
pretty boy! -That's right.
-Shut up! -Yeah, you.
You want to tell your driver
-he's gonna get somebody hurt?
-What'd you say?
-JACK: Hey! Leave it!
-MAN: Go home! You suck!
He's just pissed I got that spot
in the Busch Series
next season, not him.
Life's got no shortage of guys
like Kenny Linder.
You're good!
It's not about being
the stronger man, Dom.
It's about being the bigger one.
[engine revving]
♪
[engines roaring]
[grunts]
I swear to God, this guy.
Pop, turn two, turn two!
-[sighs]
-Got it. I'm walking him in.
[grunts] Shit!
Tell me what you see, Dom.
He's gonna come at you for that.
Get ready on your left.
[engine sputtering]
[tires screeching]
♪
[birds chirping]
Three-eighths ratchet.
Three-eighths driver.
Six-inch extension.
Are you sure?
♪
Remember what your daddy
told you.
Be precise in life.
It can make all the difference.
Now, watch this.
-See how it's working now?
-LITTLE BRIAN: Mm-hmm.
And you see what's happening?
LITTLE BRIAN:
It's turning the screw.
DOM:
You're right.
Water heater's out again.
It's the price we pay
for peace and quiet.
Want to come and give us a hand?
[engine roaring in distance]
Are you expecting someone?
Brian, remember
what we practiced.
♪
ROMAN:
Yo, yo!
We come in peace.
We come in peace!
It's me!
Roman?
Maybe you don't recognize me
'cause I've been tanning
all week, bro.
[Letty and Roman chuckle]
B, come out, son.
What you gonna do
with that thing, man?
What, you out here trying
to kill elephants or something?
We would've called first.
Except you actually need phones
in order to get phone calls.
You know that, right?
-ROMAN: Little B!
-RAMSEY: Wow, you're so big.
-LITTLE BRIAN: Hi. -TEJ: Wow.
-RAMSEY: Hi. -[Letty laughs]
Now, I know you don't carpool.
So what's up?
[staticky]:
Mayday! Mayday!
My plane is under attack
by a rogue agent!
-[garbled chatter]
-[rapid gunfire]
We're being boarded. I've got
dangerous cargo on board.
I need you to assemble the team.
[garbled]:
...still alive. I'll explain...
[static crackling]
It's an SOS transmission
from Mr. Nobody's plane.
It came through with
a mess of encrypted data,
most of which
I'm still trying to crack.
-Did anybody else get this?
-TEJ: Well, that's the thing.
He sent it only to us.
Why just us?
He caught Cipher.
But there was a midair attack,
and she was extracted.
It seems his plane crashed
somewhere here,
over the northwest region
of Montequinto.
TEJ: If Mr. Nobody survived,
we need to find him.
But the whole area's sealed off.
Isolationist, run by military.
We're not on call anymore.
ROMAN:
Wait, wait.
Dom, this is Cipher.
The woman who killed
the mother of your child.
Things change.
Listen, we're wheels up
at 8:00 a.m.,
if you change your mind.
Thank you.
[insects trilling]
LITTLE BRIAN: Daddy,
do you know where God is?
-DOM: Where is God?
-In your heart.
DOM:
He's in your heart, too.
And you know something?
I'll always be in your heart.
Hey, little guy.
I have a gift for you.
Your father gave this to me.
And now I'm gonna
give it to you.
It's very special.
Take care of it.
♪
[whispers]:
Good night.
This isn't who we are.
Brian and Mia got out of the
game when they became parents.
We're not them.
[engine starts]
♪
MR. NOBODY [staticky]: ...under
attack by a rogue agent!
We're being boarded. I've got
dangerous cargo on board.
[garbled]:
...assemble the team.
...still alive. I'll explain...
...alive. I'll explain...
♪
[engine roaring in distance]
[sighs]
["Exotic Race" by Murci feat.
Sean Paul & Dixson Waz playing]
♪ Yo voy pa la calle
y quiero velocidad... ♪
[song continues in Spanish]
[engines roaring]
Coming up on the signal,
two miles.
It's deep in the militarized
zone of Montequinto.
-I hope everyone's ready.
-Ready?
Y'all want to make jokes
about me
not making practical decisions?
This is as prepared as it gets.
We all see you, man.
Nobody thinks you're
compensating for anything.
[laughs]
-LETTY: I'll take point.
-Careful.
Careful's when you get hurt.
RAMSEY:
Right now, we have
a ten-minute window
between patrols.
Mr. Nobody's signal is close,
but we've got
to move quickly, guys.
We do not want to cross paths
with the military here.
♪
-[device beeping steadily]
-[birds calling in distance]
-It's inside.
-Cover us.
[electricity crackling]
The source of the SOS signal is
coming from inside this thing.
[Ramsey grunts]
[devices beeping]
Somebody wanted in.
Plane must have gone down
before they could cut through.
Or it was sent down
on purpose to stop 'em.
Yeah, well, their mistake
was trying to cut into it.
But just give me a minute.
I can get in.
Dom.
There's not a soul in sight.
No sign of Mr. Nobody.
-[device beeps]
-RAMSEY: Got it.
[electrical trilling]
What the hell is this?
Whatever it is, Mr. Nobody
wanted us to find it.
-How's that work...
-[rapid gunfire]
Go!
[motorcycle engine revs]
[man shouting in Spanish]
[men shouting in Spanish]
What?!
You don't know who I am?!
You think I'm scared?!
[screams]
[gunfire continues]
-[grunts]
-[men shouting]
[Roman yells]
[men shouting in distance]
-[guns cocking]
-[men shouting]
[yells]
[man groans]
[panting]
♪
[engine revs]
[Ramsey gasps]
Roman, where the hell are you?!
Who's compensating now, Tej?!
[gunfire continues]
"Peligro minas."
What does that mean?
Tej, how fast we got to go
to clear 'em?
Please don't tell me
you're thinking
-what I think you're thinking.
-ROMAN: Why?
What does "peligro minas"mean?
-Tej, how fast?
-I don't know, man.
ROMAN:
Somebody answer me!
What does "peligro minas"mean?
"Peligro minas"means
-"danger, land mines"!
-What?!
How fast, Tej?
Assuming a 50-foot blast radius
and a-a half a second trigger
delay, I'd say about 80.
I can't!
My speedometer
only goes up to 70.
-What do I do?! -You put
your foot to that floor,
and you pray!
♪
[grunts]
[screams]
♪
Get to that palm plantation,
and then we're clear.
[grunts]
[shouts]
Whoa!
[grunts]
Roman, you good?
ROMAN:
My ass is en fuego!
[tires screech]
Tej! Wait! Land mine!
[screams, grunts]
[panting]
-[rocks rumbling]
-[vehicle creaking]
[grunts]
[grunting]
[Roman screams]
[vehicle creaking]
[screams]
[Ramsey gasps]
♪
[mutters]
How in the hell
are you not dead?
[Roman muttering]
Wait, okay, I think
I found us another way out.
Two miles to what looks like
a bridge across the border.
Good. The sooner we get
out of here, the better.
DOM:
Letty, on the right.
[man grunts]
[Letty grunting]
The device.
♪
[birds squawking]
[gasps]
[engine revs]
Get in.
♪
That was Jakob back there,
wasn't it?
♪
Always check your mirrors,
bitches!
Oh, hell no.
Are we supposed to drive
across that?
Well, I said
it looked like a bridge.
[Ramsey grunts]
[Roman screaming]
ROMAN:
Oh, my God!
[sign creaking]
[screaming continues]
[grunts]
The military's not giving up.
We got to get past the border.
♪
[groans]
Where's the bridge?
No. No, no.
Dom.
[Letty gasps]
-[grunts]
-[yells]
[glass tinkling]
Well, that was new.
Look, we're in the clear.
But this thing is a mess.
The headlines out there?
Secret spy plane crashes
in a hostile country?
Followed by some kind of
covert ops firefight?
I'll get you where you need...
and then I'm gonna need
to back off.
I appreciate the favor.
I got to stop doing
so many favors.
What we doing, Ramsey?
Like, where are we going?
I-I was able to decrypt the data
that came through
with Mr. Nobody's SOS,
and I found GPS coordinates,
definitely included on purpose.
You knew about Jakob?
Question: Who is Jakob?
LETTY:
Jakob is--
or was Dom's brother.
Oh, my-my bad.
I'm sorry. I'm just processing.
Brother?
You got a brother?
Who also happens to be
some kind of super spy
with his own private army,
who drives literally like
a bat out of hell,
who preplanned an aerial jump
and landed at the bottom
of an airplane?
Who does that?
TEJ:
Who does that? A Toretto.
That's my dad! That's my dad!
-[sobbing]
-He's gone! He's gone!
DOM:
We got to get him out of there.
We got to get him out of there!
That's my dad!
That's my dad! That's my dad!
Get him out of there!
That's my dad!
There's a couple of release
forms we've got to sign.
Few clearances.
Everything else is down there
around the corner.
Hey.
Nobody's supposed to be
around here.
You Toretto's other son?
You're the useless one, right?
[panting]
What is that?
Get out of here. Go.
So a man can't pay
his last respects?
That's what that is?
No.
No, not you.
You're the one that killed him.
No, racing killed him.
Look, he knew that I was gonna
pit him into the wall.
He knew that.
Now, I don't know if
he dropped gear. I don't know.
I swear... I swear to God,
-if you don't get out
of here... -What? What?
Go find Buddy.
Now!
[chuckles]
All right, well,
now we got the golden boy.
Leave.
You here to make threats, too?
"Leave" is a simple word.
Man, what is it
with you Torettos
where you're all the heroes
in your own stories?
Look, I'm gonna
tell you a secret.
You, your dad, me--
we're all stuck,
going round and round
in the same shitty circle.
And we ain't never getting out.
You ain't half the man
my dad was.
-At least I'm alive, asshole.
-What did you say?
Get off me!
BUDDY:
Dom! Dom!
-Dom!
-[grunts]
-Dom, no! Dom!
-[tool clanking]
-No, man!
-[Dom grunting]
♪
[indistinct chatter]
[chains clinking]
OFFICER:
In here.
[door closes]
♪
[door whirs, clanks]
-[helicopter whirring]
-[indistinct chatter]
[engine starts]
Jakob.
I simply cannot believe that
magnet trick actually worked.
It looked so damn cool.
Look at this here.
I got this off the cockpit feed.
Oh, I love being rich.
JAKOB:
It was sloppy. He almost had me.
-She say anything?
-Nope. Nada.
You know, I look at her
and I feel creeped out.
And sort of turned on
at the same time.
Is that weird?
[electrical whirring]
CIPHER:
Nice operation.
You snatched me off
Mr. Nobody's plane midair
without a scratch,
and you took him down.
Money well spent.
-Do you know who I am?
-I know who you are.
Do you?
East L.A. is a tough enough
place to grow up.
But it was your brother's shadow
that turned you into this.
Isn't it?
So your whole life, you pushed
yourself to be faster than Dom.
Smarter than Dom.
Stronger than Dom.
Tell me, do you hate him enough
that it keeps you up at night?
[whispers]:
Still?
All these years later?
I should've just hired you
instead of coercing your
brother a couple of years back.
I don't work
for the competition.
That's cute.
You thinking
you're the competition.
Says the woman in the box.
Look familiar?
The other half's hidden
in one of the agency's
thousands of vaults.
I need you to find out
which one.
We secured the master drive here
from Mr. Nobody's plane.
The rest of the hardware
is a bit dated.
Pre-Internet.
To make sure you don't go
hack into anything
we don't want you to.
Say you get what you're after.
A weapon so dangerous
it shouldn't exist
for another half century.
What would you do with it?
Launch some global attack?
Sell it to the highest bidder?
Or maybe you see yourself
as a necessary shock
to the system.
I bet all you ever wanted
was a hug.
You read my psych eval.
Good for you.
I read your second-grade
report card.
That's what I do.
[typing]
Your chin-- it's distinctive.
I know the Torettos have
quite the mixed bloodlines,
but I never detected
a Nordic strain.
[typing]
Finding the two halves of
Project Aries is the easy part.
Add in your brother Dom
to the mix?
[whispers]:
You don't have a chance.
Plans are in motion.
Qasar Khan.
What?
Genghis Khan's little brother.
Nobody's heard of him either.
♪
[seagulls squawking]
[air hisses]
[rats squeaking]
RAMSEY:
Talk about off the grid.
ROMAN:
I don't think they had grids
when this place was built.
If a Ninja Turtle pop out on me,
tell you right now, I'm out.
TEJ: No way this place was
sanctioned by the agency.
This was definitely
Mr. Nobody's secret hideout.
[switch clanks]
[electricity powering up]
What now, Dom?
Whoever Jakob has become...
...and whatever he's up to...
...it's on me.
And me alone.
ROMAN:
Nah.
Whatever's on you, it's on us.
Let's get to work.
[rap music playing quietly
over speakers]
[clears throat]
Y'all ever thought about how
many wild missions we been on?
How we somehow...
-always survive?
-TEJ [chuckles]: Yeah.
-So far, so good, I guess.
-It's just luck.
ROMAN: No, no, no, see,
y'all not listening.
Think about this.
We've now been
on insane missions
around the world,
doing what most would say is
damn near impossible.
And I ain't got one single scar
to show for it?
I mean, look at my jacket.
Those are bullet holes from
14 dudes trying to take my head
clean off its shoulders.
We've taken out
cars, trains, tanks.
I'm not gonna even
mention the submarine.
And yet we're still here.
Exactly.
Ramsey, what happens
when you test a theory
over and over again only
to come to the same result?
A hypothesis becomes fact.
But you're not actually
suggesting that...
I don't know,
but when the improbable happens
again and again,
that's more than luck.
Maybe we're not so normal.
ROMAN:
That's what I'm saying.
We are not normal.
Okay, um...
just to clarify,
are you two maybe suggesting
that we're what,
invincible?
-Maybe.
Or maybe...
you're just a dumbass.
[Tej and Ramsey laughing]
Take your dumbass jacket
with you, man. [scoffs]
Pretty impressive driving
out there.
You miss the old life.
Do you?
[gun racks]
Every day.
TEJ:
Guys.
We got a little company.
Think you know this person.
-It's so good to see you.
-MIA: I missed you.
Thank you.
[whispers]:
Of course.
You should've told me.
She deserved to know.
Jakob's my brother, too.
I need to be here.
You get involved here, you put
everything you have at risk.
Your kids and the whole world
that you built.
We're all risking something.
Dom, listen to me.
My kids and yours are
in the safest hands possible.
With Brian.
Our world's grown, Dom.
I got this one.
RAMSEY:
The firewall on this old thing
is actually pretty good.
But, you know, port scan,
UDP message peek,
pop to root shell, and...
[computer beeping]
...say hello to Project Aries.
What is it?
It's what we got from
Mr. Nobody's plane.
Or at least part of it.
Aries was designed
to override and assimilate
anything that runs on code.
Any computer anywhere.
If it operates on zeros
and ones, it's vulnerable.
If you take Aries
and upload it to a satellite,
it'll spread like a virus.
Then it'll be a matter of time
before someone can control
any weapon system--
traditional, nuclear,
stuff we haven't even seen yet--
and just point it
wherever they want.
Jakob reboots the world order
within minutes.
TEJ:
Ares is the god of war, right?
If Jakob gets his hands on this,
he'll be the god
of damn near everything.
RAMSEY:
Because of how dangerous it was,
the Aries prototype
was recovered
and split into two halves
by Mr. Nobody.
Both of which are worthless
without the activation key.
Jakob now has one of the pieces.
He'll be going after
the other half next.
As for the key, it's...
it's vanished.
So we find it.
If we're gonna beat Jakob to it,
we're gonna have to split up.
Roman, Tej,
I know a couple of guys
operating out of Germany that
could get us anything we need.
I'm on it.
Wait, there's one more thing.
Mr. Nobody's transmission
had one name
connected to the key.
You guys are gonna want
to brace yourselves for this.
LETTY:
No way.
That's exactly what I said.
ROMAN: So you're saying
Han's death is connected
to all of this?
He has to have
something to do with it.
LETTY:
I'll look into it.
Tej, can you send me
-all the files you have on Han?
-Yeah.
I'll go with you.
DOM:
Letty.
I got this the day Han died.
Mexico.
Check the postmark.
Whatever he was up to,
it ended here.
Tokyo.
What are you gonna do
about Jakob?
I'm gonna find him.
How?
An old friend.
-[buzzer sounds]
-[bell rings]
[men chattering in Spanish]
Yo, what do you think?
¿Es una ilusión o es real?
It doesn't matter.
It's all about
how you choose to see it.
BOTH:
Shit. I told you I was right.
-I'm Leo.
-Santos.
Dom. What are you guys in for?
Driving while brown.
[speaks Spanish] You see that?
Hairline crack in the fuel line.
Air gets in there,
you got a lean condition.
Lean condition?
["Appetite for Destruction"
by N.W.A playing]
♪ I got a taste for wasting
and tasting the blood ♪
♪ Murder, I heard her
when she screamed and dropped ♪
♪ 'Cause her son
caught the slug ♪
-♪ Relate this to no choice
-[engine revving]
♪ And listen to
this straight-up man ♪
♪ Before they ban the voice
♪ While I rhyme
to the rhythm of a pop ♪
♪ Remember the first brother to
run is the first to get shot ♪
-[engine revving] -♪ Whoever
said that what I say ♪
♪ And portray is negativity
♪ Need to come kick it
in the city with me ♪
♪ And find the black and crack,
in fact, they take that back ♪
♪ Because they really can't
deal with that... ♪
-[crowd cheering]
-[engine revving]
[cheering continues]
MAN:
Yeah! Yeah, Jakob!
WOMAN:
That's what I'm talking about!
Who wants next?
I said, who wants next?!
DOM:
I got next.
Dom.
Well, when'd you get out, man?
I said I got next.
Come on, Dom.
You don't want to race me
in Buddy's old Charger.
Car don't make the driver.
Here's how this goes.
You win...
you can come back home.
You lose...
you keep driving,
you don't stop,
you don't ever come back.
Ever.
What do you mean, Dom?
I know what you did.
The day we lost him, Dad kept
talking about a misfire.
Remember?
You were the last one
under his hood that day.
A minute later, he was gone.
Tell me why you killed Dad.
Now let's race.
-Armed robbery in Echo Park.
-[garbled radio chatter]
-Fourth Street Bridge is open.
-Clear, clear, clear!
[excited chatter]
[engines revving]
♪
[tires screeching]
-Ready?
-[engines revving]
Set.
-Go.
-[tires squealing]
♪ Set the time
for the battleground ♪
♪ Guided missiles
will hunt you down ♪
♪ Drones surrounding your home
♪ Don't breathe,
you're not safe underground ♪
♪ Political landscape shape
has been polarized ♪
♪ Now it's time
to reveal the zeal ♪
♪ Everybody breathe,
get mobilized ♪
♪ Trying to buy
the American dream ♪
♪ But it's overpriced
♪ Five-bil deal
for the fighter jets ♪
♪ Being shipped
to the Middle East ♪
♪ It'll cost
ten billion more dollars ♪
♪ For neighbors
to feel safe to breathe ♪
♪ What, what
-♪ What, what
-♪ Breathe with me
♪ What
♪ Sometimes we got to stop
and breathe ♪
♪
[exhales]
[nitrous whooshing]
♪ Stop, breathe
♪
♪ Breathe with me
♪ Sometimes we got to stop
and breathe. ♪
-[grunts]
-[engine revving]
Too soon.
[tires squealing]
No!
[tires screech]
[breathes deeply]
[engine roaring]
♪ Green light,
we gon' ride the night ♪
♪ Loud pipes, we gon'
ride the night ♪
♪ Fishtailing
out the parking lot ♪
♪ No cops, we ain't gonna stop
♪ Switch gears,
we gon' drag and drift ♪
♪ Hit the gas
and we pack the clip ♪
♪ Muscle cars
sound mad as hell ♪
-♪ Whoa, whoa
-♪ Na-na-na, whoa
-♪ Na-na-na, whoa.
ANNOUNCER [over radio]:
...and beating the shortstop.
-[crowd cheering] -Line drive
over the head of Gonzalez
on the field for a base hit.
Up next...
[sportscast continues
indistinctly]
DOM:
Place still looks the same.
[grunts]
Just like your dad left it.
I'm looking for Jakob.
Can't help you, man.
I know you took Jakob in
after my father died.
The worst thing
you can do to a Toretto
is take away their family.
That's what you did to Jakob.
You've got people who love you,
count on you, care for you.
He ain't got no one.
You get in his way,
this ain't gonna end
until one of you guys
are in the ground.
I know you did
the best you could, Buddy.
But we both know he's about
to cause a lot of hurt.
[sighs]
[sets down tool]
I did my best
to take care of Jakob.
But I'm no Jack Toretto.
You've got to make peace
with the past if you...
...if you want hope
for the future.
♪
He's in London.
That's all I know.
Dom.
I hope you find your peace.
The chance for peace died
that day on the track.
["Bushido" by Good Gas
and JP The Wavy playing]
[song continues in Japanese]
[woman speaks Japanese]
Arigato.
This place is a dead end.
Do you think Jakob could be
onto the Han connection?
If he has all the information
we do, probably.
I never told Dom...
I stayed in touch with him for
a while after what happened.
He was over at Buddy's
for about a year, and then...
he was gone with
a message not to follow.
But after he disappeared,
I was so desperate to find him
that I would've...
would've done anything.
I even broke into
a police archive,
but I didn't find anything.
You what?
You were like 16.
I did what I had to do.
Yeah.
How about you?
How are you doing?
[chuckles]:
It's a change of pace, huh?
Just as I was remembering...
...who I was,
everything changed.
It slowed down.
There's peace for me
in the chaos.
It's like I... I need to face
the world head-on or something
to feel alive.
Seeing Little Brian
hiding in a hole because
we had unexpected company...
...that got to me.
We never used to hide.
Hey, Dom's my brother, but you
will always be my sister.
Funny how we all have secrets.
What?
You got to be kidding me.
What is it?
Remember what Han used to say
about Tokyo?
You mean how
in all the old Westerns,
cowboys would make a run
for the border to get away
from the law,
how Tokyo was his...
Mexico.
[gasps]
No way.
["Lane Switcha" by Pop Smoke
and Skepta playing]
♪ I'm a lane switcher
♪ Big tank, bank filler
♪ Real killer,
die for my gang member ♪
♪ Gun driller,
dope man dope dealer ♪
♪ Gorilla...
[exhales]
She's ready to roll.
No. No!
No, Sean!
Tell me you are not modding
the quick disconnect valve
on the LOX line.
SEAN:
Hey, man, chill out.
All right? It's all good.
-That tweak just saved us
0.4 seconds. -"All good"?
This isn't Top Gun,Maverick.
You don't follow
the rules here, you die.
Hey, come on.
That's a bit much.
When you know what too much
pressure in the LOX line
can do, come talk to me.
Till then, stay in your lane.
Yo, you're lucky
to even be in my lane.
In case you forgot,
I'm the one that figured out
how to let us build
rocket engines and get paid.
This whole thing was my idea.
So who are you gonna trust
with your brilliant idea,
this glorified mechanic...
or a rocket scientist?
Without me, you'd be
working at Jiffy Lube.
Guys, guys.
Look, it's all good.
Who cares about who did what?
Kind of hard for you
to do anything
when you pee your pants
every time you fly, Twinkie.
TEJ:
Did I hear that right?
You a runner
and you afraid of flying?
"Twinkie"?
So you must be
Ding Dong and Snoball.
-Right?
-Yo, uh...
I don't go by that name anymore.
You went by that name ever?
Like, ever?
[softly]:
I... That's-that's-that's...
[woman speaking German
over staticky radio]
-Hey! We're up.
-Oh, good.
SEAN:
Hey, fellas.
Y'all seen ten-second cars?
Well, say hello
to the two-second car.
[Sean whoops, laughs]
TEJ:
Is that a Pontiac Fiero
strapped to a rocket engine?
Impressive, I know.
No.
No, that's not impressive.
[jet engine whirring]
Eyes up! Here it comes!
Let the race begin!
[car engine starts]
[tires squeal]
[engine revving]
[tires squealing]
Plane's taking off!
Go, go, go, go!
[rocket engine sputters]
Yes!
[Earl and Sean whooping]
We did it!
[whooping continues]
[excited shouting]
[whooping]
Uh... I'm confused.
Y'all didn't actually
beat the jet.
It didn't explode.
-Yeah, or melt.
-Yeah.
She's still in one piece.
[explosion booms]
You mean "pieces"?
Hey, Jiffy Lube, next time,
will you listen to me?
Look, we heard y'all could
get us some wheels.
Preferably the kind
that don't explode.
Is that possible?
Well, the Honda dealership's
about 3,000 miles that way.
Dominic Toretto sent us.
♪
Who's Dominic Toretto?
[Tchaikovsky's
"Waltz of the Flowers" playing]
[quiet chatter]
♪
[alarm wailing]
[urgent chatter]
Hmm.
DOM:
Nice necklace, Queenie.
Diamonds and emeralds
never looked so good.
Dominic Toretto.
The word on the street is
you got locked up.
Yeah, well, in and out,
you know.
When are they gonna learn?
Some birds can't be caged.
Are you looking for
one of me sons?
[sirens wailing in distance]
Not tonight.
You do the driving,
I'll cut you in for 15%.
-My thieving days are over.
-[car alarm chirps]
Mine ain't.
You coming?
[engine starts, revs]
[tires squealing]
♪
[sirens wailing]
[tires squealing]
I'm looking for someone.
Would've shown up in town
a little while ago.
A lot of guys,
a lot of resources.
Oh, yeah, yeah,
word did go round
on a crew that just turned up,
led by an American.
[tires squealing]
Yeah, he bought some arms
off a local seller.
Rumor had it he was into
something big up in Edinburgh.
Local seller, huh?
She wouldn't happen to be
wearing a stolen necklace,
-would she?
-He paid well.
What was I supposed to do?
This geezer was about
your height, actually.
Similar features.
Oh, bloody hell, he's not your
cousin or something, is he?
He's my brother.
Get the hand brake for me,
would you, darling?
[tires squealing]
Glad I'm not the only one with
a family full of eccentrics.
[engine revving]
He offered payment
for something else.
You.
["Mala" by Jarina de Marco
playing]
♪ I am the thorn in your crown
[distorted laugh, click]
♪ Veneno you hold
in your mouth ♪
♪ That you won't spit out
[engine revs]
You know,
nothing's more powerful
than the love of family.
But you turn that
into anger and resentment,
nothing's more dangerous.
Dom?
Don't get yourself killed, okay?
You're my favorite American.
♪ Yo no tengo corazón
♪ Está hecho de piedra
♪ Solo quiere destrucción
♪ Put you bajo tierra
♪ Danger, danger
♪ Soy la peligrosa,
rio cuando lloras ♪
-♪ La-la-la-la-la
-[engines revving]
♪ La-la-la-la-la
♪ Mala.
♪
This is your kind of party,
isn't it, Dom?
Beautiful women, best cars,
best everything.
You know, best security, too.
I'm Otto.
I'm your brother's partner.
[chuckles]
Well, fi-financier.
But, you know, my dad,
he's a dictator,
so we're not talking
regular people rich here.
No, no, no, no, no.
Everything you see here, I own.
These girls, if you want
to meet one of them,
maybe two, maybe three,
just let me know.
They're on the payroll.
I offer a bomb-ass dental plan,
too. [laughs] Huh?
Where is Jakob?
He's inside.
♪
The brother
you're looking for...
he's from an old life.
-He's long gone.
-All I see is the same
scared little kid
that killed our father.
[chuckles]
That's your mistake.
The spy game...
this is my world.
So here's my offer.
It's the same one you gave me.
You leave.
Now.
You drive away,
and you never come back.
Ever.
A deal?
I showed you mercy!
And I won't show it
to you again.
[door opens]
OTTO:
Toretto.
Since my dad is head of state,
it makes me a foreign dignitary
and this place an embassy.
Which means you just trespassed
into my country
and attempted murder.
So, naturally, I called in
a little favor
with all my good friends
from Interpol.
You keep digging around
in the past, Dom,
you're not gonna like
what you find.
♪
[vehicle door closes]
And here I thought my dad
was a pain in the ass.
But your family is
a train wreck.
Well, now that your brother's
finally out of the game,
it's time we go to Edinburgh.
Get the second piece, maybe
do a little sightseeing, huh?
Any news on the key?
Don't worry about it.
Our men are closing in.
One week from now, there won't
be a superpower in the world
can take a piss
without our permission.
One week from now,
your dad will be asking you
-for an allowance.
-[laughs]
I'd like that.
[siren wailing]
Whew.
[speaking excitedly in Spanish]
What's up?
-Well done, Leysa.
-Please.
If it wasn't for you, I'd still
be stealing gas in the D.R.
So Queenie treating you right?
Like a princesa.
I'm her number-one pick,
you know.
Cara's little sister done good.
Good?
You saw my fine ass
in that white dress.
You see how I been rocking shit?
All this crew,
this is mine. Huh?
I been around the world.
Oh, I almost forgot.
You might need this.
Your boy Jakob biometrics
are encoded to this gun.
You'll have no trouble
tracking him now.
♪
[lock clicks]
Hey, Letty.
LETTY:
Yeah.
Come look at this.
What the hell?
MIA: Han never mentioned
a girl, not ever.
-Letty, Mia!
-[footsteps running]
Down, now!
[grunting]
[footsteps running]
♪
[man shouts]
[man groans]
[panting]
[shouts]
[man screams]
[women scream in distance]
[crowd murmuring]
[gunfire]
You okay?
♪
[electronics trilling]
[door buzzes, opens]
[door beeps]
WOMAN: Welcome to Saint Giles'
Cathedral of Edinburgh.
The High Kirk has a history
stretching back over 900 years.
Renowned for
its stained glass windows,
you can see
the intricate craftsmanship...
[device trilling]
-[earpiece beeps]
-We're a go.
♪
Ramsey, talk to me.
What do we got?
I pulled Jakob's biometric
signature off the gun,
and the algorithm I've run says
Jakob's team is
right on top of us.
Anywhere between
80 and 100 meters.
80 meters?
That's a lot around here.
This whole area
seems pretty packed in.
[British accent]:
So, we don't know
where the secret vault facility
Jakob is looking to hit is,
now, do we?
Wouldn't be a secret if we did.
[normal voice]:
You know what?
I'm starting to think
your little English accent
makes you sound smarter
than you are.
[tires screech]
Man, can I point out
that a good old-fashioned
tracking chip would've put us
within like
six feet of this dude?
But, nah, instead,
we out here with biometrics
and facial recognition imaging.
Feels like we looking
for Where's Waldo
-in Harry Potter world.
-RAMSEY: Yeah, uh,
strong argument there, Tej, but
tracking chips follow the chip.
Before we know it,
we'd be chasing some expensive
yet tacky jacket
to the dry cleaner's.
Biometrics, on the other hand,
are impossible to...
-[device beeps]
-[static crackling]
Wait.
Guys, okay, we have a problem.
Cameras are going down
all around us,
and my equipment is
freaking out.
[static crackling]
-What the hell, Jimmy?
-[alarm beeping]
Security alert.
Cameras are down.
[alarm wailing]
Damn.
You see anything suspicious?
Uh, where do I start?
First of all, all of this
looks a little spooky.
I even seen
these two ladies walking
with George Washington wigs
on their head from the 1700s.
I feel like I'm in Transylvania
or some damn where.
[alarm buzzing, wailing]
ROMAN: Ramsey,
we're looking everywhere.
I just grew a new bunion.
This is hopeless.
What?
-You see that?
-See what?
The ears.
They got cauliflower ears.
They fight for a living.
-Don't worry about it.
-Roman.
Hey, man, I ordered
a pair of Crocs
three weeks ago,
and I'm still waiting!
[grunting]
Where are my shoes, man?!
Man, we really need
to work on your planning.
[scoffs]
Hey, Dom, you should
get down to the cathedral.
Dumbass here just attacked
some delivery dudes
'cause he didn't like
their ears.
ROMAN:
Wait, wait, wait.
H-How much did you say
you paid for that again?
You know silver
ain't magnetic, right?
You know what?
Sh-- Just shut up.
Just shut up.
Ramsey, say we had
a big electromagnet
turned up right around here.
Wouldn't that disrupt
all electronic signals?
Including security systems.
That's it.
That's how Jakob's
getting into the vault.
RAMSEY:
Guys?
[sirens wailing]
Okay, we've got police
coming from all sides.
-The area's locking down.
-He ain't using roads.
[tires screech]
[high-pitched whirring]
I got eyes on Jakob.
[engine revs]
RAMSEY:
I see Otto.
I'm gonna tail him.
[tires squealing]
He's heading towards
a blue Jaguar.
Okay, follow him.
RAMSEY:
Me? I can't.
Why not?
Okay, this is a bad time
to tell you this,
but I don't drive.
Okay? I never got my license.
I don't know how to drive.
And, you know, no one
really drives in London.
Okay? And that is not
my contribution to this group.
It's you or no one.
[sighs]
[engine starts, revs]
Shit.
Guys, come on, man.
I feel like,
between the six of us,
we can work this out, right?
Okay. I've got...
-[electricity buzzing]
-[Ramsey screams]
[grunting]
Ramsey, shut it off!
Shut it off!
[buzzing stops]
Go, go, go!
Okay. Uh...
Brake is on the left,
accelerator right.
Oh.
[engine starts]
[grunting]
[tires squealing]
♪
-[electricity buzzing]
-Shit.
KIDS:
Hey!
[car horn blaring]
Oh! Sorry!
[horns honking]
-Whoa!
-[man shouts]
[grunting]
-[horn blares]
-[shouts]
[tires screeching]
-Oh, no!
-[horns honking]
Move!
Hey, that was not my fault!
[tires squealing]
Okay, that one was my fault.
[grunting]
[high-pitched whirring]
♪
ROMAN:
See?
What'd I tell you?
Not even a scratch.
Otto, sending you
new pickup location.
[grunting]
I've got it.
I'm headed to you now.
[woman gasping]
[panting]
[bus brakes squeak
and hiss outside]
[device beeps]
Otto, where are you?
Jakob, I'm there.
I don't see anybody.
It's because you're
on the wrong street.
[Dom grunting]
[tires squealing]
-[Ramsey grunts]
-[tires squealing]
That's my car, pal!
RAMSEY:
Dom!
[tires squealing]
Go!
-Damn it.
-[engine revving]
[sighs]
[electricity whirring]
[Ramsey grunts]
[Ramsey panting]
You're a natural.
[chuckles] Of course I am.
♪
Okay, listen up!
I want 50 of the best men!
I want guns!
I want wheels, freaking
X-wing fighters-- I don't care!
The Millennium Falcon,
Chewbacca if you can
get ahold of him.
-Money's no object. Go.
-[snaps fingers]
-Go!
-[men murmuring]
[Cipher laughing]
What?
What's so funny?
I...
I was thinking,
if this was a movie,
this would be the moment
where the villain has
an unexpected setback,
overcompensates without
thinking it through
and gets crushed
by the good guys.
[chuckles softly]
No offense, but you have
no idea what we're about to do.
And for the record,
we're the good guys.
Me?
I'm Luke freaking Skywalker.
Are you sure about that?
I mean, I get
the daddy issues, but...
Look at what you've built.
Really? Luke?
You're right.
No, I'm more of a Han Solo.
No.
You're Yoda.
-Yoda?
-Mm-hmm.
No. The little green guy?
-Yeah.
-No.
[Cipher laughs]
Ah, shit, I'll take it.
Because he's
a powerful Jedi, right?
No.
Yoda's a puppet.
With someone's hand up his ass.
♪
[seagulls calling]
[rats squeaking]
[sighs]
[scoffs] So what now, Dom?
No one outruns their past.
And yours just caught up to you.
[heavy mechanical whirring]
Man.
There is
literally zero industrial
or weapons-grade electromagnets
I can find
that are this powerful.
Look at the pull strength
level here.
-It's crazy.
-Yeah. [scoffs]
[whispers]:
Wait, watch this.
[switch clicks]
[device powering up quietly]
[electricity whirring]
[Tej and Ramsey laughing]
[laughing]:
Every time. I can't believe it.
What are you doing, bruh?
I'm hungry.
-LETTY: Hey, guys.
-[sighs]: Oh, damn.
Surprise.
Nice clubhouse.
'Sup, man?
[Tej laughs]
Nice to meet you.
♪
So you got my postcard, huh?
[metal slides, clanks]
[sighs] I'm just still
trying to figure out...
How are you still alive?
Well, after Gisele died...
I didn't know what to do.
I was aimless.
-Lost.
-ROMAN: Absolutely.
But can you get
to the part where
the car exploded
and you're still alive?
-Like, I'm trying to...
-Roman, can you...
can you just be quiet
for one minute?
We made plans.
We had dreams.
So what's our next adventure
after this?
How about...
we stay in one place?
-Where you thinking?
-Tokyo.
We always talk about Tokyo.
Tokyo it is.
HAN: You know, it's funny,
Gisele led me there,
and I wasn't even
looking for it.
But it became home.
Then one day,
Mr. Nobody came calling.
MR. NOBODY:
I worked with Gisele.
Back when I was a CIA operative
running the drug trade
in Central America.
The good old days.
Gisele was my best.
You can lose an asset
at any time.
Bullet, knife, wire.
But I never thought
I'd lose her...
to love.
[sighs]
What do you want?
I'm offering you a job, Han.
Here, in Tokyo.
Why me?
'Cause I saw your work
with Gisele.
I saw that she trusted you.
And that means I can trust you.
And that is very rare
in this line of work.
[crunching]
HAN: And all I knew
was that I had to steal
some tech from the home
of a scientist couple.
But as usual...
Mr. Nobody didn't
tell me everything.
In fact, he left out
the most important part.
I was 11.
My parents would take me
to the movies on Saturdays
if I tried hard in school
during the week.
I was so excited to go
I forgot my raincoat,
so I went back in.
[thunder rumbling softly]
At first, I didn't see it.
By the time
I looked out the window...
Mom and Dad were gone.
HAN: Turns out
I wasn't the only one
-looking for this thing.
-[explosion booms]
♪
[clattering]
[men chattering
in foreign language]
[Elle crying softly]
[men chattering]
-[gunfire]
-[men grunting]
HAN:
Get down!
[Han groans]
ELLE:
Han saved me.
Wouldn't leave me behind.
He knew I'd always be a target,
so he taught me how to survive.
We became a family.
"Always be a target"?
Why?
DOM:
'Cause she is the key.
Everybody's been looking
for a thing.
It was a person all along.
ELLE:
My parents didn't want
Project Aries to fall
into the wrong hands,
so they locked it with their
own DNA, something we share.
And then, one day,
Mr. Nobody gave me the heads-up
that one of his best agents
went rogue.
So when Deckard Shaw
came calling,
we used it as cover.
But you got killed
in a car crash, Han.
Mr. Nobody had a way
of making things look real.
[people screaming]
Pretty nifty magic trick.
Yeah, I've done better.
Now for the hard part.
[device beeps]
Keeping you dead.
[siren wailing in distance]
My death...
Became the best way
to stay alive.
[alarm buzzing]
-What's happening?
-It's some kind of
hidden subroutine
the system follows.
[urgent chatter]
[guns racking]
OTTO:
That's it, right there.
Yeah, nobody moves...
everybody lives.
Jakob.
I'm sorry, Mia.
I was the rogue agent.
Me.
Dom, you ever think about
how Mr. Nobody found you?
Think he just dropped
out of the sky and chose you?
I ran missions with Mr. Nobody
out of this place for years.
[sighs]
I've been looking for that key
for a long time, Dom.
And you just handed her over.
I told you.
This is my world.
-Got it.
-[Jakob sighs]
Got a lot of guys here.
You trust 'em?
Trust this.
You know the only good thing
to come from Dad dying?
If he hadn't, I'd have spent
my entire life in your shadow.
And now you're gonna spend the
rest of yours living in mine.
DOM: Only good thing
about Dad dying...
was he didn't have to watch
what you became.
You never deserved
the Toretto name.
You think you knew Dad, huh?
What, 'cause you were his
favorite? You don't know shit!
Okay?
You want the truth?
Dad died 'cause he was trying
to throw that race.
We were in deep debt.
'Cause of how he felt about you,
he had to ask me for help.
How was I supposed to know
that car was gonna blow?
A good son would've said no.
And a real brother
would've come to me.
Come to you?
He made me promise
you would never find out.
And through all of it...
...I kept that promise.
[guns racking]
The girl comes with me.
Jakob!
I will stop you.
And that's my promise.
Hey!
-Sue. Sue. Ah.
-[Elle and man grunting]
Come on. Come on.
[Elle panting]
♪
[door closes]
-[electricity whirring]
-Down!
[men shouting]
[gas hissing]
[groaning, coughing]
Go! Go!
Come on!
This way!
[shouting in foreign language]
[shouting continues]
I'm always here.
Tell him.
LETTY:
No...!
-[grunting]
-LETTY: No!
[screams]
[grunting continues]
[Dom yells]
[Dom groans]
[grunts]
[panting, grunting]
[screams, grunts]
[yells]
No!
♪
JACK:
Dom.
Tell me what you see, son.
See, cars like this
are immortal.
'70 Chargers are
designed so well
that if you take care of 'em,
they'll run for 100 years.
Immortal?
Just like a family, Dom.
Build it right,
you take care of it...
...it'll live beyond you.
LITTLE BRIAN:
Daddy.
Little B.
When are you coming home?
Com...
♪
No. You know I'm good for it.
I promise I'll deliver.
♪
[engines roaring]
[crowd cheering]
♪
JACK: I'm telling you,
I got intermittent miss.
-Last two laps.
-BUDDY: On it!
Get those plug wires!
Jakob! Now.
♪
[grunts]
[hood closes]
-[taps hood]
-You're good!
[crowd cheering]
[engines roaring]
[crowd and engines fade]
No!
♪
[gasps softly]
[groaning]
You came to me, Letty.
None of it is worth a thing
if I lose you.
[voice breaks]:
Do you hear me?
Is this who we are?
[chuckles]
[whispers]:
Yeah.
[Letty sighs]
RAMSEY:
From here, things move quickly.
Jakob has all the pieces
he needs.
Once he activates Aries,
all he needs to do is
send the signal global.
And then there's
no stopping him, ever.
RAMSEY: He'll have to launch
some kind of pirate satellite,
something that'll act
as an amplifier,
infecting other satellites
in orbit one by one.
So we find him, stop him,
and then we get Elle back.
Our odds are zero here, Han.
Satellite equipment is
easy enough to track,
but we're not gonna
beat Jakob to a launch.
RAMSEY: Which gives us
a two-target problem:
Jakob on the ground...
With his own private army.
-And the satellite.
-RAMSEY: Which can't be hacked.
Not remotely.
We'd have to do it physically,
50 miles above ground while
the satellite is in orbit.
Orbit?
We need help.
Otherwise, we have no chance.
DOM:
We do it ourselves.
It's where we've been
that got us this far.
No. No, no, no, no, no.
Do y'all not understand?
Clearly, y'all don't.
Because if you did,
you'd be pissing your pants
like a normal person.
Orbit.
That's outer space.
That's another level.
What we gonna do?
Hijack a space shuttle?
Put rockets on our backs?
That's exactly
what we're gonna do.
What?
♪
[woman speaking
foreign language over P.A.]
[explosive rumbling]
There goes my father's
diplomatic ties
with Eastern Europe.
This place is
going to be crawling
with every cop in the city.
Time to get the hell
out of here.
[beep, electrical humming]
[electrical whirring]
Keep her close.
[electrical whirring, crackling]
It's activated.
[chuckles]
As soon as the satellite
reaches orbit,
we start the uplink.
[rap music playing quietly
over speakers]
Ah, damn.
What?
You see that?
We can't have
an air leak, man. [scoffs]
Are you really patching
yourself up with duct tape?
Yes.
I don't know
if you noticed or not,
but this whole operation is
Band-Aids and duct tape.
Man, this is insane.
-We are headed to outer space.
-[jet engine whooshing]
You acting like
we on our way to Home Depot.
This is ridiculous, man.
I'm about to abort
this whole mission
and take my Black ass home.
We're literally gonna be
in a perpetual freefall.
Freefall?
What does that even mean?
Roman, it means
numbers don't lie.
As long as we obey
the laws of physics,
then we'll be fine, okay?
It's just all math and science.
I knew I should've listened
to my teachers.
SEAN [over radio]:
Four minutes to launch.
You fellas good to go?
Yeah, we just up here putting
a bunch of duct tape on shit.
You know, that's what Tej do.
Man, please hurry up so I can
stop hearing his damn mouth.
-Yes, we're good to go.
-We're not good.
This is the same car
that we watched
do a test run and explode.
-This is not smart, Tej.
-EARL: Don't worry, man.
With my ceramic polymer coating,
you're gonna be just fine.
You're 100% fireproof.
Exactly.
SEAN:
All eight thrusters
fully functional.
Hey, please don't tell me
you're still running
launch simulations.
Virgin Galactic launched
at 36,000 feet.
The space shuttle tests
around 50,000 feet.
Our last test run
with this load means
we'll have to go higher--
way higher!
If we don't get them
high enough,
these guys are gonna be
pancakes at IHOP
before the coffee
even gets to the table.
TEJ:
Hey!
We can still hear you!
Don't worry, guys. We got this.
We do got this, right?
♪
[tires squealing]
-[engines roaring]
-[tires squealing]
I've run thermal imaging.
Elle's in the armory truck.
And I've got a lock
on the Aries signal.
It's coming from
the beast up ahead.
We need to get in there
to deactivate it
by the time Roman and Tej
are in position.
Ramsey, power us up.
[electromagnet powering up]
Satellite is in low orbit.
Begin.
[beeping]
♪
EARL: All right,
we're passing 50,000 feet!
Time to get ready, boys.
ROMAN:
What we supposed to be doing
with these old-ass suits
that ain't been used
since World War I?
TEJ:
Oh, I'm sorry.
Astronauts "R" Us was closed
for shopping today.
Listen, these suits are
just like space suits.
They both account
for pressure differential.
Only thing is we may
blow up like balloons
just a little bit.
-That's the only difference.
-What?
SEAN: We just hit
the launch altitude.
-You guys ready for
a five count? -ROMAN: No, man!
I'm barely ready to go scuba
diving in this old-ass thing.
Don't listen to him. We ready!
-"We"?
-Yes, I said "we"!
I thought you was invincible.
Let's see how invincible
your Black ass is after this.
-Punch it!
-No! Tej!
Oh, my God!
I don't want to die!
EARL:
Ignition!
♪
-[panting]
-[rumbling quiets]
♪
Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
[Roman chuckles]
We're in outer space!
Told you numbers don't lie.
This is crazy, bro!
Man, how much candy did you eat?
Well, I-I... I eat candy
when I get nervous.
♪
[alarm beeping]
I thought you said
you took care of this.
Yeah. Hey.
You take them back to the
freaking junkyard right now!
[rapid gunfire]
[horn honks]
[electricity whirring]
[gasps]
[people screaming]
[man shouts]
[horn honks]
[gunfire continues]
[tires squealing]
All right, Han, Mia, you're up!
Now.
[grunts]
Letty.
[grunting]
Han!
[tires squealing]
-[Elle shouts]
-[man groans]
[screams]
[grunts]
[groans]
Not all of us.
[screaming]
[doors close]
Now, the satellite we looking
for should be somewhere...
There.
Right there. You see it?
Got it.
Tell me you know
how to work the thrusters.
Tej, numbers is
what you do, right?
Driving is what I do.
Two dudes from the ghetto--
outer space.
You know ain't nobody
gonna believe us, right?
You're right.
♪
Something's wrong with
the satellite array.
It's, uh, interfering
with the uplink.
I'll handle it.
[tires squealing]
Han?
Grab the wheel.
Something's up.
-[grunts]
-[screen beeping]
I think I can link
into their feed.
-Something you want to
tell me, Otto? -OTTO: My bad.
Satellite uplink is
actually going splendid.
Oh, and by the way,
I have a new business partner.
Maybe you know her.
Guess who's
out of the box, Jakob.
But I did try to warn you.
You were never my competition.
-Otto, there's something
you should know. -Yeah, go on.
-Lay it on me, dude.
-You're a spoiled rich prick,
-and I'm gonna kill you.
-Oh, man, I am so sorry.
No one told you, huh?
Spoiled rich pricks
run the world.
[grunting]
♪
[tires squealing]
[both grunting]
Come on. Come on!
[grunting]
Go.
♪
[panting]
[tires squealing]
[alarm beeping]
-What's happening?
-OTTO: Uh, well,
we appear to have lost
our escort and Jakob.
And, well, Dom is making things
a little bit difficult here,
but it's fine.
Really, it's peachy.
Don't worry, don't worry.
I'll finish this myself.
All right, let's see
what that beast is made of.
You ready, Elle?
[grunts]
[tires squealing]
Crank it.
If we can't break through,
we stop it.
[sirens wailing]
Guys, that thing is
not slowing down
and the download's almost done.
Dom, we don't get
out of here now, we're dead.
Letty, drop back and line up
with the front tires.
What?
If we can't slow it
and we can't punch through,
we flip it
and we hit the underside.
Goddamn it!
Why do I have to say this?
Flatten these clowns!
[horn blares]
[rapid gunfire]
-Letty, the wires.
-You read my mind.
Han, get in front of me.
Dom, I can't get to you.
JAKOB:
But I can.
♪
[sirens wailing]
[grunting]
[grunts]
♪
All right,
the satellite is in range.
Let's power up these magnets
and fry it.
All right, take our time.
[electromagnet powering up]
[humming]
Okay. All right.
[powering down]
-Tej!
-Hold on. Come on, baby.
Power up. Power up.
[humming]
[powering down]
-Shit.
-[switches clicking]
-Shit, shit, shit.
-What?
Talk to me. What's going on?
The pressure of the launch--
it must have jammed the cables
to the power source.
Damn it, how did I
not think of that?
RAMSEY:
Guys, where are you?
The upload is almost complete.
Why don't you just kill it?
Let's smash it.
Let's run it over, right?
No. If we crash into that
satellite, we'll probably die.
And even if we don't,
the fuel that it would take
to smash it--
we'd be stuck out here forever.
You got to have faith, bro.
Faith? Faith is not numbers.
You know what, Tej?
You're probably right.
♪
We're not invincible.
We probably just been lucky
this whole time.
This might be it.
But you know what?
If we're gonna go out...
...let's go out
on top of the world.
RAMSEY: Guys,
what's happening up there?
We've got seconds left.
Let's do it.
Let's go.
Five, four, three,
two, one.
[computer beeping]
[alarm beeping]
[sighs]
We did it.
-[grunts]
-We did it!
Let's go.
Yes! [laughs]
-[Tej laughs]
-Shit.
Not bad, man.
Not bad at all.
-Hold on!
-[engine revving]
Dom!
[jet whooshing]
[tires squealing]
[beeping]
[device beeps]
[humming]
[grunts]
[tires squealing]
Yes! [laughs]
[scoffs]
Got to be kidding me.
-[tires squealing]
-[grunts]
-Shit!
[beeping]
♪
-[tires screech softly]
-[engine revs]
♪
Think these belong to you.
There's gonna be a lot of
people coming after you, Jake.
Yeah.
This is the world I chose, Dom.
You know, Dad wasn't perfect.
And he loved us all the same.
Someone once gave me
a ten-second car...
as a second chance.
I owe you that, little brother.
♪
I lost you once.
Don't let that
happen again, okay?
[door opens, closes]
[engine starts]
♪
-[Roman grunts]
-We come in peace!
Hey!
♪ Pasa el tiempo
♪ Y yo sigo aquí
♪ Un hermano no se traiciona
♪ La familia nunca abandona
♪ Pasa el tiempo
♪ Y yo sigo aquí
♪ Un hermano no se traiciona
♪ La familia nunca abandona...
This was the last place
I saw your grandfather.
This is where he raced.
Did you race here, too, Daddy?
No.
But I'll tell you something.
Everything I needed
to know about life,
I learned on this track.
You did?
I did.
♪ Pasa el tiempo
♪ Y yo sigo aquí
♪ Un hermano no se traiciona
♪ La familia nunca abandona.
[song fades]
♪
[sirens wailing in distance]
It's all gonna be okay, Jakob.
We got some rough times ahead...
...but it's gonna be okay.
'Cause we're family.
[sirens approaching]
-[tires screeching]
-[Jakob panting]
[car doors opening and closing]
[indistinct
police radio chatter]
["Rápido" by Amenazzy, Farruko,
Myke Towers & Rochy RD playing]
♪ Tu me acelera, me acelera
♪ Oh-eh, oh-we-eh♪
♪ Maneja me a tu manera
y haz lo rápido... ♪
-Fellas.
-Hey.
[chuckles]
♪ Conduce me adonde quieras,
pero rápido... ♪
EARL:
What?
No way.
[Han and Earl laughing]
TWINKIE [laughs]:
What's going on?
I couldn't believe it
when I heard you were alive.
It's a long story.
But for now, let's just
enjoy the moment, huh?
Guys, this is Elle.
-[Elle chuckles]
-Hey, Elle. I'm Sean.
-[food sizzling]
-TWINKIE: Just call me T.
-EARL: I'm Earl.
-ELLE: Nice to meet you.
Mia.
Hi. Nice to finally meet you.
[laughs]
-Hey, guys. [sighs]
-Mm. -Hey.
How much longer on this food?
Like, I'm-I'm...
I'm ready to eat now.
I've been eating space food
for weeks.
Oh. So Tootsie Rolls
are space food?
'Cause that's all you ate.
It was fat free, bruh.
TEJ: Snickers and Twix
fat free, too?
-ROMAN: My forehead hungry.
-Yeah, okay.
-I'll see you later. -TEJ:
Y-Your forehead is overweight.
[making whooshing sounds]
LETTY:
Oh! [laughs]
You drive just like your dad.
-I do?
-Mm-hmm.
Do you know, this is...
this is where I met your mom
for the first time.
Right there.
She's watching over you
from heaven.
-She is?
-Mm-hmm.
I think Daddy has
a question for you.
You ready to say grace, kid?
But I don't know what to say.
DOM:
Oh, it's easy.
Just say whatever's
in your heart.
LETTY [whispers]:
You ready?
-Mm-hmm.
-Come on.
[grunts playfully]
[chuckles]
[quiet chatter]
Hey, guys.
OTHERS:
Hey.
Little Brian's ready
to say grace with us.
-Uh-huh. -Nice.
-[chuckling]
Now, hold on.
There's still an empty chair.
He's on the way.
[engine roaring in distance]
[car approaching]
♪
[tires squealing]
[engine revving]
[cars zooming]
["Fast Lane" by Don Toliver,
Lil Durk and Latto playing]
♪ Get rich
♪ Yeah, ay, ay, ay, ay, ay
♪ Moving how I'm speeding
through the fast lane ♪
♪ They say I know magic
how my whips change ♪
♪ They don't see what I see
♪ Go against the game,
you know it's pass me ♪
♪ Zero to hundred,
you know I'm on-on go ♪
♪ Play with my dogs, you know
I'm on-on go ♪
♪ Bottles on bottles,
you know I'm on-on go ♪
♪ Moving too fast, you know
we on-on go ♪
♪ I hit the switch
and make the wheels go up ♪
♪ If I got to make the call
♪ You made
the wrong-wrong choice ♪
♪ I roll it up,
you know I'm on-on go ♪
♪ Moving too fast, you know
I'm on-on go ♪
♪ Fast lane, bet I push
a hundred in two seconds ♪
♪ I just spent a Bentley
and a Lambo on two necklaces ♪
♪ Take 'em on a high speed,
I'm too reckless ♪
♪ Demon time when I'm in that
Demon, they can't catch it ♪
♪ Bet they get the message,
I'm the best of the bestest ♪
♪ And I'm still waiting
for a bitch to check it ♪
♪ Who want the smoke?
Better hope you don't choke ♪
♪ I be riding two-seater,
it just me and the scope ♪
♪ I like my gangster with
a mouth full of golds, uh ♪
♪ He hit the lotto,
that's goals ♪
♪ Moving how I'm speeding
through the fast lane ♪
♪ They say I know magic
how my whips change ♪
♪ They don't see what I see
♪ Go against the game,
you know it's pass me ♪
♪ Zero to hundred,
you know I'm on-on go ♪
♪ Play with my dogs, you know
I'm on-on go ♪
♪ Bottles on bottles,
you know I'm on-on go ♪
♪ Moving too fast, you know
we on-on go ♪
♪ High speed, the cars and me,
you know mine cost ten of 'em ♪
♪ All the scammers calling me
with cars, I need ten of them ♪
♪ Have these ... flexing
with these cars ♪
♪ Knowing they rented them
♪ I could put some rappers
all on blast ♪
♪ But ain't gon' mention them
♪ I hit the switch
and make the wheels go up ♪
♪ If I got to make the call
♪ You made
the wrong-wrong choice ♪
♪ I roll it up,
you know I'm on-on go ♪
♪ Moving too fast, you know
I'm on-on go. ♪
[cars zooming]
-[gloves striking punching bag]
-[man grunting]
♪
[sniffs]
-[sighs]
-[man sobbing]
[gasping]
Thank you.
Please.
I tell you where the drive is,
the plans we stole.
I tell you where it is.
You mean this drive?
These plans?
[chuckles]:
But you already got it.
Yes, mate.
How else do you think
I stay in this good of shape?
[knocking on door]
Don't go anywhere.
[man shouts]
["Lane Switcha" by
Pop Smoke and Skepta playing]
♪ I'm a lane switcher
♪ Big tank, bank filler
♪ Real killer,
die for my gang member ♪
♪ Gun driller,
dope man dope dealer ♪
♪ Gorilla, bang, bang,
lane switcher ♪
♪ Foot on the gas,
yeah, I'm lane switching ♪
♪ I could not show them
where I'm at ♪
♪ 'Cause they stay snitching
♪ I get my killer
the green light ♪
♪ Yeah, I okay the killings
♪ I take the corner,
window down ♪
♪ You see the chain swinging
♪ 400,000 on a jet,
200,000 on my left ♪
♪ Richard Mille on my wrist
and it's icy with baguettes ♪
♪ Look, it's me,
Rocky and Skep ♪
♪ Niggas better put respect
on my name ♪
♪ Nigga reach for my chain,
let it bang ♪
♪ I'm a lane switcher
♪ Big tank, bank filler
♪ Real killer,
die for my gang member ♪
♪ Gun driller,
dope man dope dealer ♪
♪ Gorilla, bang, bang,
lane switcher ♪
♪ I know you sicker
than "Sicka" ♪
♪ When you see the big picture
♪ Lane switcher,
put your sister in a twister ♪
♪ Lane switcher, paint dripper,
drink sipper ♪
♪ Cap peeler, blaow,
make you back Flippa ♪
♪ Ain't no man in the middle
♪ Hit the gas on this V-12,
it's sounding like a gorilla ♪
♪ Drinking like
I hate my liver ♪
♪ Smoking these niggas
like Swishers ♪
♪ I'm just a product
of Memphis ♪
♪ Run up a sack and I flip it
♪ She wanna get
with this pimpin' ♪
♪ But it ain't that simple
♪ I'm a lane switcher
♪ Big tank, bank filler
♪ Real killer,
die for my gang member ♪
♪ Gun driller,
dope man dope dealer ♪
♪ Gorilla, bang, bang,
lane switcher. ♪
["Hit 'Em Hard" playing]
♪ I got that heat,
coming in hard ♪
♪ Pull out the flame,
ready to spark ♪
♪ Turn up the beat,
tear it apart ♪
♪ Tear off the leash,
I'm in the yard ♪
♪ I hit 'em hard, I hit 'em
hard, I hit 'em hard ♪
♪ I hit 'em hard
♪ Ready to eat,
never gon' starve ♪
♪ Run with the beasts,
swim with the sharks ♪
♪ I'm-a get mine,
put it on God ♪
♪ Ice like the cross,
now who the boss? ♪
♪ Lamborghini with
a hundred in it ♪
♪ Ride on 'em
in the drop Bentley ♪
♪ Get the money
on a money mission ♪
♪ Had to focus,
keep a tunnel vision ♪
♪ No mercy, I'm not even
playing with 'em ♪
♪ Knock 'em off,
I had my man hit 'em ♪
♪ I made me some bands
with 'em ♪
♪ My diamond, they like
to go dance with 'em ♪
♪ No talking 'bout jogging,
we running the city ♪
♪ Opposition now
under submission ♪
♪ You moving your tongue like
you're coming against me ♪
♪ You hurt, in your feelings,
convertible ceilings ♪
♪ One push of a button,
you coming up missing ♪
♪ Count it up, tuck it,
take nothing offensive ♪
♪ Touching them M's,
what I love turned against me ♪
♪ Left me no choice
but the run it up issue ♪
♪ I hit 'em hard, I hit 'em
hard, I hit 'em hard ♪
♪ I hit 'em hard
♪ Ready to eat,
never gon' starve ♪
♪ Run with the beasts,
swim with the sharks ♪
♪ I'm-a get mine,
put it on God ♪
♪ Ice like the cross,
now who the boss? ♪
♪ I hit 'em hard, I hit 'em
hard, I hit 'em hard ♪
♪ I hit 'em hard
♪ I got that heat,
coming in hard ♪
♪ Pull out the flame,
ready to spark ♪
♪ Turn up the beat,
tear it apart ♪
♪ Tear off the leash, I'm in
the yard, I hit 'em hard ♪
♪ I'm in the dark,
diamond they dancing ♪
♪ They hitting real hard
♪ In the push start
♪ Running my engine
in the back of the car ♪
♪ I took off the chip
and I'm pushing my limits ♪
♪ I'm going real fast,
I'm going real far ♪
♪ I told her don't ... with
the bosses and business ♪
♪ I stay in my bag,
I know I'm a star ♪
♪ I stay with
them crash dummies ♪
♪ We don't give a ...,
we hitting 'em hard ♪
♪ And I'm using my brain 100%,
I don't need a charge ♪
♪ Used to play
on the handlebars ♪
♪ Now we handling firearms
♪ Just lend me the gas
and I'll do the dash ♪
♪ I'll puff, puff and pass,
can't think 'bout the past ♪
♪ I hit 'em hard.
["De Museo"
by Bad Bunny playing]
♪ Pasa el tiempo
♪ Y yo sigo aquí
♪ Un hermano no se traiciona
♪ La familia nunca abandona
♪ Pasa el tiempo
♪ Y yo sigo aquí
♪ Un hermano no se traiciona
♪ La familia nunca abandona
♪ Y yo no he cambiado
♪ Por más dinero,
por una mujer ♪
♪ Que la envidia no vive
con nosotros se muere ♪
♪ Y yo no he cambiado
♪ Por más dinero,
por una mujer ♪
♪ Que la envidia no vive
con nosotros se muere ♪
♪ La calle está que pela
♪ Siempre andamos en el ocio
♪ La máquina de museo
♪ La paseo porque
♪ La calle está que pela
♪ Nos cuidamos de lo feo
♪ Por de calle lo fronteo
♪ Aquí no lo veo
♪ Tu di se que le metes cabrón
♪ Ya vi porque eres un mamón
♪ Tu no sales conmigo
ni me pelas el día ♪
-♪ No, no♪
-♪ Gol
♪ Y ni me pegó
para la portería ♪
♪ La calle está que pela
♪ Siempre andamos en el ocio
♪ La máquina de museo
♪ La paseo porque
♪ La calle está que pela
♪ Nos cuidamos de lo feo
♪ Por de calle lo fronteo
♪ Aquí no lo veo.
[song ends]
♪
[music fades]