Someone needs to stop Clearway Law.
Public shouldn't leave reviews for lawyers.
BOY: Ever since I was three,
I wanted to play quarterback
for the New York Giants...
like my personal hero,
Eli Manning.
Annual salary is between 10
and 20 million dollars a year.
MR. KENNY: Thank you.
Next up... Reed.
Mr. Richards?
Earth to Richards.
(SIMULATES STATIC)
Beam me up, Scotty.
(KIDS GIGGLING)
MR. KENNY:
Okay, come on, guys.
Oh, I'm sorry.
When I grow up...
I want to be the first person
in human history
to teleport himself.
(KIDS LAUGHING)
(CLEARS THROAT)
I'm sorry, what?
It's already possible to transport
quantum information
from one location to another.
Right now,
there are supercomputers
that can transport
Quantum information
through space.
So why not a machine that can
send people through space?
Well, even if you could build
the thing, which you can't...
I've already built it.
Well, I'm building it.
In my garage.
Is it next to
your flying car?
(LAUGHING)
I'm not working
on that anymore.
Just this now.
I call it a "Biomatter Shuttle."
"Biomatter..."?
Technically, I'm shuttling matter
from one place to another.
Well, first matter.
But once I test
on biological
materials, I can...
All right, look...
Thank you, Mr. Richards.
This is all very interesting
but the assignment
was to pick a real career
in the real world.
Redo the report, and I'll
let you try again tomorrow.
(SCATTERED LAUGHTER)
Ben?
(MEN TALKING INDISTINCTLY)
(DOG BARKING)
JIMMY: Anyway, I tell him...
"Bro, I ain't looking
at your girl.
"Girl's looking at me.
"What you want me
to do about it?"
Know what I'm saying?
Hey, where you going?
I got homework.
What?
Look at that fridge pile.
(SOFTLY) Idiot.
What'd you say?
Hey! Clobbering time.
(GROANS)
What'd you think?
Think you can
talk to me like that, huh?
You think you can
talk to me like that, punk?
BEN'S MOTHER: What the hell
is the matter with you?
Shh! Huh? Huh?
Ma!
I didn't do nothing!
Huh? Huh?
Ma, I swear to God!
You didn't do nothing?
(DOGS BARKING)
Go check on that fuss.
You didn't do nothing?
I watched you!
What's the matter with you?
How many times do I have to tell you,
you don't hit a kid!
(SHOUTING CONTINUES)
(DOGS CONTINUE BARKING)
Hey!
(WHINING)
Hello?
Who's in there?
Please don't kill me.
Take that off.
I know you. From school.
I'm just looking
for a power converter.
I'm building something.
BEN'S MOTHER: Ben!
What's going on out there?
Hold on!
That teleporting thing?
I can show it to you.
I just need the converter.
All right.
MR. RICHARDS: Come on,
throw him the ball!
MR. RICHARDS: Throw
the ball, throw the ball!
(INDISTINCT TV CHATTER)
Come on, he's open!
Throw the ball!
(LOCK CLICKS)
MR. RICHARDS: That's what
I'm talking about. Yeah!
Is that it?
Yeah.
Help.
(GRUNTS)
(ELECTRICITY BUZZING)
Here you go.
REED: Your family
owns a junkyard?
BEN: Mmm-hmm.
REED: That place is awesome.
Here.
You're stripping the head.
So, uh, who else lives here?
Just my mom and step-dad.
They don't care about all this?
They don't understand it.
You might want to
cover your ears.
Stand back a little.
What the hell?
Damn it.
It's all right.
All right, come on.
Don't blow up.
Come on, man! Guy's open!
(RATTLING)
Whoa!
Reed! What did you do?
(BEEPING RAPIDLY)
Now!
(GROANS)
(MACHINE POWERING DOWN)
MR. RICHARDS: Reed!
BEN: Did it work?
MR. RICHARDS: (SHOUTING)
Hey, Reed!
BEN: Where'd
the rocks come from?
REED: From the same place
the car went to.
Where is that?
I don't know yet.
Reed?
What?
You're insane.
Thanks.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
MR. KENNY: Mr. Richards.
Shall I alert
the fire department?
(CHUCKLES)
What is this?
Uh, this is a
Cymatic Matter Shuttle.
Me and my associate Ben
have been working on it
every day since 5th grade
when we launched the beta
version in my garage.
And today is our first
public demonstration.
What does it do?
It modulates
the frequency of matter
from one location
to another and back again.
It's a teleporter.
A teleporter.
Model car, please?
The model...
The model car, please, Ben.
I don't have the model car.
Why don't you have
the model car?
I brought everything else.
I specifically...
But... Mr. Richards?
Okay, I will use
this model plane.
Hey, I just need to
use this for one second.
But I'll give it back,
I promise. Thanks.
Here we go.
Ben? Please?
You may want to
cover your ears.
(MACHINE POWERING UP)
(PEOPLE GASPING)
Great. Now, Ben,
bring it on back.
Yeah.
Oh, keep 'em covered.
BEN: (MUTTERS) Oh, come on.
No. Come on, come on.
Don't do this.
(LOW FREQUENCY EXPLOSION)
(FREQUENCY RESONATING)
(SPECTATORS GASP)
Oh, okay.
Now if I can have
your attention, please.
What you're looking at is sand,
presumably from
the Gansu Desert in China.
Or perhaps even from the Sahara.
You're disqualified.
We're not entirely sure
where it's from...
Mr. Richards,
you're disqualified.
Wait, what?
This is a science fair,
not a magic competition.
I don't see
any real science here.
And you're paying
for the backboard.
Did you put it on 6 or 8?
BEN: Everything was the same.
REED: I know,
but you're smashing the buttons.
It's delicate.
You can't smash it.
Hey, kid, I'm really
sorry about your plane.
You're a dick.
(SCATTERED LAUGHTER)
You cranked it up too high.
I didn't crank it up
too high.
It was on the same
setting as last time.
I know,
but it's very precise.
Excuse me, guys?
Just pack it up.
Yeah?
Did you really build this
in your garage?
Mmm-hmm.
DR. STORM: Now,
this is elegant.
What are these?
REED: Uh, Sonic projectors,
using cymatics
to modulate the field.
That's why we can't
bring the matter back
from the other dimension.
Uh... What?
We've gone so far as to send
matter to another dimension
but we haven't been able
to maintain a field
long enough
to bring that matter back.
You just did.
(CHUCKLES)
Oh, you're serious.
I think you've cracked
inter-dimensional travel.
I mean, we're not sending
anything to another dimension.
We sent something,
we think,
to another part
of the planet
but I don't know about
another dimension.
We found the same
thing you did.
We've had it
analyzed repeatedly,
but no one's ever
seen anything like it.
Oh, wow.
I'm sorry. We're from
the Baxter Foundation.
This is my daughter, Sue.
Hi.
DR. STORM: We'd like to
give you a full scholarship.
Uh, where did you say
you were from again?
Hey. You could fit the whole
neighborhood in there.
SECURITY GUARD:
What's your name?
Uh, Reed.
Richards.
Yes, of course.
We've been expecting you.
They actually
wear lab coats here.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
This is you, sir.
BEN: Here.
What?
(PAPER RUSTLING)
What is this?
It's a going-away present.
I'm not going away.
I'm, like, a 40-minute
train ride from Oyster Bay.
Reed, look at this place.
You belong here.
I've been here two minutes
and I already know that.
I'm just going to school here.
It's where
I'm gonna be working.
It looks like
you're home, buddy.
(INDISTINCT ANNOUNCEMENTS OVER P.A.)
Hey.
This place is
pretty incredible.
They have molecular chem
books from the 1950s.
Oh, hey. Sorry,
did you say something?
Yeah, I was just asking,
what are you listening to?
Portishead.
Never heard of him.
"Them."
I'll have to check them out.
I love this book.
It's about this guy,
Captain Nemo.
He invents a submarine
that goes deeper
than anything in history.
Yeah, I know. I've read it.
So, you like music?
Is that kind of
like your thing?
Pattern recognition.
Pattern recognition?
Music is just a series
of altered patterns.
The musician creates the pattern
and makes us
anticipate a resolution...
...then holds back.
Makes you wait for it.
There's patterns in
everything and everyone.
Hmm.
What's mine?
You wanna be famous.
Your parents, teachers
all told you one thing,
one way to be,
and you ignored them.
And now I'm here.
So you are.
Am I that predictable?
Everybody is.
Well, you're wrong.
I don't wanna be famous.
I just want my work
to make a difference.
Well, here you are,
Captain Nemo.
Go for it.
Bye.
DR. ALLEN: Let me guess.
Some kid from the Internet.
DR. STORM: Science fair.
DR. ALLEN: Franklin,
this board has invested
a great deal
in your little orphanage.
We need real world applications.
This has real world
applications.
I truly believe
that there is an entire...
"An entirely new universe,
"just beyond
our ability to see."
Yes, I've read your paper.
Once we get there...
If we get there.
...we'll be able to
discover new resources.
Energy sources which
will revitalize our own.
This is our chance
to learn more
about our planet
and maybe even save it.
And I'm sure you all would
agree that even if...
Wait. What is this?
Victor Von Doom is on here.
He started this project
and devoted
a decade of his life to it.
He deserves to be in jail.
He deserves another chance.
He set fire to your
data servers before he left.
I'm going to personally
supervise him.
I need his talent.
I believe he and Reed
can finally get us there.
We want to support you,
Franklin,
but you put a lot
of faith in these kids.
I put all my faith in them.
(CLASSICAL MUSIC PLAYING)
(KNOCKING ON DOOR)
(DOOR WHIRRING OPEN)
So someone stole my design.
DR. STORM:
No one stole anything, Victor.
Someone else
figured out your idea...
and made it work.
That's what happens when
you drop out of the world.
Other people finish
what you started.
Well, if you came
to ask for help,
be better you didn't
insult both of us...
and turn back around.
Don't you wanna even
look at the designs?
I told you I'm done working
for you and your employers.
They're not my employers.
You can't do a thing
without their permission, yes?
Wake up. You're an employee.
They'll stay out of my way
this time. Trust me.
It's not you I don't trust.
Yeah.
(SIGHS) Well...
I hate to interfere with
all of your important work.
Guess we'll just have
to make history without you.
Is Sue gonna be there?
I trust her.
Yes, Victor, she'll be there.
(DOOR WHIRRING OPEN)
Clean yourself up, son.
(DOOR WHIRRING SHUT)
(BUZZING)
Holy shit.
(INDISTINCT ANNOUNCEMENTS OVER P.A.)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
Amazing.
Oh, thanks.
Amazing you didn't black out
the entire Western Hemisphere.
Hmm?
You basically ripped a hole
in the fabric of space-time
with unspec'd components
and no supervision.
Yeah, that was, uh,
an accident.
And if, by accident,
you upped the power...
you would have created
a runaway reaction
that opened a black hole...
and swallowed the entire planet.
Well, I'm glad
that didn't happen.
Are you helping on this?
I'm making
the environment suits.
Based on the soil samples
from our experiments...
anyone who goes
to the other dimension
is gonna need
to be protected.
REED: Who's that?
Victor.
Who's Victor?
He started this whole project.
Oh. Does he go here, too?
It's complicated.
Rudimentary.
(COMPUTER BEEPING)
Elementary.
This is basically
a child's drawing.
You know what
Albert Einstein said.
"If you can't explain it simply,
"you don't understand it
well enough."
Ten years searching
for something
that is basically runner-up
for a baking soda volcano.
We were actually disqualified.
The potato clock got second.
Reed Richards,
Victor Von Doom.
Victor started
the Quantum Gate project
when he was
younger than you.
Wow. It's great
to meet you.
Hi, Susan.
Hey, Victor.
Do you prefer "Susan"?
No.
It's been a while.
Didn't expect to
see you back here.
Yeah, well,
I couldn't resist.
When I heard about the design,
I needed to see it
with my own eyes.
I gotta say,
it's pretty impressive...
Thank you.
...that you nearly destroyed
our entire planet
with speaker cable
and aluminum foil.
Yeah, that was an accident.
He did get it to work.
What is this?
This is where your little,
uh, accident leads to.
SUE: We put a camera on
a drone we sent over there.
The drone didn't come back,
but those images did.
Wow. It's beautiful.
Yes, it is.
New energy, resources.
It's a whole new world.
Which can help save this one.
Not that it deserves
to be saved.
I mean, think about it.
The people running the Earth
are the same ones
running it into the ground.
So, maybe it deserves
what it's got coming to it.
Dr. Doom, over here.
The failures of my generation
are the opportunities for yours.
There are no greater minds
than the ones in this room.
Is he gonna give a speech?
He's gonna give a speech.
But you're gonna have to
all come together.
Each of you working together
with a level of commitment
and collaboration...
putting aside petty squabbles...
if you want to fix
what my generation broke.
If you can do that,
work together...
then you can change
the course of history.
That's a pretty good speech.
I'm in.
Me, too.
I'm here, right?
First, design.
We figure out what went wrong
and correct it.
Then we build, then we send
organic matter over there.
But, more importantly,
we bring it back.
VICTOR: And then...
most importantly,
they send us.
"Us"?
Us, us?
We're going over there?
Not unless you get to work.
So, get to work.
(CELL PHONE RINGING)
(RINGING CONTINUES)
DRIVER: Johnny Storm.
So that's the
piece of shit Toyota
you been talking about.
Why, yes, it is.
Now you promise me
we'll still be cool
after I dust your ass.
(ENGINE ROARING)
(ENGINE STALLS)
No. Come on.
(TIRES SCREECHING)
Rookie!
(KISSES)
Bye-bye.
(CHUCKLES)
Oh, shit.
(BRAKES SCREECHING)
(GRUNTING)
(GROANS)
DR. STORM: I cannot
believe you're out here
doing this nonsense again.
I told you.
What?
I told you I was doing 45
when I spun out.
Yeah. (SIGHS)
The ground was wet
and I hydroplaned.
Funny, I don't seem to
remember any rain today.
You were probably
too busy to notice.
Johnny, I thought you were
turning things around.
What is this?
What are you talking about?
This! This!
Is this the way you want
the rest of your life to be?
You keep acting out.
You have the potential and
the IQ to do so much more.
Oh, you mean like Sue?
I know you think you know
what's best for you,
but trust me, son,
you do not.
Can you stop that?
What? Stop what?
Stop talking to me
like I'm one of your students.
Well, you're not
getting the car back.
Excuse me?
You're not getting
the car back.
I built that thing
from scratch
with my own two hands.
With my money.
My money, my car.
You want it back,
you're gonna have to earn it.
You're gonna have to
come work for me.
I'm not wearing a lab coat.
JOHNNY: Appreciate
your work, miss.
Oh, you gotta
untuck that shirt, man.
Is that Adolf? Long time.
Still not German.
And we don't need any more help.
Yes, you do.
With what,
his boundless enthusiasm?
Oh, why, thank you, Victor.
He can build anything.
With a broken arm?
What exactly happened?
What?
Were you racing again?
I don't know what
you're talking about.
I could use some help, actually.
Oh, this guy
doesn't take orders well.
Yeah, especially from
people who say shit like,
"I don't take orders well."
What you need, buddy?
Oh, that's brilliant.
Hey.
What's up? Johnny.
Reed. Nice to meet you.
Have you welded before?
Of course.
(INAUDIBLE)
(INDISTINCT)
Keeps overheating.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER AND LAUGHTER)
Hey.
What's up?
I got to say,
it's fun having you here.
Mmm-hmm.
You kind of look like
you're in your element.
Look, don't get used to this.
I'm just here
to get my car back.
Right.
It's good seeing you too.
(SHUTTER CLICKS)
(MEN TALKING INDISTINCTLY)
(GASPING)
Sorry.
Oh, whoa!
Oh, my God.
Why would you do that?
Sorry. (CHUCKLES)
I freaked out.
Oh, my gosh. Sorry.
You were sort of sleeping.
Was I? Is that what that was?
It's okay if you need to
take a nap or something.
I'm good, thanks.
Uh, so, that must
have been cool
with Dr. Storm as your dad.
Yeah.
Did he adopt you?
Mmm-hmm.
Yeah, I know what that's like.
You were adopted?
No, I just wish that I was.
Why?
I don't know. We don't
really understand each other.
Mmm.
Where were you born?
Kosovo.
You don't have an accent.
(IN MOCK RUSSIAN ACCENT)
I don't?
(BOTH CHUCKLE)
Hey, Reed. Can I have a word?
Okay, yeah.
Hey.
You're being unprofessional.
You're supposed to be
down here, working.
Yeah, I am. That's
what we've been doing.
That's not what it looks like.
We're finished.
What?
Yeah, we finished it.
Do you want to see?
Yeah.
Hey, Sue.
Can you show him?
I'm really tired.
I'm gonna go take a nap.
Can you tell Dr. Storm
for me? We did it, Victor.
DR. STORM: Harvey.
DR. ALLEN: Franklin.
Big day.
Didn't think we'd make
it here, but well done.
I told you
these kids could do it.
(WHISPERING)
Harvey's here.
MAN ON PA:
Organic test commencing.
(CHATTERING)
Clear for launch.
Goggles up.
Ten...
nine...
eight...
seven...
six...
five...
four...
three...
two...
one.
(CHEERING AND APPLAUSE)
Standing by
for video acquisition.
Status unknown. Stand by.
Trying an alternate frequency.
We've got signal.
(CHUCKLES)
Look at the plates.
It's almost primordial.
Unformed, like Earth
over a billion years ago.
DR. STORM:
That place could explain
the origin of our species.
The evolution of our planet.
Answers to questions
we don't even know to ask yet.
BPS, body temp, ventilation
rates are all elevated.
Let's bring him back.
(CHATTERING)
MAN ON PA: Goggles up.
In five...
four...
three...
two...
one.
(SCATTERED CHEERING)
How is he?
The vitals are good.
They're really good.
He made it.
It's safe.
(LAUGHING)
JOHNNY: All right!
Looks like we're next.
Gentlemen. Everyone.
You all deserve
an enormous pat on the back.
I think it's time
to start coordinating
with our friends at NASA.
What?
It works. We have to start
thinking about sending men.
Yeah.
Us.
Look, I won't deny that
what you've created here
is incredible.
But this isn't the school
science fair anymore.
We have to
bring in help now.
Why just NASA?
Why not the Army or the CIA?
We could send
our political prisoners there.
Waterboarding
in the fourth dimension
could prove very effective.
Why don't we discussthe
details of this someplace else?
In the meantime...
we appreciate your service.
Oh. Hey, thank you.
I won't let this go,
I promise you.
SUE: Just give him a second
to figure this out.
Look, I don't know about you
guys, but I could use some...
(WHISTLES)
Want a drink?
Ethanol kills brain cells.
(GRUNTS SOFTLY)
VICTOR: You are a lightweight!
(LAUGHING)
REED: Looks like
we need another refill.
Here you go, Johnny.
Yep.
Yep. (SIGHS)
Hey, Vic.
You guys know who built
the Apollo spacecraft,
went to the moon?
Yeah. Your mama.
(ALL LAUGHING)
So, the answer's no.
But you know who
Neil Armstrong is, right?
Yeah, of course.
Of course.
VICTOR: Buzz Aldrin?
REED: Yeah.
First men to
walk on the moon.
Famous faces hired
to conquer dreams
that weren't even theirs.
Dreams that someone else,
some other scientist...
who probably died
penniless and alone...
and sat in a bar,
telling people
he sent men to the moon.
That's gonna be me.
Think it's all of us.
Unless we go first.
Why don't we go first?
God, this thing works, okay?
We can go up there,
take five minutes.
We can take a flag
and plant it down,
get our footprints down there.
We're gonna be the first
people over there. Okay?
Screw those guys!
My dad might
actually kill me this time.
Johnny, by the time
your dad finds out,
we'll already be back.
Think about it.
Just the three of us?
(CELL PHONE VIBRATING)
Hello?
I'm not going without you.
What time is it?
Look, we started
this thing together,
we're going together.
I'm not taking no
for an answer, okay?
Forget Neil Armstrong!
Come on.
Neil Armstrong?
You drunk?
Yeah, I am a little drunk.
It doesn't matter!
Look, the machine works.
The machine works, Ben,
and I need you
to come with me.
Now?
Yeah. Look, Ben...
I need you to come
because we're going tonight.
I told the guys that
I'm not going without you.
Okay? Who's gonna
have my back?
All right, fine.
(STAMMERS) Just give me
a second, all right?
Okay.
Please?
All right, buddy.
Thank you, thank you.
(DOOR OPENS)
REED: He's with me.
What's up, man?
What's up, buddy?
How you doing?
It's good to see you.
Thanks, Panno.
No problem, Mr. Richards.
Why are we
doing this tonight?
Huh?
Why are we
doing this tonight?
You trust me, right?
Ta-da!
It's just like ours,
but expensive.
(INDISTINCT)
Guys, this is Ben.
How you doing?
What's up?
Are you his lucky charm?
I'm sorry, this is Borat.
Borat's a dick.
Are you guys
sure you're in
the best shape
to be doing this?
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
We're good.
REED: Let's do this.
So, I guess I should
come up with
something better than
"One small step for man..."?
VICTOR: Strap in
and get comfy, kids.
We're about to make history.
BEN: Yeah, or die. Either/Or.
REED: Wow, that's great,
Ben. Thanks.
JOHNNY: All right, gentlemen.
Hands and feet must remain
inside the ride at all times.
(DOORS HISSING SHUT)
(ALARM BEEPING)
Oh, shit.
Dad, you need
to come to the lab.
AUTOMATED VOICE:
Remote launch initiated.
Ten...
Don't blow up.
Please, don't blow up.
Oh, yeah, that's
what I wanna hear
before going
into another dimension.
Yeah, don't worry.
He does that.
...five...
four...
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
three...
two...
one.
Initiate launch.
What happened? Did we abort?
Uh...
I don't think
that we went anywhere.
God damn it.
Johnny?
Guys, can you hear me?
Wow.
(THUNDER RUMBLING)
VICTOR: I made it.
REED: Ben, look at this place.
It's amazing.
We did it.
BEN: I think we did.
(EXHALES DEEPLY)
BEN: Here, give me a hand.
Give me a hand.
JOHNNY: Oh, yeah. This one is
definitely going on Instagram.
REED: Let's do this. Ready?
After three.
(BEN AND REED IN UNISON)
One, two, three!
JOHNNY: Whoa,
look at that. Whoa!
REED: Hey, Victor,
I think you should see this.
The energy seems to be
converging over there.
Come on.
Let's check it out.
All right. Let's do it quickly
so we can get out of here.
JOHNNY: (CHUCKLES)
Nope. Uh-uh.
I'm good.
BEN: Reed, what's he doing?
We need to climb down there
so we can get a better look.
Oh, you guys
go on without me.
VICTOR: Stay here.
We need an anchor.
(CHUCKLES) Yeah, yeah.
I'll be a great anchor.
(GRUNTING)
REED: Okay.
Easy does it.
Just a little further.
Right behind you.
Okay.
VICTOR: It's responding
to physical stimulus.
Almost like a nerve impulse.
I can feel it.
The energy, it's alive.
(METER WHIRRING)
REED: It's incredible.
There's no expenditure.
Reed.
What?
I think we should go back.
This is important, Ben.
Come take a look.
(SIGHS)
(ALL SCREAMING)
VICTOR: Go, go, go! Oh, shit!
(ALL PANTING)
BEN: (SHOUTING) Come on!
JOHNNY: Come on,
come on! Hurry up!
BEN: Come on, Reed!
Come on!
REED: Victor!
Reed!
Hold on!
Reed! Pull me up!
Victor!
Grab my hand!
Reed, pull me up!
Come on! Come on!
(SIZZLING)
(VICTOR SCREAMING)
Victor, hold on!
Reed!
I can't hold him!
Don't let go!
Help me!
Victor!
Victor! No!
(SCREAMING)
Reed, let's go! Come on!
Victor!
Come on!
We can't leave him!
Reed, we gotta go now!
Come on!
Come on, come on!
JOHNNY: Move, let's move!
BEN: Move your ass, Reed!
JOHNNY: Move it! Keep moving!
Oh, my God.
Let's go, let's go, let's go!
Reed, let's go!
Okay.
Reed, come on!
The re-entry's not working!
I don't know what to do!
BEN: Get us out of here!
BEN: (DISTORTED) Reed!
Do something! We gotta go!
Guys, can you hear me?
JOHNNY: Sue! Can you hear me?
Johnny!
Do you have any idea
how much trouble you're in?
Yes, yes, I do!
Sue, I need you to manually
override the re-entry, okay?
Okay, I got it.
Manually override
the re-entry!
I'm trying!
Sue, just do it!
Reed! The door!
I can't close the door!
Ben!
The door won't close!
(GRUNTING)
(SCREAMING)
(GROANS)
(PANTING)
(SHOUTS) Ben!
Ben!
(YELLS)
Johnny!
(GROANING)
(BEN SCREAMING)
BEN: Reed!
(WEAKLY) Ben.
BEN: Oh, God!
Ben!
Help me!
I'm coming!
BEN: Reed, help me!
Can't move!
Ben!
Where are you?
BEN: Reed?
Help me.
Ben.
Reed.
Ben!
Reed, help me. I can't move!
I'll get you out of there.
(GRUNTS)
Oh, my God. What the...? What?
(GASPING)
(MEN TALKING INDISTINCTLY)
MALE DOCTOR 1:
Can we get a BP reading?
MALE DOCTOR 2:
BP 128 over 72.
MALE DOCTOR 1: Bone density?
MALE DOCTOR 2: Bone density
rates are normal.
MALE DOCTOR 3: (OVER P A.)
Reed, can you move your hand?
Where's Ben?
Keep trying, Reed.
Hey, do you guys know
where my friends are?
Can you lift
your index finger?
(STAMMERING) I...
I'm trying.
(GROANS)
Where's Ben?
Did you see him?
He was covered in the rocks.
Why won't you answer me?
(SHOUTING)
Where are my friends?
Help me!
Increase sedative. 50 cc's.
REED: What have
you guys done to me?
So, just for the record...
this program was under your supervision,
was it not?
I already told you it was,
but I wasn't there
when it happened.
All I want to know is,
where are my children?
I need to know
if they're alive.
FEMALE DOCTOR:
She's unconscious.
Somehow, she's shifting
in and out of the visible spectrum.
We don't know how.
Her vitals are stable.
She doesn't seem
to be able to control it.
MALE DOCTOR 4: Looks like
we have some activity.
(GROANING)
(MOANING)
(GRUNTING)
Son. Oh, my God.
(SCREAMING)
(EXHALES)
(BREATHING NORMALLY)
(EXCLAIMS)
BEN: (FAINTLY)
Can anyone hear me?
Please, help me!
Somebody, please!
Is anybody there?
Ben?
Somebody answer me!
(GRUNTING)
BEN: (SHOUTING)
Somebody, please!
Help me!
Can anyone hear me?
Please, help me!
Hello?
Somebody answer me!
Anybody?
(GRUNTING)
Ben?
Ben!
(SCREAMING)
Reed?
REED: Oh, my God.
Ben?
Reed, what happened to me?
I don't know.
But I'm gonna figure this out.
(ALARM BLARING)
Ben!
(GRUNTS)
Please help me, Reed!
MAN OVER PA: Subject One
has escaped containment.
Oh, shit! Shit!
Ben, I'm coming back for you,
I promise!
No, no, no! Reed, help me!
Please don't leave me!
I'm sorry.
Reed, do something, please!
Where is he? Where is Reed?
I don't know.
He's scared, Harvey.
They're all just scared kids.
We don't know
what they are right now.
All we know is that they
are dangerous and powerful.
Which makes them
extremely valuable
to the guys
who run this place.
If you think for a minute
that I'm going to allow you
to turn these kids
into some kind of...
You don't have a choice,
Franklin. And neither do I.
Either we play ball
with the government
or who knows
what happens to those kids.
Now...
Here's how this is gonna go.
So you're Ben Grimm.
Where's Reed?
I can't begin to imagine
what you are going through.
He said he'll fix it.
Where is Reed?
Reed's gone.
Your friend isn't coming back.
Look, I know you're scared.
You should be.
But we can help you.
You wanna find a cure?
We have resources here,
the best in the world.
We're analyzing
what happened to you.
Whatever it is, we can find
a way to reverse it.
We can help you, Ben.
But you need to help us, too.
(GRUNTS)
(GRUNTING)
What do you want me to do?
DR. ALLEN: His combat
effectiveness this past year
has been unprecedented.
In terms of potential,
you already know what he's
accomplished in the field.
He's been active
in covert operations
with a 100% success rate.
Protecting our men
and women in battle
and saving countless lives.
Ladies and gentlemen,
this is only the beginning.
The other survivors
of the "Baxter Incident"
all exhibited
unique physical conditions.
We developed suits
which allow them
to contain and control
these conditions.
This subject's suit
controls her spectral flares
and refractive visibility.
With intense concentration
she has also
developed the ability
to render
other objects invisible.
And, to neuropathically
produce force fields.
(SUE GRUNTS)
All these abilities
come from one place.
Another dimension
that our scientists
have taken to calling
"Planet Zero."
A planet infused
with the same energy
that transformed these survivors
and potentially could transform
our military capabilities.
We have the direct link.
With your continued support,
once the Quantum Gate 2
project is finished,
we'll have control
over more than that world.
We'll have control over ours.
Everyone, have a look.
What the hell is that?
Subject Number Two.
(GRUNTS)
(CHUCKLES)
(EXHALES)
2,000 meters in six seconds.
New record.
Just need to work
on my takeoff.
I can make it in five.
TECHNICIAN 1:
All target drones neutralized.
TECHNICIAN 2: Keep holding
your breath, Susan.
As long as you can.
Directional stability
is 33 over 10.
Rise is steady.
Pitch is eight degrees.
Your balance is getting better.
(PANTING)
Hey.
They're gonna send me
on a project.
Like Ben?
We should use these powers
to do something.
They're not powers.
They're aggressively abnormal
physical conditions that we're gonna fix.
Can you turn that off?
And what if they can't?
What if it takes
more time to get it right?
We could be talking years.
I am not going to be a tool.
Johnny...
Stan, you ready?
Yes, we are.
Flame on.
Okay, Johnny.
Thank you, Sue.
Don't forget...
We're here to get
our lives back.
The subjects have agreed
to cooperate with us
until we find
the source of their powers
and, potentially, a cure.
Why don't we go
see the big guy?
DR. ALLEN: (OVER SPEAKER) Hi, Ben.
I got some friends
of mine here,
from Washington D.C., visiting.
Got a second to say hello?
It's an honor
to meet you, Mr. Grimm.
We appreciate
all you're doing for us.
That was the deal. Right?
And there she is,
the Quantum Gate herself.
The, uh, star of the show.
(CHUCKLES)
Franklin.
I'd like for you all
to meet Franklin Storm...
who is our supervisor
here on the floor.
How do you do, sir?
Good morning.
How long until it's ready?
Well, we've had a few issues,
but we're getting closer.
Closer every day.
All right, Dr. Allen.
We'll give you what you need.
In the meantime,
we'd like to put
more of your subjects
in the field.
Subject Two is ready to go.
Get him ready for combat.
DR. STORM: Susan!
Can I have a word with you?
They're sending
Johnny into the field.
You mean he's sending himself
into the field.
The only way to stop him
is to cure him.
And that means
finishing the Gate.
I can't finish it
without Reed.
Reed's not coming back.
He abandoned us, left us here.
He was afraid. He didn't
know what this place was.
I can't believe
you're still defending him.
Help me track him down, Suzu.
He'll listen to you.
We'll reopen the Gate,
find a cure, end this.
Johnny's your brother.
It's never been as easy
for him as it has for you.
But, like it or not,
he's family.
And family means
we take care of each other.
What can I do?
The FBI, CIA, and NSA
have blips of Reed
here and there...
but they can't seem to see...
A pattern.
Where was he last seen?
Three months ago, in Panama.
SUE: Did you get an IP?
MILITARY TECH: Early on,
he was using some old,
buried e-mail accounts.
Bouncing off satellites.
He's keeping himself
pretty well hidden.
For a short while,
we were able
to ping him, here and there.
Caught him on a few sites.
He was looking for
scrap metal, buying parts.
Never stayed online that long.
Was he looking
for anything else?
He was searching for him.
I'm gonna need some music.
MILITARY TECH: Excuse me?
I need music.
It helps me think.
(LATIN MUSIC PLAYING)
(BOTH SPEAKING SPANISH)
The valve is worn, it's not worth twenty.
I'll give you ten.
I got people who work for me.
Twenty or no deal.
I'll give you five and
I'll fix your register for free.
(RINGS)
Gracias.
(GRUNTING)
(MUSIC PLAYING OVER HEADPHONES)
SUE: Captain Nemo.
That's him.
He's routing his e-mails
through this relay.
Got him.
You did what you had to do.
Hi, Ben.
We've got another
project for you.
I think you're gonna
like this one.
(ALARM BLARING)
(HELICOPTER BLADES WHIRRING)
Freeze! Do not move!
Get down on the ground!
SOLDIER: Freeze!
(GRUNTS)
Oh, my God. Ben!
So, this is where
you've been hiding out.
Wait, stop.
Okay, let me explain.
(GRUNTS)
Why?
I'm no good to you, to anyone.
This is all my fault.
That, we can agree on.
(GRUNTS)
(GROANS)
REED: Does it hurt?
I'm used to it.
I'm sorry.
That's what you said
when you left.
I'm going to fix this.
You can't fix this.
Nobody can.
I promise you,
I'm going to fix this.
I stopped believing in your
bullshit a long time ago.
You were my best friend.
Look at me.
I'm not your friend.
You turned me
into something else.
Nice work, Ben!
(GRUNTS)
(SIGHS)
Hey, Reed.
Look, I'm sorry,
but I didn't have a choice.
We need your help
to finish the Gate.
It's the only chance
we have to figure out
what happened to us,
and reverse it.
You really think
that they care about us?
You know how
they've used Ben.
Yeah. I do.
And they're gonna do
the same thing
to Johnny
if we don't stop them.
The only shot we've got is on
the other side of that Gate.
Do you ever wonder what
life would have been like...
if you hadn't come
to the science fair that day?
We can't change the past.
But we can change the future.
You said you wanted your work
to make a difference.
This is it.
This is your chance.
Are you ready?
You made it ugly.
It's good to
see you again, son.
(KEYS CLACKING)
I'm gonna need ten minutes.
To do what?
I need to make a couple
adjustments to the source code.
You have a few steps
that are out of order.
It can't be that simple.
It might not be ten minutes.
It could be a little less.
Come on. Let's go.
I got a good feeling, Stan.
I'm gonna crack five seconds.
Hey, could I take a couple
of minutes with my son?
Sure, no problem.
Guys, can you give us
five minutes?
What's going on?
Reed is back.
We're closer than
we've ever been before.
Closer to what?
Our old lives.
Oh, you mean your life?
No, son.
You always said
I had the potential
to do something important.
Who's to say this isn't it?
Sometimes things
just happen for a reason.
Johnny, you have no idea
what they are planning
to do to you.
They're not doing
anything to me.
I'm doing this with them.
Johnny, you need
to listen to me...
I did listen to you,
and that's what
got me here
in the first place.
I'm an adult.
I'm old enough to
make my own decisions.
MAN OVER PA: Clear for launch.
Stand by.
Look who it is.
Hey.
It's good seeing you, man.
Good to see you, too.
MAN OVER PA:
Sonic projectors engaged.
Goggles up.
Initiate launch.
SCIENTIST:
Systems check complete.
We have a visual.
QUANTUM GATE EXPLORER:
Roger that, Control.
Are you receiving
atmospheric data?
Copy that.
Checking configuration.
Data transmission looks good.
The landscape's changed.
How?
I don't know,
it's just different.
Commencing element
and geological test series.
SCIENTIST: Copy.
Hey, Control, I'm picking up
a heat signature
about 60 yards away.
Now, what could that be?
Hard to make out.
The signal keeps fluctuating.
It's moving.
Heading towards us.
SCIENTIST: Copy that.
Proceed with caution.
Do you have a visual?
It appears to be a human form...
with some sort of
foreign element around it.
(WEAKLY)
I knew you'd come back.
Victor?
Not possible.
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
Subject appears injured.
Get the med kit.
Let's get him
to the shuttle.
Grab him. Come on.
Easy, guys.
Abort. Bring him back.
SCIENTIST: Aborting mission.
Stabilize the subject
and prepare for transport.
Oh, shit.
Preparing for launch.
Transfer the subject
to Containment Room One.
EXPLORER: Copy that.
His thermal signature
is barely registering.
His biochemistry
is off the charts.
I want to talk to him.
Nobody talks to him
until I do.
Confine the others
to their quarters.
Victor?
We don't know how
you survived over there
but we're still
analyzing the data.
It appears that your
environment suit
fused with your body...
but we're working on that.
We're going to help you, Victor.
We're working with
the government now.
We're going to send more
expeditions to the other side
but first you need
to tell us everything
you know about that place.
VICTOR: You want to know
how I survived?
That place kept me alive.
Gave me strength.
Power.
What kind of power?
The kind men like you
must never possess.
(ALL SCREAMING)
You couldn't resist coming back.
It's not enough
to ruin your world.
Now you want to ruin mine.
Victor.
If this world must die
so that mine may live...
so be it.
(GROANING)
(HIGH-PITCHED TONE)
(CHOKING)
AUTOMATED VOICE:
Code Red. Code Red.
There is an emergency
in this building.
Follow standard
emergency protocols.
Proceed to the nearest exit
and leave
the building immediately.
Code Red. Code Red.
(PEOPLE CLAMORING)
There is an emergency
in this building.
Follow standard
emergency protocols.
(WOMAN SCREAMING)
(GUNFIRE)
Code Red. Code Red.
There is an emergency
in this building.
Follow standard
emergency protocols.
Proceed to the nearest exit
and leave
the building immediately.
Running away again?
No.
Sue!
(COUGHING)
My bad! Are you okay?
Yeah, I'm all right.
Where's Dad?
DR. STORM: Victor, no.
Just stop!
Out of my way, Franklin.
I'm going home.
This is your home, son.
Not anymore.
There is nothing
for you over there.
Only the power
to create a new world.
Victor, we're not gods.
We're just people.
And we are stronger together
than we are apart.
What good is it
if you're alone?
I have always been alone.
SUE: Victor, stop!
Just stop!
(BOTH GRUNTING)
It's too late, Susan.
The Earth is dying.
Humanity had its chance.
(GROANING)
No!
Dad!
JOHNNY: Dad! No!
Dad, no, I'm sorry!
SUE: Dad, no!
Dad!
Dad, move!
Victor, no!
(GROANS)
(WEAKLY) Promise me.
What?
Look after each other.
Dad, I'm sorry!
Dad, I'm sorry.
Dad, please.
No!
(GRUNTS)
He's overloading the system
to create a runaway reaction.
It's not gonna stop!
It'll create a black hole
that'll swallow the Earth!
He's pulling everything
into the other dimension!
Hold on!
Johnny!
Got it!
(ALL GROANING)
REED: The matter from Earth is
being converted to energy!
We need to stop Victor!
He's the source!
He's mine!
SUE: I have an idea.
This is what I do.
(GRUNTS)
(ROARS)
(PEOPLE SCREAMING)
(CLAMORING)
Where are you, Susan?
(GROANS)
Victor, don't do this!
There is no Victor.
There is only Doom.
(GROANING)
(GRUNTS)
I saw a different future
for us, Susan.
BEN: Help me!
Reed!
Ben!
(STRAINING)
Goodbye, Susan.
Ah!
(GASPING)
(GROANING)
(GRUNTS)
(GRUNTING)
Reed!
Is he dead?
If that thing's
still active, so is he.
We can't beat him.
He's stronger than any of us.
Yeah, he is.
But he's not stronger
than all of us.
Look, this place
gave him his powers...
but it gave us
all of ours, too.
It's who we are now.
Maybe it's who
we're meant to be.
We opened this door,
we're gonna close it.
So, what's the plan?
Enough!
When your world is destroyed,
and I'm all that's left...
then it will be enough.
(GROANING)
(GROANS)
Always so smug,
thinking you were
smarter than me.
I am smarter than you.
Now!
Hey! It's clobbering time!
This better work.
No.
(SCREAMING)
JOHNNY: Let's get
the hell out of here!
GENERAL: While the world
may not know
what you did to save it...
The men and the women
in this room do.
And so does the President.
That said,
we'd like to continue
our existing relationship.
So, if we're all in agreement...
We're not.
Excuse me?
We're not remotely
"all in agreement."
We don't need you or anybody
else to keep an eye on us.
We just want a place
where we can work.
And whatever we come up with
belongs to us.
And what if we say no?
(BEN GROWLING)
Say yes.
How much space
are we talking about?
A lot.
Whoa. Hey.
So, uh, I thought there were
gonna be four of you?
Oh, there is.
Labs are upstairs.
Engineering's on the south side
and Assembly's downstairs.
We've been operating out of
here for over 12 years, now.
Well, officially, that is.
But you still
won't find our name
on any government books.
Most people just refer
to this as, uh, Central City.
But call it whatever you want.
We work for you now.
JOHNNY: Oh, wow.
Now, that's what
I'm talking about.
That's pretty nice.
(SUE CHUCKLES)
I'm taking that area
over there.
REED: I could
get used to this.
I got it.
The "Franklin Storm
Research Center."
Dad was kind of allergic
to his name in big letters.
Which reminds me,
I think that the four of us
should have a name.
Why would we need a name?
Because we're a team now,
and there's four of us
so we should come up
with a name for it.
Like, "The Human Torch
and the Torchettes."
Ugh.
No.
BEN: Are you kidding me?
How about "The Big Brain
and His Neurons"?
and Her Neurons"?
How about "Two Guys, a Girl,
"and the Thing
that Nobody Wanted"?
(GROWLS)
Hey, we both know
that you could take him.
Hey.
Hey. What?
We've come a long way
since the garage.
Gotta say, it's fantastic.
Say that again.
It's fantastic.
Yes, it is.
Guys, I got it.
Ready?
Yeah.
Someone needs to stop Clearway Law.
Public shouldn't leave reviews for lawyers.