Downloaded from
YTS.MX
Official YIFY movies site:
Welcome to Navojoa.
Little brother.
Jack.
Weren't at your hotel,
so I figured this'd be
the next place to find you.
Right, well, you could
have waited for me to come
and find you when I
was ready to talk,
but that's not
your style, is it?
I know this isn't something
you wanted to do, coming here.
On the contrary,
this used to be one of
the most incredible
junkyards I ever saw.
Now look at it...
there's almost nothing left.
You know what I meant.
Ryan, I...
- I meant...
- I know what you meant.
What kinda trouble you in?
I'm all in.
Whew...
how much you need?
You know, man, you don't have
to throw it back in my face.
I know you've bailed
me out before...
I know.
I get it.
That's not what I meant.
Yeah.
Listen, I just wanna
help you get right.
So if you need cash,
I'll get some...
No, it's not cash,
it's not cash.
Cash won't do this time.
Well, then what is it?
- Four ladies.
- Oh!
Diamonds are not
a girl's best friend.
How is it that you're such
a fuck-up
when your brother Jack is out
there winning all the time?
What is that like?
You guys still close?
Well, you're gonna need him.
We need him.
Need him for what?
We need him to run the Outlaw.
Davie, listen, man...
it's out of the question.
Look, I can...
I will pay you back every
last dollar that I owe you.
I will.
It's not about a choice.
Actually, it is a choice...
do I kill you now,
or do I give you a chance
to redeem yourself.
Jack thinks as highly
of me as you do.
He will never race the Outlaw.
Not even to save the life
of his little brother?
Man, there's no way.
He won't do it.
Are you willing to bet
your life on this?
There's a race,
it's called the Outlaw.
This year it's Mexico to L.A.
God, you got
some balls, man...
some fucking balls, coming
down here, asking me that.
I retired, man.
I got outta the race game,
and I've stayed there.
Yeah, you think
I don't know that?
Get your stuff.
I'm driving you back
to the States myself.
I'm in a really bad
place with this guy, man,
a really bad place.
He has people...
people that will find me.
I can't be looking
over my shoulder
for the rest of my life.
Get in the car.
It looks like
I'm the oldest guy here
by about at least
15 years, huh?
At least you got experience
on your side.
Or I'm too stupid to know
I shouldn't be here.
Is that the guy?
Good evening, racers.
Welcome to this year's
running of the Outlaw 1000.
This year's race starts
in Navojoa,
and it's 1,000 miles
to Los Angeles.
The winner...
$5 million.
I don't care how you get there,
but it has to be on four wheels,
and there's three checkpoints
that you must hit along the way.
The checkpoints
have been preprogrammed
into your GPS systems.
Is that all of them?
Oh!
Ladies and gentlemen, we have
royalty in the house tonight...
Mr. Jack Tyson.
This motherfucker done
won more races
than any redneck in NASCAR.
Did you point a gun
at my brother?
As a matter of fact, I did...
and here you are.
Jack, Jack, wait, wait, wait!
Your brother owes me
a lot of money.
But if you win this race,
the debt will be paid.
Nelson, did you not explain?
Yeah, I did.
Come on.
Come on!
This is why you don't
meet your heroes.
Put a muzzle on
that fucking dog!
What were you trying
to prove back there?
Get your hands off of me.
You can't mess around
with a guy like Davie.
Don't tell me you're
afraid of a grown-ass man
that goes by the
name of "Davie."
Shut the fuck up!
Fuck you, man!
Hey...
what would have happened
if I wouldn't
have come down here,
huh, Nelson?
How would that have looked?
You'd take a bullet
from this asshole?
Why?
What do you want me
to tell you, man?
I kept losing, all right, and
he was the only game in town.
He saw you coming, man, and
he gave you just enough rope.
Guys like that?
They can spot the real
compulsive gamblers a mile away.
Shut up, man.
When are you gonna
get it together, man?
Seriously.
What are you even
still doing in Mexico?
You had the money to get out.
I didn't have it.
You didn't have it?
Is there a problem here?
You know what?
You could tell Davie
to take it all
and shove it right up his ass.
Him and I, we're not done.
Not even close.
Ooh, charming, Jack.
Why don't you take this anger
and channel it into
winning this race?
Drivers ready!
Nina!
You about to find out about
these eight seconds.
Still not as quick as your
boyfriend in bed, though.
This ain't no
rally race, homeboy.
Three...
two...
Go!
Jack is still one
hell of a driver.
Shame he's such
a fucking prick.
I bet it's killing you
on the inside,
not putting any money
on him to win.
Go to hell, Davie.
I'll tell you what...
I'll float you 100k.
I mean, what kind of guy
would I be to not let you
get in on the action?
All right.
How come there's not much
riding on Jack up there?
Maybe they know something
we don't know.
Well, that's crap.
What's with this
hidden camera shit?
Paranoid much?
Why don't you just shut the
fuck up and watch the race?
Fucking Jack Tyson
needle dick.
Who the fuck is Jack Tyson?
Yeah, where the fuck
you at, Grandpa?
Fuck.
Let's go.
Shit, oh, shit!
Fucking Hot Wheel driver.
Come on.
I got you.
No way, not today.
Not today, come on, let's go.
Welcome to checkpoint one.
You are?
Jack.
So this is it, huh?
Well, congratulations on
first place for checkpoint one.
Mr. Davie?
I've got a Mr. Jack in the
restaurant, first place.
Si, senor, will do.
He'd like to congratulate you
on your first-place win.
Ah. Yeah, sure.
So Davie owns this place?
Si, he's owned it
for many years.
For the winner.
And once all the other
drivers are here,
lunch will be served, okay?
Goddamn it, fuck.
Hola, race fans,
it's your girl, Six-Speed Nina,
and I am here at
El Tesoro Escondido,
in the town of Hermosio.
And it's our first stop
in the Outlaw 1000.
And you'd better believe
I'll be chowing down
on some bean burritos
before our race moves
to our next stop,
Puerto Penasco.
Can I ask you what
the hell you're doing?
Well, I'm posting to all
my followers on Instagram.
You know, checking in
every stop of the way,
letting them ride shotgun
all the way to L.A.
Or letting the cops know where
we're going all the way to L.A.
You don't wanna go
around broadcasting
where you're going
unless you want to get
pulled over and arrested.
The Mexican police
don't follow me.
Well, they will be
before long.
Says here you retired...
like three years ago.
And the last time you won
something was longer than that.
So what's Davie
inviting you for?
Your guess is as good as mine.
But when I buzzed
you back there,
you didn't know what to do,
so you don't have any
street reflexes whatsoever.
But I guess that's
the difference between racing
on a closed track
against a clock
versus having another man
in the next lane?
Is that right?
Let me guess...
the real skill comes from
doing 90 in a pedestrian zone
and losing control
and plowing into a family
who's coming home from
having ice cream?
Is that how you hone
your "street reflexes," bro?
Watch your mouth, Grandpa.
Easy, guys... easy.
It's okay, kid.
You know what, I was pretty
stupid when I was your age, too.
Yeah, when was that?
Before the car was invented?
Something like that.
I'll see you out there.
Sure... just not for long.
Good luck, guys.
Who's there?
Can you show me that
10-second car now?
Eat a dick, Nina.
Whatever.
Gotcha!
Bitch!
Ah!
- Drive! Drive! Drive!
- What's going on?
Jack has really come
through so far.
Yeah, for you, but nobody
else is betting on him.
One point eight mil?
Really?
Man, you said it yourself...
he's retired.
Been outta the race game
for a while.
These other kids are hot
in the circuit right now.
They're street punks.
They've got more recognition,
recent popularity...
things your brother
does not have.
Gillian, make the transfers
to the winners.
Alert the losers
that stage two is starting.
Okay.
I'm gonna need your name,
or you're gonna need to get out.
Is that a threat?
You don't know anything
about me.
Maybe I don't do well
with threats.
Maybe I'm about to
stab you in the face
and take this goddamn thing?
Oh, yeah?
All right.
Just wanted to know who I was
in the car with, that's all.
Name's Bianca.
Hello, Bianca.
You mind telling me
what happened back there?
You wanna tell me
who you are first?
It's only polite.
Now we're being polite.
All right, fine...
my name's Jack.
Jack Tyson.
Jack?
You're the guy...
oh, thank God.
You know who I am?
You're Davie's golden boy.
This whole thing hinges on you.
Oh, you don't know how
happy I am right now
to have found you so quickly.
Wait, you've
been looking for me?
I need you to take me to L.A.
I know I can get there
with you driving.
Davie's probably gonna try some
messed-up stuff on the way up,
but he can't afford
to lose you.
He won't do anything to you.
Well, okay, hold on.
You're gonna have to
start from the beginning.
What is this all about?
These...
I took them from his safe.
Oh!
Oh, no...
No, no, no, no.
Fuck.
Fuck!
Yeah?
Davie?
Davie, they took them.
They're gone.
Are you fucking serious?
Yeah, but I tried to stop him,
but he was too fast, and I...
I'm really sorry!
Look, you stupid bitch, you'd
better fucking find it, right?
- I fucked up, I know I...
- Now!
I don't know what to do,
I'm sorry.
Stupid fucking bitch!
God-fucking-damn it!
Who the hell is that?
Bianca.
Wait, you know this chick?
So, we there yet?
Not even close.
We're about an hour
out of Suaqui Grande,
which, now that I think about
it, is probably a good place
for me to drop you off at
a bus station or somewhere.
What? No, you can't!
Please...
Listen to me, I'm gonna
drop you off
at a bus or train station.
You'll be safer and you'll
get to where you're going
a lot quicker and easier
than with me, all right?
He's looking for me at the bus
station, and the airport.
His men are everywhere,
he's gonna kill me!
Don't you understand that?
Because of what's
on those drives?
What's on 'em?
- Evidence.
- Evidence of what?
Of all of Davie's past,
present, and future crimes.
Evidence that's gonna
get that bastard
out of our lives for good, and
put him away where he belongs.
Listen, what exactly
are on those drives?
All of his ledgers...
every record he's kept,
dating back since he started
keeping them digitally.
Oh, boy.
Did they get anything?
As a matter of fact, they did.
Was it anything important?
Shut the fuck up, Nelson.
They arrived
at the checkpoint,
the safe was broken into.
Hey...
you know why you're a
worthless, piece of shit loser?
Because you never
win at anything.
Sit down when
I'm talking to you!
You can call it luck;
I call it karma.
You come from shit,
all you can be is shit.
But when you give a shit,
you get shit.
My father was nothing,
but look at me.
Now I'm a multimillionaire
who can kill anybody
at any time.
I own this town, I own the cops,
I own everything
you fucking see.
Man, you don't own the cops.
If they knew you were
cutting them out of the race,
you'd be fucked.
Your brother,
he's a piece of shit
because you share
the same fucking blood.
Your father was a piece
of shit.
And well...
Your mother was a stupid bitch
for fucking a piece of shit.
Look at you...
the way you dress,
the way that...
everything about you says shit.
You'll always be
a fucking loser.
I'm not here by choice.
No one who does anything
for Davie is by choice.
Once they have their hooks in,
you can't get out,
no matter what you do.
Sounds like you're
talking from experience.
You know, you don't look much
like a thief or a safe-cracker.
So tell me something...
how'd you know where
the drives were?
I used to work for Davie.
I was his girlfriend.
I knew the safe code.
Ah... girlfriend.
Now, that's just
fan-fucking-tastic.
Oh, boy...
let me guess, you broke up
with him, he wanted you back,
you stole the drives, and now
everything's up in the air.
Davie's gonna kill me
if I don't deliver those
drives to Los Angeles.
He could kill anybody
without a thought.
I could never kill anybody...
couldn't even think about that.
You ever kill anybody, huh?
I didn't think so.
He's sick.
This is payback.
And look, whatever
Davie has on you,
whatever reason he has for
forcing you to race for him,
it all goes away once
I get this evidence
to the U.S. attorney.
We can put Davie away
for good, you and me.
We can do this.
No one else will do it, Jack.
I underestimated
this little bitch.
She chose Jack because
she knows I need him to win.
I don't understand.
She's trying to get
over the border
with the things
she stole from me.
She thinks Jack is her ticket.
She's so fucking wrong.
What did this chick
steal from you?
Shut the fuck up.
Policia!
I'll take care of this.
The fuck do you want,
banging on my door like
the fucking police?
Senor Davie...
Vamanos!
Vamos!
Motherfuckers!
- Yeah...
- You done fucked up!
Your whole family's gonna
die behind this shit!
- David!
- Gillian!
Damn it!
Did they just arrest Davie?
Those sons-of-bitches aren't
taking him to any jail.
Bastards!
They pick today to do this,
of all days.
It's their mistake, their error.
And this stays quiet.
As far as anybody knows,
Davie is still right here.
Oh, it's Gillian.
Gillian, what up?
Garcia took Davie.
I need you to bring him back.
All right, understood.
I'm sending the car, be ready.
We're ready, we're ready.
- What's up?
- La policia took Davie.
Let's go.
Fuck!
Get ready to fuck some shit up.
Here we go.
All right.
Come on, come on, come on.
Mick, you ass!
Woo!
Just a little bumpin', dumplin'!
Not in this lifetime, Nita!
Woo!
Shit!
Thank you, Jack!
Motherfucking fuck, fuck!
How do you like that,
you little snotty prick?
Jesus, did you just hit
that guy on purpose?
Now we're on track.
That's how we do it.
Are we really going
118 miles per hour?
Yeah, that's the point
of racing...
to go really, really fast.
Well, if you're trying
to scare the crap outta me,
it's working.
Hola.
Dos tacos, por favor.
Très tacos y una cerveza.
Que?
Those tacos aren't
coming, sweetie.
You're gonna take us to him
if you wanna
keep your fucking head,
do you understand me?
Let's go.
Why are we stopping?
Because I need
something to eat.
You should do the same.
We'll take it to go.
We gotta make that next
checkpoint by morning.
How many stops we have
until we get to L.A.?
Two more checkpoints
to the finish line.
Hola, I will have the cemita
milanesa y una Coca-Cola.
Huevos rancheros,
salsa picante.
Breakfast for dinner
kinda gal, huh?
Since I was a little girl.
But when you grew up
poor like we were,
the concept of breakfast for
dinner goes out the window.
You either eat what's in
front of you, or you go hungry.
Fair enough.
Plus I just really like
huevos rancheros.
And you think that's
the best thing to take
in a car on the go?
Don't worry, I'm not gonna
get any yolk or salsa
on your precious little car.
Okay, so listen...
let's say your whole plan
works when you get to L.A.
You said Davie has
people everywhere.
What makes you think
he's not gonna come after you
after he goes down?
The U.S. attorney's giving
me a new identity.
Witness protection?
And everything you have leads
the feds to his front door?
Yes.
So you can stop trying to dump
me on the side of the road.
So that's what you meant
when you said
everything hinges on me.
Oh, yeah... you're very
important to both of us.
I need you to help me get
this information to L.A.
He needs you to win to keep
the criminals and cartels
he works for happy and earning
millions of commissions.
He won't go after you.
I gotta run to the bathroom.
I'll meet you at the car.
Yeah, hurry up.
We gotta go.
Hola, mija.
We're gonna have some fun!
Ah!
Gimme the drives!
I know that you have them!
How about this?
No! No!
Ah!
[ shouting
Thanks for the drive,
you son of a bitch.
Puta bitch!
Jack, we gotta go!
Bianca, what the hell...
Get in the fucking car!
You okay?
Is anything broken?
I don't think so.
Oh, man.
He was looking
for the thumb drives... these.
Here, put this on your lip,
it'll help with the swelling.
Thanks.
Ow!
Son of a bitch had his
knee digging into my back,
I thought he was gonna break it.
I'll be fine.
It's nothing compared to what
Davie used to do to me.
It's not my car,
it's your boyfriend's.
What the hell did I say
about saying that, Jack?
What are you doing?
How did he know
you were here, huh?
He can see in the car?
Gotcha.
Damn it!
I think he got you.
We have... a complication.
Let's go, puto.
Get the fuck over there.
Por favor, no!
Por favor!
- Por favor!
- Shut up.
Thanks for the directions, papi.
Get down!
I said, get down, now!
Come on, Davie...
can you walk?
Okay, you're almost there.
Fucking pig!
Motherfucker.
I gotcha.
They must have drugged him.
Take his hood off.
Move!
Tanya, did you find him yet?
Yeah, yeah, we got him,
we got him.
How bad did they hurt him?
No, I don't...
I don't fucking know, Gillian.
You call me as soon as he's
able to talk to me, you hear me?
I want you to meet me in L.A.
- L.A.?
- Get to the air strip.
The jet's waiting.
Drive as fast as you can,
you got it?
I cannot risk anything
else happening to him.
- Faster, faster.
- I can't go any fucking faster!
Fuck!
You don't belong here.
Mm.
Morning.
Yeah.
Did you get some sleep?
A bit.
I stopped for a couple hours
when my eyes got heavy.
Good.
How far are we from
the next checkpoint?
I gotta pee.
Close.
I just hope it's a place
where there's coffee.
What is this?
The Sinaloa.
Cartel.
Davie moves a lot
of money for them.
I want the girl!
Send her out, and you go.
Jack, please.
Send out that puta, esse!
- Bianca...
- Send out that bitch!
Get out.
Jack, no... please.
I said get out, now!
They're gonna murder me,
you know that, right?
- Now!
- Get out, now!
My blood is gonna be on your
hands, you son of a bitch.
Now!
Go get her! Go!
Get in, get in!
Jesus!
Motherfucker!
Fuck!
You couldn't warn me first?
Woo... 2.6 miles to go!
You better believe
I'm taking this one.
Fuck you, Jack!
Jack better be fixing to reach
this checkpoint, Nelson.
If he loses a stage,
there's no good news for you.
Don't threaten me, Gillian.
"Don't threaten me, Gillian?"
You know, for an old military
grunt, you're a real pussy.
"Don't threaten me, Gillian."
Okay.
Mick is about
to win this stage,
and now you're going
to grow a pair with me?
If I were Jack,
I'd have turned my back
on your pathetic ass years ago.
Now look where you got him...
out there on the road because
you're a low-life degenerate
with a gambling problem.
Got a lot of balls for somebody
who owes us seven figures.
What are you gonna do?
I mean, you gonna kill me?
How's that get you paid?
That gets us paid.
Jack gets us paid.
If he loses, so do you.
If we have to pay out,
we're not the only ones
who are going to feel it.
Killing you is
a consolation prize,
and we'd be doing everybody
around you a goddamn favor.
Jack, what are you doing?
Get back in the car!
Why are we stopping?
Jack!
- Bianca, please...
- Jack!
Please, stop.
Gimme a fucking second,
I've gotta check for damage.
And relax, they're not
after us anymore.
You saved my ass back there.
No one's ever done anything
like that for me before.
I'm sorry I didn't
warn you sooner.
I figured the only way
they were gonna buy it
is if you thought
I was giving you up.
I sure as hell thought
you were gonna give me up.
And then you mowed him down.
Thank you.
Sure.
You know, come to think of it,
Davie said all of
the GPS systems
were preprogrammed with the
destinations of the checkpoints.
That's how he's
been tracking us.
That's how he led us
into that ambush.
Now what?
We don't know where the next
checkpoints are located.
I have an idea.
Do you have Instagram?
- Yeah.
- I figured.
Uh, look up Six-Speed Nina.
If I recall correctly,
she said something about
Puerto Poco or Puerto Puntasca
or something like that.
I got it...
Puerto Penasco?
Yeah, yeah, that sounds right.
Got it.
Hola, race fans, it's your
girl, Six-Speed Nina, and
I am here at
El Tesoro Escondido,
in the town of Hermosio, our
first stop in the Outlaw 1000.
And you'd better believe
I'll be chowing down
on some bean burritos before the
race moves to Puerto Penasco.
I knew she wouldn't
let us down.
All right, come on, let's go.
Woo!
Where's everybody at?
Did I win this
motherfucking round?
I think I did.
Whew.
Hey, yo, I'm here.
So? And you are?
Mick Hammett.
And it looks like I'm the first
motherfucker to show up.
Well,
congratu-fucking-lations.
Are you sure it's
safe to check in?
Davie won't risk
doing anything to us
in front of the other drivers.
What do you want
from me, dude?
Don't you got somebody
you gotta call or something?
I want you to call who
you're supposed to call.
- Uh, perdona me...
- Yes?
Jack Tyson, checking
in for the Outlaw?
Welcome, Mr. Tyson.
You're the stage winner.
I am?
Whoa, whoa, no,
the fuck he's not.
I was here before he was!
You were just talking to me
before he pulled up!
Man, I don't know who you are
or what the fuck
you want from me,
but you just come in here
talking about "I've arrived."
Look, man, he's right.
He won fair and square.
I was here before he got here,
you were just...
Man, back the fuck up, dude,
right now, all right?
You got five seconds.
That's right, man.
Yeah... keep walking, man.
Hello?
Yeah, this is Robert.
Got your first winner.
Mr. Tyson.
That's some major bullshit.
Well?
He did it...
two more to go.
Wait...
That's why Davie
gave me the 100k?
What?
Yeah, you needed
some action on Jack
so that no one
asked any questions.
You need this to look legit.
I don't follow.
You know, I might look
like a brain-dead meathead,
but even a kid
really could figure this out.
Yeah, the bettors,
they aren't taking Jack
because they're
losing on purpose.
Yeah... you and Davie
retain the cash
that they lose on the bet at
a commission, and then what?
My guess is you're
supposed to spend it,
or move it to where
they tell you to.
In the end, no one loses
a dime on the wager,
and you make, what,
18 million on stage two?
This is money-laundering.
Yeah.
This whole thing
is just a front.
You figure that out
by yourself?
How about that?
You know, at the end
of the day,
you and Davie are just
two lowlife degenerates
like me.
I am nothing like you.
I am a businesswoman,
earning a living...
a rather lucrative one,
I might add.
Until Jack gets to L.A.
Well, it looks like
you're gonna have to wait
a little longer
before that cup of coffee.
So, you won, right?
Well, as you can see,
there was a little controversy,
but yeah, I guess
we took the stage.
"We?"
You're in the car, too...
whether I like it or not.
So which is it?
Still deciding.
Should we let the others
know what we found in the car?
They have every right
to their privacy.
Hey, yo, Six.
Mr. World Champ.
Hey, I wanna thank you
for yesterday.
You know, helping me out
back there when Mick
was trying to run
me off the road.
No problem.
Let's just say he had it coming.
Yeah, okay.
Well, I'll tell you,
he was super pissed.
Then after what happened
in the station...
I'd watch your back.
He's stupid, but I don't
think he has it in him.
Heh... yeah.
Well, I just wanted
to give you a head's up
on what's going down.
- Well, I appreciate that.
- Mm-hmm.
- Well, now it's my turn.
- Yeah?
You think you can grab Mick
and meet me back here
in about five minutes?
I gotta tell you guys something.
- Okay.
- See you here in five.
Yeah.
You say a fucking word,
and I will kill you.
Who's calling?
Hi, Jack.
You don't know me,
so let me introduce myself.
I'm Gillian Bertrand.
I guess "attaboy"
is in order first...
two stages so far.
Gotta hand it to you.
Why are you calling me?
Where's my brother?
Relax, nobody's lying
in a ditch face-down
with the back of
their head blown off.
All right, I'm listening.
What do you want?
The same thing Davie wants.
We got a good thing going,
all of us.
Then why are you
calling me and not him?
I need you to focus, Jack.
Don't let that bitch
screw this up.
She's just another one
of Davie's crazy ex-girlfriends
with an anger
management problem.
If Davie likes making deals,
well, you can tell him
I got one for him.
Bianca for my brother...
even trade.
We never hear from either
one of you again... debt paid.
Are you there?
Oh, I'm here, Jack,
and I think I could speak
for him when I say we're
ready to agree to your terms...
even trade.
He's not coming.
Oh... his loss.
Listen, we're all being watched.
There's cameras in the car.
Wh... what?
- Yeah, come...
- But how?
Come on.
Look, check the dash and up
above, you should find...
What?
What in the hell?
Yeah.
Wait... how did you know this?
Nina, some things are
better left unanswered.
Do you want some advice?
Get out of the race game,
and you'll avoid guys
like Davie.
One of these days you're
gonna realize it's...
it's not worth the risk anymore.
Jack!
Jack, behind you, watch out!
Mick, stop, let him go!
Yeah, two of them, right now,
they're fighting in the
middle of my gas station.
Are we done?
You all right?
- You're hurt.
- Yeah.
Come on, we gotta go.
Here, keep this on there
to stop the bleeding.
What's wrong?
I have a daughter.
She's six years old.
Her name is Sophia.
And where is she
while you're here?
Somewhere safe.
I'm not gonna say where,
I never know who's listening.
Does she know how brave
her mother is for doing this?
Every waking moment
should be spent with her,
but she needs me to do this.
The feds are gonna help her.
I give them what they want,
they help me get her
into the United States,
give us new lives,
and give her the medical
procedure that she needs.
Pemex Gas.
Roberto, is there
anybody still there?
Yeah, one of them's
still here...
the one that lost.
Let me talk to him.
All right, hold on.
Yo, loser...
you got a phone call, man.
Hurry the fuck up, dude.
What's up?
Mick?
This is Gillian Bertrand.
I heard you two got
into it earlier,
and I see now Jack
has left you behind.
Yeah, I'm gonna
catch up to that motherfucker
and make him pay.
See that you do.
And make sure you
win the next stage...
whatever it takes.
My brother and I are moving a
whole lot of money to your ride.
And Mick...
don't make us regret
putting our faith in you.
Consider it done.
Hurry the fuck up.
What the fuck you doing, dude?
Here's your phone, pussy.
Jack?
We have a problem.
Yeah? What's that?
I don't have a visa
or a permit.
The U.S. attorney's office
didn't send you anything?
I couldn't let them know
I was coming,
I couldn't risk Davie
knowing what I was doing.
Oh, God.
All right, great, so how
do we cross the border?
You got any great ideas?
Yes, but it's very dangerous.
Ah, because of course it is,
and why would it
be any other way?
We need to go back around
where we came from, 20 miles.
Mm.
Wait...
wait, what's happening?
What did you do?
What is your problem?
First you're bitching that no
one's betting on your brother.
Now he's won two stages
and everybody wants a piece
of the action,
and that's no good either?
Make up your mind.
No, you...
no, you don't want Jack's
bets to win, all right?
You'd have to pay out big.
Look at the size of these
wagers coming in.
That's more than the commission
you made on the entire race.
This stinks.
What did you do?
Gillian...
please, Gillian.
Please, please.
Get out of this office,
before I blow your
fucking head off.
Okay.
I'm tired of you.
- Now!
- Okay!
If we die, I'm blaming you.
Is that who I think it is?
There's another car
following us.
Here we go.
Whew.
It's that asshole
from the gas station again.
Ah!
Here's the border,
it's right there!
Can you hit that button
and make us go faster?
Yeah, nitrous in
desert terrain...
recipe for disaster.
Crack the axle, the car is dead.
Get him!
Get him, damn it!
Ah!
Mick, you worthless
piece of...
Jack cannot win this stage!
Oh! Oh!
That's a big payout.
"More than you made on
commissions this far."
They're in Arizona.
How's your day going?
It's fucked.
So tell me about it...
what's really going on?
Man...
man, I've dealt with
some people in my life,
but this bitch, she's
something else, you know?
Ah... a real chinga
tu madre, eh?
Ah, si.
- Hit me.
- All right.
In that case, drink up.
Mm, cheers.
You gonna get that?
No fucking way.
I watched you ignore my call.
Seems like a dick move,
don't you think?
Look, Gillian, I'm just
having a drink, okay?
- Get up.
- Come on.
Get up and out!
- All right, all right...
- Now!
You don't have to do this.
- Now, Nelson.
- It is what it is, man.
Welcome to Navojoa.
- Oh...
- Leave it...
Consider it your tip.
- Thank you, boss.
- Move it!
What are you doing, Gillian?
It's time to meet up
with your brother.
I hope you're not
afraid of flying.
Jack, you okay?
Jack, help!
Tell me what's going on, Jack.
I don't know.
I'm...
Where am I?
Hey, we're okay.
We made it.
We're gonna be fine.
What can I do?
Remember you asked me
if I ever killed anybody?
Well, the answer is yes.
What happened?
It was a blind corner.
We both saw it, but I...
I miscalculated, and...
I drove us off the side.
The car landed upside-down,
the fuel tank exploded,
and the car burned up
from the outside.
I...
I made it out,
but my wife, she...
she got trapped.
It's not your fault.
Growing up, it was
just me and my brother.
But he got screwed up
in the war, you know, PTSD.
All I had was my skin, my car,
and the streets.
You know, I had this '74 Camaro,
ran like a beast.
It was an eight-second car.
I lived my life a quarter
of a mile at a time.
You know, they say you're
only as good as your last race,
and when my wife died,
I was done.
I'm so sorry, Jack.
It's funny,
because growing up,
all I wanted to do is
be the best, the fastest.
Some people would say I was.
But I never felt that way.
When my foot hits that pedal
and I hit top gear...
I feel free.
There's no better
feeling in the world.
See all the cars behind me,
look in front of me...
nobody.
But as soon as
the race was over,
I'd be right back
to where I started...
waiting for the flags to wave.
I knew I had to get out,
do something different.
But I'll tell you, Bianca,
I feel like I'm pushing my luck.
No.
We're gonna make it
to Los Angeles...
for your brother,
for my daughter.
Look at me.
You saved my life.
We're gonna get through this,
I promise.
You ready?
All right, let's go.
Gillian?
I want to make
an arrangement with you.
Forget everything
that Davie wanted.
Forget about winning this race.
I'll make it worth your while.
Forget about winning the race?
Yes, Jack...
you give me no choice.
You are coming
near checkpoint three,
and those other gearhead
idiots are nowhere near you.
What's it going to take for
you to lose this race, huh?
Five mil?
Ten mil?
What do you want?
Talk to me!
You know what, Gillian?
Right now I'm currently driving,
and I'm pretty sure
it's against the law
to drive and talk in
the state of Arizona.
Jack?
Jack? Jack!
Oh, you miserable bastard!
We're getting close
to checkpoint three,
and she is freaking out.
Good, nice to have
them on that side of things
for a change.
When does Jack get here?
Get him outta the car.
Fuck you, Nelson.
You motherfucker!
- Fucker!
- Oh, fuck you!
- Shut up!
- Fuck you!
Fuck you!
Shut up!
Get...
get down, motherfucker.
Ha, ha, ha, Nelson!
You fucking bitch.
I want your brother to see
you dead in the sand, esse.
Oh, man...
Just fucking do it!
Fuck you!
Oh!
Come in!
Jesus!
You couldn't take that
crap off of your head?
She's six, for chrissake!
Oh, you think she's pick
you up out of a lineup?
Ai...
now I got to deal with this.
Come here, come here...
Hey there, little one,
don't cry, okay?
Everything's gonna be okay.
You must be Sophia, huh?
Would you get the hell out?
Where's Mommy?
We're going to see Mommy.
Have you ever been
on a helicopter before?
What the hell is this?
Don't stop, Jack,
keep driving.
Oh, my God, it's Nelson.
Nelson?
It's okay, buddy.
I got you, I got you.
It's gonna be okay, buddy.
I'm gonna get you
to the hospital.
- Don't talk.
- I'm sorry!
I'm sorry you had...
you were stuck with me...
- No.
- ...for a brother.
- No, man!
- I'm sorry.
No!
No, Nelson!
Jack...
Davie.
It's Gillian.
I'm coming for you.
No, not for me...
for little Sophia.
Mommy! Mommy?
Where's Mommy?
What is it?
Mommy, are you there?
Sophia!
Baby, it's gonna be all right.
Mommy!
We're coming for you.
Mommy?
It's okay.
It's okay!
You listen to me.
Shut up, Jack.
You and that bitch meet me
at the finish line downtown.
You give me the thumb drives,
I'll give you the kid.
These are my terms.
Help me get my brother.
And grab that gun.
Fuck, dude.
Fuck!
What the fuck, man?
Shit, first fucking place.
It's an ambush!
Oh!
You son of a bitch, come here.
Sophia!
Let her go!
This is for my brother,
you son of a bitch!
Jack, stop, goddamn it,
or she dies, too!
Let the girl go
and you and I will sort
the rest out, you hear me?
Give my brother the thumb
drives, and let him go.
Give me back my daughter!
Gimme the drives, Bianca.
Let the girl go and
I'll let Davie here go...
even trade.
These are my terms, Jack!
Give my brother the thumb drives
and let him go.
Don't hurt her, please!
Please, don't hurt her!
Where are the drives, Bianca?
Give her back to me!
If I was you, I would
shut up real fast.
Let her go!
Drop the gun!
Let go of the girl!
Drop your weapon!
Put your hands on the car!
Sophia! Sophia!
- Wait!
- You'll see your daughter.
Take her to the vehicle.
Are you Six-Speed Nina?
Yes. What the hell?
I'll kill your whole
fucking family, Jack.
Jack, what are they gonna do?
- Are you Bianca?
- That's my daughter!
That's what she's been
telling us over and over again.
Come here, honey.
You can sit in here, up front.
Mommy and Daddy
can ride in back.
It'll all be okay,
just sit tight.
- Hi, Mommy.
- Hi, sweetie.
Mommy, I wanna get out,
I don't wanna be
in any more cars.
You and me both, kid.