Surely you're acutely aware
who slew Shinji.
Well, well...
It appears you've stopped
averting your eyes from the truth.
But I'm afraid it will be no easy feat to destroy it
after it's been in my care for so many a year.
If I had my druthers, you would have
been the one to betray Sakura,
but I suppose my contingency plan proved useful.
Contingency plan?
It's yet to be fully awakened,
lying concealed underneath its human guise,
but perhaps it may have done a good deed for once.
Zouken, where's Sakura?
So, how's you-know-who doing?
You have my gratitude.
Once, she would merely accept
what came to pass, regardless of intentions.
But you taught her to desire others.
Now that it has killed its kinsman,
it can no longer contain itself.
The Einzberns' Holy Grail
has absorbed the soul of Archer,
but now she will move to steal it,
along with the key to the gate.
Zouken!
Now, accept the shadow, Sakura!
Very well, Grandfather.
Sakura...
Oh, right. I suppose you were here, too.
Sorry to say.
Unlike Shirou, I see zero reason to spare you.
It doesn't take a genius to figure out
your next move would be to kidnap Illya.
That's not very nice.
Do you think I'm that bad of a person?
Do you even need to ask?
There was someone who wanted nothing
but to protect Matou Sakura,
and you failed to believe in him to the bitter end.
Yes...
That's how it's been so far.
But I'm no longer the weak girl I used to be.
I'll protect Senpai now.
I'm stronger than him, after all.
Verschmelzen!
Now, now.
If you use that kind of magecraft,
you'll bring the whole house down.
Delicious...
So this is the taste of your mana.
But it's not enough.
You'll stand up.
Because you're a hero.
Sakura!
Senpai...
Tohsaka!
What happened here?
Why are you defending her?
Why won't you say anything?
Why won't you chastise me?
You saw what I did to Nii-san...
No!
Zouken set that—
No, he did not.
Look at me, Senpai.
I was insane from the very beginning.
Sakura...
Doesn't it hurt to be with me?
I had no other option but to leave you.
But I can't.
You're the only thing that makes me happy.
And you can't leave me, either.
You can't betray yourself
any more than you already have.
I'll put you out of your misery.
You won't have to suffer any longer,
and you'll never have to leave my side again.
I'm simply doing what you told me to, Sakura.
You ordered me to protect Emiya Shirou, no matter what.
You're a bad girl, Rider.
Sakura, you mustn't go there.
There is nothing there.
You will be nothing but dark and alone.
I'm here to stop you.
Sakura...
Your role ends here.
Rider, it's time to absorb you.
No!
I don't need any more,
but I'll be nice and make you like Saber.
That's enough, Sakura.
I'll go with you.
Illya!
Are you insane?
You're practically saying
you're fine with being killed.
There's no point resisting, right?
You're the strongest one here.
I'm the strongest...
The final key isn't here.
If you want to open the gate as the heir,
we have to go to my castle to get it.
Very well.
I'll fall for that.
Don't ever come see me again.
Next time, I'll have no choice but to kill you.
See you. It's been a lot of fun,
Mister.
Move, Saber!
What can you do as you are now?
One way or another, Sakura will obtain the Holy Grail,
even if it results in her death.
That shall be Matou Sakura's salvation.
This is your final warning.
If you remain steadfast in your pursuit,
I will have your head.
The battle has already been decided.
In fact, this outcome had been
predestined for a very, very long time.
This twisted Holy Grail War
should have had but one Holy Grail.
And yet, there was a second one in our midst.
That vessel was a match for the Holy Grail.
Or, more precisely, its contents.
Had the vessel not been suitable,
it would have merely become
an expanding mass of flesh.
The stage is set.
Only one can find the answer,
and its birth is nigh.
If it cannot be seen from the audience,
then I shall join the actors on stage.
Kotomine...
Save Tohsaka.
Are you awake?
Can you move your body?
Kotomine...
How's Tohsaka?
She was even more drained than you.
I buried her in the Tohsaka garden.
Huh?
Buried?
She should return to her usual, snappy self by dawn.
Okay, good.
You've been a lifesaver. I have to get going.
Where do you think you're going?
Illya went with Sakura to protect us.
So...
You have taken Matou Sakura
as your enemy, then?
Come with me.
Matou Zouken's objective is to possess
the empty shell of Matou Sakura.
As such, we must bring back Illyasviel
and defeat Matou Zouken
before Matou Sakura winds up a husk.
So far, our goals align.
Goals?
I'm saying I'm willing to aid you.
Oh, come to think of it! How's Rider?
Do not fall back on her.
Her path is still connected.
We must not let her catch wind of
our actions before we reach the castle.
And now, an update on the missing persons
incidents in Fuyuki City two nights ago.
The full extent and cause of the event
remain under investigation.
Authorities are looking into potential links
...concerning the widespread blackout near Shinto—
That man would have killed
Matou Sakura before it came to this.
Your father was a man who would repress
his human emotions in the name of justice.
His way of life was unpleasant to me.
He would cast off what was already there,
and I had nothing to cast off myself.
The outcome was homogeneous,
but the process couldn't have been more different.
That difference was what decided our battle.
If you're going to cast something off,
it is better not to have it in the first place.
And yet he continued to hold on to it.
Even after tossing it to the side,
he would pick it back up after.
Honestly, what a happy man he was.
Kiritsugu was happy?
Love thyself, love thy neighbor,
forgive others' sins, accept thy punishment,
and lead a healthy life.
All the things you people call happiness
failed to bring me joy.
That is all there is to it.
Why did you save Sakura that time?
All people eventually meet their maker.
If she were the only one approaching His throne,
I would not have gone as far as I did.
I intend to bless the birth of the darkness
residing within Matou Sakura's womb.
You mean that shadow?
But that thing kills people!
But it is not yet born.
Were it birthed, it would be just
to punish it for its crimes,
but I cannot deny it its birth.
Or do you claim the son of a criminal
is a criminal before birth?
Would you take their life?
Permit me to ask you a question.
It concerns Matou Sakura.
It is beyond doubt that she has cannibalized others.
Do you still intend to protect her?
She has killed a great many people.
I cannot imagine she herself would approve of that.
Then would she not be happier to be killed?
It would serve as atonement
for the lives she reaped.
But it wouldn't make up for anything.
I see.
Then you refuse to inherit Emiya Kiritsugu's ideals.
I'll check the place out.
Commence tuning.
Analyzing base framework.
Analyzing component materials.
The third floor...
The room on the left.
Sakura...
That is enough.
Do not confuse your priorities.
You don't need to tell me.
Now then, Emiya Shirou...
Do you have any bouldering experience?
Must we really ready the dress for those people?
Have you forgotten?
Our role is to complete the Holy Grail.
It doesn't need to be me.
It can be anyone so long as the vessel fits.
Who in their right mind
chucks people through windows?!
I could no longer bear the sight
of seeing you dangling by one arm.
And who are you people supposed to be?
Ruffians.
Ah, no, we're...
Shirou.
Illya—
What are you doing here?
Leave.
There's nothing left for you to do.
Let me deal with Sakura.
This is my part to play.
You stupid idiot.
What?
I don't care.
I don't care about that!
You can grandstand and pretend
you're all fine as much as you want,
but I'm not gonna let you fool me!
Who's grandstanding?
I'm the Holy Grail, so—
That's called grandstanding, idiot!
You're Illya before the Grail!
Don't go sacrificing yourself for some cause!
You're one to talk...
Illya.
This can't possibly turn out well.
We don't have time to dillydally.
Hey! Put me down!
Uhm, but...
This is our castle.
You have nothing to be concerned about.
Take good care of Illya.
Shirou?
It baffles me that you would drop
from that height without magecraft.
Are you that desperate?
Sue me! I thought I could do it.
Huh?
Archer must be leading the way.
So you came for me after all,
Senpai!
We're leaving.
He's fast!
But at this pace...
Berserker...
I suppose you aren't just a mere puppet.
Take her.
Emiya, when saving a lady, you must not kill.
Seeing death up close wears on the soul.
Let's go, Illya!
The white Holy Grail will not escape.
I, too, have a wish to see granted.
Is he looking at me?
Shirou, leave me behind and run.
Come on, I can't—
Hmm?
What a sight you are, Kirei.
Matou Zouken...
I see.
So you came to me.
The curtain is about to fall.
Do show him some mercy, Assassin.
There is little purpose in remembering this now,
but I was born incomplete.
Happiness, to me, was agonizing,
and despair was what brought me joy.
I knew that my way of being
was an inherent evil as a living being.
A detrimental fault, indeed.
Heretic that I was,
I still had a good head on my shoulders.
I prayed and strove to correct myself.
As my final effort, I loved a single woman.
Or rather, I wished to.
I attempted to love, and even sired a child.
And yet...
I was unable to love you.
No, you love me very much.
Noble Phantasm.
And so it ends.
You cur! You've—
Hmm?
Heed me.
I shall work damnation, I shall work salvation.
To inure to agony, to reprieve to hospitality.
Withheld from my grasp none shall be.
Withheld from my sight none shall be.
Curse you! Y-You fiend!
Crumble before me.
The agèd and the broken shall I welcome.
Yield before me, to be taught,
to be subjugated, and to be laid low.
Forget not your hymns, forget not your prayers,
and forget not my visage.
I am light, courier of your ultimate emancipation.
Ah, so you mean to kill me!
Within my palm lies final respite.
The inferno of your sins shall incise my sigil.
The grant of life eternal is bestowed only by death.
Absolution is at hand.
...Sworn upon my blood and my bone—
What will this accomplish?
There is no salvation for you.
Kýrie, eléison.
So you used the Word of the Bible
to attack his spirit directly.
You were pure poison to my magus.
And you...
have already been tainted, have you not?
Hmph. I made a grave error.
See? You're crying.
That was a misunderstanding.
Indeed, I was sad.
But I was not mourning that woman's death.
If you were to die regardless,
I would rather it had been by my hand.
Shirou?
You okay, Illya?
Yeah.
Shirou, run. Berserker's looking for me.
Shirou!
It's a brother's job to protect his little sister.
But I'm...
It's okay.
You're like a little sister to me now,
so I'll do my best to protect you.
That's what it means to be family.
Shirou, once you use Archer's arm,
there's no turning back.
Yeah.
You'll die.
No.
I'm using it so we can live.
Why...
Why do you have to go that far?
You haven't done anything wrong!
Nope, I've done plenty bad so far.
But, y'know...
Thanks.
I don't know what'll happen once I use this arm.
My vow to protect Sakura.
My resolve to bring Illya back.
I may end up forgetting everything.
But he gave me this arm because I needed it.
It's fine if I defeat him, right?
Yeah.
Think you can keep up with me?
That a serious question, pal?
Get over yourself!
You're the one who's gotta...
keep up with me!
Trace on!
Trigger off.
She's in your hands now.
Shirou.
Saber...
How does it feel?
I've claimed your heart as my own—literally.
Father Kotomine, you died ten years ago.
And yet you live to tell the tale because, uhh...
I ate the reason a little while ago...
It was that golden man bathed in
the contents of the Grail.
But he couldn't be tainted,
so it flowed straight into you, his Master.
Did I get that right?
How you've changed, Matou Sakura.
Yes, indeed I have.
I'm not the Matou Sakura you used to know.
That weak girl is no more.
No need to hide it.
Hide what?
You are no alternate personality.
Even drunk on violence as you are now,
you are the very same Matou Sakura.
You're the one who made me like this!
I won't deny it.
I saved your life.
And you've met my expectations.
Witnessing you give birth to Avenger
will be a sight to behold.
You easily did what I could not.
You think this is easy?
You have no idea how painful this is for me!
I don't, nor do I need to.
Berserker?
No! Don't come in!
You're in luck. Sakura is beckoning me.
Allow me to correct myself.
Your victory earned you this short reprieve.
I suppose.
Shirou!
Shirou...
It's okay.
Everything's okay.
Let's go home.
Must be because I used the arm...
Rise and shine, Shirou.
Tohsaka! How are you feeling?
Fresh as a daisy. How about you?
Well, I am glad you're still in one piece.
Isn't that...?
Oh, this...
It's precious to me.
I have to protect it.
Huh?
Wait, what did I just say?
That still has some mana in it.
Hold on to it.
It might come in handy one day.
Yeah, true...
Anyway, get yourself out of bed.
We've got errands to run.
As the last Masters involved in the Holy Grail War,
I'll give you nothing but the cold, hard facts.
I'm going to tell you about our core.
But it's nothing you two need to shoulder.
The Holy Grail War is a battle to the death
over the ownership of the Holy Grail,
using seven summoned Heroic Spirits.
But that is just a superficial rule.
It's just an excuse for Masters
to summon Servants to this world.
All the Holy Grail needs
to be complete are Heroic Spirits.
Their souls are collected by
the Holy Grail the Einzberns provide,
and they serve as the core
to activate the Greater Grail.
The Greater Grail?
It's a magic circle on the Tohsakas' land.
It manages the system of the Holy Grail War.
It all started three hundred years ago
when the three great families—
...the Einzberns, Makiris, and Tohsakas—
tried to use the power of
the Holy Grail to reach the outside world.
That is their true objective.
A sacred mystery thought to be lost to the Einzberns.
The ultimate boon that grants true immortality.
The Chalice of Heaven, Heaven's Feel.
Magic that materializes the soul.
From here on out is the part that involves you.
You mean Sakura? Tell us.
What's happening to Sakura?
Zouken has caused Sakura's metamorphosis
out of his desire to obtain something.
That something would be Avenger.
The eighth class of the Holy Grail War.
It's assimilated with Sakura and
now is projected as a "dark shadow".
Aŋra Mainiiu.
This story took place in a small Zoroastrian village.
The villagers pondered whether there was
a way for humanity to be freed from evil
and live pure and just lives.
So they chose a single, young man,
and burdened him with all the evils of the world.
That way, they could prove that
humanity was free from evil.
And thus, a single hero was born.
He was cursed by the people as evil,
yet also worshipped as a god.
He was somebody, yet nobody.
That person was the anti-hero, Aŋra Mainiiu.
In the third war, the Einzberns
summoned him as a Servant.
But he was too weak.
He was defeated early on
and absorbed into the Holy Grail.
When that happened,
the Holy Grail granted one wish.
He was born out of the people's wish for him to be evil.
Once he found himself within the Holy Grail,
that wish finally came true.
He embodied all the evils of the world,
and was capable of cursing
all six billion humans in the world.
That is the true form of the shadow.
Kiritsugu destroyed the Lesser Grail last time.
Because of that decision,
Aŋra Mainiiu failed to be born
and was left inside the Greater Grail.
Kotomine received a part of him,
and Zouken planted a fragment
of the Holy Grail's contents
into Sakura to create an artificial Holy Grail.
Whatever form Aŋra Mainiiu may take,
he is ultimately just a Servant.
So Zouken made Sakura a Master to subjugate him.
Masters and Servants...
It's uncertain whether we
have even half a day to spare.
Once that thing is born,
Sakura will never be the same.
Nobody will be able to save her,
and nobody will be safe from her.
Before we storm the enemy base,
there's something I'd like you to do, Shirou.
Honestly, the fact that you managed
to get Illya back here helps a ton.
I want you two to read the memories of the Einzberns
and the leyline running through this land
and use them to project a gem sword.
A gem sword?
A treasure unlike any other,
passed down through the Tohsaka line.
And it's what'll help us fight back against Sakura.
Okay.
This is an Azoth dagger
that looks like the gem sword.
I've poured ten years' worth of mana into it.
Use it to help with the projection.
Shirou, be honest. How long can you last?
I don't know, myself.
But so long as I'm still alive, I'll manage somehow.
I'll be fine.
Cast off your idle thoughts.
Don't look at anything you don't have to.
O-Okay...
The ocean?
Shirou!
Shinji?
No...
It's not here. Let's jump forward.
Just a little further. Let's go.
Uhh...
For the eradication of all evil, you all—
We finally made it.
Shirou, don't take your eyes off him.
I shall have faith in those ideals.
To reach the Root, Tohsaka, Einzbern, and
Makiri shall work together and pave the way.
Now, what shall you each provide?
Tohsaka will provide the sacred ground
for the construction of the Holy Grail.
Makiri will provide the Command Spells
to bind the sacrificial Servants.
Einzbern will provide the circle for the Third Magic.
Very well.
I, Kischur Zelretch Schweinorg,
will serve as the witness.
You may begin.
Let the gate leading to the Root
now open...
Let it open.
Let it open...
Shirou!
You're in bad shape, Emiya Shirou.
Rider...
I have been keeping watch over you.
I've been tasked with
the protection of Emiya Shirou.
But you've created a weapon to use against Sakura.
So long as you seek to harm Sakura,
I cannot protect you.
So you've come to kill me?
Shirou.
Sakura summoned me without a catalyst.
Under such circumstances,
the Servant most similar to the Master is chosen.
I didn't want Sakura to end up becoming a monster.
But it's too...
Shirou, if your aim is to make Sakura suffer...
I'm not trying to kill her.
I'm trying to save her.
I'll protect Sakura to the very end.
No matter what happens, I choose Sakura.
Is that...
the answer to the question I once asked you?
There's someone I have to defeat
to accomplish my goal.
I want your help.
You have reason to believe you can win, yes?
Yeah.
Very well.
I, the Servant Rider, albeit temporarily,
swear to become your wings
and take you to the ends of the earth.
And here I thought you came back.
But you sent your shadow out to run your
errands instead. Oh, how you've grown, Sakura.
Nee-san, take Senpai and run.
If you do, I can take the child down with me.
Sakura, let me ask you something.
Do you have any plans to
sever your ties with Aŋra Mainiiu?
No.
I've got my hands on so much power.
I don't want to let go of it.
Not that I could, even if I wanted to.
Are you saying that if I take Shirou and run,
you can self-destruct and take Aŋra Mainiiu with you?
Yes.
So...
No. What you actually mean is,
"I don't know how long I can hold out".
Have you noticed?
For a while now, everything you've said
and done has been all over the place.
One second, you say you want to
take him down with you,
and the next, you say
you don't want to let go of him.
Don't get your panties in a bunch.
We're coming to see you soon.
I'll find you, and I will kill you.
Yes. I'll be waiting, Nee-san.
Nee-san...
You've done well to return, Assassin.
My lord, are you well?
Naturally. But in my current state,
I cannot conjure any mana to send you.
Sakura, apologies for the burden,
but form a contract with Assassin.
Sakura.
Lord magus, this woman is already...
Yes, the curtain fell all too quickly.
Then shall I deal with her as we planned?
You make it sound so bad.
We do this because we have no other choice.
Farewell, Sakura.
For an experiment, you did well to last this long,
and you did well to entertain me.
There will be no need for that.
Oh?
Hmm?
Well, how about that.
You never had a face in the first place.
Curse... you...
You never had an identity.
You can never become the single, genuine article.
My... name... is...
Wh-What are you doing, Sakura?
What's wrong?
You don't need him to protect you
anymore, right, Grandfather?
Wh-Wha—
I always wondered why you were so important to me
and why you could do with me as you pleased.
So I did some research.
You'd taken the place of
a portion of my nervous system.
I'd always assumed you to be bigger, Grandfather.
Wait... Wait, Sakura!
Farewell, Grandfather.
Now Nii-san and Grandfather are gone.
Now...
I can...
do what, exactly?
Not yet.
They still live.
They are coming.
Go. Let Nee-san alone come here.
What of Emiya Shirou?
Ah... K...
I swear. I can't believe...
how precious Sakura was to me.
I guess this is it, then. Off you go.
Rin.
Rider.
Shirou.
Illya.
If you don't have anywhere to go
once this battle is over,
would you like to live here with me?
Trying to take Kiritsugu's place?
No, Kiritsugu and I are two different people.
But I—
Shirou, squat down.
Uh, sure...
I'll be waiting for you, Shirou.
You'd better be back with Sakura by sunrise.
Got it.
I sense a field of some sort
being constructed in the pond above us.
That's the outward-facing gate.
If we want to get to the Greater Grail...
We have to go down, not up.
Down...
Shirou?
Uh, nothing.
Don't let your guard down.
Prioritize your life above all else.
Saber.
Rin.
Oh, I get it.
Sakura's serious.
Sorry. I gotta go on ahead.
If you want to save Sakura,
you'd better not be late.
Saber, you're not gonna let us through, are you?
Silence. This is my duty.
If I go all-out, I can contend with her for two minutes.
I will give you your opportunity.
You must stay put. Don't miss your chance.
Saber.
This is where you die.
I have to save Sakura,
and you're in the way.
This is the Greater Grail...
I see you came instead of running away.
I've been thinking.
I hate this world.
My house, you, my grandfather...
My miserable brother, the peaceful town...
I can't forgive anything
that has refused to save me so far.
I know they don't deserve my wrath.
I know this is unfair.
But I'm strong now.
There's nothing I can't do.
That so? Gotten used to the murderer lifestyle?
Yes. Assassin and Grandfather have left this world.
All that's l—
But what about Shirou?
Even now, he believes he can save you.
He is the only one I want to kill.
Great. You gave up on your humanity a long time ago.
You're bluffing.
You're jealous of my power, aren't you?
You want to take it for yourself and
become happy all on your own again.
Well, you can't have it.
All I have to give you is regret and despair.
Now drown in the Chalice of Heaven
like an insect in a lake.
This is...
A Mystic Eyes' curse!
Rider, I have a question for you.
About Saber...
Do you really have to be a Servant to injure her?
No. Servants captured by Sakura have incarnated.
With a powerful Mystic Code, I suspect...
One more question. About our strategy...
Yes, I believe that plan could work.
Right?
The problem is...
Our trust in each other, Shirou.
Are you able to remain motionless
when an ally is in danger?
I must ask you to do what you hate most.
I trust you!
Worried about Shirou?
He isn't moving.
He trusts me.
Oh, just like he used to trust...
Cease your drivel!
This isn't enough to stop me!
Noble Phantasm!
Come at me!
Commence projection!
Search. Select.
Parse!
I am the bone of my sword.
Rho...
Ex...
...Aias!
...calibur!
Bellero...
...phon!
Shirou?
Thank you.
You've saved me more times than I can count.
I'm going ahead. Once you can run, come after me.
You work people harder than I expected.
Why, you...
No...
How?
You have to ask?
I'm simply comparing our strength.
That... There's something about that sword!
You can't tell, Sakura?
This is the Jeweled Sword Zelretch,
passed down through the Tohsaka family.
It connects to infinite parallel worlds
and channels mana through them.
Huh?
Zelretch?
You've gotta be kidding me.
You don't know who Zelretch is?
Don't make fun of me!
It doesn't matter how many of those
you've got stored up.
Your instantaneous mana output
isn't much different from mine.
All I have to do is fire an equal
amount of mana to neutralize it.
That ridiculous mana pool
is a treasure wasted on you!
No fair.
No fair...
Has your head cooled down a bit
from all that hot air you were spouting?
This isn't fair.
Why?!
I'm your sister, but nobody ever treated me as human!
The Makiri family's magecraft was engraved
on my body. My meals were poisoned.
The mere act of eating was scary and painful for me.
When I was in the bug room,
I needed permission just to breathe.
Whenever I cried, those people took joy in it
and kept messing with my body!
Meanwhile, you were shining bright as a star.
I hated you for growing up without knowing hardship.
I wanted to beat you.
Just once, I wanted you to praise me
and tell me I did well.
I used to be a daughter of the Tohsaka family.
So I thought you'd come to save me one day!
But you never did!
It's been eleven painful years.
It was enough to drive me insane.
But is this really my fault?
Day after day, all I felt was pain...
I didn't ask to end up like this!
I was driven into a corner.
Yeah, so what?
Huh?
I mean, it doesn't hurt now, does it?
Why do you have to be like that?
I don't really get other people's pain.
So no matter what horrible things
you've been through,
I don't really care to understand.
However, Sakura,
even for how insensitive I am,
I never once thought
that I was blessed.
How dare you...
How dare you say that?!
Sakura.
End of the World
Welt Ende.
Oh. This ain't good.
Nee-san?
I'm a grade-A idiot.
But I can't stand it when the hard workers
don't get rewarded for their efforts.
And I love you.
I always wanted you to be happy.
I wanted to believe that the harder things were
for me, the easier they'd be for you.
Guess I don't have the right to call Shirou out on that.
When I saw you up close,
I realized I couldn't kill you.
Sorry your sister's so selfish.
And... that ribbon...
I'm glad you always wore it.
I had it.
I had it, too...
But I
destroyed it...
Senpai...
...her.
I killed her...
I killed Nee-san...
She always encouraged me to win, and I...
No.
I have to stop.
Looks like Tohsaka won.
Sakura, Tohsaka isn't dead!
She can still be saved!
We can still save her!
No! Run, Senpai!
Ah, no...
No, Senpai, I...
I know.
That little brat's throwing a temper tantrum!
Senpai! Take Nee-san and run!
No... I can't keep it in.
Run, Senpai!
Stop this.
I just have to die.
I can die on my own!
Why?
I can't be saved.
No, I shouldn't be saved!
I'm saving you!
Sakura...
Look. Can't you see, Senpai?
Th-This is who I am.
So...
I've killed so many people.
Nii-san, Grandfather...
Even Nee-san...
And you still...
You still want me to live?!
Yes!
Of course I do!
You have to take responsibility for what you took!
Senpai...
I don't know where your sins lie
or how heavy your punishment will be.
But I will protect you.
I'll protect you from everything that comes your way.
Even if it makes me a hypocrite,
I'll protect the girl I love!
Trace on.
Time for your punishment.
This is gonna hurt, so grit your teeth!
Yes.
Let's go home, Sakura.
Time to cut your ties with him.
Guess it's not stopping...
Shirou.
Oh, it's you. Great timing.
Can you grab Tohsaka down there
and take her and Sakura outside?
Uhh...
R... R...
Very well.
Thanks.
A-Also...
Give this... to Sakura.
That should be for you to...
Never mind.
Good luck.
Kotomine Kirei.
Yes. It would appear we both
made it by the skin of our teeth.
Emiya Shirou.
That thing won't grant you your wish,
even if you manage to get it out.
Quite the contrary.
It is my sole wish to witness the birth of this curse.
Why? Why are you so desperate to protect it?
It's the very definition of evil.
It is not evil yet.
Neither is it good.
Humans learn what is correct from a blank slate.
It all starts at zero.
At zero, there is nothing but the fact of existence.
If responsibility lies with someone,
it lies with the environment that human is raised in
and the ego within them.
When a life wishes to hatch,
allowing it to do so is an act of love.
Love, my ass.
That is how I see it, Emiya Shirou.
Just as you derive pleasure
from the happiness of others,
I derive pleasure from the misfortune of others.
What an irksome body.
Simply attacking requires
putting my life at stake.
You consider it evil to kill a man?
You, who wish to protect Matou Sakura?
That is what Man is.
Evildoers who perform acts of goodness in jest.
Saints who commit acts of evil on a whim.
This contradiction is what makes us human.
The act of living bears both good and evil.
But this thing only ever existed to kill!
Yes, exactly!
But we still don't know what he himself thinks of this!
Will he lament himself as evil
or praise himself as good?
If one who was wished to be as such
bears no doubts toward his own functions,
then he is not evil.
If he is born, he will surely kill without end,
exactly as he was created to.
And when only he remains, will he forgive himself?
I want to know.
That's why you're doing this?!
Yes. That is my goal.
Emiya Shirou.
Your wish is one of self-sacrifice.
I am your antithesis.
But our desires are the same!
Oh, so that's how it is.
We both consider ourselves sinners,
and we chose a single
way of life to seek absolution.
No wonder you wouldn't pull back.
In all honesty, I realize my anger is misdirected.
I am envious of all of you.
Yeah? Guess I wasted your time.
I care not.
You are low on time as well.
I don't want to die.
I don't...
Answer me, my sworn enemy.
Why did you wish not to die?
For the eradication of all evil,
you all required a miracle.
The world of man holds no salvation.
If we cannot rid ourselves of evil
so long as we are human...
If paradise cannot be reached by mere humans...
We need strive for that which transcends humans—
a new form for humanity.
Yes, to purge all evils from this world,
we shall stake our lives on this one wish.
Our five hundred-year aspirations
ultimately lasted but the blink of an eye.
Shame...
I was just one step away.
To think it came down to a simple matter of timing...
You are the final Master.
Fulfill your duty.
This... This is the last one.
My last projection.
Is...
Is this what I want?
Nope. You won't die.
I'll be the one to close the gate.
Do you want to live?
No matter what your life is,
no matter what form it takes,
do you want to live?
Wait, no...
You don't...
I'll deal with...
I'll take him...
Do you want to live?
...live.
I want to live!
Good.
No, w—
Come back...
I'll show you a miracle.
This is gonna be great.
After all, it's true magic.
I don't care.
So come back.
Damn, your name. Your name...
It's the brother's job to protect
their little sisters, isn't it?
...ya...
Yes.
I'm your big sister.
Guess I have to protect my baby brother.
Illya!
Illya. Illya.
Illya! Illya! Illya! Illya!
Illya!
Senpai...
Now that's our captain-in-line for ya!
Looks like I can retire in peace.
Yeah.
When will he come home?
The Holy Grail War in this land has concluded.
The Greater Grail collapsed, ending it all for good.
In the aftermath, I ran myself ragged
dealing with the Mages' Association
while I waited for Sakura to recover.
I want to take back the eleven years we spent apart,
so I walk with her now that our time has resumed.
Yes.
Our time without him.
The body of Emiya Shirou has vanished.
Sakura, Rin is home.
Okay. Thanks, Rider.
How've you been lately, Sakura?
Well, it's been slow going,
but I can accept a lot of things
for what they are now.
I've learned that getting crushed
under my sins is just a form of escapism.
Some things have changed,
and some still need to change.
What basis do I have to say that I've changed?
I still don't know.
I'm still looking for a path forward.
But...
In this ever-changing world,
there's something that hasn't changed one bit.
What's wrong, Sakura?
Nothing.
Come on, let's go.
I swear, you're so chipper.
Hey.
Sakura, are you happy?
Yes.
Zabaniya!
My body and mind give in
to the crawl of nothingness.
Why am I here?
Why did it come to this?
Why do I fight?
Shooting the Hundred Heads
Nine Lives Blade Works!
Delusional Heartbeat
Zabaniya!
✦
Melt
Delusional Heartbeat
May the Lord Have Mercy on This Soul
My body and mind give in
to the crawl of nothingness.
Why am I here?
Why did it come to this?
Why do I fight?
Shooting the Hundred Heads
The Seven Rings...
...that Cover the Fiery Heavens
Sword of...
...Promised Victory
Bridle of...
...Chivalry
Despite everything, take my hand
sore demo te wo totte
Stay by my side
tonari ni tatazunde
Bring back the time you first held me
hajimete dakishimeta katachi
My desires have washed grief over us
yokubatte kanashimi wo kakae sugiteita kara
The feeling of joy you have given me
shiawase wa doko ni mo
I can't carry it anywhere anymore
mou mochi kirenakute
The wind scatters the petals
hanabira wo chirashita kaze ga
And welcomes us into a new spring
tobira wo hiraite kawaru kisetsu
Within the ever-growing sands of time
shinshin to furitsumoru toki no naka
Happiness and sadness turn to one
yorokobi mo kurushimi mo hitoshiku
They melt within the palms of you and I
My smile and my atonement
Rest by your side
Perishing is just one more thing
That I can't do on my own
The selfish coward that I am
As I carry this redeemable shadow
There, in our promised land
The flowers are in full bloom
Spring comes closer without a care for either love or sin
Shining through with its dazzling light
Please, do not forgive me
I want to be broken, be born yet again
This time by your side
I'm smiling
At least tell those important to me
That I'm always living in happiness
Please deliver them these sweet dreams
I am by your side
I am in love with you
I am here with you
By your side
Those days were just like a dream
futari no tenohira de tokete yuku
hohoemi mo aganai mo
anata no soba de
kiesatte yuku koto mo
hitori de wa dekinakute
yowamushi de migatte na watashi
tsugunaenai kage wo seotte
yakusoku no basho wa
hana no sakari
tsumi mo ai mo kaerimizu haru wa yuku
kagayaki wa tada sora ni mabushiku
watashi wo yurusanaideite kureru
kowaretai umaretai
anata no soba de
warau yo
semete soba ni iru daiji na hitotachi ni
itsumo watashi wa shiawase de iru to
yasashii yume wo todokete
anata no soba ni iru
anata wo aishiteru
anata to koko ni iru
anata no soba ni
sono hibi wa yume no you ni
Aniplex, Notes, and ufotable
present
a ufotable production
Ryuudou
Temple