Emiya Shirou is pretty good.
Ain't he?
And along with Mitsuzuri Ayako and Matou Shinji,
we've got the Rookie Competition in the bag.
Yup!
But Fujimura-sensei, well...
Hmm?
Even among the first-years, Emiya feels kinda...
I dunno, different, I suppose?
I have a hard time articulating it.
You got hurt at work right before the tournament?
The hell, man?
Swear to god. Everyone's gonna be
off their game now. You know that, right?
I'm sorry.
But you and Mitsuzuri should be
able to handle it, no sweat.
Sorry.
I'm home.
Commence tuning.
Analyzing base framework.
Analyzing component materials.
Altering base framework.
Reinforcing component materials.
Is it raining?
Aren't you Shinji's little sister?
Yes. My name is Matou Sakura.
Shirou! I'm here to check up on you!
How you holding up?
I can explain!
Look, it's not what it looks like!
I mean, I've been able to get by
on my own just fine, y'know?
I can hardly put my friend's sister to work now, can I?
As Shirou's guardian, I also have my reservations...
I'm there to save his butt from all the chores,
so it's okey-dokey on that front!
Oh dear, what a coincidence!
We just happened to run into each other!
Now, on to today's stories—
The dishes go in the top cupboard.
The bottom one is for the rice, knives, and, uh...
Wh—Stop!
You fold the shoulder around the back,
then line the sleeve up parallel to the crease.
Finally, you do the other side,
and make sure it doesn't come unfolded...
Don't sweat it. Practice makes perfect.
Let me try again.
All right, from the top.
I'll be on my way.
See ya tomorrows, Sakura-chan!
Oops.
Yeah, I remember now.
One day a year and a half ago,
I had to give up on convincing a certain stubborn girl.
The season came and went.
My shoulder had finally healed,
but our new lifestyles stuck.
I can't remember which of us suggested it anymore.
Regardless, it was probably a trivial matter.
If there's one thing that changed,
it'd be that I stopped going to club.
I wanted to work more hours instead,
and I only really joined to stay in shape anyway,
so it felt like a good opportunity to quit.
And finally, and this may seem
pretty minimal all things considered,
I'm home.
Welcome home, Senpai!
I found myself rarely using my own key anymore.
Ho-ho-ho! Merry Christmas!
Lemme tell ya...
Shirou was always copying Kiritsugu-san.
Always going, "I'm gonna be a superhero!"
What's this about now? I swear, drunk people.
Kiritsugu-san was Senpai's father, yes?
Kiritsugu-san was Shirou's hero.
No wonder he wanted to be just like him.
You must have someone
you look up to too, right?
My hero...
Senpai!
Hey, Emiya.
Oh. 'Sup, Issei.
Well, if it ain't Emiya!
Help us scout some new recruits, will ya?
Hmm? Who's this?
Oh, this is Shinji's sister.
Ooh, for realsies?
Why, hello there! You into archery?
Your brother does it, so you've gotta be, yeah?
Oh, you're...?
Sakura...
Sakura! Great!
How's it sound? Wanna join the archery club?
Or you eyeing another club already?
N-No...
Perfecto! Come join us, then!
Geez. Pushy as ever.
C'mon, what's the hol'-up? Let's go!
What's wrong, Emiya?
Nothing...
Hey, Shirou!
Thanks a bunch, teach!
You know you're a teacher too, right?
Senpai?
Oh, it's nothing.
Okay, everyone. Say "cheese"!
Trace on.
Ugh, that's another one I've gotta take apart...
Sakura-chan, what's for dinner tonight?
They had some good eggplants,
so I was thinking of making arrabbiata.
Ooh, sounds good!
Oh. Here it comes again.
The flames lap away at my old memories,
as if to forbid me from retaining them.
Whenever I dream,
this is the scene I always end at.
Which means I'm waking up soon.
Senpai.
Good morning.
Morning, Sakura.
You really don't have to come over
every single day, y'know?
You have your own life to attend to.
It's fine, really.
I don't really have any hobbies
outside of cooking and archery, anyway.
Speaking of which, my current goal
is to best you at cooking.
It won't be long until I surpass you.
Oh, yeah?
You saying you've been learning my secrets?
Absolutely. I hope you're ready.
Besides, I can't really enjoy food anymore
unless I'm eating at your place.
C'mon, get a move on. We'd better hurry
if you want to make it to morning practice.
Emiya, are you going out with Matou's sister?
Huh?
Well, I saw you enjoying yourselves
on your way to school together.
Come on, she's my friend's sister.
Get real.
Heck, if you saw me, you should've said hi.
Unfortunately, I am still in training.
Such daring advances are far beyond me.
Whatever.
Anyway, I'm done with this one.
Morning, Shinji.
Hey, Emiya.
Starting the day strong by
sticking your nose where it doesn't belong?
You've got some weird hobbies.
Well, I've got nothing better to do.
If you ever need help with something,
just say the word.
You've always had a rough time
stringing and fixing bows, right?
Emiya, you're through with the archery club, right?
Don't you think it'd be in your best interests
to mind your own business?
First off, pronunciation.
Even if it's spelled the same way,
the pronunciation may differ.
It's super easy to get it wrong,
so keep your eyes peeled!
Emiya, wanna have lunch?
Sorry. I'm going to the cafeteria today.
Oh, Sakura—
Sakura.
Hello, Senpai!
That girl you were talking to...
Oh, she's a second-year. Her name is Tohsa—
Tohsaka, right? Tohsaka Rin.
Do you know her?
Well, you know, she's kinda famous here.
She always stands out.
You're right.
Tohsaka-senpai's so pretty, so gallant...
Sakura?
Senpai, are you ever going to
come back to the archery club?
I dunno.
I don't think Shinji would be all too pleased.
I think you just rub him the wrong way.
But still, he likes you much more than anyone else.
He can be hard to understand.
His favorite people are those he hates the most.
That's one heck of a personality.
Good night, Senpai.
Are those bug noises?
But it's the middle of winter.
Well, well.
I hear you've done a great deal
for my granddaughter.
Uhm, I'm sorry! My name is Emiya Shirou.
I'm in Shinji's class.
Emiya...
Is the Einzberns' daughter in good health?
Huh?
This dream again.
This is the part before Kiritsugu saves me.
If you don't summon yours soon,
you'll die, Mister.
Now on to our next story.
Late last night, a large-scale gas leak
occurred in the office district of Shinto.
Perfect.
Sakura, can you get me a plate?
Sure.
Everything okay back there?
Sakura, you sure you're okay?
You haven't had a single bite yet.
You can skip morning practice if you want.
Even the club advisor says it's okay.
No, I'm fine.
Senpai, I have a favor to ask of you.
Could you please try to come home
from school as soon as possible today?
This just in:
Four victims were found dead in the
residential district of Miyama Town, Fuyuki City.
Preliminary reports from the Fuyuki Police Department
state that they were all found with stab wounds.
The police are currently...
Emiya.
Emiya!
Mornin', Emiya.
Morning, Mitsuzuri.
Emiya, have you heard about the murders
that took place in Miyama Town last night?
Murders?
Did they catch the perp?
No, not yet.
It'll be best if we suspend all
after-school activities for a while.
Excuse me.
Ryuudou, can I borrow you?
Of course.
Sorry, Emiya. We can continue this conversation later.
Well, well. If it isn't Emiya.
This isn't your classroom anymore, is it?
What might you be doing here?
Shinji...
I thought club was canceled today.
Club or no club, I'm a busy man.
I've got things to do.
Hey, why don't you—
Try not to give Mitsuzuri too much trouble, okay?
Where'd that come from?
An outsider has no business butting in like that.
That reminds me, Emiya!
Mind doing me a solid?
Sure. What is it?
Just some dumb clean-up
after that dumb archery club.
Isn't that supposed to be your job?
I'm a busy man, remember?
But you should be free, right?
So help a fella out,
Emiya.
Sure. Consider it done.
That so?
Have fun then, Mister Goody Two-Shoes.
After-school club activities
have been suspended for the day.
All faculty and students are to leave
the school grounds by six PM.
Come on, let's go home.
'Kay!
See you tomorrow!
See ya!
Hey, let's stop by that place!
Sure, I've been meaning to for a while now!
Let's go!
Might've gotten a little too into it.
Guess I'm done here.
What the...
Who's there?!
What the hell? What the hell was that?!
I've gotta get outta here...
If I don't,
I'm dead!
Yo.
Pitiful. This summoning was much
too incomplete, much too sloppy.
Though the actors have finally been selected,
their positions and stage remain yet unarranged.
This Holy Grail War is a far cry
from the grand ritual we once sought.
However, once it has begun, it cannot be stopped.
If water fills the chalice, someone must drink it.
But as fortune would have it, the supervisor
from the Church is none other than that priest.
He will mediate this twisted Grail War well.
The Grail calls forth Heroic Spirits,
and the very same Heroic Spirits require contractors.
If one is swept up into this ritual,
their fate is to kill or be killed.
There need only be one survivor.
The seventh Servant to be summoned
was that very same Saber.
And her Master is the son of Emiya.
Truly, a match only fate could entertain.
The Church is a neutral zone.
I cannot move against him.
Now, will that man be a saint worthy of
preaching the gospel, or will he prove otherwise?
You coming, Emiya-kun?
I haven't the slightest why a failure of a magus
like you was chosen to be a Master,
but the man we're about to meet will explain
how the Grail War functions to you.
You've gotta be careful around him, though.
He's a bit of a creep.
And here I thought you would never
respond to my repeated summons.
Yet here you come,
with a rather peculiar guest in tow.
Am I right to presume he is the seventh?
I am Kotomine Kirei,
the man entrusted with this church.
Emiya Shirou?
Am I correct in assuming
that you are Saber's Master?
Saber did save me, yes.
But if you want a proper magus,
I'm not the guy you're looking for.
So you wish for us to pick another Master?
Interesting.
Then I imagine you have no interest in learning
about the events that transpired here ten years ago?
The Holy Grail holds omnipotent power
in the world of magi.
A vessel that can grant any wish without restraint.
The chosen Masters fought,
slaughtering one another to obtain it.
As a result, an unfortunate accident occurred.
An accident large enough to be deemed a disaster.
Are you telling me that was...
Yes. A great happening that
weighs upon the hearts of all in this city.
Five hundred casualties. One hundred and
thirty-four buildings burned to the ground.
That raging inferno
whose cause is yet deemed unknown
was a scar left behind by the Holy Grail War.
Emiya-kun!
Kirei, I told you to explain the rules!
Not open up old scars!
Is this Holy Grail thing the real deal?
In the last war, there was a man who
obtained the Holy Grail, albeit temporarily.
What happened to him?
Absolutely nothing.
That Holy Grail had not achieved completion.
The Holy Grail will not avail itself
to a man who avoids battle.
You make it sound like you were there.
Why, that's because I was.
I participated as a Master and fought
for the Holy Grail during those times.
Hang on, are you for real?!
I fought until partway through the war.
However, at the time I had made
a crucial error in judgment.
As a result, I walked away
with merely an empty Grail.
What do you mea—
Our conversation has only just matured,
but we have a rather impatient guest at the door.
Hey, have you heard of the Einzberns?
And thus, young man, the time is nigh.
What shall your decision be?
Emiya-kun!
If the Grail War really was
the cause of that disaster ten years ago,
then I'll...
I'll fight.
I'll fight as a Master!
Rejoice, young man.
Your wish will be granted at last.
Every superhero needs a villain to defeat.
Well, I suppose a Servant wouldn't remember.
Are you done chatting?
Good evening, Mister.
I'm Illya.
Illyasviel von Einzbern.
I appreciate the manners.
Okay, time to kill you.
Get them, Berserker.
Saber!
Run...
Please, just run!
Of all the times to not have Archer around!
That's the spirit, Berserker!
She regenerates, so lop off her head
and have your way with her!
What the hell am I doing?
Wait, stop!
No way.
Why?
This is so boring.
Master!
God, what is wrong with you?!
When I was a kid, I wanted to be a superhero.
But being a hero comes with a time limit.
Once you're an adult,
it becomes harder to call yourself one.
Kiritsugu...
And to add to that, being one person's hero
means being another person's villain.
What do I have to do to become a superhero?
Huh?
I'm not wounded?
Master.
Are you all right?
Bright-eyed and bushy-tailed now?
Tohsaka...
Did you fix me up?
No, you healed those wounds by your own power.
As if. I can't do anything crazy like that.
Then perhaps your contract with Saber
is affecting your body somehow.
First things first, let's hear your excuse
for that stunt you pulled.
I mean, I did nothing wrong.
It just didn't go as well as...
Us Servants can only exist because of
the mana provided by our Masters.
If that source were to cease,
it would render us unable to subsist.
Oh, I didn't know.
Well, now you do.
Anyway, I'm gonna get going.
I need to go treat my own Servant.
Oh, and just so we're clear:
Next time we meet, it'll be as enemies.
She has a good heart.
What about your injuries, Saber? Are you okay?
Yes, though I'd hesitate to say I'm in perfect condition.
Uhm, do you want the Holy Grail, too?
Yes. It's why I'm here.
Berserker's Master said
her name was "Einzbern", right?
Didn't think they'd drag little kids into this.
Saber?
Someone is using magecraft nearby.
I do not sense Berserker.
It's a different party entirely.
Master, your orders?
Let's check it out.
Keep your guard up.
A bounded field has been erected.
Where have I felt this before?
M-Mitsuzuri?
Mitsuzuri!
Now this is a surprise.
Wasn't expecting to see you here, Emiya.
What are you...
Oh, you wondering about this?
I guess you could say we had
our dear president do us a little favor.
Shinji?
Is that thing your Servant?
Let me do the honors!
Say hello to my Servant.
Let's have 'em fight, Emiya.
I've always wanted to see two Servants duke it out!
What? You're a Master, Shinji?
The Matous are an old and noble lineage of magi.
Hell, in the grand scheme of the Holy Grail War,
we're one of the three great families.
It kills me to let a bumbling idiot
like you in on that, though.
It's obvious that I, the eldest son,
would be a player in this war, is it not?
Shinji!
Man, you really gotta learn to take a hint!
Need me to spell it out for you?
This is a game we're all playing for keeps!
Fuck 'em up, Rider!
Huh?
Uhm...
Hey.
Who told you you could lose, huh?
Stand up.
C'mon.
Get up already!
You're making me look inferior, jackass!
Wh-What the hell? Why?
Dammit!
Stop! Go out!
Go—
Shinji!
It seems the burden was too much
for you to bear, Shinji.
This is as far as the Matous go.
What a shame, indeed.
You're...
Grandfather! Wait!
I'm a magus of the Matou family! I'll...
Once incompetent, always incompetent.
The Matou bloodline has fallen from grace.
I never had any expectations for you in particular.
"You in particular"?
Wait! Hold on!
You're not making Sakura do this stuff, are you?!
Why the hell would you bring her up?
I'm all we need.
That bitch knows fuck-all about magecraft!
The teachings of the Matous are mine and mine alone!
Mitsuzuri!
She is a victim of the Holy Grail War, so the proper course
of action would be to leave her with the supervisor.
Oh, dear. I did not expect you to return so soon.
Fascinating.
You appear to be entranced
by an affliction most vile.
Huh?
I shall put her in my care for now.
I see you stayed.
How's Mitsuzuri?
I have finished treating her.
There is no need to worry.
In fact, you appear to be much worse off than she is.
I'm fine now.
In the war ten years ago,
there was a man who stood against me
despite suffering lethal wounds, like yourself.
He was the man who fought me at the very end,
as well as the man who would become
the victor of the previous Holy Grail War.
His name was Emiya Kiritsugu.
Saber.
Mitsuzuri's gonna pull through.
That is a relief.
That took a considerable amount of time.
Yeah...
He told me about Kiritsugu. My father.
Master,
there's something I must tell you.
The man known as Emiya Kiritsugu
was, in a word, a hitman.
He made it his livelihood
to assassinate magi exclusively.
All magi are unbound by
the ethics of the world at large,
but even among them, he was atypical.
Last time, I was called to this time period
and fought as the Einzberns' Servant.
My Master's name at the time was Emiya Kiritsugu.
But...
He truly never did shed blood or tears.
He would stop at nothing to secure his goal.
Even face-to-face with a foe begging
for their life, he would show no mercy.
During the war, Kiritsugu considered
that priest his greatest foe.
A fitting descriptor for us.
We had little option but to kill each other.
He and I fought in the Holy Grail War
and were triumphant in the end.
But then he...
Emiya Kiritsugu betrayed
the Holy Grail at the very end.
He destroyed the Holy Grail.
Kill the one to save the ten.
He was the epitome of an unsalvageable saint.
Even so, the Kiritsugu I knew would never
abandon the victims of the Grail War.
I've always looked up to superheroes like him.
That's why I'll fight.
I should've said this sooner, but Saber,
I want you to fight by my side.
Regardless of my past, the Command Spells
bind me to my current Master.
Yeah.
If you're cool with it, you can call me Shirou.
Then Shirou it is.
Yes, I do prefer calling you that.
Thanks.
Ready to head home?
Yes.
Wow, you knew Kiritsugu-san?
What a tragedy though,
what with your luggage arriving late...
Sorry you have to use Shirou's hand-me-downs.
Oh, it's no trouble at all.
Kiritsugu-san's such a lady-killer.
He traveled abroad a lot, and now I get why.
Ooh! You have any fun memories
you'd like to share with the class?
Uhm... Well...
Sorry that this came kinda outta nowhere, Sakura.
I don't mind.
So, uhm...
Did you see Shinji this morning?
Yes. Why are you asking?
No real reason. Just making sure everything's okay.
Sakura.
Uhm, Senpai...
Sakura, that bruise...
Was it Shinji?
Emiya-kun.
You've got balls, coming to school
without your Servant.
Do you not think of me as a threat?
Let's make a deal, Tohsaka! I need your help!
Huh?
Uh... Huh?
So to recap: Shinji's a Master,
Ayako was attacked, and Rider's gone...
So? That's not the entire story, is it?
Shinji has a sister.
Her name is Sakura.
What about her?
There's a good chance she'll get roped into this.
I doubt Shinji's given up so easily.
If we don't do something, he'll...
Then you should probably
keep her safe at your place.
At least, if she's really that important to you.
Sakura.
Breakfast this morning was sublime.
And now you're even preparing lunch for us.
You have my thanks.
Huh?
Oh, it's nothing...
If there's any way I can be of service,
please don't hesitate to call upon me.
What?
Uhm...
You got this!
W-Well, if you insist...
I'm home!
I figured it'd be a good time
to do some stockpiling.
Saber, this is for you.
Your, uh... luggage came in.
Oh, that's adorbs!
Man, I owe Tohsaka big-time.
Senpai,
I understand stocking up on daily necessities,
but don't you think you went a bit overboard?
Oh, right.
Fuji-nee, is it okay if we let Sakura
stay over for the foreseeable future?
What brought this on so suddenly?
It's gotten pretty dangerous
around town lately.
Plus, Shinji's been busy and isn't home much anymore.
Sakura?
Uhm...
Oh, th-that's right!
I have to go get Saber-san's room ready.
Ow!
I'll go help her.
Not gonna stop Saber-chan?
You not afraid Sakura-chan's got the wrong idea?
What makes you think that?
Get a load of this.
I hear Sakura-chan's an E cup!
Why would you tell me that?
Shirou, Sakura's collapsed!
Senpai?
I'm sorry.
Guess my idea's paying off already.
I'll stick around a little longer.
I'll keep an eye on you for another
half an hour, so try to get some rest.
Okay.
I appreciate it.
Senpai.
Hmm?
About what you said earlier...
Why are you letting me stay here?
Is it out of worry?
Yeah, spot on.
It'd be a load off my shoulders
if you stayed here for a while.
Uhm, I'll take you up on that.
All right.
Nary did I expect such manner of serpent...
Is something the matter, Souichirou?
Stay here with the others.
Assassin, come out.
Assassin!
Master Souichirou...
What is this man?
First, cut its neck.
Arms, legs, all cut.
Sliced gut open, too.
But it moved.
So you're the true Assassin, are you?
Unleash me of your shackles, witch.
Are you happy now?
Emiya-kun.
It's all right.
You have my consent.
You can have your way with me.
Tohsaka...
Uhm, Senpai...
Come on, what am I thinking?
Next, a follow-up on the recent gas leak incident.
Another gas leak of unknown cause occurred
within the Shinto district of Fuyuki.
The affected building was located on
the east side of Shinto Station.
Security personnel and several office workers
present within the building were found comatose.
Several people living close to
the accident have reported feeling ill,
and the authorities are currently
investigating any potential links.
Sak—
Hello?
Oh, Fuji-nee.
Why can't you come over today?
Gotcha.
I checked out Ryuudou Temple last night.
The mana from the coma incidents
in Shinto seemed to flow back there.
Archer's all healed up, so I figured I'd investigate.
Long story short, Caster was using
Ryuudou Temple as her base.
But by the time I got there,
someone had already dealt with her.
The residents were robbed of
their mana and are comatose right now.
And since Kuzuki-sensei was the only one
who got killed, he was probably Caster's Master.
Now, here's the real problem.
There was another coma incident
in Shinto this morning.
Even though Caster's out of the picture?
Sakura ended up staying with you, right?
Huh? Yeah.
She's been at my place since yesterday.
Wanna team up, Emiya-kun?
Everything's turning out different
this time from what my father told me.
So I'd like to prioritize figuring out
what's different this time.
So you want to form a temporary alliance?
Yup, exactly.
Rin.
I see no purpose behind teaming up
with that sorry excuse of a Master.
What was that?
Am I wrong?
Archer, you'd better do as your Master says.
Let's hit the ground running.
Can you go out tonight?
You formed an alliance with Archer's Master?
Yeah.
Sorry for the suddenness.
It's fine.
Besides, the faster we end this war,
the sooner Sakura can lead a normal life again.
Shirou, I believe Sakura is in rather poor health.
Oh, no. Perhaps I'm overthinking it.
Sakura, who's that at the door?
What is it, Emiya?
I'm Sakura's brother.
There a problem with me taking
my adorable little sister back home?
What kind of brother hits his sister?!
There's no way I'd trust you to keep
Sakura safe after what you did to Mitsuzuri.
Oh, gotcha.
If you're so set on her already, that must mean...
you don't wanna let her go 'cause
you haven't had enough of her yet, huh?
Screw you!
Senpai!
Shinji!
Ooh, I love that look in your eyes.
Come at me, punk. Let's continue where we left off.
Stop, Nii-san!
Sakura...
I'll do whatever you say.
Just please don't do it in front of Senpai!
Sakura, never forget what you just said.
I'm sorry, Senpai.
You have nothing to apologize for.
No good. I can't focus.
Senpai? Are you there?
Sakura?
Uhm...
Can we talk for a bit?
Sure...
I'm sorry for the way my brother acted.
I told you, you have nothing to apologize for.
It's freezing, huh? Gimme a sec.
Sakura.
It's so warm.
You fixed it?
Yeah.
Took a lot out of me, though.
Senpai, I wonder if you'll remember this.
It's something I'll never forget.
A memory from way back,
before I got to know you.
It was a bright red sunset.
The schoolyard, the hallways, everything was red.
It was pretty, but also lonely.
That's when I saw someone doing
running high jumps in the schoolyard.
Back then, I wasn't a very good girl.
I watched him, hoping he'd mess up.
But...
No matter how many times he tried,
he never made the jump,
and once he realized he couldn't do it,
he cleaned up and went home.
Uh, Sakura...
Would that person happen to be, uhh...
Yes. He was the upperclassman
sitting next to me right now.
I've known about you since then.
Oh. That's news to me.
Uhm, Senpai.
Can I ask you a difficult question?
I heard this from Fujimura-sensei.
Were you really adopted into this family?
Yup, sure was.
And it doesn't bother you?
It took some getting used to,
but it's nothing worth losing sleep over.
You must have been surrounded by kind people.
Rather, all the older folk
surrounding me were a total mess.
Kiritsugu couldn't do housework to save his life,
and you know how Fuji-nee is.
I started doing the chores
and just kinda fell into a groove.
I just really wanted to be like Kiritsugu.
You mean like a superhero?
Huh? That's odd.
Senpai, I have another question.
If I ever did something bad, would you forgive me?
No. If you do something bad, I'll get mad at you.
I'll be first in line to yell at you.
Thank goodness.
I'd like that very much.
I'll go to bed now.
Good night, Senpai.
Miyama HQ to Miyama ambulances.
Incoming report from dispatch.
Numerous injured and in need of aid
in building across from Shinto Station.
All available vehicles promptly head on-site. Over.
Miyama Paramedic Two to Miyama HQ.
Yo.
That your handiwork?
Nah, that'd be a little hard
for a filthy sandflea like you.
You ain't goin' anywhere.
Come!
Give up on those tricks.
I was born with this skill.
Projectiles ain't gonna work on me.
A skill to protect one against projectiles, I see.
Black-painted weapons to hide 'em in the darkness...
Pathetic.
You have seen beneath my mask, Lancer!
I'll be seeing plenty more soon enough.
This is where you lead me?
What's a sandflea gonna pull in a watering hole?
It'll consume you if you don't move.
You got any idea what the hell this damn thing is?
It's...
Noble Phantasm!
Zabaniya!
'Tis a bit early, but I'm finishin' this now!
Gáe...
...Bolg!
You have lost this battle!
Well, this couldn't have gone worse.
Senpai...
Tohsaka.
We can walk and talk.
Be mindful that we're being watched.
Am I right to assume that was your doing,
elder of the Matou family?
Impressive, daughter of Tohsaka.
I expected no less from you.
Zouken!
I thought the Matous were out of the game!
Not once did I indicate that I, myself, had lost.
Archer!
You swine...
You dare make a mockery
of a Heroic Spirit's remains?!
Saber! Watch out!
Don't let that sword—
Don't let that sword touch you!
That sword dispels magecraft.
It can sever even a Master-Servant contract.
She's bad news...
I had hoped to settle this quickly.
Her magic would indeed be futile against Saber.
But can the same be said of the Master?
Impossible.
Preposterous!
What's going on?
Tohsaka, look!
What in the world is that?
An imaginary number space?
Absurd.
This is unthinkable.
How utterly absurd!
Caster vanished?
Tohsaka!
Emiya-kun!
Shirou!
He didn't touch the main body.
It's no more grave than chills and a fever.
Archer, do you know what that thing was?
Nope.
But that shadow's probably
what's been sucking the citizens dry.
Shirou.
Emiya-kun, are you okay?
Y-Yeah...
Looks like it's hardly the time to
prioritize personal vendettas now.
Sakura, I'm sorry. I should have prevented this.
I'll take it from here.
You're only making things worse for him.
So you came.
Apologies for calling you out here.
I arrived early, so I took
the liberty of ordering a meal.
It's fine.
Want some?
Hell, no!
Why did you call me here?
Emiya Shirou, what did you see last night?
You see, I have been overseeing this Holy Grail War,
and have received a report from Rin
concerning an incident at Ryuudou Temple.
We got into a fight with Matou Zouken.
He had Caster with him, but, uh...
It looked like he was puppeteering her corpse.
So that old man has made his move...
Emiya Shirou.
What I am about to uncover
is something not even Rin knows.
The night Caster was killed at Ryuudou Temple,
a single Servant left its bounded field.
Do you know which one?
No...
It was Assassin.
How'd you figure that out?
Why, my Servant, Lancer, saw it all.
I'm saying I was a Master, too.
Uh, crap...
I can't keep up with this.
I had ordered Lancer to surveil Assassin.
He cornered him at Ryuudou Temple,
but never returned.
Did Assassin kill him?
Assassins often rely on a skill to erase their presence.
Their individual combat abilities are not high.
It is inconceivable that Lancer
would lose in conventional combat.
Emiya Shirou,
Matou Zouken and Caster weren't
the only ones you saw last night, correct?
I wager Assassin was perfectly aware
of what he was doing and lured Lancer into a trap.
What lurks there has turned against not just Servants,
but the people of this city, as well.
If we liken Caster's absorption
of mana to drawing blood,
then that thing's methods
are the act of consuming a meal.
Should this continue,
this city will soon become uninhabitable.
Thirty people found unconscious?
That took place in the fourth district of south Miyama.
What else is located there?
Ryuudou Temple...
What is the matter? Will you not eat?
If you want me to be a dinner buddy so badly,
it'd have to be over my dead body.
Sakura?
It's begun snowing.
Hey, Sakura's at your place, right?
Huh?
Y-Yeah.
Okay, that's a relief.
That way, I won't run into her by accident.
I'm heading to the Matou household
to go straight after Zouken.
That's a bit...
I have a bit of a history with the Matous.
You can leave the old-fashioned magi duels to me.
Hey, Emiya-kun.
What are you gonna do?
Saber-san, I don't know what you and Senpai are doing,
and I don't think I'd get a straight answer if I asked.
But I can't overlook the fact that
Senpai came home injured last night.
I don't want him getting into danger.
I'm gonna go after that shadow.
We can't let it roam freely.
It's already hurt too many people as is.
Oh?
Then I guess our ceasefire's
continuing for a little longer.
Tohsaka...
We can't turn a blind eye to that shadow,
but don't bite off more than you can chew.
Not until we know what it is.
Okay.
Sakura reprimanded me thoroughly
regarding last night.
I wasn't capable enough to protect you.
I went and collapsed on my own there.
If there's a problem, it lies with me.
I cannot stop you from going to battle.
But I will fight by your side and protect you.
That is my duty.
For Sakura's sake, as well.
The hell?
Shirou!
Sa—
Shirou, it's Assassin!
Stay where you are!
Saber!
How very like you to come here.
Matou Zouken!
That wind...
It would prove fatal
were I to take the brunt of it.
O Wind...
Run amok!
The blessing of wind protection.
Indispensable for any who would cross the desert.
I care not if you refuse to approach,
but my lord is currently entertaining yours.
Fiend!
My job was merely to draw away your attention.
Curse you, Assassin!
No Servant can resist that shadow.
The sanity of one as pure as yourself
will be stripped by a simple touch.
But before that,
I will be taking your heart.
Trace on!
What can you do with a single flimsy stick?
Zabaniya.
Saber!
I'd expect nothing less
from such an excellent Servant.
She chose to confront her own darkness
over having her heart ripped out.
It appears matters have been settled.
As her Master, you should be aware
that your Servant has been
obliterated from this world.
Bastard!
I leave this matter to you, Assassin.
Are you unhurt?
That is good.
Saber!
What the hell are you?
Oh. I guess this means
I'm officially not a Master anymore.
What is this?
He calls this a training ground?
This... This disgusting hellhole is...
Do you curse me,
he who extends his rotting life
with the bodies of others?
No.
Your tenacity for survival
makes you fit to be my lord.
There's a mischievous kitty among us.
A kitty, you say?
Meow, meow, meow.
Sella, ready the car.
I'm heading into the city tomorrow.
I don't know who you are,
but that belongs to the Einzberns.
Have I lost?
Is that...
Could it be?
Give it up.
It's the Holy Grail!
I must obtain it!
I'm telling you to give it up.
Who are you? Why do you stand in my way?
Who am I, you ask?
You need merely gaze upon me to realize.
Senpai...
Where have you been?
You got hurt again...
You need to take better care of yourself!
Sorry.
I'm sorry.
But...
I'm home, Sakura.
Yes.
Welcome home, Senpai.
Tell me, Kiritsugu.
I don't get it.
What do I have to do to become a superhero?
I can't let it end here.
There's still someone I have to deal with.
Senpai, I...
I thought maybe I could see you if I came here.
The Tohsakas had two children
with an aptitude for magecraft.
This makes the second time I've received
something important from someone special.
Die at once, girl.
I promise. I'll...
Delusional Heartbeat
Barbed Spear...
...that Pierces with Death
Delusional Heartbeat
sono hibi wa yume no you ni
okubyou na hohoemi to
yasashii tsume wo
nokoshite itta
taikutsu na hanabira no you ni
kurushimi wo wasurete
anata no senaka de sotto
naite waratta
kaeranu hibi wo omou you na
kimyou na itoshisa ni michita
hakoniwa no naka de
iki wo hisome
kisetsu ga yuku koto wo wasure
shizuka na minasoko no you na
jikan ni ita
tsumetai hanabira yoru ni chirisaku
marude shiroi yuki no you da ne setsunaku
anata no ue ni futta
kanashimi wo subete harainokete agetai dake
anata no koto kizutsukeru mono subete
watashi wa kitto yurusu koto wa dekinai
yasashii hibi
namida ga deru hodo
kaeritai
anata to futari de
miageta
hanabira ga chitta
tsuki ga kumo ni kakurete
anata wa michi wo nakushite
nakidashisou na
me wo shiteta
gizagiza na kokoro datte
futatsu awasete mireba
yasashii mono ga kitto
umarete kuru wa
watashi wo kizutsukeru mono wo
anata wa yurusanaide kureta
sore dake de ii no
tawamure ni nobasareta
anata no te ni shigamitsuita
akirameteita sekai ni
yagate atataka na hi ga tomoru
tsumetai hanabira yoru wo kirisaku
watashi ga tsunda hikari wo minna tabanete
anata no ue ni zenbu
yorokobi no you ni
makichirashite agetai dake
warui koto wo shitara kitto anata ga
okotte kureru to yakusoku shita yo ne
dakara kitto mou ichido watashi wo mitsukete kureru yo ne
sabishii tokoro ni
mou inakute ii ne
hitori de miageta
hanabira ga chitta
Those days
With a timid beam
And kind claws like a dream
Remained
I forget the pain which I rack
And gently sob
And laugh on your back
Like a petal in tedium
Inside the miniature garden
Filled with queer loveliness
I bate my breath
As I think of the days of transience
I forgot the passage of the season
Trapped in time
As if stuck in the bottom of the ocean
A cold petal falls and blooms in the night
Much like white snow, it piles over you
It renders my heart
I just wish to brush away all of your dismay
Everything that comes to hurt you
Is not able to be forgiven
I wish to return
To those kinder days; oh, so I urge
So much so tears surge
The petal which we gazed at
Just you and me
Came to no longer be
The moon hides behind a cloud
You lost the path you should have trod
And looked as though
Your tears were going to blow
Even if you match
Two jagged hearts
Surely something tender
Will be birthed into splendor
All I insist
Is for you to resist
Those that bring me pain
I clung to the hand
That you extended out in jest
A considerate torch was at last lit
In this world which I wished to quit
A cold petal rips through the night
I just wish to spread it all
All the light I plucked and gathered
All over you
If I did a bad deed
You promised to get angry at me
So once again
You will discover me, right?
There's no need
To be all alone
The flower petal I was gazing at alone
Has fallen
Aniplex, Notes, and ufotable
present
a ufotable production
Summer
A year and a half ago
Don't worry about club.
You can come back
once you get better.
Taiga
PS: I'll come check
up on you later!
Today's Topic
Fireworks Spectacle Over The Sea
Miyama Fireworks Festival
Yesterday, 8:00 PM
Autumn
A year and three months ago
Winter
A year and two months ago
Spring
Ten months ago
Autumn
Three months ago
One day ago
SUSPECT FLED FROM CAR WRECK
Today's Weather
GAS LEAK IN DOWNTOWN SHINTO
Present day
MURDERS IN MIYAMA TOWN
Today's Weather
Student Council Room
Quickly hydrates and
restores lost minerals.
Feel rejuvenated!
ANOTHER GAS LEAK IN DOWNTOWN SHINTO
Today's Weather
Ryuudou Issei
Suzuki Tarou
Takada Naoki
Kobayashi
Preview
In theaters