Aniplex, Notes, and ufotable
present
a ufotable production
Saber!
Saber...
Thank goodness. You're o—
Saber!
Why am I back here?
What...
are you?
Wh-What is...
...an investigation underway.
However, when the police arrived
this morning, they discovered...
Today's Topic
Partial Cave-in on Enzou Mountain, Fuyuki City
Uhm, Senpai.
Senpai?
Oh, what is it?
F
Fuy
Fuyuk
Fuyuki
Well, Saber-san returned to
her country rather suddenly, didn't she?
Yeah.
But now you don't have to
go out at night anymore, right?
You don't have to put yourself
in harm's way anymore, right?
Well,
you misunderstand, Sakura.
I wasn't tagging along with Saber's errands.
She was tagging along with mine.
I may be out of the house even more now.
Could you stop waiting for me
by the door when I'm running late?
This is still far from over.
There's still someone in this town
I have to settle the score with.
ROAD WORK AHEAD
ACCIDENT AT FUYUKI ENTRANCE
LANES CLOSED AHEAD
FUYUKI ENTRANCE LANES NOW OPEN
Shinto.
Central Park.
Ryuudou Temple.
What's that shadow-looking thing's end goal here?
How does it tie back to Zouken?
Is it working under him?
Nah, he's gotta be using it.
Welcome to Fuyuki
I'd better hear Tohsaka's thoughts, too.
uki
What?
Oh, you're alive, Mister!
Tell me your name.
What's your name?
I'm Shirou. Emiya Shirou.
Shirou!
Shirou. You're Shirou!
Got it.
Huzzah!
Whoa—H-Hold on a sec!
Don't forget that we're enemies, Illyasviel!
Just call me Illya.
Masters are only allowed to fight at night, right?
I'm here because I wanna chat with you.
Look, chopping a guy in half isn't really
a good way to get them to talk with you.
What do you mean?
That's completely separate.
You were the one who came flying at me
despite how weak you were.
I could kill you on the spot if I chose to.
Without Saber, you wouldn't last a heartbeat.
And...
I've been waiting all this time.
You could at least give me this, right?
You live in that castle in the forest, right, Illya?
All alone?
I have Sella and Liz with me.
I had to pull a fast one on Sella
to come meet you today.
You should feel honored.
Uh-huh...
Can I ask you one more thing?
Does the name "Emiya Kiritsugu" ring a bell?
Illya?
It doesn't. Never heard it before.
I don't know it.
I'm going back.
Illya!
Huh?
Emiya-kun?
Tohsaka.
What a happy coincidence.
I wanted to have a chat with you, too.
Why not do it at school?
Archer, could you make us some tea?
No?
What's with the long face?
Fine, have it your way!
Huh?
Aren't those...?
What are you doing?
Come on, let's get strategizing.
I need to get dinner ready.
Sakura's got a fever and you only tell me now?!
You wouldn't let me get a word in edgewise!
It isn't locked?
Sakura, you up?
Emiya-kun?
For crying out...
Shinji! Let her go right now!
Shinji!
Don't worry, Sakura.
I won't kill him.
But I may need to get a little rough.
Fight Rider.
If you make it out in one piece, she's free to go.
Go get him, Rider.
If you seriously intended to fight,
you shouldn't have come alone.
What's up, Emiya?
Don't be lame and go down that easily, now!
Your endurance has won you this battle.
Looking good. No need to hold back anymore.
It's time to get lethal, Rider!
Nii-san, don't!
Sakura.
Senpai...
Why... How?
Magecraft...
Rider!
Fucking kill him!
What?
T-Tohsaka...
Why?
Emiya-kun and I formed an alliance.
We've been together all day.
Now that you've dragged Sakura into this,
you've made an enemy out of me as well.
Sakura...
Sakura this, Sakura that, Sakura...
It's always Sakura, Sakura, Sakura!
Who gives a shit about her?!
I was chosen as a Master, not her!
Get up, Rider!
You piece of...
No...
Rider, no...
Make it stop!
Sakura—
Emiya-kun, get down!
No way...
Is that really Rider?
Now that's more like it, Rider!
Wipe the floor with them!
Hey, Rider!
So that's how it is.
The Matou bloodline has dried up.
They can't produce anyone who can use magecraft.
I figured Zouken summoned Rider
and handed her over to Shinji,
but in truth, it was much simpler than that.
Tohsaka?
The person most suitable to be
a Master in the Matou family now...
That would be the Matous' legitimate heir,
their magus of this generation.
And that would be you, Sakura.
Sakura's a Master?
You transferred your Command Spells and
used one to make her obey Shinji's orders, huh?
That's how Shinji became Rider's Master.
Hey.
And in exchange you forfeited
your rights as a Master,
making you just another magus.
Where do you think you're looking?
That little trick was only possible because the Matous
created the Command Spells. Right, Sakura?
Hey! I'm right here!
We still have unfinished business!
One more time, Sakura!
Give me command rights again!
What's with this dumbass goody-two-shoes act?!
You still have one Command Spell! Just use that!
Shinji, if she runs out of Command Spells,
Rider will be free.
At that point, even a tome
would just burn up immediately.
You were controlling her
with borrowed Command Spells.
You were never a Master in the first place.
Shinji...
Yeah, I knew.
I knew! I damn well knew, okay?!
I knew I wasn't cut out for it!
So you have to do it.
You have to kill them in my stead, Sakura.
No, Nii-san.
Let's stop this.
You broke your promise.
You said you wouldn't kill Senpai!
So let's end this!
All right, fine.
You can die with them for all I care.
Sakura!
Senpai... no...
Don't look at me...
Sakura...
Looks like she's lost control.
Get away from here!
If she gets struck with mana
the wrong way, she won't turn back!
Don't get in my way.
Listen to me, Rider!
Your lord has gone out of control.
If we don't deal with this,
she'll burn through all her mana and die!
Then we need only provide her
with mana faster than she loses it.
Looks like swapping lords
did little to change your nature!
A bounded field?
Stop...
Please stop, Rider...
This isn't what I summoned you for!
I can't obey that order.
I must prioritize your life above all else.
No way...
Mystic Eyes of Petrification!
Tohsaka!
No!
Sakura...
Sakura!
Emiya-kun, how are you feeling?
Tohsaka!
Awake at last, I see.
I have just finished treating Matou Sakura.
Is Sakura...
Is Sakura okay?
Calm down.
Rider and I brought her here.
Kirei, how's Sakura's condition?
Not stable, but her life is
no longer in immediate danger.
Wait a second. What happened to your Magic Crest?
I had no choice but to use it all to treat Matou Sakura.
All of it?
Now, about the results of my treatment...
Crest Worms?
What are those? Uh...
Think of them as living Magic Circuits.
Once a Crest Worm sinks its teeth into you,
it penetrates the entire body, eating your life away.
It pierces and dampens the skin with its mucus,
sating its hunger by elevating
and destroying the pleasure centers.
As a result, any woman preyed upon by these insects
will be entirely violated in both body and mind.
Matou Sakura is no excep—
That's enough!
I thought you required an explanation.
As long as those things remain within her body,
her life force—her mana—will be leeched without end.
Left alone, she will lose her life.
But you said the surgery succeeded!
Not entirely.
She has been in this state for eleven years.
One wrong move during the extraction,
and her body will give out.
To fully remove the Crest Worms would truly
require a miracle akin to the Holy Grail.
Tohsaka...
As Fuyuki's supervisor, I have to dispose of her.
Dispose of her? Matou Sakura, you mean?
Yes. A magus who's lost control
of their power can't be allowed to live.
She's nothing but an insane Master now.
Will you go through with that,
even if she is your sister by blood?
Sister?
The Tohsakas actually bore two children.
But magecraft can only be passed down to one.
I inherited the magecraft of the Tohsakas.
Sakura was adopted by the dying
Matou family as heir to the Makiri line.
Then—
Sakura and I are blood-related sisters.
Not that we've ever treated each other as such.
Wait, Tohsaka.
That's all the more reason to...
If we leave her be, history will just repeat itself.
Except it'll be random passersby
paying the price this time.
So I have to kill her before that happens.
You win, Sakura.
Here, have this.
This makes the second time I've received
something important from someone special.
Sakura...
I have to find her before Tohsaka does.
But once I do, what do I...
Good evening, Shirou.
I thought we were supposed to fight at night.
You're not a Master anymore.
I already know everything that happened.
Rider's Master collapsed,
and now there's only two left.
You want to save Rider's Master,
but can't find her, right?
I know!
You look like you're on the verge of tears.
Illya, aren't you angry at me?
No, I'm not.
I'm on your side.
You're on my side?
When you asked about Kiritsugu this morning,
I lied. I actually do know him.
I was born to win the Holy Grail War,
but my personal goal was to kill you and Kiritsugu.
But I've changed my mind.
If you want to protect someone dear to you,
I'll be on your side.
It's only natural to want to
protect the girl you like, is it not?
I know all about it.
Now I've lost every last place I can call home...
Sakura.
Senpai...
Let's go home.
You're still not over your cold, right?
I can't.
That potion back then wasn't poisonous or anything.
It was just a medicine that heightens my senses.
It took that little for me
to lose my mind and hurt you!
I'm not hurt one bit.
I'm perfectly fine.
I'm a magus of the Matou family—I hid that from you.
I never told you I was a Master, either.
I only started going to your house
out of fear for my grandfather!
I lied to you the whole time,
only pretending I wanted to help you!
I always thought
that I didn't deserve to be by your side.
Every time I thought that, I considered leaving
and just pretending I didn't know you the next day.
If we saw each other in the hallway,
I'd just walk right past you.
I'd also make sure to ignore you after school.
Then I'd go home and forget everything again.
But I couldn't!
It was scarier than when I tried cutting myself.
I was too scared to deceive you,
and too scared to stop!
Everything around me scared me.
I couldn't take a single step.
I didn't know what to do!
I didn't want to let go of the times we shared...
Nothing else in life ever held any meaning to me.
She's all I want to protect.
The one I hold most dear.
If I want her to stop shedding tears...
If nobody else will blame Sakura,
if she has to do it herself...
I'll take her by the hand
and drag her into the sunlight.
Even if no one else will forgive her...
I'll forgive you in your stead.
Come on, don't cry.
I know full well what a bad person you are.
I don't know when I'll lose my mind like that again.
I'm sure I'll end up doing something I'll regret.
What kind of home could there be
for someone like me?
This is your home.
I... I...
I'm not a virgin.
My first time was long, long ago.
And to top it off, these weird things
have been touching me since.
I don't deserve your protection!
I'll protect you.
No matter what happens,
even if you feel like ending everything,
I'll be there to protect you, Sakura.
Senpai...
I'll be your personal superhero.
No, Senpai.
If you do that, I'll end up hurting you.
You'll get hurt.
Let's go home.
Sakura.
Nee-san...
Tohsaka-senpai...
Emiya Shirou.
If you plan to uphold your
prior convictions, then so be it.
I know where that leads.
But if you choose to follow this path,
Emiya Shirou will have no future.
You will lose absolutely everything.
You must be tired.
Get a good night's sleep.
Okay.
What's wrong, Sakura?
You got a fever?
Well, you were getting soaked out there.
It's... not a cold...
I'm running a bit low on mana.
Is there anything I can do for you?
Uhm...
Could you...
No, all I need is a little bit of your blood.
Uh-huh...
Will this work?
Yes.
You good now?
Great.
Then, uh...
Good night.
No.
Any more than this,
and I'll just hurt him...
Sakura, can you prep the soup stock?
Sure.
What should we do with the spinach?
Let's dress it with sesame seeds.
Sakura, eggs please.
Here.
Thanks for the food.
Feels like it's been a while since we've done this.
Indeed.
Not gonna eat?
No need to be shy.
We don't need to absorb nutrients like you do.
Really? Saber ate a bunch.
Yup!
Your customs and I do not mix.
Oh, well, in that case...
So, about our plans moving forward.
I want Sakura to win and use the Holy Grail.
But I think she should stay holed up inside.
It's too dangerous to have her
see Zouken face-to-face.
Your assessment is correct.
But how do you plan to defeat that magus?
I propose we work with other Masters.
Who else is left?
Tohsaka and Archer, you and Rider...
Zouken has Assassin...
Other than that, there's Illya and...
Berserker...
Will you be okay?
Yeah, probably.
Don't go outside, okay?
Are you regretting this?
After all that's happened, I can't regret anything.
Rider, if it gets too dangerous, bring Senpai home.
But Sakura,
I believe the priest warrants
more caution than that old man.
You're right.
I was actually thinking the same thing.
But don't worry, Rider.
He doesn't stand a chance against me.
All right, then.
Senpai...
That's it. I just have to make sure
he doesn't go outside anymore.
Then he'll never be in danger again.
Huh? What am I thinking?
Well, this poses a problem.
Am I supposed to follow it?
Huh?
It's gone.
What's it doing here?
You're a cowardly Servant, not unlike your lord.
Neither of you are willing to fight me.
Your life is simply too precious to you.
Indeed it is,
for I seek immortality.
Behold my body.
It's prone to rot, emits a foul odor, and is quick
to lose all my accumulated knowledge.
Can you comprehend the pain of rotting alive?
No human exists who does not fear death.
But if it will grant my wish,
I'd be more than happy to kill off
every human in the world, one by one.
I'm floored.
How could you have lost sight
of yourself this badly, Makiri?
Remember our precious wish.
Remember what led us to long for a miracle.
Remember why we humans attempted to
reach a domain man cannot tread.
That was an impressive recital for a mere puppet.
But you may have taken imitating
your ancestors too much to heart.
Enough of this tomfoolery.
I, the great Matou Zouken, have come
to claim the Einzberns' Holy Grail.
No, Berserker!
Tohsaka? How come?
I see great minds think alike, huh?
You've gotta be kidding!
Get away from there!
If that thing catches you, there's no coming back!
And so it's decided.
I leave the rest in your hands.
Don't squander this opportunity
to erase that Einzbern girl.
Berserker!
Illya!
Archer, I swear...
Berserker...
If you want to touch them,
you'll have to go through me first.
Archer.
I'm counting on you.
This is the end for you.
Even the purest of Heroic Spirits
cannot resist that mass of curses.
As you are now, you're no different
from the vengeful spirits filling this forest.
Berserker!
This is bad.
Berserker...
Berserker!
No...
No!
I have fulfilled my duty.
You may handle the rest.
You have my gratitude.
Now I can make up for my blunder.
Saber!
Illya!
That's as far as you go.
You've served your purpose.
Can't even kill one little boy without
one of your fancy surprise attacks?
Pathetic.
How did you manage to get here?
I wonder.
Archer!
Hurry!
If that thing catches up to you, you're done for.
We can talk later. Run, boy!
Now that you've taken Illya's hand,
you'd better hold on to it 'til the end!
Let's go!
How?
How can you still move?
Surely you know!
Unlike the others, I am no upstanding hero.
As I am not pure, I can tolerate
a certain amount of taint.
I am, myself, a twisted Heroic Spirit!
Good job, Archer!
You can go back to spirit form now.
Let's hurry and get out—
Tohsak—
Huh?
No...
Archer!
Tohsaka!
Get moving already, you fools!
It's gathering mana.
At this rate, we'll...
Tohsaka, run!
I am the bone of my sword.
Steel is my body.
I have created over a thousand blades.
Rho Aias!
The Seven Rings that Cover the Fiery Heavens
Shirou...
Why?
Sh-Shirou!
Shirou!
This is as far as I go.
You did great, Tohsaka.
Are you sure about this?
If you go through with that, you will...
I don't have to think twice about it.
If I sit idly by, two will disappear.
But by doing this, one will certainly be saved.
I'm home, Sakura.
Oh, right.
Yeah, I guess this isn't really a pretty look.
I, uh, got a bit of a scratch.
It looks worse than it actually is
'cause it's all wrapped up,
but it's nothing to worry about.
Oh, I ran into Tohsaka while I was there.
She helped me out, so we agreed to a ceasefire.
And this girl here is Illya.
Uhm, sorry to spring this on you...
Sakura?
Can you move your arm?
No.
Not surprised.
It's downright insane to transplant
a Servant's body parts onto a human.
Listen closely.
If you use that arm even once,
Archer's Magic Circuits will activate.
Your body can't withstand that influx of mana,
so it'll collapse from the inside out.
Then this cloth is...
It's a seal.
Thanks a bunch, Tohsaka.
Huh? Where'd that come from?
I only plan on teaming up with you
until we've dealt with Zouken,
and it's simply more convenient
for me to have her in sight.
I'm glad you're also keeping Sakura in mind.
Look, that's not what—
I'm glad I became a Master. Else we would've
never even known about each other.
That's where you're wrong.
I don't know about you, but I've been
aware of you for quite a while now.
It was about four years ago, I'd say.
You were doing running high jumps until sundown.
I was there.
There was this idiot who
kept trying jumps he couldn't do.
And I was gawking at him like one, too.
It's in my nature to give up
the moment I decide I can't do something.
I'm rather cold at heart.
But, you know, I'm a magus.
Right when I was contemplating
if that was what I wanted to do in life,
I ran straight into my polar opposite.
It really threw me for a loop.
Don't take them.
Don't take my memories from me.
Ow.
Who knows? Maybe it'll be the same
as always once I take the cloth off...
No...
This is not good.
Shirou.
I have a question for you.
Sakura's at her happiest when you're there for her.
She holds no other wishes.
I want her to live past this war.
I've grown rather fond of her.
Shirou, will you be on Sakura's side?
No matter what may come?
Senpai...
Sakura?
Oh, you need mana?
Come in and give me a second.
Let's see, what did I do with my box cutter?
S-Sakura?
Senpai, why do you protect me?
Because...
I wanted you to be with me.
I need you. I couldn't even imagine us being apart.
Do you see me as family?
Or do you see me as a girl?
Yeah. I love you, Sakura.
Then make love to me.
Senpai, am I tainted?
Is there something wrong with me?
Simply coming into your room reduced me to this.
Even if I try to console myself, I can't suppress it.
I can't think of anything but you.
I'm so disgusting.
No. You aren't disgusting at all.
You're beautiful.
Senpai...
I'm horrible.
When Nee-san took you away earlier,
I was so afraid.
I'm sorry for not noticing.
Senpai...
Sakura...
I love you, Senpai.
It is time for the blessing.
Blessing?
For what?
For the other Holy Grail in the process of being born.
It bears within it all the evils of the world,
unwittingly brought forth by Man.
The distinction between good and evil.
Rather than ponder that dilemma, what if one were to
give birth to something that held the answer?
The answer is nigh.
Even if this question were to be
blasphemy against God,
I will stand before Him, and with all my soul,
I will kill even the Lord.
I couldn't live with myself if I were just freeloading.
The least I could do is make breakfast.
I'll go help Tohsaka-senpai.
Ah, Sakura.
Yes?
Uhm, try calling Tohsaka...
Hmm, what to do?
Nee-san, I'll wash these vegetables.
Yeah, thanks a...
Does it sound weird, Nee-san?
Oh, I w-wouldn't say w-weird...
Illya, can we talk about you-know-what in my room?
What's this you-know-what?
I figure we need a secret weapon or two.
Archer's arm holds knowledge of the Einzberns.
Tohsaka said we might be
able to put it to use somehow.
I don't really care about Kischur Zelretch's leftovers,
but I'm sure a magician's treasures will be lovely.
Kischur Zel...
Senpai.
Uhm, thank you.
I only ever watched her from afar,
so never in my wildest dreams did I imagine
I'd get to call her Nee-san again.
Did you two not hang out
after you went to the Matous?
No.
We just knew that we were sisters,
and tried our best not to
come into contact with each other.
Besides, if she knew about my magecraft,
she'd come to hate me.
Hate? How come?
The Matou family's techniques have always
been limited to taking from others.
All they do is steal.
They have no teachings about accepting others.
Do you hate the Matous' magecraft?
Sure, their teachings are harsh,
but they're nothing compared to what you go through.
I've seen the training you do at night.
I wanted to stop you so many times.
The things you put yourself through
are too dangerous.
It's as if you're stabbing yourself in the throat.
It isn't something anyone forced on you, either.
You decided to keep that routine up yourself.
I can confidently say that
you're the strongest of us all.
Not because of your magecraft,
but because you're pure of heart.
I could tell from the moment we first met
that you'd never betray anyone.
You took everything from me, Emiya!
Why?
Why won't anything happen?
MULTIPLE BODIES FOUND IN SHINTO CENTRAL PARK
Today's Weather
We now move on to the next headline.
Multiple bodies thought to be homicide victims have
been discovered at Shinto's Central Park in Fuyuki City.
See, look!
Those weeds have turned black.
Then that means the shadow did it?
Is this Zouken's handiwork?
I'm not sure.
I don't think he'd leave so much evidence behind.
That's odd. I can't taste anything.
He's so warm.
It's okay. I can still feel him.
I wish this moment could last forever...
The lovely girl went on a lovely walk.
Bobbing to and fro, her head
was clear, no real goal in mind.
And so she shook from side to side.
Go, go.
And sang with a chuckle.
And the empty limbs rolled
along the ground like paper balloons.
And floating through the air
would have to wait until she grew up.
Go, go.
Someone came up to her and squeaked.
It roared at her in laughter.
She had no reason to be scared of it!
The shrill laughter echoed throughout the room,
so her empty stomach growled.
You've been busy, I see.
Had you only died as I told you to,
it would've saved us both the trouble.
So shiny and pretty...
This has gone on long enough.
Know that this is an act of mercy.
What? You yet cling to life?
I see your shadow isn't the only thing that's changed.
You dare presume to make me kneel?
Damned mongrel!
How could you have grown so...
Did you see that?
Huh?
Shirou!
Come to the living room! Now!
At 10:08 PM today, a widespread blackout
occurred near Shinto Station.
SHINTO STATION
The authorities have also received reports of
people going missing or vanishing into thin air,
among other unexplained incidents, around this time.
Sakura!
Don't move. I'll go get a first aid kit!
Saku—
Shut it out.
Stop.
They're nothing alike.
There are currently over sixty confirmed victims.
MULTIPLE MISSING PERSONS IN SHINTO
Furthermore, there are forty buildings
whose residents are currently unaccounted for.
MULTIPLE MISSING PERSONS IN SHINTO
How's Sakura?
Alive.
But...
But... what?
Sakura's body looks like it's
put together well on the surface,
but the muscles in her arms and legs are in tatters.
It's as if she died and was glued back together.
I can't tell you who killed her,
but the pain may have destroyed
not just her body, but her mind as well.
We don't have a second to waste
if we want to beat Zouken and the shadow.
Let's do what we can right now.
But, Shirou,
if it turns out that Zouken and that shadow
aren't actually working together,
what will you do?
Good morning.
Are you still in there, Sakura?
Where did you get that soul from?
Assassin and Rider are still alive.
I'd be surprised if you were full already.
Sakura, do you know what's going to happen to you?
No. What's going to happen to me?
You'll die. There's no saving you.
I'm home! I made some free time to hang out!
Huh? Shirou? You around?
Who's that?
I swear. Whatever happened to Shirou?
He needs to be here for you.
Hey, don't push yourself.
Senpai said he would protect me.
But I'm sorry.
It's my fault his dreams were shattered.
Why?
Because I'm a bad person.
Shirou's the kinda guy who'll
get mad at you for doing bad things.
You want to fix that part of you, right?
Yes.
Then you have nothing to worry about.
Shirou's dream is to be a superhero, right?
It's only natural he'd have
someone he wants to protect.
But shouldn't he treat everyone equally?
If Shirou's trying to be like Kiritsugu-san,
then it's fine for him to have this special someone.
Kiritsugu-san played favorites all the time, y'know?
Even after moving here, he was always abroad.
He kept going out until
he couldn't even move anymore.
There must've been someone
he really wanted to see.
It hurts a lot if you can't see that special person.
Superhero or not.
So make sure you always hold Shirou close by, okay?
Will you betray him?
Will you betray your past self?
Wait...
Stop...
If you will betray him,
you must...
Stop!
No...
I couldn't...
Emiya Shirou, I presume?
My magus wishes to speak with you.
You arrived much faster than I expected,
son of Emiya.
Zouken...
I only have one thing to say to you:
Let Sakura go, right now.
Let her go?
I suppose that is one way of putting it.
Emiya Shirou, I called you here to ask a favor of you.
I wish for you to kill the shadow.
Isn't that thing in cahoots with you?
Cahoots?
That thing cannot be reasoned with.
As of last night, I cannot even pacify it.
Oh, but before we continue,
I must tell you what that shadow is.
Simply put, it's the contents of the Holy Grail.
The wills overflowing from the gate
are what we call the Grail.
That's what that shadow is.
The shadow and... a gate...
I asked you to kill the shadow,
but that would prove difficult.
However, you can kill the gate.
It would see right through myself or the Tohsaka girl.
Servants are its feed.
Stop...
I planted a shard of the Grail in it and raised it
as the Matous' Holy Grail for the past ten years.
The only one left who can kill it is...
Shut up!
Surely you've realized by now
that it is awfully similar to Sakura.
That doll who does nothing but exist
will die at the hands of the man she loves.
She could ask for no better end.
We're running out of time.
When Sakura's consciousness grows faint,
the Holy Grail she unconsciously
borrowed will rise to the surface.
The disaster from ten years ago will be recreated.
If Sakura is to be saved, she must endure until
the time limit for the Holy Grail War runs out.
Following precedent,
that would be about four more days.
What do you think?
Will Sakura be able to hold out?
She will.
She definitely will!
But the same cannot be said for others.
She may have eaten her fill last night,
but she will strike again as early as tomorrow.
How many days will it take for her
to finish feeding on the people of this city?
Surely you understand.
Strike down evil for the sake of the many.
If you wish to become Emiya Kiritsugu,
then Matou Sakura is your enemy.
Sakura, you up yet?
Yes.
Good morning, Senpai.
Hey, Sakura.
Is there anything you wanna do
after the battle is over?
I can't really think of anything.
As long as I'm with you,
I'm fine with anything.
Then how about we go somewhere fun?
Where would you like to go?
Well, I suppose I'd like to go flower-viewing...
Gotcha.
I promise we will.
I'll create a warm illusion with a frozen heart.
When winter passes and a new spring arrives,
we'll go see the cherry blossoms together.
Yes.
Go see the cherry blossoms...
Senpai.
My name is Matou Sakura.
Here, have this.
This makes the second time I've received
something important from someone special.
I'll...
A superhero?
Senpai...
I didn't want to let go of the times we shared.
I wish this moment could last forever...
Senpai.
Senpai!
Senpai...
Will you betray him?
Yeah. I will.
Thank you, Senpai.
You've given me so much.
Thank you, Nee-san.
I'm happy I could call you that again.
Fujimura-sensei, thank you for everything.
I'm sorry I couldn't keep my promise.
Rider, thank you for not killing Senpai.
Sakura...
By my final Command Spell...
Please, Rider...
I'll be the one to stop Grandfather.
It may have taken me a long time,
but I can't cause any more trouble than I already have.
Morning, Sakura.
Wait, what?
Hi there, traitor.
Took you long enough to come crawling back.
Uhm, Nii-san, I...
Hold this for me.
It's nothing dangerous.
So pretty...
You're something else, Sakura.
You might even surpass Tohsaka someday.
Nii-san...
Get off your high horse.
You're nothing but my plaything.
I've made another mistake.
That's why something horrible
is going to happen to me.
It's okay.
I just have to put up with it for a while, like usual.
Put up with it, put up with it,
put up with it, put up with it...
Sakura.
No!
No. I belong to Senpai now!
What's this crap?
Looks like he's trained you good!
No!
Hey!
What's wrong with you?
Why does this always happen to me?
Behave yourself! Hey!
That thought always lingered in my mind.
I've hated him for so long.
Why does the world around me hate me so much?
Hey, I'd better tell Emiya, too.
I should tell him how much you've clung to me so far
and how dirty you are in bed!
The world would be better off without him.
Nii-san...
Sakura!
Please give me your pity
awaremi wo kudasai
Touch me the way you would a fallen baby bird
ochita kotori ni sotto fureru you na
And caress me with that same sadness
kanashimi wo kudasai
Let your eyes fill with tears, glance gently down upon me
namidagunde mioroshite
And whisper those sweet words of pity
kawaisou da to kuchi ni dashite
I won't mind if you kick me over with your shoes
kutsu no saki de korogashitemo kamawanai wa
Tell me it's okay to be sullied
yogoretetemo ii kara to
By holding my mud-covered hand
dorodarake no te wo totte
Say, let's form a circle and dance!
nee wa ni natte odorimashou
Let's go and eat up
mezawari na uzou muzou wa subete
All of those eyesores
tabete shimaimashou
Can I add spices until the dish is ruined?
supaisu wa taegatai kurai ga ii wa
Lie, lie, lie, la la la
La lie, la lie
Lie, la la la la la la la
Lie lie lie, la la la
La la, la la
La la la la la la la
The scared little bird
obieta kotori wa
Was unable to speak farewells
sayonara nante ienakute
It falls silent, an act to beg for more love
ai wo kou shigusa from damarikonde
Yet still thinking it's being modest
tsutsumashii tsumori de ita
Lie, lie—It's a lie
Not a lie, it hurts too much
not a lie mou tsurai
Cover me in wounds
sanzan kizutsuite
Anyone would want to live in a gentler world
yasashii sekai ni dare datte yukitai wa
Let us melt into one
hitotsu ni tokete shimaimashou
Let hate and love get all jumbled up
nikushimi mo aijou mo mushamusha to
And let's stuff our cheeks full with it
hoobatte shimaimashou
Inside this sweet, sweet pot of chaos
konton no amai amai tsubo no naka de
Lie, lie, lie, la la la
La lie, la lie
Lie, la la la la la la la
Lie lie lie, la la la
La la, la la
La la la la la la la
When you flash that uncertain smile
aimai ni warau kara
I want to be with you again
aitai to omou no yo
I know you're here to stay with me
I just want to be loved
aisareteitai dake
Lie, lie, lie, you're to be with me
There, where the thunder blooms
raimei no saku tokoro
A miserable, heavenly feeling
santantaru heavenly feeling
Let love be all that remains
ai dake nokoreba ii
Silently, nothing but sadness keeps snowing down on me
shinshin to kanashimi dake ga furitsumoru
Both wishes and regrets are just being crammed inside me
ganbou mo kaikon mo tada umetsukusu
Even the scars of our fateful spring day
kizuna musunda tooi haru no hi wo
Have fully faded away
kizuato sae mo kieteshimau no
At last, within my sparkling dream
yagate kirakira yume no naka
The dying light
kuchiteyuku hikari wa anata ni
Should one day reach you
todoku hazudakara
My tears won't stop
mabushikute namida ga tomaranai
Say, please be by my side
nee douka soba ni ite
Hold my mud-covered hand
dorodarake you wo not totte
Don't let go
hanasanaide
Please stay by side forver
douka zutto soba ni ite
Don't let go
hanasanaide
It's getting dark
kuraku naru no soba ni ite
Please stay by my side
hanasanaide
I can't see
mienai wa
Don't let go
tada zutto soba ni ite
Just stay by my side forever
hanasanaide
Just forever
tada zutto
I love you
aishiteru
Preview
I told you before. I'll be your personal superhero.
So grit your teeth!
The Final Chapter
Coming to theaters Spring 2020