05 Final Destination 5 - Horror 2011 English
[MAN 1 OVER PA]
Good morning, Presage employees.
We hope you're all ready for our exciting
team-building retreat.
Please enjoy your breakfast...
and then make your way to the bus,
which will leave shortly.
Hey, Sam, when I said, Would you put
breakfast together for the retreat?
I meant, like, some stale doughnuts,
some coffee.
But this is amazing.
Thanks, man. Just remember that when you
see my sales report for last month.
Oh, I saw it last night.
Shit. Has Dennis seen it?
Not yet.
Look, you just need to make a decision,
you know?
Are you gonna be chef or are you
gonna be sales guy?
I'm saying that as your friend because,
as your boss, I'm ready to fire your ass.
- As your friend, I appreciate that advice.
- Good.
[EVER CLEAR'S I WILL BUY YOU
A NEW LIFE PLAYING ON STEREO]
Inside my baby's room.
Hold on, man, I'll be right back.
Yeah, I guess I'm doing okay
I moved in with...
[MUSIC STOPS]
[SAM]
Molly. Your ticket's cancelled.
Tell me that's a mistake.
I was gonna tell you after this weekend.
Uh, tell me what?
That I don't think it's such a good idea.
What, the trip? It's my brother's wedding.
What's going on here?
We should talk about this later.
Let's just...
What, pretend like I didn't see this for the
next two days? No, let's talk about this.
It's not working out, Sam.
We're not working out.
Hey.
Hey. Oh, it's, uh, Candice, right?
- Not funny.
- Oh...
Okay, sorry, this is not a vacation.
Okay, this is a business retreat.
So we're gonna be all business
for the next two days.
Sorry.
I love you, but doesn't change the fact
that you're still an intern.
[CANDICE SIGHS]
Oh, um, but that 12:30 curfew tonight?
You should plan on breaking that.
Why?
For the naked team-building.
[LAUGHS]
[IN AUSTRALIAN ACCENT]
Hey, Olivia.
Don't forget these.
Oh, yeah. I keep trying to.
- Hmm.
- I like it. It's very Lisa Loeb.
Oh, well, you know...
I'd rather be very Olivia.
We got a gig on Sunday.
Yeah, I'll be there.
Morning, Peter.
- Looking good.
- Uh, hi.
Olivia. Have you slept
with every hipster in town yet?
Candice. Do you actually get paid
for this internship...
or does Daddy
just increase your allowance?
You know, if you wanna get rid of that
baby fat, you should try the gym.
They have these workout machines
that you use on your back.
You're good at that.
Sweetie, it's not fat.
They're called tits.
You're not looking so hot there,
Moll-face.
Gee, thanks.
Did you try the little jam-bread whatever
your boyfriend made?
I gotta tell you, he's a pre... Uh-oh, that's
what it is, is it? Did I touch a nerve?
- Just leave me alone, Isaac.
- Hey, Moll? Moll? Look at me.
If you ever need anyone to talk to...
[CELL PHONE RINGING]
I've been told I'm a good listener
by a lot of ladies. Shh, wait.
Tell me this is Kimber from last Tuesday.
Wait, I'm sorry, which Kimber is...?
Hey, let's sit next to each other
on the bus.
No, no, I remember you.
You were, like, a bigger gal, right?
You know what you should do?
You should apologize.
- Why?
- Doesn't matter.
Never matters. I'm sorry, because I...
[HORN HONKING]
Oh, shit.
Hey, Stan, how's it going?
Uh, it's Sam, sir.
Did you just correct me?
[SAM STAMMERS]
No.
Look at me.
- What's my name?
- Dennis.
Look away.
All set, Pete?
Yes, sir.
Yeah, we're just waiting on Nathan.
What's the one thing
we can't recycle, Pete?
Wasted time, sir.
Exactly. I wanna be on the road
in 90 seconds.
Uh, well, I just saw his car,
so I'll go track him down.
Way to show some initiative, Stan.
It's gonna be a good day.
[SAM] Hey, guys.
[MAN 1] Hey, man.
[SAM]
What's up, bud?
[MAN]
Why you riding Nate so hard, man?
[ROY] You know,
I'm just trying to make sense of it here.
Three weeks ago they brought you in
as assistant plant manager...
- and now you got a day off?
- It's not a day off. It's a re... Re...
Re... Re-what? Retarded?
It's a retreat.
[NATHAN] I don't wanna go.
I'm just following orders.
- So if you don't like it, then you can...
- [ROY] I can what? What? I can what?
Nathan, hey. Come on, man,
we're all waiting for you.
- Yeah, okay.
- Now, hold on. What you gonna say?
What you gonna say?
I got 15 years on you here. You got, what,
four years in some classroom upstate?
Listen, if you think I'm gonna sit here...
Not a good idea, Roy.
Not a good idea, man.
We're fine for the day.
Why do you let him get away with that?
No choice. He's the union rep.
I fire him and suddenly
I've got a factory full of Roys.
But I'll win him over, even if it kills me.
What about you?
When are they gonna offer you
that permanent gig at the restaurant?
- They already did.
- Dude, that's great.
[SAM]
I don't know, man.
I mean, they wanna send me
to the flagship restaurant in Paris...
for who knows how long?
Could be six months, could be a year.
I just thought
I'd be leaving too much behind.
Although now I'm not so sure.
Well, look, if you do go to Paris,
do me a favour.
- What's that?
- Take Roy with you.
Aw, hell, no.
[KNOCKING]
[NATHAN]
Hey, Sam.
You coming?
Yeah.
[MAN ON TV] Get ready for a new
adventure at 180 Corporate Consulting.
For the next two days, you will be tested,
both physically and mentally...
to help you reach your true potential...
through working as part
of your corporate team.
This weekend, a professional will guide you
to achieving better results...
What are those for?
Oh, it's, um, just something I do
to relax me. And for luck.
Gymnasts are worse than baseball players
at this kind of thing.
She's superstitious.
[CELL PHONE RINGING]
Hey, Katrina, how you doing?
Nah, just this stupid retreat thing
with the idiots from the office.
No, no, no, not you, sir. Them.
Hold on a sec, let me go some place
a little more private.
Bald's the new black, sir.
Bald's the new black.
Yeah, no, hang on a sec, babe. Just
gonna head on back to my private office.
[MAN SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY ON TV]
[WORKER]
The right-hand side!
Whew.
Ow. Damn it.
[MAN ON TV] For management,
the valuable skills necessary...
for being a good leader
will be cultivated through a variety...
[ON RADIO] Dust in the wind.
All we are...
[WORKER 1]
We'll tie it off from the far side.
[WORKER 2]
Oh, whoa!
[WORKER 3]1 Whoa, what the hell?
[RATTLING]
- Peter, did you feel that?
- What?
Something's wrong.
[WORKER 4]
Look out!
- [SAM] Molly, come on.
- Candice.
[WORKER 4] Go!
[WORKER 5] Go, go!
Candice! Candice!
[CANDICE]
Peter!
Peter! Peter!
[PETER]
No, Candice! Aah!
[SCREAMING]
No!
[WHIMPERING]
Peter! Come on, Peter, let's go!
Molly, come on!
What the fuck?!
[ALL YELLING]
[SAM]
Oh, no! No! No!
Come on, let's go! Let's go!
[GRUNTING]
[SCREAMING]
[BOTH GRUNTING]
[OLIVIA]
Oh, shit!
[SAM]
Over here! See the railing?
You can do this. Let's go.
Let's go. Do it!
You can do it. Don't look down!
Good. Good.
[CABLE SNAPS]
[MAN 1]
Run!
[OLIVIA]
Help me!
- Sam!
- Olivia!
Olivia!
- [OLIVIA] Sam!
- I'm right here. I'm right here. Okay.
[MAN 2]
It's coming loose!
[SAM] Do you feel it? All right.
[MOLLY] Olivia, come on.
[SAM] It's okay, it's safe. Now you've just
gotta follow this to Molly's voice, all right?
Come towards me.
Come on, you're almost there! Come on.
[SCREAMS]
[GRUNTING]
Come on.
- Come on. Come on!
- Molly.
[OLIVIA & MOLLY SCREAM]
No! No!
[SCREAMING]
[GASPING]
- Aah!
- Olivia!
[NATHAN]
Sam! Wait for us!
Oh, my God!
Sam!
Aah! Sam, be careful!
[GRUNTING]
[DENNIS SCREAMING]
[SIZZLING]
[PETER]
Sam!
Peter! Hurry!
Sam! Sam!
Sam!
[ALL SCREAMING]
[MOLLY]
Hold on!
Come on, come on.
[MOLLY SCREAMS]
Sam, hold on!
[YELLS]
[SAM YELLS]
[MOLLY]
No! Peter!
[BANGING AND CREAKING]
[SCREAMS]
[PANTING]
Ow. Damn it.
[MAN ON TV] - as well as
define controls and procedures.
We will help you build a culture
of corporate ethics by defining...
[ON RADIO] Dust in the wind.
[MAN ON TV]
Risk management process.
We all gotta get off.
What are you talking about?
- The bridge is gonna collapse.
- What?
- We're all gonna die.
- What the hell is going on?
We're all gonna die
if we don't get off this bridge now!
Stan, relax, it's just some construction.
Molly, please. Please, God, follow me.
Open the door.
This is a major liability issue. If something
happens to them, it's on us, you get that?
- Yeah.
- Then go get that.
Yeah. Yeah, yeah, all right.
Hey, Sam? Molly?
[SAM] Peter, please, just follow.
[PETER] Come on!
Okay, everybody just calm down.
- I'm gonna go help.
- Please don't.
[PETER]
Hey, guys, come on!
[SAM]
Let's go!
[PETER] Sam, just get back on the bus.
We can talk about it.
Molly, Sam, come on, guys.
Did he seem weird to you
when he got on the bus?
No, he was fine. It's like he just snapped.
- What's going on?
- What the hell is going on out here?
[CABLES SNAPPING]
[DENNIS]
We should, uh...
[ISAAC]
Holy shit!
[DENNIS]
Get off the bus!
[CROWD SCREAMING]
[SAM]
Come on!
How did you know?
[MAN]
That's the big question here.
How did you know?
It says right here in your statement:
I saw it collapse.
I knew it would happen.
That sounds premeditated to me.
No, no, no. That's not what I meant.
Had a vision.
Okay. A vision.
Psychic phenomena, ghosts, Bigfoot.
You actually believe in that stuff?
Don't know.
I'll tell you what I believe:
There's an answer for everything.
There's an answer for why
you knew to warn everyone...
the bridge was going to collapse,
and minutes later, it did.
I told you, I saw it conning.
I don't know how.
I just did.
And no one else did?
Like I said, it just came out of nowhere.
Did Sam have issues with authority?
Did he ever demonstrate
any sort of extremist behaviour?
No.
Wait. Extremist behaviour?
You mean like a terrorist?
You see him talk to anyone that morning?
On a cell phone, pay phone?
Just his girlfriend.
His ex-girlfriend, I mean. Molly.
- But that was in person.
- Molly.
Ex.
[BLOCK]
Tell me about the breakup.
Was he upset? Scale of 1 to 10.
It's personal.
You must have been pissed, right?
Getting dumped like that.
What does that have to do
with anything?
I'm just trying to get all the pieces
of the puzzle together...
before I start moving them around,
making them fit.
Look, I just had a hunch that something
bad was gonna happen. That's it.
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
Excuse me.
Forensics came back with the analysis.
- And?
- They're chalking it up to high winds...
and structural damage
from the construction.
High winds?
[AGENT]
Yeah. Send everyone home.
You're free to go.
I have a feeling
we'll be seeing each other again.
Call it a hunch.
[WOMAN ON TV] Authorities are calling
the North Bay Bridge collapse...
a freak act of nature...
citing a highway improvement project
that may have weakened the superstructure.
Among the survivors were eight employees
of Presage Paper...
on their way to a business retreat.
The other 17 employees
were killed in the collapse.
And although they've been branded
the lucky eight...
the surviving employees
now face an uncertain future.
[NATHAN]
Hey, guys.
[MOLLY]
Hey.
[PETER]
Anybody know
when this thing's supposed to start?
When Dennis gets here, I guess.
That agent still hounding you?
No. You heard the news,
it was natural causes.
Yeah, more like supernatural.
How you holding up? I tried calling.
No, yeah, I saw. I was just tired.
[ISAAC]
So?
How did you explain it?
I didn't.
Couldn't.
Sam, there had to be a reason.
Heh. That is exactly
what the agent kept saying.
Whatever answer you're looking for,
I don't have it.
Yeah, Sam's right.
It doesn't matter how it happened.
We should all just put it behind us
and be grateful we're still alive.
Definitely beats the alternative, right?
[DENNIS]
I look out at the faces today...
and I see family members, friends.
But the people that left us on the bridge
that day, they were more than that.
People like Jennifer Alcott...
Chris Boylan...
David Buckler.
Maybe you worked next to them.
Maybe you worked for them.
But we all worked with them, huh?
Who can forget Trevor Winn's smile?
Or Isaac Palmer.
Did he just say my name?
[OLIVIA SNORTS]
- That's not funny.
- I know, I'm sorry.
I just get weird with tragedies. I'm sorry.
[WHISPERS] I see dead people.
[OLIVIA LAUGHING]
Guys.
Death...
doesn't like to be cheated.
Excuse me?
What's that supposed to mean?
You all just be careful now.
[PETER]
Okay. Thanks for the advice!
Creepy guy.
[BLUDWORTH WHISTLING
LEANING ON THE EVERLASTING ARMS]
[COOK]
How's that foie gras, Sam? Waiting on you.
[TERRY POISON'S BALLROOM
PLAYING]
Wasted like a drunk
She drank, drunk, drunk.
Stop it.
It's not forgotten.
[COOK 1]
Thanks.
[COOK 2]
Got my dessert?
[MIKE CLEARS THROAT]
What's the matter with it?
Said it was flat. No flavour.
- Do they want something else?
- MIKE: Yeah.
He check.
Let me taste it.
The customer is an ass hole.
The bourguignon is good.
[MOLLY]
Hold on.
You mind if I come in?
Yeah. Sure.
Hanks.
I thought you'd be working tonight.
Yeah. You know,
I worked the first shift, but...
there was something else I needed to do.
[WHISTLING]
- Can I...?
- Oh.
Yeah. Sure, go ahead.
[THUNDER RUMBLES]
Thank you.
Listen...
When everything started going down
on that bridge...
the only thing I thought about
was you.
Getting you to safety.
You are the only thing
I care about, Molly.
What ever's wrong, I can fix it.
You haven't done anything wrong.
Then, what? What is it?
Paris.
We talked about that.
I'm not going to uproot my life,
leave you, for that job.
But it's the only thing
you've ever dreamed of.
Life is too short, Sam.
You have to go after what you love.
Am.
You should take the job.
Go to Paris.
- Hey.
- [CANDICE] Hey.
What's the matter?
I don't know. I'm not ready.
I don't feel ready.
It's been really hard to concentrate
after everything.
Yeah? Are you sure?
Yeah.
Because this is the last practice
before the championship.
And it's your last practice
of your college career.
[CANDICE]
I know, but...
I think you got this.
- Really?
- [PETER] Yeah.
I mean, you love it out there.
Okay. You're right.
And besides, coach would kill me. Heh.
Yeah.
Here.
Hanks.
Come here.
Bye.
[PETER]
You got this.
[MAN 1] You have to get a little more
speed. You gotta hit that follow-up.
[GIRL 1] I'm sore from the back extensions.
[GIRL 2] Really?
Okay, seriously, this is stupid.
They've gotta make it cooler
or we're gonna pass out.
They're working on it.
[CANDICE]
Well, they should have it fixed by now.
[BEEPING]
[COACH]
Come on, Candice. You're up.
[PETER]
Come on, Candice. You got this.
[COACH]
Candice, now.
[MAN 1]
Really strong value on this.
[GIRL 3]
Hey, coach! How was that?
[MAN 1] I wanna see you guys
run the routine all the way through once.
- That's good.
- Whew.
[MAN 1]
All right, Janine next. Let's go.
Let's go, ladies, and drink water.
Hat's it.
Every time, Candice.
- There you go.
- Thanks.
[COACH]
Nicely done, Candice.
Okay, go to bars.
[WOMAN]
Come on. Hit the floor. You can do it.
[PETER]
Go hard this time, Candice.
Let's be aggressive.
[COACH]
Here we go, Candice. Stay loose.
[MAN 2]
Okay, Porter, it's your turn.
Stay focused.
[MAN 3]
Good.
[COACH]
Looking good, Candice.
[SCREAMING]
[YELLING]
[GIRLS SCREAMING]
Candice? Candice?!
[GIRL 4] Oh, what happened?
[MAN 1] Don't touch her.
[COACH]
Someone call 911.
Candice?
[AMBULANCE SIREN BEEPS]
[CHATTERING]
Peter.
I came as soon as I heard.
She was doing great.
She was almost finished with her routine
and then...
Why did it happen?
This doesn't make any sense.
I don't know, man.
I'm sorry. I'm so sorry, Peter.
Let's just go, Sam.
Hey.
How's it going?
It's weird.
Being here, I mean.
It's just so quiet.
Yeah, well, Dennis had all the calls
rerouted to corporate.
Yeah, well, it's depressing.
Holy crap. Did you guys
get your bereavement pay yet?
Hey, what's he doing here?
I think he just needed the distraction.
Yeah.
Yeah, that's a bummer about Candice.
Guess we all should have seen
that coming.
What?
You see the crazy shit those gymnasts do.
I'm surprised it doesn't happen more often.
[MAN OVER SPEAKERPHONE]
Once you've handled the e-mail...
you'll need to deactivate all the
key cards of the deceased employees.
Instructions are in your binder.
Well, shouldn't that be the job
of the facility manager?
The facility manager's dead.
[SIGHS]
Dennis, you want me to fly someone
up there?
No, no, I got it.
Aw, Debbie.
You were so naughty.
[COINS JINGLING]
Fuck it.
Robert, my man.
Ow.
Shit.
You shouldn't have, buddy.
Hey, man, what are you doing up here?
Had to get off the factory floor, man.
Roy's driving me crazy.
So, uh, who wants one?
Where'd you get these?
I stole it out of Roy's truck.
Ha, ha. It's good, right? Ha, ha.
I got something better.
[OLIVIA]
Ooh, nice one.
Yeah, count me in.
Are you sure you wanna share that?
If I don't, I'll end up drinking it alone,
which is just sad.
Well, this day just got way more fun.
No, I did call you.
Of course. I just called you
right now, didn't I?
Because I really do
wanna take you out again.
Yeah, yeah, we'll do, like, a nice
romantic dinner.
You know,
somewhere maybe outside the city.
Hold up.
You know what? I gotta go.
No, no, no. I'm not blowing you off.
Hey, listen. Hey, who's my girl, Kimber?
Amber, yes, that's what I said.
Excuse me.
Amber? Amber, I'm sorry, wait a second.
Is that weird sound on your end or mi...?
Sorry about that. My, uh, sister
tends to get a little chatty sometimes.
- Uh-huh.
So tell me about stress relief.
And what does this really get me?
This covers a session
for two different physical therapies.
Like massage therapy?
Erotic massage?
This is a family operation.
Everyone on staff is professional.
Hey, that's great. I prefer a professional.
In fact, you know what? I kind of demand it.
I'm just trying to clarify, though, that
this professional experience ends, uh...
[WHISPERS]
happy.
I know exactly what you need.
[IN NORMAL VOICE]
Oh, I'm sure you do.
- Follow me, please.
- I'd love to.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Slow down there a little bit.
Yeah. Yeah, you have
a lovely little canter.
[ISAAC CHUCKLING]
Yum yum, dim sum.
Hold up there a second.
All right, these are solid.
Just making sure.
Tend to be a bit noisy,
if you know what I mean.
Ha, ha. Yo, Buddha.
Slow down on the rice cakes.
- Just close your eyes.
- Mm-hm.
- Relax.
- Ooh.
And someone will be in
to service you soon.
Oh, yeah.
[MOANS]
Feels dynamite.
No, no. You're going the wrong way there,
little lady.
[CHO SPEAKING IN CHINESE]
Oh.
Wait a second, what happened
to the younger version of you?
Okay, I'm sorry.
Do you come with subtitles?
[IN CHINESE]
Maybe I should go.
Don't know what that means. No idea. Yep.
Ow!
Fuck!
No, no, that's okay.
That's okay, I'm all right.
Holy shit, you're strong.
CHO:
What are you doing? Ow.
You're a little aggressive.
What's capay?
I don't know what that means.
I don't want a foo-hay.
No foo-hay. Aah!
[SCREAMS]
[ISAAC SOBBING]
ALL:
Cheers.
[OLIVIA]
Mm.
[CELL PHONE RINGING]
Shit, that's my ride.
Shit. I gotta go.
[SAM]
Leaving more for us.
[GLASS BREAKS]
[SAM]
All right, well, more for me.
All right, bye.
- See you later.
- Okay.
Later.
This is the end,
so, what are we toasting to?
To, uh, finding new jobs.
Because it's only a matter of time
before they shut us down.
- Hear, hear.
- Oh. To starting over.
[SAM]
Peter?
It just doesn't make sense.
She dies doing something
that she's done...
almost every day
for the last 15 years of her life.
She said she didn't wanna do it.
She said she wasn't ready.
And I should have stopped her.
I should have done something.
I should've...
Peter, there wasn't anything
you could've done.
How do you know?
[GLASS SHATTERS]
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Hello, Agent Block? This is Dennis.
Yeah, Peter just freaked out
about something, I don't know what.
Does that mean anything?
[OVER PHONE]
You told me to call if I saw anything odd.
I don't know yet, but thank you, Dennis,
and call me if you see anything strange.
Stranger.
Should we maybe have code names
for one another, do you think?
Over and out.
All right, ahem,
show me how this happened.
Don't think I can.
[BLOCK]
What do you mean?
I mean, I could try it a hundred times and
never re-create exactly what happened here.
This is some freaky shit.
[WATER DRIPS]
[ISAAC SCREAMS]
[ISAAC]
God!
[ISAAC GROANING]
Oh, that actually felt great.
[IN CHINESE]
Oh, yeah. Awesome.
Oh...
Wait. Are those things even sterilized?
No, no. I'm not catching any diseases
unless I've earned them.
[ISAAC SCOFFS]
Wait a second. You understood that.
You speak English.
[CHUCKLING]
Oh.
All right, you know what?
Let's do this.
Two billion people can't be Wong.
I said Wong. You follow me?
You get it, you're Chinese.
[ISAAC YELPING]
Ow, ow. Okay, it's in. It's definitely in.
Ow, okay, yes, it is in.
How many of these are you gonna
put in me?
[CELL PHONE BUZZING]
Oh, uh, hey,
can you grab that for me? Thanks.
Hey.
That's not very nice, you know.
Okay, your thumbs are kind of
in my eyes.
I'm not gonna lie, it's a little annoying.
Once again, Chinese lady,
I don't have a clue what you're saying.
[IN ENGLISH]
Thirty minutes. You sleep.
Sleep.
Oh.
Hey! Fire!
Hello?!
Hey!
Hey! Hey!
Hey, there's a fire in here!
Hey, there's a fire!
Get in here!
[GASPS]
[GRUNTING]
[WHIMPERING]
[CELL PHONE BUZZING]
[GASPS]
Oh, shit.
[SCREAMING]
[SIGHING]
[SCREAMS]
[SAM]
You should come with me.
To Paris?
Yeah, you know, you said it yourself.
Like, you're gonna have to start over.
Start over with me.
How many drinks have you had?
Enough. Molly, I'm serious.
Look, you were right.
If I don't take the job, I'll regret it.
But I'm not willing to lose you.
Why does it have to be
one or the other?
I'm better when you're with me.
Uh, guys, you're not gonna believe this.
They're saying it was a freak accident.
Yeah, raise your hand
if you believe that.
Who dies during a massage? Seriously.
[PETER]
First Candice, now Isaac.
It can't be a coincidence.
It's not.
Where are you going?
[NATHAN]
It's that creepy dude.
[SAM]
Why are you following us?
Who are you?
You were at the cemetery,
then the gym, now here.
What are you doing?
My job.
[BLUDWORTH WHISTLING]
[SAM]
What's happening to us?
What makes you think I know anything?
[SAM]
You warned us.
At the memorial service.
You said Death didn't like to be cheated.
It's just that I've seen this before.
You've seen what?
A lucky few survive a disaster.
And then one by one,
Death comes for them all.
You changed things on that bridge.
There's a wrinkle in reality.
And that wrinkle is you.
So, what, we're doomed to die?
I mean, is that it?
We just got our lives back,
so, what kind of fucked up karma is that?
Are you saying that we can't stop this?
You were supposed to die on that bridge.
You're not supposed to be here.
You shorted Death.
So you let Death
have somebody else in your place...
and then you take their spot
in the realm of the living.
All the days and years
that they have yet to live.
And they take your place in death.
Hen the books are balanced.
Wait a minute. We kill someone, we get
their life? Is that what you're telling me?
Don't make the rules.
I just clean up after the game is over.
[ENGINE STARTS]
Maybe that's why
Candice and Isaac are dead.
They weren't supposed to survive,
and now it's coming after the rest of us.
No.
No, not all of us.
Molly made it, she didn't die.
What?
Well, when I had that vision,
or premonition, or whatever it was...
I got you across
before the bridge collapsed.
You survived.
You saved her?
Why, because you decided that she
deserved to live more than the rest of us?
That's not what he's saying. I don't
deserve to live more than anyone.
You deserve to live
more than Candice.
Whoa, Peter, hang on.
[NATHAN]
No, look, guys, come on.
You're not drinking the Kool-Aid,
are you?
Killing people
to survive Death's list. Really?
I may not know what's going on,
but it's not what that guy's selling.
Yeah? What else is it, then?
Shit.
We need to tell Olivia.
Come on.
[OLIVIA]
My forms are all signed.
[MAN] I see that it's been quite a while
since your first consultation.
What made you decide
to take the leap today?
Uh, well, a lot is going on in my life...
and I just don't wanna miss anything...
you know, important.
Same reason I had it done myself.
- Come on in back. Let's get you started.
- Okay.
Oh.
[LEONOTTI] Yep, that's the first step.
You'll never need those again.
[OLIVIA CHUCKLES]
Here we are. Come on in.
What's with these?
Oh, just for some of
our younger patients.
And, um, sometimes our older ones too.
Come on.
[DRONING]
What was that?
Relax.
You know, it looks a lot worse
than it really is.
Okay, I'm gently going to
position your head...
and I want you to tell me...
when this feels snug.
I can't move my head.
Perfect. Just what we want.
There we go.
Okay, now comes the fun part.
Here comes a drop.
And you will feel a little numbness
in your eye...
which is a good thing.
Deep breath.
Relax.
Very good.
That a girl.
Here.
That's not so bad, is it?
Looks good.
[CREAKING]
- What was that?
- Just relax, Olivia.
I'm just gonna enter some data into...
Dottie!
Dot...
Do you know what?
My assistant's given me an incomplete file.
I'll be right back.
[OLIVIA]
Hold on, you're leaving?!
[BEEPING]
Is that supposed to be happening?!
[BEEPING FASTER]
[WHIMPERING]
[MACHINE WHIRRING]
[SCREAMING]
Help me!
Olivia Castle. Where is she?
[SAM]
She might be in danger.
She's fine.
We do this kind of procedure all the time.
[OLIVIA SCREAMING]
[SOBBING]
Help me!
[SCREAMING]
DOTTIE:
This has never happened before.
[DOTTIE & DETECTIVE
SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY]
Sam.
Stay with me tonight, please.
Of course.
Five different systems had to go wrong...
for that laser to fail us
so spectacularly. Five.
What do you want from us?
I want you to tell me
what you think is going on.
Two deaths? Okay, all right.
That's a coincidence.
Three? That's a pattern.
Now...
I know you two didn't do this.
All right?
But I think you know something.
What is it?
We don't know anything.
Take a guess.
We think we weren't supposed to survive
on that bridge.
What?
And now something
is trying to set it right.
Something?
That's all you got?
[SAM]
Right now, yeah.
But if you come up
with any other explanations, let us know.
Thank you.
Something.
Hey.
Been up long?
Uh, I don't know. I couldn't sleep.
I just kept thinking about the bridge.
Sam, you can't do this to yourself.
No. No, no, no. I was thinking about,
in the premonition...
we all got off the bus,
but the ground gave way and Candice fell.
Then the bus tipped over.
And Isaac, he never got off the bus.
He went with it.
What are you getting at?
I know that there was just
so much going on...
Look, I know that I helped you across.
Hen I reached back for Olivia.
But she didn't make it. She fell.
So first was Candice.
[SCREAMS]
'Hen Isaac.
Hen Olivia.
[SCREAMS]
They're dying in order.
Who dies after Olivia?
[SIGHS]
[NATHAN OVER PA] Roy, would you come
to the control room, please?
[MAN] Uh-oh, Roy, that's the boss.
You in trouble, Roy.
[ROY] Okay, schoolboy,
what do you wanna talk to me about?
[NATHAN] What is with your time card?
[ROY] Let's talk about my time card.
You cut my hours,
which means you cut my pay!
I cut everyone's hours, okay?
Corporate has us operating at less than
50 percent until this thing blows over.
My bookie ain't operating at 50 percent.
- My dumb kid ain't operating at 50 percent.
- Roy.
My ex-wife, she's taking 50 percent,
so I'll tell you what I'm gonna do.
No, we gotta move, man.
[ROY] Hey, I'm not going anywhere. Hey!
[NATHAN] Look, we gotta move! Gotta move!
We gotta move now!
[ROY GRUNTS THEN SCREAMS]
[NATHAN]
Roy! You okay down there?
- Hey, Dennis?
- [DENNIS] Hey.
They're closing us down.
They're shutting down the plant?
Not the plant, just us.
Just sales and administration.
Can you believe it? Us?
It's the factory guys
that usually get laid off.
Not us, we're supposed to be safe.
Yeah, Dennis, we got bigger problems.
Olivia and Isaac are dead.
Who's Isaac?
Isaac Palmer, tech support.
Wasn't he dead already?
No, Dennis.
Listen, it's going to happen to us too
if we don't do something about it.
Yeah, I understand.
Listen, it's called survivor's guilt.
No. No, guilt doesn't kill you.
Obviously, you've never met my in-laws.
I'm not fucking around here, Dennis.
Anyone could be next.
It could be you. Understand?
Nobody's safe.
What are you talking about?
We weren't supposed to survive
that bridge collapse.
And so now it's kill or be killed.
You get that, Dennis?
Whatever.
I warned you.
Do whatever you wanna do.
[DOOR CLOSES]
I will.
Hey, Agent Block, it's Dennis. Um...
Listen, Pete just came in here
and he's just completely lost it.
He's yelling about kill or be killed.
Oh, yeah,
it definitely sounded like a threat.
What happened?
[NATHAN] I don't know. I don't know.
It just happened so fast.
- Nathan. Are you okay?
- Yeah.
- We heard, and we thought...
- No. No, uh, I'm good.
Did you kill him?
What?
No. No, I just...
It was just timing, you know?
He got in the way and...
No, you did, didn't you?
You saw it conning, and then you took
his life. You put him in the way.
No, I didn't really do anything.
- Tell us the truth: Did you or didn't you?
- Hey, Peter, calm down.
Did you or didn't you?
Yes. I think I did.
I killed him.
So if the theory works,
then you traded spots.
He should have your death,
and you should have his years.
How do we know for sure?
Think there's an order to these deaths.
They mirror the order everyone died in
on the bridge.
Hen who would be next?
Who wants to be first to tell me
what the hell happened?
Who is it, Sam?
Who's what?
[ALL GASPING]
Dennis! It was Dennis.
No shit.
[MAN]
Jesus.
Why are you fighting me on this?
You're not seriously going to work,
are you?
Molly, Isaac died on a massage table.
If Death is gonna come for me,
I don't think it matters where I am.
You have to do something.
- What, kill someone so I can live?
- No, of course not.
We'll just have to
figure something else out.
I have figured it out.
Something saved me on that bridge.
Maybe it doesn't want me to die.
Maybe.
We can't live our lives in fear, Moll.
So if it happens tomorrow,
or 50 years from now, whatever.
As long as we're together...
I'll be okay.
Right? Why don't you come by
after my shift...
and I'll make you
a nice late dinner, okay?
All right, give me this.
[SIGHS]
[CHATTERING]
[WOMAN] Excuse me.
We don't have to wait for them, do we?
HOSTESS: I'll let you know.
[WOMAN] Okay, thank you.
[TERRY POISON'S GIRL ON THE RUN
PLAYING ON SPEAKERS]
To the girl on the run
[SINGER SINGING IN FRENCH]
[COOK 1]
Veal's ready, take it out.
Samuel. Get to work on the bourguignon.
[SPEAKING IN FRENCH]
Whoa.
[COOK 2]
Pan coming through.
[COOK 3]
Whoa, watch yourself.
[MANAGER] Okay. Meat's in. Pick it up, eh?
[COOK 4] Yes, sir.
Whoa.
That could've been ugly, huh? Ha, ha.
Yeah. Could've been.
Vincent, speed it up, okay?
[SAM]
Whoa, hey!
[SPUTTERING]
[SIGHS]
[CHEF]
Hey, clean that grate.
- Just met your girlfriend.
- Oh.
Are you sure it's okay
if I make her a little something?
Make sure to clean up afterwards.
I will, of course. Thank you.
And, chef...
[SPEAKS IN FRENCH]
The apprenticeship.
If the offer still stands...
I'd like to take it.
It's yours.
[WOMAN SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY
OVER RADIO]
[SAM]
Okay, no more suspense.
[MOLLY CHUCKLES]
What you've been waiting for.
Wow. You're gonna help me
with this, right?
Yeah, sure, if you want me to...
No? You don't want me to...?
So how's your French?
Heh. Terrible.
Oh, good. Well, then,
we can be terrible together.
- Why?
- I took the internship.
What? Sam, that's amazing.
I'm so proud of you.
- Peter.
- Hey.
You okay, man?
You look a little, uh, upset.
Yeah. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Just a rough couple days.
Yeah. Yeah, for everyone.
For some more than others.
Do you mind if I come in?
Oh, yeah, of course. Yeah, come in.
Here, have a seat.
Hanks.
Hey, Peter.
Hi, Molly.
Peter, can I get you anything to eat?
I can make you up some pasta.
Uh, no. No, no, no. I'm good.
Uh, thank you.
Uh, I'm sorry. I just thought...
It's good that you're here.
You shouldn't be alone right now.
Yeah, you know,
I'm surprised I'm here at all.
Uh...
Still alive, I mean.
I'm next to go, right?
It's me and then you, isn't it?
Any ways, uh, I was up all last night,
you know...
thinking about if I could really do it.
- Do what?
- Take someone else's life.
If I could actually kill some stranger,
replace their life with my own.
And I thought about it.
And I convinced myself that...
yeah, I could.
So I went on a walk.
You know, nowhere in particular...
but every couple of minutes,
an opportunity would just present itself.
He7. Like clockwork.
I could just grab somebody
and pull them into an alley.
Or just shove somebody off a curb
into traffic.
You know?
It'd be real easy.
Peter, what did you do?
- Did you...?
- No, I didn't.
I couldn't.
I realized that...
I couldn't kill somebody
that didn't deserve to die.
And I thought about Candice,
and I thought, Wait a minute.
Candice didn't deserve to die.
Olivia didn't. Dennis didn't.
I don't.
Do I?
No, of course you don't.
Well...
none of us deserve to die,
then why is it...
that you deserve to live, Molly?
You said it yourself...
you don't.
[GUNSHOT]
Go!
Repeat, shots fired.
Requesting backup. 1026 Washington.
Hide and I'll distract him.
When you can, go.
[PETER]
Not done yet, Sam.
Where is she?
- Where is she?!
- I'm not gonna let you hurt her, Peter.
You're gonna have to kill me first.
Well, that doesn't do me any good.
Heh, heh.
Death's after you too.
This is crazy, Peter. Don't do this.
Just think for a minute, all right?
You are not a killer.
I don't wanna kill anybody, Sam.
I don't wanna die yet either.
[BOTH GRUNT]
Heh. It's not your time yet.
Don't worry, Molly...
I didn't kill him.
But I didn't need to, Molly...
because Death
is gonna do that for me.
Doesn't mean I can't help it.
Hat's it.
- Are you okay? What's going on?
- It's Peter. He has a gun.
[GUNFIRE]
Oh, my God.
You killed him.
It's Sam's turn.
[MOLLY]
Peter, just go.
You have Block's life, you're safe now.
Please.
I'm sorry, Molly.
But you just witnessed the murder
of a federal agent.
And I'm not gonna spend
the life I just earned in prison.
[MOLLY SCREAMS]
[BOTH GRUNTING]
Molly, go! Go get help!
You son of a bitch!
Tell Candice I love her.
Peter.
It's gone. You killed him.
So does that mean I get Block's life?
[MOLLY SCREAMS]
Yeah.
I guess I do.
Do you mind if I take the window seat?
- You're gonna make me sit in the middle?
- Uh-huh.
- [SAM] I'm like twice your size.
- Not really.
- All right.
- [MAN 1] Sit down.
[MAN 2] I'll remove him.
[GUY] Fuck you. I'll remove myself.
[GIRL]
Get off him!
Settle down!
- Come on, Browning! Come on, you punk!
- Get off the plane!
Get off the plane. You don't understand!
[LEWTON]
Everybody just stay where you are.
- What's all that about?
- I have no idea.
[PILOT OVER PA] Ladies and gentlemen,
we'll be pulling away from the gate as...
[STATIC CRACKLES OVER PA]
[MOLLY]
Here we go.
[WOMAN 1 OVER PA] The cabin lights
have been dimmed for take off.
[MAN 3 SPEAKING IN FRENCH OVER PA]
[KANSAS' DUST IN THE WIND
PLAYING ON HEADPHONES]
With curiosity.
Dust in the wind
[MOLLY GASPS]
Sorry about that.
[WOMAN 2]
Oh, excuse me.
Those passengers who got off the plane
earlier, what was that all about?
[FLIGHT ATTENDANT] A kid had
a panic attack and wanted off the plane.
Said he had some kind of vision.
No.
Oh, my God!
[PASSENGERS SCREAMING]
Sam.
[SCREAMING]
[MOLLY SCREAMING]
[SAM]
I got you!
- Sam!
- Molly, hold on!
No!
[SCREAMS]
[SAM SCREAMING IN SLOW MOTION]
[KANSAS' DUST IN THE WIND
PLAYING ON SPEAKERS]
[CROWD CHATTERING]
Nice of you to come, Nathan.
I know Roy
wasn't the easiest guy to work with.
You know.
I still can't believe he's gone, though.
Yeah. Yeah, no kidding.
I guess it was for the best.
What do you mean?
Company did an autopsy
for insurance purposes.
Turns out Roy had an enlarged
blood vessel in his brain so big...
it was about to burst.
They said he'd be dead any day now.
[OVER SPEAKERS]
Nothing lasts forever but the...
Any day?
Life's a bitch.
Dust in the wind
[SCREAMS]
[TIRES SCREECH]
[GROANS]
[MUFFLED SCREAM]
[SCREAMS]
[YELLS]
[BLUDWORTH]
You all just be careful now.