[man muttering]
Uhh...
I'm up!
Up and ready
for a new day.
Ohh.
♪ oh, what a beautiful day! ♪
I can't find my socks!
Woman's voice:
They're in your shoes!
Where are my shoes?!
They're on your feet!
Thank you!
[robotic squawk]
Thank you, weber.
[squawk]
Ahh. Oh.
Morning, weebo.
[woman's voice]
hi.
[squawks]
Have you seen the paper
this morning?
Oh, yes, I did.
You know,
if I could solve
This whole metastable
compound business,
I could save
the college.
You know,
a new energy source
Would be worth
a fortune.
You better hurry up.
The loan's due
at the end of the school year.
Not to worry, weebo.
I'm very close.
May I see my schedule,
please?
[fork vibrates]
[matching fork's pitch]
♪ aaaa ♪
...After school,
there's something.
I know there is.
What is it?
This is
your complete schedule.
Hmm. Let's see.
Unless you didn't
tell me something.
What is it?
There's something.
There's something there.
What is it? Oh...
It's something to do
with white.
Oh, what is it?
I know it's
something important.
Well,
I don't know.
I knew it.
I'm sorry.
Oh, come on.
Ahh...
I know.
It's so frustrating.
I wish I could help you.
Ahh, but I can't.
Haircut.
Ha. [chuckles]
[fork vibrates]
♪ hmmm ♪
They can't just
close down the school.
Outside of the ivy league,
name me one private college
Or university that isn't
in financial trouble.
Oh, all right.
Name another.
You don't think
it's too much?
No. It's elegant.
And it's
a wonderful idea
To go with
the big wedding
This time.
It does put
the pressure
On the professor
to show up.
If he forgets this time,
that's it.
Well, in his case,
once is justifiable,
And twice is...
Understandable,
but 3 times...
[high-pitched honk]
Coming through.
Thank you.
[honk honk]
Morning.
Or afternoon.
Whatever the case may be.
We have a lot
to talk about today,
So let's get into it
without delay.
Oh. Oh, uh, thank you,
Whoever gave me
the plate of fruit and the...
Dead pheasant.
This does not count
as extra credit.
Last time, we were talking about
newton's law of gravitation.
To review, you see, this "g"
is like the "c" in e=mc-squared.
It's a constant--
it's a constant universe--
As much as anything
is constant in the universe.
It's saying that the force
of attraction between 2 bodies
Is in direct proportion
to the product of their masses
And in inverse proportion
To the square
of the distance between them.
An example would be--
let's make a naked man m1,
Naked lady m2.
Now, according to this formula,
their attractive forces
Would want to close
the distance to zero.
Why don't they?
Hmm?
The earth!
Ah. So...
In essence,
that is gravity,
And this...
Is dr. Richards
life drawing.
It's not my class, is it?
Philip!
Over here!
Sara!
Ooh. Very sorry.
Its own momentum.
May I sit here?
Hello, sara.
What a pleasant
surprise.
Hello, ruthie.
Martha.
Martha what?
Me, martha.
You martha.
Me professor.
Yes, I know.
Ah, I was just gonna,
you know, grade my lunch,
Eat a few tests,
and hope for the best.
How do you
hold it in?
Well, like everybody else,
ruthie.
I just cross my legs
real tight.
No, I was talking
about your excitement.
Excitement?
The wedding.
Congratulations.
No.
The wedding!
Sara and I. Oh, the wedding.
Oh, I'm looking forward
to it. Aren't you, honey?
It's today.
Are you sure?
The wedding is today, ok?
Mmm. I believe you.
6:30.
Mm-hmm.
At the presbyterian church
on beech street.
I've been there.
We had our rehearsal there
last night.
That's right. We did.
It went well?
Yes, it did.
Good.
But it
doesn't count.
No?
The wedding counts,
And I want you to promise me
on everything between us
That you'll be there, ok?
I'd rather die
than disappoint you.
Well...
This is going to be
the very last time
I try to marry you.
I imagine so.
I know that I love you,
But...
I'm not sure
that you can love me.
That's ridiculous.
I love you
with all my heart,
With every cell,
with every molecule,
With every atom.
I love you
on the subatomic level.
Hmm. Prove it to me
tonight at 6:30.
Prove what, honey?
That you love me.
I love you.
6:30.
Good luck.
Thank you, betty.
I knew I shouldn't
have come, but...
Oh, I'm very
crazy about him,
You see, miss rich,
ohh.
And this is
the god's truth--
I want him to have
what he wants,
Even if it means you
instead of me.
No, no. You love him.
Don't give him up.
[vacuum cleaner]
Hey! I'm watching
something!
Weber!
Ohh!
Why don't you
be quiet?
I'm watching tv!
Download
some manners.
Ohh!
Oh, but he ain't in love
with me, miss rich.
Mmm. Tell me about it.
[philip whistling a tune]
[philip muttering]
[resumes whistling]
Hello, phil.
What are you working on?
Can't remember? Ah ha ha.
I understand.
It's a shame they're
shutting your college down.
I read about it
in the paper.
It's not over yet.
Oh, we're doing fine
at rutland.
No such financial problems.
Hey, are you still working on
that lighter-than-air compound?
It's a...
Propulsive polymer.
And I don't mean
to be rude, wilson,
But I have to go.
Don't seem too happy
to see me, phil.
I'm not.
Well...
Ah, all the years
we've known each other,
Studying,
working together.
What happened
between us, phil?
Well, I just got tired
Of you stealing
my ideas, wilson.
[laughs] and what would
you have done with them?
You would have
misplaced them,
Forgotten them,
lost them.
There's no doubt you're
the brighter of the two of us.
You have a genius for science,
I grant you that.
It's just the science
of daily life that eludes you.
I've heard that cup
of psych before.
Excuse me.
That's very volatile.
I won't deny that I hate you
for your brilliance.
I'm petty, corrupt...
Probably would have gone mad
Trying to compete with you
in pure thought,
But, uh, I'm not an innovator
like you, phil.
I'm an adapter.
And to that end,
I have profited from your ideas.
Why are you here?
Got to be honest.
I'm here this weekend
to steal your fiancée
And make her my wife.
Well, I think you'll be
sadly disappointed.
I'll see you
at the wedding then.
[chuckles]
Ha ha ha ha!
Weebo: Ehh.
It's a little crooked.
Yeah. There you go.
Weebo.
Mm-hmm?
The wedding
was not on my schedule.
No.
Why was that information
deleted?
Hmm.
I don't really know.
Do you have
another virus?
You know,
now that you mention it,
I am feeling
a little feverish.
Really?
Mm-hmm.
You are a little hot.
Say ah.
[growl]
aaaaaaa...
Aaaaaaa...
Ah. Aaaaa...
Aaaaaa...
Aah.
Oh, yes!
Hot. Cold. Hot.
That's it.
The hydrocarbons
Have been inhibiting
the cooper pairs.
But if you go from hot
to cold very quickly,
You get
a conductive polymer,
And you complete
the metastable sphere.
Behold!
There it is!
Now it'll work.
Yes!
But, uh...
What about
your wedding?
Sorry, sara.
Ah heh. Ah ha ha ha ha!
Should I call the church
And tell them
you'll be late?
Right.
Check all systems.
3, 4, 5...
Very good.
Ah. Flowing...
In the condenser...
Pressure reactor...
Yes.
[clang, clank,
squeak, squeak, plop]
Ah ha. Ah ha ha.
[clank, clink, clink]
Yes!
Oh! It's ready.
Organic catalyst.
Give it a little positive...
And the...
Nn-ee-ee-gative.
Little touch
of electricity.
[whirs, clinks,
powers down]
Hmm.
[ding]
[moans]
Wow.
What a bang.
Yeah. Little touch
of electricity.
[laughing]
That's not helpful.
Oh, boy.
This is not good.
No, sir.
Weebo...
What?
Get a broom.
That'll help.
[organ music playing]
[crowd whispering]
2 years.
Ow.
Wow.
[warbles]
[small raspberry]
[raspberry]
[raspberries
"shave and a haircut..."]
"...2 bits"]
[whistles]
[gurgling]
[puckering]
Oh.
Ah-choo!
Oh. Bless you.
You have a cold.
You should.
It's 77 degrees kelvin.
It's very cold.
Come on up.
All right, uh...
Let's try and describe you.
Uh, you're an elastomer.
That's, uh, um...
You're highly viscous,
But yet you can phase shift.
Whew. Well, let's see.
You're...
[straining]
moldable.
[beeps]
[giggling]
[laughing]
It's a little ticklish.
Haah!
Oh.
You're foldable.
Arf arf!
You're gullible.
Oh, right.
Let's see.
Oh, wait a minute. Ok.
And...
Oh. You're ductile.
[playful snarling]
[mumbling]
Ha ha ha--oh!
You're elastic.
Let's just see
how elastic you are. Ok.
I'm the hacky sack king.
Hey. Hey. Hey. Hey.
♪ ho ay, hey, hey ♪
♪ yay hey,
hey, hey, hey, yup ♪
♪ oh, ay! ♪
[applause]
Weebo:
Bravo! Encore!
Ooooh, boy.
Uh, weebo.
Yes, sir?
Take our picture.
Ok. Look this way.
Smile.
[screeches]
huh.
Hup. Ho.
Hahh.
Yow!
Ow!
Huhh.
Olé.
Aah.
Ah.
Weebo.
Professor--
It's amazing.
Excuse me--
It's miraculous.
Professor--
It's...
It's gone.
[glass shatters]
It is.
Uh-huh.
Ohh.
Professor, I think you gave it
a little too much free will.
Oh, no.
[whimpers]
There's not a darn thing
to be afraid of, pal.
How can anything
get in your window?
It's closed, ok?
Whoa!
[thunk, cat screeches]
Huh?
Oh! No!
[tires screech]
,
whoa oh!
[gasps]
[rrrr, rrrr]
Flubber: Yah!
Yee-hah!
[small roar]
Whaah! Oomph!
[birds tweeting]
Ha.
[car alarm]
Mmm! Whaah! Weebo!
I got it!
Great.
Now what are you
gonna do with it?
Unh! It has
incredible inertia.
Maybe it's just
glad to see you.
Ha ha!
Weebo--
yes?
Oh. Do you know
what this is?
Flying rubber?
Yes. That's what it is.
It's flying rubber.
[coos]
It's flubber!
Ouch.
Thank you
for waiting so long.
Yes, ma'am.
I'm sorry, sara.
Are you going to tell me,
"I told you so"?
No. No. I'm going
to give you a ride home.
Thank you.
There you are.
Watch your gown.
I've got it.
Thank you.
[sniffs]
[soft chuckle]
Philip, muffled:
It's perfectly safe, weebo.
It's just an ordinary
radioactive isotope...
[filtered breath]
That weber is now removing
from the lead containment unit.
[squawks]
Very good, weber.
Now, you place
the radioactive isotope
Carefully behind
the sliding shutter.
See, the sliding shutter
works just like a camera.
It regulates the flow
of gamma radiation.
Instead of billions
of random particles,
You have a precise
stream of atoms.
We carefully...
Place the sliding-shutter
mechanism...
Underneath the flubber.
And I'm burning up
in here.
Weebo...
The gamma radiation
triggers a metastable decay
In the flubber
itself,
why?
Which releases
enormous quantities of energy,
And that's what
propels the flubber.
Now, doing it
this way,
I believe,
is a lot more scientific
Than dropping it
or kicking it
Or bombarding it
with light-bulb photon flashes.
Absolutely.
I believe...
By controlling
the gamma radiation flux,
We can control the movement
of the flubber itself.
Cross your fingers, weebo.
Here's hoping.
Weebo: Good luck.
[shutter whirs open]
[gurgling]
[laughing]
It works!
Ha ha ha ha ha ha!
[guffaws]
Descend gradually.
Ha ha ha!
Back up again.
Yeah!
[watch alarm]
My wedding.
I've gotta go, weebo.
But you haven't finished
the experiment yet.
You're just
getting started.
You can't just stop
in the middle.
The wedding. Oh, I can't
miss this one, weebo.
I'm aware of the time,
thank you,
But your days are wrong.
I'm getting married
Friday, 6:30 p.M.
No. No, you're not.
Why not?
Because you're not
getting married, philip.
Yes, I am.
You missed the wedding.
It's 6:30...
In the morning.
No.
Yes.
I'm sorry.
It is?
Yeah.
Sara.
You have a lot of nerve
to show your face around here
After what you did
to me last night.
Will you please
let me explain?
No.
There's nothing to explain.
You weren't there.
For the third time,
You left me
standing at the altar.
I'm sorry
with all my heart.
But please
listen to me, sara.
Please. You know me.
You know how
sometimes
I can get really
fixated on an idea?
I don't wanna hear it.
Sara, you've
gotta hear it. Sara.
This is the reason
I didn't make it
last night.
It's flubber.
Flubber.
It's a metastable
compound, sara.
In layman's terms,
If you apply a small
amount of energy...
Flubber: Whoo! Wow!
Then it liberates
An enormous
quantity of energy.
But the total effect
is transient, sara.
The moment you stop
applying energy,
It returns to
a quasiplasmoid state.
Isn't it remarkable,
sara?
What's remarkable, philip,
Is that I ever
fell in love with you.
You broke my heart...
So that you could stay home
and make some green goo.
Sara, it's much more
than that.
Flubber could save
this college.
Let me demonstrate.
No. No.
Just give me
one minute, ok?
The flubber is placed
in my back pocket.
When I exit this window,
I will fall
to the ground.
When I hit the ground,
The flubber will send me
right back up unharmed.
Watch.
Ta-ta, my love.
Are you nuts?
I'll be right back.
Whoo hoo hoo
hoo hoo!
Philip!
Ahh...
[flubber
laughs]
Ouch.
Philip.
Are you hurt?
Just my pride.
Well, if you think that you
are going to get my sympathy,
You are wasting your time!
[clunk]
ooh!
We are finished!
[weakly]
sara.
Ohh!
[crash]
[tv plays]
Junior's home.
Dad?
Dad!
Somebody in your
organization
Screwed up big time.
I got thrown off
the basketball team.
I flunked chemistry.
I'm on academic
probation.
How did this happen?
I'm supposed to get as.
At least,
that's what I was told.
The only reason I
loaned this jerkneck
college money
Was so he could
get straight as
And go to harvard
business school.
This isn't
supposed to happen.
Well, yes, sir.
We talked to
that brainard guy,
The chemistry
professor.
Now, either he did not
understand us or he forgot.
The boy knew that
we were having
Persuasion
problems, sir.
I have a science
requirement, you morons.
Quiet.
We'll have to get
the "f" changed
to an "a."
Won't work.
This guy, he doesn't
live in the real world.
He has principles.
Get something on him
That we can use to
force him to change
the kid's grade.
When a man says
he has principles,
What he means is,
he can't be bought
cheap.
Ah-choo!
Adding 500 milligrams
crystallized flubber
To common hand cream.
Stirring in solution.
All right.
Just need one spherical
test subject.
Perfect.
There, now...
Part 2.
Applying flubber
in a solution
Externally to a golf ball.
All right.
Very good.
Evenly over
the entire surface...
Kinetic test number 1.
Ooh!
Are you all right?
All right...
Applying light coating
of flubber
To surface of bowling ball.
All right.
Oh...Very good.
Right in the head.
That golf ball
was really moving.
How'd he do that?
I don't know.
Commencing kinetic energy
test number 2...
Controlling
horizontal momentum.
Commencing now.
Hit the deck!
[high-pitched] this definitely
has applications
In the field of sports.
Ha ha ho. Yes!
Heh heh.
[cat howls]
What?
Ah...
Fluid flubber...
With a convenient
spray applicator.
It's clogged. Hmm.
[dog barks]
You seen enough?
Plenty.
All right, after
the bowling ball hits,
We break
for the car.
,
oh. There we go.
You can adjust it.
Go!
Whoa!
Aah!
Aaaah!
[power tool hums]
Ah...Oh!
Yes! Weebo...
Yes, sir?
It's gonna work.
Heh heh.
I hope so.
Let me show you how.
I connected
the accelerator
To a sliding shutter.
If I press down
on the accelerator,
It releases
the gamma rays
And that increases
the thrust.
Ah, listen
to that baby chirp.
Now...
The steering wheel
controls lateral motion.
If you turn right...
Ok.
It'll steer right.
Ah.
It turns right.
If we go left,
it steers left.
So it functions a lot
like a normal
automatic shift
With drive, park,
neutral, reverse.
Yes, yes, yes--
Professor! Help!
Let me out!
Oh, weebo.
Professor...Oh!
What were you
doing in there?
Flirting with
the alternator.
Hope you didn't
touch anything.
It's not
the time to play.
We're about to make
a major breakthrough.
Yeah...
I think we're ready.
Weebo?
Yes?
What do you say
we take her for a ride?
Fly me to the moon.
That's it.
That's the spirit.
We'll fly over
to sara's house,
Park this baby
on the roof,
And then maybe she's
gonna change her tune.
You know, maybe
you should just
go without me.
Why?
Because I get carsick.
Oh, come on, you're
not gonna blow chips.
You don't have
a stomach.
I have
a queasy gyro.
Now, get over it.
This is not about cars.
This is about sara.
Now, get in here.
No.
Now.
All right.
Whoa.
We're fine now.
Heh heh.
Ah...Out
into the world.
Ok, here we go.
Look at this!
Let's see what
this baby will do.
Oh...It works!
Yes, it does.
I'm flying.
Oh, boy.
You know what this means,
weebo?
What?
I'll never have to
buy tires again.
Ha ha...
See what's
on the radio, weebo.
Ho! Latin!
♪ bum bum bum-bum
bum bum bum bum-bum ♪
♪ bum bum
bum bum bum ♪
Hey!
[singing along]
Right turn.
Whoa. Yes!
Huh?
We're fine.
Whoa!
It's all right.
I saw it.
Ha ha.
I don't think so.
Weebo. There's nothing
to worry about--
Aah!
Ohhh...Mayday!
Come on, easy...
Oh...Sorry.
First-time flyer.
Aaah!
[honk honk]
Whoa!
I'm very sorry.
[wak!]
Hang on, weebo.
Aah!
Whoooaaaa...
Ha ha ha ha!
Oh! Yes!
Oh, weebo, come on.
Please, you've
got to see this.
Wow.
Is this what
you call heaven?
Almost.
Look at it.
The whole world
below and beyond.
It's beautiful.
The solitude up here,
the stillness...
The silence.
Uh-oh.
Aah!
Aaaah!
Silly me.
Turned it off.
Turns right back on.
The shutter's jammed
probably, weebo.
We're ok.
Pleeease turn on!
For the love of newton,
turn over!
Abandon ship.
Aaaaaah...
Ohhh, yes.
Oh.
Ah, it's such a pleasure
to spend time with you
Without having brainard
hovering above us.
Mm.
More wine?
No. No, thank you.
I have to say
good night.
I have a busy,
busy day tomorrow.
Rutland would die
to have you.
We'd be together
with nothing but time.
Sara...
I'm sorry, wilson.
Forget it.
It's ok.
We have lots of time.
Listen, I'm driving up
On Thursday to rutland
for the game.
I'll see you there.
Should I make
dinner reservations?
Since rutland
is going to lose,
I'll pay.
All right.
If your team wins,
you can buy me
dinner.
If your team loses,
We go up
to the mountains
for the weekend.
Cad.
Do we have a bet?
I'll think about it.
I can't lose.
She's mine.
Sir isaac.
Oh! Ow!
Out!
All right.
One more time.
What happened?
He took a golf ball,
He rubbed
this cream on it,
And then the golf ball
took off and--whack--
Popped smith
in the head.
Several times.
Mm-hmm.
I got hit
with a bowling ball.
Repeatedly.
Were you drinking?
No.
2 beers at dinner.
Wesson had a white wine.
With dinner.
Right.
It's this stuff
he's got, sir.
It's--I don't know
what it is.
I don't know where
it comes from,
but...
It will give you one
heck of a headache.
Oh...Goodness.
Weebo: I--I wish I could
make you feel better.
Hmm.
So do I.
Oh, maybe
I'm old-fashioned,
But I believe a woman
should love a man
for what he is
And not for what
she wants him to be.
Thanks for
the sentiment, weebo.
This is really
not an area
You're qualified
to offer
perspective on.
Well, I don't have
much of a smile,
But I do
have a brain.
I have to deal
with this alone.
It's a human matter.
Not for computers.
It's for people.
Good night, weebo.
Good night, professor.
Mm...
Hmm?
Got it!
Oh, no!
I gotta turn
this thing off.
This is so
embarrassing.
Weebo, I just had
this amazing dream.
Weebo...
Hurry, hurry, hurry...
Weebo, wake up.
Mm...
Ohh...

I've solved
all our problems.
I'm all ears.
Flubber is going
to the basketball game.
Ha ha...
Basketball?
Yes.
Testing, testing.
Applying a thin layer
of fluid flubber
To synthetic leather
surface of basketball.
Application complete.
Wow.
Oops.
2 points.
Implementing plan "b."
Very tight...
Tight...
Careful, careful, careful.
Ahh.
Secondary
flubber experiment.
Control elements--bungee cord,
3:1 elasticity ratio,
50 pound ballast,
Commencing now.
Wish me luck.
Oh...
Whooooaaaooh!
Yes!
Ohhh...
Gotcha.
Bungee! Bungee!
Help!
Aah!
Aaaaaah!
It worked!
Ha ha ha ha.
Yes.
Ahem.
End test.
[muffled]
did you fully fix
the flubber on each tack
Before we painted?
Excuse me, darth vader,
but what did you say?
Did you fully fix
a 15% flubber solution
to each tack
Before weber
started painting?
Yes. I'm positive.
Excellent.
And how long
does it take
The paint
to wear off?
30 minutes.
Be a little suspicious
if the flubber started
working immediately.
Uh, isn't this
cheating?
No, it's not cheating.
It's equalizing.
You've seen the team.
They should have
their own telethon.
Come on. We've got to
win this game.
I've got to do it
to prove to sara that
flubber really works.
I'm gonna do it
right under
wilson croft's nose.
Don't fail me.
Weebo.
Yes.
While I'm out,
you're in charge, ok?
Ok.
No phone calls
to russia again.
I think
that was weber.
Oh--make sure the flubber
stays in the tank.
Got it.
Under no circumstances
are you to release it.
Of course.
'cause you know
what would happen.
Ho ho ho.
Do you
understand?
Yes, sir.
I understand.
Promise?
Have no fear.
That's my girl.
Go, medfield!
Ha ha ha...
Ok...
P.A. Announcer:
Good evening, everybody,
And welcome to
rutland arena
For the 86th meeting
of the rutland rangers
And the medfield squirrels.
Rutland, if they can
just stay awake,
Should be able to
steamroller the squirrels
here tonight...
All right, squirrels!
Listen up, here, now.
Ok, rutland may have us
in height and reach,
Weight and power...
Agility, speed, and talent.
They have the advantage
on offense
And defense.
Sure,
they're better coached,
Better trained,
And their will to win is
unmatched in the conference.
They're undefeated
in their last 108 games.
But that doesn't mean
we can't whip these guys, right?
[whistle blows]
Ohh...
Rutland!
Rangers!
Ok, flubber,
It's time that you and I
got to know each other.
Announcer: Another easy basket
for the rutland rangers.
They have built up
a commanding lead
in the first half.
Evening, sara.
Excuse--
What a coincidence.
Come on, you guys!
You gotta--
Not now, herbie,
not now!
Go, medfield!
[horn blares]
Ow!
Oh, sorry. Sorry, wilson.
See if you can
get me another
10 grand on rutland.
You got a problem,
bennett?
You're betting
against my team?
It's not your team.
They threw you off,
remember that?
Ooh, baby,
that's got to hurt.
He fouled him!
He threw his hip
into that.
Flubber?
Flubber! Where are you?
[cooing]
[big band rumba music plays]
Whoo-hoo! Yeah!
Rutland arena
for half number 2.
The medfield squirrels
trailing by 51 at intermission.
If coach barker
has any sense, he has
to be thinking forfeit...
Come on, boys.
Expect the unexpected.
Dale. Come on now,
son, you can do it.
Come on, bruce.
Here we go.
Warner,
be a flying squirrel.
Brock, the impossible's
possible.
Come on, lawrence.
Show time.
It's--
Oh.
That's pretty good.
Go! Big lawrence, go!
Whoa!
Oh.
Oohh.
Yes! Yes!
We've never--
Yeah!
Did you see that?
Did you see that,
dad? Yes!
What the--
[cheering]
Sara: We did it.
Wow!
Hey! Are you blind?
They're doing something
illegal out here.
Look, coach, nowhere
in the rule book
Does it say anything
about jumping too high.
Now sit down.
Looks like
a lonely weekend
In the mountains
for you, croft.
[whistle blows]
Yeah!
Did you see that, croft?
Dale! Dale!
Yes!
Ha ha ha ha.
No.
Dale!
No!
Not the tacks!
I don't know.
Coach:
This game is
not over yet.
You just want
to steal the ball...
Excuse me, boys,
educator coming through.
Coach, I know very little
about basketball,
But I do know chemistry.
And I believe that dale
is having a problem,
Not with motivation,
But with some sort of
adhesive build up
In the bottom of his shoes.
Do you have any
ethyl alcohol?
What?
Excuse me.
Hello, dale.
Oh, hello,
professor brainard.
May I see your sole?
I mean the bottom
of your shoe.
Oh. Oh.
Game's not over yet.
Keep your chin up
and your potential
energy high.
'cause you know why,
dale?
Get the ball, jump
with all your soul.
But I'm on this end, sir.
Jump, or I'll flunk you.
What?
You heard me.
Jump, or I'll flunk you
out of my department.
For good.
Ok.
I think that's
a little harsh...
Jump!
Announcer:
The medfield squirrels
Are trying to complete
this astonishing comeback.
Be patient, rutland.
Plenty of time, baby.
Rutland has the lead with
the clock winding down.
These rodents have fought
their little hearts out
tonight,
But it looks like
the squirrels
Are gonna come up a couple
of nuts short of a bushel.
Playing keep away
are the rangers.
Here's a wide open
"j" by hatch.
Jump, dale! Jump!
Announcer:
Jepner soaring into the air.
He makes the steal.
Look at him go!
Jepner with wings
on his shoes
Soaring to the other end.
He soars. He dives.
And medfield upsets rutland
On an incredible play
by dale jepner.
And the squirrels
are going nuts.
We won!
We did it!
Foul! Since when is it
within the rules
For a player
to accompany the ball
through the hoop?
Oh, I don't know.
Come on, I'll
buy you dinner.
Sara?
Good night, philip.
Good night.
Brainard had something
to do with this.
It's the same stuff
we saw the other night
Over at his house.
Right.
I don't know how, but
I'm absolutely certain
That your team cheated.
You're just
being a sore loser.
Sara?
May I speak to you
for a moment?
Alone?
What you have
to say to her
You can say
to both of us.
If you can remember.
Sara...
Flubber.
Flubber? Sounds like
baby shampoo.
Flubber.
It's what won the game.
That amazing aerial ballet?
Because I flubberized
the boys' shoes.
A little on the bottom...
You're remarkable.
Sara?
Good night, philip.
Watch yourself.
Now, what do
we have to do
To get you
to take a hint?
It's over, philip.
You lost.
Go home. Play with
your rubber.
What kind of car does
that brainard fellow drive?
Old t-bird. Why?
I just saw it.
So?
It was flying.
You heard me. Flying.
Weebo: Hey, who won?
We did.
Um, professor?
Why the long face?
I think you know why.
Would it be...
A sara issue?
Wish I understood
human beings.
Wish I understood women.
Wish I understood
emotions and passions.
Wish I understood any of that.
If I did, I wouldn't have had
to spend my entire life
In a laboratory
trying to figure out
How the world works.
I would have been
out in the world
Trying to figure out
why it works.
I know I love her, weebo.
Every neuron
in my limbic system
Is saturated
with phenylethamine.
That triggers euphoria,
elation, exhilaration.
Truth is, weebo...
I'm not absent minded because
I'm selfish, crazy, or...
Or inconsiderate.
I'm absent minded because
I'm in love with sara.
Professor...
That doesn't matter anymore...
'cause I don't get
any more chances with her.
Now, that's not true.
There's always
another chance.
I mean,
you never know, right?
Probably just as well
that it's over.
She has to move on.
I'm not right for her.
But you knew that,
didn't you, weebo?
Huh?
You never wanted me
to marry her.
Hmph. Well,
you were right.
I wasn't right
for her.
You're the one
for me, weebo.
Just the two of us.
And flubber makes 3.
Good night, weebo.
Good night.
Uh...Uh,
profes...Sor...
And this is
the god's truth.
I want him to have
what he wants.
Even if it means you
instead of me.
Ooh.
Sara?
Sara, it's me.
Weebo.
May I come in?
Oh, I'm sorry to
wake you like this.
But I can't ring
the doorbell.
Is everything ok
with philip?
Oh, yeah.
It's not
a conventional
emergency.
Oh, philip would be very angry
if he knew I left.
But I have to show you
something.
Do you have a minute?
Listen.
I know I love her,
weebo.
Every neuron
in my limbic system
Is saturated with
phenylethamine.
That triggers euphoria,
elation, exhilaration.
Truth is, weebo...
I'm not absent minded
because I'm selfish,
Crazy or...
Or inconsiderate.
I'm absent minded
because I'm in love
with sara.
This will be
our little secret.
[whispering]
philip.
Sara?
Sara: This is it.
This is the solution.
This is how we save
the school.
That's what
I've been saying.
Flubber.
You saw what it did
at the game.
Yes.
Imagine the line
of shoes we could
develop.
Oh, no, no, no, philip.
Not shoes, no.
Look...This.
Flight.
Flight?
Yes.
Oh, of course.
Air travel.
Oh, sara.
Yes.
We better sell this
to a car company.
Oh, philip.
Dr. Reynolds.
Professor.
It's a pleasure
to finally meet you.
I believe
you know my son.
He used to play
basketball
for medfield.
Lovely old car.
Mind if I take a look
under the hood?
Yes, I do.
And I don't appreciate
you gentlemen
Letting yourselves
onto my property.
I expected something
more complex.
There's a lot of money
in your discovery.
Perhaps we could
make a deal.
Any discovery I make
Will belong
to medfield college.
At the end of the term
there isn't going to be
a medfield college.
We'll see
about that.
You could make
a lot of money.
If we were interested
in making money,
We wouldn't have
become teachers.
You think you'll
be able to sell it
for what you owe me
By the end of the term?
We will.
I'll forget the debt
right now.
No. I'm not selling.
When I leave I take
my offer with me.
We understand.
Good luck.
Watch your back,
smart guy.
Bad move, professor.
Good morning!
Pardon me, mr. Seldon.
Are you interested in seeing
a philip brainard?
Who?
He's the college professor
you spoke to on the 6th
About a brand new
car design.
Tell him I'm busy.
Thank him
for the interest.
And send him a hat.
He's here.
[car horn honks]
He's right outside.
This watch we have hereest
is called a scarab.
It has swiss--
[yawning]
Good night, weber.
[creak]
What?
[barking]
[flubber growls]
One goon...
2 goons...
[tap tap tap]
Nate.
What?
Think I found it.
You found it all right!
Ooh.
What was that?
Take 2.
Knock, knock.
[bugle blowing charge]
Kiss me, big boy!
Did you get it?
Yeah.
I-I-I've never seen
so many zeros.
When they saw us flying,
they couldn't wait
to write the check.
This will save
the school, philip.
Weebo?
They took the flubber.
[electrical spark]
Um...She's leaking
battery fluid.
Weebo...
It's me.
Do have a signal?
Do you have
audio signal?
Tracking.
It's me
professor brainard.
Focus. Weebo.
Can you see me?
She sees me.
Weebo...
It's all right,
I--I--I--I need
to get some sort of
Extension cord,
something so I can
Recharge her.
I've gotta--I've gotta
download her quick.
Weebo...
It's all right.
It's ok.
Weebo...
Can you hear me?
It's gonna be
all right.
It's like that time
you ran into the wall
When I first made you.
We'll get you upstairs,
hooked up to a.C. And...
She's losing--
she's losing power.
It's ok.
It's all right.
I've just gotta get you
to the docking station
So I can make repairs.
Good-bye, my friend.
I don't know what
to do with her.
What happens to the soul
of a machine, sara?
Can you fix her?
I could make repairs,
But I can never
bring back the life
and will she had.
That's gone.
I never knew what
it was to begin with.
It some sort of
glorious accident.
I kept trying
to recreate it
And isolate it and
find out what it was.
I never could.
What was that word
She was displaying
on her screen at the end?
Probably a file name.
Why was she displaying it?
She was damaged.
It's--download--random
piece of information.
What was that word?
Can you remember?
No.
Try.
I am.
Began with "s."
Hello, philip.
It's me...
Weebo.
If I was human, that is.
If you're watching this,
I'm no longer here.
I hope my demise
didn't cause you
any undue distress.
Philip?
A full and complete
design of me
is in this file.
You didn't forget it.
I never showed it
to you.
I've made a few changes.
I've removed
a few of my flaws
And added
a little of you.
I hope that you can
love my daughter
As much as I loved you.
Ooh.
Wesson:
Surprise, surprise.
Professor brainard,
dr. Reynolds...
Good evening.
Sit down.
Chester: You look, uh...
Bennett: Weary.
Yes.
Weary.
You came to repay
your loan?
No.
I know you didn't.
I was just having
a little fun.
I'm here to sell you
the flubber.
You been to your house
recently?
Yes.
Do I really need
to buy it?
Flubber's a very
quixotic substance.
It's very difficult
to handle.
If you try to do
anything with it--
My man is working on it.
It won't be a problem.
I can make it
a lot easier for you.
If you give us a 30-day
extension on the loan,
I'll tell you
everything I know
And make you
a great deal of flubber.
I'll give you
the 30 days,
And after that,
you give me 2 years.
Whatever you come up with
over the next 2 years is mine.
That's not fair.
Shop somewhere else, lady.
I'll do it.
May I see the flubber?
Would you like to show
these good people
to the library?
[beep]
[whirring and gurgling]
You're going to enjoy this.
Professor?
[typing]
I got you a little help.
Ah! The lovebirds!
Wilson!
Shame on you.
Welcome.
So you finally
gave up teaching.
How could I pass up
the opportunity
To transform
the energy industry.
Flubber...
Very interesting, phil.
Too bad
it's so unstable.
I was just looking over
the formula.
Dangerous mix.
You just have to know
how to deal with it, really.
It just takes a few
simple precautions.
He, hey!
Hang on, einsteen.
Stein.
Whatever.
What's this?
It's a hand cream
that acts as
a separating agent.
Right.
[sniffs]
It's so I can handle
the flubber.
It's ok.
She needs to assist me.
Rub it on your hands.
Uh!
It's a, uh...
Squirt gun.
Heh heh heh.
What's it for?
I use that to lower
the temperature
of the tank.
Let him have it.
No, no.
Give it to him.
No. No, no.
Stop that
and give it to him.
Look, put it in his hand
and give it to him!
No, no, no, no!
Give the gun to him!
Oh.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
You ok?
It's me.
There you go.
[rrr]
Aah!
Do it for weebo.
Look out!
[beep]
Chester: Get him!
Oh, deer.
Sara...
Going somewhere?
Wilson...
Left, left, left,
right, left.
Sara!
Grab her.
Jump!
I'm coming, sara!
Sara: Whoa!
Aah!
[karate yell]
Philip: Hey, lumpy!
Philip: Come on.
Let's go, smart guy.
Ow.
Sara: Philip, look out!
[squirt]
Sara!
Philip: Get him.
This one's for weebo.
Aah!
[gulp]
Ohh!
[giggling]
Oh, mommy.
Wow.
[whistles]
Hmm.
Beautiful.
So as much as these
2 people have finally
consented together
In holy wedlock,
And have witnessed the same
before god and this company,
I pronounce--
believe it or not--
That they be
husband and wife together.
You may now kiss the...
Video screen.
Love you, sara.
[bridal March playing]
I love you.
I'll meet you
at the reception.
I'm almost done.
It's going to be
remarkable.
Philip, please be careful!
Don't worry.
These chemicals are
completely compatible.
There's no chance that
anything could go wrong!
Hey, pal...
We're 30,000 feet
up in the air.
There's no monsters
or bad guys way up here, ok?
You can look out the window.
Mom! Mom!
Flubber's gone.
Get back here!
Weebette: When we
get to the hotel,
I don't care
what you say.
I am not sharing a room
with him. Look at him!
He's gross!
He bounces all the time.
He squeaks.
He phase-shifts.
I mean,
he's a quasiplasmoid.
If it's hot in hawaii,
I hope he melts.