Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
I don't know how you talked
me into this, Tommy.
Hell, I must be crazy, heh.
You know...
if the institution ever
found out about this...
they would haul our butts
back in in straitjackets.
- Permanent.
- You didn't have to come, Hawes.
- This is between me and Jason.
- I know, I know, I know.
But I still don't get
the therapy here.
All you need to know is
Jason's dead, right, heh?
Seeing his corpse ain't gonna
stop the hallucinations.
Seeing it won't,
but destroying it will.
Jason belongs in hell, and
I'm gonna see he gets there.
Okay, there it is, huh, heh?
There's his grave.
- Okay, let's go.
- Wait a second.
What?
I gotta be sure.
Okay. There's your proof.
There's his coffin. Let's go.
- Hand me the crowbar.
- You're not gonna open that.
Hand me the crowbar.
I got it.
I really don't like this.
Die!
- Die!
- Tommy!
Die!
- Die!
Tommy. Tommy, get the
hell out of here!
Where are you going?
Hey, what's that for?
Tommy, what are you doing?
Oh, shit.
Oh, boy.
He must've really messed you over.
Yeah, fuck you, Jason.
What are you doing?
Tommy. Would you just
leave that thing alone?
Please.
Tommy, please. Let's get out of here.
My heart can't take any more of this.
Hawes!
- Don't shoot. Please.
- You in show business, kid?
- You sure know how to make an entrance.
- Look, you gotta do something.
Jason's alive. He killed my friend,
- now he's coming for me.
- You better cool out, boy.
- You almost got your head blown off.
- Will you listen, dammit?
Don't piss me off, junior or I will
repaint this office with your brains.
Look, Jason is alive.
We dug up his body.
- I was gonna cremate it.
- Hold it. What's your name, son?
Tommy Jarvis. But look,
we've gotta do something.
He's even more powerful now...
Aren't you the kid whose mother and
friends were killed by that maniac?
Yeah. Jason murdered them.
You've been in some
psychiatric clinic ever since.
What the hell's going
on with the weather?
- Sorry. I didn't know you had...
- No problem, Rick.
I want you to meet a former
resident here, Tommy Jarvis.
- He's got some kind of prank...
- There's no time for this bullshit!
- Jason's gotta be stopped!
- What prank, Mike?
- Hey. Hey!
- Unh!
That's what's known in the books as
"screwing the pooch." Iron this punk.
No, wait. You gotta listen to me.
Jason's coming here. He's after me!
- I tried to destroy him, but I fucked up.
- You got that right, punk.
You listen to me. I'm sorry about what
happened to you and your folks years ago...
but no one in Forest Green
wants to be reminded...
of what that maniac did here.
That's why we changed the name.
People wanna forget
this was Crystal Lake.
They don't need some kid
stirring up Jason shit again.
Now, you just lie down
and get some rest.
- In the morning, I'll call that clinic.
- No.
If you just go to the cemetery,
you'll see I'm not lying.
Either you get some sleep, or I'm
gonna come in there and put you out.
You're gonna be sorry
you didn't listen to me.
if you don't shut up.
Take a nap, junior.
Take it easy. It's hard
enough to read this thing.
- Well, who told me to take this cowpath?
- Wait a minute.
You admit the sign did say Camp Forest
Green with an arrow pointing this way?
I admit nothing without
talking to my lawyer.
I told you we should've left
a trail of bread crumbs.
Don't start.
So much for the head counselors ever
getting back to the camp on their own.
I say we stop the car, get out
and start screaming for help.
- I was just kidding, Lizbeth.
- Darren, we'd better turn around.
- Why?
- Because I've seen enough...
horror movies to know any weirdo
wearing a mask is never friendly.
Whoa!
There's no way that we can do this.
If the car drops into that
gully, we'll never get it out.
Do you have a better suggestion?
Yeah.
We're gonna scare him.
- We're gonna scare him?
- That's right.
Just drive towards him. He'll move.
- Nobody wants to die.
- Well, that's a freaking fact.
- Least of all us.
- Just drive.
He'll get out of our way.
Yeah. That really scared
the shit out of him.
- Oh, no.
- That's it.
We're driving this baby
back to town in reverse.
The hell we are.
- Where'd you get that?
- Don't worry about it.
- Just stay cool.
- Stay cool?
You ain't Dirty Harry.
Now, stop it.
All right, scumbag.
Get out of the road.
Now.
Darren, get back in here
right now. He'll kill you.
Not if I get him first.
No, no.
No!
Please.
Please, wait a second.
Please. Take these...
Please.
You can have the...
Come on, Dad. You can at
least have Rick drive out...
and look for them.
Megan, my deputy has more
important things to do...
than look for camp
counselors with car trouble.
Come on. Can't you put out
an all points bulletin?
- That would be wicked decent.
- Your mother own a sewing machine, kid?
- Excuse me?
- Hey, off.
Oh, hey. Sorry.
Darren and my sister
Lizbeth are in charge...
of organizing the new campgrounds
and we don't know what to do.
And all the kiddies arrive today.
We're not ready to deal with that.
I sympathize with you kids.
Best I can do is call the station in
Carpenter and have them keep a lookout.
I've got a bad feeling
what might've happened.
Hopefully they're fine,
but with Jason out there...
- Shut up.
- Jason who?
Megan, stay away from him.
He's dangerous.
I'm not dangerous.
Jason is out there.
He's looking for me. He's
probably headed back to the camp.
I told you to shut up.
You mean the Jason of Camp Blood?
- Yes.
- No.
You kids better leave.
This boy is not well and I need
to talk to him in private.
- Come on, Dad. We were just...
- Megan.
Take your friends back to the camp.
I'll let you know if I hear
anything about your camp leaders.
Don't beat him up
too bad. He's cute.
Megan, leave.
Ooh. He's cute.
I was gonna call that clinic
and have them collect your ass
but I don't want you
here any longer,
poisoning my daughter or anyone else,
with your warped sense of humor.
They have to be warned, sheriff. Jason
will return to the area that's familiar.
No matter what you call it, it's
still Camp Crystal Lake to him.
We're gonna escort you to the
edge of my jurisdiction.
Then we will say goodbye and we'll
never see you around here again.
Do we understand each other?
Shit. Shit. Damn.
I know I'm gonna get
blamed for this.
Say old Martin ain't
a good caretaker.
Hell, I'm a damn high
school graduate.
And I deserve this job.
I earned it.
Nobody's gonna find out.
Shitheads couldn't even
stick him back in right.
Well, I ain't gonna
touch the slimy sucker.
Why'd they have to
go and dig up Jason?
Some folks have a strange
idea of entertainment.
Hey, you guys. You guys,
I'm getting worried.
- About Jason? Ooh.
- No, about Darren and Lizbeth.
They should've at least
called, don't you think?
- Megan?
- What?
- Hello?
- Yeah, heh.
This girl's back in the jail
cell with her prisoner of love.
Aw. Ha, ha.
Don't be messing with no
crazy jailbird, girl.
- Those dudes are bad news.
- Oh, and how do you know?
I been around long enough
to see plenty on TV.
- TV?
- Yeah. Heh.
I don't know about that guy, Megan.
He seemed pretty weird
with all that Jason stuff.
You know what you need? I've been telling you
this forever. You need a guy like me, eh?
- Guy who's not so twisted.
- Maybe he was telling the truth.
Just because our parents
keep telling us...
that Jason was only a legend
doesn't mean it wasn't true.
What if he did come back here...
looking for the camp counselor that
caused him to drown as a boy...
searching for the one that
decapitated his vengeful mother?
And you do know what today's
date is, don't you?
And I can think of only one
thing even more terrifying.
What?
The kids are here.
Yeah, right!
Be careful. You may fall.
Here they are.
And they're all yours.
Think I'd rather
deal with old Jason.
Once we nail Roy,
that's it. Victory is ours.
It's taking forever. I'm starving.
That's your trouble, Larry.
That's why your sales are
always behind quota.
Your instinct to eat is stronger
than your instinct to win.
- You're a real ass, you know that?
- Better than being all ass.
- Oh. That is so unfair.
- Oh, here we go with unfair again.
- War is not fair.
- Give me a break, would you, please?
- This is not war. This is a game.
- War is an ugly thing.
- I'm hungry. I wanna get a sandwich.
- Wait till we kill something, then you can eat.
Calm down, would you?
- You're an insurance salesman.
- Death is my business.
You become this whole other
person when we're out here, Stan.
- I don't like it.
- Hey, this is a man's game.
Requires a man's cunning.
A man's intelligence...
Fuck!
- With a woman's touch.
- Now, wait a minute!
- I thought Burt shot you!
- See any paint?
Sorry, guys. I did in Mr.
Commando, weapons and all.
Survival's the name of the
game and that flag is mine.
I can't believe this.
Burt never gets shot.
- Never should've let her play.
- It's a damn company exec game...
and she's a damn company exec.
Now, now, boys. Don't be spoilsports.
Put on your headbands.
Dumb broad. She tricked me.
God, they're gonna
laugh for months.
She should've stayed in the
kitchen where she belongs.
A woman shouldn't even be
allowed in these games.
It's not a game. It's life.
Jason really screwed up that
poor son of a bitch's mind.
He really believes that Jason's
still alive, doesn't he?
That's not what worries me.
It's how far he'll go
to try and prove it.
Darn.
Oh, no.
No.
Oh, my God. No.
What...? Come...
Where...? Oh, no. Oh, no. God.
Come on out, you guys!
The game's over.
You don't know. What about Roy?
- Nobody's seen him.
- Of course not.
If he hasn't accidentally pelleted
himself, I'm sure he's lost.
- Well, the game's not over till it's over.
- That's right.
Shh.
Wait a second. What was that?
- What?
- Nothing.
I could swear I heard something.
- I'm hungry.
- Oh, God.
Be quiet.
Oh, my God. My God.
Help, guys! Help me!
Help!
Oh, no. Help me, guys! Help!
Oh, God. Oh, God. Oh, God.
Oh, God. Help me. Somebody help me!
He's gonna kill me.
Fucking-A, what did I tell you?
Hit the noise and the cherries.
Sheriff. Sheriff, wait.
- You gotta listen.
- I'm tired of listening to you, kid.
I gotta... I gotta show
you Jason's grave.
I've seen it. Come on, get up!
- Get up!
- Please, sheriff.
You'll see we dug it up.
Well, he must've got chilly in the
night and pulled the dirt back over.
That's not right.
Somebody covered it over.
- I gotta see it.
- Freeze it, psycho.
Now see what you've done.
You made my deputy
draw his revolver.
He's been dying to try out
his mail-order laser scope.
Wherever the red dot
goes, you bang.
- What's the problem, sheriff?
- No problem, Martin.
Just a vagrant kid.
We got it under control.
- Did you cover up Jason's grave?
- What are you talking about?
Don't concern yourself.
This kid needs treatment.
Jason's not in his grave,
Hawes is. Dig it up!
You gotta dig it up!
Dig him up?
Does he think I'm a farthead?
Yeah!
Okay. Is this gonna be
the best weekend ever?
Yeah!
- Are we gonna go fishing?
- Yeah!
- Are we gonna scare all the boys?
Okay. Are we gonna, uh...?
Are we gonna not eat
Brussels sprouts?
- Yeah!
- What happened to Cort?
Are you ready?
He's taken the young men off to
teach them my favorite sport.
- Heh, which is?
- Boy Scouting, honey.
Heh. Cort? You've gotta be kidding.
You gotta be kidding.
Listen, you obviously don't
know anything about Indians.
Probably none of you do. Look, here's the
story. These are called Indian markers.
Let's just say you have
a chief, all right?
And he dumps his squaw
or his wife or whatever.
He decides, "I'm gonna pick up with
another woman and take off with her."
He takes off, leaving his
son with the mother.
A week or two later, the son
wants to catch up with his dad.
He wants to learn how to
shoot a bow, kill a buffalo.
So, what happens is
he comes along...
sees the rocks, says, "Dad,
he went that way," obviously.
He knocks them all down before
the mother catches up...
because he doesn't wanna
see any of her anymore.
Pretty much, that's the basic
story. It tells you where to go.
If this is exciting as it gets,
we're in big trouble, dude.
Let's go.
Like the sign says, you are
now leaving Forest Green.
Don't forget to buckle up.
You are damn lucky, kid.
With all the grief
you've given me...
you should be leaving wearing
your balls as earrings.
And if I ever see you around here
again, you can guarantee it.
Let's get the hell
out of here, Rick.
Take you home again, Kathleen
To where...
Your heart will feel no pain
I'll take you home again
Steven, it's beautiful.
God, I love it. I really do.
I don't know. I mean,
you know, I'm sort of hurt.
You thought I brought you up
here just to... Ah, never mind.
Yeah, well, I guess I do owe you.
Yeah. No, look. I have a headache
and I've been working out.
- Mm-hm. Ah.
- I'm... I'm sore...
- And...
- Yeah. Right. Forget about it.
Well, it's a messy act and...
- What the heck.
- Great.
Again, Kathleen
Oh.
Where'd the road go?
I can't find the road.
Where's the road?
Kathleen, you led me astray.
What's that? What's that?
Huh?
Darling, you're gonna
be the death of me.
Yeah, but what a way to go, huh?
- Stay here.
- Steven, please.
- No, Steven. Don't.
Steven. Steven, what's going on?
- Annette, let's go.
- Okay.
Never mind.
- What are we gonna do?
- We gotta get to the sheriff's office.
- Pick a card.
- I don't wanna play anymore, Sissy.
- Oh, come on. Pick a card.
- No, I really don't.
Okay. Okay. I've got a great game.
It's called Camp Blood.
- Great.
- Yeah.
The object of the game is, first
you take this jack of spades...
which is Jason, right?
And then you have all these face
cards, which represent counselors.
The queen of hearts is me.
- Now, who do you wanna be?
- Oh, come on, Sissy.
Okay, you be the queen of diamonds.
What you do is you shuffle Jason
up in these cards here...
and you put them in piles, because
the piles represent cabins.
Now, the object of the game is to
find out which cabin Jason is in.
Did Megan say when
she's coming back?
Of course not. You wanna
bet she took him...
a loaf of bread with
a saw hidden in it?
I'm gonna call her.
Hopefully her dad has found out what's
happened to Darren and Lizbeth.
I say if they're not here by
morning, we send the kids home.
We're not prepared to run this...
- She saw a monster!
- Who did?
- It's okay. We're here.
- Yeah, honey, we're here.
- So, what happened?
- There was this monster.
And he was after me and
he wanted to kill me.
- Where?
- He was everywhere.
- Oh, you mean you had a bad dream.
- No.
It was real, just like on TV.
Okay, listen, sweetie.
What's your name?
- Nancy.
- Well, Nancy...
I'm Paula, remember?
And this is Sissy.
And we're gonna be right out there all
night so nothing can hurt you. Okay?
So no more bad dreams can
come around here, huh?
Good. Okay, lay down.
There. Okay?
Okay.
Hey, wait a minute, where's Cort?
I haven't seen him for hours.
I don't know. He called somebody,
then he just took off.
Said something about checking out
things that go bump in the night.
You're the best. The best.
You gotta keep it up to
the end of this song.
How much longer?
It's only 10 more minutes.
- Fuck!
- Oh, yeah.
Wait a sec and I'll...
Cort, you didn't already?
Oh, come on, wasn't that
the end of the song?
Great, just great.
If this thing is burned out, frigging
Horace is gonna have my butt.
- Who's Horace?
- My frigging stepfather...
and asshole in residence.
Ah. Now, how'd that happen?
What?
Will you go out and
plug the cord back in?
- Who unplugged the cord?
- Smokey the Bear. I don't know. Go do it.
- Do you know how cold it is out there, Nikki?
- I don't give a shit, Cort. Go do it!
You're a real pain in the ass.
A major pain in the ass.
Will you hurry up? I gotta get this
back before Horace finds out I took it.
Hurry up.
- Will you come on?
- All right.
I'm going. I'm going, okay?
God, shut the hell up.
- What...?
- Cort.
- Nikki.
- What are you doing?
- Look at this.
- What happened to it?
I don't know, but I say unless you
wanna look exactly like it...
we make this place a
memory right now.
Nikki, somebody's out there.
- What if it's that guy Jason?
- I don't wanna know.
- No way. This isn't happening.
- You're right, it isn't.
- You gonna drive or not?
- Whoo! Out of here.
Shit! Damn it, Cort.
Shit!
Go!
Shit! Cort!
Whoo! Boy, this baby jams.
Let me tell you, for a big
truck, it's not bad at all.
That's it! Pull over, I'm driving.
No way, babe, I wanna rock!
Yeah! Whoo.
Whoo. This is... This is great!
I've never driven a house before.
I like this. This is great.
Sounds like you're having fun back there.
What are you doing? Need some company?
Ooh, that sounds great.
Do you need some
company or what, huh?
Cort!
Whoo! This is great. I am
having such a good time.
Ha, ha. This is great!
Hey, Nikki, what are you doing
back there, taking a dump?
Mind if I come back
and snatch a peek?
Or vice versa?
Whoo! Yeah!
Nikki, listen to this.
What makes you so high and mighty?
You keep forgetting, little
Megan, I'm the parent.
You're the child.
When are you gonna stop
treating me like one?
When you stop acting like one.
Tommy Jarvis is a very sick boy.
Oh, how do you know, Dad? What'd
you do, take his temperature?
Better watch that
smart-mouthing, young lady.
"If your mother were
still alive..."
That's it. Out. I don't need
this tonight. Out, Megan.
Sheriff's office.
Oh, I'm sorry, he can't come
to the phone right now.
He's in the can draining his lizard.
May I take a message?
Oops, here he comes
now. Please hold.
- It's Rick.
- What?
- What kind of problem?
- You better get the hell down here.
I found what's left of
those counselors...
and it looks like someone did
them in using Jason's old MO.
I knew I should have done
something about that son of a...
Where are you?
- Right, I'm on my way.
- What is it?
Seems your boyfriend wants people
to believe Jason has returned.
- I thought Jason was just a legend.
- That's right.
Only, Tommy wants to prove
the legend is true.
Now, you stay put.
And I'm not kidding.
Sheriff's office.
I'm sorry, he's not in.
Can I take a message?
Oh, hi. This is his daughter, Megan.
I met you this morning, remember?
Yeah, hi. Listen, I've gotta talk
to your dad about... About Jason.
I've got a plan. But first I
need to buy some supplies and...
Tommy, my father's out
looking for you right now.
Something happened tonight and he's
sure you're responsible for it.
- If he finds you, he's gonna...
- Yeah, he made that real clear.
Megan, Jason is out there.
I'm positive he's headed back
to the camp. He's gonna...
- Where are you? I'll come pick you up.
- What?
It's the only way. If my
father sees you in your car...
he's gonna nail you in
a second. Where are you?
Uh, Karloff's General
something, um...
I know just where it is. I'll see
you in a half-hour, heh. Whoo!
Megan.
- Okay, lift it, ugh.
- Ugh.
I want all officers, units and
stations within a 50-mile radius...
- alerted about this wacko kid.
- Yes, sir.
You have his vehicle description.
I want roadblocks.
- Sheriff, get over here!
- Shit, now what?
Come on.
Mike, over here.
Is that all you found?
I wish it was.
I'll order up some body bags.
Our boy sure wants us
to believe his story.
Well, he picked the right
day to pull this shit.
What do you mean?
Happy Friday the 13th.
All right, who's out there?
What's going on?
Think I hear somebody
fooling around out there.
It's gotta be Cort. You know how
he loves to try and scare us, heh.
Teach him a lesson.
You guys, try not to wake the kids.
I'm gonna borrow your car.
You can't do this.
It's too dangerous.
You gonna talk about dangerous?
You wanna leave that truck in plain sight?
Hide it behind the store
and let's get out of here.
Look, this isn't a game.
You're not going with me.
I'm already responsible for...
You said you needed
some supplies, right?
- Yes, but I...
- Then let's get going.
We can argue about it on the way.
Tell me what you need and I'll get it.
- Megan...
- Besides, nobody drives this puppy but me.
Now, hide that heap and let's book.
- Can't this tub go any faster?
- You got it.
- You just keep your eye out for roadblocks.
- Okay. There's one.
Get down.
Hey! Hey!
Unit 45, Officer Pappas to
Sheriff Garris, do you copy?
- Yeah.
- We've got a different vehicle...
that took off when they saw us.
I saw somebody duck down.
- Got a description or plates?
- I got the whole enchilada.
It's a '77 orange Camaro. License
number Mary, William, 85-10.
That's my daughter's car.
Uh, how do you want
us to proceed, sir?
With extreme care, asshole.
If that kid is with her, there's every
good chance he'll do something crazy.
Please, don't do anything crazy.
I know what I'm doing. I got
you your supplies, didn't I?
If I can just get us to
Cunningham Road, I can lose them.
Stay down.
Whatever you say.
That's what I want.
This is gonna be a
hairy turn. Hang on.
Megan, step out of the car.
End of the line.
Oh, shit.
Paula, I can't sleep. I'm scared.
I saw someone at my window.
- Where did you get this?
- I found it outside.
Ah, you know what? Sissy and
Cort are playing jokes.
You know, trying to
scare each other.
- Why?
- Well...
because grownups think
it's funny to be scared.
- What?
- Heh, never mind.
I can't believe it's that
late. No one called.
- I better...
- Who you calling?
Why don't we go and find
Sissy and Cort first.
Then you can go to bed.
- Wait. What if they try to scare us?
- Well, we'll scare them right back.
- Okay, heh.
Let's go. Let's find them.
I said, shut up!
All he's asking you to
do is just check it out.
- You've got me where you want me.
- If I had you where I wanted you...
they'd be pumping your
ass full of formaldehyde.
Why don't you at least call the camp,
make sure everything's all right.
We have, trying to track you down.
The phone there's disconnected.
- Doesn't that tell you something?
- Yeah, they should've paid their bill.
Sheriff.
You just sit tight, Jason.
As soon as the authorities...
- from Carpenter get here...
- Sheriff! You better take this.
Sheriff Garris.
What time?
I'll be right there.
- What's happened?
- Rick.
Keep an eye on this wacko.
I'll be back as soon as I can.
What's going on?
Make sure my daughter
stays put. She's grounded.
Tell me!
They just found your
friend Cort and some girl.
Her head was crushed in and Cort, he
had a knife rammed through his skull.
No.
Tommy Jarvis is a
psychopathic killer.
- He wants you to believe that...
- It was Jason.
Sheriff, when did it happen?
For God's sake, Meggie,
stay away from him, please.
- What time did this happen?
- What difference does that make?
- What time?
- Eight-thirty, 9:00. Why?
Tommy was with me
all that time, Dad.
Rick...
I'll call you from there.
Lock him up.
Okay, flash, into the cage.
I'm sure Sissy and Cort are
back in their cabins by now.
So you just go back to
sleep and don't worry.
But what if I get scared again?
Shh!
You know what I used to do when
I was a little girl and I got scared?
I would close my eyes and
say a little prayer.
And you know what? Pretty soon,
everything scary went away.
It worked for me. I bet it'll
work for you too, heh.
- Good night.
See you in the morning.
Cort?
Sissy?
No!
- No.
- Yes.
So, what are you drawing?
So, what's it to you?
Pipe down, Jarvis!
I was just curious as to
what she's drawing, is all.
There, you happy?
- No.
- Why?
Because it stinks.
- Okay, give it back.
- Come and get it.
I'll get it for you, babe.
Come and get it.
Give it back, punk!
Hey!
Hey, hey! Get your
hands off her, animal.
You little turd! I ought
to punch you silly.
Let him out of there, Rick.
Megan.
Don't clown around.
I'm not the one with
the funny red nose.
Now, open the cell and let him out.
Meggie.
I'm not kidding.
You better do as she says...
because wherever the red
dot goes, you bang.
You son of a bitch!
You're really screwing
up here, missy.
Don't do this, Megan!
Megan!
- I thought he took your key.
- He did.
- But I've got my hide-a-key.
- Not this time.
- Hey, wait a minute.
- I appreciate you getting me out...
but I have to finish
what I started here.
Come on, hot lips, let's go.
You drive, I'll navigate.
Let me know when we're about to blast
into hyperspace. I'll fasten my seatbelt.
I got a bad feeling
we're already too late.
Are you sure this is gonna work?
Why didn't we just bring
the gun and blow him away?
The only way now to stop Jason is to
return him to his original resting place.
Where he drowned in 1957.
- Lake Forest Green.
- Crystal Lake.
Where this nightmare began.
Now I lay me down to sleep.
I pray the Lord my soul to keep.
If I should die before I wake,
I pray the Lord my soul to take.
Now I lay me down to sleep.
I pray the Lord my soul to keep.
If I should die before I wake,
I pray the Lord my soul to take.
- So, what's the story here?
- Why don't you boys nose around.
I gotta break the news to Megan's
friends about what's happened.
- Holler if you see anything.
- Like what?
Anything that don't belong.
And don't wake the kids.
Come on, handsome.
Girls?
It's Sheriff Garris.
Hey!
Oh, my God.
All right, come on out of there.
I'm gonna ask you one more time.
Come on out of there.
Hey, hey, hey. What are you
doing running around out here?
- Now, you go on back to bed.
- No! No, there's a scary man!
Oh, what scary man?
No, no, no. It's okay. It's okay.
It's okay. Everything's all right.
Everything's okay,
honey. It's okay.
Come on, boys, let's go.
Come on, kids. Come on.
Now, I want you to listen
to me very carefully.
I want you to all lie down
on the floor under the beds.
Do not get up until I come back. Do you
understand? Now, move, hurry. Come on.
Come on.
Fuck!
- See, they did show up.
- Yeah.
We'll have to take...
Megan, wait!
Oh, God. Dad! Daddy!
It's okay. It's me, Megan.
Don't be afraid. It's okay.
Shh, everything's gonna be
all right. Don't be afraid.
- Is everyone okay?
- They're fine. They're fine.
It's okay. Everything's
gonna be just fine, okay?
I'm gonna go find my daddy, the sheriff,
and then we can all go home, okay?
Now, uh, go back and lie down
where you were before...
and stay there. Go ahead.
And we'll come back and get you.
I promise. Go lie down. Stay there.
What do you think?
I think we're dead meat.
Daddy!
Dad, answer me!
Dad, where are you?
Megan! Use your dad's
radio! Call for help!
And an ambulance!
Oh, God.
Stop it!
Daddy, where are you?
Daddy, please come to help us!
Daddy!
Real dead meat.
So, what were you gonna
be when you grew up?
Daddy, where are you?
Daddy! Come help us, please!
No, not her!
No!
Dad!
Dad, answer me!
Ouch.
You've gotta help me find my dad.
We need him to help us.
Hand me the padlock.
Aren't you listening to me?
Yes, and I said,
hand me the padlock!
- Here! You're gonna be sorry.
- I hope not.
Megan.
Megan, get back to the
cabin with the kids.
Megan, please!
- Wait a minute. You can't do this.
- Get back in there before it's too late.
Megan, no!
Megan!
Megan! Megan, no!
Jason!
Jason, come on!
Come and get me! It's
me you want, remember?
That's it. Come on,
maggot-head. Come on!
Come on, maggot-head.
That's it, come on!
Tommy!
Get out of there!
Hurry!
Hey, asshole!
It's me you want,
remember? Come on!
Come on, chickenshit.
Come on, I'm standing here
waiting. Come on, you pussy!
No!
Is he killed?
Stay here.
All right! Yeah!
It's over.
It's finally over.
Jason's home.
You're with your baby
And you're parked alone
on a summer night
You're deep in love but
you're deeper in the woods
You think you're doing all right
Did you hear that voice?
Did you see that face
or was it just a dream?
This can't be real,
that only happens, babe,
On the movie screen
Oh, but he's back
He's the man behind the mask
And he's out of control
He's back
The man behind the mask
And he crawled out of his hole
You're swimming with your
girl out on Lover's Lake
And the wind blows cold
It chills your bones but
you're still on the make
That's a bad mistake
Ah, but the moon was full
And you had a chance
to be all alone
But you're not alone
This is your last dance
And your last romance
Yeah, cos he's back
He's the man behind the mask
And he's out of control
He's back
The man behind the mask
And he crawled out of his hole
Oh, if you see him coming
Get away if you can
Just keep on running,
run as fast as you can
He's a dangerous, dangerous man
And he's out tonight
And he's watching you
And he knows your house
No, don't turn out the lights
Yeah, cos he's back
He's the man behind the mask
And he's out of control
He's back
The man behind the mask
And he's after your soul
He's back
He's the man behind the mask
And he's out of control
He's back
The man behind the mask
And he's after your soul
He's back
He's the man behind the mask
And he's out of control...
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org