Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
I don't wanna scare anyone...
...but I'm gonna give it to
you straight about Jason.
His body was never recovered
from the lake after he drowned.
If you listen to the old-timers,
they'll tell you he's still out there.
- Camp Crystal Lake is jinxed.
- It's got a death curse.
Some folks claim they've
even seen him...
...right in this area.
Who is that?
Oh, hi. What are you doing
out in this mess?
The girl who survived that night
at Camp Blood, that Friday the 1 3th...
...she claims she saw him.
The boy. ls he dead too?
We didn't find any boy.
Then he's still there.
She disappeared two months later.
Legend has it that Jason saw
his mother beheaded that night...
...and he took his revenge.
A revenge that he'll continue to seek
if anyone enters his wilderness again.
Jason was my son.
And today is his birthday.
That's a good boy.
- Good.
- Good Jason.
Jason's out there.
No! Aah! Aah!
You can't be alive!
Got another white coming in, Larry.
Let's keep the area clear.
Where are they?
What do you need
and where do you need it?
We got ten of them.
Yours is in the barn.
What's wrong with him?
He's dead. Yeah, they're all dead.
You can pull it up over there.
- All dead. Some emergency.
- Put her over there.
This the guy that's been leaving
the wet stuff?
This time he got seven kids
and three bikers.
This time they got him.
- Lainie?
- Hmm?
- Belt him.
- Yeah.
What's the matter with you?
He's dead.
Okay,
boys and girls, let's get rolling!
God!
Dr. Wellsely to O.R. 2.
Here, sign it.
Hmm? Mm.
- This your last?
- No, got one more over there.
- Real cute girl.
- Was.
She still is. All you gotta do
is go over there....
Nice talk. Real nice talk.
I get the top copy.
- Take care, Axel.
- Mm.
Man, he's crazy.
Miss Aaron,
telephone, please. Miss Aaron.
- I'm free, doll.
- And a bargain at twice the price.
- Hey. What's the matter?
- I have a headache, Axel.
- For you, I always have a headache.
- Oh, I can fix that.
Oh.
Meet me in the cold room.
I'm closing up for the night.
What do you say? Okay?
Axel, I am not going to
fake any more orgasms for you.
You got the curse?
If I do, you're it.
Axel?
Axel.
Oh, Axel.
Axel?
Aah! God, Axel!
I'm so glad you could come.
Axel, you are the
Super Bowl of self-abuse!
I just came to watch the news.
Now back to today's news.
The tragic story of mass slayings....
I'm sorry.
And so begins
yet another chapter in a story...
...most residents of Crystal Lake
had prayed was over.
A trail of mangled bodies has finally
led local authorities to conclude--
I really came to watch the news.
We're still awaiting
positive identification of the body.
But to answer your question,
yes, the man responsible...
...for the murders in Wessex County
this past week...
...is at this moment in the Wessex
County Medical Center morgue.
- Yeah!
- Hey.
That's you they're talking about
on TV, pal.
I don't believe you, Axel.
- Then...shut...my...mouth.
- My...mouth.
--in the wake
of what will always be known...
...as the Crystal Lake massacres.
And now back to you, Bill.
Jesus Christmas!
Holy Jesus goddamn!
Holy Jesus jumping Christmas shit!
You better get that sucker
in the icebox!
I must be nuts! I mean, I really....
- Good night, Axel.
- Hey, where are you going?
I'll tell you where I'm going,
I'm going crazy!
Shit! Shit!
Hi, girls. Thanks for waiting.
Oh, no.
Shit!
Get lost, Axel, I'm busy. I've had
more than enough of you for one night.
Read my lips. Leave me alone! Aah!
No!
- I talked to Dad.
- How is he?
Oh. He said he was lonely.
He asked me to come out and see him.
Did he tell you to take a number?
No, but he asked about you.
Did he?
Actually, you really should
go out there to see him.
Yeah, I know.
I bet he could stand a visit.
What do you think?
- I think you're getting horny.
- Oh!
Tommy, turn that down!
Mom, I got 98,000.
- How many robots is that?
- Thirty-five.
Now, why don't you try killing
a few more up in your room?
I can't. I need a bypass patch cord.
Maybe you can get one in town.
Trish will drive you.
Oh, honey, get a haircut, hmm?
Oh, Ma.
- That's a nice mask.
- Do I have to get a haircut?
You're getting pretty terrific
at making those things.
Thanks. I just customized it.
- Where's Gordon?
- He went out.
Oh. Someone left the front door open.
We're in the country.
Well, what happens
if the psycho wanders in?
He'd probably challenge him
to a game of "Zaxxon."
Hear any more
about the place next door?
Mm-hm. It's been rented by some kids.
- Great.
- How many?
- Six.
- It'll be nice to have some company.
Country boy, country boy
Sitting in the grass
Along came a prairie dog
And crawled right up his
Ask me no more questions
You broke up with BJ Betty?
So to speak. And would you
lighten up on her? She's all right.
Yeah, I'll say she's all right.
You should have treated her right.
I mean, that girl wanted
to be treated right.
I did. I did. I treated her right.
I treated her right.
That's what's driving me so crazy.
I mean, first I would call her
and she would take my calls...
...but she would have something to do.
And then she wouldn't even
take my calls.
I mean, can you figure that?
What the fuck happened?
Let me put it in the old computer.
- No, I'm serious about this.
- Hey, the computer don't lie.
Now, let's see.
What?
It says....
It says you're a dead fuck.
What? A dead fuck?
A lousy lay. You know?
- A dead pecker.
- Oh, I see.
Don't hold it back from me, doc.
Give it to me straight.
I did not say it. The computer did.
- Yeah, well, there is no computer!
- Aha! And there's no Betty either.
Then I'm a dead fuck.
Like I said, the computer don't lie.
God, I'm horny.
- Where are we now?
- Lost.
We are lost.
Pretty creepy, huh?
Yeah.
All right, I think I got it.
Go straight ahead two miles
and hang a right.
Paul, let's pick her up.
Sammy, where we gonna put her?
Hey, honey, you got a sister?
Ruff, ruff!
Oh, Mom, I thought we were having pizza.
I thought so too, honey, but we've got
a refrigerator full of leftovers.
You're not smiling. You're not
in the mood for my tuna salad?
- Well....
- I'm not either.
I'm in the mood for....
- No.
- Yes.
I feel like....
- No!
- A Jarvis sandwich!
- Wait, somebody's at the door.
- Oh, no, you don't.
- No, Mom, I heard that too.
- I'll go.
Gordon! Hey, Gordon.
Where have you been, huh, Gordon?
Have you been sneaking around?
Do you have a girlfriend or something?
Tommy, close the door.
Listen, Gordon, we'll talk later.
All right.
- Hit me with the beer.
- You got it.
- See? What did I tell you?
- What? You told me you were horny.
No, see, I've come to realize
that a guy can have a good time...
...without having to
have girls all about.
That's a sin, you dead fuck.
I really, really don't want you
to call me that anymore.
Aw.
Hi. What a handsome mutt you are.
- His name's Gordon. I'm Trish.
- Hi, Trish.
I don't know how you do it.
Heh. I don't know how you don't.
I mean...
...you do it with everybody.
Oh, I do not!
I do it with Paul.
- Really?
- Come on, Sara!
You know how guys are.
They lie about that all the time.
They say that about everybody.
They don't say anything about me.
I mean, I don't have....
- Ha, ha. A reputation?
- I didn't say that.
Oh. Look, I got my reputation
in sixth grade.
Well, what does Paul think?
Paul thinks I'm great in bed,
so that's where I keep him. Ha, ha.
What are the sleeping arrangements here,
anyway?
Paul and I are taking the bedroom
at the end of the hall...
...so you and Doug can sleep next door.
Really?
Yeah. It's okay, they're bunk beds.
Don't worry about it.
I'm gonna go to bed now, Mom.
Good night.
Don't forget, 6 a.m.
Once around the lake.
Good night.
- Sleep well.
- You too, Mom.
I think when we get into town
I should give Betty a call.
Ted. Ted?
I think when we get to town
I should call Betty.
Jimbo, calling Betty is definitely
a dead-fuck thing to do.
Look, first rule of love: Never get
rejected by the same girl twice.
I mean, that's useless.
If you wanna make a fool
out of yourself...
...always do it with someone new.
Well, I don't know anybody new.
Well, sex is a great way
to meet them.
Ooh. Oh, my!
- Sorry.
- Don't worry about it.
- Hi.
Hi.
- You, uh-- You girls live around here?
- How far is it to Crystal Point?
- Well, that's where we're going.
- Yeah. It's a long walk.
- We can take it.
- I'm going back to get the car.
- Sara, do you want some company?
- This way?
Thanks. I'll just meet you guys there.
All right.
They're cute.
Two of them. Two.
Count them, one, two.
- Yes, yeah, and two of us.
- Exactly.
Come on in! Ha, ha.
Oh. No.
No, we have no suits.
All right!
Skinny-dip! Ah!
Whoo! Sam!
- Gordon, wait up!
- Gordon.
Gordon, wait up! Wait a minute!
Gordon!
- Jimmy!
- Come on, Jimmy!
Come on, Jimmy!
Whoa.
- Turn around.
- Can't I just--?
- Turn around!
- Trish, come on in!
No, thanks.
I think I'm overdressed.
- Hey, Trish!
Bye-bye.
Party tonight!
Come on, Gordon,
we're too young for this.
Some pack of patootsies, huh?
Tommy.
Oh, no.
What next?
Can you fix it?
- I need a screwdriver.
- Maybe there's one in the trunk.
I need the keys.
Thanks.
Tommy, come on!
Come in, Sara,
let's see what you got.
- No.
- Come on, Sara. Strip and dip.
Sam, I said no.
Well, then, I'm gonna go under
and stay under until you do.
See you later.
Sam?
Sam!
God, Sam!
God.
Sam!
Sam! Sam!
Aah! Samantha, you bitch!
- You like that?
- You bitch!
Turn it on, Trish.
Turn it on!
- Whoa!
- Hi. Rob Dyer. Sorry about that.
- Oh. Hello.
- Hi. What's your problem?
- No problem.
- I mean with the car.
Oh, the car. Um, it won't start.
Well, get in. Give it a crank.
Look, I've tried everything already.
The only thing it could be
is the solenoid.
If you had a screwdriver....
Okay, give it a crank.
You need a lift?
I didn't think anyone lived
this deep in the woods.
We do. What are you hunting
for up here?
Bear.
Anybody up at the lake today?
You can't be hunting for bear.
How about kids? There any kids,
vacationers, people like that?
Yeah. A bunch of kids moved in
yesterday. Right next door to us.
- This is it.
- Thanks for the lift.
Gordon!
Would you like to come in
for a minute?
I don't think I can.
Well, you gotta come in.
Come on, I got something real neat
to show you up in my bedroom.
Hi, Mom!
Tommy, who's your friend?
Mom, this is Rob.
Rob, this is my mother.
- Hello, Mrs....
- Jarvis.
Amazing.
Come here, I wanna
show you something.
No way, not tonight
No way
Not today
Just 'cause you play it cool
Would you care to dance?
- To this?
- It's good.
All right
Oh, well, good.
Don't ask me to stay
Don't think you got it made
No, no
You're wrong
'Cause you can't fake it anymore
I know what you're waiting for
I should turn away
And walk right out that door
Because I know--
Hey, how come you
turned that off?
Relax, Jimbo.
You're gonna love this.
Wanna give Teddy bear a kiss?
Heh. Mm! Teddy. Teddy, uh--
I've gotta get another drink.
With her eyes of night
- Excuse me.
- You like this stuff?
You like slow dancing?
Tangerine
I could learn to.
Kiss me, you fool.
- Certainly.
- Ha, ha.
Uh, maybe we could dance to this one.
Come on, let Teddy bear
show you how it's done.
Stay near the trail.
- It goes all the way around the lake.
- Yeah, I will.
- There's only three of you up here?
- Mm-hm.
My parents have separated.
You know, middle-aged crazies. Heh.
I kind of hope they get back together.
Yeah, I hope so too.
- Looks like another rainy one, huh?
- Yeah.
Listen, if it gets too bad out there...
...or if you wanna take a shower
or whatever, we're always home.
And if we're not,
Tommy usually leaves the door open.
- Good night.
- Take care.
Hey, how you doing with yours?
Nowhere, huh?
Check.
You gotta warm her up.
Watch me. Do what I do.
And, Jimbo, don't be
such a dead fuck.
I told you. I told you that
I didn't like that.
- Besides, you've got the hot one.
- Check.
- Hi.
- He thinks that's funny.
He thinks that's a funny
thing he's doing.
- Okay, you ready, Tina? On three.
- All right.
- One!
Two!
Three!
And the winner is...Tina!
All right!
What do I win?
What do you want?
Jimbo, put on another record.
Jimbo.
You don't mind, do you?
Actually, I was thinking
about taking a little swim.
It seems to be getting
a bit close in here for me.
- Sam....
- Sara. Sara, let's dance.
I don't wanna dance.
Well, let's mind our own business.
Look, I'll talk to Paul.
All right?
Mm.
- I wanna talk to you for a second.
- Man, I am going to kill him.
- I said I wanted to talk to you for a second.
- Not now, dead fuck.
That's what I wanted to
talk to you about.
Do you believe this guy?
- I mean, I had her. She was mine.
- Oh.
Well, you know what I suggest you do
about that, Teddy?
I think you should run that
through your little computer.
Paul?
I know you're out there, Paulie.
Okay. Screw you, Paulie.
Come on, Paul.
I know you're out there.
Paul?
Screw you, Paul.
Look, what's the matter?
I can't go through with this.
I'm sorry. I gotta go.
What good is a song
If words just don't belong?
You wanna dance?
Yeah. Yeah.
No good alone
To each his own
For me there's you
If a flame is to grow
I thought that you wanted
to be with Ted.
Well, I did.
But now I wanna be with you.
That makes me feel like a rat.
Two lips must insist
On two more to be kissed
Well, do you wanna join them?
Jimmy.
Why don't we just go upstairs?
Upstairs. Heh.
Ahem. That's a teddy bear.
Wanna give Teddy bear a kiss?
Fuck!
Shit.
This is-- This is a neat room.
This is your room.
No. Actually, it's Paul's room.
You're neat.
- Oh, what a shock.
- Sorry.
Hey, you guys! Look what I found.
What is that?
God, what a pig!
Tina? We gotta go.
You go.
Tina, I'm gonna leave without you.
Take an umbrella.
You slut!
I'm going upstairs.
You tired?
No.
Do you mind sleeping
in the bottom bunk tonight?
Why, you wanna sleep on the top?
No.
Give me a few minutes.
Okay?
Good night, Teddy bear. Ha, ha.
Good night.
- Ha, ha.
- Stop.
Tommy? I'm gonna towel off
and then I'm gonna strangle you.
Tommy? Trish?
Anybody home?
Gordon?
Where's Tommy?
Where's Trish?
Matter of fact, where the hell are you?
Gordon?
Watch it!
Can we slow down a little?
The party's gonna go on all night.
I think I'm gonna lose my lollipop.
Mom, we're home.
Mom?
- Where is she?
- I don't know.
Mom?
- She's not here.
- Maybe she's still jogging.
She's never gone this long.
And in the rain?
- I'm going out on the path.
- Me too.
No, you stay here
in case she comes back.
- I'll go!
- Stay here and fix the lights.
- What the hell are you doing here?
- What are you trying to do, kill me?
Tina? Ahem.
Hmm?
Never mind.
Tell me.
Um....
Did I...? Was, um...?
Was I...?
Was I a dead fuck?
- What?
- A dead fuck.
No.
You, uh--? You know what I think?
You know what I really think?
I think you were incredible.
- And I wanna do it again.
- Yeah.
Don't you move.
I'll be right back.
Oh. Ha-ha-ha.
Check it out.
Why don't you run this through
your computer, Teddy bear?
Hey, congratulations, Jimbo.
Where's that bottle of wine?
Why don't we celebrate?
I think maybe I drank it.
I was great!
I was great. I was great.
Love, Teddy bear!
L-O-V-E.
Hey, Ted, where is...?
Where is that corkscrew?
That fancy corkscrew for
the wine bottle?
Ted?
Hey!
Ted? Ted! Hey, Ted,
where the hell is the corkscrew?
Jimmy?
My sister Sandra was
a really great kid.
But the man that killed
your sister is dead.
No, he's alive.
Look.
Jason as a child, right?
Artist's conception of Jason as
described by a would-be victim, right?
And then the murders.
But he's dead.
Jason's body
has disappeared from the morgue.
- It was stolen.
- It was not stolen.
Two people at the hospital are missing.
This is coincidence?
He's alive.
Oh, my God. Tommy's at the house.
Ha, ha. Teddy.
Oh, man.
Oh.
Oh. Ha, ha.
So you wanna give the old
Teddy bear a kiss?
Jimbo?
Sara, I think I'm in heaven.
I think I'm in love.
What?
I'll meet you in the bottom bunk.
Tangerine, she is all they claim
With her eyes of night
And lips as bright as flame
Tangerine
She is
Sara? Change your mind?
Come on. Get in here.
There's plenty of room.
We can sing a duet.
Who is it, Paulie?
Paulie.
Hey, Paulie, is that you?
Hey, Paulie. Whoops.
Dropped my bar of soap, old buddy.
Lucky you ain't in
here with me, old pal.
Ho-ho-ho.
I came to hear you sing.
So sing.
Aah! Sam! Samantha!
Sam! Sam! Sam!
Sam!
Sam! Sam!
Oh, Tommy. Thank God you're okay.
- Oh, Tommy.
- What happened?
- Where's Mom? Is she back?
- No, not yet.
I'm gonna call for help.
Rob, what's going on?
- I'm not getting anything.
- I wanna go next door.
- I'm going with you.
- No.
I'm going with you.
- You stay here and lock the door.
- Tommy, hold the fort.
Gordon!
- He's been here.
- Wait. What if he still is here?
Take this. Take it.
I'm going downstairs.
You stay right here with Gordon.
- No.
- Stay right here with Gordon.
Gordon.
Gordon!
Gordon?
Rob! Rob, he's here! He's here!
Rob! Rob!
Rob! Rob! Rob!
Rob, he's here!
- He's here. He's killed all of them, I know it.
- Oh, my God.
Shit. Give me a hand.
- Gotta get the knife.
- No! No.
No!
Oh, my God!
Oh, God, he's killing me!
He's killing me!
Run, Trish! Run! Trish!
Trish, run!
No! Get off me!
Tommy!
- All the doors locked?
- Yes.
Go get me a hammer
and nails right now.
- ls he here?
- Yes.
Tommy, hurry!
Help me! Help me!
Let me go!
Help me! Put me down!
Put me down!
Tommy, help me push this.
Where is he?
What's he doing?
Listen, Tommy,
I'm gonna get him out of the house.
And when I do, I want you
to run like hell, do you hear me?
Run like hell, okay?
Oh, my God!
- Trish!
- Tommy, no!
Trish!
Tommy?
Tommy, you were supposed to leave!
Tommy! Tommy, get the hell out of here!
No!
You son of a bitch.
I'm gonna give you something
to remember us by.
Jason!
Remember me, Jason?
Jason, don't you remember?
Remember, Jason?
Jason, remember?
Remember?
Tommy.
Tommy!
Die!
- Die!
- Tommy!
Die!
- Die!
The shoulder will need some surgery.
But we can wait
till she's a better candidate.
Now, you just get a good rest,
young lady.
You haven't answered my question.
Neither one of you
is answering my question.
Often, during extreme duress,
people are capable...
...of extraordinary behavior.
That's what happened when your
brother violently attacked the killer.
At that moment it was perfectly normal
for him to act to protect himself.
He's going to be just fine.
But right now, what you need is rest.
Can I see my brother now?
Sure. But only for a minute.
I'll send him in.
Tommy.
Please rate this subtitle at www.osdb.link/yw64
Help other users to choose the best subtitles