Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org
Oh my, God. Please help me!
Oh, God...
Jason! It's all done, Jason.
You've done your job well,
and Mommy is pleased.
That's a good boy.
Now, come to Mommy. Come on.
Come on.
Mommy has a reward for you.
Jason, Mother is talking to you.
Come on.
That's my boy. Come.
Kneel down.
That's a boy.
Kneel down, Jason.
That's my good boy.
That's a good boy.
Good, Jason.
Ginny!
Come on. Let's go. Ginny.
Jesus.
Come on.
God damn it, Harold! I spent all day
yesterday washing your clothes.
Look what you're doing to them!
You know I work very hard around here
trying to keep up with you
and all your sloppy habits.
And I get no help from you at all.
-The community of Crystal Lake...
-Jerk!
...was shocked today with reports
of a grisly mass murder scene.
Eight corpses have been discovered
in what is already being called
the most brutal and heinous crime
in local history.
A police spokesman told Eye-On News
that they've been combing the area
since just before dawn
and are afraid that their gruesome
discovery is just the beginning.
Police Chief Scott Fitzsimmons
had no comment about the murders
when reached early this morning.
Detectives at the scene,
however, were baffled
by the brutality of the killings.
Bodies were found literally strewn
over the four-square-mile campground
in the remote lake region.
Ginny Field miraculously survived
repeated attacks
by the axe-wielding killer
and was taken to a local hospital today.
-She is in serious condition...
-Oh, my God.
...suffering from multiple stab wounds
and severe hysterical shock.
The names of the eight victims
are being withheld
until notification of next of kin.
Reports of cannibalism
and sexual mutilations
-are still unconfirmed at this hour.
-What are you doing out there?
The person responsible for the
Crystal Lake horror remains at large.
Harold, I swear...
Jesus Christ, Harold.
Just take what's yours
and leave the rest for me to do.
Very considerate.
Could've at least finished the job.
Do I have to do everything around here?
Harold?
Okay, boys, soup's on.
What's the matter, Lionel?
Aren't you hungry? Come on, it's good.
Here, look. I'm eating.
It is good.
Dayfly eggs?
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
Come on. If Edna catches you in here,
she'll make a fur coat out of you.
Come on, I'll take you home.
Didn't I feed you enough for supper?
The doctor said you have to lose weight,
now didn't he?
You know, I'm trying to help you,
but you just keep sneaking food
behind my back.
What am I gonna do with you?
And would you put that filthy animal
back where it belongs? Come on.
Hey, hey, hey. What are you
so nervous about? Come on.
Who would do something like this?
What's the matter? What happened?
It's all that crap
you've been stuffing yourselfwith!
It's Easy Money time, the easy money
show where everybody wins.
Now, where's that other needle?
Thank you, Johnny, and good
evening, ladies and gentlemen.
Yes, it's Easy Money, Charlie Lincoln,
and I'm here to give away money.
I've got a pocketful of money
burning a hole in my pocket...
Charles Dickens, ladies and gentlemen.
Harold?
Fourteen straight weeks in a row.
That's not the end.
Harold?
It's the white house on the left.
-Shelly, come and meet your date.
-Bring her to me!
Maybe this wasn't such a good idea.
Sex, sex, sex. You guys
are getting boring, you know that?
What would a weekend
in the country be without sex?
-Cool it, Andy.
-I didn't mean it that way.
Look, you guys, I want you
to have a good time this weekend.
What happened to me at the lake
happened a long time ago.
I'm fine, really, okay?
Just forget about me.
I'm supposed to forget
that we've been friends...
God damn it, Shelly! Why do you
always have to be such an asshole?
I beg your pardon.
I'm not an asshole. I'm an actor.
Same thing.
Look, Shelly, you're my roommate,
and I like you. Most of the time.
But you've gotta quit doing those things.
Now, I got you a date, didn't I? Didn't I?
-Yeah.
-So don't embarrass me.
Just relax. Be yourself.
Would you be yourself
if you looked like this?
-Yes?
-Hi, Mrs Sanchez. I'm Chris.
We've come to pick up Vera.
She is not going!
-What are they saying?
-I don't know. I flunked Spanish.
Hi, everybody. What are you looking at?
Is everything all right?
Just your basic
old-fashioned mother problems.
So which one's my date?
Hi.
You're Shelly?
Sorry.
Hey, the van's on fire!
Is that all you two are gonna do
this weekend? Smoke dope?
Why not, man? Is there a law against it?
There are better things to do
with your life.
-Like what?
-I can't think of anything.
Hey, Chrissy.
How much further to the lake?
We would've been there already
if some people
didn't have to go to the bathroom
every five minutes.
That's what happens
when you're pregnant.
Sure, why not?
Hey! Let's share the wealth with those
less fortunate up front here.
Yeah.
-What do you got in there?
-My whole world.
-In that little thing?
-Stick around. You'll see.
-It's the cops.
-Oh, my God!
-What?
-They're catching us.
-What are we gonna do?
-Destroy the evidence! Hurry!
-No way, man.
-Let's go, Chuck! Come on!
-They're gaining on us.
-Throw it out!
-No, they'll see it.
-We gotta get rid of it. Eat it.
The cops are gonna get us.
We're going to jail!
-I'm driving.
-Breakfast?
No way! We're pregnant, remember?
Faster! Eat faster!
-Why don't you help us?
-I guess I'm just not hungry.
You're always hungry, Shelly.
Come on, eat!
-I'm allergic to pot.
-I gotta pull over.
-Oh, man!
-Oh, no!
Shit!
Charlie 63 is unable to handle...
Help out the ambulance.
I'll get the crowd.
Okay, you guys, show's over.
Let's move it back over here, all right?
Come on, you guys.
Hey, kiddo. Don't let your imagination
run away with you.
-Chris, stop the van. Stop!
-What is it?
-What are you doing?
-You almost ran over him!
I must have been daydreaming.
I didn't even see him.
Hey, he looks just like my grandfather.
Why,
I must be in heaven!
Don't touch him.
You don't know where he's been.
-Thank you.
-Sleeping in the middle of the road?
You are, indeed, all of you,
kind and generous young people.
Look upon what his grace
has brought unto me!
-What is that?
-I found this today.
-There were other parts of the body.
-That's an eyeball!
And he said that he wanted me
to have this. This.
He wanted me to warn you!
Look upon this omen
and go back from whence ye came!
I have warned thee!
I have warned thee.
Check it out!
Why don't we take our bags
into the house first.
Chris, come on down.
You go ahead. I'm gonna take my bags
in the house first and look around.
Don't you dare! I'm not ready!
Hello?
Is someone here?
Rick!
Is it my imagination
or did itjust get cold in here?
Did I do something wrong? Did I?
No. It's just being here again.
I know it's only been two years,
but I feel like I've been away forever.
Doesn't look like
anything's changed, though.
Even the paintings are still crooked.
Well, you've certainly changed.
Don't you even say hello any more?
I'm sorry.
-Hello, Rick. How are you?
-Well, that's a start.
Could you just slow down, please?
There's a whole weekend ahead of us.
Let me get to know you again.
Let me get to know this place again.
Okay. But there's only
so many cold showers I can take.
Come outside
and help me with the bags.
Oh, God!
You know, Chris, I think you've gained
some weight since last summer.
I have not! You creep. Put me down.
Here, you get the ones inside.
I'll get the ones off the top.
Wasn't this door closed
a few minutes ago?
-What did you say?
-Nothing.
Chris...
That's my bag. I'll take care of it.
Shelly, what are you doing in there?
Why aren't you down at the lake
with everybody else?
They said
they were going skinny-dipping.
And I'm not skinny enough.
This was my bedroom.
It's yours for the weekend.
Great.
Chris? I don't mean to be picky
or anything, but where's the bed?
Chris?
It's right here.
-What's this?
-It's your bed.
-A hammock?
-You might like it.
Why not?
Where's the bed?
All right.
Chris, I don't understand
why you guys have so much hay.
You don't even have any horses.
You never did.
It's my father's idea. Every year,
he makes plans to buy a horse
and every year, he buys all this hay
but no horse. You figure it out.
You realise, of course,
that I gave up an opportunity
to spend the weekend
with Mary Jo Conrad for this.
You mean you actually
gave up the chance
to be with the Mary Jo Conrad
for little old me?
That's right.
Boy, are you dumb.
Okay, Chris, I realise
I'm just a dumb country boy
and my feelings really don't matter.
But this is the sweat of a worker
on my forehead, not of a lover.
Now, I believe
that there is a time
and a place for everything.
And now's the time and now's the place,
if you know what I mean.
So, what I think we should do
is set aside three hours a day
to fulfil our needs.
One in the morning and two at night.
If you agree, I agree.
Were you talking to me?
-Is anyone in here?
-What's going on?
You check down here.
I'll check the upstairs.
Is anybody in there?
Don't look at him.
Let's just get the hell out of here.
-We heard screaming.
-Oh, my God!
-What happened to him?
-Is he dead?
-Don't touch him, Andy!
-Don't move him!
You creep! Get up!
I guess I fooled you?
-You jerk!
-Chris, leave him alone.
-He doesn't know any better.
-It was a joke!
-Chris.
-It was just a joke.
-I didn't mean to...
-You never mean to.
I gotta get out of here.
I'm going to the store.
-Can I use your car?
-Oh, sure.
Thanks.
Asshole!
Hey, hey, hey. Hey, let me go with you!
I gotta get out of here too.
Chris. Chris, wait up.
What's wrong?
It's that creep, Shelly.
What a sick sense of humour.
Oh, that's just his way
of getting attention.
He doesn't know what happened.
I know it, Deb.
But from the minute we got here, I've
been seeing things and hearing things.
It's probably just my imagination.
I shouldn't have
come back here so soon.
Don't let it get to you.
Relax. Enjoy the weekend.
Nothing's gonna happen to you
when we're all here together.
Okay.
-Hey. How are things with Rick going?
-Okay.
But he just doesn't understand.
That'll be $18.50.
We don't accept no food stamps.
Shelly!
I need some money.
Excuse me,
but I believe that's my wallet.
Make a wish.
Can I buy you two guys a beer
or something?
I'll take that now.
Is this your rubber?
Didn't your mama teach you manners?
If you want something, you ask.
-Nice.
-Please, be cool.
May I please have the wallet?
You mean,
"May I please have the wallet, ma'am?"
May I please have the wallet, ma'am?
That's good. That's real nice.
Hey, that was a 20!
-Are they following us?
-No!
-Good.
-Here. You drive.
The way I feel right now,
I'd probably get us into an accident.
Next time, I'll know how to handle
a situation like that.
Let's just hope next time isn't too soon.
Oh, shit!
"Oh, shit" is right. Let's get out of here.
Hold on!
-What are you doing?
-He went too far this time.
Oh, shit!
-I did it. I did it. I did it! Did I do it?
-Yes, you did it.
-You were great.
-I was great.
You son of a bitch! You ought to
come back here, you bastard!
You ain't getting away with this!
God damn it! I'm gonna get you!
What do you say
we go get some exercise?
This is all the exercise I need.
That was close.
Hey, you better watch out
with that thing.
Come on. I'm warning you, Andy.
I'll break your string.
I wonder what happened to them.
What happened
to your windshield, man?
We had a slight misunderstanding
with a motorcycle gang.
Yeah, but Shelly made them see the
error of their ways. Didn't you, Shell?
It was nothing.
My poor car. What did you do to it?
Yeah, well, we're real sorry, you know?
But it wasn't our fault.
A few minor repairs,
it'll be good as new.
That's it. I've had it.
I thought it would be a good idea
for us to spend some time together,
but this is a little more
than I bargained for.
Where are you going?
Away from here.
Stay with me.
-Why should I?
-Because I want you to.
You don't play fair, do you? Get in.
-Hey. Let's go for a swim.
-I don't know.
Come on. We'll be all alone.
We can do whatever we want.
-Nobody'll see.
-Sounds disgusting. Let's go.
I'll grab a couple of towels.
I'll see you down there.
-Maybe we shouldn't do this, Ali.
-We gotta even the score, don't we?
Nobody's gonna get hurt, okay, baby?
-Right.
-Trust me.
-Let me do it.
-I know what I'm doing.
Oh, shit.
Who's up there?
Here, take this in the barn
and start pouring. And find Fox.
What the hell are you doing?
Get off that thing.
This feels good!
Ali is gonna be pissed,
he sees you screwing around.
Now, come on. We got shit to do.
What the hell?
Fox?
Where are you?
Stop screwing around.
You're messing everything up!
You're dead now, woman.
Fox.
Fox. Loco.
Open the damn door.
Fox.
What the hell are you guys doing
up there? You hear me talking to you?
Fox!
When I find you, you bastard,
you're a dead man!
Shit!
-I don't wanna go home. This is fun.
-I know.
-What are you doing?
-We haven't been in the barn...
We haven't been in the barn yet.
Let's take a look.
Not now. I'm cold.
Come on, Debbie,
how about a little roll in the hay?
Go play with yourself.
I'm going into the house.
Hey, wait up!
-Is that better?
-Yeah. Thanks.
You know, I don't think
I could live anywhere else.
The nights are always
so peaceful and quiet here.
-It's deceiving.
-What do you mean?
The quiet can fool you. It fooled me.
Chris, why'd you come back here?
To prove something to myself.
To prove I'm stronger than I think I am.
What about us?
I'm here with you.
Can't that be enough for now?
I don't know. I mean,
I don't see you for months on end.
Then when I do, you put this barrier up
between us. How do I break through?
-You give up?
-You out of your mind?
-Do you give up?
-Never.
I know how to stop this.
Andy? I can think of much better things
for you to be doing with your hands.
You win.
I guess that leaves you and me. Sort of.
Yep.
You really are very good at that.
It's nothing.
Vera, you and I have gotten to know
each other a little today, you know?
And I like you.
I like you a lot. I was thinking
that maybe, you know, we could...
I don't think so. Look, I'm gonna go
outside for a few minutes.
And then when I get back in,
we'll talk, okay?
Sure. We'll talk.
Bitch.
-How do we do it?
-Well, first we take our clothes off
and then you get on top of me,
or I could get on top of you.
I know how to do it. I mean,
how do we do it in the hammock?
Well, I think you can
figure something out.
I'll think of something.
You're right.
I should have told you everything
a long time ago, but I couldn't.
Look, Chris, you don't have to
if you don't want to.
I want to. I want you to know
what happened so you'll understand.
Everything is so clear in my mind,
as if it were happening right now.
I don't know if you remember,
but when you dropped me off
that night, it was very late.
I knew my parents would be waiting
for me, but I didn't care.
We had such a good time.
The minute I walked in the door,
my parents started yelling at me
and cursing me.
We had such a big fight.
My mom slapped me.
That was the first time my mother
had ever hit me. I couldn't believe it.
I ran out the door and into the woods.
I wanted to punish them.
So I decided to hide out all night.
I thought I'd get them so worried
that they'd be sorry for what they did.
It had been raining
and the woods were cold and wet,
but I found a dry spot
under an old oak tree.
I guess I fell asleep.
All I can remember next
is being startled out of sleep
by the sound of footsteps.
I was sure it was Dad,
so I just sat up and I listened for him.
But the footsteps stopped.
Then there was
this cracking noise behind me.
I turned around,
and standing there
was this hideous-looking man.
He was so grotesque,
he was almost inhuman.
He had a knife.
And he attacked me with it.
I was so hysterical, I don't know
how I was even able to think,
but I kicked the knife
out of his hands and I ran.
But he ran after me and he caught me
and he pulled me down on the ground.
I was kicking and screaming
and yelling, but it didn't do any good.
He dragged me along the ground.
I blacked out.
I don't know what happened after that.
I just don't know.
Chris? It's all right. You're all right.
When I woke up, I was in my own bed.
My parents have never said
a word about it.
They act as if the whole thing
never happened, but it did.
All I want is to just forget it, but I can't.
I'll never forget that horrible face, never!
What's that?
Damn it, it's that battery.
I charged it yesterday.
Must not have taken.
It may just start anyway. Let me try.
We're gonna have to walk back.
It's okay.
-Okay?
-Yeah.
I know a pretty good shortcut.
Shelly?
Heavy shit!
Who's there?
Shelly, if this is
another one of your tricks...
Sorry, I didn't mean to scare you
like that.
Between you and Shelly, I'm lucky
I haven't had a heart attack already.
What's butterball up to now?
I don't know.
He just ducked into the barn.
Come on, let's give him
some of his own medicine.
I don't think he's in here. Let's go back.
Maybe that wasn't him.
Chili.
Are you crazy?
-I guess he must've left.
-Come on, let's get out of here.
I'm not going to let anybody hurt you.
Gee, thanks. I feel a lot better now.
That'll teach you a valuable lesson:
A beautiful girl like you
should never go out in the dark alone.
Damn it, Shelly!
Why do you do these stupid things?
-I have to.
-No, you don't have to.
-I just want you to like me.
-I do like you.
But not when you act like a jerk.
Being a jerk
is better than being a nothing.
-I never said you were nothing.
-You don't have to say it. I could tell.
You're wrong. Shelly!
Chuck? Chili?
Hey. What are you guys doing in there?
Are you guys doing something
I shouldn't see?
That's great.
Hey, I dropped your wallet.
I'm sorry. I got it.
Who are you?
What are you doing?
Hey, now cut that out right now.
That's not funny.
That was the best one yet.
Was it you, me or the hammock?
-I vote for me.
-I vote for the hammock.
Where you going?
I'm taking a shower.
You ought to try it sometime.
-Hey, Debbie, can you hear me?
-Barely.
I'm gonna go downstairs
and get a brew. You want one?
Andy?
Oh, Jesus.
-Do you want a beer or not?
-Sure.
-All right. Be right back.
-Okay.
Andy.
-Andy!
-Yeah?
Are you still out there?
I can't hear you.
Andy?
Will you quit fooling around?
Cut it out.
Andy? I changed my mind.
I don't want that beer.
Andy?
Andy? Did you hear me about that beer?
Andy!
Oh, God,
I hate when you don't answer me.
What?
Where's this coming from?
Great shortcut, Rick.
-Come on, let's move it.
-Always spoiling my fun.
-What was that noise?
-What?
I don't know.
I heard something over there.
Come on, let's get home.
-Did I hear you screaming?
-No.
It's probably Debbie having an orgasm.
How come you never scream
when we have sex?
Give me something to scream about.
-What's the matter?
-Nothing. I was just practising.
Don't do that to me!
Here. Go down the cellar
and check the fuse box.
In the dark? Alone?
Be a man, man.
Nothing to be afraid of, man.
So, what if it's dark?
Nothing to be afraid of.
Jeez!
Oh, God.
All right.
Who's there?
Chuck, you back already?
Well, at least you got
the outside lights working.
Nice makeup job.
Stop fooling around, man.
That's better.
What's going on?
Get up!
Shelly, enough is enough!
Oh, my God!
Andy? Debbie?
Shelly's dead!
He's dead!
Andy! Deb...
No!
Oh, my God! Oh, my God!
This wind sure came up.
Seems awfully quiet.
It's hard to believe
the wild bunch is already in bed.
Yeah, well, who knows with those guys?
I can't get this door open.
There's something behind it.
-Oh, I smell something burning.
-Here, take this. Let me do it.
No wonder. Some idiot put this chair
there. Something is burning.
Lights aren't working either.
Oh, real smart. What's going on here?
You tell me. They're your friends.
I'm gonna go out to the living room
and check what's going on there.
Okay.
Andy, Debbie, are you guys up there?
Anybody here?
Everybody else has taken off and left us.
-They wouldn't do that.
-I don't know what's going on,
but I'm gonna go outside
and take a look around.
Rick, wait. I wanna come with you.
Andy? Is that you?
Rick?
Is everything all right?
Where's that coming from?
I don't know what kind of game
you guys are playing, but I don't like it.
Debbie? You guys up here?
Hey, come on, you guys.
You're wrecking the house.
Rick!
Rick! Where are you?
Rick! Help me!
Rick!
Rick! Rick!
No!
Keys. Keys!
Come on!
What's happening?
No!
Come on. Come on!
Gas.
You can't be alive.
You!
You psycho!
No!
No! No! No!
Looks like she's the only one left alive.
What was all that
about a lady in the lake?
She must've flipped out.
That poor kid's been through hell.
All of her friends...
I'll take her.
It's okay. You're gonna be all right.
You're gonna be fine.
Please rate this subtitle at www.osdb.link/a2y
Help other users to choose the best subtitles