-== [ www.OpenSubtitles.com ] ==-
There's a legend around here:
A killer buried but not dead.
A curse on Crystal Lake.
A death curse.
Jason Voorhees' curse.
They say he died as a boy...
...but he keeps coming back.
Few have seen him and lived.
Some have even tried to stop him.
No one can.
Jason's alive.
He's even more powerful now.
Jason belongs in hell
and I'm gonna see he gets there.
Jason, come on!
Come and get me!
It's me you want, remember?
He is down there, waiting.
- Don't give me that.
- Please.
- I'm gonna sell this place and get out.
- Tina?
- Hey, leave her out of this.
- Tina, come inside.
- Yeah, come on, join the party.
- Please, don't drink any more.
Don't tell me what to do!
Tina?
Tina, come inside, honey.
Tina!
Wait! Tina!
Tina, don't.
Please, honey, come back.
- You hit Mom again.
- Tina! Tina!
I hate you! Go away!
Please, baby, I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to.
Go away. I hate you!
I wish you were dead!
Oh, my God!
No!
No, Daddy. No!
John!
Daddy!
Tina, honey, are you all right?
I'm fine.
I don't think this is such a good idea.
Tina, honey, this is really
hard on all of us.
Will you just give it a try?
It doesn't seem to be so
hard on Dr. Crews.
He really wants to help you, Tina.
I'd hate to see you go back
to the hospital.
I guess you're right.
There he is.
- "Bad News" Crews.
- Tina.
- Hi, Dr. Crews.
- Hi.
I hope we didn't keep you
waiting too long.
No, no, I really
like it up here. It's beautiful.
- Did you have a good trip?
- It was a very nice drive.
- Hi, Tina. How are you?
- Hi.
- There goes the neighborhood.
Nice outfit.
Looks like her mom dressed her.
Melissa.
So this is where it all started.
Well, well, well.
Dr. Crews, you really think that
we're doing the right thing, don't you?
We've done all we can do for her
at the hospital.
She hasn't made enough progress.
I know it's tough on both of you
to come back here, but trust me.
We'll do the best we can.
You'll help her.
So, what do you think of Nick?
Gee, I hadn't noticed.
Oh!
- Let me help.
- That's all right. I can do it.
- No, really, here.
- Really.
No, it's no problem.
- Uh, I'm sorry.
- Thanks.
- Here.
- Thanks. You've been a great help.
I don't know what I would've done
without you.
Great, asshole.
Do we really have to do this now?
Tina, we're late already.
Just sit down, please.
- Why am I seeing things?
- I don't know, Tina.
Why do you think you're seeing things?
Is that really necessary?
What, the camera?
I just wanna keep track
of our progress, all right?
Now, uh....
Let's get back to work, all right?
Tina, look at me.
See this matchbook?
I'm gonna set it on the desk here.
I want you to concentrate.
I want you to think about your feelings...
...and just focus them in
on the matchbook.
And maybe we can get it to move.
- You're not trying, Tina.
- Yes, I am.
Think about it moving and make it move.
I can't! I told you,
I don't know how it happens.
Sometimes it happens
and sometimes it doesn't!
And you're lying to me!
You are lying, because it happens
when your emotions are at their peak.
Come on, you're holding back.
Concentrate.
Concentrate, Tina!
Well, well. What did you do?
What went through your mind?
I was thinking about you.
Look, I don't know how
any of this is gonna help me.
Your psychokinetic ability is a projection
of the suppressed guilt feelings you have.
Would you speak English?
You're more interested in this
telekinetic stuff than you are in me!
That is not true, Tina.
I'm here to help you overcome the guilt
that you have about your father's death.
- That's all.
- That's bullshit!
I rest my case.
- Hey.
- Yes?
If this is my uncle's house,
why are we sleeping in the van?
Who says we're sleeping?
Tina.
Honey, are you all right?
- Mom, I miss him so much.
- I know, I miss him too.
Tina!
Please, baby, I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to.
- Tina!
- I hate you! I wish you were dead!
John!
I wish you were dead!
No, Daddy. No!
I'm sorry, Daddy.
I'm so sorry.
I wish I could bring you back.
Daddy?
Dr. Crews, it's Tina!
- Tina, sweetheart, are you all right?
- Tina, what happened?
Where is he?
Dr. Crews, I saw him,
but I can't describe him.
But you said "him."
Are you saying a man came
out of the lake?
I know what you're thinking,
but this has nothing to do with my father.
Tina...
...don't run away from it.
Your guilt over your father's death is....
Well, it's a powerful thing.
But it wasn't my father.
Your mind is manufacturing
hallucinations because--
- It wasn't a hallucination.
- Yes, it was.
No!
Piece of shit.
When's the last time
you put oil in that thing?
Yesterday.
- Let's just camp here.
- But we're almost there.
- Jane, woods is woods and I'm beat.
- Michael!
What? We're gonna have to go back
to the car in the morning anyway.
- Nick can take us.
- Nick?
What would he be doing out here?
- He's already here.
- What are you talking about?
This was supposed to be
a surprise party for your birthday.
Everybody's waiting for us to show up.
I got this great cabin and everything.
No way.
Never mind, the whole thing's ruined.
Happy birthday.
- Hi.
I washed this for you.
- I'm Nick.
- I'm Amanda Shepard. Nice meeting you.
- Nice to meet you.
- So have you been having fun up here?
Yeah, a bunch of us got together...
...to throw my cousin Michael, heh,
a surprise birthday party.
- I came over to invite your daughter.
- I don't know.
Well, you can always spend
the evening with me and Dr. Crews.
- Let's go, heh. Bye.
- Bye. Have a good time.
Where'd she go? Uh, who's that boy?
Oh, relax, Dr. Crews, she's just
going to visit the kids next door.
But I thought we agreed,
no distractions. I mean, I'd....
I'd hate to send her back
to the hospital.
She just needs a chance to be normal.
Isn't that what this is all about?
Yes, of course it is.
This is some birthday.
It's gonna be a great birthday. Promise.
Hey, be back in two shakes.
Just hurry.
Michael, get a move on.
- Christ! It's cold out here!
- Ha, ha.
Jane?
A party. You know,
cake and ice cream.
Oh, shit! Nick, help me out.
- Whoa! Got it.
- I need an objective opinion.
- No, grab it underneath. It's wet.
- Is anybody making the popcorn?
What do you think of Starlycon?
Thirty thousand years into the future,
the entire galaxy is populated...
- ...by highly evolved protozoa.
- Thanks a lot.
- Good, huh?
- You all right?
Only one human
being and his woman...
- ...still exist amongst the stars.
- Just give me a drink.
I see you met our resident writer, Eddie.
- Ice cream and cake, huh?
- Just something with alcohol.
Eddie's a little out there, Tina, but believe me,
everybody else here, perfectly normal.
So he goes, "Let me see your ID."
So I go, "Well, I left it at home."
And he goes, "You have to go
and get it." So I go, "Okay." And I go.
Put something under that drink, all right?
You're gonna ruin the table.
- Outrageous.
- You like him?
Me too.
What is this?
Ah, will you look at this?
The party hasn't even started...
...and already this place looks like
closing time at the stock exchange.
- Russ, honey, we'll clean it up. I promise.
- Yeah, chill out, Brooks Brothers.
But they're eating my uncle's food.
We're supposed to bring our own food.
He's gonna shit.
- Everybody, this is Tina from next door.
- You guys!
- Hi.
- Ow.
- Oh, shit!
Fuck!
Where did that come from?
- What was that?
- Nick, help me.
- Tina....
- Why are these people such slobs?
Trouble.
Now, there's a guy I'd love
to give a surprise party for.
- Hi, I'm Melissa.
- I'm Tina, from next door.
I know.
Whose friend is that scuzzball dopehead?
Only the birthday boy's best friend.
Melissa, those are so pretty.
They're absolutely gorgeous.
- What a stupid place to put a lamp.
- They're real.
On my last birthday, my daddy goes,
"Melissa, you're the perfect daughter."
And he gives me these and says,
"To the best little girl in the whole world."
Ah, disgusting.
Look, it's all over me.
- Tina, wait a minute. Come back here.
- Who is that girl?
Nick, let me tell you
something about women.
- Mom?
- Tina? Honey, what is it?
- Mom, I saw him again.
- Who? What?
The man, the thing in the lake,
I saw him again.
He was killing a boy with a metal spike.
Tina, relax, relax. Relax, relax.
What do you mean, you saw "it"?
Well, I didn't actually see it,
but I know. I know.
Okay.
What were you doing
right before it happened?
- Why?
- Because these are delusions.
Tina, you're creating images
of your father.
All right. Well, he left a large delusion
stuck in our back porch.
Why don't you just go look,
if you don't believe me.
All right. Okay.
Okay, I will.
- Tina....
- I know I'm right. I'm right.
Tina? Mrs. Shepard?
Tina, where? I....
But it was here. It was right here,
the large spike that I saw.
What's happening to me?
Help me, please.
Shh, shh, shh.
I'll help you,
but you have to help me.
Honey, come on in the house.
Come on, sweetie. Come on, in the house.
- It was there.
- Okay.
It was there.
I just don't know what's happening.
It's okay.
I'm cold.
- Why don't we crawl in the sack?
- Why don't you fix the fire?
- There's no wood.
- Heh, we're in a forest.
Come on, let me heat you up.
Dan, we need wood.
It's gonna be a cold night tonight.
I'll be back.
Okay, you big hunk of a man,
come and get me.
Dan?
Dan, what are you doing?
It was great.
Derrick F. Z. Simms' greatest film.
The Battle of the Gargantuan Throngar
was a work of genius.
- Right, Eddie.
- Hey, you don't have to take...
- ...my word for it. Ask Ben, he was there.
- What?
Ben, why don't you tell us
all about Throngar.
- Throng what?
- Oh, no, my mistake. lt wasn't Ben.
Gee, look at the time.
Gotta get moving, get something on paper.
Uh, some surprise party
that turned out to be, huh?
Michael probably got pulled over
for drunk driving...
...and spent the night in jail.
I mean, the guy can smell a party
1 00 miles away. He'll be here.
- Now, where's my coffee?
- Where would you like it?
Has anyone seen Nick?
I think he went next door
to see Marilyn Munster, heh.
Your friends must think
I'm a complete joke.
Yeah, who cares what they think?
They're not my friends.
I just came up for my cousin.
So where are you from?
- Where are you from?
- We're doing real good here, aren't we?
Okay, here goes.
I grew up in Pittsburgh,
I used to hang out with a real bad crowd.
Then my dad kicked me out and now
I go to night school. Your turn.
We used to come up here all the time
till my dad got killed in the lake.
I don't like it here.
Oh, is this where...?
I think it was my fault.
I know it was my fault.
Look, you're a really nice guy
trying to get your life together.
You don't wanna mess around with me.
Just listen for just a minute.
I saw my father get killed
when I was a kid.
It really messed up my head a lot.
- So you're okay now. Aren't you?
- You know that guy in my house?
He's my doctor. He came out
to help me from a mental hospital.
I.... Um, I saw it.
It's a big, pink elephant.
You know, with my luck, you're probably
gonna turn out to be another delusion, heh.
Good morning, heh.
- Heh, well, what was that for?
- Nothing.
- Nothing?
- Mm-hm.
- Hello, Tina.
- Hi.
We've got tomatoes,
peppers, onions....
Sandra, don't do it that way.
It's gonna fall through the grill.
Okay, let's see what else.
Garlic, pepper....
Well, great.
Move it! Steve, come on.
Bye.
- Did you cut all the tomatoes?
- Yeah. They're all done.
It looks great.
What happened with you and Ben?
He blew me off to go out
with Eddie the other night.
- I can't believe he lied.
- What's wrong with Kate?
Just throw the ball.
Look at this.
It's made with latex.
- Have you seen Nick?
- He's around.
Dip?
She's like that with everybody
except boys. Come on.
Cocktail hour.
Ah, Robin, did you see the way
David just looked at me?
Oh, get real, Maddy.
You're not his type.
You need a little touchup work first.
Thanks.
The Colombian Express
is pulling out. All aboard.
Ding, ding, heh.
- Hey, Eddie, wanna do me a favor?
- Yeah, sure. Anything.
- I'm gonna do it.
- Robin, you don't smoke.
- I do now.
- No, you can't. Robin.
You and I made a deal.
We were gonna come here
and have a good time, right?
Well, I'm gonna stick to the deal.
You in?
Okay.
- Hi.
- Hi, David.
Come on.
So you wanna smoke with me?
- Yeah.
- Good.
So is Nick here or not?
I really wanna talk to him.
Don't worry, he'll show.
Hey, Tina, isn't this the way they wear
their jackets in the mental hospital?
What's she doing?
- Ah.
-Wow.
God, heh.
- What happened?
- Tina.
Hey, wait, Tina!
What's going on, you guys?
I hate this place.
He's making me do things that
I don't wanna do. I'm seeing things.
I could've killed somebody.
How could I have done that?
Because, Tina, when you're highly emotional,
you do almost anything, you see.
It just proves my point.
I mean, you made the matchbook
move, you broke the pearls.
If you can believe
that I did those things...
...then why can't you believe that
I saw someone get killed?
We do believe you, Tina.
Your psychokinesis and these delusions
are just all tied together.
No, you're not listening to me!
You haven't heard a single word I've said!
Can we go back now?
I don't wanna stay here anymore!
Go back where, Tina? Look at me!
Back to the hospital?
We're starting to make some real
progress because you are here.
- Please!
- We'll go back tomorrow.
- You can't leave.
- It's not working.
Do you wanna throw this all away?
We're at a very critical point right now!
Do you wanna see her in the hospital
for the rest of her life?
- Is that what you want?
- Look what you're doing to her!
- Hey. Whoa. Whoa. Where you going?
- Oh, Nick, I wanna get out of here.
- Melissa was a bitch.
- No, forget Melissa.
There's something really wrong here.
I know it, and no one else believes me.
- Tina, what are you talking about?
- Did your cousin ever show up?
- No, he didn't.
- Well, what did...?
What does he look like?
I don't see what this has to do
with anything.
Can you tell me what he looks like?
Do you have a picture or something?
Yeah, I do. I think I do.
It's right here.
Oh, God.
What?
I think he's dead, Nick.
Tina, pack your things,
we're gonna leave in the morning.
When did you first fall
in love with me?
The first time I saw the enormous
size of your beautiful...wallet.
Heh, there was this huge bulge in
your pants just calling out my name.
"Sandra, Sandra, take me now."
- You coming?
- What are you doing?
Come on. You chicken.
You're crazy.
Gonna go for a little swim?
Okay.
You need a formal invitation?
Russell, party for two,
right this way, please, heh.
No!
Russell, come on.
Russell! Russell!
King Tut rises from the tomb.
So we go to all this trouble
and no Michael. Typical.
- Know what I like about you?
- What?
You hardly sweat at all.
You wanna get high?
So, what do you wanna do?
Hit me?
Come on, Michael.
Come on, answer the phone.
I love you...
...squid-face.
Look, Michael has not shown up yet,
so I'm gonna go in the woods and look for him.
Hi, Nick. Are you still mad at me?
What was that crap you pulled
on Tina this afternoon?
That chick's crazy.
Besides, all is fair in love and war.
- Melissa, I don't even like you.
- Heh, "Like" has nothing to do with it.
I know. Star Mummy.
Excuse me. Hey.
We have got to get to know
each other better.
Are you joking?
Now, why would I do that?
You really think I'm cute?
Of course I do.
Since when?
I've always thought so.
You've just been too
blind to notice.
Dr. Crews?
I told you,
I don't know how it happened.
The Anderson case
in '65. The documentation here is much greater.
By keeping Tina's trauma
and stress levels high...
...I am confident I can induce
huge psychokinetic reactions.
What do you think you're doing?
You... You never intended to help her.
Be reasonable.
That's why I'm here.
First I find this spike and
then this.... This....
- What have you been doing to my daughter?
- I have been trying to help her.
What's this? ls this what Tina's talking about?
Have you been hiding this all this time?
I can't expect you to understand
this highly complicated process...
- ...that is integral to your daughter's treatment.
- Liar! I can see what you've been doing.
You have deliberately turned
my daughter into an emotional wreck.
That's not true.
Mrs. Shepard, what you saw was....
Was a side effect of her treatment.
Treatment?
You bastard.
You brought her here so that
you could watch her perform.
- It's out of your hands.
- How could you do this to her?
I don't care what you say,
I'm her doctor.
We'll put her in the hospital. We'll begin
psychotropic drug therapy right away.
Do you...? Do you really think
that I'd ever let you see her again?
Mrs. Shepard, she needs help.
She's dangerous to herself,
she's dangerous to all of us.
How can you say that?
She's not dangerous.
She killed her father.
Look what she's tried to do with me.
I see no other choice
but to get her into the hospital.
- No.
- Mrs. Shepard...
...I'm gonna have to commit her,
even if it is against your wishes.
Tina?
Tina, no!
Mom?
No!
"Need a little touchup work,"
my ass.
David?
David, are you out there?
Where are you?
David!
My earring.
Ah, thank God.
- Nick.
- Tina.
I just saw my mom.
I've gotta go find her.
What's that?
Tina? Tina!
Oh, my God!
- She's gone.
- Oh, no. No.
- What if she's hurt?
- We didn't pass her on the road.
Tina! Tina!
Wait, wait. Wait a minute!
Don't go! Don't leave!
Ouch.
- What?
- Your watch.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry. God.
What's that?
- What?
- That.
- Oh, shit. I hope it isn't Michael.
- Oh, what timing.
- Quick, get a balloon.
- Yeah, right. Happy fucking birthday.
You're here at last, birthday boy.
Stop shaking the van.
- Let's surprise him, heh.
- Heh, right.
On the count of three. You ready?
- One, two, three.
- Ahem
- Go. Surprise!
- Surprise!
- Where is he?
- He's probably out there somewhere.
- Let's get him.
- I'm not going out there.
Come on, the motherfucker's
out there.
I'm gonna get him.
Make it fast.
Be right back.
All right, Michael.
Come on.
Where are you, buddy, huh?
Come on, Michael.
Where are you, buddy? Come on.
Ben, are you coming back or not?
Ben, where are you?
Ben!
Michael?
Hey, I'm talking to you.
Stop screwing around.
Eddie.
This just isn't gonna work out.
- What's the matter?
- I lied.
- Lied about what?
- About everything.
You just don't turn me on.
Really.
Look, come on,
at least I gave you a chance.
You just didn't come through.
Anyway, I was kind of hoping Nick
would come back and find you with me.
- Why'd you lie?
- You know. Make him jealous.
Rejection.
Okay. Fine. I can take it.
I've been rejected by
some of the finest...
...science-fiction magazines
in the continental United States.
Eddie, where are you going?
To take a cold shower.
I got a date with a soap on a rope.
What happened to the lights?
Who cares?
Come here.
Michael?
Michael.
I knew it.
I saw it.
Oh, Nick, I'm sorry. But we've gotta
keep going, we've gotta get out of here.
- I'm hungry.
- How romantic.
I'm really stoned.
The Neanderthal man,
hunter-gatherer, seeks nourishment.
Ooh.
It's dark.
- Here.
- Gee, thanks.
- Bye.
What the fuck?
Maddy?
What are you looking for?
My father's pistol. I know that
he has one in here somewhere.
Crews knew.
- What'd you find?
- I don't know.
Come on, Tina,
let's go get the others now.
Oh, this is important.
Jason Voorhees.
It was him in the lake.
What are you talking about?
Oh, my God, that's you.
"Happy birthday, Michael.
You lucky son of a bitch.
Many happy returns.
Love, Melissa."
Cunt.
"Personal penis enlarger."
You all right? You sure?
Listen. If this Jason guy
is really out there, Tina...
...I wanna get everybody together
so we can get the hell out of here.
- What, Tina? What is it?
- She's in the woods, Nick.
- Who?
- My mother. I know that's where she is.
All right. We'll find her, Tina.
We'll find her, but let's get everybody
so we can leave together.
So change your mind or what?
Melissa?
Maddy?
David?
Are you in here?
David, are you in there?
Just a cat.
Kitty.
Come here, kitty.
Whose kitty are you, huh?
Are you David's kitty?
No, David doesn't have a kitty.
You're cute. Yes, you are. What?
You scared, kitty?
Don't be scared.
Where are you going, hmm?
No!
- Tina.
- I've gotta go find her.
Can we get everybody
together first?
I can't go with you. What if she
comes back and I'm not here?
- I don't wanna leave you alone.
- Well, then, you go. You go.
And I'll stay right here.
- Just hurry back.
- Don't move.
David?
Maddy?
Tina?
- Tina!
- Mrs. Shepard.
- Answer me! Where are you?
- Look at me.
You're wasting time.
She's probably back at the house.
- Do you know that?
- You saw the car. Tina!
Let's call the police, all right?
- Why? Damn it, she's out here!
- We are wasting time.
Don't you understand that,
Mrs. Shepard?
- What's the matter with you?
- Wait, wait.
Nothing.
- What is it? What aren't you telling me?
- I'm gonna leave.
You can find your own way back.
You're not just a lousy doctor,
you're a fucking coward!
Give me that key.
Listen to me. Tina knew.
She tried to tell us. She did.
- What? What are you doing?
- Oh, my God!
No! No!
Maddy?
Melissa? Anybody?
Tina?
Tina!
Jesus Christ.
- Where's Tina?
- A psych ward. How should I know?
- Eddie's dead.
- What?
He's dead. Michael's dead too.
I saw him.
- Get real.
- Just don't go over there, Melissa.
Okay.
Tina. Tina! Shh. Shh. You have to come back
with me now, please.
What are you doing here?
Where's my mother?
She's, um.... She's back at the house.
Come on, please.
- You're lying!
- I am not lying!
- You're lying, I was just there!
- Tina, please.
When I tell you to come back,
I mean it! Come--
Blood?
What happened? What did you do?
You've gotta help me.
We've gotta get out of here.
Where is she? Where's my mother?
- She's gone.
- What?
She's gone.
- Tina. Tina!
- Mother!
Tina, don't go in there! Tina!
Mom?
Mom!
Mama! Oh, God!
Kate, is that you?
Kate?
Jason?
What the hell?
Tina?
- Tina.
- My mom.
He got my mom.
Who?
I killed him.
Jason's dead.
Okay, okay, shh, shh.
All right.
- You are nuts.
- Shut up, Melissa.
I don't believe you.
You people give me the creeps.
Hey, where do you think you're going?
I'm going back to bed.
You wanna come?
- Look, Melissa, just stay here with us.
- It's not my style.
- Don't go out there!
- Fuck you.
No. No, fuck you both!
Careful.
- Go!
- Ahh!
Shit!
- Run!
- Ahh!
Shit! Ugh!
Tina, come and--
Tina, what are you doing?
Come on.
No!
Nick?
Tina, come on! Go!
Run! Hit the deck!
Go!
Are you okay?
It's all gone.
Everything's gone.
Shh.
It's okay.
Let's get out of here.
No! Tina!
Daddy?
- Right there.
- Over here.
Pretty much got her under control,
but, uh, we may need some backup.
Help me with this,
will you, Charlie?
I need.... I need about four guys over here.
That should do it.
How's she doing?
Nick? Nick?
He's all right.
I just found another one.
A little more hose, please.
I got it, I got it.
- Jason. Where's Jason?
- We took care of him.
Please rate this subtitle at www.osdb.link/467ea
Help other users to choose the best subtitles