Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
The itsy-bitsy spider
Crawled up the waterspout
Down came the rain
And washed the spider out
Out came the sun
And dried up all the rain
And the itsy-bitsy spider
Crawled up the spout again
Jesse, you get in this house right now!
Oh, Mom.
Right now.
No!
Who are you?
Well, I'm Mrs Voorhees,
an old friend of the Christys.
No, no. They're all dead.
They're all dead.
All right, I'll go look.
Please don't leave me.
He'll kill you too!
I'm not afraid.
No!
Did you know
that a young boy drowned
the year before
those two others were killed?
The counsellors
weren't paying any attention.
They were making love
while that young boy drowned.
His name was Jason.
I was working the day that
it happened. Preparing meals.
Here. I was the cook.
Jason should have been
watched, every minute!
He was...
He wasn't a very good swimmer.
We can go now, dear.
No!
My sweet, innocent Jason.
My only child.
Jason.
You let him drown.
You never paid any attention!
Look what you did to him.
Look what you did to him!
No!
Kill her, Mommy. Kill her.
She can't hide.
No place to hide.
Get her, Mommy. Get her.
Kill her. Kill her.
Two of my men pulled you out
of the lake. We...
...thought you were dead too.
Do you remember very much?
The boy. Is he dead too?
- Who?
- The boy. Jason.
- Jason?
- In the lake.
The one who attacked me.
The one who
pulled me
underneath the water.
Ma'am, we didn't find any boy.
Then he's still there.
God!
Hello?
Hi, Mom.
I know. I'm sorry.
I meant to call earlier, but I fell asleep.
Really, I'm fine.
I need a little time alone, that's all.
I know you and Dad worry,
and I appreciate that.
Come on, Mom,
we've been through all of this before.
I just have to put my life back together,
and this is the only way I know how.
Look...
Mom, please. It's getting late,
and I really don't want to get into it.
I'll call you tomorrow. Bye.
Mom!
Hello?
Cute.
You want something to eat?
All right, keep your eyes peeled.
I think we're getting close.
Hey, there's a gas station.
Okay, let's call Ted.
Hey, Teddy, buddy!
We just rolled in.
Yeah, yeah, Sandra's here.
Hi, Ted!
Hey, so you gonna come down
and get us or what?
Yeah, okay.
Okay, give me the directions.
Here, wait, wait, wait. All right.
Okay, go ahead, I'm ready.
All right, Old North Road,
and then look for a Dairy Queen?
Okay. And then over...
I told the others.
They didn't believe me.
You're all doomed.
What? Oh, no, nothing.
No, go ahead. No. All right.
So... All right, covered bridge.
Okay. Then what?
All right, so, then past an old cemetery.
All right.
And then...
Left down an old dirt road
for half a mile.
Oh, my God! They're towing us!
Shit! Ted, I'll call you back.
- Hey, wait!
- Hey, mister!
This is my truck! Come on!
This is my truck!
Asshole, this is my truck!
Shit!
Welcome to God's country.
You rat shit!
Thanks, Max!
Max owns the gas station.
- He's crazy too.
- I should have known.
It's great to see you.
It'll be like old times.
Yeah, that's what I'm afraid of.
Help me load my gear and we'll split.
So, Ted, what's the scoop?
I know that guy Paul
that's running the course. He's okay.
He's kind of macho, though.
He takes the whole thing very seriously.
Senior camp counsellor, of course.
We'll probably all get
a Brownie badge ifwe survive.
- lf we survive?
- That's right.
Didn't I tell you you're gonna be
a second assistant?
Oh, no!
Wait, listen, listen.
A bear and a rabbit are in the woods.
Both are taking a dump.
The bear looks down
at the rabbit and says,
"Excuse me, Mr Rabbit,
does shit stick to your fur?"
The rabbit says, "No, Mr. Bear."
So the bear wiped his ass
with the rabbit.
What the heck is that?
- Where did this sucker come from?
- I don't know. Let's move it.
This place is spooky.
It looks like somebody dragged it here.
Yeah, but what for?
Hey, you guys, look at this.
It's Camp Blood. This place is
on the same lake as we're gonna be.
- Camp Blood?
- Isn't that the place...
- Let's get out of here.
- Can't we take a look?
- No way.
- What's the problem?
You don't wanna hear about it, man.
Believe me. Not before lunch.
Need some help?
No, it's okay. I got it. Thanks, anyhow.
Okay, let's settle down.
It's great to have you here
at our new counsellor training centre.
You've all worked as counsellors
at one camp or another.
Terry, Vickie,
you were upstate last summer, right?
Scott! Hi! Good to see you here, buddy.
You need it.
And, Mark, I know we worked
a season or two together, right?
Okay. The rest of you
I'm sure I'll get to know soon enough.
I'm also sure there's one thing
I don't have to tell you.
Being a counsellor isn't the gravy
summer job everybody thinks it is.
And what we're gonna do
over the next two weeks,
if the rest of my staff ever shows up,
is go back to basics.
Survival, first aid, boating,
archery, rifle range, all of it.
What the hell...
I'll be right back.
Hi! I'm late.
What is this crap?
You're supposed to be my assistant.
- Everyone else got here hours ago.
- I said I was sorry.
You did?
I'm sorry. Okay?
- But my car's sick.
- You could have called.
Paul, I tried, but your phones
aren't even working yet.
Okay, get your gear stowed
and help me outside, okay?
Paul, look,
the course starts today, right?
Well, here I am.
And I promise you, I'll never, ever
be late again in my entire life.
Is it a deal?
All right, all right, what the hell.
Ginny, I was starting to worry about you.
Bullshit, Paul.
Ginny, put your car on the lot, okay?
This place looks like a Burger King.
Where was I?
You were about to give your
"Let's keep our shit together" speech.
Mr Holt.
Right, Ted. Right.
Okay, look, a few words about safety.
Axes, knives, lanterns, saws.
They can all be trouble.
Their misuse is the main cause
of camp accidents.
Take care of your equipment,
and it'll take care of you.
Now, a word of caution
about our friends in the forest.
Among other things,
this is bear country.
And contrary to what everybody hears,
bears are dangerous.
That means no food fights.
Change often.
Food odours cling to clothing.
If you're a woman, don't use perfume.
And keep clean
during your menstrual cycle.
Having trouble?
You gotta treat them gentle.
Just like kids.
Use a little of that child psychology
you're majoring in.
Try it.
It's more fun using
that child psychology on you.
You're such a sucker for it.
- Thanks much.
- I don't want to scare anyone,
but I'm gonna give it
to you straight about Jason.
His body was never recovered
from the lake after he drowned.
If you listen to the old-timers,
they'll tell you he's still out there.
Some sort of demented creature,
surviving in the wilderness.
Full-grown by now.
Stalking.
Stealing what he needs,
living offwild animals and vegetation.
Some folks claim they've even
seen him, right in this area.
The girl who survived that night
at Camp Blood, that Friday the 13th,
she claims she saw him.
She disappeared two months later.
Vanished.
Blood was everywhere.
No one knows what happened to her.
Legend has it that Jason saw
his mother beheaded that night,
and he took his revenge.
A revenge that he'll continue to seek
if anyone enters his wilderness again.
And by now, I guess you all know,
we're the first to return here.
Five years.
Five long years, he's been dormant.
And he's hungry.
Jason's out there
watching.
Always on the prowl for intruders.
Waiting to kill.
Waiting to devour.
Thirsty for young blood.
Hey, come back! Come back!
Okay, look, now that we've got that
out of our system,
I don't want to hear any more about it.
It's ancient history. Jason drowned,
Mrs Voorhees was killed,
and Camp Crystal Lake is off-limits.
You got it?
Got you, huh? What did you think?
The second act needs work.
- Too bad.
- Come on.
You got him. You got him.
You got him now.
Go on.
- That's luck. That's luck, all right?
- Thanks a lot.
Next.
- Hi, Terry. Do you wanna dance?
- No, thank you.
Hi there. How about you?
Do you wanna dance?
So there I was, sitting in this
fast-food joint, thinking to myself,
"Scott, old boy, what are you gonna do
with the rest of your life?"
I'm striking out all over the place.
Well, I think I've got you. Check.
Wrong, white man.
Checkmate.
Well, what next?
I could get my arm broken by Mark,
my brains Ponged
by our electronical wizard
or bed.
Good night, Paul.
See you in the morning.
Jeff, I just gotta see that place.
- What place?
- That camp. Camp Blood.
- You're crazy.
- I've just got to.
Maybe there is something
to that legend. I'm serious.
No way.
You're not getting me out there.
- Besides, Paul said it was off-limits.
- We'll see.
Hello?
Who's there?
- Paul, God damn it! What do you...
- Hey, hey, hey. Calm down.
You'll wake the natives.
I'm not supposed to be fraternizing
with the staff.
I won't tell.
I missed you, Ginny.
And I really was worried
when you didn't show on time.
Oh, Paul, there's something
I think I should tell you.
Come on! Come on!
What's the matter, guys?
Jeff, the women are showing you up.
What's the matter with you?
Hey!
We've got about a half a mile,
then we're gonna have lunch.
Try to stay on this trail, because
there's a lot of poison ivy along here.
- How far are we from camp?
- Hey, you guys, don't trip on that.
Mr Holt.
What are we gonna have for lunch?
Ted's probably gonna cook.
All right, after lunch,
we're gonna do some more running.
- Here you go, Ted.
- Thank you, dear.
- Come and get them!
- I'm here.
Muffin? Here, girl. Muffin.
Muffin?
Terry, lunch!
Okay. I'm coming!
- Jeff.
- What?
You ready?
- For what?
- Camp Blood.
I thought we weren't supposed
to go near that place.
Come on, it's only a short walk.
They'll never know we're gone.
Jeff, I'm serious. I really wanna see it.
Look, when we get back to the city,
we can tell everyone we were there.
Oh, come on, you chicken shit.
Okay, let's go.
Okay, you guys. I got one. Ready?
What's green and red
and moves 100 miles an hour?
- What?
- A frog in a blender.
Ha-ha. That wasn't funny.
- What's brown and sits on a piano?
- Your face.
Beethoven's last movement.
God.
- This must be it.
- Yeah.
- Oh, my God!
- What is it?
It looks like a dog.
- It's too mangled to tell.
- What do you think did it?
Wild animal, I guess.
What are you kids doing out here?
You're gonna have to keep your people
away from that place. It's condemned.
Next time I catch anybody there,
I'll run them in.
- He told us...
- I'll handle this, Jeff.
- I might just get a warrant against you.
- Oh, really?
Look, Holt, people say what you're doing
with these kids is great.
You've got a good reputation.
But if I was you,
I'd have located in the next county.
You're too close.
Things have been quiet for five years.
That's the way we want it.
So do I, Officer. So do I.
Okay, you two, take off,
and I'll talk to you at dinner.
- We'll never do it again, sir.
- Thanks, Mr Holt.
You're not even gonna reprimand them?
No punishment?
What kind of place is this?
- Ginny?
- Yes, Paul?
No seconds on dessert
for Jeff and Sandra tonight.
You okay?
Should we tell Terry?
You know, about what we saw?
No way. As far as I'm concerned,
we didn't see a thing.
Hey! Hey, you!
Oh, my God.
- Oh, no.
- Anybody want...
Who made this shit?
Okay, people.
Today was fun and games, right?
I like to start you out slow, ease you in.
Tomorrow, we'll get serious.
Anybody who wants a last night
on the town, now's your chance.
Okay, who else?
We only have two cars.
By the way, our wanderers
have volunteered to stay
and watch the camp.
Isn't that nice of them?
I think I'll stay too. Muffin may show.
Well, I'm gonna go change, you guys.
You know, I'm pretty tired.
I think I'll stick around too.
- Get me another cup of coffee?
- Sure.
- Don't drink too much.
- Bye-bye.
Hey, you staying?
Yeah. Nothing spoils a party faster
than a drunk in a wheelchair.
That's crap.
Look, we can go together if you want.
I appreciate that, but I'm in training.
- Then I'm staying too.
- Suit yourself.
So how about it, second-in-command?
You coming?
- You buying?
- Sure.
- You got a deal.
- Got the keys?
Beer time!
Take it easy. Have fun.
I'll have a Jack for you.
- See you later!
- Bring back my truck in one piece.
- I'm going for a walk.
- We'll wait up for you, all right?
Go, scooter.
Now I know how you can afford
tuition to grad school.
You always find some fool
to fix your car and buy you a beer.
You got it.
Muffin?
- Here we are!
- All right.
Everybody, get out for some beers!
All right!
Come on, Mark.
Come on.
You're gonna lose. All right!
- Hey!
- Cheater.
- Okay, okay, okay. Two out of three.
- All right.
Jeff, don't wear yourself out.
You wanna wrestle, come with me.
Later, scooter.
Wanna take me on?
Sure. Have a seat.
- I only want your fingers.
- What?
Take your pick.
They're Ted's. It's okay with him.
Football and hockey.
- Which one do you prefer?
- The one with the puck.
- You mean hockey?
- Is that what you call it?
Okay. What do you wanna play for?
Position.
Looking for something?
- Come and get it.
- Give me my shirt, Scott.
If I get my hands on you...
Scott!
It's no longer funny, Scott.
Help! God damn that Paul!
Him and his wilderness bullshit!
- What can I do?
- Get me down, that's what!
- I'll have to get a knife to cut the rope.
- Well, hurry, okay?
I ought to let you hang, you pervert.
Come on, Ter. Give me a break.
- You gonna cut the crap?
- Sure, anything. I promise.
Okay.
Don't go anywhere.
Very funny.
Where is she?
Scott, I'm gonna cut you down.
But I swear, if you ever do this to me
again, I'm gonna kill you.
Scott?
Look at this.
I think I'm in love.
No, no, it's just tremendous affection.
Are you sure you don't
want me to clear those?
- No, I'm collecting these.
- Have it your way, honey.
I just don't want the bar
to fall down on you.
Thanks.
- I think she likes you.
- I think so too.
This whole thing's ridiculous, really.
Two of our kids got hauled in today,
because five years ago
some girl panics and falls out
of a canoe. It's absurd.
- What if there is a Jason?
- Oh, bullshit, Ginny.
No, what if there is
some kind of boy-beast
running around Camp Crystal Lake?
Let's try to think beyond the legend.
Put it in real terms.
I mean, what would he be like today?
Some kind of
out-of-control psychopath?
A frightened retard?
A child trapped in a man's body?
Let me out!
- He'd be grown by now, right?
- Right.
And, you know, the only person
that ever knew him was his mother.
He never went to school,
so he never had any friends.
She was everything to him.
Yeah. Deranged killer.
No, no, no.
You're missing my whole point.
I mean, I doubt Jason would have
even known the meaning of death.
Or at least until that horrible night.
He must have seen
the whole thing happen.
He must have seen his mother killed,
and all just because she loved him.
Isn't that what her revenge
was all about?
Her sense of loss, her rage
at what she thought happened,
her love for him?
Bizarre, isn't it?
He must be out there right now,
crying for her return, her resurrection.
- Well, what do you think?
- I think you're drunk.
I'll drink to that.
Hit us again, sweetheart.
Not me.
You know, Paul,
I'm really serious about this though.
Jason's a legend, Ginny, a legend.
Your turn.
Three goals or you're gonna lose.
I've heard that one before.
Mark, what happened
that you have to be in a chair?
Motorcycle accident, paralysed my legs.
Is it permanent?
The doctor thinks so. I don't.
I don't intend to be in this thing
the rest of my life.
Just your legs, huh?
Is everything else okay?
Oh, I do all right, one way or another.
Toke?
I'm in training, remember?
For what?
What does the winner get?
- What does the winner want?
- Guess.
Want to stay together tonight?
I was just about to ask you.
My cabin or yours?
Ted's in mine.
I don't think that would work out.
We've got the whole camp.
We'll find our own cabin.
Just give me a few minutes
to get some things, okay?
- Sure.
- I'll be right back.
Oh, damn it.
Terry, you turkey.
There you are.
Vickie?
Vickie, is that you?
I looked up "ugly" in the dictionary.
There's a picture of him.
- I got to get some sleep.
- I'm tired.
- You guys quitting already?
- Ted, you'd have me out till breakfast.
- I'm gonna ride with you, okay?
- Okay.
- Good night, Ted.
- Good night, Ginny.
When this place closes,
come straight back to camp.
- Yes, boss.
- And let Maggie drive the pickup.
Yes, boss.
Okay, let's make a run for it.
- Move it!
- I'm going! I'm going!
This thing had better start.
- You fixed it.
- I know, that's what worries me.
Are there any
after-hours places around here?
- Sure are.
- "Sure are."
Mark?
Mark, where are you?
Is anybody still here?
Sandra?
Jeff?
Sandra? Jeff?
Sandra.
Sandra?
No! No!
No!
No! Stop!
No! No!
Nice night.
Yeah, for a duck.
God.
What the hell are all the lights on for?
Paul, they wouldn't have
left the place like this.
Think something's wrong?
I'll check upstairs.
These kids smoke better dope
than I do.
Paul!
Yeah, Ginny, what...
What is this, a joke?
They wouldn't do anything like this.
Ginny, come on.
Wait for me.
Kitchen light's still on. Must...
Must be the main fuse again.
- Paul, what's going on here?
- Nothing.
Where is everybody?
I don't know.
The rain's stopping.
We'll go look for them.
Paul, there's someone in this room.
Paul, there's someone
in this fucking room!
Oh, my God! Oh, my God!
Paul? Paul?
Paul?
Answer me!
God, please, keys, be there.
Keys, be there...
Come on, car! Come on, car!
Please start. Please start. Please start.
Start!
Oh, shit!
Oh, my God!
Please help me.
Oh, God...
Jason! It's all done, Jason.
You've done your job well,
and Mommy is pleased.
That's a good boy.
Now, come to Mommy. Come on.
Come on.
Mommy has a reward for you.
Jason, Mother is talking to you.
Come on.
That's my boy.
Come. Kneel down.
That's a boy.
Kneel down.
Kneel down, Jason.
That's my good boy.
That's a good boy.
Good Jason.
Ginny!
Come on. Let's go.
Ginny.
Jesus.
Come on.
Paul!
Come on. I'll carry you.
It's all right.
Hey, you're all right. You're all...
God! Oh, God!
No, you're okay. You're okay.
You're okay, Ginny. You're all right.
It's all right.
Oh, Muffin!
Muffin.
Oh, Muffin.
Come here, Muffin.
Paul? Paul?
Where's Paul?
Please rate this subtitle at www.osdb.link/3zzn4
Help other users to choose the best subtitles