Downloaded from
YTS.MX
Official YIFY movies site:
Hey, yeah. The 1960's?
Happy times, heavy times.
- All right, so you get your daughter, right?
Your daughter, she might be Catholic.
She might be Jewish. She might be anything.
So you bring her up in what they call the bourgeois,
American-type-society family, you know?
You bring them up
so they don't screw until they get married.
You take them to church on Sunday.
Then you teach them all you can.
What you think you can teach 'em
about how to bring up a family,
how you should look and act,
then they send 'em to college.
You bust your hump.
No government subsidy.
Nobody's paying nothing.
You save your money, or you borrow the money.
You work overtime. You send her to college.
You want her to get an education.
The first Easter she comes home on a vacation,
she says, "Hey, Dad, I'm living with some guy."
"You're living with some guy?
What do you mean you're living with some guy?"
"Well, this is the thing now, free love."
- We're getting away from,
we're getting away from the original point.
What we're trying to find is,
why are these bastards rioting?
Because they did dope.
Listen, you're going in the wrong direction.
What of it?
What happens is, look,
I'm sending you to school.
I'm breaking my ass and I'm sendin' you to college, right?
I expect you're going to learn something.
Not to be a janitor?
Learn something to justify my investment in you.
But some of these people revel in the fact
that their kids are leaders, are rabble-rousers.
This son of a bitch just started a riot.
Oh, Joe, too much.
These kids think they're the first generation
that ever screwed before they got married.
We all did, but we always had one girl.
She screwed that girl you took out.
It's better off these kids don't get married
because, if they get married,
they haven't got the guts to stick with it.
♪ Hey, you fucking intellectuals ♪
♪ You think you're so where it's at ♪
♪ Before you fill your minds with any junk ♪
♪ Better listen to Fritz the Cat ♪
♪As writers and poets and artists ♪
♪ It's your duty to live life to the most ♪
♪ So butt out, brothers and check out the world ♪
♪ Give me a ride to the coast ♪
♪ Fritz the Cat ♪
♪ He fought many a good man ♪
♪ Laid many a good woman ♪
♪ Live life to the fullest ♪
♪ Cry out for more until it bleeds ♪
♪ Help me, help me help you, mother ♪
♪ Love me, I hate you ♪
♪ Love me, I kill you ♪
♪ Love me, I love you ♪
- Sheesh! What a mob in the park today.
God, the place is crawling with phonies.
- Yeah, high school punks.
- Man, you know, those creeps
are always here on weekends, man.
Most of them are total jag offs.
- Oh, so many people here and nobody here.
- Hey, dig that chick, man!
- Oh, over there?
- Man, look at that ass on her!
- Oh, yeah. What a baby carriage.
- Well, so what, man?
- Hey, if you hadn't showed up so late,
Fritz, we would be all right now.
- Yeah, Fritz always does it, man.
- Everybody's here with their guitars already, man.
- Cool, right, but I got-
- Sixteen versions of "Lemon Tree."
I just want some place where I can sleep.
I mean, I can cook.
I mean, I can sew and I can do housework
and things like that, right?
- Get out, get out the guitars.
Come on, get them out. Get them out!
And one, two, three.
♪ Once I had a little girl ♪
♪ Who was in love with me ♪
♪ Well, well, baby ♪
♪ I know, I know ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah ♪
♪ Oh, mama, mama ♪
♪ Singing it, ho ♪
Dumb chicks.
- Easily impressed by spades.
- It's the thing, man.
- Uh, look, um, I'm gonna split. I'll see you guys later.
- Yeah, hang loose, Fritz.
- I've read everything James Baldwin's written.
He has a true sense of the problems of Black people.
- I worked for Head Start for free last summer.
Black kids are so much groovier.
- I went to a couple of Black Panther meetings.
The time for non-violent revolution is past.
More power to the people!
- I'm taking a course in African studies at school.
I had no idea you people were so civilized.
Do you know that property values actually go up
when a black family moves in?
Freud didn't write for the black man.
- Why does a great actor like James Earl Jones
always have to play Black men?
- Don't you hate it when people say "Colored"
or "Negro" and not "Black"?
Black is beautiful.
- It's so great that Black people
are wearing their hair natural.
Not emulating the image of beauty
that White people inflict upon them.
- I had a black girlfriend once
who said that Jewish people
were the closest to Black people.
I'm Jewish, you know.
- I ain't no jive-ass Black nigger, honey.
Who do you think I am, Geraldine?
- Oh! Oh, God!
Oh! Oh, Jesus!
- How awful.
- My soul is tormented.
- Gee.
- Oh, no. - I've been up
and down the four corners of this big old world.
I've seen it all! I've done it all!
- Gee. - Oh, wow.
- I've fought many a good man
and I've laid many a good woman.
I've had riches and fame and adventure.
I've stood face to face with danger
and death countless times.
- Hey! - Why, why-
- Are you somebody famous?
I think I saw you in a movie once.
- Hey, try not to interrupt, huh?
I've tasted life to the fullest
and still my soul cries out.
Yes, cries out in this hungry,
tortured, wrecked quest, "More!"
- Look at the good side of life.
- Things aren't all bad.
- Gee, he's handsome.
- You. You can help me.
You must save me.
But, by so doing, you, too, will be saved.
- Well, I, I'd like to, but what can I do?
- Lovely set of eyes there.
Ah, little sweet one, with your heart of gold.
I know of a place where we can be alone
to join our souls
in sacred truth. - Gee, you're good lookin'.
- Hey. - Hey!
I want to be in on this thing.
- Yeah, what about my soul, you fink?
- Four in bed, that's a kink I haven't tried yet.
- What? - Huh?
Yes, together, we shall all learn
of the real existential essence of the life force.
- Yeas, "existential." I heard that word once.
- What's it mean?
- It means, like, "Cool, gear". You know, stupid?
- You are a true genius, Fritz.
- Wild, this is wild. - Oh, honey, I could go, too.
- Oh, my! - I know that.
I know you know. How do you think I knew?
- I'll get it. God damn it!
- What's happening, man?
- Hey, Fritz the Cat has become the stud of the year.
We're having a session here now, so I don't know.
- Hm. Say, anybody using that room?
- That's the john, I mean, if you're really strung out, man.
- We'll take it! We'll take it!
This way, group. Come along, now, step lively.
Watch your step.
That's a girl, rub-a-dub-a-dub.
Okay, a new world of experience awaits us, my loves.
This bathtub is now transformed
into a space capsule of truth and love.
- Wow! This is wild! - Yes, yes!
Only in naked closeness like this,
can we all know each other.
- Yes! Right!
Very good, Winston, darling! "Naked closeness," true.
You are a perceptive girl.
Closeness, we must all get very close.
As close as possible, as a matter of fact.
- Yeah! - Yes.
That's right. - It's so-
- Let's all get close together.
Ooh, boy, closeness and fulfillment of our hidden desires
through which we reach the truth.
Fulfillment is important. Don't you think so, Winston?
Ooh, yes.
Very important. - Yeah.
Oh, wow! Yeah, now I'm getting to the truth, I think, yes.
- Oh, yes! - Hmm.
It's all very clear now.
OK, Winston. Here come the truth.
You got the word.
Oh, Fritzy. - You got such
an existential little body.
Jeez, wow!
- Oh, shit! Maybe we better go, huh?
- No, no, no! Not at all!
No, I, look here. You get down over here.
And you down, that's right, down like that.
- My arm! - That's right.
- Right under here. Watch the foot.
No, right, that's right. Right under here.
Okay, ready, everyone? Here we go.
- Hey, hey, hey Ralph.
This is, I think this is the place we got the report on
where there's these kids upstairs doing this shit
and smoking and everything, I think.
- Tell me what to do. I never went in before.
Tell me what to do.
- Well, yeah, because you're a rookie
and this is your first beat.
You just follow me. You see, we walk up the steps.
We make no noise. Like, we don't make any noise.
And you follow me slowly. You got that?
I do, just like Dick Tracy.
- No, it's like "Terry and the Pirates".
Dick Tracy's old hat. Now, let's go inside.
- Wait. Could I get to search the girls?
- Yeah. I've done enough of that.
Here we go. And watch me, 'cause I'm a natural in action.
Up the steps.
- Hey, man.
What the hell's going on in here?
- For Christ's sake, what do you want?
- For Christ's sake,
Fritz is having his own private little orgy.
Move over, man.
- Will you get out of here? We're seeking after the truth!
- It's my bathtub, man.
Don't pay attention to that Fritz.
He got a Jesus complex.
- Oh, I know it!
- Have some joy puff, sweet little bird.
- Hello, hello, New York.
Heard you're having a hash session here.
- Wow, this is where it's at!
- Right, yeah, man, come join us.
Good stuff and lots of it, man.
Only close the door, we're modest.
- Har har har, the guy's a riot.
- Oh, God! God, I'm there!
I'm there! - You're really there?
How is it? - It's, oh, it's-
- How is it?
- That's funny. I'm not there anymore.
Oh, shit.
- I'm a writer. Let's talk about it.
- Ever made it with an aardvark before?
It's a rare opportunity, you know? We're scarce.
Really?
- I can't tell if I'm there or not. How do you tell?
- Oh, you'll know when you are.
- Oh, balls. It doesn't work for me.
I'm a failure as a pot smoker.
- Don't be sad. Someday you'll make it, really.
Shh. I think we're here.
- Do you hear anything, Ralph?
- It sounds like a bunch of degenerates in there.
- Shh, shh, now, listen, Ralph. Now, listen.
You got the deeper voice, you see?
And I want you to yell, "Open the fucking door."
Now, say the word "Fucking"
because that makes you sound tough.
When I say three, you yell, "Open..."
- I'm even gonna ad-lib! I'm gonna ad-lib!
- No ad-libbing, Ralph. No ad-libbing.
- Let me call them preverts. Let me call them preverts.
- What's a prevert?
- A prevert is a degenerate. Didn't you know that?
- A prevert's a degenerate?
- Didn't you have no bringing up?
- I got bar-mitzvahed.
- You ain't supposed to laugh, Ralph!
This is a serious job and we're getting paid for it.
Cut the fucking shit out. Let's go!
- All right. Open up in there!
It's the law, hippie bastards! - Good job!
Good, Ralph, do it again.
- Op, okay!
- What the fuck's your problem?
- Cut it out! - I won't laugh!
I won't laugh! Open the door, you preverts!
- Open up! Law and order's here!
- Open up! -All right in there!
All right in there!
- Okay, open up! Here we are!
Oh, wow! I can do it!
- Oh, baby, do I feel high! I'm flying!
What a wonderful, wiggly world!
We're outside, but we'll get in!
Law and order's here!
- Open up! -All right in there!
Your fucking bath party's over!
- Over here! - Okay, guys!
- Right in the mouth! Yeah, I love it!
Take that, take it! Hey, you!
Get your hands out of my thing!
- Here we are! - Where the fuck are you?
Over there, in the head!
Get your hands off of my dick!
In the head! Ooh, I love it!
I love it! Ralph, where are you?
Ralph, help! Gotcha!
Now I gotcha! Here, take that!
Gotcha! In the heart and the head!
Over there! Watch that thing!
Hey! Where's the cat?
Wow.
- Hey, look at this big fucking gun.
I killed the john! I killed the john!
- Oh, wow! - Kill, destroy!
Can you give him your glasses because I can't?
I have to look.
- You can't see?
- I'll give them back.
A little bit, oh, boy, this is good for me.
Can you dig it in your eyes? You're younger than me.
You're forty-five, forty-eight, whatever you are.
I'm sixty-seven.
- I wish I knew. I would give you glasses.
I'd take another pair from the house.
- No, I didn't think I would need the glasses.
I'm not so young no more, got to remember.
- You don't see nothing?
- I'm older than you are. I'll see.
I'll mention that I see.
- You're doing fine. You're doing fine.
You know something that you don't have
to look at the book, right?
So, say it. Say it.
All right.
Remember.
- That's good. - All right, good.
- Good. - Beautiful!
- Thank you, thank you. - Just normal.
You know, nice and quiet.
No, wait a minute. Don't rush.
- Mother of God, I'm a fucking fugitive.
- This is the place! I saw him come in here!
- Oh, my God, it's a synagogue.
- What kind of a place is this? What is it, a church?
- Hey, listen, I can hear them.
That don't sound like English.
What are they, Puerto Ricans?
- Ralph, you're trying my patience, Ralph.
- You go down that aisle, I'll go down this aisle.
- Good, it's about time you said something bright.
And Ralph, please be quiet. It's my people.
- Excuse me, Rabbi. - They all got long hair.
- Sorry, Rabbi. - They all got long clothes.
- Excuse me. - Must be a hippie church.
- Hi, Rabbi. - Did you see him?
- God!
Ralph, would you please shut up?
- I ain't talking loud.
- Excuse me, Rabbi.
Hi, Ma. Excuse me, Rabbi.
Uncle Ben, how are you? I'm catching a criminal.
Excuse me, Rabb, it's you. Did you find him?
No, he was over there, but,
But I was just telling you.
- Cut it out!
- But I was just, I ain't talking loud!
- What are you doing? Oh, what's going on here?
You saved my life!
We interrupt the Israeli-Arab war
for this special announcement.
The president, after conferring
with the Israeli prime minister Golda Meir has agreed
to send more arms and equipment to Israel
based on the return of New York City
and Los Angeles to the United States.
- Mazel tov! Mazel tov!
- Stop, you motherfucking cat!
- Stop in the name of the law!
- Stupid, Ralph, you're not supposed to dance.
- But I didn't want to break the circle!
- You're not supposed to dance.
- I got musical feet.
- You dumb rookie. Dumb rookie!
You dumb rookie, dumb rookie!
You're not supposed to dance, Ralph
'cause you're not Jewish!
- I had a great thing going till
the frigging fuzz showed up.
I wish that skinny broad didn't turn on the shower, too.
I think I'm getting a cold. Hello, men.
Everybody all busy studying for their goddamn exams and all?
Hey, Buzz, how'd it go with that Dee-Dee chick, huh?
She's got some bod, huh? You have to admit.
Oh, Charlene isn't bad, either, though, right?
Like, wow! Hines!
You swine, old buddy pig!
You groove behind Alvina, get some kicks tonight, huh?
Bastards, you'd think the goddamn exams was the be-all
and end-all of existence, cosmic life force or something.
You'd think they were the frigging fugitives.
Can't even get in a few decent words to a guy.
Bastards! What a bore, they just sit there and take bennies.
And stay up all night with their face stuck
in a bunch of books and their thumb up their ass.
Oh, yes, yes, I remember the time
when it was all very inspiring and enlightening,
all this history and literature and sociology shit.
You think learning is a really big thing
and you become this big fucking intellectual
and sit around trying to out-intellectual
all the other big fucking intellectuals.
You spend years and years with your nose buried
in these goddamn tomes while the world is passing you by.
All the stuff to see and all the kicks
and all the girls are out there.
And me, a writer!
And a poet who should be having adventures
and experiencing all the diversities
and paradoxes and ironies of life
and passing over all the roads of the world!
And digging all the cities and towns and rivers
and the oceans and making all of them chicks.
Oh, God.
As a writer and a poet, it is my duty to get out there
and dig the world, to swim in the whole frigging scene
while there is still time, man.
My farting around days are over, baby.
From this day on, I shall live every day
as if it was my last.
Yeah, yeah! I must do it!
No more of the dreary, boring classes,
the dismal lectures, the sitting around bullshitting
with pretentious fat-ass hippies.
No more of the books,
the spoutings of a bunch of old farts
who think they know the whole goddamn score.
Oh, my God, what have I done?
I set all my notes and books and stuff on fire
and now I can't study for my exams.
I'll flunk out and my folks will be pissed off as hell.
I'll get a blanket.
The blanket's on fire.
We better call the fire department.
♪ Gonna buy his baby a diamond ring ♪
♪ If that diamond ring don't shine ♪
♪ He gonna take it to a private eye ♪
♪ If that private eye can't see ♪
♪ He better not take that ring from me ♪
♪ Bo Diddley caught him a nanny goat ♪
♪ To make his pretty baby a Sunday coat ♪
♪ Bo Diddley caught him a bear cat ♪
♪ To make his pretty baby a Sunday hat ♪
♪ Maybe someday you will fall in love ♪
♪As I fell in love with you, baby ♪
♪ The one you love just keep falling in love with you ♪
♪ Then when you all alone ♪
♪ You know it'd be best, baby ♪
- You can sing like that.
♪ Little coquette, I love you ♪
- Sing, 'cause I want to. If I get tired, I quit.
- But you don't want to sing.
I want to sing, man. I'm good.
- You sing as good as you want,
but you don't- - If I get tired, I quit.
- I went to school in Oakland
and I had quite a few White-type of school kids with me.
I'm forty-nine.
At that time, I had White kids going to school with me.
I would have peanut butter.
I got some peanut butter I don't want it,
but I ate so much when my mother gave it to me.
With apple butter, I got two cans of it now
that I don't eat because Whitey was eating ham sandwiches
and I was eating peanut butter sandwiches.
Sandwiches!
- I got to get out of this town for some Southern times.
Let me out of here. That's right.
Suck! The bus only cost $17 to New York.
I say, "I ain't made $17 in two weeks."
Got air to live.
- Riding a ship coming out of Pearl Harbor.
And all my White friends,
Then we drank water out of the ditches.
If I had a K-ration, I gave them some of it.
And I would ride this bus.
I couldn't sit with my friend
on this bus at Houston, Texas.
I had to ride at the back end of this bus.
- I'm about to get hot now.
As a matter of fact,
you couldn't even go no place down South riding a bus.
Couldn't even get a soda,
walk in there and get you a sandwich.
- I don't give a damn about who's racist.
I just want equality. I want to be equal with the next guy,
because I'm paying my taxes.
Well, that's a different thing.
I'm a working man and I'm paying my taxes.
The money is what's happening. See what I mean?
- No, I'm talkin' about- - When it all counts,
that is what's happening.
I'm talking about about as far as,
if you want to be revolutionary, you get some bread first,
and then you can talk trash.
- Whitey blind us with religion.
- Yeah, if you fight violence with violence,
like the late Malcolm did, man, you gonna get some results.
- Right. - Really.
Because before this rioting and shit,
you didn't have no Head Start programs for kids.
You didn't have shit!
Really, you didn't have a goddamn thing.
Got you down in Harlem selling horse meat.
You know, if one of them motherfuckers down
and out selling horse meat, they dead.
- Another civil war.
- Civil war? - And I'm gonna
be standing back.
"Get 'em, baby!"
- Hey, man, you in a bag?
- Yeah, that's it. I'm in a bag.
- Well, just don't lose your coolness, cat.
I mean, don't lose your coolness.
- Easy for you to talk. You're a crow.
I wish I was a crow.
If I was a crow, I'd fly away, man.
I'd fly away from this miserable town for good.
- You think being a crow is a big motherfucking ball?
All you cats the same, man.
You don't know where it is.
There's nobody to tell you where it's at.
And you come up here, try to find out where it's at,
but you got to be up here, man,
to find out what's happening.
- Look, I know it isn't a ball, man.
I studied the race problems. I know.
- You don't know nothing about the race problem.
You got to be a crow to know about the race problem.
You know what I mean? Do you dig where I'm at?
You know what I'm talking about?
- Well, listen, man,
this thing affects me very deeply, fella.
As a cat, I have a considerable guilt complex
because my kind have always brought suffering on your kind.
- Yeah? - Yeah.
Yes, indeed.
See, my soul is tortured
and tormented by this racial crisis.
- No shit?
- I kid you not, man.
Sometimes I really get hung up about it.
You know, uptight, strung out.
- In a bag? - Yeah, in a bag!
- I'm gonna buy you a drink, cat.
Just 'cause I think you got coolness.
- Oh, great! Hey, boy!
Hey, boy, can I have a drink?
- Oh, man!
- Hey, Duke! Hey, Duke!
Hey, Duke! They blowing pot like mad up in Mildred's pad!
- I'm on my way, man.
Hey, cat, how would you like to bug out now?
- By God, man! I'm gonna bug out!
- Did he say bug out, baby?
- Go ahead, baby, bug out.
- Ain't no bug out. - What kind of shit is that?
- It's a bug out to him. - It's some kind of dance.
Hey, listen, man.
Anybody looking our way?
- No. - Some stud gone
and left his keys.
- Hey, what are you doing? You stealing that car?
Hey, shove over, Jack! Let me drive this goddamn thing.
- Move it out!
Hey, man, you cats can't drive.
You don't know nothing about nothing.
Can't you see that car go by?
- Cool it, will you? I know how to drive.
I drive like a crow, man, really.
Man, look, slow down!
- I see it. I see the light.
- Man, you'll get killed up here!
- Bullshit, Ralph! Would you please shut up?
It's bad enough we got transferred up here
without you bullshitting all night.
Now, I gotta cover my beat
and I'll meet you back here in an hour.
One hour, Ralph. And, Ralph, please, be careful.
- Yeah, but Harlem?
- Come on, slow the car down! Look out, man!
I ain't ready to die yet!
Harlem?
- I know what I'm doing.
- You know, the only faces you can see
in a crowd up here is ours.
The way they look, all you can see is their eyes.
I don't like it here.
- I see the fuzz. I see the fucking fuzz.
- Cool it, just cool it.
- Right through the head I'm gonna get you!
- Throw that pig out! - Look at it!
Look out!
- Cool it, man, will you? I know what I'm doing.
- Like hell you do.
- Duke, you saved my life, man!
- Shit!
♪ Yesterdays ♪
♪ Days I knew as happy sweet ♪
♪ Sequestered days ♪
♪ Olden days ♪
♪ Golden days ♪
♪ Days of mad romance and love ♪
♪ Then gay youth was mine ♪
♪And truth was mine ♪
♪ Joyous, free, and flaming life ♪
♪ Them sure was mine ♪
♪ Sad am I ♪
♪ Glad am I ♪
♪ For today ♪
♪ I'm dreaming of ♪
♪ Yesterdays ♪
- That you, Sonny?
- Yeah, it's me, baby.
- How's the crowd tonight?
- Not bad. We're pushing enough grass to make our money.
- Just enough, but it sure ain't like
the good old days in Harlem when White money was boss
and them fine, White cats came up to Harlem,
spreading it all around Big Bertha.
Oh, child.
That was before all those peace marches,
sit-ins, riots, and 'dos.
- Ain't nothing wrong
with no peace marches.
- It's me, baby.
- Who's that joker?
- Friend of mine.
Cat, you ever been high on pot?
- Are you kidding me, man, grass?
Who doesn't, you know?
What do you think, I'm some kind of a hick?
- Hey! Let's get that cat going on pot!
Take one. That's what I'm talking about, baby.
Nothing wrong, take two. Come on, be a club member.
That's it! Take three!
Take four! Come on, five, six, seven!
That's it, baby!
He ain't losing now, no, indeed.
A joint, Hilly, a joint! Stay loose!
Fritz, come on, now, stop! Yo, Fritz!
Fritz, come on, now, stop it!
No, don't stop! Oh, yeah!
Oh, no, Fritz! Come on!
Hey, toro! Hully gully cat!
Climb, sugar!
Really? Yeah!
Oh, yeah! No, Fritz!
Come on, Fritz! Ooh, Fritz!
Aw, man, yeah!
Ooh, will you look at that?
Fritz, you ain't Black enough, hon.
Oh, Fritz!
That old black magic got me!
- Oh, Fritz! That's right!
Right there, honey! Wow, wow, wow!
Pump that thing!
- Suddenly it's all very clear!
I must tell the people about the revolution!
- Huh? - Revolt, revolt!
- Damn you! What the hell you jabbering about now?
- Revolt!
Revolt! Revolt!
Revolt, you thick-skulked idiots!
You have carried heavy burdens for the bosses!
You have sweat your lives away for the bosses!
The bosses, they ride around in limousines!
- Get the fuck off my car!
- The bosses, they're eating strawberries and cream!
That's funny! Cats are real boss!
- All right, what's going on here? Break it up!
- Cool it, officer. He's just blowing hot air.
No one's paying no mind.
Come the revolution,
there gonna be no more limousines!
there gonna be no more strawberries and cream, see!
- Hey, Ralph, you know how these dumb kids are.
They don't know what they doing.
- Yeah, fucking A right.
- There he is! He's the one who keeps the bosses in power!
He's the one who's holding you down!
- Who, me? - You!
- No, no. Not me, you.
- No, you! - You.
- You, you, you. - Me?
- Not me! - Yeah, you.
- You! - Fuck you!
- You first!
- The spiked boot of capitalism!
The iron thumb on the heads of the proletariat!
- They're gonna kill us.
- Let's just tell 'em where it is.
- Would you like to see a picture of my kids?
- Come on, man! You'll get killed up here!
- Get them, get them! - Kill them!
- Move over, nigga! - Motherfucker!
No, no, now-
- We shall overcome!
- Group Commander to Formation B.
Don't give them a chance to scatter.
Attack all congested areas.
- I've got to find him. Where could he be?
This is the alley behind that place he was standing at.
It gives me the creeps.
- Psst. - Fritz, Fritz!
- Good evening, madam.
Eek!
Oh, Fritz! Thank God I found you!
Come on! Join me, Winston, my love.
It's not very pretty looking, but it's cozy as a bitch.
- Fritz, come out of there, will you please?
- The hell you say?
With the fuzz combing the whole city looking for me?
Hey, has my picture appeared on TV yet?
Have they broadcast an alarm?
Have they offered a reward
for any information leading to my arrest?
- Oh, don't be so melodramatic.
You and your illusions of grandeur.
I'm not getting in that filthy, grimy garbage can with you.
- Okay, go fuck yourself.
- Oh, you're such a child.
Such a self-centered, egotistical child.
Oh, this is disgusting.
Look, if you're gonna talk
about my garbage can that way,
you can just get the hell out.
Listen, Fritz, are you still going
to bug out or not?
Are you kidding, toots?
I got no choice at this point.
Listen to me, will you?
I've got a car and some money.
I can get all the things we need
and we can leave right away.
We can go out to the coast.
I'll get a good job as a private secretary
and you can work on your poetry and all.
- Oh, okay. - Then,
we can get married and rent a nice little pad in Frisco
and dig the scene out there.
It's supposed to be a great town.
Frisco, yeah. Hey, okay.
♪ She makes men into boys ♪
♪ She makes giants into men ♪
♪ She'll have you feeling guilty ♪
♪ Before you can count to ten ♪
♪ Poor Winston ♪
♪ Sharp mind and a body to match ♪
♪ Fine fancy karma able, too, at that ♪
♪ Who is the girl in the fiberglass shorts ♪
♪ Well, it's got to be Winston Schwartz ♪
♪ You can't outtalk her ♪
♪ 'Cause she talks too fast ♪
♪ You can't out think her ♪
♪ She's a New York flash ♪
♪ She makes love to you ♪
♪And tell you you're in love ♪
♪ You make love to her ♪
♪ She says you don't know how to do it ♪
♪ Poor Winston ♪
- Ah, Winston, my love.
At last we're zooming down that old lonesome highway.
Oh, it's wild!
- Yeah, marvelous.
- Marvelous, my ass! It's exalting, elating.
The cool night wind blowing past the window. Oh, man!
- I'm hungry. Let's stop some place.
- The hell with stopping.
I just want to feel those miles flying by.
I'm hungry!
- Hey, let's dig one of those little greasy truck stops.
I'd like to talk with those truck drivers, you know?
Hear what they got to say about life on the road.
Yeah, I bet they got wild stories of the road.
You know, drivers, trucks, hijackers, fights!
Yeah, yeah, let's do it!
- Here's a good place.
I'll have your deluxe steak
with salad and coffee, black.
- All right. What would you like, sir?
- Oh, that was really a fine steak.
You can always depend upon Howard Johnson's.
Let's get back on the road, huh?
- Oh, goddamn. Fritz, Fritz, wake up!
- Huh? What?
- Fritz, the car is broken down
and I can't get the damned thing-
- What? Where are we?
Oh, fuck a duck.
We're out in the middle of the frigging desert.
Jesus, it's great!
- Exactly. You've been sound asleep for two days.
- What?
- Two days.
You really must've been dragged out after your big binge.
- Shit. I guess I was.
All that drinking and blowing pot and screwing, man.
Hey, man, I get horny just thinking about it. Like, wow!
- Start thinking about fixing this car, Fritz
or we'll be sitting here forever.
Okay, yeah. Look, is something bugging you, pal?
Yeah, the car won't go!
- Oh, okay, well, let's have a look.
Yeah, okay, I knew that all the time.
The engine's not up here. It's in the back.
Let's just check it out.
- What's wrong? - Let me see, I'll just.
If I move that, no. - What's wrong, Fritz?
- Well, it's all very complicated, Winston.
I couldn't begin to explain it.
I think the piston rod's stuck in the drive shaft.
Either that or the carburetor is rusted out.
- Oh, good God.
- Hey, here comes a pickup truck.
Maybe he'll give us a push to the next gas station.
- What's the trouble, buddy?
- Our car is busted down.
Could you give us a push to the next gas station?
- Well, let me look at it.
One thing I'm good at is fixing things.
Shut up! You shut up, chickens!
Shut up! When I say shut up, I mean, shut up!
One thing I'm good at is fixing things.
Dumb chickens.
Let me see now.
Ain't nothing the matter with this car here.
Hey, buddy, ain't you got any sense at all?
You just gonna let your car run out of gas.
I swear, these motherfucking hippies in New York.
There's a gas station a couple of miles back.
I'm going this way.
You ought to stop for gas once in a while, you stupid.
You gotta keep your engine fed. Wise up, buddy.
Well, how do you like that?
New York hippies come down here and they think they can,
I never, honest and true.
You think a thing like that happens.
- Son of a bitch.
- You're so clever, so clever, big mechanical genius.
Here's a bucket, smart guy. Good luck!
- Hey, this is for shit!
You made a big bourgeois deal out of everything
and ruined it completely.
I was gonna bug out and be free
from all this bullshit and roam around
and dig everything and really have a good time.
- Your naivete is astounding.
You'd be completely lost without me, Fritz, and you know it.
- You're a motherfucking bitch.
- I see the hard facts of life.
I am realistic, something you're incapable of.
You'd be better off with one of those stupid morons
like Charlene, who you could just sleep with
and throw away when you're done.
You can't cope with a mature woman.
You haven't the faintest idea how lucky you are
that an intelligent woman loves you and wants
to give you something of value,
something that will inflame your creative potential!
Now, get going and hurry up!
- We'll see who gets lost without whom.
♪ Fritz the Cat, Fritz the Cat ♪
♪ Fritz the Cat ♪
♪ Help me, help me, now you can see ♪
♪ When me and my chick goes rattlin' round ♪
♪ I'm the envy of each and every guy in town ♪
♪ She looks so sharp and my girl does, too ♪
♪And everybody knows what I'm gonna do ♪
♪ Gonna take a ride on my bike ♪
♪ Gonna take it and ride all night ♪
♪ Tell my Chevy to take a hike ♪
♪ Take another ride on my bike ♪
Oh, Blue, I'm crazy about you.
- Penniless, a regular bum,
a hobo with no money and no place to go.
- Hey, you old scroungy old alley cat.
Get out of them garbage cans.
- You talking to me, Jack?
- What the hell you doing there, anyway?
- Hey, man, here we are on the brink of the apocalypse,
the eve of destruction, so to speak,
and I can't think of anything to do.
- Offhand, son, I'd say you have got a problem.
But at least you're honest.
The revolution can use a man like you. Hop on!
- Okay. Hello there.
- Hi. - How are you?
- High. - I'll introduce you
to the guys at the cell meeting.
- Blue! Glad you could make it, man.
- Howdy, John. I brought along an old buddy of mine.
He's a bright lad but bored with life.
Fritz, this here is John, former biker
and small-time hood turned fighter for the cause.
That cat was a beautiful head.
- Glad to meet you, man.
- Another cast out for the bourgeois view.
From the mold of bankrupt sedentary.
What's the state of his political consciousness?
- Practically nil, I'm afraid.
- Our shipment of weapons just came in today: Thirty-two.
- Can I get one? - Enough to go around.
Hey, chief.
- Getting ready for a little action planned for tonight.
- Yeah, we're gonna paralyze the whole fucking city.
- It's going to be great, man.
- The shit is really gonna come down tonight.
- We've got everything we need
for three synchronized sabotage actions.
The city will be ours.
- The machinery of the establishment's gonna
be in ruins by the morning.
The government will fall without firing one goddamn shot.
- The new mayor will resign and we'll move in
and set up a tribunal.
- It's curtains.
- Blue, honey, talk to me a minute.
- Don't bother me.
- I want to talk to you, honey. Let's go.
- Leave me the hell alone.
- Oh, come on. We'll go and get some chinks.
I'm so hungry.
- I ain't hungry.
- Don't turn off on me.
Besides- - I don't need that garbage.
- Every time you're with your friends
you don't pay any attention you son of a bitch!
That hurt me, god damn it!
What do you think I am, a boxing ball?
- A punching bag!
- Hit her! Hit her!
- You know what you guys are? You're a bunch of closet fags.
Shut up!
- And when I leave this place,
you'll all get together and you'll screw one another.
- That's nice. Oh, that is nice.
Oh, she loves it. I love it, too.
- Oh, we've got a lot of lousy time to kill.
- I think I'm gonna ride that goddamn horse.
- Then go on, have a go. You'll love it.
- Let me ride that goddamn horse.
- Get on with it. - You know what you are?
You're a bunch of fucking Nazi fags!
Guys, that's uncool.
Don't do that.
Listen, you son of a bitch, you lousy-
- Hey, cut it out! You're hurting her!
You maniacs! What are you doing to her?
- Go ahead and hit me if that's how you get your rocks off!
My God, my God!
I can't take it anymore!
This isn't working out, Blue. Our relationship stinks!
Come on, Harriet. Let's go inside, huh?
It's cold. - Oh.
I have to go to bed by day.
Come on inside, baby. You'll get hurt out here.
Listen, I tried to stop them, but I-
- Come on, Fritz!
- Hey, wait a minute, huh?
John says this night will mean a great leap forward
for America's social evolution.
Yeah, dig it. We're gonna blow up the power plant.
This will keep you warm.
I gotta go.
- Hey, baby.
We all had a good time today and got our rocks off.
Now we must devote ourselves
to the great task that lays before us.
- What'd you have to hit her so hard for?
- She loved it.
Listen, man, me and you have been assigned
to blow up the power plant.
That's all I care about, the revolution.
- You're full of shit!
All you care about is a reason to hurt,
to destroy, to blow up.
You don't know what a real revolution is.
None of you sons of bitches do.
Harriet, well, she's good, I mean.
She's real. She loves.
She loves and when you get right down to it,
I mean, that's where it's really at.
Yeah. The love you give is equal to the love you get.
Well, fuck it. I ain't doing it.
- So long, Fritz.
- I ain't planting this bomb for you schmucks.
Far out.
Dr. Pooh, Dr. Pooh.
And though after my skin worms
destroy this body, yet in my flesh shall I see God,
whom I shall see for myself.
- Fritz, Fritz! You gotta let us see our Fritz!
- I'm sorry, girls. - Where is he?
What have you done with him?
- You can't go in there. You just can't.
I'm sorry, girls. He's under house arrest.
- Let us see him! Please!
- No, no, no one gets in. - Please?
He's hurt. - Lord Jesus
and shalt believe in thine heart
that God hath raised Him from the dead.
- I reckon he must be through, finished.
- For with the heart man believeth unto righteousness
and with the mouth, confession is made unto salvation.
He that covereth his sins shall not prosper
but whoso confesseth and forsaketh them, shall have mercy.
Fritz, we're so sorry, baby.
Shh! He's trying to say something.
- I've been up and down the four corners
of this big old world.
I've seen it all
and I've done it all.
I've fought many a good man
and I've laid many a good woman.
And if there's one thing I've learned
it's, it's, you get over here!
And you get down there like that!
- Poor cat. He was a tough kid at that, wasn't he?
♪ Down the lane they're strolling two by two ♪
♪ Holding hands, they smile like we used to do ♪
♪ Here with their one and only ♪
♪ I'd forgotten I was lonely ♪
♪ Oh, how I wish ♪
♪ That here were there with you ♪
♪All the days of sadness ♪
♪ They seem so needless now ♪
♪ Yes, it's taken me ♪
♪ This long, long time ♪
♪ To see it's clear ♪
♪ That my dreams keep drifting back to me ♪
♪And our strolls ♪
♪ Beneath these same stars above ♪
♪And when the leaves are falling ♪
♪ My heart will be recalling ♪
♪ You're the only girl ♪
♪ I ever really loved ♪