A NETFLIX ORIGINAL FILM
Mom! Mom!
Look what I made, Mom!
Me, too!
But mine's cooler than Al's.
Edward, Alphonse, that's great!
You both manage to make
such amazing things with alchemy.
Do you think Dad would be proud of us?
Mm-hm.
One day, he'll come home
and tell you how proud you make him.
Yeah! All right!
Be good boys!
Watch out for--
Mother?
Mother!
I'm hungry, brother.
I'm cold, too.
I want to see Mom.
There's a passage about homunculi
in the alchemy book.
You mean the artificial humans?
I wonder if we can bring Mom back.
But creating humans
with alchemy isn't allowed.
Okay,
so we'll just keep it to ourselves.
35 liters of water.
20 kilograms of carbon.
Four liters of ammonia.
1,5 kilograms of lime.
800 grams of phosphorus.
250 grams of salt.
100 grams of niter.
80 grams of sulfur.
7,5 grams of fluorine.
Five grams of metal.
Three grams of silicon.
Plus 15 grams
of miscellaneous chemical elements.
All these ingredients
that make up an adult human
are available at the local market.
According to
the Law of Equivalent Exchange of alchemy,
we have everything that we need.
That's the last ingredient,
the makeup of a human soul.
Hey. Is this really okay?
Don't say that now!
Yes, but the alchemy book says
it's absolutely prohibited to--
Don't you wanna be able to see Mom again?
I do…
Good. Then let's go!
Ready, Al?
Ready.
Something is wrong!
Al!
Brother!
REOLE
Hmm.
Hey, Gramps.
Why don't you just gimme that ring?
That's the Philosopher's Stone
all right.
Oh.
Give it up!
Whoa! Awesome!
That's what
the Philosopher's Stone can do.
It must be the real thing.
You can do alchemy
without a transmutation circle?
You saved my ass!
You're hollow inside!
What are you? Who are… you two?
Ow.
Oh, no. That hurts.
Take this!
That…
prosthetic arm…
and prosthetic leg!
You're…
the FullMetal Alchemist!
I'm honored that you've heard of me.
Now that that's out of the way,
hand over the Stone!
Come on!
Hmm?
Oh!
-Pastor?
Hey, hey, what…
Oh.
-Huh?
-Now you know the truth!
He's not a pastor
who can perform miracles.
He's just a lowlife conman
who's been deceiving you.
What's going on?
Oh…
Stay away!
Or she'll meet her maker!
Know your limit, third-grade alchemist.
I'll show you what separates us.
Oh!
-Huh?
Gotcha!
It's been a while, FullMetal.
Colonel?
Whoa! The Flame Alchemist.
-Arrest him!
-Hup!
Hey, what's going on? Let me go!
I just happened to be in town
for an inspection,
when I heard talk about
a puny alchemist who was causing havoc.
Who do you think you're calling puny? Huh!
What in the devil
have you made here?
Let go of me!
Do you know what it took for me
to find that stone?
The Philosopher's Stone is
a perfect object, and is indestructible.
Is that correct?
Looks like it's another fake, brother.
I'm sorry, Al.
Wait!
-Take him to Eastern Headquarters.
-Yes.
Ed.
Reole!
Ooh!
Wow!
Hey, now. You must be
the famous FullMetal Alchemist!
Oh, wow! You became a state-certified
alchemist when you were just 12!
Oh! That armor that you wear.
That must be how you got your nickname.
I think you must mean my brother.
Not me.
Huh? You mean the short guy?
Yes.
No way!
But it's true!
My brother is so good
that he can perform alchemy
without drawing a transmutation circle.
Sure, he might be short,
but he has a big heart.
Well, whoever. What I want to know is,
can you ask your shrimpy brother
to replace my food stall
with one that's made of marble?
Alchemy is not magic.
It's science.
We can't do that.
Don't be stingy. Come on!
Do this!
Alchemy follows
the Law of Equivalent Exchange.
You can only materialize things
of the same value.
It also follows the conservation
of mass laws, and natural providence.
Then there's the three major elements,
and the four protyles…
Aah.
Okay…
If I have one portion of something,
I can only create
the same amount of something else.
If I had water, I would only be able
to create something
that was similar in nature.
Huh.
Nothing you say makes sense.
But, in short,
you can't make marble out of wood.
I'm really sorry.
Al!
Winry!
Oooh!
It's been so long!
Huh? Where's Ed?
I'll find it no matter what!
Listen to me!
The Philosopher's Stone is just a myth.
Yeah? Well, what about the red stone?
That wasn't the work of standard alchemy!
Like I already told you,
the stone was an amplifier.
The military has also researched
how to amplify alchemy.
To disappointing results.
Twice, maybe three times greater.
How much would you need
for human transmutation?
A thousand times? Ten thousand?
Regardless, the state denies
the existence of the Philosopher's Stone.
The military would love to believe that!
What's that?
You're a state alchemist.
Would you defy its position?
Without the Philosopher's Stone…
Al will never be able
to get his body back.
I became a state alchemist
so I could access valuable information
about the Philosopher's Stone.
I'll be the military's dog
as long as I can get Al's body!
And find a way to recover your lost limbs.
Don't you get it? I don't care about that!
Al comes first.
I only want to get my brother's body back.
And you would… destroy a whole city
in the pursuit of this goal?
I would do anything.…
to get Al's body back.
Whatever the reason,
your duty is to follow orders.
My advice to you? Forget
about the Philosopher's Stone,
and explore other options.
Excuse me, Colonel.
Hey!
Captain Hughes!
You're looking good, Edward.
General Hakuro.
Aah. So you're the FullMetal Alchemist.
I've been looking forward to meeting you.
I heard you've been causing
some chaos lately.
And what about your younger brother?
In the armor.
Uh, well…
He's fixing up the town right now.
He's picking up after you!
I would love to meet
this armored brother of yours.
I'd also love
to hear about your adventures some time.
Yeah!
"Whatever the reason,
your duty is to follow orders."
Hah! He acts so superior.
Every time I meet the Colonel,
he's more obnoxious.
We joined the military at the same time.
But I guess he has what it takes
to get promoted to command.
And are you saying
you don't, Captain?
Hey!
Watch it!
So, why are you at Eastern Headquarters?
I wasn't demoted,
if that's what you're thinking.
I'm just here for an inspection.
I just got in from Central City,
and I am beat!
Edward!
Winry…
Oh!
Oh. Oh!
What did-- Are you kidding me?
Do you know how much time I put
into this top-notch automail arm?
Sorry.
What did you do this time
to ruin it like this?
-I don't know. There was this stone dog…
-A what?
-"Raaarrr!"
-This is beyond repair!
I need to make a brand new one.
Your peer showed up
without notice from Central.
You're here for an inspection?
Right this minute?
Yes, I am.
Pardon me asking,
but do you have an ulterior motive?
Do you have reason to think I do?
No.
Hmm.
As you know,
the Führer works in mysterious ways.
I expect great things from you, young man.
But watch your back.
Elites like you are easy targets.
Shou Tucker. Have you ever heard of him?
Yes. Isn't he the alchemist
who specializes in transmutating chimeras?
That's Tucker, yes.
Could you introduce the brothers to him?
You mean Ed and Al, sir?
I want to…
do something to help those boys.
Affirmative, sir.
Hey-- Hey! Wait a minute!
I still have those townspeople
in the palm of my hand!
Listen!
Everything got screwed up
because of your Philosopher's Stone!
Which was a fake!
Hmm. A fake, you say?
Do you think there's
a real Philosopher's Stone?
Unless there was a real one,
there couldn't be a fake one, right, Envy?
Look at that.
Now there's no real Cornello.
Well, then, I suppose
I can't be called the fake one, then.
Hey! Hey, Lust.
Can I eat this? Please?
Aaah!
Not this one, Gluttony.
If you eat this one,
he'll… upset your tummy.
Miss Gracia, are you sure it's okay
for us to stay the night?
Be my guest. The more the merrier.
We're here for a month.
But the house is huge for us.
So, the military wastes money
and resources on captains, huh?
Ugh!
Winry, as a mechanic, I bet you have
all kinds of trouble with this guy.
Ugh! Ed is the only person
who manages to break the automail I make.
Yeah, well, it's not like it's on purpose.
Doesn't matter!
Don't go breaking it again!
Otherwise it looks like
the work I do is cheap and shoddy.
You really shouldn't
put down your client, okay?
And you really shouldn't talk back!
Huh?
She's worried about you.
You can tell how much danger Ed was in
by the damage done to his automail, right?
No, I don't really worry about him…
So, you've all been friends
since you were kids?
Oh, right. We were born in Resembool
and grew up there.
We've known each other forever.
We're almost like siblings.
Hmm.
Uh, and now,
how did the two of you meet each other?
-Huh?
-Whoa! Cut to the chase?
-Get right into it!
-Yeah!
Okay, where do I begin?
Once he gets started, he'll go on forever.
Let me get you a little more food.
Ah, don't get up. I'll do it.
You need to take care of our little one.
Aah!
Mmm.
Hey, Al?
Edward!
Al!
Uh…
What was I doing?
Hello!
Who is it?
I am who you call the world.
The universe.
God.
The truth.
The one.
And all.
And I am you.
I'll show you…
…that which you have always wanted…
I'll show you the truth.
My head is splitting apart!
Don't break me!
Please don't!
Please, make it stop!
Mother.
Mother!
How'd you like it?
I understand it now.
Huh.
I saw the truth.
My theory of human transmutation,
it wasn't wrong!
I was this close
to the truth of human transmutation.
I have to go back. Please show me again.
No, you can't do that.
You've seen as much as you can
for the toll that you paid.
Toll?
Yes.
The toll.
You remember equivalent exchange.
Right? Don't you, alchemist?
Al!
Damn it. He took it.
Somebody help me.
Please, Mom.
Mother?
I'm sorry!
This isn't what I wanted.
Al.
This is all my fault.
Give me….
my brother back.
I don't care what the toll is.
You can take my leg or my arm.
Take my heart if you want.
Just give him back! He's all I have!
You're back again.
How foolish of you.
Again?
Was it the same nightmare?
In the dream,
it's always the same, reliving that day.
Every detail.
The Sewing-Life Alchemist?
That's right.
His name is Shou Tucker.
A pioneer in biological alchemy.
Lately, he's been attempting to transmute
chimera with the ability to speak.
Chimera who can communicate?
That I want to see!
Two years ago, he transmuted a chimera.
It said one thing.
"Please kill me." And then it died.
Okay. But why are we meeting with him?
General Hakuro told us to.
He thinks he might have an idea
about how to get Al's body back.
This house is huge!
-Edward?
-Brother?
Dad! Look at all the visitors we have!
Hey, Alexander!
Whoa! Oh…
Yeah. Sorry for the mess.
It's pretty much been like this
since my wife left two years ago.
Thanks for seeing us. You must be busy.
No problem! It really is a privilege
to meet the famous Fullmetal Alchemist.
The pleasure is all mine.
So, then. If General Hakuro
is behind your visit,
I will make you my top priority.
-Please.
-Thank you very much.
Al! This way!
-Al! Over here?
-Where are you?
-Oh!
-Here he comes!
Nina is… happy
to have someone to play with.
Sadly, I haven't had much time lately.
Because your state evaluation
is coming up.
Honestly, the progress reports
I submit every year to Central Command
really take a lot out of me.
Hmm.
I'm certainly not a genius like you.
It's just that my credentials
could be revoked this year.
I just can't let that happen.
You think I'm not telling you
why I'm here?
If I'm being perfectly honest, yes.
Since the Ishvalan Civil War,
things just haven't been the same.
The upheavals and riots
have been relentless.
Suspicion's rising among the citizens.
You think I'm suspicious too.
I'm not suspicious of you.
But at Central Command,
some people are suspicious
of what Eastern Headquarters is up to.
So because we're friends,
they sent you here to keep an eye on me?
Roy. If you want to get to the top…
you'd better watch out for yourself.
Not everyone in the state military
will be supportive.
Should I watch you?
Yes, you should.
Whoa!
They call me
the pioneering creator of chimera,
but really, many of them are imperfect.
But you did manage
to create a chimera that speaks.
Yes. Just once, two years ago.
You really did it. That's so impressive!
Yes, but… it only spoke three words,
and shortly after, died.
But those three words were enough
to earn my state alchemist credentials.
So, then, your mom's not around.
But it's okay. I still have
my dad and Alexander here with me.
Although…
lately, my dad is spending
a lot of time in his lab.
So it's sometimes just me.
Well, now you have us to play with.
As much as you want!
-You sure?
-Uh-huh!
Yay! It'll be fun, Alexander!
Come on!
In the end, I managed
to return to the Gate of Truth,
but all I was able to do
was get back Al's soul.
So you transmuted Al's soul
and you harnessed it
to the suit of steel armor.
The price that I had to pay
for returning Al's soul was my right arm.
But I…
I would have gladly given my life
if it meant getting back Al's body.
It must have crushed you.
Mr. Tucker.
Is it possible for you
to get Al's body back?
I'm afraid…
it's beyond my capabilities.
Yeah, I… I didn't think so.
Although…
I'd like to do an experiment.
Hey, Edward!
Oh! No. No, no. Oh! Oh, oh, oh!
Ah!
-I made it!
-Sorry we had to leave so quickly.
Yeah, I got caught up in some paperwork
and i almost missed you.
For you. Gracia made it.
Wow! Please, tell her thank you for us.
Oh, hey, where's Al?
Oh, Mr. Tucker wanted Al to stay there.
He thinks he might be able
to do something for him.
That's good.
So, did you get some information from him?
He told us about a man named Dr. Marcoh,
who's been researching
the Philosopher's Stone.
Right. It seems that
Dr. Marcoh disappeared a year ago,
but recently, someone said
they saw him in the Barns.
Ed, I hope that this time,
you find the Stone.
Mmm.
Hmm.
My research
wasn't very highly regarded last year.
If I don't do well this year, I'm at risk
of them revoking my state credentials.
You'll be okay. Cheer up, Dad.
Because you always study so hard.
I love you, Dad.
You just watch.
I'll pull it off.
You seem worried.
Don't worry.
Al's not a child anymore.
I'm not worried about him.
It's just…
I'm not used to being without him.
Yeah, I know.
The two of you are always together.
Anyway, Mr. Tucker seems nice,
and Nina and Alexander are there.
That's right. So cheer up!
Oh, by the way, Nina seemed
to really take a liking to you.
Come on, Ed!
Mmm!
Come on, Ed! Play with me! Please!
-Yeah, little kids always seem to like me.
-Right, because you're their size.
Uh--
Apple pie!
-Are you gonna eat it already?
-It's okay?
Gracia baked this for us to eat it.
You know what I mean?
Have a piece.
Al couldn't eat… any of this,
even if he wanted to.
He doesn't sleep.
He doesn't feel pain or anything.
Remember, Mr. Tucker said
he'd use hypnotism on Al,
so he could study him
and learn everything about him.
It'll just be like he's sleeping.
Maybe Al's dreaming now.
Yeah, right.
In his dreams, he'd be eating
a huge apple pie all to himself.
Sure, sure! An extra-large pie
baked just for him.
-A tall pie's weird.
-Huh?
Wouldn't it be big sideways?
Think so?
You want another slice? Have a tiny one.
Hey!
I feel like… like I'm hot all over.
Maybe your soul is being
drawn back into your body.
Maybe. Or…
Or what?
It's possible that your…
artificially implanted memories
are just being harnessed.
Artificially implanted memories?
It's very rare for an alchemist to succeed
in harnessing a living soul
to an inanimate object.
Are you suggesting
that my memories are made up?
It would be a logical explanation…
But you might also be a rare exception.
I feel… dizzy.
Artificial memories.
-We're getting off!
-Uh--
Winry! Your bag!
What's going on?
We're not in the Barns yet.
The photo!
-What?
-Show me the photo Mr. Tucker gave you!
Here.
It's really him.
Doctor Marcoh!
Winry!
Hey, wait up, Winry.
Oh, hello. Excuse me!
Excuse me. Did you see this man just now?
No.
Just a minute.
-Can I see that again?
-Of course.
Ah, this is Dr. Mauro.
Uh, he works in that hospital.
I didn't recognize him,
because he looks younger in the photo.
Excuse me?
Dr. Marcoh? Are you here?
Why are you here?
How do you know my real name?
Please calm down, Dr. Marcoh.
I won't ever go back there.
Uh…
Hmm.
I'm sorry about that.
I thought, when I saw you,
that they had come to take me back.
Who are they?
I heard you did research on
the Philosopher's Stone with the military.
Is it something that's related to that?
We didn't come here
to investigate for the military.
Please.
You have to tell me this one thing.
Does the Philosopher's Stone really exist?
You should go now.
What?
With the shotgun. I saw you
perform alchemy without a circle.
You've attempted human transmutation.
And as a result,
you accessed the Gate of Truth.
That's why I'm looking
for the Philosopher's Stone.
Please believe me.
You should stay away from the Stone,
for your own sake.
I need to find it,
even if it costs me my life!
Any involvement with the Stone
is playing with the devil.
Pursuing it will land you in hell.
I've already been to hell.
How dare you?
You actually killed me.
But how is-- What is she?
Nice to see you again, Marcoh.
So you've been hiding out here
all these years?
Lust.
I'm not coming with you.
You won't have to,
because you're no longer needed.
-You witch!
-Shut up.
Ed!
Winry!
Stop your squeaking…
…FullMetal boy.
If you can keep quiet, I'll let you live.
You'll make a fine sacrifice.
But you, Marcoh, are worthless.
Don't kill him!
I'm okay.
Dr. Marcoh!
Keep this.
It's the circle.
To transmute… the Stone.
You actually transmuted
a Philosopher's Stone?
Laboratory…
Number 5.
Laboratory Number 5.
Dr. Marcoh? Dr. Marcoh?
Go, it's fine.
I'll take care of the mess
and catch up with you after.
But, Winry, it…
Don't worry, I've got it.
I'll ask the local authorities for help.
You finally got a good lead
on the Philosopher's Stone
Be safe.
Go make sure
everything's all right with Al.
The Philosopher's Stone.
It exists.
Mr. Tucker!
Mr. Tucker?
Huh?
Hey, Al?
Nina?
Oh, hi, Ed.
I just got back.
Mr. Tucker, I have something to tell you.
Hey, where's Al?
Oh… don't worry. He'll wake up soon.
I've finally completed it.
Look at it, Ed.
A chimera who understands human language.
Listen.
That person is…
Edward.
Ed…
…ward.
That's right. That is very good.
Wow! It can really speak.
Yes.
I managed to make it
in time for the evaluation.
Now the military will have no choice
but to recognize my true talent.
Edward.
Edward!
Ed, play with me! Please?
Mr. Tucker.
Yes?
Do you really think it's possible
to get back Al's body?
When did you get the state credentials
for your chimera research?
Well, it was…
two years ago.
And when did you say your wife left you?
Two years ago.
One more question, if you don't mind.
Nina and Alexander…
where are they?
I hate insightful little brats like you.
Bastard!
Two years ago, you used your wife.
And now, you've transmuted another chimera
using your dog and your own daughter!
It makes sense. There's only so much
you can do with animals.
But experimenting on humans?
Why are you so upset?
Without human experimentation,
mankind would have never progressed.
Have you completely lost your mind?
Do you think you'll be forgiven
for toying with human lives?
I toyed?
That's right. And what about the things
that you did to you and your brother?
You also toyed with human life!
You and I, we're exactly the same.
Shut up!
FullMetal Alchemist!
There's nothing that separates us.
Shut up!
Shut up! Shut up!
-Shut up!
-Brother.
If you keep that up, you'll kill him.
Sometimes, you've gotta
get your hands dirty.
Mr. Tucker.
If you say another word,
I'll be the one to lose control.
Dad…
What's wrong
Dad?
Nina. I'm sorry.
There's no way to turn you back.
We're not capable of helping you.
We…
can't trust anyone anymore.
I'm sorry.
Play with… me?
Play with me?
We're revoking
your state alchemist credentials.
Once at Central,
you'll be court-martialed.
Take him away.
Do you think the two of them will be okay?
Alphonse! You and I got so close
to finding the truth!
See you soon!
How long will you sit there
and feel bad for yourself?
Leave me alone.
You do realize
that you are a state alchemist?
You joined to use that privilege
to find a way to mend
your and your brother's bodies.
And they call us devils!
Don't let something like this stop you.
"Something like this…"
Yeah, you're right.
I don't care if they call me
the military's lapdog. Or a devil.
As long as Al and I get our bodies.
But the thing is…
we're not really devils.
We're not gods, either.
We're just humans…
We're just puny humans
who can't do anything!
Even save a little girl.
Go back and rest.
Before you catch a cold.
So, Ed's been locked up
in the library for three days now.
He's hardly eaten anything.
Yeah.
He won't let me help him.
He says it's too dangerous.
What happened when you two were away?
What are you doing
in this dungeon all by yourself?
Captain Hughes.
Did you find what you're looking for?
Why do this alone?
We are friends, aren't we?
Hey, Ed! Aren't we friends?
Of course.
And friends help each other out.
Please, come in!
Meet Lieutenant Ross and the sandwiches.
Eat some, or you'll collapse.
Thank you,
but she works for Colonel Mustang.
She's a highly trusted officer.
She's also a good friend.
Can't go wrong
with friends of friends, right?
-I said, can't go wrong with friends--
-Yeah, I heard you!
Eat something.
Then we'll talk
about the transmutation circle.
-And Laboratory Number 5.
-What?
Winry! I told her not to tell anyone.
Ah, you can't blame her.
I'm very persuasive.
Huh.
But… this all falls under
the category of classified information.
Dr. Marcoh was murdered.
-Anyone involved runs that risk.
-You must not have heard.
I'll say it again.
We are friends.
I don't know.
We haven't found anything related
to Marcoh's transmutation circle
for the Philosopher's Stone.
It seems like they have destroyed
any of Marcoh's remaining documents.
The question is… who's behind it?
And why did they do it?
It's looking to me like an inside job.
I think you're probably right.
The military, the stone.
And the mysterious woman with the tattoo.
She's not human.
I can't believe that woman is human.
What about Laboratory Number 5?
Marcoh belonged to a lab,
but it was Laboratory Number 3.
There's a total of four
official military laboratories.
But there's no record anywhere
of Laboratory Number 5.
But I'm sure I heard him say
Laboratory Number 5.
-Is this a special meeting?
-General Hakuro!
Oh! Hughes is here too.
Uh… we were… looking…
Oh, that's right. That was what
a select group of people used to call it.
Sir?
I'm talking about your lab. Laboratory 5.
Do you know where it is?
It was before I was stationed here.
I think it's this one.
It's a cannery.
Why did they call a cannery
Laboratory Number 5?
Hmm.
The cannery is not operating.
It's in ruins now.
Thank you very much,
General Hakuro!
Hey, Ed!
General! Emergency!
It's Reole, sir.
Full-scale riots are underway.
Reole?
Where the sham priest was operating.
Sir,
there has been a report of casualties.
I'll leave now.
-Lieutenant Ross, return to your station.
-Sir.
-You're our guest, Captain.
-Uh… but, sir…
I'm in command at Reole.
Mustang will need to be at Headquarters,
leaving you to stay here and help out.
There's already been so much
bloody violence in this country.
First in Ishval, now it's Reole.
This is the last one.
There's no sign of a laboratory left.
Oh damn!
I know we're so close to the secret
of the Philosopher's Stone!
Cheer up, Al.
We're really close to the secret.
Once we discover it,
we'll get your body back--
Tell me what happened
when you were with Dr. Marcoh.
Al.
Is there something
that you've been keeping from me?
Uh… No.
We don't even know for sure
that my body actually exists.
How can you be so sure that we're ever
going to be able to get it back?
You say you transmuted my soul.
But maybe it's not really a soul.
Maybe it's just
some made-up memories you created.
What are you talking about?
Tucker told me that transmuting a soul
and harnessing it within an object
would be virtually impossible,
especially for a kid.
That bastard Tucker…
Whatever that lunatic said to you,
he wasn't telling you the truth.
You have to trust me.
I have to trust you?
Look at me. I'm hollow!
How can I trust anyone?
Maybe I never even existed.
Al…
Maybe everything is just made up!
I know you're all deceiving me.
Ed, you're a liar!
Ed!
No.
Maybe you're not even my real brother!
What do you think you're doing?
Just stop it, you two!
Brother, use your right hand.
You're going to ruin your left one.
Al, you idiot!
Ed cares about you more than anything!
Edward is…
always, constantly thinking about you.
Even when it's just the two of us,
all he does is talk about you.
Winry…
He believes that…
it's entirely his fault
you lost your body.
He's always blamed himself.
Don't you know that's the reason
he does all those dangerous things?
To get your body back!
Hey!
What idiot would risk his life
just to create a fake brother
to torment himself with?
The two of you…
are the only thing the other one has!
Hey, Al.
I'm not finished!
Brother.
That hurts.
Liar!
You don't feel pain!
Brother.
It hurts…
to see you hurt.
I'll get your body back, Al.
No matter what the cost is.
I promise.
Ishvalan Civil War.
And riots in Reole.
There were riots in the north and the west
as well as border conflicts.
Oh God.
Hold on a second.
Now, think. Who's behind this?
Wait a minute.
That's what I thought.
The position of the four laboratories
is strategic.
So it makes sense for Number 5 to be…
There you are.
Now you know too much.
The Ouroboros tattoo!
You're the one
who attacked and killed Dr. Marcoh.
Hmm.
Nice to meet you.
Or would "goodbye" be more appropriate?
I mistook him for the brainy type.
That was a good fight, Captain.
I'm calling from outside
because the internal lines aren't secure!
-May I have the security code?
-What a pain in the ass!
Uncle, Sugar, Oliver, eight, zero, zero.
Security confirmed, thank you.
I'll put you through to Colonel Mustang.
Damn it, Roy, pick up the phone!
We're all in trouble.
Roy?
What is it?
Come with us. We have orders to escort you
back to Eastern Headquarters.
Is this some kind of an emergency?
What do you think is going on?
Brother.
Don't worry.
I'll contact you when I know what it is.
What's goin' on?
Stand by in this room
until otherwise instructed, sir.
What?
You're treating me like a criminal.
I'm not gonna use alchemy in here!
They got you too, huh?
Lieutenant.
What's goin' on?
It's Captain Hughes…
He was murdered.
All personnel have orders
to arrest the suspect.
Who was the killer?
Tell me!
Colonel Mustang.
There were witnesses.
Anyone close to the colonel has been
put under surveillance or detained.
There's one more thing.
Tucker got out.
Alphonse! You and I got so close
to finding the truth!
See you soon!
Al…
Did Mustang help Tucker escape?
Where is he?
Where is Colonel Mustang?
No! Don't do it!
Sorry about that.
Found it.
So Mustang said, "Laboratory Number 5"?
After he finished talking with Hughes,
he hurried out
saying he'd head
for the old prisoner-of-war camp.
I thought Lab Number 5
was in that abandoned cannery.
No. Colonel Mustang said that researchers
used to call the prisoner-of-war camp
"Lab Number 5."
Fall in!
-Attention!
-Hup!
I figured.
Colonel, come with me, please.
It's you, Lieutenant Ross…
I'm under orders to arrest you
for the murder of Captain Hughes.
Heavy security detail
for an abandoned prison.
I wonder how you knew I'd come here.
Don't move, or I shoot.
Please don't make me.
It's shoot to kill if you resist.
Colonel, last warning! Don't!
Colonel, don't do it!
Ross…
Don't panic.
That was damn hot.
How did you know?
The mole on Ross's face. Wrong side.
Ah, is that right?
I got that wrong.
Hey! I've been exposed, Lust.
So I see.
Yes, you have.
Hey, wait! I know you!
Oh. Hi, Fullmetal boy.
Thanks for remembering.
The Ouroboros tattoos.
FullMetal, they aren't really human.
Homunculi.
They are… artificial humans.
Homunculi?
You did your homework well.
Do you know Maes Hughes, by chance?
I know him well.
He was a smart man, and very gifted.
It's a shame…
I didn't get the chance
to finish him off myself.
Hello? Is this Hughes?
What's wrong?
Answer me.
Who are you?
Tell me.
Nice touch, isn't it?
Hughes, what's wrong?
Hold on. I'll be right there. Hughes!
Lab… Number 5.
Old… prisoner-of-war camp.
Hughes…
Hughes!
Answer me! Hughes!
Hughes. Hughes!
Hughes!
My plan was to frame you,
as the military conspirator,
and then afterwards, finish you off,
like your friend Hughes.
Get on your knees!
I would never kneel down before you.
No mercy.
No wonder you're a hero
of the Ishvalan Civil War.
You're the ones
who helped Shou Tucker escape!
So, what is it you want?
Tucker?
The chimera professor broke out?
Damn it. That bastard deserved to rot.
Envy!
Gluttony. You can eat all of them,
except FullMetal boy.
She said that I could eat you all!
Colonel!
Even the Flame Alchemist has a soft spot.
FullMetal.
You have to stop them.
We'll be fine. Just go!
-Al!
-Brother, don't come up here!
Not so fast, Ed.
If you come any closer…
I'll put a hole in her forehead.
I'm sorry, Ed. I couldn't protect her.
Tucker, you bastard.
I'll rip you into pieces if you hurt them!
You're always so violent!
First, I'll ask you
to remove your right arm.
Huh?
Your alchemy is too dangerous
for me to ignore.
Stop.
Hurry up!
I really should start by thanking you.
I mean, after all, I learned the secret
of harnessing a soul to an object.
by studying your handiwork.
I, uh--
I guess actually, I should be thanking
your younger brother over here.
I asked him to take a look for me,
inside the Gate of Truth.
You've got what you want.
Why don't you let them go?
Can you tell what this is?
The Philosopher's Stone.
That's correct.
I hold in my hand
the true Philosopher's Stone,
the object of your obsession.
Look down at the floor,
what you're standing on.
The circle to transmute the stone.
But that says…
Oh, no.
That's impossible!
That's why you're a genius.
Just like that, you understand
precisely what this circle means.
-It can't be.
-Yes, it can, and it is.
This place has an abundance of material.
You know, of course,
this used to be a prisoner-of-war camp.
It's…
To transmute
the Philosopher's Stone…
you need living humans!
These are the Philosopher's Stones
that Marcoh and his colleagues transmuted!
What have you done?
You accused me
of toying with lives.
But when you compare it to what they did,
I'm just tinkering!
See? Isn't that right?
Am I right, FullMetal Alchemist?
But why?
What would they ever do this for?
I wondered, too.
And there are so many of them!
I'm not interested…
in the slightest in these little pebbles.
But I do have one personal wish.
I'd like to see you fail
to fulfill your brilliant promises.
It would be the kind of supreme pleasure
only a superior man could enjoy!
My gift to you is to put an end
to your miserable little quest.
Is anything worse than a chatty man?
This is not what I ordered you to do.
You know, looking down at a lady
the way you're doing
is very unsophisticated.
General Hakuro.
I showed you the secret
of how to make the Philosopher's Stone.
But I won't show you how to use them.
You won't?
I don't need you to.
The brilliant Mr. Tucker
solved that particular mystery for me.
Oh, did he, now?
The government deemed him worthless,
but I was smart enough to know
that they were incorrect.
General Hakuro, what's goin' on here?
Do you know why the military
prohibited human transmutation?
Of course.
Because it's immoral and unethical.
Correct, that's the official reason.
The real reason is
because it would allow a person
to create an infinite amount of soldiers.
If you were to do that,
a single person could form
a powerful military force.
Let me show you
what the military feared the most.
I seriously doubt
you can handle those babies.
Well, I assure you that I can.
I saw Tucker doing a wonderful job.
And what about your plan?
Did you think you could rule over humans
with those, homunculus?
Are you thinking of disobeying orders?
I know that you are controlling
some higher-ups in the military,
but no one gives me orders anymore.
Now, each Philosopher's Stone
injects a soul into each dummy,
and they become
the world's toughest soldiers.
They feel no fear, they feel no pain.
And when I am finished,
I will have an unstoppable army,
made of invincible soldiers!
Crazy, selfish bastard!
All those human lives, so you can
build an army with these dummies.
Well, I won't let you.
With my army, I will rule the world!
Papa. Papa.
That's right.
Come to your papa, my children.
Papa.
Papa. Papa.
I told you. Now, what are you gonna do
with all these dummies, huh?
Ugh, that guy really screwed up our plan.
Hmph.
There really is no end
to their foolishness.
Papa…
Gluttony.
Can I eat them?
Yes.
And don't leave any leftovers.
Stand back!
Inform the soldiers outside.
Stop them. Do not let them escape.
If any get out,
the public will be at risk.
But how?
Papa. Papa.
Target their heads.
Target their heads. Now go!
Papa. Papa.
Papa. Papa. Papa.
I… can't move my body.
Move it!
Stay away from my brother!
Brother!
Papa. Papa…
-Ed, I'm sorry.
-Papa…
I messed up…
-No, you didn't.
-Winry!
It's 'cause I got caught that Al couldn't…
Later. I've got to get those homunculi.
Al, can you stop those creatures
from gettin' out?
I'll try.
Winry, remount this. Do your best.
You got it.
Damn it!
Now you've pissed me off.
You won't get away with what you've done!
So you seared your wound
to stop the breeding.
Very resourceful.
I almost fainted
a few times doing it.
But I can't die until…
the last of you is down.
How many times do I have to stab you
before you shut up and die?
No leftovers, she said!
Attention!
Target their heads.
That's how you kill them.
Do not let any of them out!
Yes!
Fire!
This time,
I'll punch so many holes in you,
you'll have to sear your whole body
to stop the bleeding.
Well done, FullMetal boy.
I'll reveal my secret as a reward.
We're man-made.
The Philosopher's Stone
is the core of our existence.
No matter how many times we die,
the Stone resurrects us.
So you're immortal.
You monsters.
Don't be rude.
We don't look any different
compared to you.
We have senses, emotions,
affection for our creator.
We're human.
You bastard.
You burned me to death, over and over.
But that's not enough to kill me yet.
You're an important candidate
for the sacrifice, FullMetal boy.
But unfortunately,
we can't let you live.
Colonel.
You noticed too?
Looks to me like it's taking longer
and longer for the skinny one to recover.
I was wondering why
the woman with the tattoo
was stalling me
with meaningless explanations.
You said, "Not enough to kill me yet."
Now, to me, that makes it sound like
you have a limited number of lives.
Perhaps your slow recovery
implies that you're gettin' close
to reaching your limit.
Am I right?
I bet you're on… your last life.
I won't go easy on you now.
Damn it.
Go ahead.
I'm taking FullMetal boy with me.
How about that? You have a weakness too.
Take this!
I finally brought you to your knees,
homunculus.
How many times do I have to burn you
before you shut up and die?
I'll kill you until you're dead for good!
This one is for Hughes.
I can…
die.
I can die, just…
like a human.
Colonel!
FullMetal.
Lust is dead.
Brother? Is that the…
Yeah.
This is the Philosopher's Stone.
We've looked for it relentlessly
for so long.
We finally have it.
And now that it's ours…
I can't believe…
I can't believe how they made it!
Brother.
Please, Ed, no. Don't do it!
That stone is human life!
Brother!
How have you been, alchemist?
So, you came back
with the proper toll this time.
Al. So you were here the whole time.
You've gotten so thin.
Now, let's make the exchange.
Al. I'll come back for you,
no matter what.
I promise.
Al!
Brother?
Brother!
Al.
I'm sorry.
Please forgive me.
It's okay, You did the right thing.
I don't want it
at the price of another life.
I'd rather stay like this.
Yeah…
But, Al…
your body was actually there.
Really.
It's really there. I saw it.
That's great.
It really exists?
Did I… look all right?
Yeah.
You were all grown up there,
I was surprised.
Ed, was I taller than you?
Hmm.
Uh-huh.
You're taller than me.
I am?
Aren't I great?
Colonel. I want you to climb the ranks.
All the way up,
so you can get to the bottom of this.
Hughes would want the same thing.
That's always been my intention.
-Eeny, meeny, minie, mo.
-Oh. Oops!
-I choose you!
-All right!
Yes!
Oh, man.
I'll keep my promise, Al.
I'll find another way
to get your body back.