♪ Sweet dreams are made of this ♪
♪ Who am I to disagree? ♪
♪ Travel the world and the Seven Seas ♪
♪ Everybody looking for something ♪
♪ Some of them want to use you ♪
♪ Some of them want to get used by you ♪
♪ Some of them want to abuse you ♪
♪ Some of them want to be abused ♪
♪ Some of them want to use you ♪
♪ Some of them want to get used by you ♪
♪ Some of them want to abuse you ♪
♪ Some of them want to be abused ♪
Put the fucking team back in!
Turn me around.
Shit!
Good run, Kable.
- My name is Tillman.
- Whatever your name is,
you got to the save point fast.
- Who the fuck cares?
No one is getting out of here alive.
I am. I'm gonna make it out.
Sure you will.
They said you got 3 battles left
before you get out.
Bob!
Alright, let me handle this.
- Do we have the interview or don't we?
- Yes
We are a cunt-hair close.
Look I'm not going to blow the
3 Asian Wars for 'close'.
With all do respect, Bob,
nobody cares about dead Orientals.
- They care about Ken Castle.
- Can I hear from Gina, please?
Okay, Bob ...
Bob, are you aware that Castle has clocked
exactly one media appearance date,
and that was Walter's last interview
before she died nine fucking years ago!
Stop menstruating and just tell me
whether we fucking have it?
We fucking, have it.
Good!
Palindromes.
Okay, focus.
Let's get lunch.
Iranian, Sushi, or Mexican?
Uh, no.
Burger, chilli, fries?
I could freak a burger.
We live in Society.
We visit Society.
I mean, which one ...
which one's more real?
Really?
I mean, which one's really real?
Know what I mean?
You're watching
Gina Parker Smith.
A live
'World Link Tonight' exclusive!
This motherfucker is
off the charts.
You realize he could
buy the network.
Yeah, why would he?
The son-of-a-bitch pulls in ...
650 millions pay-per-views
for one single broadcast.
Going live in ...
5 ... 4 ... 3 ... 2 ... 1 ...
First, there was "Society".
The ultimate SIM environment,
where players don't control ...
virtual animated characters,
but actual,
living, breathing, human beings.
They walked them. They talked them.
They juiced them. They rocked them.
Rickity-dickity-doo.
We had that on T-shirts
back in 2010.
The creation of reclusive genius
Ken Castle ...
"Who is Ken Castle?"
"Society" took the world by storm,
becoming the #1 guilty pleasure
of billions.
You can get paid to be controlled,
or you can pay to control.
And generating one of the
world's largest private fortunes,
surpassing Bill Gates
practically, over night.
Nine months ago,
Castle availed a new simulation.
One that would take gaming to
new heights of thrilling excess ...
and controversy.
SLAYERS
Slayers.
If "Society" let us
live through others,
"Slayers" would let us
die through others.
Slayers gives the gamer full control
of a flesh & blood human being,
in full scale kill or be killed combat.
And when we say "flesh and blood" ...
we mean, flesh ...
and blood.
Slayers.
Slayers!
Why isn't it murder?
Gina, when was the last time you saw
somebody volunteer to be murdered?
I'm sure you know that every last one
of our Slayers is a bonified death row inmate.
Each one offered the chance to participate
as an alternative to their sentence.
You stay alive for 30 sessions,
you get set free.
That's not a bad goddamn deal.
And has any of these men or women have
actually survived long enough to be set free?
Well I'd remind the audience that Slayers
was put together with a full cooperation ...
and approval, of the United States
Federal government.
That the revenue that produces ...
is responsible for funding
our entire prison system ...
keeping the bad guys
behind bars.
And that the Prop. (Proposition) was voted
for by a cock-solid 68% of the American public.
In an election tainted by
a suspected digital fraud.
Let's talk about the
so called "Genericons" ...
sent into the Slayers' environment,
With a set of pre-programmed actions,
with no one controlling them,
and no way to react.
Their chances of survival are next to nil.
There's plenty of men and women in prison
who can never cut it as Slayers.
Shouldn't they be given the same chance
to roll the dice for a ticket out?
Besides they only need to survive
one session.
Right.
So Mr. Castle,
how the hell does it work?
It begins with a single nano cell
planted in the motor cortex of the brain.
This cell can replicate,
replacing the cells around it
with perfect copies.
And these copied cells contain
remote access functionality.
Therefore nano plus cortex,
equals a "nanex".
Isn't it true, that every human
that undergoes this procedure,
will have a distinct "IP" address,
like a mobile device ...
or a notebook computer?
- Similar, yeah.
But control is strictly localized ...
to the parameters of
our gaming environment.
You take "Society" for instance.
Once a cast member has left the workplace
they're completely free ...
from the control and
monitoring of their player.
Oh well, that's a relief!
For some, maybe.
For some ...
Don't you suspect a good many folks
wouldn't mind or need a bit of controlling?
Someone else making
all the decisions for you?
No tough choices?
No responsibilities?
- Think about it.
- We will, Mr. Castle.
We will!
The Gina Parker Smith Show!
Sponsored by ...
SLAYERS
Good little talk?
Oh, shit!
My pleasure!
Can I just tell you, I cannot wait
until the next Slayers,
I mean, Kable has been unbelievable!
His arms are just so ...
well I know they're terrible!
What the hell was that?
Ken Castle wants you to believe that
we are living in a better, safer world.
- His a liar! Mind controlling his Slayers ...
- Mr. Castle, we have no idea where this is ...
We will all be his dogs if we allowed
this evolution to continue.
That's a goddamn hoot!
This is nuts, it's like the signal is generating
simultaneously from six countries.
Bypass overload. Reroute to
the backup servers please, now.
Now!
Uh, Mr. Castle, we can't stop every
virus that sneaks in.
You might want to let my home boys
take a look at your firewall.
We're on it. They'll be off
the air momentarily.
So sorry.
What about you, sugar?
I wonder if I might breach your
firewall one of these days?
You're bad!
He's good!
Hit him!
Fuck him up!
Get down!
Get the fuck down!
Get down! Get down!
Kable!
My name is Tillman.
Yeah, yeah. Tillsman, Tillsman.
They said your name was Tillsman.
You're just sitting, eh?.
Sitting and looking, just looking
and sitting ... Just like me, man.
Keeping my wholes down,
you gotta keep your whole's down ...
Everyday I do it, and then
everybody snaps, breaks ...
starts to crack up, you know,
because you don't know if
you're going to live
a day or two or die.
Anybody but you, right?
27 battles, huh? Three to go ...
Nobody has ever done it.
No man has ever come that close.
No one has even got 10 games
without getting their brain shot ...
Everybody but Kable. Kable, because
he's sitting and looking, huh man?
You're gotta plan in your head.
You got a mission.
You never break.
You never snap.
You never say shit either, but you
take care of your business, don't you?
Niggers can get spooked by that kind of
single mindness, you know what I mean?
Cause you're spooky.
You spook me.
Whatcha in for?
You want to get back to them.
It's all you think about.
It's the only thing that keeps you alive.
Who's talking?
Sign it.
What?
Sign it. Please Tillman.
My son David is your biggest fan.
He prays for you.
I need to prove it's authentic.
Makes it worth more.
Why would anyone want my name?
You don't even know what's
going on out there, do you?
All medical personal
report to central process.
Damn, gotta go.
No, no! Wait.
How did you get this picture?
Have you seen them?
♪ Sweat baby sweat baby
sex is a Texas drought ♪
♪ Me and you do the kind of stuff
only Prince would sing about ♪
♪ So put your hands down my pants
and I bet you'll feel nuts ♪
♪ Yes I'm Siskel, yes I'm Ebert ♪
♪ and you're getting two thumbs up ♪
♪ Come quicker than FedEx never reach an apex,
just like Coca-Cola stock you are inclined ♪
♪ to make me rise an hour early ♪
♪ just like Daylight Savings Time ♪
♪ You and me baby
ain't nothin' but mammals ♪
♪ So let's do it like they do on the
Discovery Channel. Do it again now ♪
♪ You and me baby ain't nothin'
but mammals, so let's do it ♪
♪ like they do on the Discovery Channel.
Gettin' horny now ♪
Hey.
Hi.
- Hi.
So what's your damage?
You know, just hanging out.
Just looking to meet people.
... meet people.
Lucky you. You met me.
- I'm Nika.
- I'm Dale. I like your fur.
- Do you wanna go somewhere?
We are somewhere.
Ken Castle ... is a liar.
Liar!
Fuck!
A new video prank by
the subversive group "Humanz" ...
caused a nation wide
stir today.
All contact between "Society" city, and
an estimated 3 quarters of a million players
were shut down for 3 hours
while Castle technicians
worked to remove what they described
as a "satellite infection" ...
These pranks, at first,
attributed to rogue isolated hackers
are now suspected to be the work of
an elaborate and sophisticated,
network of programming cells,
spread around several countries.
Experts estimate
that the service interruption
will end up costing Castle
billions in lost revenue.
Well don't cry for Castle,
he can cover this with
change in his couch cushions.
On a personal note,
that shit was fucked up.
Yeah it was.
I literally pissed myself.
Sounds like fun.
Seriously, these Humanz cock suckers,
they're are out of control.
- Sandra.
- Quiet.
- My name is Sandra.
- Stop talking.
They can't say I didn't try ...
Fuck yeah!
We're all going to die!
Oh God!
Let me out of here!
I'm not supposed to be here!
Who are they?
Who the fuck are they?
Who the fuck is playing us, man?
Shut up, fish.
Gay, gay, gay, tardily gay.
- Swarmers.
The latest innovation
from Browning,
this self detonating cartridge ...
offers the widest
and deadliest spray available ...
from a full tracking,
cornering coordinates.
- Daddy like it.
- Simon!
Fan girl, stop hacking me.
You suck Simon. You're going to get
my boyfriend killed ...
before he can get out of jail and before
he can fill me up with his hot seed!
Simon!
I just wanna play you.
- Forget about that star fucker.
- Shut up bitch!
So when am I going to get to meet you,
for like, real?
What's that?
What's up looser?
Mum says: Go to college,
move the fuck out, and ...
And, oh yeah! You're a sick retard!
You're pathetic.
You smell like Jeffrey Dahmer.
- Wanna make out?
- You wish.
I can't wait until they
cut you out, Simian.
Your balls bitch.
- Simon?
- Maybe.
Oh my God! Is really you!
- Nice.
- Do you want to see our tits, Simon?
Yes, yes I do.
Now that we have your attention, here's
an offer that you can't refuse.
- Here we go.
- 50 million euros ...
for control of Kable.
instant transfer to the account
of your choice.
Kable is not for sale,
thank you.
Baby, make it a hundred ...
It's been real!
What the fuck?
If you want to talk to Kable,
we can show you how.
Look at it.
The new face of Slayers.
Pure, crystalized horror,
two stories high and
bathed in bloody red.
He is what they want.
They love Kable.
They do now,
but when they watch their hero die
right in front of their eye balls ...
so sharp and vivid ...
if feels like it could've reach out
and touch the wet flesh.
They're going to change their point of
view and be seduced by the power ...
.. the violence, the dominance.
It's human nature.
Kable's made it through 28 battles.
Every player in the game
is trying to take him out.
Yeah, Kable is a perfect soldier,
He's a tactical killing computer.
His only vulnerability is
the nanex itself. The ...
delay between Simon's commands
and Kable's ability to execute.
So why should this one
be any different?
Who controls him?
No one.
Get it out of me!
What the hell happened
to this one?
Looks like he escaped.
Hi girls. Back to your Jazz-ercise.
That's Hackman,
Hackman, Hackman, knack man.
They say he killed a
whole bunch of people, man.
Killed himself all kinds of people.
And then one day, he just walks up
and turns himself in ...
like he wants to be inside
or some crazy shit like that.
You know what I'm saying?
So it's going to be all
kinds of Slayers, man.
As long as you got motherfuckers like
that running around killing ...
Kable! Let's go!
Upgrades, come on.
Why don't you upgrade
a brother man?
Why don't you shut the fuck up?!
Shut the fuck up. Shut the fuck up.
Fucking, shut the fuck up.
- Who wimps?
- What?
Who wimps,
The player or the slayer?
I am the hand.
Someone, somewhere else is the eye.
It's tripped out, man.
Sometimes, they take over ...
completely, they ...
move you around like a robot.
- But that don't work so good.
- Why?
The delay.
Yeah the ping.
They talk about that.
About how long it takes the
Slayer to respond to the command.
Whatever they call it,
the slice of a second out there, is the
difference between living and dying.
When that trigger pulls ...
.. it's just me.
Hey, Kable.
Look.
I just killed someone.
This is the blood.
Look.
He's back here.
Wanna see?
You know your head ain't on straight.
I'm going to kill you too,
on Sunday.
Yeah, probably.
That's why they put me here.
I got no strings.
I got no strings,
so I have fun.
I'm not tied up to anyone.
They got strings,
but you can see,
there are no strings on me.
You go two whores, Kable.
- What the fuck did you say?
- On the outside.
I'm sorry,
I meant your pretty girls.
So you want to get back to them.
But I'm going to visit them first.
Alright.
Kable.
Kable, dude. It's me.
It's me.
Who?
Simon, I'm playing you.
- How come I can hear you?
- Well, it's a mod.
Gamers can't talk to cons.
I know.
It's fucking unbelievable.
This is amazing.
Cool yeah?
No it's not cool.
Pay attention to the fucking game!
Okay, okay.
I got it, I got it.
What are you, 12?
I'm 17 actually,
thank you.
This is unbelievable.
How am I not dead yet?
Cause I'm a badass,
motherfucker.
Shit!
Freak, you shouldn't be here.
- Gibs.
- What?
Like giblets - Kibbles and Bits -
Chunks - Pieces everywhere.
These are real humans fucker.
Death row, psychos ...  so what?
They had it coming anyway, right?
I guess that goes for me too.
Yeah, but you're different.
Different, how?
I don't know, because
you're my psych.
Damn new area.
Think about it Kable, all the shit
we've been through together,
what an epic run, man.
It's gonna suck to see it end.
Are you fucking kidding me?
Oh yeah,
I get that for you it's different.
This way.
- There's nothing there.
- Trust me, kid.
It's restricted area. It's beyond
the borders of the game
I couldn't put you there if I tried.
Warning.
Access denied.
Shit.
Bye, Kable.
Come on.
This kid's going to get me killed.
Dude I'm right here, man.
I can hear you.
Listen to me.
I don't know who's behind it or why,
but I was supposed to die tonight.
Lucky for us,
I can beat them ...
but not with you controlling me.
What the hell are you talking about?
Turn me lose, kid.
You want to win? Turn me lose.
Find a way.
Bastard.
So Ms. Roth. Says here you're
applying for custody of your daughter?
Delia, her name is Delia.
Spouse incarcerated. Life,
without the possibility of parole.
- You use your maiden name?
- Uh-huh.
My husband ... he's ...
it's not entirely true
regarding his sentence.
In fact,
he's due to be released soon.
Ms. Roth,
your husband was charged and con ...
He was charged and convicted
of first degree murder.
I can't hardly consider his release,
if it were to happen at all ...
I don't think it would be a good thing.
So it's says you're an actor?
I don't know that I've
seen you in anything.
I work in "Society".
It's a job.
Ms. Roth, your child has been
exceedingly well placed.
The new family is very wealthy,
She will never want for anything.
Now I can understand that
you love your daughter.
Probably very much. But do you really
think she would be better off ...
with ...
people like you?
Yes, I do.
I'm her mother.
We will give your application on
the consideration of merits.
Do you like the software?
Software?
The walkie-talkie, player.
No shit.
You're the guy from the TV,
the Humanz.
That's right, baby.
You think about
what the brother said?
To what brother do you refer,
brother?
Kable wants the freedom to ass kick.
Do shit his way.
- Are you going to give it to him?
- You were listening?
We see and hear everything ...
everything that goes on inside
that so called game.
Alright then,
Kable said we got lucky ...
They were gunning for us.
What's that all about?
Kable got a past,
he knows things.
Things you don't even know.
- What things?
- Things that Castle is afraid of.
As long as your boy stays on the inside,
Castle knows he can keep him quiet.
But if he ever got out ... Castle
would never let that happen.
There's one battle left,
I think I can handle my own business,
thank you very much.
You're not hearing me.
This is not something you can control.
They're gonna kill his ass, Simon.
In the eyes of the world,
and then what?
You're just another poor
little rich honky.
No cable, no pussy, no shit.
Look man, this ... this is too heavy.
I don't even know what the hell
are you talking about.
- I just play games, man. Games.
- That's right.
It is a game.
You want to win, don't you?
Yeah, I intend to.
Then you need to cut your
strings puppet master.
Imagine a slayer that don't got
to wait to be told what to do.
No ping, you dig?
That would be cheating.
A mod.
That's all it would be.
You know why?
Because the game's got to evolve.
- You feel me?
- I do.
I do feel you my, giant brother.
Well then, let's rock baby.
Tillman ... he knows you talked to him.
Your player.
Who are you?
A friend.
I don't have any.
Listen to me.
Simon is going to give you what
you want. What you asked him for.
How do you know that?
I know something else.
Whether or not he's controlling you,
you will never reach the save point.
Castle won't allow it.
We'll see.
No, you have to escape.
Your wife and your
daughter need you, Tillman.
If you want to get out and see
the people in the picture ...
you will have to find another way.
I need you to get me something.
What? Tell me.
Drunk.
What have you got there?
Kable, what the hell is that?
Put it down.
Put it down!
Fuck face!
Throw the bottle in the trash!
Oh, I see it was a great idea
turning you loose.
- What happened?
- You happened!
You wanted control,
you got it.
What's the matter with you, Kable?
Kill something!
This is unbelievable.
Kable, listen.
This is the last game ...
you're going to end up dead and I'm
going to look like a total asshole ...
if you don't pull
your balls together, man!
Damn it!
Kable, what the hell are you doing?
Aw, what the hell?
That's just gross, bro.
Go, go, go, go!
I'm not your fucking cheerleader!
Motherfucker!
Kable, please, please,
I beg you, get back in the game.
You're screwing my ass, Kable.
This is a restricted area.
Return to the battle zone.
RESTRICTED
I'm dead.
♪ Sweet dreams are made of these ♪
♪ Who am I to disagree? ♪
♪ Travel the world and the seven seas ♪
♪ Everybody's looking for something ♪
♪ Some of them want to use you ♪
♪ Some of them want to get used by you ♪
♪ Some of them want to abuse you ♪
♪ Some of them want to be abused ♪
What the fuck just happened?
Initial reports are that Kable,
the most recognizable face
of the Slayers phenomenon ...
next to Ken Castle himself,
is officially listed as fragged.
Just one session away from being
the first Slayer ever ...
to win a full pardon and release.
And in NetCast, fledged by technical
difficulties and dead spots,
the report could not be confirmed,
however Kable, born
John Tillman of Albany, New York ...
and convicted of murder
just 4 years ago,
has been removed from Slayers
rosters and upcoming events listings.
His player, gaming mega star,
Simon Silverton,
could not be reached for comment.
Do you have a question?
Tillman left a wife
on the outside, right?
- Tillman, yeah.
- Find her.
Blink, activated.
She's not home.
But Castle's personal security will be,
soon enough and trust me ...
- You don't want to meet them.
- Who are you?
You asked me that once before.
- Your voice.
- You know, you should really come with me.
Like now!
See that's why you're a fool!
That's what I'm talking about!
Could you stop it with that
freaking awful bullshit?
Come one man, that's why
it's a game of deception, man!
That's bullshit, man!
You know that's bullshit!
So you're the ones who broke me out?
- We only freed your mind.
- And your ass followed.
Holly shit ...
You made it!
You're really here.
Kable. You're great.
- You got questions.
- A few.
So she took my blood.
Why?
The nanex.
It modifies the actual cell
structure of your brain.
We can crack it, but it's not one size
fits all. We need your DNA ...
so that we can generate custom code.
Alright, then why me?
Because Castle is afraid of you man.
It ain't just a game, Tillman. Every
day there's more people stepping forward.
Want to be a part of Castle's world, throwing
away everything that means to be human.
Right now is the desperate ones.
Convicts, addicts, the sick, the poor.
The ones that fell through the cracks.
The federal prison system
is growing out of control.
Set to bankrupt the whole damn USA,
then Castle rides in on a white horse.
Says he has a plan to bail us all out
and we just fall in line?
The healthcare system is collapsing.
And this time he's pushing for
total control over genetic diseases.
Birth defect is no longer an issue.
All we have to do is exchange our cells
for the ones he wants to give us.
Promise of a longer life
and a fatter wallet ...
- Do you think people will refuse?
- Fuck no.
Then the next thing you know ...
we're all slaves.
I can't help you.
Tillman.
We know where she is.
Hi, Nika.
- Oh hi. Rick Rape, right?
- Rick Rape, right?
I thought you weren't allowed
to come here anymore.
That was last month.
I was a bad boy.
Are you still a bad boy?
- Please, don't kill me.
No.
- I'll do anything.
- Don't say that.
Stop!
Goddamn it.
You, in there controlling ...
Let her talk!
I can't she has to say what I tell her.
You can hear me.
I know you can.
I love you.
I love you too.
Shut up!
Don't say anything else.
I'm going to find you ...
and I'm going to rip you to fucking
pieces, do you understand me?
I'm getting you out of here.
I'm going to take you to some place
where you can turn it off, the program.
Hi Kable.
Look at me bitch!
Anybody in there?
Go on.
Do it.
What the fuck do we do?
I can get you out of here.
Oh shit!
I can't believe it's you!
This is ... listen, Tillman,
you can trust me, I swear.
If not ...
you're dead!
Okay.
Faster! Faster!
I guess you remember that day, huh?
You just gotten Kable through his
10th consecutive session alive.
No one ever thought an icon
could last that long.
Pretty hot shit, aren't you?
Kid player.
Good times.
Sure, on the outside.
Now look at these.
That's what it's like on the inside.
Wonder how long you would last
on the other side of the screen?
You know, Simon ...
you being held here today ...
suspected of aiding an escape
of a convicted murder ...
from a maximum security penitentiary.
The charges are beyond serious.
Your hard drives have been seized.
Forensics are depicting the content
as we speak.
Your internet activity over
the last 10 years,
is being scrutinized and cataloged.
In minute ...
vivid detail.
In addition, your father's bank
accounts have been frozen,
pending further investigation.
After all, it was essentially his money
that funded Mr. Tillman's escape.
Now I need you to tell me ...
everything that happened leading
up to yesterday afternoon.
Anybody you talked to, everything
you saw, everything you did.
And I need you to tell me that
right now.
Yeah, huh ...
I'm going to need something too.
Oh really?
And what might that be?
Could you guys do a sandwich like ...
peanut butter,
or almond butter, walnut butter ...
huh, pecan butter, pistachio butter ...
pretty much any kind of ...
you know, nut butter
with some grape jelly.
Pistachio butter.
- They make that?
- It's awesome.
Now what?
Now we just put the DNA into the suit,
light it up, extract it ...
a few modifying sequences
into the code and ...
we're good to go.
- It's an anti-spyware program.
- Basically.
We can't quarantine the foreign
cells per say, but ...
we can disable their ability
to transmit and receive.
Fuck that.
I'll make you cut it out me.
That would be like cutting out
a part of your brain.
The nanex cells replace the cells,
they replicate.
They become you.
We're going to have to keep her
sedated until we kill the link.
Otherwise she will be broadcasting
everything she sees and hears,
30 minutes.
You give us a robot ...
we give you back a super hot female.
Tillman!
We need to talk.
- So talk.
- Come on.
They tested it on soldiers.
The first volunteer was
a Corporal Travis Scotch.
A friend of yours, I believe.
And the second was you.
The idea was to replace your brain,
bit by bit, cell by cell.
The new tissue would never
break down, never deteriorate.
A new era in human longevity,
that's what they told us.
9 weeks later Scotch was dead ...
and you were serving life in maximum.
Castle's project was shut down.
But the same technology
resurfaced within a year ...
in a game.
Castle called it "Society".
Tillman, listen man, whatever
happened in that project, is
something Castle wanted buried.
We need that shit man.
What you saw, what you know.
I don't know what to tell you.
You gotta tell me shit.
I want you to show me.
Okay, we're ready to rock.
Let's break the link in ...
3 ... 2 ... 1.
Who's there?
What are you doing here?
- Who are you?
- Tech support.
- What are we looking at?
- His memories.
Translated into raw audio-visual data.
I read something about this.
But that tech is not supposed to be
available for another decade.
They'll have better shit than
this in Best Buy in 18 months.
Oh, son of a bitch!
John Tillman.
Man I never thought I would be so
happy to see your ugly face.
Scotch.
Is it me or is this place fucked?
They got me hooked up to
computers 5 hours a day.
Feed me vitamins, and pills,
and god knows what ...
giving me injections,
taking and giving me blood ...
These nurses are whipping my ass ...
and they're male nurses too, bro!
I can't believe I let you
talk me in to this.
And I'm having these, like, blackouts ...
and it's scaring the shit out of me.
I don't even know
how long I've been here ...
Hey man ...
Are they letting you out already,
you son of a bitch?
I'm not getting out.
Okay.
Johnny ...
Are you good?
I'm fine.
Man you don't look fine.
I'm sorry.
Yeah that's okay.
It's not like you ever looked that
good in the first place.
What's the gun for, John?
What's happening?
Really you're scaring me man.
What's the gun for?
I can't st ...
I can't stop.
Stop what?
What did they do to you man?
John, stop it! You're scaring me now.
Stop it.
Sorry Scotch, I ...
John, no! Don't!
Stop!
Not the best commercial for Ken Castle.
He made him do it.
- Castle made him do it.
- It was a test.
Cha-ching.
Excuse me, media whore.
This isn't just a story.
The whole world
is splitting down the middle.
Sooner or later, everyone
is going to have to take a side,
even scavengers like you!
It's you.
I missed you, so much!
You are the reason I held on.
- I love you.
- Where's our daughter?
I couldn't stop them. I'm sorry.
Nobody could.
The foster parents paid good money
to remain anonymous.
But there's always a data trail
if you know where to look.
Where is she?
I'm sorry, Tillman.
She's with Castle.
Tillman!
That's all the story
you're going to get.
Silverton, get up.
What's going on man?
Looks like someone up the chain
has decided you're no longer a threat.
CHEATER
FUCK YOU CHEATER!
NANEX
ACCESS DENIED
We'll find him.
Don't worry.
He'll come to us.
- Not bad for a video, huh?
- What?
The latest and greatest, I defy you
to tell it from real life ...
could you imagine porn on this thing?
♪ I've got you under my skin ♪
♪ I've got you deep
in the heart of me ♪
♪ So deep in my heart ♪
♪ that you're almost a part of me ♪
♪ I've got you under my skin ♪
♪ I'd tried so not to give in ♪
♪ I said to myself:
this affair never will go so well ♪
♪ But why should I try to resist
when, baby, I know so well ♪
♪ I've got you ♪
♪ under my skin ♪
♪ I'd sacrifice anything come what might ♪
♪ For the sake of having you near ♪
♪ In spite of that crazy warning
voice that comes in the night ♪
♪ And says these words in my ear ♪
♪ Don't you know, little
fool, that you ain't never gonna win? ♪
♪ Use your mentality,
where is your reality ♪
♪ But each time that I do
just the thought of you ♪
♪ Makes me stop before I begin ♪
♪ 'Cause I've got you ♪
♪ under my skin. ♪
You're awesome!
Castle.
Kable.
I don't care about you.
You just want your little
sugar pie, I know.
So don't do anything stupid.
My house, my rules.
Come on,
I want to show you something.
I wanted to thank you for
leading me to them,
the Humanz's cell, that is.
Of course sooner or later
they'd be whistling my tune ...
just like everybody else, but ...
in the meantime, there's that little cracker
program they dreamed up that got my attention.
That was a genuine nuisance.
No doubt about it.
One thing even they didn't know, though:
I'm wired too.
I replaced 98% of my own noodle
with nano-tissue years ago.
But mine's different.
It's built to send,
to transmit,
whereas every other nano-cell
that I've put out there,
including the ones
in your head Kable,
are designed to receive.
I think it, you do it.
We're talking every Slayer,
everyone in Society city.
I believe your better half would
fall under that category,
provided they were within
range of my transmitters.
Very nice, Castle. So you got
an army of psychotics ...
and deviants to dance around for you?
You're thinking small, Kable.
But not as small as me.
See, nano-cells are real small.
A thousand times smaller than
these dust particulars.
You inhale it. They go to work;
replicating, spreading ...
like a virus, multiplying
in exponentials.
Six months time, I can have a
hundred million people converted.
Ditch diggers, porn stars,
and Presidents.
Not one would be the wiser.
A hundred million people who buy
what I want them to buy,
and vote how I want them to vote,
do pretty much damn well anything
I figure they ought to do.
For instance ...
You should have let him
fight for himself.
Maybe you would've had a shot.
- I think you're missing the point, my man.
- No, no, I get it.
You're pulling all the strings
around here.
Which makes my next move pretty ...
Neglected to mention
my smart boys reversed ...
that crack the Humanz worked for you.
Easy-breezy once
I had access to their drives.
You're mine boy.
Come on, let's boogie-woogie
rock & roll.
I think that badass Slayer of the game
don't seem like much, does he?
Lucky shot.
Not really.
I need an audience boys ...
No, no, no, you crawl ...
on your belly like a toad.
Is this bad?
I'm really bad.
That's sweet.
Alright boys are you ready?
It's time for a true test.
Just like last time, remember?
Yeah, you're stronger now,
a little more fight in you ...
but I think the end result
will be just about the same.
What the hell was that?
Someone from the outside
is sending him commands ...
We're being broadcast live.
Jam the signal!
Goddamn retards!
We're working on it ...
I think it,
You ... fucking ... do it ...
Look at this knife ...
imagine me sticking it into your gut.
Think about it ...
make it real!
Yes!
- Are you okay?
- Are you my daddy, Tillman?
I'm your daddy.
Wait.
- Shut it off.
- Pardon?
The nanex.
It means nothing to you.
It's just a mouse click.
Set us free.
Well played, Kable.