Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org
George, George,
George of the Jungle
Strong as he can be
Watch out for that tree
George, George,
George of the Jungle
Lives a life that's free
Watch out for that tree
When he gets in a scrape
He makes his escape with help
from his friend an ape named Ape
And his elephant Shep
can fetch a log
He's man's best friend
is George's dog
He's George, George,
George of the Jungle
Swing from tree to tree
Watch out for that tree
George, George,
George of the Jungle
Lives a life that's free
Watch out for that tree
Now George was a king
and a daddy too
There's just too much
for poor George to do
Though George loved Ursula
with all his heart
Her momma's evil plots
broke them apart
There was lying and thieving
and stealing and cheating
But their true love
just can't be beaten
So find his kisskin unhypnotised
Now George is the king from 9-5
George, George,
George of the Jungle
Friend to you and me
Watch out for that tree
Hear him holler, swing and sing
All the animals come
to the jungle king
So grab a vine and swing in time
If you smack a tree just pay no mind
Like George, George,
George of the Jungle
George, George,
Strong as he can be
Watch out for that tree
Watch out for that... tree
George, George,
George of the Jungle
Watch out for that tree
The jungle to the untrained eye
looks the same as in our first movie,
but things have changed,
and it's not just because
we're using a different set,
domestic bliss
has broken out over the Bukuvu,
parenthood has found
that defender of the innocent,
and all-around good guy,
George of the Jungle.
George, George,
George of the Jungle
Watch out for that tree
And as our story begins,
our popular potent potentate
has produced a prince.
Huh? Wait a minute!
Who the heck are you?!
Me, new George. Studio too cheap
to pay Brendan Fraser.
- Let's go, Dad.
- How did you get the part?
- New George just lucky, I guess.
- Hey, dad, check it out.
Let's play fetch with Shep.
- Shep!
Here we go, boy. Fetch!
Fetch stick, Shep.
Come on, Shep.
Now that the prince is turning five,
George is grooming his son
to be the heir to the throne.
George, that's grooming him
to be heir, not grooming his hair.
- Oh.
- Oh, yeah.
While George was preparing his son,
Ursula the love of his life,
and the heiress who gave up
everything to be his jungle queen,
was wondering why
George wasn't home for lunch.
Why isn't George home for lunch?
But George
couldn't go home for lunch
because he had to attend
to a very important matter.
George pretty good at coconut ball.
OK.
Hit me!
But suddenly the game was
interrupted by an urgent bongo gram.
I said, an urgent bongo gram.
George really late for lunch.
George, George,
George of the Jungle
Strong as he can be
Watch out for that... tree
Sorry George late, but George had
important royal duty to attend to.
In other words,
you were playing coconut ball.
George score winning goal.
Ursula come
and try out for cheerleader?
I tried, but the gorillas turned me
down because I wasn't pretty enough.
- You look pretty to me.
- You should tell the gorillas.
George promise tonight
spend whole night with Ursula. OK?
OK.
Can George give Junior
vine swinging lesson?
Vine swinging's a little dangerous.
- Must be from your side of family.
- Vine surfing is much cooler.
What dangerous about swinging?
Swinging fun.
- George show you.
- Maybe that's not such a good idea.
Why? Lt easy.
George, watch out for that...
For the first time in history,
George didn't hit the tree
he was aiming at,
but that didn't stop him
from hitting... the second tree.
And, in case you were worried,
the new George takes a tree
as well as Brendan Fraser.
While George
was sliding down the tree,
Ape has been in Las Vegas
becoming a different sort of swinger.
But while pursuing
his singing career,
the lure of the cards has proven too
much for our travelling troubadour.
You got to learn to play it right
You got to know when to hold 'em
Know when to fold 'em
If you wouldn't mind,
could you stop singing?
Sorry.
Cut the cards.
Welcome to Las Vegas, baby.
And they say humans
are more evolved.
Meanwhile, back in the jungle,
George was taking care
of some serious jungle business.
George, the sink's stuffed again.
Well, kind of serious.
Don't worry, George fix.
OK.
George, you better answer the bird.
Hello.
Animals in big fight.
George know he promise Ursula
he see her tonight,
OK if George go to help animals?
If George can come home early, would
Ursula still go out with George?
George, George,
George of the Jungle
Watch out for that...
Stop the movie!
That's how animals usually sound,
right?
In our movie the animals
are all going to talk,
- so you humans don't miss a thing.
- Where's your team now?
Anyone know how to fix sink?
For the convenience of you animals
we've added subtitles,
so you can follow along too.
This is all their fault.
The birds keep dropping
their zug-zug on us.
Incoming.
It's disgusting! I gotta wear a hat!
Why not make zug-zug treaty?
Zug-zug treaty?
Yes, zug-zug treaty.
This is Disney,
if we're gonna do a zug-zug joke,
we're gonna make it educational.
We make treaty and get everyone
to go zug-zug in separate areas.
- That's a good idea.
- Now you can play coconut ball.
- George can't stay.
- And why not, George?
Have evening planned with Ursula.
When lions ruled the jungle,
we never neglected our subjects,
why are you neglecting us?
- George in love.
- You've gotta be kidding me.
Get outta here.
Run home to your family.
Never trust anyone without fangs.
George didn't impress
his bachelor pals,
but he did manage
to impress his wife.
George lucky man.
He's got Ursula and Junior...
...and really strong head.
Honey, I wouldn't worry
about Junior swinging.
He's the son of the greatest swinger
of all time,
how could he not learn how to swing?
That make George happy.
Sorry about sink.
It's not your fault,
it's just the way
things are sometimes.
Sure Ursula like being here
with George?
How can you say that?
Then Ursula think things be OK,
right?
Cos George rather not be king
than lose Ursula.
Oh, don't be silly,
everything's fine.
George hope so, cos he love Ursula
more than there are stars in sky.
And George have special surprise
to cheer Ursula up.
Ursula, dance with George.
Like a simple question
looking for an answer
Now I am, now I am,
listening to some inner call
Swimming blindly to pull
myself upon your shore
What if I don't find you
when I have landed?
Would you leave me here to die
on your shores flat dead?
I think I know why the dog
howls at the moon
I said
When I'm with you...
George and Ursula were in love.
Little did they know that someone
was approaching,
who was going to change their lives
for ever,
someone so malevolent,
so Machiavellian, so...
Well, for you kids, let's just say
really, really mean.
Stay still, I don't want to fall off.
Yes, it was Beatrice Stanhope,
Ursula's mother.
Hello.
It's the man who would be
your son-in-law.
Yes, that's Ursula's foppish
former fiancé, Lyle Van de Groot.
You remember the graceful
Van de Groot from the first movie.
Was it really necessary
to show that scene?
Lt seems the vengeful,
venal Van de Groot
had bought the casino
Ape was gambling in.
Lyle had finally come up
with the perfect plan
to destroy George by stealing
the deed to Ape Mountain.
Are you sure Ape has the deed?
Lt is, after all,
called Ape Mountain.
And as soon as I have cheated
the ape out of the deed,
and driven that half-wit George
off of his land, bulldozers roll,
driving Ursula right back
into my waiting arms.
When they see my gifts,
they'll miss civilisation so much
they'll beg me to take them back.
I've gotta go. What did he say?
He said hold on. I'm going to...
Oh, I've had it!
Are you sure
we're going in the right direction?
Why, yes.
We remember from the first movie.
It's very important
I get to Ape Mountain today.
It's my grandson's fifth birthday.
I'm taking him and Ursula
back to civilisation.
What did he say?
He was admiring your luggage.
Oh, well, whatever.
And he wondered why you want to
take your grandson out of the jungle.
I'm not having him grow up here
an illiterate savage.
Someone help! Put me down! Help!
Sorry, we can't kill Beatrice.
If she dies, we have no story.
And if we have no story, George
couldn't disappoint his wife again
by being late
for his own son's birthday party.
I wonder what's keeping your father.
Guess we may as well get started.
Now remember, sweetie,
you can wish for anything you want.
Except your grandmother,
because she's already here.
Grandma!
- Mother!
- Darling.
Hello, Junior.
Well, where's that husband of yours?
Shouldn't he be
at his own son's birthday party?
He's running late.
How could he possibly
be running late? This is the jungle.
Traffic back up
on the Bukuvu Expressway?
Dad!
George sorry he's late, but zug-zug
treaty broke down and had to step in.
Hello, old Mrs Ursula.
Beatrice cunningly connived to tempt
Ursula and Junior back home
using a ploy that has worked
since the beginning of time.
I have gifts for you.
Mother, you shouldn't have.
George also make present.
Cool! Thanks, Dad.
Whoa! Cool, a spear!
- That's nice.
- Yeah.
How'd you like to play with this?
Wow!
You just flip the switch
and it can do anything you want.
That not look so hard.
Beatrice put in motion
her gift-giving gambit
to get Ursula to come home.
Meanwhile, George demonstrated
why he was no William Tell.
- And neither was his aimless son.
- Stay there. OK. Good. OK.
OK, aim. Good.
See gorilla? OK.
Now throw. Throw.
Throw!
Good.
Huh?
But a coconut wasn't enough to
nullify the muddled mind of our hero,
George continued to be torn by the
conflict between home and throne.
Come on, George. Ya have to
supervise the oo-oo feather picking.
Sorry, George can't.
Promise Ursula he stay home.
But no king has ever missed
oo-oo feather picking.
At least not when lions ruled.
Face it.
He doesn't care about us anymore.
- George.
- Old Mrs Ursula.
Come talk.
George,
do you love your wife and your son?
George love Ursula and Junior
very much.
And George sorry George late
for Junior's birthday party.
I understand perfectly.
You don't have enough time
for your subjects or family
Which is why you can see how much
happier Ursula and Junior would be
if they came back to San Francisco.
Ursula's lonely.
She misses her friends and
someplace to wear lovely dresses.
Junior needs to live in civilisation
and go to school with other children.
What do you think George should do?
George should let them go.
As much as she tried to resist,
the once opulent Ursula was tempted
by the bangles and baubles.
Feeling dazed and confused,
or more dazed and confused
than normal,
George sought professional help.
George know Tookie trying,
but need talk to brother Ape.
Maybe Tookie fly to get brother Ape?
Then George just talk more.
While Tookie was winging his way
to Las Vegas, he...
I said Las Vegas!
Ape found himself
with problems of his own.
If you're gonna play the game, boy
You got to learn to play it right
You got to know when to hold 'em
Know when to fold...
I've had more pleasure
listening to alligators sing
than you, ya stupid bum!
While Ape was busy strangling
his pestering poker partner,
Tookie's tuckered mind
began to wander.
Another mimosa, Mr Tookie-Tookie?
Oh, Tookie, you cad.
As our jungle jet-setter
flew to visit his primate pal,
Ursula confronted Beatrice
for befuddling her handsome hubby.
Mother. I'd appreciate it if you
wouldn't play with George's mind.
Well, there really isn't much
to play with, but alright.
Ursula, I know you're unhappy here.
You can't fool your mother.
I'll admit there are certain things
I miss about home,
but I love George
and I am staying here.
So deal with it. OK?
- Hello.
- Ursula's definitely weakening.
If I can just get her back
to civilisation and to you -
That is, if you've got your obsession
with her under control?
Of course I have it under control.
Obsession... a strong word.
Have you got the deed from Ape yet?
No, but I'll have it tonight.
And when I do, bulldozers will roll.
Roll! I have a foolproof plan.
He did. Because in a demonstration
of despicable dishonesty,
Lyle had entered the poker game.
See if you can figure out
which one he is.
You foolish fowl.
What are you doing here?
George is suffering
deep psychological damage
over whether Ursula's happy and
if he's a good husband and king,
and he's in need
of my immediate advice and counsel?
In a moment!
I'm sitting on a great hand here!
Yes, the gambling bug had bit
our normally guarded gorilla.
I'll take three.
Maybe my luck will change.
But luck wasn't in the cards
for our poker-playing primate.
As the game progressed,
there was a strange sense
in the room
that Ape was about
to be cheated out of the deed.
I'd like to stay in, but I have
nothing left to bet. I'm broke.
Maybe you have something of value?
Stocks, bonds,
real estate... in Africa?
I'm afraid not.
Don't you own...
Oh, what's it called, Ape Mountain?
No, the deed belongs to the legendary
George of the Jungle.
Perhaps you've heard of him?
Vaguely.
So, what are you holding,
Nostril-damus?
There. Just four queens.
Well, I'm holding four Lyles.
But don't you worry your pretty
little hairy head about it.
You can work off the debt performing
in my club... for the next 17 years.
What?
Hello.
Lt turns out the big ape
didn't have the deed.
How could Ape
not own Ape Mountain?
That's like saying the Rockefellers
don't own Rockefeller Center.
- They don't!
- Oh.
Lt turns out
your idiot son-in-law has it.
But where does he keep it?
Let me ask him.
George, where do you keep
the deed to Ape Mountain?
George hide in butt flap.
Enchanting.
He keeps it in his underwear.
How do we get him and his underwear
back here... so I can take it?
Tookie.
Ape can't come talk to George
because broke? In big trouble?
George must go Vegas to help.
Thrilled that George was leaving,
Beatrice beamed like a Cheshire cat.
George is coming.
What's he doing
with all that luggage?
Hey, he's leaving.
It's comments like that
which justify why I eat you.
Now I know why they call you
Really Mean Lion.
Oh, yeah.
Last time he left,
the jungle nearly fell apart.
It's so obvious, George only wants
to be with his own kind now.
But don't worry,
I'll take care of you.
Unaware of the threat
home and abroad,
George and his extended jungle
family took off on their first trip.
Look. Look.
Las Vegas!
Anxious to speak to his brethren,
Ape,
but not wanting to stand out
like a simian from the sticks,
George made a stop.
New George
look pretty good in Armani, too.
Farklempt at finally
finding each other again,
George and his brother, Ape,
had a big emotional reunion.
- Hi.
- Hello.
Oh, come on,
you can do better than that.
Oh, George! Please!
Let it off.
George so happy to see brother, Ape.
Me, too. What are you doing here?
George here to help.
Tookie say Ape in trouble.
Broke. Busted. No Benjamins.
Broke? It's all
a big misunderstanding.
I'm perfectly fine. That's... why
I'm giving away all my furniture.
George happy Ape perfectly fine.
Only wish George perfectly fine.
What's the matter?
Ursula and animals think George
spend too much time with other.
George so upset,
think about taking off neck crown.
Look, I understand your concern.
And if I return...
When I return, I'll coordinate your
schedule to everyone's satisfaction.
- It's just a question of balance.
- George good at balance.
George worried about Ursula.
She's lonely and she worried
she not cook or clean as well as Ape.
Well, she might have a point there.
George worried she miss civilisation
more than she miss George.
Don't be ridiculous!
Ursula adores you.
She's probably just suffering
from the five-year itch.
- What George do?
- What any husband would do.
Get her a nice present
to help scratch it.
A... backscratcher.
To help with itch.
As the jungle king demonstrated
the many uses of his gift,
his arch animal enemy
was back in the jungle
trying to take over his throne.
George of the Jungle
has deserted you.
If you elect me your king,
I promise to make every Tuesday
"Meatless Tuesday."
- But if you don't make me king...
- Oh, I'm scared!
...you have no idea
what a mean lion I can really be.
As the Mean Lion
schemed against him,
his perfidious plotters in Las Vegas
put the finishing touches
on their perspicacious plan.
Better turn off the alarm.
The old witch says he keeps the deed
in his underwear.
- That's disgusting.
- At least it'll be easy to find.
These look familiar.
Obviously he was planning
to stay for a while.
You would think at some point, Ursula
would recommend a zebra pattern.
Unaware of the deadly denizens
determined to destroy him...
Well, that's a change of pace.
...our accidental tourist took his
family backstage at Circus Circus.
As George gleefully greeted
his performing pals...
...Ursula wondered
if she'd ever come first.
George, this is Rocky.
He's very honoured to meet you.
Why do they call him Rocky?
Because when he gets nervous,
he does that.
George... honoured...
to... meet... Rocky... too.
He says he was born in a cage,
but he wants to return home with you
and learn to become
a real jungle kangaroo.
Cage is not good for animals.
George, kangaroos live in Australia,
we can't bring Rocky
back to the Bukuvu.
Tell him we're really sorry.
Don't worry, George,
he won't bother you again.
While our simple simian was being
stalked by a star-struck kangaroo,
Lyle and the women were still
searching our simple simian's shorts.
What now? It'll take us years
to go through the rest of these.
And it would have, too,
had the precise, practical, pragmatic
Ursula not labelled them.
Oo-oo feathers.
Hyena burger.
Wait a second. Deed.
Lyle immediately dispatched
a dastardly disciple to the jungle,
who enjoyed evicting the animals.
In every other story the king
of the jungle is a lion not a human.
And so, as is my birthright,
I now declare myself
king of the jungle!
- This is really bad!
- Tuesdays are still meatless, right?
You can't be king without the amulet.
Then I'll just have to get it back,
won't I?
We need George. Where's George?
George's friends were worried.
While Lyle celebrated getting the
deed in a typically mature fashion.
I have the deed
This is the deed I have
Getting the deed
is only half the battle.
Lt means nothing unless you get
Ursula to fall in love with you.
- Are you prepared for tonight?
- I'm prepared.
And so was Ape,
because they had all come to see
the swinging songster perform.
Eat!
Now, when I count to three,
you will awaken and feel refreshed,
and remember nothing.
One. Two. Three.
Ice cream?
But I'm lactose intolerant!
Oops.
Sorry.
Remember, I am Armando,
and I can hypnotise anyone
to do anything! Good night!
The Conrad Jupiter's Hotel
and Casino is proud to present
the selected song stylings
of the one and only Ape!
Here he comes
Walking down the street
He gets the funniest looks
from everyone he meets
Hey, hey, I'm a monkey
And people say I monkey around
Well, I'm too busy singing
to put anybody down
I'm just trying to be friendly
Come and watch me sing and play
I'm the young generation
And I've got something to say
Hey, hey I'm the monkey
Hey, hey, I'm a monkey
Yeah! Hey! Yeah!
Yeah! Thank you. Thank you.
- Thank you. Girls.
- You were wonderful
Ape will be back in a few minutes
with his tribute to Tony Orlando.
It's from the gentleman over there.
Lyle.
Beatrice, you're looking lovely.
Ursula, what a small world.
You remember my son-in-law, George.
I do. George.
Clearly the best man won.
But no hard feelings. Shake.
What are you doing here?
Last time we saw you,
you tried to have George killed,
Ape captured,
and dragged me off to marry you.
That actually wasn't me, kitten,
that was the altitude sickness.
Lt just so happens,
I have my doctor here, Dr Kerner.
In my opinion Lyle was not
responsible for his actions
due to the lack of oxygen
in the Bukuvu Mountains.
You knew I was gonna be here?
You're fired.
I didn't know
that you were gonna be here.
I ran into the Lords of Oompah
practising your favourite song,
I Wanna Know What Love Is.
What's that?
Wait a minute.
That not Ursula's favourite song.
This Ursula's favourite song.
One banana, two banana.
No!
- We're dead meat.
- I thought I was making progress.
That ape has a better chance with her
than you do.
He does? What have you heard?
It's time
we brought in some reinforcements.
- Here's your towels, Angels.
- Thanks, Charlie.
- Hey, don't hog the Choco-Blast.
- Mmm.
I'll give you it if Courtney
gives up the Funky Monkey.
Haven't you seen
enough funky monkeys?
- I've missed you guys.
- And we've missed you.
Speaking of things you've missed,
Lyle's looking amazing.
You're right. He's such a catch.
He's charming, rich, sensitive.
And is equally at home
with small animals and children.
Are you reading that?
I can't believe my mother flew you
here just to tell me about Lyle.
Your mother didn't send us here.
We're worried about you.
Yeah, I mean, a fling
any of us could understand.
And would gladly
have traded places with you.
Yeah.
- We're concerned you'll change.
- Come on. I haven't changed a bit.
I can't believe I just did that.
I guess I have changed.
You belong here. Your whole identity
will get swallowed up by George,
and the Ursula we know and love
will disappear.
You deserve a husband who'd rather
spend time with you than a gorilla.
But I love George.
Doesn't mean he's right for you.
You and Lyle have more in common.
She's right. You should be with
someone who's refined, polished,
someone who cares
about your feelings.
George doesn't know
how to make you happy.
Look, what's this great present
he gets you? A backscratcher.
And where did he take you on
your first day back in civilisation?
Backstage at Circus Circus.
Can you believe his lack of feeling?
You've been isolated
from all your friends,
hungry for human companionship,
and he brings you to an animal show.
How selfish.
This man doesn't love you, darling,
he hardly knows you.
It'll be so wonderful
when you're finally home.
The opera opens next month.
And we can go to the Canyon Ranch
to have some kind of total makeover.
And there's that wonderful charity
cruise for some kind of poor people.
Oh, yeah.
- Wait a second.
- What?
I... am the luckiest woman
in the whole world.
So he isn't
the greatest retail shopper.
I have a man I love
and a child I adore,
and he gives me
what all of you pray for.
I want my George.
What do we do now?
I don't know.
Oh, look to your left.
I think I have an idea.
Yes,
in a brilliantly desperate attempt
to bring Ursula and Lyle together,
Our masterminding major-domo
mother-in-law
has hired Armando to hypnotise
Ursula into forgetting George.
When you awaken,
the name George of the Jungle
will forever be stricken
from your memory.
Hey. Sorry I'm late.
There was a fat lady in a wheelchair
hogging the handicap spot.
His face will be blank.
You will not recognise him.
He will mean
absolutely nothing to you.
Oh, yes. Ursula, your husband
is Lyle Van de Groot.
One. Two. Three.
Pumpkin!
Lt took two movies
and a crooked hypnotist,
but the lecherous Lyle Van de Groot
had finally gotten his wish.
Ursula was, in a manner of speaking,
his wife.
Hello?
Turn the phone around, you idiot!
This George,
George looking for Ursula.
Oh, she's here with Junior.
She doesn't love you anymore.
She's left you for Lyle.
Ursula leave George?
Yes. She's with Lyle now.
George want to tell her that George
stop being king if she take him back.
Too late. You should have thought
of that when you had no time for her.
The people she misses are here.
She lives here now.
Face it, George,
your experiment with having a family
has been a failure.
You're not fit
to be a husband or a father.
Go back to the animals
where you belong.
Junior.
Goodbye, Ursula.
Come on, dear,
we don't wanna miss our flight.
Everything's so foggy.
- Lyle's my husband?
- Yes, darling.
You've been under
a lot of stress lately.
- Hold your father's hand.
- You're not my father!
Not polite kick Daddy!
Having heedlessly hewn our hero's
heavy heart into hittle hieces...
I mean, little pieces,
the vengeful Van de Groot tried to
impress his pilfered princess Ursula
with a dazzling display
of animal magnetism.
Come here.
See, honey, horses are my friends.
Kind of.
Maybe "friend" is too strong.
Are you sure Lyle's my husband?
See, honey, horses love me.
Come here.
Horses... love... me!
Horses love me!
You guys ready to go for a ride?
How'd you ever let me marry that guy?
While they tried to figure out
why Ursula was married to an idiot,
Lyle's bulldozers were arriving to
clear the animals out of the Bukuvu.
Locked up by the Mean Lion to keep
him from contacting his former king,
the tactile Tookie-Tookie
had been plotting his escape.
George can't live without Ursula,
so George going to get her back.
Tookie!
Mean Lion crown himself king?
Animals kicked off land?
Need George to save animals?!
Have two days?! Ape!
We have to go right away.
I should've told you earlier,
but I have some gambling debts
that I have to work off
for a little while.
- How little?
- 17 years.
George think maybe
that might be too late.
When we get home, Ape can take out
loan from Bukuvu Credit Union.
George, these aren't nice people.
George won't go without Ape.
Future of jungle
and George depends on it.
- Alright, George.
- Yeah!
Yes. Yes.
Must get wife and son, who don't
want me, and amulet to lead troops.
Then the question is, how to get
the two of us up to San Francisco?
Better make that three of us.
Come on! Come on!
Jungle boogie. Go, go, go!
Going somewhere?
Who are you, Xena,
Princess of Vegas?
We'll see how funny you are
in a cage at the Van de Groot Zoo.
In case you've forgotten, you still
owe us 17 years of employment.
- Get moving.
- Run!
Rocky, get hopping.
Come on. Let's get 'em.
- Excuse me.
- George sorry.
Thank you. Excuse me.
- Outta the way!
- Move!
Nice.
Look out!
Quick, George!
Outta the way. Let's go.
Watch out, George!
Yeah, that way.
I'll get backup!
Quick!
Watch out for that...!
Hey, you! Stop!
Call the police! And Animal Control!
- What now, Ape?
- Oh, dear.
Back away
from the edge of the building.
- Come on, guys. Up here.
- There they are.
Don't move.
You're surrounded.
You have no choice but to surrender.
We'll send a man down
to cut off any escape.
I'm sorry, old chum,
we did everything we could.
George have idea.
Just do like George!
Ape! Jump! Come on! Go!
George, I've been away
from the jungle a very long time!
George catch you!
Don't make any sudden moves!
Don't you think that's beneath us?
Ape!
Good kick, Rocky!
- Don't do it!
- Here goes!
- What are they doing?
- Whoo!
Do not swing on the ladder!
We're going to find
a safe place to land.
Do not swing.
You're destabilising the helicopter.
We gotta land.
Oh, this is lovely.
This best swing George ever had!
Because George and his jungle
buddy are swinging together?
No, because not possible
for George to hit...
Yes fans, we've also included
the Empire State Building.
At least the Las Vegas version.
Watch out for that...!
You didn't think
we were gonna pass up this parody.
George! Come on!
You can do it! Come on!
Reach!
Now! Again! Swing over!
Thanks for joining us. In a bizarre
case of life imitating art,
tonight's drama over Las Vegas
has reached the very heights
of the Empire State Building.
Our correspondent...
Something about that ape
feels really familiar.
It's King Kong.
I thought King Kong
was in black and white.
Would you believe Hollywood?
They colourised it.
Reach! Reach! Grab me! Come on!
Got you! Pull!
Units are arriving on the scene
to get you down.
- So got any other ideas?
- Follow George.
Brilliant.
Meanwhile, that dastardly duo
of damsels, Sally and Kowalski,
were searching
every nook and cranny.
That's cranny, not granny!
As halfway around the world,
an advancing army
prepared to invade the Bukuvu.
And in San Francisco, Ursula
pondered her present predicament.
I always had the fantasy
that when I kissed the man I love,
I'd hear church bells ringing.
Church bells ringing?
And fireworks.
Fireworks.
Loud, spectacular,
take-your-breath-away,
Fourth of July fireworks.
With Lyle, there's just...
...Lyle.
Yeah.
So much for fantasy.
I can't help feeling
that something's missing.
That somewhere out there,
something's waiting for me.
Sorry to surprise Ursula.
George can't live without Ursula.
George madly in love.
Look... I don't know who you are,
but I'm married... unfortunately.
Right.
George Ursula's husband.
Ursula more confused than George.
But no time to talk.
Bukuvu in trouble. Must get back.
George put Ursula first then jungle.
Listen. I've never heard
of the Bukuvu and Lyle's my husband.
Though I have to admit,
you are quite attractive.
And have the sinewy arms of a god!
But I'm old-fashioned and take
my marriage vows very seriously.
Then can I have him?
Sorry, George love Ursula
more than anything in the world.
Ursula mean everything to George.
- Do you have any brothers at home?
- I have brother Ape.
Oooh... an ape.
Can you give him my phone number?
Having deposited his dipsy darling
with Ape,
George nervously swung in to see
if his son still remembered him.
Junior?
Daddy!
I missed you so much.
George realise something.
If Junior want to surf
and not swing it's OK with George,
because George love Junior so much,
nothing else matters.
Come here.
I love you too, Dad.
But I think you better talk to Mom,
because she's been acting strange.
Yeah.
Come on!
I'll take the stairs.
OK.
So with his devoted son
and dormant wife,
George headed back
to his homeland.
After a tip from Brendan Fraser, who
was cramped during the first picture,
this time he made sure
to get a bigger crate.
- Dad, I'm afraid.
- Hmm.
What are we gonna do about Mom?
George not know.
But Ursula not recognise George
even before George level her.
What Ape think?
Either we should check the crate
for pods,
or she's in some sort of hypnotic
trance. She doesn't know who you are.
Upon arrival, George whistled
for Shep to take them home.
Hey, boy! Over here, boy!
Come on! Come on, Shep!
Come on, Shep!
Come on, boy! Come On!
That's a good boy.
Shep!
See if you can spot
our discreet product placement.
That's my Shep.
The elephant's wearing New Balance.
Go, Shep! Go!
Go, boy! That's it!
I tell you, George,
it's good to be home.
Maybe Tookie wrong
and Mean Lion not king.
Jungle not look different.
- Not different? Look at
the signs, George! The signs!
But George missed the signs.
Signs even an illiterate warthog
would've noticed.
Because there was a big problem.
Lyle's maniacal machinery was
moving ever closer to Ape Mountain.
Meanwhile,
the cowardly constituents scampered,
as our fearless hero ran after them
beseeching them to stand and fight.
Don't run!
If we work together, we can win.
George still king.
I'm the king!
You know you're not the king.
You've had a narcissistic personality
since you were a cub.
And there's no reason that the rest
of us should have to suffer for it.
If you really care about Bukuvu,
then better idea
we have a bone-crushing fight
for kingdom afterwards.
When we still have kingdom.
What Mean Lion think?
Eat fur, Jungle boy!
Yes! Get him!
And they would've had their big,
bone-crushing fight for the kingdom
had it not been for the trick
Ape taught him as kids.
The ear, George!
Cool!
There. See.
George wish life always this easy.
Yeah, Dad!
- Well done, George.
- Alright, who's with George?
Why should we follow you? You care
more about your family than us.
Sure George care about family.
Even half of family sleeping
through best part of movie.
But you've always been
George's brothers and sisters.
Don't you remember?
We took first steps together.
And you taught me how to swim.
And you were with me first time
we read Playape Magazine.
So George beg you, not as king,
but as brother,
to join him and save homeland.
George...
OK?
OK, George try
something completely different.
We few. We happy few.
We band of brothers.
For he today that sheds his fur
with George,
shall be George's brother.
And other animals shall think
themselves cursed they were not here.
And when we get old,
ye will remember with great pride
what feats ye did today.
Land all we have. George king.
And king ask animals to join him
and save homeland!
Then, George fight alone.
Feeling more alone
than Siegfried without Roy,
our dauntless, daring,
defiant jungle gunslinger
went out to save the Bukuvu.
But soon his friends joined him.
Like The Magnificent Seven,
if they hadn't been magnificent,
and had consisted of a dim king, an
elephant who thought he was a dog,
an ape, a bird, a little monkey
and a kangaroo.
They marched, flew and hopped out
to meet the enemy.
And, just between you and me...
it didn't look good.
Guess just us.
But luckily for George,
after a delayed reaction
to his insouciant iambic pentameter,
the jungle's vacillating varmints
joined the fight
with their potent potentate.
For those without a thesaurus...
After a delayed reaction
to his speech,
the other animals joined
the brouhaha with their king.
Imagining the cold steel
of the deleterious 'dozers
separating his upper half
from his lower,
he ordered his troops back
in a slow and orderly retreat.
Let's go!
George realised the only way to win
was to fight fire with... coconuts?!
So he called in the heavy artillery.
Yes!
Nice shooting!
Oh, no! Not elephant zug-zug!
Good shot!
Yeah!
With Shep down, George felt
the need to rally his troops.
Don't worry!
George not know meaning
of word defeat!
Not know meaning of most words,
but especially defeat!
And George will stand here just
as long as George's name is... Herb.
But Herb, I mean George,
quickly realised that a deadly 'dozer
was heading to destroy the tree
house and his still dozing wife.
George not hit women, so appreciate
it if women not hit George.
George realise
that to save tree house,
Bukuvu and entire jungle lifestyle,
George now have to hit woman.
But, in name of sportsmanship,
George give woman fighting chance.
Note to George,
rethink sportsmanship.
Having finally defeated
the pugnacious pair,
Indiana George found himself
with an even bigger bugaboo,
how to turn off the bulldozer?
What this do?
Didn't stop.
Tree house. Not good.
Move, animals!
Junior?!
George son swung!
We did it, Dad. We saved the jungle.
Yeah!
Can we join your little celebration?
Yes, it was Ursula's
meddling, mendacious, mock mate,
who, along with Beatrice,
had tracked her back to the Bukuvu.
Mom?
Lyle?
Ursula.
We've come to take my daughter
and grandson home.
You're not my father!
I was expecting that,
that's why I wore shin guards.
Ingrowing toenail!
Now, George,
you may think you've won the war,
but there'll be more bulldozers.
You give me back Ursula and Junior
and I'll give you back the deed.
George love Ursula and Junior.
George, I'm sorry, it's no use.
Lyle's my husband,
Junior and I should be with him.
- I'm sorry.
- That's right.
Take it easy, Jungle Head.
- Come along. Let's go.
- No!
Don't let Lyle take me, Dad.
I wanna stay with you.
Alright. OK!
Tell 'em to back off,
or Mighty Joe Old gets it here.
George appreciate
what gorillas do for George,
but George not want anyone
to die for him.
Sound advice, doofus.
You've used your head
for more than just cracking coconuts.
Tell 'em to back off. Way off!
I want you to have this.
Somehow, I think it belongs to you
in this world.
Oh, really. Must I be forced
to endure this drivel?
Take Ursula and Junior
and let's get on with it.
No problem. I'll get right on it.
OK.
Thanks for watching my family for me.
What George do?
George love animals and jungle,
but more than anything,
George love Ursula and Junior.
So what are you waiting for?
Get after them!
Go on!
Hey!
Classic moment of Western movie,
where hero holds bad guy up in air,
then humiliates with tree wedgie.
George!
George! Un-wedgie me.
That was so nice.
George.
Ursula know George?
Well, of course. You're my husband.
She know George!
As it turned out a kiss from George
was stronger than any hypnotic spell.
Hard to resist kiss from George.
Would you take your hands
off of my wife, please,
whom you have unhypnotised.
I haven't been this disappointed
since sixth grade
when my sister stole
my Shaun Cassidy lunch box.
George confused.
Shaun Cassidy was a popular
TV character in the late '70s
along with Parker Stevenson.
I followed both their careers.
Not confused about Shaun Cassidy.
George confused about
unhypnotising.
Would you like me to explain?
Sure.
That's what I'm here for.
We've all been wondering about that.
Let's not start in, OK?
I speak for everyone
including the audience
when I say this constant stream
of annoying alliteration is annoying!
What are you gonna do about that?
Come on! That hurts!
Wait!
Anyone else
have any critiques or comments?
Good.
But before we can end our movie with
the traditional jungle wedding scene,
George still had
one more official duty.
George!
Helping Ursula bring her friends
out of their hypnotic trance.
George!
But I still don't recognise him!
Stan?
Stan? Is that you? Stan?
- Hello.
- And you're a big hairy ape.
Yes!
So domestic bliss has once again
returned to the Bukuvu.
And with Beatrice's full blessing,
George and Ursula
decided to renew their vows.
George want everyone to know,
George no longer available all hours.
From nine to five,
George belong to animals.
From five to nine,
George belong to Junior.
But at all times,
George belong to Ursula.
And Ursula will wear neck crown.
Because without his queen, George
could not be king, or anything else.
Jolly good.
So all's well that ends well
for that defender of the innocent,
protector of the weak,
and all around good guy,
George of the Jungle.
And now that George
has learned to balance his time,
he has vowed
never to be late for lunch again.
Lunchtime!
Coming through!
Go, Dad!
Hi, Mom. Watch this!
That's my boy!
Jungle surfing not so hard.
George, watch out for that...
George, George,
George of the Jungle
Strong as he can be
27R, take one.
OK.
27R, take 41.
Thanks, sweetie. Here's the one.
27R, take 222!
Cut!
Watch out for that tree
George, George,
George of the Jungle
Lives a life that's free
Watch out for that tree
Look out!
Are you OK, Shep?
When he gets in a scrape
He makes his escape with help
from his friend an ape named Ape
And his elephant Shep
can fetch a log
He's man's best friend
is George's dog
What the...?!
He's George, George,
George of the Jungle
Strong as he can be
Watch out for that tree
George, George,
George of the Jungle
Friend to you and me
Oh, dear. Sorry.
Watch out for that tree
Hear him holler, swing and sing
All the animals come
to the jungle king
So grab a vine and swing in time
If you strike a tree
just pay no mind
Like George, George,
George of the Jungle
George, George,
Strong as he can be
Watch out for that tree
George, George,
George of the Jungle
Lives a life that's free
Watch out for that tree
When he gets in a scrape
He makes his escape with help
from his friend an ape named Ape
And his elephant Shep
can fetch a log
He's man's best friend
is George's dog
He's George, George,
George of the Jungle
Strong as he can be
Watch out for that tree
George, George,
George of the Jungle
Friend to you and me
Watch out for that tree
Hear him holler, swing and sing
All the animals come
to the jungle king
So grab a vine and swing in time
If you strike a tree
just pay no mind
Like George, George,
George of the Jungle
George, George,
Swing from tree to tree
Watch out for that tree
And so that ends the movie.
And, as always, everyone
winds up happy except for me.
But who cares about a narrator?
Well, fine, just leave me alone.
Go out with your boyfriend or
your girlfriend or your best friend
or your husband or your wife.
Just go, I said.
Go on. Nobody cares
about these credits anyway.
Contractually,
we have to show the credits.
Who are you?
I'm the narrator from Mulan.
Well...
it's really nice to meet you.
George, George,
George of the Jungle
Watch out for that tree
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today