Watch Movies, TV Series and Live Sports
Signup Here -> WWW.ADMITME.APP
Here, you can take this ticket!
You can have this ticket and
keep it! I'm not paying that ticket!
Jesus! Why don't you watch
where you're going!
Then I want you to go
downstairs to the cellar
and check the water under the boiler.
I wanna do that today, all right!
- Could you do that?
- Would you mind giving me a hand?
I ain't the doorman, Ms. Barrett,
I'm the building superintendent.
You're also a human being.
It's not my job, but what
the hell, I'll do you a favor.
Listen, when are you gonna get around to
fixing the radiator in the baby's room?
- You know, I asked you last week.
- Didn't I do that?
Well, it's getting really
cold in there. I...
Okay, well, it's no problem.
Hey!
Hey, stop that carriage!
- Get it!
- Stop!
That's my baby!
Watch out!
Jesus!
Oscar, watch out!
My God!
Please!
Stop that carriage!
♪ Ghostbusters ♪
♪ If there's something strange
In your neighborhood ♪
♪ Who you gonna call? ♪
♪ Ghostbusters ♪
♪ if there's something weird
And it don't look good ♪
♪ Who you gonna call? ♪
♪ Ghostbusters ♪♪
- How many of them are there?
- Fourteen. They're in here.
I hope you can handle it.
It's been like a nightmare.
- How big are they?
- Four feet.
Hey, kids, listen up!
Listen up! Look who's here!
- Hey!
- Boo!
How you doing, kids?
I thought it was gonna be He-Man.
- Yeah.
- Hey, hey, I know.
Why don't we all sit
down and we'll have fun.
Yeah!
You know, my dad says you
guys are full of crap.
- Jason.
- Well, some people have trouble
- believing in the paranormal.
- No, he just says you're full of crap
and that's why you
went out of business.
Song.
Come on, everybody!
♪ There's something strange
In the neighborhood ♪
♪ Who you gonna call? ♪
- He-Man!
- He-Man! He-Man! He-Man!
♪ And it don't look good ♪♪
- Let's go get a beer, all right?
- Yeah.
- Thank you. Call anytime.
- Bye.
Look, that's it. I've had it, Ray.
- No more parties.
- Here's your share.
Look, I'm tired of taking abuse
from overprivileged 9-year-olds.
I know, Z, but we can't quit now.
The holidays are coming up.
- It's our best season.
- Ray.
Man, face it. Ghostbusters
doesn't exist.
A year from now, those kids
won't even remember who we are.
Ungrateful little yuppie larvae.
After all we did for this city.
Yeah, we conjured up a
100-foot marshmallow man,
blew the top three floors
off an uptown high-rise,
ended up getting sued
by every state, county
and city agency in New York.
Yeah, but what a ride.
right out into the middle of traffic
and I started really running after it.
And then it just suddenly stopped,
right in the middle of the street.
Mm-hm. And did anyone
else see this happen?
Well, sure, hundreds of people.
- Egon, I didn't imagine this.
- I'm not saying you did.
It's just in science, we always
look for the simplest explanation.
- We're ready, Dr. Spengler.
- Good.
We'll start with the
negative calibration.
- What are you working on, Egon?
- Trying to determine
whether human emotions actually
affect the physical environment.
It's a theory Ray and I had when
we were still Ghostbusters.
Can they see us?
No. They think they're here
for marriage counseling.
We kept them waiting for
two and a half hours.
I've been gradually increasing
the temperature in the room.
It's up to 95 degrees
at the moment.
Now my assistant has asked them
if they'd mind waiting
another half-hour.
Oh, good. Very good.
Very, very nice.
- So, Egon, what do you think?
- Excellent. Just excellent.
Do the happiness index next.
I mean about the carriage.
Well, I'd like to bring Ray in
on this, if you don't mind.
Sure. Whatever you think.
But not Venkman.
Oh, no.
- Do you ever see him?
- Occasionally.
- Peter?
- How is he these days?
Well, he was borderline
for a while.
Then he crossed the border.
Does he ever mention me?
No.
Oh. Well, we... We didn't
part on very good terms.
And then we sort of lost track of
each other after I got married.
- We're ready for the affection test.
- Good, send in the puppy, please.
I thought of getting in touch with
him after my marriage ended, but...
Oh.
Isn't that sweet?
I appreciate your doing this.
Try not to worry.
Here's my phone number.
You'll call me?
Yes.
I'd rather you didn't mention any
of this to Peter, if you don't mind.
No, I won't. I won't.
Thanks.
Let's see what happens when
we take away the puppy.
This... Gee, I don't know...
father encouraged...
Hi. Welcome back to
World of the Psychic.
I'm Peter Venkman.
I'm chatting with my guest.
Author, lecturer and psychic,
Milton Angland. Milt, your new book
is called The End of the World.
Now, can you tell us
when it's gonna be,
or do we have to buy the book?
Well, I predict that
the world will end
at the stroke of midnight
on New Year's Eve.
- This year?
- Mm-hm.
Well, that's cutting it a little
bit close, isn't it? I mean...
Just from a sales point of view,
I mean, your book is just coming out,
you're not gonna see any paperback
sales for at least a year.
It'll be at least another year before you
know whether you've got the mini-series
or Movie of the Week kind of possibilities.
Just devil's advocate, Milty.
I mean, shouldn't you have said,
"Hey, the world's gonna end in 1992"?
- Wait a minute. This is...
- Or better yet, 1994.
This is not just some
money-making scheme, all right?
I have a strong psychic belief...
that the world will end
on New Year's Eve.
- For your sake, I hope you're right.
- Thank you.
Okay, but I think my other
guest may disagree with you.
Elaine.
Now, you had another date in mind.
According to my source,
the end of the world will be on
February 14th in the year 2016.
Valentine's Day.
Bummer.
Where'd you get your date, Elaine?
I received this information
from an alien.
As I told my husband,
it was in the Paramus Holiday Inn.
I was having a drink
at the bar, alone,
and this alien approached me.
He started talking to me.
He bought me a drink.
And then I think he must
have used some kind of a ray
or a mind-control device,
because he forced me to
follow him to his room.
And that's where...
he told me about the
end of the world.
So your alien had a room at
the Holiday Inn, Paramus?
It might've been a
room on the spacecraft
made up to look like a
room at the Holiday Inn.
I can't be sure about that, Peter.
Of course not. And that is the
whole problem with aliens,
is you just can't trust them.
Occasionally you meet a
nice one: Starman, E.T.
But usually they turn out to
be some kind of big lizard!
That's all the time we've got for
this week on World of the Psychic.
Next week, though...
Give me Ira. Hairless pets.
Weird. Until then,
this is Peter Venkman, saying:
See you then. Bye.
Norman, where do you
find these people?
Weren't we supposed to have the
telekinetic guy who bends the spoons?
He canceled. This is the best we
could do at such short notice.
Look, no respected psychic
will come on the show.
- They think you're a fraud.
- I am a fraud.
Mr. Mayor. Lenny. Lenny!
- Pete Venkman.
- Can I help you?
Yeah, get your hand off me.
Thank you, I'm an old friend of the mayor's.
I wanna say hello, give him a kiss.
I'm Jack Hardemeyer, I'm
the mayor's assistant.
I know who you are, Dr. Venkman.
I just don't see any ghosts anywhere.
That's why I wanted to
talk to His Highness.
See, we did a little job for the city a
while back and we got stiffed on the bill
by some bureaucratic
bookworm like yourself.
Look, you stay away from the mayor.
He's running for governor next fall.
And the last thing we need is for him
to be associated with two-bit frauds
and publicity hounds like
you and your friends.
You know, I'm a voter.
Aren't you supposed to lie
to me and kiss my butt?
All right, yes. Now, I want you
to put the Vigo in the arch.
Under the arch there.
Everything you're doing is bad.
I want you to know this.
You be careful there, all right?
No one listens to me.
Well, Dana, how are you doing?
- How's this Bonington coming?
- It's coming along fine.
This mixture you gave me
is working really well.
Yes? Well, I make pretty
good cocktails, don't I?
Yes, you're doing really
- quite good work there.
- Thank you.
It won't be long before
you can assist me in...
more important restoration.
Just a... A white thing.
Well, thank you, Dr. Poha.
- Janosz.
Um, I've enjoyed working here,
but now that my baby's a little older, I'm
gonna try to go back to the orchestra.
Oh, I'm sorry to hear that
you will not... Be not here.
Well, could I say goodbye?
You know, maybe bring
you to a brunch today?
Well, I can't today, I have an
appointment. In fact, I'd better go.
I don't understand this. You know, every
day I say, "Can you do something?"
You say, "No, I can't
do something."
- Do I have bad breath or something?
- Of course not.
All right. Well, I'll
give you a rain check.
I think that she likes me.
No, I do. I truly do.
This one's interesting,
Ray. Berlin, 1939.
A flower cart took off by
itself, rolled half a kilometer.
- Three hundred eyewitnesses.
- My best to the coven.
Berlin, huh? You know,
you should also check Duke University
studies on controlled psychokinesis.
- I pulled it.
- Perhaps you could you help me,
I'm looking for a
love-potion aerosol
that I could spray on a
certain Penthouse Pet
to obtain her total submission.
- Hello, Venkman.
- Hi, Pete. How's it going?
Very well. Hi, Egon. How's school?
I bet those science chicks really dig
that large cranium of yours, huh?
I think they're more
interested in my epididymis.
Ray, let's close this place up
so you can buy me a calzone.
I really can't do that right now,
Pete. I'm working on something.
But your book came in.
- Magical Paths to Fortune and Power.
- Thank you.
Good luck with that, Venkman.
- Put this on my account, please?
- Sure.
- Ray, take a look at this.
- Oh, yeah.
What are you guys working on?
- Uh, well, we're just kind of...
- Ahem.
checking something out
for an old friend.
Neat. Who?
Um...
Ray's Occult.
Seven o'clock on weekdays,
midnight on Saturdays.
Thank you.
- Who?
- Just someone we know.
- Oh.
Who?
- I can't! No! No! No!
- Yes, you can. Who?
- Nobody! Nobody!
- Can you tell me now?
- I can't!
- Now?
Dana Barrett!
Ow.
My Dana Barrett?
I'll get it.
- Hi, Dana.
- Hi, Ray.
How good to see you.
Thanks for coming.
Hey, no problem. Always
glad to help. And hug.
- Hello, Dana.
- Hi, Egon.
Nice place.
Well, I know I'm just
asking for the big hurt
but I thought I'd give
us one more chance.
He tortured me. He pulled my ears.
Hello, Peter.
Hello, Dana.
- So, what would you like to do first?
- We'd like to examine the baby.
Yeah, and anything associated with
the baby, especially stuffed toys.
- Then we'd like to see the buggy.
- All right. Can I put him here?
- And wherever he sleeps.
- Yes.
- This'll be fine.
- This okay?
- That's fine.
- Okay.
We'll have to lay him down flat.
Okay, sweetheart, now they're
gonna take a look at you.
We'll do a cursory
medical examination.
What do you say? Gammel and
Pross Infant Acuity Test?
Sounds good. We'll finish
with an Apgar score.
It's nothing that's
gonna hurt him, right?
No. No, I don't think so.
He'll be fine.
- You ever done this before?
- On a chimp.
So whatever happened
to Mr. Right, anyway?
I heard he ditched you
and ran off to Europe.
He didn't ditch me.
We had some problems
and he got a very good job offer from
an orchestra in London and he took it.
So he ditched you.
Okay. Subject is a male Caucasian,
- approximately...
- Twenty four inches.
Twenty-four inches in length.
Subject weighs approximately 18
pounds and is about 8 months old.
Okay. Ocular?
Pupillary response normal.
Auditory.
- Appears normal.
- Apillary reflex.
- Appears to be ticklish.
- Yep. Baby ticklish.
You know, you'd have been
better off marrying me.
You never asked me.
And whenever I brought it up,
you'd get drowsy and fall asleep.
You never got it, Dana.
I'm a man. I'm sensitive.
I need to feel loved.
I need to be desired.
It was when you started introducing
me as "the old ball and chain."
That's when I left.
Well, I may have a lot
of personal problems,
but I'm a total professional
when it comes to my job.
- Hey, Egon.
- What?
- What are we doing?
- He seems to be fine, Dana.
- Mm-hm. He's very healthy.
- He's okay.
When he does sleep,
where do you put him?
Right around here. I'll show you.
Venkman, would you get
a stool specimen, please?
Business or personal?
It's a little messy.
Well, we don't wanna play with anything,
we just wanna sweep for valences.
Mm. Very cheerful.
My parents didn't believe in toys.
You wanna play with a big kid?
You know, I should
have been your father.
I mean, I could have been.
I understand.
Help! He's gone completely
berserk. Help!
- Uh-oh.
You mean you never
even had a Slinky?
We had part of a Slinky.
But I straightened it.
Help! Help!
He...
He had some sort of clear
liquid coming out of his mouth.
Yeah, well, that happens.
Well, what do you think?
Well, he's ugly.
I mean, he's not Elephant Man ugly,
but he's not attractive.
Was his father ugly?
- Don't listen.
- And he stinks.
You're ripe, señor.
Did his father stink?
Yeah. Daddy was a smelly, huh?
- What's your name?
- His name is Oscar.
Named after a hot dog.
You poor man.
You poor, poor man.
But seriously, there's nothing...
unusual about him, is there?
Well, I don't have a lot
of experience with babies.
But you're excited now,
because Mama's here to get your
stool sample. Right, Mama?
- Stool sample?
- Yeah.
- Nothing.
- So, what, brainiac?
I'd like to run some gynaecological
tests on the mother.
- Who wouldn't?
- Let's check the street.
It stopped right over there,
- in the middle of the crosswalk.
- All right, I can get us out there.
- Hey. Venkman.
- Hold on.
We're scientists, excuse us.
Get out of the way!
Thanks a lot. We gotta
do an inquiry here.
Hold on. Thanks. Appreciate it.
Thanks.
You gonna move out
of there or what?
Relax, you're on the meter. Come on, hey!
We're scientists, get out of the way.
I think we hit the honeypot.
There's something brewing under the
street. I've got 1118 on the PKE.
Two-point-five GEVs
on the gigameter.
Well, what does that mean?
Hey! How you doing?
- Me?
- Yeah.
- Fine. Fine. It's cutting fine now.
- Great.
Why are you cutting?
Why am I cutting?
- Yeah.
- Boss!
Who told you to stop cutting?
- Somebody tell you to stop...?
- What're you guys doing here?
Did you tell him to stop cutting?
Yes, I told him to stop.
What are you doing?
What's it look like we're doing here? Why
don't you let us work? We let you work.
Hey, take it easy. He's been working
overtime. I tell you why we're here.
We're here because some
diaper bag downtown
is being a jerk and making us work on
a Friday night. Am I right, Peter?
Of course you're right,
Raymond. Is he right, Ziggy?
Yo.
- You guys take it easy, all right?
- Come on. Come on.
What have you been doing?
What have I been doing? While you
were getting coffee for an hour,
I've been digging a big hole
in the middle of the street.
Looks like you uncovered
an old air shaft.
Man, that just goes on and on.
This is very intense. We
should get a deeper reading.
Yeah. We're gonna need
a deeper reading.
Yeah, somebody has
to go down there.
Yeah, somebody's
gotta go down there.
Stinging! I'm stinging!
Listen to me.
What? Who?
I, Vigo, the scourge of Carpathia,
the sorrow of Moldavia,
command you.
Oh, command me, lord.
On a mountain of skulls
in the castle of pain
I sat on a throne of blood.
What was, will be.
What is, will be no more.
Now is the season of evil.
Evil?
Find me a child, that
I might live again.
Yes. A child.
A child. A child?
A child.
You all right?
Yeah, I'm good.
The speed's good, boys.
Keep it coming.
We're breaking through.
I see some light.
I'm in some kind of a chamber.
There's tile work.
- Slime!
- What?
It's a river of slime!
There's gotta be 25,000 gallons of it.
It's flowing through here like a river.
Van Horne. Pneumatic
transit. I can't believe it.
It's the old pneumatic transit
system, it's still here.
Okay. That's good.
Hold me up. That's good.
What do you see?
All right. Let's see
if I can get a sample.
What's going on here?
Hey, what's the story?
Hey, what, you boneheads are gonna
come and roust me out again?
I got 3000 phones out
in Greenwich Village.
I got about 8 million miles
of cable I gotta check.
You gonna come shake
my monkey tree again?!
What are you talking about, buddy?
The phone lines are over there.
What did I say to you? The
phone lines are over there.
- What did I say? How many times?
- Hey! Hey!
Hey, you're not with Con Ed or
the phone company. We checked.
So tell me another one.
I've got a major gas leak here!
Where do you think all this
is coming from, the sky?
Okay, boys.
Boys?
Pull me up now, all right?
There's some kind of activity
going on with this stuff.
Boys? Hey, help!
- Take me up!
- Ray!
Start it! Start it!
Boys? Hey, what's
going on up there?
Come on! Get me out of this hole!
Sweetie.
Hello.
Go back to sleep, darling.
- Who is it?
- It's Janosz.
Janosz.
Hello, Janosz.
- This is a surprise.
- Oh, hello.
Uh, yes. Well, I happened to
be here in this neighborhood
and I thought that I would stop
by to see how is it with you.
Yeah, because of all
this blackness, it was.
- We're fine. Thank you. Thank...
- Well, then, you're okay?
- How's the baby?
- He's okay. Yes.
Whoo.
- He's sleeping.
- Oh, but I "woo"-ed.
- That's okay.
- All right, and
do you need anything? You know?
Do you want me to come in?
- No, thank you.
- All right.
Just thought that I
would check. You know.
Well, hey, you. Don't
let the bedbugs bite.
Good night, Janosz.
Before we begin this trial, I want
to make one thing very clear.
The law does not recognize
the existence of ghosts
and I don't believe in them either.
I don't want to hear a lot of malarkey
about goblins, spooks and demons.
We're gonna stick to
the facts in this case
and leave the ghost stories
to the kiddies, understood?
Wow, sounds like a pretty
open-minded guy, huh?
Yeah, they call him "The Hammer."
What can we do? It's all in
the hands of our lawyer now.
I think you guys are
making a big mistake.
I do mostly tax law and some
probate stuff occasionally.
I got my law degree
at night school.
Well, that's fine, Louis.
We got arrested at night.
Look, just put these guys away fast
and make sure they go away
for a long, long time, okay?
I don't think it's gonna be hard,
with this list of charges.
Good. Very good.
Violating a judicial
restraining order,
willful destruction of public
property, fraud, malicious mischief.
See you in a couple of years,
at your first parole hearing.
You'll never take us alive.
All right, all right.
Let's get on with it.
Your Honor,
ladies and gentlemen
of the audience,
I don't think it's fair to
call my clients frauds.
Okay, so the blackout was a big
problem for everybody, okay?
I was stuck in an elevator for two hours
and I had to make the whole time.
But I don't blame them.
Because one time I turned into a
dog and they helped me. Thank you.
Very good, Louis.
Short but pointless.
Mr. Fianella,
please look at exhibits A through
F on the table over here.
Do you recognize this equipment?
Yeah, that's the stuff the
cops took from their truck.
Do you know what this
equipment is used for?
I don't know. Catching
ghosts, maybe? I don't know.
May I remind the court the defendants
are under a judicial restraining order
that strictly forbids them
from performing services
as paranormal investigators
or eliminators.
So noted.
Now, Mr. Fianella,
can you identify the substance
in this jar marked "Exhibit F"?
Yeah. Yeah, that's
the stuff, all right.
Your Honor, I've been working
underground for Con Ed for 27 years.
I never saw anything
like this in my life.
Whatever's down there,
they must've put it there.
- No, we didn't!
- Ray, Ray.
Shut up!
- So you were just trying to help...
- Help out a friend.
- Who was frightened.
- Who was scared.
And when you're scared... What?
- There was no evil...
- No evil was intended. No malice.
When you live in a place and
you love it like you do,
you don't want nothing
bad to happen.
- What?
- It was a one-shot...
Because it'll never happen again. It's an
isolated incident, it's a one-shot deal.
- Objection, Your Honor.
- What?
- He's leading the witness.
- Sustained.
Give me a break.
We're both lawyers.
Mr. Tully, do you have any
questions for this witness
that might have some
bearing on this case?
- Do I?
- No, we've helped them out enough.
No, Your Honor.
Your witness.
Dr. Venkman...
would you please tell the court why
it is that you and your co-defendants
took it upon yourselves to dig a very
big hole in the middle of First Avenue.
Well, there's so many
holes in First Avenue
we really didn't think
anyone would notice.
Keep that up, mister,
I'll find you in contempt.
I'm truly sorry, Your Honor.
I'll ask you again, Dr. Venkman,
why were you digging the hole?
And please remember
you're under oath.
There are some things in this world
that go way beyond
human understanding.
Things that cannot be explained,
things that most people
don't wanna know about.
That is where we come in.
So what you're saying is that
the world of the supernatural
is your exclusive province?
Kitten, I think what
I'm saying is that
sometimes shit happens,
someone has to deal with it,
and who you gonna call?
Shut up!
Peter Venkman, Raymond Stantz,
Egon Spengler, stand up!
Get up!
You too, Mr. Tully.
I find you guilty on all charges.
I order you to pay fines in
the amount of $25,000 each.
I sentence you to 18 months at the city
correctional facility at Riker's Island.
Egie, she's twitching.
I'm not finished!
On a more personal note,
let me just go on record
as saying that there's no place
for fakes, charlatans...
- Uh, your Honor...
- Shut up!
- Tricksters like you in decent society.
- Your Honor, this is important.
You play on the gullibility
of innocent people.
- Yes, sir.
- Be quiet!
- But...
- If my hands weren't tied
by the unalterable
fetters of the law
then I would invoke the tradition
of our illustrious forebears,
reach back to a purer,
sterner justice
and have you burned at the stake!
Wow.
Oh, my God, the Scoleri brothers.
- The Scoleri brothers!
- Friends of yours?
I tried them for murder!
Gave them the chair!
You gotta do something!
Why don't you just tell them
you don't believe in ghosts.
You gotta do something. Help me!
Don't talk to me.
Talk to my attorney.
That's me! My guys are still under
a judicial misstrangement order.
That blue thing I got from her.
They could be exposing themselves.
And you don't want us
exposing ourselves.
- You're next, Bubbles.
- All right! I rescind the order!
- Case dismissed!
- Hurray! We won the case!
Now, do something!
I always hated this
part of the business.
You know, it's been a couple
years since we used this stuff.
- I hope it still works.
- It should.
Power cells have a
half-life of 5000 years.
There's no time for a bench test.
Heat them up.
- Do...
- Re...
Egon!
Whoa.
You got him, Venkman!
Hold him! Steady.
Come on, big boy. I'm gonna take
you home to my private zoo.
You got him. You got him!
- Egie, bring the trap.
- Okay, okay.
Behind you, Ray!
Hold him, Ray!
Venkman, start bringing him back!
Come on, you big meanie.
Let's go, chubby.
Ray, keep pulling him to the right.
Okay, the trap's going in.
No, no, Spengie!
- Hold it, Ray!
- Hit it!
- Two in the box!
- Ready to go!
- We be fast.
- And they be slow!
Wow.
We're the best! We're the
beautiful! We're the only
- Ghostbusters.
- We're back!
Ghostbusters.
Yes, we're back.
♪ Something strange going on
Something's wrong ♪
♪ Gloom in the room
Outside is the storm ♪
♪ All alone in the crib ♪
Certified check,
cash or money order.
♪ Yo, is that what I did?
Did I see something move? ♪
♪ Chills down your spine
Your heart fills with fright ♪
♪ Not filled by the things
That go bump in the night ♪
♪ Walk through the wall
With no time to stall ♪
♪ You call the Ghostbusters
Well, that's who you call ♪
♪ Ghostbusters ♪
♪ We ain't, we ain't
We ain't afraid of no ghost ♪
♪ Ghostbusters ♪
Get him!
Bye-bye.
- What is it, honey?
- It's that darn ghost again.
He just won't leave us alone.
I guess we're just
going to have to move.
No, wait! Don't worry,
we're not moving.
He is.
Who are you going to call?
Ghostbusters.
♪ I ain't, I ain't afraid of no ghost
I ain't, I ain't afraid of no ghost ♪
♪ Ghostbusters ♪
♪ I remember the time
I visited the grave ♪
♪ My life on the line
Only my life to save ♪
♪ All by myself
With no one around ♪
♪ Did not understand a hand
Coming out the ground ♪
♪ I knew it wasn't mine
It was somebody else ♪
Now.
♪ I just screamed for help
Then ♪
♪ Ghostbusters ♪
♪ Packs strapped to their back
Screaming ♪
♪ Ghostbusters ♪
Janine, lunch!
Boy, it smells like
somebody took a big...
♪ G-H-O-S-T ♪
♪ Ghostbusters ♪
♪ I ain't, I ain't,
I ain't afraid of no ghost ♪
♪ Ghostbusters ♪
♪ I ain't, I ain't,
I ain't afraid of no ghost ♪
With our special
half-price service plan.
What? Hold on. Half-price?
- Have we all gone mad?
- I guess so, Pete.
Because that's not all.
Tell them, Egon.
Oh, you mean the Ghostbusters
hot-beverage thermal mug
and free balloons for the kids?
♪ Ghostbusters ♪♪
We've been experimenting with the
plasm we found in the subway tunnel.
Careful.
- Should I get spoons?
- Don't bother. Watch this.
Try it, Ray.
You! You worthless piece of slime!
You ignorant, disgusting blob.
You're nothing but an unstable
short-chain molecule!
You foul, obnoxious muck!
You have a weak
electrochemical bond!
I have seen some
disgusting crud in my time
but you take the cake.
- You're a... You're just...
- Hey. Whoa, whoa, whoa.
This is what you do
with your spare time?
Peter, this is an
incredible breakthrough.
What a discovery.
A psycho-reactive substance.
Whatever this stuff is, it responds
to human emotional states.
Mood slime.
Oh, baby.
You mean this stuff actually
feeds on bad vibes.
Like a cop in a doughnut factory.
We've been running tests to see if we can
get an equally strong positive reaction.
What kind of tests?
Well, we sing to it
and we talk to it
and say supportive,
nurturing things to it.
You're not sleeping
with it, are you, Ray?
Oh, you.
- It's always the quiet ones.
- You hound.
- Ahem. How about the kinetic tests?
- Okay.
Ordinary household toaster.
We'll take your word for that.
It responds to music, so we've
been doing some experimentation,
playing easy listening.
Middle-of-the-road-type stuff.
You know, Paul Young, "Dust in
the Wind." That works okay.
- Works for me.
- Loves Jackie Wilson.
Jeez. You guys do this at
night when I'm not here?
Oh, I get it. It sings. It
sounds exactly like Jackie.
- That's fantastic.
- Just watch.
Does it do Emmylou Harris?
- ♪ Your love is lifting me higher ♪
- Oh, it dances too.
♪ Than I've ever
Been lifted before ♪
Shake it up!
♪ And I'll be at your side... ♪
Oh, baby! Oh, you're my number
one Christmas boutique gift item.
Right, and the first time somebody gets
mad, that toaster could eat their hand.
No, no, no. We put a warning label
on it. We don't have any liability.
Ow. Ow!
Oh, did you ever go for it!
The old man-eating toaster bit.
- Get him!
- No!
Hello. I'm looking
for Dana Barrett.
- Room 304, restoration.
- Thank you.
Hey, Dr. Venkman!
World of the Psychic.
- That's right. How you doing?
- I'm a big, big fan of yours.
Thank you very much. Thank you.
It used to be one of
my two favorite shows.
You're kidding me. Well, great.
What was the other one?
- Bass Masters. It's a fishing show.
- Yeah, I know Bass Masters. Sure.
You're good, pretty eyes.
I didn't paint it.
I'm just cleaning it.
- It's a Gauguin.
- Oh, I've heard of him.
Hey, Dana. Aren't you going to
introduce me to your friend?
Sure. Peter Venkman,
this is Dr. Janosz Poha,
the head of our department.
Yes, I have, of course, have
seen you on the television.
Quite enjoy. You're not
here on business, I hope?
Well, it's top-secret. Say,
Johnny, you got a Gauguin too.
No. Actually, I'm preparing this portrait
for the new Romantic exhibition.
Yes. This is Prince Vigo, the
ruler of Carpathia and Moldavia.
Bit of a sissy, isn't he?
He was a very powerful
magician, Dr. Venkman.
And a genius in many ways.
He was also a lunatic
and a genocidal madman.
I hate this painting.
I've felt uncomfortable
ever since it came up from storage.
Well, you're probably feeling
what Vigo is feeling:
Carpathian kitten loss.
He's missed his kitten.
We'll just put one in
here by the castle.
We don't go around altering
valuable artwork, Dr. Venkman.
Go. Yes, I think, go.
Yes, the joyfulness is over.
He's kidding.
Well, you're not gonna get a green
card with that attitude, pal. Okay?
I don't know what to...
Oh, of course. Of course.
I get it. You're sweet on
this hunky stud, aren't you?
You know, Peter, every now
and then I get the feeling
that painting is watching
me, even smiling at me.
You know, I think we got
more food on your shirt
than we did in your mouth.
Okay.
Bath. You get to take
a bath, don't you?
Yes, do your favorite thing.
Because I know what you get to do.
You know what you get to do?
Do you know what's more
fun than anything? Huh?
Splash Mommy.
"I get to splash Mommy." Yes.
We'll be ready in just a moment.
Mommy's gonna take
her shirt off too.
No! No!
Peter, it's me. Please let us in.
What the hell is this?
Peter, let us in, please.
I didn't know where else to go.
The most awful thing happened.
The bathtub... The bathtub
was trying to eat Oscar.
I was giving him a bath. There was
all this pink ooze everywhere
- and it was reaching for him.
- Okay, you're all right.
I'm not gonna let them get you.
- All right. You're all safe now, okay?
- I was so terrified.
- Yes, darling. I'm so sorry.
- You guys just sit down. Relax.
Come on. Just sit down. I'll get you
guys a shirt or something. Hold on.
Ray. Yeah, Dana's just
come over to my place.
Well, actually, her
tub tried to eat her.
What? Are you serious?
Well, that's great!
I mean, that's terrible.
But it's great for what we...
Yeah, I will.
Yeah, sure, we'll get right on it.
Spengler. A major slime-related
psychokinetic event.
- What happened?
- Something came out of Dana's bathtub.
- Tried to grab her and the baby.
- Are they all right?
- She got out and went to Venkman's.
- This is interesting, Ray.
Remember the painting
Venkman mentioned?
I ran "Vigo the Carpathian"
through the occult reference net.
Look what came up.
Ooh. Nice ugly history.
You think there's a connection between
this Vigo character and the...
slime?
Is the atomic weight
of cobalt 58.9?
We better get over to Dana's apartment.
I'd like to check out that bathtub.
It might be a good idea to go
to the museum in the morning,
get a look at that painting.
Ray's gonna go on over to your
place and just take a look.
- He is?
- Okay.
I have been holding on to
this for a long time, Oscar.
I got this from a girl who got
this from Joe Willie Namath, okay?
We don't know how.
We don't wanna know.
So I would appreciate it if you
would not hose this thing down,
you know, give it your own
personal rinse. Thank you.
Be an excellent time for
you to start practicing
a thing we big guys like
to call self-control.
Get out of here. Oh, look at him.
Look at him. Oh, look at his gut.
Oh, he's a coconut, this guy.
You're gonna be staying at Uncle
Pete's until this thing blows over.
This is your place now.
Hi.
Come on in. This is my place.
So how are we gonna handle
the sleeping arrangements?
Well, what's best for me is
if I lie on my side like this
and you spoon up beside me,
your arm draped over me.
We do it the other way,
I get your hair caught in my
throat and I choke in the night.
Well, how about you on the sofa
and me and the baby in the bed?
It's a way to go.
It's so late. I really
ought to put him down.
- May I?
- Yeah, if you want to.
You're short.
Your belly button
sticks out too far.
And you're a terrible
burden on your poor mother.
You find anything at Dana's?
Nothing but mood some slime
residue around the bathtub.
But I did get something on that
Vigo character you mentioned.
Found it in Magicians, Martyrs
and Madmen. Dig that.
Vigo the Carpathian,
born 1505, died 1610.
105 years old. He hung
in there, didn't he?
He didn't die of old age, either.
He was poisoned, stabbed, shot,
hung, stretched, disembowelled,
drawn and quartered.
Ouch.
- I guess he wasn't too popular.
- Not exactly a man of the people.
Also known as Vigo the
Cruel, Vigo the Torturer,
Vigo the Despised and
Vigo the Unholy.
Wasn't he also Vigo the Butch?
And dig this. There was a prophecy.
Just before his head died,
his last words were:
"Death is but a door. Time is
but a window. I'll be back."
Let's suck in the guts, guys.
We're the Ghostbusters.
- Go! Go. Please, go. You. Yes, you.
- Who's this wiggler?
- He's yours, Ray. Sic him.
- I have...
Hi, how are you? Ray Stantz from
the Ghostbusters. Nice to see you.
Beautiful lab you have here. We're
just doing a routine spook check.
Dr. Venkman, Dana is not here.
- Yeah, we know that, Johnny.
- So why are you came?
Well, we got a report there was
a major creep in the area.
We checked our list, and
you were right on the top.
Johnny, where in the hell
are you from, anyway?
The Upper West Side.
The whole room's
extremely hot, Peter.
- Ew, that's one ugly dude.
- Hot?
Oh, that's Vigo. Mr. Vigo? Vigs,
would you look this way, please?
No, don't. No! No!
No photographs, please.
Slides are available
in the gift shop.
Yeah, thanks. Thank you, Winston.
All right. You know what?
Give me angry, will you?
Give me angry. You've had a bad day.
You're cranky. Yeah, thank you.
Good, good. Ooh, angrier.
I'm scared. You're scaring me.
Stop it. Yeah. Good!
Okay, walk for me, talk
for me. Yeah, yeah!
Okay, give me hot and sexy.
Can you do it? You can. Oh, boy.
Show me some teeth. Come on.
I bet the girls like you,
huh? Do the girls?
Do the guys? Bet they both do, huh?
What about the animals?
They like you? That's it, more!
Yeah, come on! You're big, you're big.
All right, destroy me. Destroy me!
Yeah! Destroy me.
Yeah, yeah! Give it, give it!
Venkman, we need to talk. Come on.
I've worked with better.
But not many. Thank you.
John, thanks.
- Hey. Hey, you finished?
- Yeah, I'm finished here.
- Are you all right?
- What?
I mean, you're not coming
down with something?
Me?
Dana. Your prince.
Oh, no.
Oh, no. Oh, no.
She cleaned.
- Hi.
Shh. He's asleep. Come here.
- So what happened with my apartment?
- Well,
the guys spent the
whole night there.
They went through all your
things, your personal stuff,
they tried on some of your clothes,
made some long-distance phone calls,
- cleaned out the fridge.
- Did they find anything?
They found a little bit
of that pink slime.
Oh, God. Well, what am
I supposed to do now?
You are supposed to get
dressed and get crazy with me
- on the streets of Manhattan.
- I don't think...
This is exactly what you need.
I have got you a babysitter.
- The whole thing's wired.
- I don't think we should go on a date.
You know, and I can't leave
Oscar in a strange place
with a strange person.
Strange person? Janine
Melnitz, from my staff.
Janine has experience babysitting?
Here.
Thank you.
I've also brought some
things from your apartment.
Some wardrobe choices. A couple
of provocative ensembles in here.
- I'll leave it up to you.
- Okay, but after dinner.
Don't put any of those old
cheap moves on me, okay?
- No, no, no.
- It's different.
I have all new cheap moves.
Hey, you. Hey, you.
It looks like you're awake,
huh? You're awake.
Yes, Osco.
You're gonna have the whole
place to yourself tonight, pal.
It's gonna be pretty neat.
I got some Laura Antonelli
tapes if you wanna watch them.
Dana, did you see some shirts here
- in the floor-bed area?
- Yeah, I put them in the hamper.
- I have a hamper?
- Yeah, it's in the bathroom.
Neat.
Will you tell me next time you're
gonna do that, though, please?
Well, I thought they were dirty.
I have more than two
grades of laundry, okay?
There's not just clean and dirty.
There are many subtle levels, okay?
You hang this outside the
window for 20 minutes,
it's perfectly fine.
Interesting role model
for you, Oscar, huh?
Well, they couldn't get to you
until after the New Year.
Well, just don't go in there.
Louis, I'm closing up!
Well, should I take the
subway or the surface roads?
- Or what? It's kind of busy...
- Well, I'm walking. Good night.
Well, now. Well,
well, hang on, now.
Do you maybe wanna...? No, no.
Do you wanna have
something to eat with me?
Well, yeah, I'd love that.
But I told Dr. Venkman
I'd babysit for him.
- Oh, well...
- Do you wanna babysit with me?
- Okay. I would.
- Great. His place at 8.
- Bye.
- His place at 8. All right.
- I can get his address from the W2...
- Hey, buddy. Move it!
We were right, Ray. Multi-planar
Kirlian emanations.
Yeah, well, here's your
next month's cover of GQ.
Check out the aura on this sucker.
Now, there's definitely
a living presence there.
We should get a deeper look.
Why don't I run this wider shot
through the spectral analyzer.
Good, I'll try turning
up the roentgens.
So, what do you think? Chinese?
- How about Thai?
- No, it's too spicy.
- Greek?
- Mexican?
- Pizza.
- Thin or thick?
Chicago.
What the hell is that?
I know what it is.
- I've seen it before.
- Where?
When you guys had me dangling
like a worm on a hook
a hundred feet below First Avenue.
That's the river of slime.
Ray.
We need a blanket or
a hose or something.
Get out.
Why is this closed?
Winston! Winston!
- Fire!
- Back away, back away.
What are we gonna do,
put our heads in the toilet?
Taxi!
Pete, it's great that you're here.
We've got incredible news.
Wait a minute. Can I have one try?
All-you-can-eat barbecue
rib night at the Sizzler?
No. We analyzed the
photos you took of Vigo.
The spectrogram shows a river
of slime flowing behind him.
Just like the one I saw underground. We're
going into the subway and sewer system
to see if we can trace
the source of the flow.
Yeah, come on. Change your
clothes. We'll wait for you.
Yeah, Egon thinks there might even
be a tremendous breeding surge
- in the cockroach population.
- Hi, boys. What's up?
Hi.
Dana, the guys are going down into
the sewer to check for slime stuff.
And Egon thinks there may even be
a huge surge in cockroach breeding.
Wanna blow off this dinner
thing and go with them?
Taxi!
Women, huh?
Will you watch your step?
I hate this.
According to this old transit map, there
should be an entrance along here somewhere.
I'm not getting anything yet.
Well, at least it's too dark
to see the cockroaches.
Forget about cockroaches. It's the
subway rats you gotta worry about.
Big as beavers.
Yeah, some of them go 4 or 5 kilos.
Hey, hey. Enough, all right?
Listen. You can hear
them behind the walls,
scratching. There must
be thousands of them.
- Just shut up about the rats.
- Okay, okay.
Hello!
Hey!
Winston.
Okay, I'm out of here.
They're gone.
What the...?
Before we go any further, I think
we should get our proton packs.
Good idea.
- What's that?
- What's what?
Sounds like a train.
Uh-uh. These lines have been
abandoned for 50 years.
Oh.
Probably in one of the
tunnels above us.
I don't know.
It sounds awfully close to me.
I think that was the old New
York Central, City of Albany.
Derailed in 1920, killed
hundreds of people.
Did you catch the number
on the locomotive?
Sorry. I missed it.
Something's trying to
stop us. We must be close.
Where's Ray?
- Ray?
- Ray!
- Ray.
Guys!
- What?
- Oh, sorry. I found it.
- Right here. There's a hole.
- Let's go.
Hey, fellas, what about the packs?
What about the packs?
Unbelievable.
Uh-huh. Did I tell you?
I wasn't lying, was I?
You know how much negative energy it must
have taken to generate a flow this size?
New York, what a town.
All right. Let's see
how deep it is.
- Get a sounding.
- Yeah.
All right, 6 feet.
- Twelve feet.
- Twelve?
- Something's pulling it.
- Hold on!
- Well, I'm trying to hold it.
- Ray, help him.
- Give me a hand. Give me a hand!
- Ray, help.
- It's got ahold of him.
- Get his belt off!
- I can't hold it!
- Wait, wait, hold...
A toast to the most charming,
- kindest...
- Oh, it's me.
It's you. And most unusual man
I've ever broken up with.
Speaking of breaking
up with neat guys,
- why did you dump me?
- I didn't dump you. I was
protecting myself.
I mean, you weren't very
good for me, you know.
You know that, don't you?
Heck, I'm not even good for me.
You're much better than you realize.
You don't give yourself enough credit.
I need to hear that kind of stuff.
If I had this kind of support
on a 24-hour-a-day basis,
I could whip myself into shape
by the end of this century.
Well, why don't you just give
me a jingle in the year 2000.
Why don't I give you
a jingle right now?
So the seven little dwarves had a limited
partnership in a small mining operation.
And one day a beautiful princess
came to live with them.
They bartered housekeeping services for
room and board. Which was a real good deal,
because they didn't have to withhold
social security or income tax or nothing.
Which you're really not supposed to do, you
see, but for the purposes of this story...
It really is a great place.
I mean, it needs a woman's touch,
but I think it looks really
good. You know...
Shh. Bedtime.
You're very good with children.
Thanks. I practiced on my hamster.
So you live alone?
I used to have a roommate,
but my mom moved to Florida.
Why don't you come over
here and sit with me.
Okay.
So you wanna play Boggle
or Super Mario Brothers?
You know...
I think motherhood's a
very natural instinct.
I'd like a child myself.
Would you?
Tonight?
Nice going. Ray.
What are you trying
to do, drown me?
Oh, Yeah, Zeddmore,
like it was my fault.
You were too stupid not
to drop that plumb line!
Stupid? You better watch your
mouth or I'll punch your lights out.
- Oh, yeah?
- Yeah!
- Well, anytime!
- Come on!
It's go time, man. I want you bad!
Come on!
Wait! Wait!
Stop, stop. Get your
clothes off, quick. Strip.
Oh, dear. Ray, what were we
doing? I was ready to kill you.
It's this stuff. It's like pure,
concentrated evil.
And it's all flowing
right to this spot.
- You sure this is it?
- Yeah, he said Armand's.
- Excuse me...
- It's all right. We'll look in the back.
Venkman!
Hey, Venkman!
Please leave. You cannot...
Get out of my restaurant!
It was absolutely incredible!
The greatest tangible evidence
of psychic energy in 100 years.
- You're disturbing our guests!
- This is an emergency. One second.
Boys, you're scaring the straights, okay?
Is there any way we can do this tomorrow?
No, this won't wait until tomorrow,
Venkman. It's hot and it's ready to pop.
- Yeah. It's all over the city, Pete.
- Under it, actually.
- Rivers of this stuff.
- It's all flowing right to the museum.
Yeah, the museum!
Look what he got all over me!
What is this stuff?
- Sorry.
- Oh, God. You mean my museum?
I was gonna tell you between the
dessert and the cheese course.
- There they are!
- You can never go back there.
- You're gonna have to find a new job.
- Psychomagnotheric plasma.
- It affects behavior. We were fighting.
- We were in a fight.
He had him by the throat...
I'm glad they're here.
We gotta see the mayor.
♪ Well, I guess we're gonna
Have to take control ♪
♪ We got, we got, we got ♪
♪ If it's up to us
We've got to take it home ♪
♪ Too hot to handle
Too cold to hold ♪♪
- Oh, Ghostbusters!
- How you doing?
Hey, guys, come right this way.
You guys got another one of those proton
packs? My kid brother really wants one.
- The proton pack is not a toy.
- I guess he's right.
Ah.
Dana, we were just
babysitting, honest.
And we watched some TV and had something to
eat and then and one thing led to another.
- I know what you were doing.
- I didn't know anything would happen.
Hi, Dana. How was your date?
- It wasn't a date, it was just dinner.
- Well, where's Peter?
He was arrested.
Typical.
- Did he call?
- No, no. Nobody called.
Well, how's Oscar? Is he all right?
Oh, he's fine. Such a good baby.
He was a little fussy at first,
then we just gave him
some French bread pizza,
passed right out.
Good. Good. Well, I'll
just give him a look-see.
- So you think we should go?
- Gee, I don't know.
I don't think we should
leave her alone.
You're right. Let's stay.
- Lenny! Big man!
- Ghostbusters.
Mr. Mayor.
What is this? A slumber party?
That's what we're
here to talk about.
Look, I don't wanna hear
anything about it.
You've got two minutes.
Make it good.
Well, first of all, Mr. Mayor, it's
a great pleasure to see you again.
We'd like to say that almost 50 percent
of us voted for you in the last election.
- I appreciate that.
- I'm just sorry we always meet
under these circumstances.
Mr. Mayor, we're here tonight because
a psychomagnotheric slime flow
of immense proportions is
building up beneath the city.
- Psycho-what?
- Psychomagnotheric.
- Big word.
- Negative human emotions
are materializing in the form of
a viscous, psychoreactive plasm
with explosive
supernormal potential.
Does anybody speak English here?
Yeah, Your Honor, what we're
trying to tell you is, like,
all the bad feelings, I mean,
all the hate, the anger and violence
of this city is turning
into this sludge.
I didn't believe it at first either,
but we just went for a swim in it,
and we ended up almost
killing each other.
This is insane! I mean, do we
really have to listen to this?
Can't you stop your lips from
flapping for two little minutes?
Lenny, have you been
out on the street lately?
Do you know how weird it is out there?
We've taken our own head count.
There seem to be 3 million
completely miserable assholes
- living in the Tri-State area.
- Oh, please.
I beg your pardon.
3 million and one.
What budgie-brain here doesn't realize
is that if we don't do something fast,
this whole place is gonna blow
like a frog on a hot plate.
- Yeah, right.
- What am I supposed to do?
Go on television and
tell 10 million people
they have to be nice to each other?
Being miserable and treating
other people like dirt
is every New Yorker's
God-given right.
Your two minutes are up.
Good night, gentlemen.
- Wait.
- You're making a mistake, Mr. Mayor.
A very newsworthy mistake. The
Times is gonna be interested in this,
- and you know The Post...
- Whoa, whoa, whoa. Now, now...
"Mayor Drowns in River of Slime."
- "Times Square Slime."
- "Slime Square."
Fine. Now, before you go running
off to the newspapers with this,
would you consider telling this slime
business to some of our people downtown?
It's gotta be done right away.
Well, it's gonna come back!
This city's in danger!
The whole state! The world!
- All we wanna do is help!
- I'm warning you.
The mayor wants them kept under strict
observation for the next few days.
We think they're seriously disturbed
and potentially dangerous.
- Well, we'll do whatever's necessary.
- Thank you, doctor.
I await the word of Vigo.
I, Vigo,
- the scourge of Carpathia,
- No, you told me this, the scourge.
- the sorrow of Moldavia,
- Sorrows, I've heard all of this, yes.
- command you.
- Command me, lord.
The season of evil begins with
the birth of the new year.
Good.
Bring me the child,
that I might live again.
Yes!
Lord Vigo...
I was wondering.
This woman, Dana,
is fine and strong.
Now...
if I was to
bring the baby,
could I have that woman?
So be it.
On this day of darkness,
she will be ours.
Wife to you and mother to me.
Yes!
Thank you, lord! Thank you.
- I mean, is she the killer or what?
- No, that's Rita Hayworth.
She was married to Citizen Kane
while they were doing this thing.
Right after they finished, she dumped
him for some polo player. Thanks.
I don't know why beautiful women love
horses so much. Do you love horses?
- No.
- You really don't have to stay.
I'm sure Peter will be back soon.
Oh, we don't mind.
Can you see okay?
Yep.
Oscar?
Oh, God!
Oscar!
Louis!
- What?
- It's Oscar!
- Oscar.
- Call 911 right now!
Oscar.
Oh, no.
Oh, God. No!
No!
- It was a ghost!
- No.
- No, that was Janosz.
- What?
- He took him.
- What? What's happening?
- What should we do?
- Where's the baby?
The museum!
- Where are you going?
- I've gotta get my baby!
We gotta find the guys.
As I explained before,
we think the spirit of a
17th-century Moldavian tyrant
is alive and well in a painting
at the Manhattan Museum of Art.
And are there any other paintings in
the museum with bad spirits in them?
You're wasting valuable time.
He's drawing strength from
a psychomagnotheric slime flow that's
been collecting under the city.
- Yes, tell me about the slime.
- It's very potent stuff.
We made a toaster dance with it.
And a bathtub tried to
eat his friend's baby.
A bathtub?
Don't look at me. I think these
people are completely nuts.
Oscar.
Sweetheart.
I thought I'd lost you, that
I'd never see you again.
Oh, baby.
Hello, Dana. I thought
that you might come.
You stay away from
us, Janosz. I mean it.
Oh, don't worry. He
will not be harmed.
He has been chosen
to be the vessel of
the spirit of Vigo.
And you will be the mother
of the ruler of the world.
Doesn't that sound nice?
No, it sounds ludicrous.
You stay away from him. I mean it.
Well, I don't think we have
choice here, yes? Take a look.
It's not Gainsborough's
Blue Boy there, huh?
He is Vigo.
I don't care who he is.
You're not gonna take my baby.
Oscar!
Oh, you bastard!
♪ All around the city ♪
♪ Everywhere I go ♪
♪ Something strange is happening ♪
♪ To everyone I know ♪
♪ Hear the voice of loneliness ♪
♪ Crying in the night ♪
♪ See the madness in their eyes ♪
♪ Dancing with delight ♪
♪ I want to know why ♪
♪ Everyone I know
Has gone flip city ♪
♪ You say it ain't true ♪
♪ What can I do now?
I'm going flip city ♪♪
Is this a big dinosaur
or a little dinosaur?
A skeleton? Which
way was it heading?
Wait a sec. What was
chasing you in the park?
The park bench was chasing you?
- I see.
- What?
Wait a second.
Lieutenant, I think you
better talk to this guy.
I'm busy here.
It's some dock supervisor
down at Pier 34.
What's the problem?
He says the Titanic just arrived.
Well, better late than never.
We're swamped. We've had more than
3000 calls since midnight last night.
We've got every man in uniform on
the streets and I'm still shorthanded.
We've got meter maids chasing
ghosts all over midtown.
There's this shell thing over the Manhattan
Museum of Art. We can't make a dent.
- Have you tried dynamite?
- We've tried everything.
What the hell's going on?
It's pandemonium out there.
- I know. We're working on it.
- Great. While you're working on it,
I'm going down in history as
the mayor who let New York
get sucked down into
the 10th level of hell.
All right. We've got no choice.
Call the Ghostbusters.
Wait!
Now, I'm sure there's another way.
Jack, I spent an hour last night in my
bedroom talking to Fiorello La Guardia,
and he's been dead for 40 years.
Now, where are the Ghostbusters?
They're not available.
What do you mean,
they're not available?
Well, I had them committed to the
psychiatric ward at Parkview Hospital.
- You what?
- They threatened to go to the press.
I was protecting your interests.
Yeah? Well, you can stop
protecting my interests.
You have exactly three minutes
to clear out. You're fired!
But the election...
- Remove this man.
- You're making a mistake.
- And get me the Ghostbusters!
- Mr. Mayor, come take a look at this.
Wow.
What is it?
Have you ever seen
anything like that?
Somebody get me the Ghostbusters.
Then he put the baby in a
carriage and then levitated away.
Where did Dana go?
She was going to the museum
to get the baby back.
Then there was an eclipse. The whole
town went dark and everybody's nuts.
It all fits. Vigo wants
in on the 21st century.
He needs a human body to
inhabit. Little Oscar must be it.
And I bet we're the
only ones who can help.
You bet we are.
♪ Well, I guess we're gonna
Have to take control ♪
♪ We got, we got, we got ♪
♪ If it's up to us
We've got to take it home ♪
♪ Too hot to handle
Too cold to hold ♪
♪ They're the Ghostbusters
And they're in control ♪
♪ Well, I guess we're gonna
Have to take control ♪
♪ Gotta, gotta take it home ♪
♪ If it's up to us
We've got to take it home ♪♪
it looks like a giant Jell-O mold.
I hate Jell-O.
Oh, come on. There's
always room for Jell-O.
Soon it will be midnight and the
city will be mine and Vigo's.
Well, mainly Vigo's.
Dana.
You and I have this terrific opportunity
to make the best of this relationship.
We don't have a relationship.
I know! Marry me, Dana.
Together we will raise
Vigo as our son.
And let me tell you something here.
There are many perks in being
the mother of a living god.
I'm sure we could get a
magnificent apartment,
a car, free parking.
Many marriages begin with a
certain amount of distance.
Yet I think that perhaps
you and I could learn...
to love each other?
Yes.
I could learn.
Pull them.
Full neutronas.
Let's cook!
Save them.
That slime wall is
pulsing with evil.
It would take a tremendous amount
of positive energy to crack that shell
and I seriously doubt that there's enough
goodwill left in this town to do it.
I just can't believe things have gotten so
bad in this city that there's no way back.
I mean, sure, it's dirty, it's
crowded, it's polluted, it's noisy,
and there's people all around who'd just
as soon step on your face as look at you.
But come on!
There gotta be a few sparks of sweet
humanity left in this burned-out burg.
We just have to figure
out a way to mobilize it.
He's right. We need something that everyone
in this town can get behind. We need...
A symbol.
Something that appeals to the
best in each and every one of us.
Something good.
Something decent.
Something pure.
Kind of makes you
wonder, doesn't it?
Wonder what?
Whether she's naked
under that toga.
She's French. You know that.
Got it.
Ready with the speakers,
Ray. Slime blowers ready.
Okay. Internal audio set.
Internal electric set.
Slime blower primed and set.
Ooh, good slime. Good slime. Winston,
is our slime in a good mood tonight?
I hope so. She's a lot
bigger than a toaster.
All yours, Venkman. Let's go.
Thank you. Testing,
one, two, testing.
Hey, how many of you people here
tonight are a national monument?
Would you raise your hand,
please. Oh, hello, miss.
- Let's frost it.
- It's slime time.
Beautiful.
Pilot controls are ready.
All right. It's getting late. It's
almost midnight. Let's go, Venkman.
Here's something off the request
line from Liberty Island!
We gonna squeeze some New
Year's juice from you, Big Apple.
- ♪ You know your love ♪
- ♪ Your love keeps lifting me ♪
- ♪ Keep on lifting me ♪
- ♪ Love keeps lifting me ♪
- ♪ Higher ♪
- ♪ Lifting me ♪
- ♪ Higher and higher ♪
- ♪ Higher ♪
- ♪ I said your love ♪
- ♪ Your love keeps lifting me ♪
♪ Love keeps lifting me ♪
- ♪ Lifting me ♪
- ♪ Higher and higher ♪
- ♪ Higher ♪
♪ Now once I was downhearted ♪
♪ Disappointment was
My closest friend ♪
Man, I can't wait to see people's
faces when we come onshore.
This should really get the city's
positive energy flowing.
Keep kicking, Libby.
You make this work,
we'll pop for a weekend in Vegas
with the Jolly Green Giant.
You look fantastic in this.
I was born to wear this stuff.
Boy, this equipment is heavy.
♪ I'm so glad I finally found you ♪
♪ Yes, that one in a million girl ♪
♪ And now with
My loving arms around you ♪
It's a love-fest, New York!
- Sing it out!
- Come on!
- ♪ I said your love ♪
- ♪ Your love keeps lifting me ♪
- ♪ Keep on lifting me ♪
- ♪ Love keeps lifting me ♪
- ♪ Higher ♪
- ♪ Lifting me ♪
- ♪ Higher and higher ♪
- ♪ Higher ♪
- ♪ I said your love ♪
- ♪ Your love keeps lifting me ♪
♪ Your love is lifting me higher ♪
Come on, you sing!
♪ I said your love ♪♪
- We're running out of time, Ray.
- Can't you go any faster?
I'm afraid the vibrations
will shake her to pieces.
- We should have padded her feet.
- They don't make Nikes in her size.
Don't worry. She's tough.
She's a harbor chick!
Sorry! My fault!
Happy New Year.
Stay fit. Keep sharp.
Make good decisions.
Oh, good. Oh, good. Oh, good.
Okay.
Oh, it's you.
Okay, but I didn't know
you had your license.
Four minutes to go, and then
party times.
It's happening.
It's really happening.
No. No!
Go away from here!
- I love you when you roughhouse!
- Hit it, Mama!
- Drop the hammer on her!
- Go! Do it now!
- Oscar, look.
- Go away!
- Don't know who that is?
- Happy New Year.
He's Vigo! You are like the
buzzing of flies to him!
Oh, Johnny, did you back the wrong
horse. Will you hose him, please?
Hose him.
- One down.
- On the ground.
- Boy, am I glad to see you.
- Oh, Oscar. Oscar.
Is he dead?
Uh-uh. This slime is
positively charged.
He'll wake up feeling
like a million bucks.
Whoa, this gentleman
is a little bit ripe.
That's all right, my friend.
I think I had an accident too.
Get him away!
Get a knife or something!
We gotta cut her out of this!
Okay.
All right. Now, listen. You
gotta stay right here.
Don't move. Uncle Pete's gotta
go help your mom for a second.
You stay here and don't
say anything, okay?
Uh-oh.
Hold it right there, deadhead!
You want a baby? Go ahead and
knock up some willing hellhound.
Otherwise, I'm giving you three to get
back in that painting where you belong.
One!
Two.
Three!
You got him! You got him!
That was really stupid.
Ray, can you move?
No. Are you okay?
No.
Venkman, how are you?
I'm fine.
No.
No! Oscar.
Please, do something!
Not so fast, Vigo!
Hey, Vigo!
Yeah, you. The bimbo with the baby.
Didn't anybody tell you the
big-shoulder look is out?
You know, I have met some
dumb blonds in my life,
but you take the taco, pal.
Only a Carpathian would
come back to life now
and choose New York.
Tasty pick, bonehead!
If you had brain one in that
huge melon on top of your neck,
you would be living the sweet life
out in Southern California's
beautiful San Fernando Valley.
Oh, darn it.
Now we become one.
- Where's that singing coming from?
- People outside.
Excuse me. Ghostbusters.
Wow.
I'm here with you, guys.
He's weakening! The singing
is neutralizing the slime!
I can move!
Oscar!
Oh, sweetie.
It's okay.
He's back in the painting!
All right, go find a shady spot.
Vigie, Vigie, Vigie. You
have been a bad monkey.
Ray, we'd like to shoot the monster.
Could you move, please?
- Ray.
No!
I, Ray and Vigo,
shall rule the Earth!
- Be gone, you pitiful half-men!
- Now!
- I did it! I did it!
- That was great!
- I'm a Ghostbuster!
- I loved it!
- You all right?
- Come on, get up. Let's get this off.
Here.
Here we go.
- How do you feel?
- Groovy.
- You all right?
- Yes. Thank you, Peter.
Spread out, shorty.
I love you guys.
- I love all you guys.
- Great, Ray.
- And I love Venkman.
- Uh-huh. Let's go.
- We gotta live with this?
- Real friendship.
Yeah.
Sir, are you all right?
Why am I drippings with goo?
You had a violent, prolonged,
transformative psychic episode.
Sorry we had to hose you there, but
you were kind of out of control.
Hey, man,
let me tell you something.
I love you.
- Yes?
- Yeah.
Well, I love you too.
Wow.
Hey, fellas.
You wanna take a look at this?
Wow.
Early Renaissance, I think.
Raphael or Piero della Francesca.
No, I believe it's one
of the Fettuccines.
♪ if there's something strange
In your neighborhood ♪
♪ Who you gonna call? ♪
♪ Ghostbusters ♪
♪ if there's something weird
And it don't look good ♪
♪ Who you gonna call? ♪
♪ Ghostbusters ♪
♪ I ain't afraid of no ghost ♪
♪ I ain't afraid of no ghost ♪♪
♪ If you want something done
You gotta do it yourself ♪
♪ Too hot to handle
Too cold to hold ♪
♪ They're called the Ghostbusters
And they're in control ♪
♪ Had 'em throwing a party
For a bunch of children ♪
♪ While all the while
Slime was under the buildin' ♪
♪ So they packed up their group
Got a grip, came equipped ♪
♪ Grabbed their proton packs
On their back and they split ♪
♪ Found out about Vigo
The master of evil ♪
♪ Try to battle my boys?
That's not legal ♪
♪ If I was you and you were me
You'd wanna be winning ♪
♪ If you want something bad, yo
You gotta wanna give your all ♪
♪ 'Cause I believe so much in we
And no we're not kidding ♪
♪ If you feel the same as me, yo
You gotta wanna take the ball ♪
♪ Now I found out
That nothing is given ♪
♪ Don't know where
The cards may fall ♪
♪ All I know is
That we've gotta get it ♪
♪ We've gotta make it On our own ♪
♪ Well, I guess we're gonna
Have to take control ♪
♪ We got, we got, we got ♪
♪ If it's up to us
We've got to take it home ♪
♪ Too hot to handle
Too cold to hold ♪
♪ They're the Ghostbusters
And they're in control ♪
♪ Well, I guess we're gonna
Have to take control ♪
♪ Gotta, gotta take it home ♪
♪ If it's up to us
We've got to take it home ♪
♪ Gotta, gotta take it home ♪
♪ Gotta, gotta, gotta
Take it home ♪♪
♪ Spirit, some people hear it
Some people fear it I
♪ Spirit, some people
Just won't go near it ♪
♪ Sure as I'm me
And you should know that you ♪
♪ The spirit is the key
To unlock the true you ♪
♪ Spirit, some people hear it
Some people fear it ♪
♪ Spirit, some people
Just won't go near it ♪
♪ Sure as I'm me
And the skies are blue ♪
♪ The Ghostbusters are back
And all brand new, come on ♪
♪ Warm it up
Say what? ♪
♪ D, D, D Check it ♪
♪ Now that evil's presence
Make it pleasant in ♪
♪ Every resident
And take a mother's ♪
♪ Newborn baby
And Dana's the lady ♪
♪ To build an establishment ♪
♪ For an evil magician on a mission
In the pitching position ♪
♪ And no condition
Will stop him on the transition ♪
♪ Of making it in time
With the help of the slime ♪
♪ But somebody
Gotta draw the line ♪
♪ Who stand for all
Who you gonna call for the brawl? ♪
- ♪ Ghostbusters ♪
- ♪ It's like that, y'all ♪
♪ Ghostbusters ♪
♪ It's like that, y'all ♪
- ♪ Ghostbusters, Ghostbusters ♪
- ♪ Are back, are back ♪
- ♪ Ghostbusters ♪
- ♪ It's like that, y'all, hit it ♪
♪ Spirit, some people hear it
Some people fear it ♪
♪ Spirit, some people
Just won't go near it ♪
♪ Sure as I'm me
And you should know that you ♪
♪ The spirit is the key
To unlock the true you ♪
♪ Spirit, some people hear it
Some people fear it ♪
♪ Spirit, some people
Just won't go near it ♪
♪ Sure as I'm me
And the skies are blue ♪
♪ The Ghostbusters are back
And all brand new, come on ♪♪
♪ You find yourself
Caught up in a silly game ♪
- ♪ That's child's play ♪
- ♪ Don't play me out ♪
♪ The world depends
On every little move we make ♪
- ♪ It's serious ♪
- ♪ Cold serious ♪
♪ Now the time has come
For all good to glow ♪
♪ And overthrow the bad ♪
♪ We're here to make a change
So all can be free ♪
♪ A call has been made
And we ♪
♪ We're back ♪
♪ Oh, we're back ♪
♪ Back to fight the evil ♪
♪ We will never deceive you ♪
♪ Working hard ♪
♪ To try to fight
The evil plague, yeah ♪
♪ But I've come too late ♪
♪ Nothing get in the way ♪
♪ Now the time has come
For all good to glow ♪
♪ And overthrow the bad ♪
♪ We're here to make a change
So all can be free ♪
♪ A call has been made
And we ♪
- ♪ We're back ♪
- ♪ Oh, we're back ♪
♪ We're back to fight the evil ♪
♪ We will never deceive you ♪
- ♪ Oh, we're back ♪
- ♪ We're back ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ We're back to fight the evil ♪
- ♪ We will never deceive you ♪
- ♪ Oh, we're back ♪♪
♪ Ghostbusters ♪
♪ Something strange going on
Something's wrong ♪
♪ Gloom in the room
Outside is the storm ♪
♪ All alone in the crib
Watching the tube ♪
♪ Yo, is that what I did?
Did I see something move? ♪
♪ Chills down your spine
Your heart fills with fright ♪
♪ Not filled by the things
That go bump in the night ♪
♪ Walk through the wall
With no time to stall ♪
♪ You call the Ghostbusters
Well, that's who you call ♪
♪ Ghostbusters ♪
♪ We ain't, we ain't
We ain't afraid of no ghost ♪
♪ Ghostbusters ♪
♪ We ain't, we ain't
We ain't afraid of no ghost ♪
♪ Ghostbusters ♪
♪ Stop, bridge, hit it ♪
♪ I ain't, I ain't, I ain't ♪
♪ I ain't afraid of no ghost ♪
♪ I ain't afraid of no ghost ♪♪
Watch Movies, TV Series and Live Sports
Signup Here -> WWW.ADMITME.APP