Watch Movies, TV Series and Live Sports
Signup Here -> WWW.ADMITME.APP
It all started with
a small immigrant family.
That's me, Alex Danyliuk.
And that's my mom and dad,
Mr. and Mrs. Danyliuk.
We left Ukraine
in search of a new life.
- Welcome to Canada.
- Thank you.
We couldn't afford
to live in the city,
so we ended up in London...
London, Ontario.
Of course, like most hopeful
immigrants, we found ourselves a house
- that we couldn't
actually pay for...
so things got worse.
Mom and dad started
arguing a lot more.
But eventually a Russian
friend of the family
helped mom get a job as a
bookkeeper's assistant at a bank.
Please leave a message.
Mr. and Mrs. Danyliuk,
we're calling about
- your overdue payments
on your line of credit.
Please give us a call.
Don't touch anything.
But dad wasn't of much use.
He tried, but people
didn't trust him.
So we basically
lived on welfare.
Everything my mom earned
went to pay off the mortgage.
I didn't have any friends to
play with or socialize with
except my mom's computer, and, to
be honest, we got along very well.
I'm talking Internet,
video games, forums,
chat rooms with random
strangers, all sorts of sites,
easy access to information,
and infinite possibilities.
It was this that made me
want to go to college.
I wanted to follow in the footsteps
of Steve Jobs and Bill Gates
and one day change the world
for the better.
Fortunately, or unfortunately,
I learned early on that I needed to
save up money for school myself.
My very first dollars.
My job was being a clicker.
I'd build up traffic to sites
by changing my ip address
and visiting the same site
over and over again.
It was boring,
but it was easy money.
For every 1,000 clicks,
I made $20.
It wasn't a lot, but all big
things have small beginnings.
Time went by, and I wanted to learn
more about how the world worked,
especially the money world.
The Internet was full of ideas and
opinions about the banking system,
the financial crisis, the
vulnerability of the system,
and about the need for change.
But some things
just never changed.
So that's how I grew up.
As you can see,
it wasn't a fairy tale,
but I was hoping
that would change.
Just a coffee, please.
Yesterday,
a cyber-attack
was perpetrated on a number
of government sites and banks.
Responsibility for this attack
was claimed by Darkweb,
an online criminal organization
led by a hacker named zed.
Now, he is considered to be
an international criminal
implicated in dozens of cases
around the world.
Now, this video was uploaded
claiming that responsibility.
We are Darkweb.
We will not stand by and allow slave
masters to control our lives.
We will fight back. We will bring them
down. This is just the beginning.
And in other news, the stock market has
been unstable due to these attacks.
Mom, I'm home.
Mom?
Hey, hey, hey. What's wrong?
What's wrong, huh?
Okay, now, mom, that's bullshit.
That bank owns the mortgage, and
now they know that I'm unemployed
and I can't pay monthly bills.
We will lose the house.
Okay. Well,
what did dad say?
Dad... he's asleep.
Okay. Okay, mom.
What is this?
This is money.
All right, this'll last you
for a few months, and then
after that, I can get more.
Where did you get this?
Did you steal it?
No, no, no.
I didn't steal it.
I been saving up for college.
But how? You never told us,
and... where did you get this?
Mom, okay, that doesn't matter.
What matters is we're
not going to lose the house.
I can't take it.
You need to pay for school.
Look, mom, please, okay,
I'm an adult.
Okay, I can...
I can get a job.
I can... I can make this back,
but, please, take it.
What will I say to dad?
Tell him the truth.
Thoughts were
rushing through my head.
Why? For what?
I hated the bank
that fired my mom.
Even if the bank had
a hundred reasons,
I still fucking hated them.
I spent years saving up
that money.
I put down a deposit for school, and
now I risked losing everything.
I had to start over.
I didn't have years to spend.
I needed something faster, but the
Internet was just full of scams.
And then,
I remembered something.
Darkweb was this online hacker group that
was getting a lot of news at the time.
I was surprised that their site
hadn't been shut down.
It all seemed
kind of simple at first.
I just needed to make
an account and sign up.
But real access wasn't
given out so easily.
"Soldier"?
They told me
to do something illegal,
like stealing a person's
credit card number,
and that was how
they verified the rookies.
To me, this seemed simple,
but I needed a victim,
and I had an idea.
- There was
this one guy at school
who really had it coming,
Randy Bickle.
Whoo! Maybe next time,
watch where you're going.
What's your problem, man?
What did you just say to me,
Dostoyevsky?
I said why don't you pick on
somebody your own size, huh?
You want to go? Huh?
You want to go?
Huh? Huh?
Yeah, next time, asshole.
What a dumb-ass.
I built a pretty simple site
that sold fake supplements,
and Randy fell for it.
He used his dad's credit card,
and it had a lot of money on it.
Dad! Can I use your credit card?
Yes.
I leaked the information to
Darkweb, and before I knew it,
one of their guys was
communicating with me.
This guy who called himself
Roosevelt gave me low-level access.
In reality, it was more of
a job, black market trading.
His prices were much lower
than market value,
and this made it easy
to find buyers.
First time around, he sent me a
couple of powerful gaming laptops,
and I just had to sell them,
so I went on Craigslist
and found a buyer.
This guy was a small-town gamer
who liked to play for money,
but I didn't care who he was.
Most importantly, he had
the cash that I needed.
I'd never made this much money
at once.
I sent Roosevelt his cut and
bought myself a new laptop.
In other words,
I was in business,
and I liked it a lot.
Roosevelt kept sending me
things, and I kept selling 'em
and making the money
that I needed.
The products were always
something simple
phones, jewelry,
watches, laptops...
- easy to carry,
easy money.
But there were other ways
of making money, too.
Forums that kept a list of
vulnerable online shopping sites,
and they were easy
to break into.
I didn't want
to cross that line,
but these companies
had insurance,
so there really
wasn't too much damage.
I pulled a few hundred credit
cards and sold them on Darkweb.
I would have used these cards myself,
but I needed fake I.D.S to match them,
so I was happy to get
whatever I could for them.
Took me four years
to save up 30 grand.
This time, I did it in four
weeks, and now I was ready.
So I'll call you guys
when I get there.
Be careful.
All right.
And I'm going to be sending
you guys money every month,
so... spend some time together.
Look after each other.
I left my parents behind and
took the bus to the big city.
I wasn't sure if I'd made
the right decision,
but it was too late to go back.
It was pretty cool
to move to Toronto.
Everything was bigger.
Welcome to your new home,
Mr. Sawyer.
The building has 24-hour
security, has a shared rooftop.
There's a loading dock
around the back.
You've got all brand-new
stainless steel appliances,
floor-to-ceiling windows.
The neighborhood is absolutely
up-and-coming.
There's not much more
you could get.
Do you have any questions?
Yeah, how do I connect
to the Internet?
Unfortunately,
my payment was late,
and the university said I could
only start in January.
That meant I needed money
to live.
I'd made enough money
for Roosevelt
that he increased
my access on Darkweb.
I could now buy credit card
numbers and fake I.D.S
and use 'em for online shopping.
Next station
is St. George.
- I'm expecting a package.
- Okay.
Yeah. Let me check it out.
Yeah, this should be it.
Okay.
Just sign right there.
Sure.
And there we go,
Mr. Munchausen.
Thank you.
Can you take me to Chinatown?
But things weren't so simple.
I couldn't use Craigslist
to find buyers in the city.
Too many cops and fakes,
so I tried my luck
with a few pawnshops
and jewelry stores.
Hey.
You... you speak English, yeah?
I... I have watches.
Okay?
I want to sell them.
Do you want to buy them?
Look, these are real...
These are real watches, okay?
This cost... this cost $15,000.
I sell for... for ten.
- Thousand?
- Yes.
- W-what's that?
- No, no, no. Look, look.
See, these are real watch,
too, okay?
I sell these to you
for 200 bucks.
Ten. Ten. I got...
There's three watches.
- Now ten.
Hey, wait.
- Hey.
- What can I do for you?
Says here you purchased these three
days ago. How come you're selling 'em?
I... you know, I just
didn't want 'em anymore.
I can't. I lost the card that
I used to purchase 'em, so...
Well, wait for
a replacement card.
I mean, surely it's worth the wait
rather than losing money on the resale.
Look, do you want to buy them,
or do you not?
Okay. Mr... Munchausen...
We're going to need two pieces
of I.D. And a proof of address.
Bank statement is fine.
Then we're going to get you
to sign a form
stating that
these were not stolen,
at which point,
we'll review your application.
If everything checks out,
then you can come back,
and we'll make the purchase.
- You can't just buy 'em now?
- Sorry.
You know, I can drop the price,
by another thousand.
Hey, you know, don't worry about it.
I'll just... I'll keep them for now.
Sure.
You having a rough day?
Sorry. Do I know you?
Sye.
Hey, I just wanted to talk
to you about your watches.
No, no, no.
I'm not a cop.
I just might want
to buy your watches.
Yeah, what do you want
to talk about?
Look, if it'll help,
I'll give you five grand
for all of 'em.
I'm not an idiot.
Thirty grand.
Seven.
All right, tell you what.
I go in there.
I sell 'em for at least 30,000.
I take 30 percent off the top.
All right, but you get the money
today, huh. Otherwise...
Otherwise, you take
your watches and go.
Hey, look, the watches
are stolen anyway, right?
So what do you got to lose?
- All right. Yeah.
- Yeah, all right. Let's go.
Hey, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Wait. Wait.
I go in alone, all right?
Hey, Christopher!
Look who it is.
How you doing, buddy boy?
What the hell?
Aw, you dick.
That's rude.
Come on.
Walk with me.
What happened back there?
What? Exactly what I said
I was going to do...
No, you disappeared, though.
Yeah, I went out
the back door. Here.
You didn't tell me you were
going to go out the back door.
What's this?
$24,500 in very dirty 20s.
Well, it would have taken a while
to get fifties and hundreds.
But you sold my watches
for 35,000?
Receipt's in the bag.
See, now you don't strike me as some student
who has very expensive taste in watches,
and you don't seem like a thief, so I'm
thinking to myself, "who is this kid?"
How'd you do that so fast?
I'll tell you
if you tell me how
you got those watches.
Hey, hey, don't worry.
It's all in there.
I promise.
Okay.
Yeah.
And that was how I met sye.
And you want to approach
every buyer differently.
I know that sounds simple,
but it is important,
because you say the wrong thing,
you could lose credibility.
You know, you could get
blacklisted real quick.
You don't want to do that.
You're still working
in these conditions, eh?
I mean, it takes a lot of
strength to do what you guys do.
You should give yourselves
a pat on the back.
You guys are troopers. And you
know who else shares my opinion?
Your wives, your parents,
your sons and daughters,
and I think that you should
be able to call them.
Now, you ever use one of these?
But if you can put yourself
in the shoes of the buyer,
whew, you're gold.
Thank you very much.
And then there are also people, you
know, sometimes people in high places
that you... you don't
think are on the market,
and they're not until you find
them something they like.
All right, what we have for you gentlemen,
nothing short of extraordinary.
So we got monochrome
LCD display, USB interface,
20 megabytes of built-in memory.
It's got an electronic compass.
More importantly, your friends
will be really impressed
as to how you actually
got your hands on 'em, so...
Who'd you steal from this time?
I know someone works
for the watch company.
I'm getting 'em
for a good price.
How many have you got?
Two for you.
Eight for your friends.
Yeah, we'll take 'em.
Now then,
there's your longtime buyer.
Now, you always got
to make them happy.
You got to keep
bringing 'em stuff,
because trust is the most important
commodity in this business, all right?
Takes a long time to build, but
you can lose it just like that.
What's up?
- Hey, I'm Chris, by the way.
- Hi.
So what can I do for you?
Boom.
In just a couple months,
we made about 60 grand.
That's your half.
I sent some money to my parents
and saved the rest,
the criminal mastermind behind last
night's cyber-attack on the world bank
has claimed responsibility for
what he calls an act of justice.
But authorities say the breach
in security was substantial.
The banks of this world have
enslaved their citizens
and then quietly stand back and let the people
suffer under the weight of their debts.
That is not the fault
of the people.
It is the manufactured sin
of the bank.
A drug addict makes a mistake,
but the drug dealer
commits the crime.
Banks and bankers,
watch your backs.
Darkweb is coming after you.
I thought about these words
and realized a university life
wasn't for me.
Hey.
If you... if you haven't
bought all your books yet,
these'll save you a few bucks.
So I called up sye and asked
him for help with another job.
I told him I wanted
to try something bigger,
forums had a blacklist of corrupt
bankers who were going to get punished,
but we needed to get
into their wallets,
'cause their online information
was highly protected.
Hey, sweetie.
I think I got some friends
that could help.
You know, I'm sure
it'll surprise you,
but the single most important
people that I get to know,
people in the service industry.
Anybody that knows anybody,
right,
those are the people who are going
to help you get to the people
that are staying there at the
hotel or at the restaurant.
These are the people
that you need to know.
Like I said, these
bankers were all corrupt.
Darkweb wanted to punish them, so I wanted
to pitch in to fight for the cause.
Nobody knew that I was doing
it, and that was the point.
-We were anonymous.
- Just got another one. I'm going
to send it to you. -Nice.
And of course I couldn't have
done it without sye.
He knew a lot of people
in a lot of different places.
Hey, Chavez.
How you doing, man?
Boys!
Oh, Robin, come to me,
you saucy little minx, you.
Mwah. Mwah.
Where have you been all my life?
Well, you never
come around anymore.
Thought you started
playing for the other team.
Very funny.
Robin, this is my friend, Alex.
Alex has never been
to a strip club before.
You're not missing anything,
sweetie.
So remember that fat-cat banker
I was talking to you about?
Yeah, yeah, yeah. He comes in
here all the time, so no problem.
I'll get one of the girls
to work him.
So, I have something else
for you.
This guy comes in last night.
He's with a bunch of people.
They're throwing money around.
Think he was Colombian.
Anyways, everything was fine.
The girls were making money.
But then he tried to force himself on
one of the girls, so I stepped in.
Anyways, he left his card here.
None of us were so keen
on giving it back to him,
- so there you go.
- Hmm.
Holy shit, that's an infinity.
What does that mean?
Means it's got a shitload
of money on it.
We can use it at stores.
Knock yourselves out, boys.
Wait. Whoa! How much
money you want for it?
Nothing!
It's a gift.
Just make sure you punish
that asshole.
I love you.
I love her.
- No.
- What?
We can't take money off that
card. It's too dangerous.
What are you talking about?
I wasn't even...
All right, look, man.
It is easy money.
You said so yourself. It's got a
shit-ton of money on it, right?
- Yeah, but...
- So why don't we...
So what's $20,000, $30,000
to this guy, huh?
So we'll just, you know,
get a fake I.D.,
put on a disguise,
go the bank, boom.
And then we will never
touch it again.
I promise.
I should be the one
going in there.
I look way more Colombian
than you do.
Just don't stress me out, man.
Come on.
Well, maybe you're right.
Maybe this isn't a good idea.
What if the guy already
reported the card stolen?
I'm already checking.
What? What are you doing?
I'm using the card
to buy a song.
It only costs 99 cents,
but if it works,
that means we know
the card's still working.
Okay, done. It works.
All right, you sure
you want to do this?
All right, now you got to be
confident, all right?
Don't mess with your clothes. Just
act like you belong, all right?
- Okay. -This rental
was really expensive.
- You better make it worth it.
- I got it, I got it.
All right. No pressure.
Go, go, go, go!
Drive! Drive!
What happened?!
Relax. We're in the money.
Whoo!
♪ I see you bringing it ♪
♪ making that ass
and swinging it ♪
♪ I'm the queen bee
come in stinging ♪
♪ take it out
and turn it round ♪
♪ drop that feeling
get on track ♪
♪ to my manic Mac attack ♪
♪ take it out
but don't fall back ♪
♪ pick me up ♪
♪ down, down, down... ♪
Sye loved to party, but
that wasn't really my thing.
It only made me wonder what the
hell I was doing with my life.
And then I found something
very interesting.
The bank that fired my mom and
owned the mortgage on our house
ended up on the vulnerable list.
I remembered my mom's tears,
and I wanted to find a way
to kick them in the balls.
They'd never know it's me,
but again, that was the point.
Hey, sye, you think you could
help me with a job?
I want to cause a little chaos
in the bank,
and I want to do something
that'll disrupt their system,
stall 'em for weeks, something
that'll make them close their doors.
Sounds good, but I don't get it.
Where are we making our money?
Oh, it's not always
about the money, sye.
All right, this time,
it's about payback.
What do you need me to do?
Well...
You look good.
Confidence.
- Not too confident.
- Yep. Yep.
Remember, confidence.
I'll go into the bank
and pretend to be a new client.
I've already been inside,
so I know where I need to sit.
Just before lunch, I'll go in as
though I'm asking for a loan.
The only thing is I need
to chat up this banker girl.
And that's where you come in.
Hi. Can I help you?
- Can you do a British accent?
- Uh... probably.
- If you can, do a British accent.
- Why?
Chicks love it.
She'll fall for it on the spot.
- You sure?
- Works every time, mate.
I'd like to inquire about a
loan for a small business.
Oh, okay. So that would be
a commercial loan.
- Do you have an account
with us already? -No.
Okay, so we have a couple
of different products
I can talk to you about. So, why don't
I get some basic information from you.
You know what I just noticed? You have the
most beautifully symmetrical facial features.
It's really...
You'd be great in movies.
- Oh. -Actually, I have
a director friend
who would be happy to audition
you for his next film.
- Oh.
- Just crossed my mind, you know?
Okay. Can I get
your name from you?
Yeah, sure. Yeah.
I'm so sorry.
- No, that's okay. Don't worry about it.
- No, no, no.
- Really have a lot of pens.
- Sorry.
- That's fine.
Why don't I try
to open an account for you?
- Sure. -Let me just,
uh, type the date in.
Oh. That's strange.
Oh, that's weird.
There seems to be a problem.
Something wrong?
There's a problem here.
Um...
That is strange.
Don't know what that's
all about.
Looks like it's lunchtime
for you, so I might...
I can go, and I can
come back later.
Yeah, that sounds
like a good idea.
Good luck.
Carol.
Carol, there's something wrong.
There's...
And then, once I'm done,
I'm going to quietly walk out of
the bank and head to the car,
and no one will suspect a thing.
- Sir. Excuse me, sir.
- -Fuck.
Excuse me.
Can you come with us?
What's wrong?
We have a small security issue.
Oh, that's terrible.
What kind of security issue?
Won't take very long.
Please, come with us.
Hey! Hey!
Excuse me!
Excuse me! Officer!
Alex and sye...
I appreciate your Patience.
I'm head of security
at this bank.
Oh, actually, sye,
you can leave. Thank you.
I think I'm going
to stay with my friend.
Yeah, absolutely not.
Sye, it's okay.
I got this.
Yeah, it's okay.
Um-hmm.
Ah, that's a pretty cool
little thing you got here.
Did you make it yourself?
I'm not saying anything
without a lawyer.
Well, first of all, you don't have a
lawyer, and you can't afford one.
Secondly, I'm not the police,
so you can open
right up with me.
Did you make this yourself?
I wrote the software.
Ah. Not bad for a young kid.
Where'd you get it?
Online.
Where online?
We're going to charge you
with breaking and entering,
Cyberterrorism, and conspiracy to commit
credit card fraud on the federal level.
You're looking at five to ten
years in prison,
and you will not be allowed to touch another
computer again for the rest of your life.
I mean, of course unless you want to
tell me where you... you bought this.
Fine. Then I will
call the police.
Hey, sir, can I ask your name?
Curtis. Yeah.
Is that your... is that your
first or your last name?
Both.
Okay, Mr. Curtis,
can you...
Can put the phone down
for a second, please?
You have exactly one minute.
Look, this was just a prank, okay?
I wasn't trying to...
I wasn't trying
to steal anything.
Your security system is awful.
Firewall's outdated.
The software that I created
was able to put a virus
in the system very easily.
I mean, it doesn't look good
for you if an 18-year-old
was able to break in to the bank
and steal all this information.
I mean, bank like this
should be more secure.
Okay.
Okay, what... what I'm
suggesting is, uh,
you let me upgrade
the software for free.
You can tell everyone that, you
know, that you had a security test
and you brought me in
to fix the problem.
Bank'll look bulletproof, your
bosses will be thanking you,
and in exchange, all I ask is that you let
my friend and I just walk out of here,
and we can all pretend like
none of this ever happened.
Does that seem... fair?
What the hell happened in there? Why'd
they let you go? What'd you tell 'em?
I told them I wouldn't do it
again. They let me go.
Wait. That's all you said?
Yeah. Thought you'd be happy.
Just seems a little bit
too easy. That's all.
I wanted to punish
this bank, and I failed.
But some people
didn't see it that way.
Someone leaked information
on Darkweb,
and everyone knew it was me.
At first, I was worried
that I'd get in trouble,
but apparently people
were impressed.
Even the head
of Darkweb noticed.
No way. Sye. Sye.
Sye, wake up, man.
Hey.
Look at this.
I just got a like from zed.
You like who?
No, no, zed,
the guy I told you about.
He just sent me a like.
Look at that.
I'm happy for you.
I'd never gotten this
kind of attention before.
Apparently, what I did
was pretty ballsy,
'cause I actually went
into the bank,
whereas most break-ins
happen remotely.
That's why he noticed me.
Dude, you're famous.
Huh? What...
Hey, what are you doing, man?
I just got you... a date.
What the hell?
What? She wants to
meet up with you.
She said she's got some ideas
on how you guys can work
together. Cute, right?
What, you set me up on, like,
a date with a random stranger?
I mean, we got to lay low, man.
No, you need to get laid.
I mean come on.
What's the worst
that could happen?
So you're Kira, huh?
Yeah, but it's not my real name.
Where are you from?
I don't give out
my personal information.
Okay. Then what are we
supposed to talk about?
Where are you from?
I'm from London.
I don't hear an accent.
London, Ontario.
Really? That sucks.
Thank you. Thanks.
Um... so when's
your birthday?
It's the 23rd of June, 1993.
See? You're an idiot.
Excuse me?
I know your name, where you're
from, and your birth date.
With that information, I could steal
your identity and ruin your life.
It'd be a shame for someone
like you to go down like that.
Someone like me?
I mean, you might as well tell me what your
mother's maiden name is or her occupation.
She doesn't have one.
- That's rough.
- Yeah, but she's...
She's tied to our house with,
you know, mortgage by the bank
that fired her little while ago,
and they know she couldn't even
afford it if she had the job.
They say the drug addict makes the mistake,
but the drug dealer commits the crime.
Did you just quote zed?
Yeah, I did.
Do you follow him?
Well, yeah, doesn't everybody?
No. Most people are in it
for the money.
Huh.
So, have you met him?
Um, I almost met him.
"Almost"?
What does that mean?
If you want to meet zed,
you have to do something big.
Are you going to answer that?
Yeah. Sorry.
Yeah.
Are you banging her yet?
I...
No, hey, I'm just kidding.
I'm just kidding. Just kidding.
Listen. I've got an idea.
Uh-huh. Okay, what is it?
What if we ask if she wants
to work with us?
Okay.
No, you sure that's a good idea?
I mean, we just met her.
I mean, all that shit she was
writing me on the computer
about credit card printers
and Bitcoins.
I mean, no offense, but she
knows more than you do,
and if we're going
to keep growing, get bigger,
girl can always help. I mean,
alone, we're just two dudes,
but she can be a girlfriend,
a distraction, a decoy.
Look, listen.
You trust me, right?
Just ask her if she wants
to work with us.
All right. Yeah.
I'll call you back, all right?
Hey, hey, ask her.
- So...
- I was thinking...
All right, you go.
I mean, I was just wondering if you
were working with anybody right now.
That's funny, because I was going to
ask if you wanted to work together.
Ah.
We got pretty
carried away with Kira.
First thing she did was make us
buy a credit card printer.
I have a couple thousand blank
cards I picked up in Thailand.
We can stamp them in here and
sell them on the Darkweb,
or we can use them in stores,
and this is how we can get
credit card information.
We used our old crew
to get the credit card numbers,
and we'd print the duplicates,
hide them in magazines,
and ship them to buyers
all around the world.
Then she got us using Bitcoins.
This was digital currency that
was pretty much untraceable,
and people used it to pay us
for the credit cards.
Then she introduced me
to onion browsing.
Apparently, you could buy an atom bomb
on there, and no one could trace it.
Address. I can type it in
again here.
And then she proved to be
useful in a very practical way.
Like it, sweetie?
Uh-hmm.
We'll take it. Thank you.
Kira basically upgraded us.
She managed to find targets
with much bigger wallets.
That's how we were able to
afford big, expensive toys.
We went from online carding
to real carding.
Why do you keep taking
the pictures?
My clients need to know
what I'm selling.
Having fun? Great.
When do I get to buy something?
Finding right car is like
finding the right woman.
You want to get inside her
several times a day,
show her off to your friends,
but never let them touch her.
- Then you've come to the right place.
- Ah.
It just all depends how much you
want to spend on the wedding.
Oh, depends. What kind of girl?
Italian.
Ah.
You like her, boss?
Never been kissed.
When it came time to sell,
Kira was surprisingly good.
Wow.
I sold the watches.
That's great.
Why didn't you let us know?
Just wanted to take
some initiative.
That's awesome.
That is awesome.
Oh, and I found someone
to buy the diamond ring.
She used a social media site called Mobli
to advertise our products to her buyers.
We were very impressed.
But we suspected she was
working with someone.
Of course sye wasn't very happy
about this new arrangement.
After all, he usually did
all the selling.
Where do you find these guys?
My uncle helped me. I usually
give him a piece of my cut.
Then we're going to have to meet him
if he's going to be working with us.
Well, he really just works with me,
so we don't have to include him.
As long as that's okay
with you guys.
Shouldn't be a problem.
You don't mind, right, sye?
I don't, Alex.
I don't mind at all.
You all right, man?
- Yeah. Yeah, I'm fine.
- Yeah?
It seems like something's
bugging you.
Look, if you don't want to work
with her, we don't have to.
I don't know.
Just seems like she has all these
buyers that don't even haggle with her.
I mean, how the fuck does
she know these people?
- She fucking 'em?
- Or her uncle's helping her.
Okay. Then why does
she need us, huh?
She seems to be doing
just fine on her own.
My gut's telling me
something's up here.
Maybe your gut's gotten a little jealous
'cause she can do what you can do.
You're joking, right?
I don't know. I mean, it
just seems like
you're a little off
on this one, you know?
Hoo! And they gave me
a ten percent tip.
Why? What,
you give 'em a tug?
Dude, don't be like that.
I think we should move
to Hong Kong.
Why? What's in Hong Kong?
Well, remember I told you there's
a lot of action happening there.
I think you and I could do
really well there if we tried.
Seriously.
Hong Kong is the place to be
for people like us right now.
Sye could keep running
some deals here,
but you and I should go.
If only for a little while.
I can't just get up and go,
especially without sye.
He's like my best friend.
Can't just leave him here.
Well, think about it.
- Hey. -This better be
fucking important.
Roosevelt.
It's nice to...
Nice to finally meet you.
Make it fast, kid.
I don't have all day.
Yeah. You know,
I just wanted to...
I wanted to say
thank you and, uh...
You know, meet you
in person, obviously.
That's what you asked me
out here for?
Well, you know, it's...
I think it's important...
Okay, well, you know,
you brought me in.
You, you know,
here you gave me a shot.
That's my token of gratitude.
How much is it?
It's five grand.
Pretty nice of you.
But I heard that you been...
Can I get a fucking
coffee here?!
I hear you been going
to the stores. Why?
Well, I can make
more money that way.
Oh, that tastes like shit.
And I wanted to find out if you
knew about a girl named Kira.
Yeah, she's a lieutenant.
No, i... no, I never heard of her.
Why? Do you want to fuck her?
No. No, no, no.
I just... I was curious.
Well, if I haven't heard of her,
then she's probably no good.
Anyway, I think we're done here.
Well, no. Do you know
how I can meet zed?
You know zed?
You a cop?
No, of course I'm not a cop.
Don't ask stupid
fucking questions.
This is a fucking stupid idea.
You need to relax, pal.
Who the fuck are you to tell me
to relax? And I'm not your pal.
Jesus. You've been
with us a few weeks,
and you think you can
tell us what to do?
I'm not telling you what to do.
I'm just saying if
we don't do this right,
it's going to take forever
to get rid of all this stuff.
I think it's pretty logical.
No, no, no, no, no.
What's logical is to stay small,
keep pushing smaller loads,
and then when it's time, grow
bigger and push larger ones.
That's exactly what we're doing.
We're growing, so keep up.
Alex, you better step in, or I
am gonna tip this truck over,
and she's gonna kill herself when she hits the
ground and I fall on her face with my ass!
You know, you need
to calm down, okay?
Oh, are you fucking
serious right now?
You're making everybody tense.
You're fucking supposed
to be tense.
Look, it's a dumb idea
walking into this meeting.
How do you know?
'Cause they're buying
a shitload,
and unlike miss fancy-pants,
we don't know
who the fuck they are.
Why does that matter,
though? They're buying.
It matters because...
Ah, god. Jesus, Alex.
You're not thinking. All right?
Look, we got a good thing
going here, man.
I don't want to screw it up.
All right, I been watching her.
Something's not right.
I can't put my finger on it.
It's on me, okay,
'cause I brought her in,
but I'm telling you that fucking girl
is putting us under too much risk.
We'll go in. We'll
evaluate the situation.
If we can't, it won't matter because we
can just sell them all individually.
Huh?
- It's not...
- Alex!
Everything looks good.
We'd be happy to make a deal.
Well, of course I
share your opinion.
It looks good, and I would
love to make a deal.
But I'd like to know,
what's your real commitment?
Honestly, how many of these things
do you want to buy today, hmm?
A few? Half? How many?
'Cause our principle of business
is based on trust,
because without trust,
you can't have business.
And, of course,
I want to become trustworthy,
so I don't want you to feel like
you got to buy everything today.
You know, you're welcome to just take a
few pieces and then come back for more.
Actually, no.
My partner's mistaken.
There is no negotiating here.
Either you buy everything
in that truck,
or we walk and find
another buyer.
That's our deal.
- Take it, or leave it.
- What the fuck are you doing?
I'm selling, because clearly you're
not man enough to do it yourself.
This is the biggest deal we've ever had.
I'm not gonna let you ruin this.
Why don't you just back off and
let the adults deal with this?
Because you're about to ruin this deal
with that fat little mouth of yours.
What makes you feel like
you can talk to me like that?
I'm protecting my interests. My money paid
for the stuff just as much as yours did.
Where do you find these guys?
Not a single one of them seems to know
who you are, so where'd you find 'em?
Sye, it's her uncle, all right?
It's fine.
- Just let her handle it.
- Oh, god, this fucking uncle.
What are you, taking her side?
No, hey, hey, hey.
She brings in these sketchy-ass buyers
who, as far as we know, might be cops.
- The buyers are not cops.
- How the fuck do you know, huh?!
God, you're always so
fucking sure of yourself.
You need to calm the fuck down.
All you ever do is talk!
Yeah, I'll talk all I want to,
sweetheart,
'cause I been doing this
a lot longer than you have.
Okay, why don't we
just make a deal, guys?
No, there's not gonna be a deal
with this fucking girl here!
- Is there a problem here?
- No. There's no problem...
Whoa, whoa, whoa,
whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa!
Okay, look, we don't want
any trouble, okay?
So let's just make the deal.
No deal.
Okay, that's fine.
All right.
All right. We'll go.
Stop being pussies.
We are making this deal
right now.
You are gonna buy
everything in that truck...
All right, sye, Kira, I need you to
just shut the fuck up right now, okay?
It's fine. No deal.
You walk. We'll walk.
We can make a deal another time,
okay?
Deal is off the table
for good now.
If we ever see you again, if you
deal with anyone that we know,
we will not be as pleasant
as we were today.
Let's go.
That was pleasant?
- Good job, sye.
- Fuck off!
You have to be
so up in his face?
These are my contacts.
You guys are ruining all of my contacts.
What a waste of my time.
Fuck!
That was a fucking mess.
You guys either need
to get along,
or we all go our separate ways,
'cause I don't want to get shot,
and I'm pretty sure
you guys don't either.
So, sye, you got to relax.
I mean, if she thinks
she can handle something,
you got to give her
a chance, man.
Sorry.
Yeah, whatever.
Sye.
Fine. I'm sorry.
There's cops at our truck.
We got to get out of here.
That was really close.
Why'd he just leave like that?
Who cares? He's gone.
Okay, guys, I been thinking
about what happened today,
and I think it's a sign
for us to move somewhere else.
He's right.
Those buyers could
actually come after us.
They're all mobbed up.
All mobbed up?
You hooked us up
with mobbed-up buyers?
That doesn't matter anymore, because
we're going to get out of the city.
Okay, then where are we
going to go?
How 'bout Hong Kong?
So Hong Kong
became our new home.
We'd made a ton of money,
so we decided to enjoy it
a little bit.
This is nice.
Yeah, it's beautiful.
Eh, it's all right.
Seriously?
What? It's a fucking
hotel room.
Going to go find the minibar.
We also got ourselves
a brand-new car
and a quiet place
where we could work.
Here we kept all of our gear
and our money.
And after everything
that happened,
we hoped that things would calm
down and we'd move up in the world.
At least,
I had hoped they would.
Thank you.
Me Gusta.
Here, our volumes got bigger.
We bought more,
we sold more,
and for higher prices.
But it was all the same shit,
watches, jewelry, computers, phones.
It didn't feel like we were
doing anything special.
I like them.
We'll take it.
All of them.
Great. Thank you.
I want you to appreciate the quality of
the product that I'm bringing to you.
How much, all?
Two hundred.
For you.
It felt like we were
just making money.
We had no purpose.
We weren't moving forward.
Please have her sign here.
We even started getting sloppy.
Anytime we used the card,
we always did
a test purchase online
to make sure the card
wasn't blocked,
but we had hundreds
of credit cards,
and it was hard
to keep track of them,
so we got ourselves a pick-up.
I'm... sorry, sir.
Go, go, go, go, go, go, go!
A pick-up was when
a card would get canceled,
and if a duplicate was used,
the terminal would recognize
that it's a fake
and would warn the cashier
to hold the card
and call the cops.
We took that risk whenever
we didn't test the card.
Like I said, we were just
making money, a lot of it,
and the trouble with that is
money doesn't change people.
It reveals them.
And I got to see a side of sye
that I'd never seen before.
Jeez, would you quit
with the computer already?
We still get buyers off Mobli.
I feel like we're not
getting anywhere.
We're doing the exact same shit
we were doing in Toronto.
It's getting kind of boring,
don't you think?
It's not like we're sending anyone
a message or hurting the system.
We're just making money.
So what do you want to do?
I don't know. We just got to...
We got to step our game up.
We got to do something that's
big, something that'll hurt.
Well, zed prides himself
on being a visionary.
He knows that to send
a message to the system,
you have to talk in terms of dollars
and cents, because money is power.
If we can figure out a way
to make money and cause chaos,
we can finally get
his attention.
Okay, so how do we do it?
- What if we try...
Guys, we should be celebrating!
Celebrating what, failure?
It's my birthday.
Ah.
So what do you think?
I can't believe we forgot
his birthday.
We gotta get him something.
No, Alex,
I was talking about the ATM's.
That's my girl, not yours.
She doesn't want to be with you.
I paid for her the whole night.
I paid her three times as much,
so fuck off!
You can't afford her anymore.
Oh, shit.
Excuse me. One side.
Sye!
Calm down, buddy!
Calm down! Calm down!
Shut the fuck up!
I'm sorry, man.
Hey.
Look, I know.
I fucked up.
Okay.
I get it.
Andrew Smith.
Eric Dupere.
Come out.
What happened?
What's going on?
My uncle.
Where's sye?
I don't know. He was
gone when I woke up.
Listen, I think I have what
we've been looking for.
Yeah, what's that?
- ATM's.
- What do you mean, "ATM's"?
So, banks keep physical cash
in vaults,
safety-deposit boxes,
and ATM's.
- Okay. -Wire fraud gets
covered by insurance,
but if we knock a physical location, then
it's a question of security and reputation,
that's amazing. Why have we been wasting
our time with all the other shit?
Check it. Check it.
Check it.
You like?
How did you get that?
I did what I'm good at. I bought
some things. I sold some things.
Don't say I don't got it
anymore. I still got it.
And it's also an apology
for yesterday.
- That's a nice job, man.
- Yeah, way to go.
Oh, and for old times' sake,
look what card I used.
- You fucking serious, sye?
- What?
You went out, used this fucking
card? Are you out of your mind?
What's your problem?
Well, for one, where's your
fucking disguise, sye?
Don't worry about it.
It's not a big deal.
- I wore my sunglasses.
- Sunglasses. That's great.
The problem is that we took
money from this card, sye!
You can't just go out and use it
without a fucking disguise!
Do you not know
they can find us?!
Jesus, I was just
trying to help.
Just like you helped yesterday,
got us thrown in jail, huh?
I already told you I was sorry.
What more do you want from me?
Nothing. I don't want anything
from you anymore. You know why?
'Cause you been acting
like a dick lately.
You've been fucking
everything up.
You don't trust Kira.
You're drunk all the time.
And now you've gone
and used the fucking card
that I specifically told you
not to use again, sye!
I think you should just go.
Just go back to Toronto, huh?
Is this coming from her?
Did she tell you to say this?
She didn't say shit.
This is me, sye.
This is me asking you to leave.
'Cause while you're here, we're
gonna get fucking locked up
or we're gonna fucking die!
So you should just...
Just take your cut and go, huh.
Okay.
I'll pack my bags.
I left my ids in the drawer.
Good luck with everything.
You know, this used to be fun.
Oh, fuck.
What the fuck did I just do?
Oh, shit.
234 Tak man street.
Now let's try the ATM...
18 Kierna Waiden road.
5052 ma hang road. It's busy,
but you can take a lot.
That's the last one.
I'm out.
$2.3 million was stolen across
various ATM's in Hong Kong.
Authorities are at a loss, as
no one knows how this happened,
but we do have confirmation that a
notorious cybercriminal organization
has claimed responsibility.
Darkweb, the online mafia
controlled by international
fugitive zed,
left their business cards
at the scene of the crime.
Was committed by Darkweb,
and we won't stop
until we find the people
responsible for the citizens...
To causing a little chaos.
World banks now fear for
the safety of their assets.
So we should probably pack up
and get out of here tomorrow.
Whole city'll be looking for us.
Yeah.
Everything okay?
Yeah, I'm fine.
Hey, come on. Look at me.
What's on your mind?
I want to get out.
That's what we're doing.
We're leaving.
No, I mean I don't want
to do this anymore.
I want to disappear.
Disappear? Where?
Anywhere. Let's just go.
With this money,
if we invest it,
we don't have to worry about
anything ever again.
Are you fucking serious
right now?
Don't swear at me.
Okay, look, I'm sorry,
but that's fucking stupid,
all right?
You just want... you want to
leave all this behind
and go live a boring
old life, huh?
Would it really be that boring
if it was just the two of us?
Yes. What the fuck
would we do?
We would relax, enjoy life.
But for how long?
Are you Cr...
I mean, you're the one who said
we got to cause chaos
and make some money.
Yeah, well, now that we've done that, I
think maybe we should relax for a minute.
Fuck that. Why do you want
to leave? What's changed?
I had a different plan for my life,
and now it's just different.
Okay, well, you know,
I appreciate that,
but i...
I can't just drop this.
I mean, my parents almost lost everything
'cause of those fucking banks.
I'm going to punish all of them.
Those fuckers don't deserve
to sit in their chairs
and rip people off every...
Oh, my god. It's zed.
It's done.
You have no idea what you're
getting yourself into.
Okay. I don't...
I don't fucking understand you.
You're the one who said we
needed to get zed's attention.
Yeah, I'm in Hong Kong.
Yeah, there's two of us.
Yeah.
Kira's plan had worked.
Zed noticed us
and arranged a meeting
off the island of Hong Kong.
But the man behind the Darkweb
mask was very different
to what I'd imagined in my head.
Get out of the car.
Leave your stuff.
He's going to search you.
So what brings you to Hong Kong?
Well, we...
We almost got caught in Toronto.
We got tired of that, so Kira
suggested we move here.
Why would you suggest that?
Because Hong Kong is the place
to be for people like us.
Also we heard that maybe
you'd be out here, too.
We wanted to meet you.
You wanted to meet me?
What made you think that you
would even get my attention?
We had a plan that could
bring in a lot of money.
Oh. Well, I don't care
about money,
but I understand
that many people do.
So, why do you need me?
Oh, we need a lot of resources.
The plan wouldn't work
without you.
Okay.
Then after you tell me,
why do I need you?
'Cause we know how
to get this job done.
I would have people
to do that for me,
hmm, more than likely
even better.
Well, sir, I believe you
to be a man of principle,
so if I bring you an idea
and you like it,
I can only hope that you'll let
me see it through to the end.
Well, before you tell me what
you're about to tell me...
I need you to understand
who I am.
I am not your friend.
I'm not your boss.
I am your owner.
If you work for me,
you'll become my property,
and if you do your job right,
you could have
anything you want.
But if you make a mistake,
you will die.
And so will your families and
so will all your friends.
So, if you want to hold the ax,
you make sure to cut off
the head clean.
Because with me,
there won't be any mistakes.
So why didn't you say
anything in there, huh?
There's no limit
to what he can do.
What the hell?
Got a missed call from sye.
Hey, Alex, it's me.
I'm just...
I'm really sorry about the...
The way that things went down,
and I just...
I been thinking a lot,
and I just really want a chance
to make it up to you and Kira,
just go back to the way
that things were.
So, I came back to the hotel,
and I'm here right now,
and I'm just going to wait for
you till you get back, so...
Oh, maybe that's you right now.
What... just wait.
Wait, wait, wait. Wait.
He's at the hotel.
Really?
Yeah.
Sounds like he's feeling better.
Maybe we should go talk to him.
Maybe we should.
Sye?
Sye.
Sye! S...
Fuck!
I'm gonna call
the cops. I'll call the cops.
Alex, you cannot call the cops.
- I'll call the ambulance. They
can do something! -Alex...
- No, they can't, Alex.
- They'll come and help him!
- There's no helping him!
- We can't leave him, Kira!
- There's no helping him right now, Alex.
- Fuck you!
- I'm gonna call the ambulance!
- Give me the phone!
- Fuck you!
- Give me the phone.
Ow! Stop!
Stop! Get out...
We have to get out of here!
Stop! Please!
The Colombian man who left his credit
card at the strip club in Toronto
he missed the first transaction, but
he was ready for the second one.
If sye hadn't come back...
Kira and I would have been dead.
There's a team waiting for you.
They'll do whatever
you ask them to.
I heard about what
happened to your friend,
and I understand
this must be hard for you,
but I want you to say
to yourself,
"I will still get
this fucking job done."
I'm still going to get
this fucking job done.
Listen, I think
after all this is done,
we should find
a place to hide out.
Yeah, I agree.
We should go back to Toronto.
No. We need to go
as far away as possible.
I have an idea as to where
we should meet.
You know, ever since the banks started
to suffer these cyber-attacks,
the market has been shaky.
Fortunately, the federal reserve chairman
started to put more money into the economy,
and things have started
to stabilize.
Better housing, less taxes,
more money for you,
more money for me,
more money for all of us.
Where were you?
Just using my phone.
We're 15 away.
- Are you sure, sir? -Yes,
I'm sure, Mr. Dimayo.
Sir, each of these stock options
might not cost a lot right now,
but they're going to expire in half
an hour, and they will be worthless.
You see, by opening up
these positions,
you're betting that the market
is essentially going to crash.
I just want you to understand
that, you know, my job...
Your job is to do
exactly as I tell you,
and if I tell you to open,
you will fucking open.
They'll be up on your screen
once we fill the orders.
- I can't do this.
- No, no, no, no.
Look, look.
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey.
What are these kids doing?
Get back to your seats.
I think we should walk away.
What are you talking about?
Things are not right here.
It's going to go badly.
Guys.
It's not going to go well.
They're almost there, guys.
I need you here, okay?
No, Alex, you don't
need me here.
You can do this yourself.
Okay, fine, fine.
I want you here.
They're pulling up
to the building.
All right, look, I don't want
to do this without you.
Okay, after this, we can go.
We can do whatever you want to do, but
now I really would like you here.
It's not that simple.
Kira, please, come on.
Guys, we really need you
here right now.
Guys, here we go.
Sir, sir, can you comment
on the current market situation?
Can we be expecting any
market corrections, perhaps?
No comment.
- For bringing the market
back onto its feet...
Fuck, yeah!
Are they ready?
- Yes, sir.
- Begin.
We're just getting
a breaking news alert.
We have some live breaking news.
We have a shot for you.
There's been an incident with the
chairman of the federal reserve.
Tragic situation, and of course
this is affecting the state
and the entire country
as we wait with bated breath.
No confirmation on
if he has been killed.
He was rushed to hospital.
The chairman of the federal
reserve has just been shot
outside the federal reserve
building.
We have no idea where...
We have a report that the chairman of
the federal reserve has been shot.
It is unconfirmed whether
or not he has been killed.
Is this thing
actually happening?
Good god.
Well, of course, yes.
Unload everything.
Yes, everything!
Just do it!
Bloody yanks.
Sir, from the looks of it,
there will probably be
an investigation.
Pull the positions.
Send the rest of the money
to these accounts.
Twenty percent to Alex, and the
rest you can divide up equally.
Sir, maybe we should wait until
Monday so that the sec...
Just do it. Remember, oz,
money doesn't change anybody.
It only reveals them.
Let's see what our friend
does with his money.
- Need to get out of here.
- Yeah. Just one more second.
That's for sye, asshole.
Is what? Hold on. Sir!
News says you've been killed.
Hello.
What the hell are you
talking about?
How can I be dead
if I'm talking to you?
And that's the closing bell.
After today's tragic incident,
the market witnessed a nosedive,
and by the looks of it,
the sec has ordered a stop
on all trading accounts
until further notice.
It's unclear what this means
for the economy,
but we can expect the fallout
to last for a while.
- Hey, Alex. Time's up.
- What's going on?
No. Alex!
You bastards! Alex!
Where is Kira?
What have you done with her?
Hey, fuck you!
Fuck you!
Where is Kira?
We're just going to sit here?
Is that what's happening?
Yeah.
Let's go.
Who was that?
That your mom?
You inviting her to the party?
Quiet.
Hey, hey, what are you doing?
What the fuck?!
Uh... JFK as fast
as possible, please.
I need to use your phone,
please.
The number you have called
is not assigned.
Both Kira's and zed's
phones were disconnected.
How was that possible?
Who set us up?
Who were those guys that
kidnapped me, zed's people?
I didn't know,
and I didn't know what to do.
I had to go and meet Kira in the one place
where she said no one would ever find us.
Here, I felt cut off
from the rest of the world.
I was alone,
and everything
was stacked against me.
Kira and I agreed that
if anything happened,
we'd meet at noon at the temple of
dawn two days after the operation.
So I had to wait.
And in that moment,
I remembered my parents.
I had completely
forgotten about them.
We are unavailable to take your call.
Please leave a message.
Hey, mom, dad.
It's me, Alex.
I'm sorry I haven't called.
I'm sorry I kind of disappeared.
I'm going to be home
in a few days. I promise.
Yeah, I miss you.
Okay, bye.
Alex. Alex!
- Cell phone. Hey, guy.
- Yeah?
- Phone?
- Oh, yeah.
- Yes, BlackBerry.
- No, cheaper.
- Something cheaper.
- Cheap?
- Yeah, yeah, yeah.
- It's cheap. 1,000 baht.
- Half. 500 baht.
- No.
- No?
- 600 baht.
- Okay. 600.
- Yeah.
- Yeah. Thank you.
- Thank you.
- Good luck.
Thank you.
Can I have a single, please?
Can I have your passport,
please?
Yeah, yeah.
Do you have Internet?
- The Internet doesn't work.
- No? Okay.
- Your key.
- Thank you. Thanks.
I waited and waited for her,
but she never showed up.
Now I really felt alone again.
No friends, no family, no one.
Excuse me.
What time is it?
- Sorry?
- What time is it?
Oh. Uh... 12:15.
Thank you. Thanks.
Excuse me.
What time is it?
Uh, ten-to-three.
Okay. Thank you.
I was lost.
I didn't know what I was doing.
I didn't know where to go,
but I had a weird feeling
in my stomach.
Something was off.
Hi. I need to
use the Internet.
Okay. You pay first.
Yeah. Yeah.
You take card, right?
You go there, number five.
On the left.
- Number five. Oh, yeah.
- The left.
Yeah, left.
Days after the staged account on the
chairman of the federal reserve,
the stock markets are finally
up and running again.
The authorities apprehended those
responsible for the attack.
The notorious computer hacker
zed has been taken into custody
and will be charged with over
five dozen counts of wire fraud,
as well as charges of insider
trading, tax evasion, and terrorism.
The authorities have also shed light on
zed's partner in crime, Kira Whittal.
Now, she's been with zed's
outfit from the very start.
She was shot dead while attempting
to flee from federal agents.
Police were compelled to use deadly
force when Whittal opened fire.
How was that possible?
And finally, a third conspirator
was arrested this morning.
A Colombian businessman known
as Alfonso Regalo
was apprehended when it was found that
his money financed the operation.
No, she couldn't be dead. She must
have left a clue for me on her page.
Mobli. Okay.
Excuse me.
I'm not connected.
Can you reconnect me, please?
- Can you connect...
- Hey, you.
Your passport. You.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
- Five minutes.
Five more minutes.
No, no, it's very important.
Just go and press the button.
- No! -Five minutes. What's "five
minutes" in Thai? Please.
- Please come with us.
- I just need to talk to...
- I just need to talk
to somebody.
No, no, no. Please, no, no, no.
You don't understand.
Somebody...
I need five minutes.
Five minutes. Five...
I need to talk to somebody!
I just need five
fucking minutes!
Can you please
give me five minutes?!
No, no, no, no, no.
Listen. Just listen.
If you'd just hear me out.
Please. Come on.
You understand English?
Can you stop for a second,
please?
I just need five minutes.
Can you come back, please?
I just need five minutes
on the Internet! I...
I'd hoped that Kira was still
alive and that she'd find me.
With every day that went by,
I lost hope.
I've been asking for a while
now, and I really...
I wouldn't mind... I really wouldn't mind
if I could just have... just five minutes.
Five minutes is...
Is not a very long time!
Five minutes on the Internet!
How fucking hard can it be?!
How many times
do I have to ask?!
I can fucking hear you!
I can hear you walking around!
Can you at least say something?!
Just say, "no"! Tell me no,
but don't fucking say nothing!
Hey!
- And then...
- Help me.
I resigned myself to it.
I accepted the fact
that I was alone.
My parents,
sye, Darkweb, Kira, zed,
it was all so far away
and so long ago.
Back then, I wanted to change
the world for the better,
but now my world was dead.
So I decided to just
give up on life.
But life wasn't ready
to give up on me.
I decided to stop living in the
past and just decided to live.
Even if I lived like a caged
animal, I was still alive.
I realized that by the time
I was 21 years old,
I'd caused a lot of harm
to a lot of people,
that I was responsible for the
death of the people I loved.
Everything had changed,
all the chaos,
the conspiracies, my beliefs.
It was all different.
But I guess there was always that
one thing that never changed.
It killed me to know that
she'd sit and wait for me,
and I'd never show up.
I missed my parents.
I wanted to see them so badly.
I wanted to hug them like
I'd never hugged them before.
I wanted to sit down and
talk to them about nothing.
I just wanted to be near them,
because they know who I am.
I was done pretending
to be someone else.
I just wanted
to be myself again.
And then, after two years,
I was released.
I could hardly believe it, 'cause I
was released under my fake name,
but the important thing was...
Furlong, you're free to go.
I was free,
and I was finally ready
to go home.
- Hi.
- Hello.
How are you here?
You're obviously very good
at what you do,
so if you'd like to get out of here
early and have a clean record...
We have a job for you.
What the hell happened in there? Why'd
they let you go? What'd you tell 'em?
I told 'em I wouldn't
do it again. They let me go.
Just a little bit too easy.
We have a guy we think
can get us closer to him.
- He's young.
- So are you.
We'll give him a way
to get him interested in you.
What do you know about
the New York stock exchange?
You're going to
help him make money,
and we're going
to organize everything.
And if anyone ever
gets suspicious,
you just refer to me
as your uncle.
Where do you find these guys?
My uncle helped me.
Then you're gonna need
to get him to Hong Kong.
Hong Kong is the place to be
for people like us.
What if he doesn't fall for it?
We'll scare him into leaving.
I've been thinking about
what happened today,
and I think it's a sign for us
to move somewhere else.
Once you're there, you'll need
to push the ATM operation on him
so that zed notices you.
I was talking about the ATM's.
And we will always be
nearby if something goes wrong.
What happened? What's going on?
My uncle.
What do you mean you
don't think he can do it?!
Are you falling for him
or something?
I had a different plan
for my life,
and now it's just different.
Oh, my god. It's zed.
All we'll need is a paper trail that
shows that he financed the operation
and that he knew about
the market collapse.
We'll get him on
insider trading and fraud.
I need a clean out
for me and Alex.
I will not do this if it means
him getting arrested.
Do you understand me?
Sure, but...
You can never see him again.
Fine.
Where were you?
Just using my phone.
I wasn't lying when I said
we had to get
as far away as possible.
I was going to meet you there
and tell you everything,
but I didn't know that they had
other plans for me.
Zed's partner
in crime, Kira Whittal,
was shot dead while attempting
to flee from federal agents.
No. Alex! You bastards!
Alex!
As soon as I got out,
I went looking for you.
I knew the passport you had, so
it wasn't hard to track you down,
but took me a while
to get you out.
I wish I could have
sent you a note.
I wish I could have told you
that I was coming,
but I couldn't risk it, in case they were
watching, so I had to wait till today.
Why didn't you just tell me?
I tried.
No, you didn't.
You lied to me.
You know... I never
really lied to you.
I just didn't tell you
the whole truth.
So, what are you doing here?
Can I give you a ride home?
Might have some trouble
crossing the border.
Not if you use
your real passport.
You okay to drive?
Um-hmm.
In the end,
I got a chance to start over,
live an honest life,
and make an honest living.
And, Kira, well,
I was just happy she was alive.
Watch Movies, TV Series and Live Sports
Signup Here -> WWW.ADMITME.APP