Watch Movies, TV Series and Live Sports
Signup Here -> WWW.ADMITME.APP
Push!
Oh, God, it's coming!
No!
Please, give him to me.
Please.
No. Please, my baby.
Please, give him to me.
Damn you!
When Michael Myers was six years old,
he stabbed his sister to death.
For years he was locked up,
locked away in Smith's Grove Sanitarium.
But he escaped.
And suddenly...
Halloween was another word for mayhem.
He needed to wipe out his entire family.
He struck them down at night,
and always on Halloween.
The police tried
everything to stop him.
He overcame them all
and disappeared.
The world thought him dead,
But I... I wasn't sure.
I wasn't sure that
Michael Myers had died.
Jamie, come to me.
Jamie...
Come with me if you
want to save your baby.
- Oh, God... He's coming.
- We've got to move, now.
Come on.
No! Oh, God.
It's okay!
You can do it.
There!
It's that way!
Go, now. Save your baby! Go now!
Jamie?
Hey!
What are you doing in my truck?
Run!
What the hell're you doing in my truck?
What?
Run!
Danny. Danny.
- Kill for him.
- Mommy!
Danny?
Mommy's here.
What is it, baby?
The Voiceman. He's here.
- No one's there, sweetheart.
- But I've seen him.
You've been watching way
too much TV, you know that?
He says things. Bad things.
Like what?
Okay.
Stay away monsters,
stay away ghouls.
Stay away from Danny,
you jerks know the rules.
Better? Here.
Good night, Danny.
Good night, mom.
It's "Back Talk" with Barry Simms.
Who is that guy?
We're in the second hour of a special Halloween
edition of "Back Talk". I'm Barry Simms.
As usual, we're coming
to you live from
high atop the Sears
Tower here in Chicago.
Tomorrow night, we will be
coming to you from Haddonfield,
the town that has banned
Halloween since 1989,
when infamous serial killer Michael Myers,
his niece, Jamie Lloyd, and about a
dozen cops were killed in an explosion.
We have a caller waiting.
Who's next to talk to me?
I... I know this may sound crazy, Barry, but...
I really think I'm in love with him.
He's so untamed, so uninhibited.
He's everything I've ever wanted in a man.
You know, this is good.
I can see the tabloids now.
"Psycho Lays Nympho:
The Best Sex He Ever Dismembers"
Is this the type that you always fall for, lady?
Any other serial studs on the list?
You know, Bundy, Manson?
What about that Dahmer guy? I bet...
- I bet you could really cook with him.
- No, I just want Michael.
I... I wanna know what's behind that mask.
Deep down, I think he's
just like you and me, Barry.
He just needs someone
to understand him.
- Someone to love him.
- Yeah, deep down I'm sure that's true.
You're talking about one of this
nation's most notorious serial killers
like he belongs in some
kind of sex seminar.
You know, I hate to be the one
to break the news to you, lady,
but Michael Myers has
been dead for six years.
Now...
we've got someone who actually
claims to have seen that Michael Myers.
- Does this wacko caller have a name?
- My name's Tommy.
I was only eight years old, when I saw him.
But I was one of the lucky ones.
I survived.
There is help out there
for people like you.
It's called electro-shock therapy!
Come on. You don't really believe
that Michael Myers is actually alive.
Michael's work isn't done in Haddonfield.
And soon...
Very soon...
He'll come home...
To kill again.
But this time I'll be ready.
Actually, Tom, I hear Smith's Grove is
having a blue light on Vicodin; check that out.
The lines are open, so
give me your best shot
at 1-800-968-7825.
Now, Dwayne.
What's on your feeble excuse
for a mind tonight, Dwayne?
I'd just like to say that I listen
to your show every night, Barry.
I think you're the best.
I can't tell you how excited we are
that you'll be paying a little visit
to our little town tomorrow night.
So do you have a point
to make here, Dwayne,
or should I just keep
spanking the monkey?
Barry, you're too much.
I'd just like to say that I
understand how things
have changed in the 90's.
Gays in the military,
cut off your husband's dick
and become a national hero.
I just can't see any sense in
bringing Halloween back to Haddonfield.
Wink, wink. Thank you, Dwayne.
You may leave me now.
Next caller.
I say it's about time they had
a Halloween revival in this town.
Now my kids can
stop driving me crazy.
That maniac's either
long dead or long gone.
Either way, I say let's bury this
sucker and get the party started.
Party, woo-hoo!
Beer! Yeah!
Thank you, Ashley.
Barry, what happened to that
psychiatrist of his, Loomis?
I heard the old quack was dead.
Not dead. Just very much retired.
- Good God. Terence. Come in.
- Christ, what a night.
Not even so much as a sign
for five miles on that road!
That's the beauty of the countryside.
I thrive on it.
- God, you look good, Sam.
- I feel great.
I had surgery, plastic surgery.
Skin grafts. It cost a fortune, but at
least I don't frighten people anymore.
Don't tell me the revered
Rasputin of Smith's Grove
has grown complacent
in his old age.
Well, I won't believe
that for a second.
Well, I can't remember you
making house calls, Dr. Wynn,
especially at this hour.
And you're right.
I've come to celebrate?
Why are you listening to that jerk?
Oh, it's a program about Haddonfield.
I'm taping it.
So, who is responsible for getting
this Halloween rally thing together?
We are, the students of
Haddonfield junior college.
But why go to all the trouble
of throwing this soiree?
So what if Halloween has
been banned in Haddonfield?
Who gives a damn?
We do! We live here.
I mean, it's time we got on with our lives.
That's what tomorrow night is all about.
- This town is dying, Barry.
- Wow.
You know, I've heard Michael Myers blamed
for a lot of things tonight, but this is a first.
He's actually killed the economy!
Look, tomorrow night is
going to change all that,
especially after you do your
broadcast live from campus.
You have reached Haddonfield
Emergency Services.
Due to severe weather conditions,
all circuits are momentarily busy.
If this is not an emergency...
You gonna get up there on the stage with old Bar'?
- Uh, yeah, I will.
- Yeah?
Well, I'll see you tomorrow night.
This is "Back Talk" with Barry Simms.
Give me a call at 1-800-968-7825.
That's 1-800-YOU-SUCK.
So come on, all you
boogeyman believers out there.
Give me a call.
Call me tonight.
Well, after 32 years,
guess who is finally
relinquishing his duties
as chief administrator
of Smith's Grove?
- Good god, you don't mean to say you're—
- Retiring!
I came by to give you
the news myself.
Well, I wish you well, Terence.
It's been in the planning
stages for some time now.
To old friends...
To retirement...
To new beginnings.
Old friends.
Sam...
I want you to come back to Smith's Grove.
You should know that it's not wise
to play Halloween pranks on me.
It's no prank. You are the one I've chosen, Sam.
I want you to come back.
After my stroke six years ago they
practically had to hold a pistol
to my head to get me to retire, but...
Things are different now.
I'm different.
I've buried the ghosts.
I've buried them in this manuscript.
I don't want to practice medicine anymore.
- They're coming! They're coming!
- Yeah. So they're coming, they're coming.
Don't tell me, your name is Joan...
Joan of Arc, and you're also
hearing voices, right?
Now, who's coming?
It's Michael.
Michael Myers.
Look, someone, anyone...
Help me. Dr. Loomis, are you out there?
- Can you hear me? Dr. Loomis, I need your help.
- Please, please. No, no, stop. Stop that.
What the hell is going on tonight?
Every looney in the state is calling.
What is this? A full moon?
Oh, man. I guess Halloween
brings out all the wackos.
I can't wait until we get
to Haddonfield tomorrow.
Shhh. Shhhh.
It's okay.
Yes. It's alright.
Shhh. Yes.
It's okay.
No!
Leave us alone!
You can't have the baby, Michael.
You can't have the baby.
Enough...
of this Michael Myers...
bullshit!
Now, you stinking kids got about three
seconds to get the hell off my property!
One!
Two!
It was Jamie Lloyd.
That was six years ago, Sam.
You know she died with
him in that explosion.
- You know it!
- That's what someone would like us to believe.
But I tell you Michael is alive.
I can feel his evil heart beating,
I can see him just as I
did all those years ago
behind these very same walls.
Staring, staring.
Always growing stronger.
Please. As my colleague, as my
friend, I can't go through this again.
Not alone.
I need your help
to stop him.
Dr. Wynn, I didn't
expect you in this morning.
Donna, this is Dr. Loomis,
the man I was telling you about.
Oh, yes. It's a pleasure
to meet you, doctor.
It will be wonderful to
have you back at the hospital.
Dr. Wynn, there's
something you should know.
Donna, I'd like you to get
Dr. Loomis anything he needs.
Files, tests, records of every
treatment we've ever administered
to a former patient of
ours, Michael Myers.
- Michael Myers?
- Is something wrong?
I just received a phone call.
That girl Jamie Lloyd...
Her body was found this
morning near Haddonfield.
Notify the Haddonfield sheriff;
tell him we're on the way.
I want the entire staff on alert.
We go to code red lockdown
for twenty-four hours.
If that maniac
is really out there...
I plan to bring him back.
Alive.
Yo, G, wassup?!
Barry's my
homeboy from Chicago.
Yes, that Barry Simms.
Beth and I are
down on this gig.
Danny.
Look, you just bring the posse
tonight, and we'll hook you up.
Ace.
Doesn't Danny look cute
dressed up as his Uncle Tim?
Great. Now I've got a six-year-old
gang member for a son.
Perfect.
This is the famous Tim
Strode stomach pounder.
- You down for the challenge?
- Hit me, G.
Good try, Dan man.
You better stick to orange juice.
Shitheads.
Defacing my property.
- I showed them.
- John, they were just kids.
Kids, my dear Deborah, are
what's ruining this country.
Everywhere you go it's the same damn thing.
There's no goddamn respect.
I rest my case.
Kara, you'll never pass that
exam on an empty stomach.
"Cognitive therapy and emotional disorders".
What are they teaching you in college these days?
The art of going crazy?
It's called psychology, mom.
Living in this house is
enough to drive anyone crazy.
Oh, yeah?
Well, who the hell asked you to
come back here in the first place?
I better get Danny to school.
Doesn't show her face around
her own family for five years...
then comes back and expects
us to roll out the red carpet.
You think going to college is gonna
make up for your mistakes, girl?
- John, please.
- Lay off her, dad.
Let's go, Danny.
Kara, wait, please. John, can't we just
sit down for once and try to be a family?
Sorry, Mom.
Oh, yeah, that's it, Deborah.
Just keep slipping her the cash.
You know, while you're at it,
I got a great idea. Here.
Why don't you give her
all of our goddamn money?
Why don't you leave her alone?
Nothing ever changes, does it?
You've gotta wake up.
I got news for you, girl.
Before you came around,
everything was going fine.
Until you landed on our doorstep.
You and that little...
bastard of yours.
I see only one bastard in this house.
Danny...
Get away from her!
- You shut up and stay outta this!
- John, please, don't!
- Kill for him.
You ever talk to me like that again
and so help me God...
You understand?
Give me the knife, Danny.
Hey...
Hey. Make way for the Hardin County Express.
Where's Tim?
We're supposed to go over
the list of events for tonight.
Oh, God.
Did he do that to you?
Another episode of "Father
Knows Best" at the Strode house.
What the hell happened this time?
- What's gotten into you?
- Just glad to see you, that's all.
You guys okay?
Tonight's the night we bring
some life back into this town.
Shit, Beth, why do we have to be
the ones to organize this friggin' fair?
I mean, it's only Halloween.
How many times do I have to tell you.
It's not about Halloween.
Now, Danny, you know Grandpa
didn't really hurt me, right?
Right, Mom.
Well, you'd better
go catch your bus.
But tonight when you come home
we'll go trick-or-treating, okay?
Okay.
- I love you, Danny.
- I love you, Mommy.
Give me a squeeze.
Yeah. Okay.
I just can't live with her
anymore, Deborah.
You don't understand, do you?
It's not about Kara,
it's about you.
I don't care what she's done;
she's your daughter.
She's not my daughter anymore.
Beth, who's that guy who
lives across the hall from you?
Why, you interested?
Yeah, right.
He's always staring out his window.
Last night, I caught him watching me.
That must be Tommy.
On a weirdness scale of one to ten,
he rates about a 13.
Supposedly some scary shit happened
to him, when he was a kid.
Messed up his head pretty bad.
He's harmless, though.
- He's probably just lonely.
- Or horny.
Something you probably haven't felt in a while.
Tim...
Happy Halloween, Mrs. Blankenship!
Best part about living in that boarding house is
that crazy old lady wouldn't hear a truck
drive through her living room.
Please. Look, you've gotta listen to me!
They're coming! They're coming!
Yeah, so they're coming, they're coming.
Don't tell me. Your name is Joan...
Joan of Arc and you're also hearing voices, right?
Come on. Now, who's coming?
It's Michael.
Michael Myers.
Look, someone, anyone, help me.
Dr. Loomis, are you out there?
Can you hear me, Dr. L...
It's Michael.
Michael Myers.
...your attention, please.
Bus 611 from Pontiac...
Look, someone, anyone, help me.
Dr. Loomis, are you out there?
Can you hear me, Dr. Loomis? I need your help.
- God, please, help.
- May I have your attention, please?
Bus 34 from Peoria, Russelville and Gardner...
with through service to Chicago, Illinois...
will be arriving in five minutes.
Ticketed passengers, please wait inside
the door until arrival of bus number 34.
Can I help you, sir?
Can you tell me if a bus arrived
from Pontiac last night?
Sure did.
- Are you looking for someone?
- Thank you.
May I have your attention, please?
Bus number 34,
service to Chicago,
has arrived and is now ready for
boarding through the side doors.
Jesus.
Shhh. Shhh.
No. It's okay.
It's okay. It's okay. It's okay, man.
It's okay.
Shh, shh, shh, shh, shh.
Good God, what's that?
It's... his mark.
He's come home.
Dear God.
Jamie.
Only God can help her now, sir.
Sam, don't.
Let them take care of her.
- Doctor Loomis.
- Yeah.
They told me you'd be coming.
Now I suggest you go right on
back to your crackpot asylum.
You people got no
business in my town.
Michael Myers is my business.
It's been quiet here for six years
and that's the way it's gonna stay,
and the last thing I need now is you
going around spouting off ghost stories.
I suppose it was a ghost
that did all this, then.
It was a ghost talking
on the radio last night.
That's a ghost being
carried out of here right now?!
Yo, check it out!
Tonight's gonna be killer.
Kara, I swear. One of these days,
you're gonna get lost in that thing.
- I can't find my term paper.
- So copy someone else's. I do it all the time.
Works primo.
Oh, shit!
Looks like your little boy has got
himself quite an imagination.
He's been having nightmares.
I think it's cool.
- Must be some nightmares.
- Beth, we got work to do.
Hey...
Are you gonna be okay?
"Thorn"?
I need to see a doctor.
- What seems to be the problem?
- Uh, it's my baby.
There's been an accident.
- What kind of accident?
- Get me a doctor! Now!
Security?
Sam, there's nothing you
can do for her now.
Dr. Loomis?
Yeah.
Dr. Loomis...
Thank God you're here.
You heard her last night, didn't you?
It was Jamie.
I'm sorry.
- I don't know you, do I?
- I'm Tommy.
Tommy Doyle.
Laurie Strode, Jamie's mother, was
baby-sitting me the night when...
Tommy Doyle.
What're you doing here?
Please...
I need to know the truth.
Michael Myers has come
home, hasn't he?
What do you know
about Michael?
I know he's still out there.
People in this town,
they want us to believe he's dead,
but I know.
I've always known.
She's out there fighting for her life.
If she should die...
- She is the last of his bloodline.
- No, Dr. Loomis.
She's not the last.
Oh, God.
There's a family. Relatives of
the people who adopted Laurie:
the Strodes.
They're living in the Myers house.
Dr. Loomis, about Michael...
- It's just a theory of mine of...
- That's him.
Meet me tonight.
9:00 at the campus rally.
Tommy, wait!
Wait!
Oh, there you are.
Who is that boy?
An old friend.
Great.
I'm very sorry, Mrs. Strode.
Is everything all right?
Who are you?
I came to help your family.
Shh. Shh.
It's okay.
Okay.
Steven.
You like that name?
Yeah, I think it suits you.
It's okay. It's alright.
I won't let anything happen to you.
For 15 years I've been obsessed to find
out what was going on inside of him.
It's been my life's work,
and my ultimate failure.
This force, this thing that lived inside
of him came from a source too violent,
too deadly for you to imagine. It...
It grew inside him.
Contaminating his soul.
It was...
pure evil.
- What makes you think he'll come back here?
- This house...
is sacred to him.
He has all his memories here.
His rage!
Mrs. Strode...
I beg of you.
Don't let your family suffer the same
fate that Laurie and her daughter suffered.
- Jamie? I... I thought that she—
- She's been found.
Outside Haddonfield, stabbed.
What should I do?
I really am sorry, but you haven't
a moment to lose, Mrs. Strode.
Michael Myers has come
back to Haddonfield to kill.
Strode Real Estate.
John, something terrible's happened.
What do you want now, Deborah?
A man came by the house,
a psychiatrist by the name of Loomis.
And he told me about the terrible things
that happened here in our house.
Deborah, what the hell are you doing?
Talking to strangers, letting 'em in our house?
John, they found Jamie Lloyd this morning.
Someone tried to kill her.
Deborah, I don't know what
the hell you're talking about.
You ought to stop watching
those damn TV talkshows.
I'm getting the children out of here.
At least until I know what's going on.
John, I want you to come with us.
You know. You know, Deborah.
You've lost it. You know that, Deborah?
You've just lost it.
The reason you moved us into this house...
Your brother could never sell it
because of what happened here, could he?
And you knew.
And you didn't tell us, John.
You knew.
Goddamnit!
Happy Halloween, little girl.
Hello?
We want the child.
Who is this?
Oh, Michael.
I'm coming.
Yeah, I'm...
Get ready, oh, yes! Yeah. Yes.
I'm coming, all right, and you'd better
be there at the Halloween Harvest fair.
Let's do it, together.
Sorry.
Mom? I'm home!
Hello?
Mom!
Mom?
Danny?
Are you there?
What are you doing here?
I'm your neighbor from across the street.
- Tommy Doyle.
- What are you doing with my son?
And... and where's my mother?
She wasn't here... when Danny came home.
Danny, go downstairs.
But Tommy's my new friend.
He knows all about dinosaurs.
You're in danger. Come with me.
Hi, Mrs. B!
You don't really expect us to stay here, do you?
I want you to watch your house.
You can see everything from that window.
Do you know how insane this is?
Who am I supposed to be looking for?
Him.
Yeah. It's okay.
It's okay, Steven.
Mommy!
Mom!
Not now, Danny.
Here you go.
Come on.
What?
Here. Let me try.
There.
See?
All it takes is a mother's touch.
Uncle Michael, please don't hurt me.
Oh, God, please forget me.
Your work is done now, Jamie.
I let you down again, Jamie.
I never should have left you.
Runes were a kind of... early alphabet...
that originated in Northern Europe about 500 B.C.
They were symbols carved out
of stone or pieces of wood,
used in pagan rituals to portend
future events and invoke magic.
Of all the runes, Thorn had
the most negative influence.
Among the ancient druids, Thorn
represented a demon that spread
sickness, destroyed crops, and brought
death to hundreds of thousands of people.
According to a Celtic legend,
one child from each tribe
was chosen to be inflicted with a curse of Thorn.
To offer the blood sacrifices of its
next of kin on the night of Samhain.
Halloween.
The sacrifice of one family meant
sparing the lives of an entire tribe.
So why are you so concerned
about us if Michael's only out
to kill his family?
In his mind, anyone living
in his house is his family.
For years I've been convinced
there must be some reason.
Some method behind Michael's madness.
And the common link I found is Thorn.
The druids were also great
mathematicians and astronomers.
The Thorn symbol is
actually constellation of stars
that appears from time to
time on Halloween night.
Whenever it appears, he appears.
I've traced it back to 1963,
when Michael murdered his sister, Judith.
The next time was in 1978; Michael
escapes from Smith's Grove.
It happened a decade later,
and the year after that. He kills again.
Now Jamie says Michael is back,
and for the first time in 6 years,
Thorn reappears.
Coincidence?
What would happen if he succeeded,
if he killed the last member of his family?
Well, Michael's power would end,
and the curse would be
passed on to another child.
I think that's why these people,
whoever they are,
are after Jamie's baby.
To make it Michael's final sacrifice.
Where are you going?
To find the only man who can
stop him before it's too late.
Oh, no. Where's Danny?
Danny?
Danny!
Mrs. Blankenship!
Have you seen...
Danny, don't ever walk off without
telling me where you're going!
Take him upstairs.
Lock the door and wait till I get back.
Kara...
Whatever you do...
Don't go back to your house.
You let him get to her!
How could you?
Dr. Loomis, during surgery we discovered
that Jamie's uterus was hemorrhaging,
and we found this.
It's placental fluid.
Good God in heaven, do you mean to say—
I estimate she gave birth
no more than 24 hours ago.
Then the question is:
Where is the baby?
I think I...
I may already know.
Do you know why we celebrate Halloween?
Because that's when we go
trick-or-treating and get candy.
Oh, well...
Yes, but...
A long, long time ago,
it was a night of great power,
when the days grew short
and the spirits of the dead
returned to their homes to
warm themselves by the fireside.
All across the land huge bonfires were lit.
Oh, there was a marvelous celebration.
People danced and they played games.
And they dressed up in costumes.
Hoping to ward off the evil spirits.
Especially the boogeyman.
What's the boogeyman?
Come on, Danny.
Say good night to Mrs. Blankenship.
- Good night, Mrs. Blankenship.
- He hears the voice, you know.
Just like the other boy that lived in that house.
What are you talking about?
I was baby-sitting with him that night.
Little Mikey Myers that lived across the street.
And that's when the voice came,
the night he murdered his sister.
Michael heard a voice?
It told him to kill his family.
- Where the hell's Barry? Let's go!
- Don't get star-struck on me now.
We got a real agenda here, and Barry
is gonna help us get the message out.
Hey, look...
Helloooo, Haddonfield!
- Barry!
- WKNB presents "Back Talk" with Barry Simms.
- live from Haddonfield, Illinois,
- Barry!
the home of Michael Myers!
Deborah!
I'm home!
Thanks for the dinner.
Come out, come out...
Wherever you are.
Goddamnit.
She actually left.
I know what's going on.
It must be the boogeyman.
Here I come, boogeyman.
'Cause, you know, I am really scared.
What the hell?
The power's off.
Tell me, kids, how's it feel to...
finally pull Halloween out of
the proverbial Haddonfield closet?
What we're saying here is...
we will no longer let the powers
that be control our minds.
For years...
Halloween has represented everything
that's wrong with Haddonfield.
But Michael Myers is long gone.
There is NO boogeyman!
Whoa!
Does she get this riled up in the sack, Tim?
I bet she wears crotchless
panties and barks like a dog.
Beth...
What do you say, honey?
You and me, uh...
As I was saying...
We have to stop acting out of fear.
Just look at Tim's family.
They live in the Myers house.
You do?
We do?
Uh... yeah, we do.
Great house.
- Strong wood.
- I see. You mean to tell me you actually live...
in the house...
of the most brutal
mass murderer in history?
This is the Barry Simms show.
And when we return...
we'll be coming at you live...
from the one...
the only...
Myers house.
How's that for a Halloween shock-fest?
How far to your house, kid?
About half a mile, but I don't know if my folks...
Good, I'll meet you
there in five.
What about the kids?
We're supposed to throw all the candy.
Phone!
Relax your crack, sweetheart.
Quick tootle around the old household
and we'll be right on back.
Pull the van out back, so that I can
sneak out of here nice and quietly.
Oh, no. No, no, really, really.
You're too good to me. Really.
No. Thanks for putting me in the middle of this
cheap-shit country bumpkin outfit, Paul.
I really appreciate it!
My fans expect better than this.
No, no. Look, you tell that penny-pinching whiner
Mike Sarducci that when I get back,
I am personally gonna cut off his
balls and wear 'em as earrings.
Where's the goddamn van?
God!
Oh, no, I'm trotting out for a cheeseburger.
I'm taking the show to the real Myers house,
where we should have
done it in the first place.
Ten minutes in that house and I'll have
every fruitcake medium in the country
calling in trying to channel the
spirit of that pussy Michael Myers.
Sure, we can do another show about him.
Kick the audience in the face enough
and they'll lick you all over.
I'll call you when I get back, Paul. Bye-bye.
Where the f...
What happened to the lights?
Do you really think Barry's gonna show up?
Let's hope not.
I'm sorry he turned out
to be such an asshole.
It's okay.
Where is everyone?
Mom?
Kara?
They're probably at the fair,
which is where we should be.
Beth...
What you said before about
Michael Myers living in our house.
Is that really true?
It was a cold Halloween night.
He stood in the shadows,
watching through the windows...
as his sister and her boyfriend made love.
Then he crept inside...
picked up a huge butcher knife...
and made his way up these stairs.
He raised the knife up behind her...
She turned around...
and he stabbed her!
Cut it out, Beth!
I really didn't know that Michael
Myers lived in my house, okay?
It freaks me out.
I'm sorry.
I was just fooling around.
It's okay.
Let's get the candles.
Just a minute.
Mommy, it's raining.
It's raining red.
Mommy, it's raining red.
Mommy, it's raining.
It's raining red.
Mommy, it's raining red.
It's warm.
Why is it warm?
Dr. Loomis.
It's happening.
Your sister would kill us if she
knew we did it in her bed.
Hey, that was your idea.
I am bad, aren't I?
Only when you wear crotchless
panties and bark like a dog.
Where are you going?
I gotta take a shower.
You know, to stay fresh.
Watch out for the boogeyman.
Hey, Beth, can you bring a
towel in here? I'm freezing.
Where are you when I need you, honey?
Thanks.
I'll be in in a minute.
Mommy?
Hold on a second, Danny.
Danny... Come to me...
- Hello?
- Mom? Wait, who is this?
No, this is Beth.
What are you doing there?
- Do you know where my mother is?
- She's not home. No one is.
What's wrong?
Is Tim with you?
He's in the shower.
I'm across the street.
I can see you.
Beth, I want you to listen to me.
Get Tim and get out of that house.
Right now.
Carol, what the hell is going on?
Beth, look out! There's someone in the room.
He's right behind you!
No!
Danny, no!
Danny!
Danny.
Danny?
Mommy?
It's okay.
Danny, run!
Danny.
Come to mommy.
Danny, please.
The baby.
Where's the baby?
Please!
Open the door!
Someone help us!
Please, somebody help us!
Help us, please!
Get 'em upstairs!
Now!
Where's the baby?
He's gone.
Who else knew I had the baby?
- No one.
- No!
There had to be someone else...
- Who knew?
- Nobody knew except me and...
Danny. Come to me.
Come Danny, come to me.
Danny, no.
No.
Please.
Careful with the girl.
Kara!
Wynn.
Mrs. Blankenship!
Oh, God, hurry! We have to...
Hello, dear.
Where is she?
Where's Kara?
I feel like I've been drugged.
We have been drugged.
Why are they doing this?
Why didn't they just kill us?
It's his game.
And I know where he wants to play it.
- Dr. Loomis, you know that can't stop Michael.
- Nothing will stop Michael.
But...
Wynn.
I tried to tell you
in the hospital.
I think Michael is under the
influence of an evil rune.
Thorn.
I saw the symbol marked up
where we found Jamie stabbed.
Well, there are runes of light... Protection.
If Thorn could somehow be trapped by these
runes the energies could cancel themselves out.
The evil could be destroyed.
You wait here.
Don't go anywhere until I come back.
Wynn.
About time, Dr. Loomis.
Welcome to your fate.
The time has come for
you to know the truth.
The time has come
for you to join us.
Why now?
After Jamie escaped last night,
I knew that she would come to you,
and I knew that you would
lead us to her baby.
Her very special baby.
I needed her, just as I need you now.
It's your destiny, Sam.
It lives inside you.
It always has.
You know that, don't you?
You...
are...
a madman.
Look around you, Sam.
Madness everywhere.
Famine, war, a great plague.
These are signs that we must restore
balance to the natural order of things.
- We merely provide the means.
- Michael?
We've given him the power.
The gift of Thorn.
I am its deliverer. I follow it,
act as its guardian.
I protect Michael, watch over him.
And now it's time for another.
Now it's time for you....
Dr. Loomis.
I thought Michael was a monster.
But you...
Leave him there.
It's his office now.
Spirits and powers of the flame.
Attend and witness this ritual.
Bear our gifts to Thorn.
Open us to the path of darkness.
By these runes transform us.
Let the hammer descend on the chosen
one to whom we offer this sacrifice
of innocent blood.
And then, Danny,
your journey begins.
Kill for him.
No.
Michael, your final sacrifice.
Michael, you can make him stop it.
Don't kill the baby.
You can stop it.
You know whose baby it is, don't you?
- Michael!
- The baby is yours, isn't it?
Isn't it, Michael?
Back off!
- Untie her.
- Do as he says. Do it!
You should join us, you have talent.
Shut up.
Danny, come on.
Go! Okay? Let's go.
Run!
Go!
Go, go!
Move it! Go, go!
Shit!
- Come on!
- It's not working.
Come on. It's not working!
It's not...
Back up from the gates!
Get 'em out of here!
Get in there!
Go on, get in!
Mommy!
Samhain.
Tommy! Where is he?
It worked.
The power of the runes stopped him.
Michael.
What have they done to you?
- Where do we go now?
- As far away from Haddonfield as possible.
- Come with us.
- No, I have a little business to attend to here.
Michael.
It's all over.
It's all over!
It's all over now.
Michael.
Michael's gone.
It's your game now, Dr. Loomis.
Watch Movies, TV Series and Live Sports
Signup Here -> WWW.ADMITME.APP