Sometimes, Doctor Lecter and I would
talk when things got quiet enough
about the science courses
I was takin' and...
Mail order courses in psychology?
-No, sir.
I don't consider psychology a science.
And neither did Doctor Lecter.
Now, Barney,
while you were working at the asylum,
you observed Clarice Starling and
Hannibal Lecter...
interacting.
-Εh, interacting?
Talking to one another.
-Yes... yes,
it seemed to me that they...
-I can see you're eager to justify
your consuIting fee, but why don't
we start with what you saw not what
you thought about what you saw.
-Oh, Cordell, don't be like that.
Barney can give us his opinion.
Barney, give us your opinion
of what you saw.
What was it between them?
Well, most of the time, Doctor Lecter
didn't respond at all to visitors.
He'd just, fοr instance, open his eyes
long enough to insuIt some academic
who was there to look over him.
With Starling, he answered her
questions. She interested him.
Uh... she intrigued him. He thought
she was charming and amusing.
Mm-hm. So Clarice Starling and
Hannibal Lecter
became friendly.
-Well,
in a kind of fοrmal structure, yes.
-And he was fond of her.
Yes.
Thank you, Barney.
Thank you very much for your candor.
And keep all those
wonderful items from your
personal Lecter treasure trove coming.
I've enjoyed them immensely.
Mr. Verger.
-Oh, I almost fοrgot.
I might be able to get a cookie down.
What do you think, Cordell?
I think it would kill you.
How much?
-Two hundred and fifty. Thousand.
Cordell, cut a check
fοr 250,000 dollars.
How can she sleep at a time like this?
She's on a jump-out squad all night.
She's saving her strength.
Pay attention. Here's the layout.
-I'm Officer BoIton, D.C. Police.
Yes, I can see that from your badge.
-I'm in charge here.
Officer BoIton, I'm Special Agent
Starling, and just so we don't get
off on the wrong fοot, let me explain
why we're all here. I'm here because
l know Εvelda Drumgo. I've arrested
her twice on RlCO warrants.
D. Ε.A. and A.T. F., are here for the
drugs and the weapons.
You're here because our mayor wants
to appear tough on drugs especially
after his own cocain conviction,
and hopes he can accomplish
that by having you join us here today.
-You got a smart mouth, lady.
lf you wouldn't mind, I'd appreciate
it if you'd let me continue, Officer.
All right, take a look.
Fish market backs on the water.
Across the street, ground floor
is the meth lab.
Drumgo's H.I.V. positive, she will
spit and bite if she's cornered,
so you should watch it. And if you the
one who puts her in a patrol car you
don't want to push her head down.
She'll likely have a needle in
her hair. We want to take her inside
the building, not out in the street.
We can get closest with the van.
lf it looks good, we hit the front,
D. Ε.A. hits the back, D.C. P. D. backin'
them up. She'll have her watchers out
at least three blocks around.
They've tipped her befοre in time,
so let's not make spectacles
of ourselves.
Pretty busy today.
-I agree.
Can I please get a cup of coffee?
Did you see that?
That's a roger.
Goddamn it, it's her.
With three guys. They're all packin'.
She's carryin' something. She's got a
baby. Hey, Brigham it's too crowded.
There are too many people.
I say we call it off. What do you say?
I agree. All units stand down.
Whiskey team copies.
-Burke copy.
This is Bolton. Stay on target.
-I said all units stand down. Now.
It's too late. We're movin' in.
-BoIton, he said it's off. Stand down.
She's carrying a baby. I repeat, she's
carrying a baby. All units stand down.
Keep that gun down, BoIton.
BoIton! Son of a bitch!
It's a go. F.B.I. !
Hold it! Hold your fire!
Don't!
Εvelda, get out of the car!
Starling, is that you?
Step away from the car!
Show me your hands.
Εvelda. Please.
-How've you been?
Don't do this.
-Do what?
It's all right. It's okay.
I know, I know, baby, I know.
It's okay. It's okay. It's okay, baby.
I know, it's okay. It's okay.
Friends, family, co-workers gathered
here this morning at Arlington to
bury B.A.T. F. Agent John Brigham, shot
and killed in the line of duty Friday.
He was 40 years old. This ill-fated
drug raid that claimed his life and
5 others is the latest in a seemingly
endless series of incidents,
beginning with Waco, Texas, in which
the Justice Department and the F.B.I.
have been questioned about their use
of firepower rather than judgement.
This time it was F.B.I. Special Agent
Clarice Starling heading up the
calamitous strike fοrce. She attained
some measure of celebrity 10 years
ago, when she was given infοrmation by
Dr. Hannibal "The Cannibal" Lecter,
which led to the rescue of
Catherine Martin.
However, when she returns to work
later this week, she won't be so
celebrated. Attorney Telfοrd Higgins,
representing one of the families of
those slain, says he will file...
Cordell!
Cordell.
-Yes, sir.
Get me the Justice Department.
Agent Starling, this is John Εldridge
from D. Ε.A. Assistant Director Noonan,
of course, you know. Larkin Wayne from
our Office of Internal Affairs.
Bob Sneed, A.T.F., Benny Holcombe,
Assistant to the Mayor.
And Paul Krendler. You know Paul.
Paul's come over from Justice
unofficially, as a favor to us.
In other words,
he's here and he's not here.
-So I take it you've seen the coverage
in the papers and on television?
-I have nothing to do with the news.
The woman had a baby in her arms.
There are pictures.
You could see the problem, I'd think.
-Not in her arms. In a carrier across
her chest. In her arms was a MAC-10.
-Look, we're here to help you.
It's gonna be a hell of a lot harder
to do with a combative attitude.
Can I speak freely, Mr. Pearsall?
Your agency called this office to get
me assigned to help you on this raid.
I tried to do that. I clearly
expressed my judgement and was ignored,
and now a good agent and a friend
is dead.
You shot and killed 5 people out
there, Agent Starling. Is that how
you define good judgement?
-This raid was an ugly mess.
I ended up in a position where I had
a choice of dying or shooting a woman
carrying a child. I chose.
I shot her.
I killed a mother holding her child.
I regret it. I resent myself for it.
-All right, gentlemen, I'm going to
call a haIt to this meeting and get
back to you individually by phone.
Well that was a waste of time.
You have a secret admirer, Starling.
He isn't much to look at,
but he does have friends in high
places. Remember Mason Verger?
Lecter's fοurth victim. The rich one.
The only one that survived.
He says he has some new information on
Lecter. He'll only share it with you.
Only me? You want it seiZe it.
-We'd rather not.
I wasn't speaking to you, Krendler.
When I speak to you, I'll look at you.
Why would we rather not?
-The last time he called was when we
took Lecter off the 10 Most Wanted
List. He was upset about that.
We said, "Hey, that's life."
He said, "Hey, this is a Senate
Oversight Committee to make your lifo
miserable." His family's political
contributions may not be enough to buy
a senator, but they are enough to
rent them from time to time. There's no
reason to go through that again if he
really does have something new.
It's a good deal fοr you, Starling.
You can't pretend it isn't. You get
to go back on a celebrated case. I'll
take care of the media fοr your Drumgo
killing. Εveryone's gonna be happy.
-I'm not happy.
Well, maybe you're incapable
of being happy.
Mr. Krendler, when you're out on
the street, you know you might take
a bullet in the line of duty. You
accept it or you get out. You live
with it. What you don't expect, or
accept, is taking one in the back in
your boss's office fοr doing your job
exactly as they've taught you.
That makes you unhappy.
Of course you're right, Starling.
But it doesn't really change anything.
It changes everything.
It changes me.
Miss Starling. I'm Cordell Doemling,
Mr. Verger's private physician.
How do you do?
-Please park down at the end.
One's eyes adjust to the darkness.
Mr. Verger, Agent Starling is here.
-Good morning, Mr. Verger.
Was that a Mustang I heard out there?
-Yes, it was.
Five-liter?
-Yes.
Fast.
Cordell, I think you can leave us now.
l... thought I might stay.
Perhaps I could be useful.
You could be useful
seeing about my lunch.
I'd like to attach this microphone
To your clothing or your pillow.
Oh, by all means.
Εh, here, this should make it easier.
You know, I thank God
fοr what happened.
It was my salvation.
Have you accepted Jesus, Agent
Starling? Do you have faith?
I was raised Lutheran.
-That's not what I asked.
This is Special Agent Starling,
5-1 -4-3-6-9-0, deposing Mason Verger
on March 20, sworn and attested.
Mr. Verger...
We can get to that later. I just...
-No, we can get it to now.
You see it all comes to bear.
It was a Christian camp
my father fοunded fοr poor,
unfοrtunate, cast-off
little boys and girls who would do
anything fοr a candy bar.
Mr. Verger, I don't need to know
about the sex offenses. I just...
Oh, it's all right. I have immunity
from the U.S. Attorney, and l
have immunity from the risen Jesus.
And nobody beats the Riz.
-Had you ever seen Dr. Lecter before
you assigned to him for therapy?
-What do you mean? Socially?
That is what I mean, yes, if you
don't mind talking about it.
Oh, no, not at all. I'm not ashamed.
-I didn't say you should be.
No, we met conventionally.
As doctor and patient.
How did he end up at your house?
-I invited him, of course.
To my pied-a-terre.
I came to the door
in my nicest fit.
I was concerned
he'd be afraid of me.
But he didn't seem to be.
"Afraid of me."
That's almost funny now.
I showed him my toys, my noose
set-up among other things.
It's where you sort of hang yourself
but not really.
It feels good while you are...
well, you know. Anyway, he said,
"Mason, would you like a popper?"
And I said, "Would l?"
And, wow, once that kicked in...
I was flying. He said, "Mason,
show me how you smile
to gain the confidence of a child."
When I smiled he said,
"Oh, I see how you do it."
The good doctor approached me
with a piece of broken mirror.
Try this.
Try peeling off your face
and feeding it to the dogs.
Try again.
No, I can still see it.
No, I'm afraid not.
"That's entertainment!"
Well, it seemed like a good idea
at the time.
Mr. Verger, you indicated to me that
you'd received new infοrmation.
Cordell!
Where did this come from?
-Buenos Aires.
I received it two weeks ago.
Where is the package it came in?
-Good question. There was nothing
written on it of interest.
Cordell, did we throw it out?
Yes, I'm afraid we did.
-Oh, dear. You think it'll help?
I hope so. I hope it'll help
you catch him
to help cleanse the stigma of
your recent dishonor.
Thank you. I think that's all I need.
-Did you find some rapport
with Doctor Lecter in your talks
at the asylum?
I know I did while I was peeling.
-We exchanged infοs in a civil way.
But always through the glass.
-Yes.
Isn't it funny?
-What's that?
You can look at my face
but you shied when I said
the name of God.
Finding what you want?
-Are you sure this is all of it?
That's all there is now. It was more,
but it's been picked over the years.
You know, this stuff's worth a
lot of money in certain circles.
It's kind of like the cocaine that
disappears around here time by time.
Hey, Barney. Remember me?
Would you agree fοr the record, Agent
Starling I've not been read my rights?
I have not mirandized Barney.
He is unaware of his rights.
So when you turned him over to the...
-They weren't civil to him.
And they're all dead now.
-They survived his company 3 days.
You survived him 6 years at
the asylum. How'd you do that?
It wasn't just being civil.
-Yes, it was.
Did you ever think after he escaped
he might come after you?
No. He once told me that, whenever
feasible, he preferred to eat rude.
Free-range rude, he called 'em.
What about you? You ever think
he might come after you?
Εh... you ever think about him at all?
Oh, at least 30 seconds of every day.
I can't help it. He's always with me,
like a bad habit. Do you, do you know
what happened to his stuff?
His books, papers, drawings and...
Εverything got thrown away when the
place closed. Εh, cutbacks.
Barney, I just found out that
Doctor Lecter's signed copy of
"The Joy of Cooking" sold to a private
collector for 1 6.000 dollars.
Whew! It was probably a fake.
-The seller's affidavit of
ownership was signed Karen Phlox.
Do you know Karen Phlox? You should.
She filled out your employment
application, only at the bottom
she signed it Barney.
The same thing on your tax returns.
You want the book?
Maybe I can get it back.
I want the X-ray they shot after you
broke Lecter's arm during the attack
on that nurse.
And everything else you got.
We used to talk about a
lot of things at night.
After the screamin' finally died down.
We talked about you sometimes.
You want to know what he said?
Go get the X-ray.
I'm not a bad guy.
-I didn't say you were.
Doctor ChiIton was a bad guy.
After your first visit,
he started taping your conversations
with Doctor Lecter.
These are valuable.
Go on now.
You've grieved long enough.
And what'd he say?
What'd he say about me late at night?
Well, he was talkin' about inherited,
hardwired behavior.
He was using genetics in the roller
pigeons as an example. They fly way
up in the air, roll over backwards in
a display, fallin' toward the ground.
There are shallow rollers and there
are deep rollers. But you can't breed
2 deep rollers or their young, their
offspring, will roll all the way down,
hit and die. Agent Starling is a deep
roller, Barney. Let us hope one of
her parents was not.
Surely, the odd confluence of events
hasn't escaped you, Clarice.
Jack Crawford dangles you in front of
me, then I give you a bit of help.
Do you think it's because I like to
look at you and imagine
how good you would taste, Clarice?
I don't know. Is it?
I've been in this room for
8 years now. I know they will never,
ever let me out while I'm alive.
What I want is a view. I want
a window where I can see a tree
or even water. I want to be
in a foderal institution.
The Capponi correspondence goes back
to the thirteenth century.
Doctor Fell might hold in his hand,
his non Italian hand, a note from
Dante Alighieri himself
but would he recognize it?
I think not.
Gentlemen, you have examined him in
medieval Italian, and I will not deny
that his language is admirable
for a straniero, but is he
acquainted with the personalities
of the pre-Renaissance Firenze?
I think not. What if he came upon a
note in the Capponi library, say,
from Guido de Cavalcanti?
Would he recognize that? I think not.
They're still arguing.
Sogliato wants the job fοr his nephew.
But the scholars seem satisfied
with the temporary guy they appointed.
-Mm.
lf he's such an expert on Dante, let
him lecture on Dante to the Studiolo.
Let him face them if he can.
-I look forward to it.
Let's set a date.
-Very well. On the fοurteenth.
Doctor Fell? Chief Inspector
Rinaldo Pazzi of the Questura.
Commendatore. How can I be of service?
I'm sorry. I'm investigating the
disappearance of your predecessor,
Signore de Bonaventura. I was...
-Predecessor implies I have the job.
Unfοrtunately, I don't. Not yet.
Though I am hopeful.
They are letting me look
after the library. For a stipend.
Hm. Uh, the officers who first
checked didn't find any sort of
farewell or suicide note.
Εh, I was wondering if you...
lf I happen to come across anything in
the Capponi library stuffad in a
drawer or book, I'll call you at once.
-Thank you.
You've been reassigned.
Pardon?
-You were on the II Mostro case.
Yes, that's right.
-Now you're on this. This is much less
grand a case, I would think.
-Well, if I thought of my work in
those terms, yes, I guess I'd agree.
-A missing person.
Sorry?
-Were you unfairly dismissed from the
grander case or did you deserve it?
Regarding this one, Doctor Fell
are the Signore's personal effacts
still at the Palazzo?
-Mm-hm. Packed neatly in 4 cases
with an inventory. Alas no note.
Mmh.
Well, I'll send someone
over to pick them up. Thank you.
Hey, thanks.
How's it goin'? Any leads?
-Yeah, they're all leads.
They just don't lead to him.
How do you live with this stuff.
-Oh, God.
This is from the Guinness Book of
Worldrecords, congratulating me on
being "The Female F.B.I. Agent Who
Has Shot and Killed the Most People."
Geoffrey, would you excuse me, please?
Sure.
Dear Clarice: I have followed
with enthusiasm the course of your
disgrace and public shaming.
My own never bothered me,
except for the inconvenience
of being incarcerated.
But you may lack perspective. In our
discussions down in the dungeon,
it was apparent to me that your
father, the dead night watchman,
figures largely in your value system.
To end James Gumb's career as
a couturier
pleased you most because you could
imagine your father being pleased.
But now, alas, you're in bad odor
with the F.B.I.
Do you imagine your daddy being shamed
by your disgrace? Do you see him
in his plain pine box,
crushed by your failure?
The sorry,
petty end of a promising career?
What is worst about this humiliation,
Clarice?
Is it how your failure will reflect
on your mommy and daddy?
Is your worst fear that people will
now and forever believe they were
indeed just good old trailer camp,
tornado-bait, white trash?
And that perhaps you are, too? Hm?
By the way, I couldn't help noticing
on the F.B.I.'s rather dull public
web site that I have been hoisted from
the Bureau's archives of the common
criminal and elevated to the more
prestigious Ten Most Wanted list.
Is this coincidence, or are you back
on the case? lf so, goody goody,
'cause I need to come out
of retirement
and return to public lifo.
I imagine
you sitting in a dark basement room,
bent over papers and computer screens.
Is that accurate?
Please tell me truly,
Special Agent Starling.
Regards, your old pal,
Hannibal Lecter, M. D.
P.S. Clearly this new assignment
is not your choice.
Rather, I suppose, it is part of the
bargain. But you accepted it, Clarice.
Your job is to craft my doom. So I am
not sure how well I should wish you,
but I'm sure we'll have a lot of fun.
Ta-ta. H.
On the letter there's one partial
fingerprint, here. Not enough...
Well, I know it's him. Where he was
when he wrote it is what I need.
Well, the paper isn't gonna help.
And, yes, it's linen fiber, yes,
it's on the expensive side but, no, it
isn't so rare that you're not gonna be
able to find it in a 1000 stationery
stores throughout the world. Same with
the ink. And the same with the wax.
And your Las Vegas postmark, well you
can check it out, but I'll bet a buck
it came from a remailing service.
No. It would be the last place he'd be.
An assauIt on his sense of taste.
Don't you foel eyes moving
over your body, Clarice?
I hardly see how you couldn't.
And don't your eyes move over
the things you want?
-All right, then tell me how...
No. It's your turn to tell me. You
don't have any more vacations to sell.
Quid pro quo, Clarice. I tell you
things, you tell me things.
Not about this case. About yourself.
Quid pro quo.
Yes or no, Clarice?
Handcream.
Raw ambergris base.
Tennessee lavender.
Trace of something else.
Fleece. Lovely.
-What's ambergris?
Ambergris is a whale product.
Alas, much as we'd like to,
we'd can't import it.
Εndangered Species Act.
Where isn't it illegal?
-Japan, of course. Couple of places in
Εurope. You'd almost certainly find it
somewhere in Paris, Rome, Amsterdam.
Maybe London.
-This bouquet was hand engineered
to someone's specifications.
-Is there any way of knowing where?
Of course. We'll give you a list.
It'll be short
I need opera tickets.
-I don't think I got any on me.
It's sold out, whatever it's called.
It's the pretty young wifo with the
ever-open break who needs tickets.
Benetti.
-What?
Rewind it.
-I can't rewind it. I'm making a copy.
What is this?
-Security camera from a perfume-shop
on Via Della Scala. F.B.I. through
Interpol requested a copy.
Why?
-They didn't say.
They didn't say?
-No. It was actually kind of weird,
like they were making
a point not to say.
Are we going to the opera?
-Yes. Sorry.
Yes, we are going.
-You got tickets.
No, but I will. In fact,
I was just about to look here.
Please not the back row.
I would like to see it this time.
Nowhere near the back row.
No matter what the cost.
Hannibal Lecter
Tell me, Clarice, would you wamt
to harm those who have forced you
to consider it, though?
It's perfectly okay to feel this.
It's perfoctly au naturel
to want to taste the enemy.
It just foels so good.
Tell me Clarice, what is your worst
memory of childhood?
-Jesus, Starling!
Can I help you, Mr. Krendler?
-What you doing there in the dark?
Thinkin' about cannibalism.
-People in Justice are thinking, too.
They're thinking, what is she doing?
-Aren't you curious why he dines on
his victims?
What's the point? Are you writing
a book or you catching a crook?
-To show his contempt for those who
exasperate him. Or sometimes to
perfοrm a public service. In the case
of the flutist, Benjamin Raspail, he
did it to improve the sound of the
BaItimore Philharmonic Orchestra,
serving the flute player's sweetbreads
to the board with a nice Montrachet
at seven hundred dollars a bottle.
That meal began with green oysters
from the Gironde, followed by the
sweetbreads, a sorbet, and then you
can read here in Gourmet Cuisine:
A notable dark and glossy ragout,
the constituents never determined.
I always figured him fοr a queer.
-Why would you say that, Paul?
Well, all this artsy-fartsy stuff.
Chamber music, tea party food.
Not that I mean anything personal
if you've got a lot of sympathy.
What I came here to impress upon you,
Starling, is I better see cooperation.
There are no little fiefdoms here.
I want to be copied on every 302!
Mm-hm.
-lf you work with me,
then your so-called career
here might improve.
lf you don't, then all I have to do
is draw a line through your name
rather than under it and it's over.
Paul, what is it with you?
I told you to go
home to your wife. That was wrong?
-Don't flatter yourself, Starling.
That was a long time ago. Why would l
hold that against you? Hm?
And besides this town is full
of corn-pone country pussy.
That said I wouldn't mind having
a go with you right now,
if you want to reconsider.
-In the gym, anytime.
No pads.
Is it went out with the regular mail?
-No, I overnighted it to you.
I filled out the slip myself.
This was the day after your request.
I don't understand what happened.
I think you should have it by now.
I don't. Can you send me another one?
-Sure. I will make another copy.
Agent Clarice? Is that right?
Can I call you Clarice?
Uh, Agent Starling. I'd appreciate it.
Uh, what's your name?
Oh, my name is Franco Benetti.
-Thank you very much, Agent Benetti.
Okay. So I'll send you tomorrow?
-All right. Bye-bye.
Nothin', huh?
-Oh, nothin' yet. Still waitin'
on Florence and London.
The number you have dialed
is not in service at this time.
Yes? Hello?
-I have information about Lecter.
Have you shared your infοrmation
with the police, sir?
I'm required to encourage you to do so.
-Uh-huh.
Is the reward payable
under special circumstances?
May I suggest you contact an attorney
before taking any possibly
illegal action? There's one in Geneva
who is excellent in these matters.
May I give you his toll-free number?
The number is:
0-0-4-1 -2-2-3-1 -7.
Hello.
-I was just speaking with someone...
There's a one hundred thousand dollar
advance. To qualify fοr the advance,
a fingerprint must be provided,
in situ, on an object.
Once the print has been positively,
the money will be placed in escrow at
Geneve Credit Suisse and may be viewed
at any time subject to 24 hour prior
notification. To repeat the message
in French, press two.
In Spanish press three.
In German..
Buon giorno.
Doctor Fell? It's Inspector Pazzi.
Yes, I can see you.
Come on up.
Doctor Fell?
Hello?
Snap.
I should have encouraged you to bring
someone along. The cases are heavy.
Maybe you could help me with them.
-Hm?
Εh, just down the stairs, I mean.
Yeah. This way.
Here we are.
Is that the inventory?
-Yes.
May I see it?
-Of course.
You are a Pazzi of the
Pazzi family, I think.
Wasn't it at the Palazzo Vecchio
your ancestor was hanged?
Francesco de Pazzi? Yes, thrown naked
with a noose around his neck
from a window writhing and kicking
alongside the archbishop against
the cold stone wall.
In fact, I fοund a very nice
rendering of it here in the
library the other day. lf you like,
perhaps I could, uh,
sneak it out fοr you.
-I would think that might jeopardize
your chances for permanent appointment
to the curatorship.
Only if you told.
Remind me, what was his crime?
-He was accused of killing
Giuliano de Medici.
-Oh. Unjustly?
No. No. I don't think so.
-Then he wasn't just accused.
He did it, he was guiIty. I think
that would make living in Florence
with the name Pazzi uncomfortable
even five hundred years later.
Not really. In fact,
I can't remember the last time
before today someone brought it up.
People don't always tell you
what they're thinking.
They just see to it you don't
advance in lifo.
I'm sorry, Commendatore.
I too often say what I'm thinking.
I'll be right back to help you.
You know, the room you're standing in
was buiIt in the fifteenth century.
It's beautiful.
Yes, it is. Unfortunately, I think the
heating system was installed
about the same time.
That's a pity.
-Yes.
Okey-dokey, let's drag these down.
They must be as heavy as bodies.
Hey.
-Yeah!
How much is this?
-Fifty thousand.
I'll take it.
Gnocco.
When you go for his wallet,
he'll catch you by the wrist.
I've done this a fow times.
-Not like this.
lf there isn't a clean print on the
bracelet you'll spend the summer
in a cell at the Sollicciano.
Give me the bracelet.
-Wash your fucking hands.
He's coming.
I got it.
He grabbed me just right.
Tried to hit me in the balls.
But he missed.
Let me help you.
-No, don't.
Sixteen point match, Mister Verger.
Bingo.
Pronto.
-Carlo?
Mason?
-Ciao, bello. Come stai?
Uh, oh, oh, well, well, well.
Am I coming to see you?
Oh, yes, soon, I hope.
But, uh...well, first I need you to
pack off the boys. Yes, I know,
the day you never thought would
arrive has. Now, Cordell will fax
the veterinary forms directly to
Animal and Plant HeaIth
but you need to get the vet
affidavits from Sardinia.
Yeah. Va bene?
-Uh-huh, bene, bene.
Uh, how are they?
Ah, they are big, Mason. Very big.
Tommaso!
Say again?
-They are big, Mason. Really big.
Maybe twohundred and seventy kilos.
-Oh, wow!
Can you hear?
Oh, they sound fantastic!
Oh, super!
The full balance of the money is
payable upon receiptof the doctor
alive. Of course, you won't have to
seize him yourself. Rather just point
him out. In fact, it's preforable to
all concerned if that's the extent
of your involvement from this point.
I prefer to stay involved.
To make sure things go right.
Professionals will see to that.
-I am a professional.
You enjoy the performance?
-Oh, very much.
Um, Allegra, this is Doctor Fell,
curator of the Capponi Library.
Signora Pazzi. I'm honored.
-Are you from America, Doctor?
Not originally. I've traveled there.
-I've always wanted to visit.
New Εngland, especially.
-I've enjoyed excellent meals there.
You wrapped up in the libretto.
I thought this might amuse you.
Dante's sonnet from La Vita Nuova.
-Mm-hm. It's beautiful.
Rinaldo, look at this.
-Oh, yes, I can see.
"Joyous Love seemed to me, the while
he held my heart in his hands
and in his arms my lady lay asleep
wrapped in a veil."
"He woke her then and trembling and
obedient, she ate that burning heart
out of his hand. Weeping,
I saw him then depart from me."
Doctor Fell, do you believe a man
could become so obsessed with a woman
from a single encounter?
-Could he daily foel a stab of hunger
fοr her and find nourishment in the
very sight of her?
I think so. But would she see
through the bars of his plight
and ache for him?
Please keep that.
Oh, I couldn't.
-I insist.
Commendatore. Allegra.
Ciao.
-Ciao.
Uh, good-bye.
-Let's get something to eat.
Of course.
-Why not?
Is that you, Doctor?
Questura. Pandolfini.
-Chief Inspector Rinaldo Pazzi please.
Agent Starling, American F.B.I.
-All right. Εh, one moment.
Pazzi! F.B.I.
-I'm not here!
Pazzi.
-Inspector Pazzi, Agent Starling,
F.B.I. How do you do?
-I was just leaving fοr the day.
Can I call you back tomorrow?
-Oh, this won't take long.
First of all, I'd like to thank you
for sending us the security tape.
When I say you, I mean your department.
Agent Benetti.
Is he there? Can I speak with him?
-I'm sorry, he's gone home.
Oh, that's all right. I should tell
you this rather than him anyway.
I'm late for an important appointment.
-Well, the person I'm looking for,
Inspector, who was indeed shown on
that tape, is Hannibal Lecter.
Who?
-Doctor Hannibal Lecter. Never heard?
Umm, uh, I'm not familiar.
-And the tape confirms
that he is, or was recently,
in Florence.
Oh, really?
-He's a very dangerous man, Inspector.
He's killed 1 4 people that we know of.
-I really have to go, Miss, uh, eh?
Starling. Just another minute. Are you
sure you've never heard of him?
No, I haven't.
-I'm confused, because someone there
has been accessing our private VlCAP
files on Doctor Lecter with some
regularity on your computer.
-Εverybody uses everybody's computer
here. Maybe one of the detectives on
II Mostro was looking at profiles
of killers...
-I'm speaking about the computer
at your home, sir. You're trying to
catch him yourself, aren't you?
For the reward. I cannot warn you
strongly enough against that.
He killed three policemen down in
Memphis while in custody,
tearing the face off one of them,
and he will kill you, too, if...
Yes?
-I want him out of Tuscany fast.
Believe me he'll be gone from the
face of the Εarth fast.
Feet first.
Because of his avarice and his
betrayal of the Εmperor's trust
Pier della Vigna was disgraced,
blinded and imprisoned.
Dante's pilgrim finds Pier della Vigna
on the seventh level of the Inferno,
and like Judas Iscariot,
he died by hanging.
So Judas and Pier della Vigna are
linked in Dante by the avarice he saw
in them. In fact, avarice and hanging
are linked in the medieval mind.
Now this was the earliest known
depiction of the Crucifixion,
carved on an ivory box in Gaul about
A.D. fοur hundred.
It includes the death by hanging of
Judas, his face upturned to the
branch that suspends him.
Here he is again on the doors
of the Benevento Cathedral,
this time with his bowels falling out.
Ah, Commendatore Pazzi.
-It wasn't easy, but I got
this number without tellin' 'em why.
-Sorry.
Not at all. Welcome.
Please join us.
Now, in this plate from the fifteenth
century edition of the Inforno,
Pier della Vigna's body hangs from a
bleeding tree. I will not belabor the
obvious parallel with Judas Iscariot,
but Dante Alighieri
needed no drawn illustration. It was
his genius to make Pier della Vigna,
now in hell speak in strained hisses
and coughing sibilants as though
he is hanging still.
Come l'aItre verrem per nostre
spoglie.
Ma no pero ch'alcuna sen rivesta.
Che non e giusto aver cio ch'om si
toglie. Que le strascineremo,
e per la mesta selva saranno i nostri
corpi appesi.
Ciascuno al prun de l'ombra
sua molesta.
Avarice, hanging, self-destruction.
lo fei guibbetto a me de le mie case.
I make my own home be my gallows.
Thank you, ladies and gentlemen,
for your kind attention.
I'm not a scholar, but I think you've
got the job.
Thank you.
-May I buy you a drink?
Fine. I'll gathering my things.
-Oh, well, take your time.
Yeah?
-Allegra, I'll be home just a little
later than I said. I'm taking Doctor
Fell out for a drink. Yes.
Yeah. I can see the people
coming out now.
Yes, bye, honey. My wifo.
-Of course.
Oh, I should have shown them this one.
I can't imagine how I missed it.
I told you about it. It's a rendering
I fοund in the Capponi library.
Can you make it out?
There's a name there.
The one I told you about?
It's your ancestor, Commendatore,
hanging beneath these very windows.
Francesco de Pazzi.
On a related subject,
I must confoss to you
I'm giving very serious thought
to eating your wife.
So I'll ask you the questions
and then we'll see, all right?
Okay?
Now, was it Mason Verger
you sold me to?
No, no, no.
Blink twice for yes, once fοr no.
Was it Mason Verger you sold me to?
Yes? Good. Thank you. And are
his men waiting fοr me outside?
Was that a single blink?
Oh, you're confused. Well, please
don't be confused, because I may have
to fillet Signora Pazzi after all.
Have you told anyone
in the Questura about me?
No, I thought not.
Have you told Allegra?
No? You sure?
I believe you.
Okey-dokey, here we go.
Okay.
Your heart is really palpitating.
Oh, it's not your heart.
Well, shall I answer it?
Pronto.
-I've spoken to your section chief.
Someday you'll thank me, or you won't.
I don't care. You'll be alive.
Inspector Pazzi?
-Is this Clarice?
Well, hello, Clarice.
I'm afraid I have bad news fοr you.
Is he dead?
-Did you get my note? I hope you liked
the skin cream. I had it specially...
-Is he dead, Doctor Lecter?
Clarice, there's nothing in this world
that I would love more than to be able
to chat with you. Unfοrtunately,
you've caught me at an awkward moment.
Please fοrgive me. See you around.
An old friend.
Okay, hold on.
Here we go.
I'll go around back! Cut him!
Kill him if you have to!
So, what's it to be? Bowels in or
bowels out? Like Judas.
Are you confused? Then I'll decide
for you, if you'll permit me.
Ciao.
Carlo!
Yes?
Good evening.
Cordell,
to you, does that look like a
wave good-bye
or hello?
So, what do you think?
Does Lecter want to
fuck her or kill her or eat her or what?
-Probably all three,
though I wouldn't want to predict
in what order.
Here's what I think. No matter how
Barney might want to romanticize
it or make it "Beauty and the Beast".
Lecter's object,
as I know from personal experience,
has always been degradation
and suffering, but..
Cordell, get this damn thing off me.
I can't breathe in this thing.
He comes in the guise of a mentor,
as he did with me and her.
But it's distress that excites him.
To draw him
she needs to be distressed.
To make her attractive to him,
let him see her distressed.
Let the damage he sees
suggest the damage
he could do.
When the fox hears the rabbit scream,
he comes a-runnin'
but not to help.
-I don't understand.
Well, there's nothing to understand,
Paul. All you have to understand is,
is what it's worth to you.
-No, no, I don't understand
why she didn't turn this over. I mean,
she's such a straight arrow.
She didn't turn it over because
she didn't receive it. She didn't
receive it because it was never sent.
It was never sent because Lecter
didn't write it, because I did.
-Oh!
So, what do you think?
-You'd have been better off if you
never got her out of trouble.
-Oh, woulda, shoulda, coulda! I meant,
what do you think about the money?
-Five.
Ha! Oh, well, let's just
toss it off, like "5". Let's say it
with the respect it deserves.
-Five hundred thousand dollars.
That's better. Well, will it work?
-It'll work. It won't be pretty.
What ever is?
Cocksucker.
-I've never seen this before.
Then how do you account for its being
fοund in your office? Your basement.
How do you want me to answer that?
Let me ask you this: What possible
reason might I have to withhold it?
-Perhaps because of the content.
Reads to me like a love letter.
-Has it been tested fοr prints?
No prints on it. Like the last one.
-Handwriting analysis?
"Did you ever think, Clarice, why the
Philistines don't understand you?
It's because you're the answer to
Samson's riddle: You are the honey in
the lion." It sounds like him to me.
-Do you mean, like a homosexual?
Like a nut with a crush.
-Εxcuse me...
I am placing you on administrative
leave till Document Analysis tells me
unequivocally a mistake's been made.
You remain eligible for insurance and
medical benefits. Surrender your
weapons and your identification.
I want to say something. I'm entitled.
-Go ahead.
I think Verger is trying to capture
Dr. Lecter for the purposes of
personal revenge. And Mr. Krendler is
in collusion with him and wants the
F.B.I.'s effοrts to work fοr Verger.
I think he is being paid to do this.
You're lucky you're not sworn here.
-Swear me! You swear, too!
Clarice, if the evidence is lacking,
you'll be entitled to full
reinstatement without prejudice.
lf you don't do or say anything
in the meantime that would make
that impossible.
Relieved of field duty pending an
internal affairs into the charges,
Agent Starling, began her career with
an assignment to interview madman
Hannibal Lecter. Εarlier today we
heard comments from Justice Department
spokesman Paul Krendler.
-Mr. Krendler, can you comment the
decision at this morning's meeting?
-F.B.I. and Justice Department are
looking carefully into the charges,
and, yes, they're extremely serious.
I'd like to add a personal note.
Starling is one of the best agents
that we have...
No, no, no, no, no. Stay. Stay.
Do you think that...
-Look, it's much too soon
to condemn her. Okay?
Shh...shh...shh.
Good boy.
Ah, and this.
I think she's nice.
She's always been nice to me. Polite.
Don't you think?
-Do you know what a roller pigeon is?
Roller pigeons climb high and fast,
then roll over and
fall just as fast towards the earth.
There are shallow and deep rollers.
But you can't breed two deep rollers,
or their young, their offspring,
will roll all the way down, hit and
die. Agent Starling is a deep roller.
Let's hope one of her parents was not.
Hello?
-The power on that battery is low.
I would have changed it, but I didn't
want to wake you. You're gonna have to
use the other one, in the charger.
Hopefully the light on it is green.
This is gonna be a long call. Εven
though you've been stripped of your
duties, I know you wouldn't abandon
them, you'll try to put on a trace.
So, we'll disconnect long enough for
you to exchange the battery.
Shall we say...uh, three seconds?
Are you ready?
Yes.
-Go.
Very good.
-Thank you.
Remember, Clarice, if you get caught
with a concealed, unlicensed firearm
in the District of Columbia,
the penaIty is pretty stiff.
But bring the guns if you have to.
Now get in your car.
The reason we're doing it
like this, Clarice, is because
I like to watch you as we speak,
with your eyes open. No, it
does not excite me. It pleases me.
You have very shapely feet.
Where are we now? Call it out.
-Massachusetts Avenue.
Take it.
-I thought, to begin with,
you might tell me how you're feeling.
-About what?
The masters you serve and how they've
treated you. Your career,
such as it is. Your life, Clarice.
-I thought we might talk about yours.
What's the next cross street?
-Capitol Street.
In 2 blocks make a left into
Union Station. Park.
My lifo? What is there say about mine?
I have been in a state of hibernation
for some time. A little inactive.
But now I'm back home.
I'm very happy and very heaIthy.
You, though,
it's you I'm worried about.
-I'm fine.
No, you're certainly not fine.
You fell in love with the Bureau,
the institution, only to discover,
after giving it everything you've got
that it does not love you back. That,
in fact, it resents you. Resents you
more than the husband and children you
gave up to it. Why is that,
do you think? Why are you so resented?
-Tell me.
Tell you? God bless you.
Well, isn't it clear?
You serve the idea of order,
Clarice. They don't.
You believe in the oath you took.
They don't. You feel it is your duty
to protect the sheep. They don't.
They don't like you because
you're not like them. They hate you
and they envy you. They're weak and
unruly and believe in nothing.
-Mason Verger wants to kill you.
Turn yourself in to me,
and I promise no one will hurt you.
Will you stay with me in my prison
cell and hold my hand, Clarice?
We could have some fun. No, Verger
does'nt want to kill me any more than
I want to kill him. He just wants to
see me suffer in an unimaginable way.
He is rather twisted, you know. Have
you had the pleasure of meeting him?
I have.
-Face to face, so to speak?
Yes.
-Attractive, isn't he?
Doctor Lecter? Doctor Lecter?
Okay, back to you. I want to know what
it is you think you will do now that
everything in the world you've ever
cared about has been taken from you.
I don't know, Doctor Lecter.
-Tell me, Clarice. Do you think
you'll work as a chambermaid
at a motel on Route 66,
just like your mommy?
What do you think now? Are you paying
attention to me, ex-Special Agent?
Are you, by any chance, trying
to trace my whereabouts?
I'm being followed, Doctor Lecter.
-I know. I've seen them.
And now you're in a real dilemma,
aren't you? Do you continue to try
to find me, knowing that you're
leading them to me?
Do you have so much faith in your
abilities that you believe you
could somehow simuItaneously arrest
me and them? It could get very messy.
Like the fish market. Hey, Clarice.
-Yeah?
What if I did it for you?
-Did what?
Harmed them, Clarice.
The ones who have harmed you.
What if I made them scream apologies?
No, I shouldn't even say it,
because you'll foel, with your perfoct
grasp of right and wrong,
that you were somehow accompli.
-Don't help me.
No of course not.
Forget I said it.
Piero.
Clarice, you were very, very warm.
You were so close.
But now you're getting colder again.
Yeah warmer again.
Well, I think I've been generous
enough with you, and the clues.
You're on your own now, Clarice.
-Doctor Lecter?
Hope you like them, Clarice.
Ta-ta.
Va bene.
Get out of the way!
I know the first thing an hysteric
says is, I am not an hysteric,
but I am not an hysteric. I'm calm.
-I'll ask you one time. Think good.
Think about every good thing you ever
did. Think about what you swore.
Two men in a van. A third driving.
Another man down. They put him in the
back. I think it was Lecter. I've
given you the license plate, and I'm
reporting it all to you again.
-All right.
I'll go with it as a kidnapping.
I'll send someone out with,
if he' ll let us on the property.
-I should go, too. Deputize me.
No. You're not going.
You're going home
where you'll wait for me to call and
tell you what, if anything, we found.
Thank Mr. Verger for look around.
-He's always happy to see you.
Phone.
-What number, please?
Carlo.
Piero.
Hello?
-How is he?
Uh, sleeping.
-Bring him home.
You've reached Clarice Starling.
Please leave a message.
Pick up, Starling. There was nothing
out there. I'm gonna say it again,
in case you didn't hear me clearly:
You are not a law officer while you're
on suspension. You're Joe Blow.
I hope, you're in the bathroom.
Hylochoerus Meinertzhageni.
Ring any bells from high
school biology, Doctor?
No? Well, I could list its most
conspicuous features,
if that would help jog the memory.
Three pairs of incisors,
one pair of elongated canines,
three pairs of molars,
fοur pairs of pre-molars,
upper and lower,
for a total of forty-four teeth.
The meal will begin with an
hors d'oeuvre tartare.
Your foet.
The main course, the rest of you,
won't be served until 7 hours later.
But during that time
you'll be able to enjoy the effects
of the consumed appetizer with a
full-bodied saline drip.
I guess you wish now you'd,
you'd fod the rest of me to the dogs.
No, Mason. No, I much prefer
you the way you are.
So, dinner at eight.
You will stay fοr the evening's
entertainment, won't you, Cordell?
lf it's all right with you
I think I'd rather not.
Rather not or will not?
Your little brother must smell
almost as badly as you do by now.
Hold it! Hands where I can see 'em!
-Si.
Quiet!
-Si. Vai!
What was that? Cordell, quickly!
Down on your stomach!
-Good evening, Clarice.
It's just like old times.
-Shut up.
Can you walk?
-I can try.
You look well.
-I'm gonna cut you loose.
lf you touch me, I'll shoot you.
-Understood.
Do right and you'll live through this.
-Spoken like a true Protestant.
Better hurry. This might go faster if
you hand me the knife.
There was a third in the loft.
Behind me.
Cordell! Get the gun and shoot him!
-Go into the pen?
Yes!
-No. I'm staying out of this.
You're involved is what you are,
in all of it. Now do it!
No.
-Yes!
Hey, Cordell! Why don't you push
him in? You can always say it was me.
Cordell?
Cordell? Cordell! Cordell!
I'll be at my lake house all weekend.
Don't want any calls fοrwarded either,
you understand? Whoever it is,
they can all wait, okay?
Mary, listen, it's Fourth of July,
for Christ's sakes. Thank you.
What the fuck?
Good, you brought the wine.
-Oh, God! Oh!
Yeah, we've traced your call and units
will be there in about ten minutes.
lf you can do it safely,
then just get out of the house.
Otherwise, stay on the phone with me.
Ma'am? Are you there?
Are those shallots?
-Mm-hm. And caper berries.
Ah. That butter smells wonderful.
-Mm-hm. You foeling hungry, Paul?
V ery.
What's the main course?
-Ah you should never ask.
It spoils the surprise.
Clarice, what are you doing up?
You should be resting. Back to bed.
-I'm hungry.
Hello, Paul.
-Paul, don't be rude.
Say, "Hello, Agent Starling."
-Hello, Agent Starling.
I always wanted to watch you eat.
-What have you got in your hand?
Something to bash me over the head
with? Put it on the table.
Good girl.
-Hey, that's mine.
Now sit down.
Hey, Clarice. I love the dress.
It's beautiful.
What do you think, Paul?
-Nice. Nice.
Why don't you say grace, Paul?
Me?
-Yeah.
Grace?
-Sure.
Okay. Bow your head.
Father, we thank Thee fοr Thy
blessings and dedicate them to
Thy mercy we are about to receive.
Forgive us all, even white trash
like Starling here
and bring her into my service.
Amen.
Now I have to tell you, Paul, even the
Apostle Paul couldn't have do better.
He hated women, too.
-May I have some wine, please?
No good idea. Not with the morphine.
Better you should eat some broth.
By the way, Starling, that was a job
offaring I worked into the blessing.
I'm going to Congress, you know.
-Are you?
Come around campaign headquarters.
You could be a office girl!
Can you type and file?
Can you take dictation?
Take this down:
Washington is full of corn-pone
country pussy.
-I took it down.
You said it already.
-Paul, now you're being rude.
And I hate rude people. Drink your
broth like a good boy.
Come on. Sip.
Good.
Ugh. It's not very good, buddy.
-I admit I added something to yours.
It's clashing with the cumin. But l
assure you, the next is to die fοr.
Ah, ah, ah! Come on, Clarice.
-No.
That's a good girl. Good.
You see, the brain itself feels no
pain, Clarice, if that concerns you.
For example, Paul won't miss this
little piece here, which is the part
of the prefrontal lobe which they
say is the seat of good manners.
Your profile at the border stations
has five foatures. I'll trade you.
Trade?
-Stop...
How does that word taste to you?
Cheap and metallic
like sucking on a greasy coin?
-Who's Clarice?
Agent Starling. lf you can't keep up
with the dialog, don't try to join.
Me, me, Paul. I'm Starling.
-See.
Here, right here is the sac
that contains the brain.
I would really like some wine!
That smells great.
-Yes. Why don't you try a piece?
I would really like some wine.
It is good.
-All right. But just a little.
Okay? No?
Given the chance, you would deny
me my life, wouldn't you?
Not your lifo.
-My freedom. You'd take that from me.
And if you did, would they have
you back, do you think? The F.B.I.?
Those people you despise almost
as much as they despise you?
Would they give you a medal? Would you
have it professionally framed
and hang it on your wall to look at
and remind you of your
courage and incorruptibility?
All you would need for that,
Clarice, is a mirror.
I had plans fοr that smart mouth,
but I'm never gonna hire her, you now.
Paul?
-Paul?
Remember what I said?
lf you can't be polite to our guests
you have to sit at the kiddies' table.
Don't get up, Clarice.
Paul will help me clear
and make the coftee.
Just think about what I said, Clarice.
Coffee.
I came halfway around the world
to watch you run, Clarice.
Let me run, huh?
Tell me, Clarice
would you ever say to me,
Stop? lf you love me, you'd stop?
Not in a thousand years.
That's my girl.
Now that's really interesting,
Clarice. I'm really pressed fοr time
so where's the key?
Where's the key?
Okay.
Above or below the wrist, Clarice?
This is really gonna hurt.
Show me your hands!
ldentify yourself!
-I'm Clarice Starling! F.B.I. !
Hi.
-Hi. What's that?
Oh, that's caviar.
-What are those?
These are figs.
-And that?
And this?
Oh, that I don't think you would like.
-It looks good.
Oh, it is good.
-Can I have some?
You're a very unusual boy, aren't you?
-I couldn't eat what they gave me.
Nor should you. It isn't even fοod
as I understand the definition.
Which is why I always bring my own.
So which would you like to try?
Aha.
Well, I suppose it's all right.
After all, as your mother tells you,
and my mother certainly told me,
It is important, she always used to
say, always to try new things.
Open up.