Watch Movies, TV Series and Live Sports
Signup Here -> WWW.ADMITME.APP
Go!
- Morning.
- Yes, it is.
Shit!
Come on!
- You got $1.25 on there?
- Is this machine working?
Is my machine working?
- There you go. Five quarters.
- Yes.
We've got a lot of people in a hurry
here. So whatever you can do.
Sir, it's what I've got.
I got you.
There you go.
Hey, the machine's working.
- $1.25.
- All right, have a seat.
Open the fuckin' door!
Sir, I don't even know
what you're talking...
- So you don't know what I'm talking about?
- No, sir, no. I do not.
That's interesting, because we have you
and your little slut bunny
on camera getting all nice and cozy
with the same guy in the parking lot.
So I'm going to ask you again...
Who is this fuckin' guy
and where is our fuckin' money?
I... I don't know.
There's only so many ways
that I can ask you nicely.
This... this is nicely?
Fuck.
Oh, fuckin' Christ, man!
What the fuck? What the fuck?
Fuck! Fuckin'...
No.
- God!
- Damn it! Let go of me!
- Babe... baby, I'm so fuckin' sorry.
- Oh, my God, baby! What did they do to you?
- We don't know who he is, asshole!
- I'm sorry.
Asshole? Okay.
Asshole, it is.
She didn't mean that!
She didn't mean it!
Derrick!
Derrick. Derrick.
Bat's not always the answer.
Funny thing about these e-cigarettes.
I miss the satisfaction of burning something
down to fuckin' ashes in your hand.
My apologies.
Derrick can be
a little overzealous at times.
- Mr. Pope, this is just...
- I'm not finished.
I've been Derrick's mentor for a while
now. I taught him everything he knows...
how to run a casino floor,
how to run a business,
how to really run a business,
but most importantly,
how to spot a thief.
Because in our business,
the number 1 rule is
"Never let anyone steal from you,"
because if even one person steals
from you, even as little as...
- 10 Gs.
- ...$10,000,
it's a sign of weakness. It's a drop
of blood in shark-infested waters,
a hole in your defense.
And when people think you're weak,
they come in droves to take what's yours.
Like flies to the proverbial shit.
Normally I'd give Derrick here all night
to make your regret stealing from me.
No, but we didn't...
But now, you've made me late for my own
surprise party. So here's what we're gonna do,
I'm going to give you both 10 seconds
to tell me where the money is
and whose idea it was
to take it in the first place,
or Derrick here kills you both...
- Oh, God!
- ...and I lose out on 10 grand,
which, frankly, means shit to me.
'Cause you know what?
This is about principle, not money.
- No, please.
- It's that simple.
- Ten, nine...
- We don't know who took your fuckin' money!
- ...eight, seven...
- Please!
- ...six, five...
- No, Mr. Pope! Mr. Pope!
- ...four, three...
- We don't know who he is! Please!
- ...three...
- Mr. Pope, we don't have your money!
- ...two, one.
- Fuckin'! Glenn Haley! Glenn fuckin' Haley!
He's staying at Candlewood, 451!
And it's all her fuckin' idea!
- What? What? You fuckin' bastard!
- It's all her fuckin' idea!
I can't...
- Oh, fuck!
- You see, Derrick?
- No, fuck!
- Bat's not always the answer.
When it comes down to it, when it's you
or them, as a species, it's in our DNA,
our very nature,
to choose self-preservation.
I don't care if you're Mother Teresa,
Mahatma Gandhi or fuckin' Ned Flanders.
When the chips are down, we choose life
over loved ones, every time.
- Got it.
- You know.
Can I... Can I go now, Mr. Pope?
Sure, you can go now.
Derrick, show him the door.
30 years.
30 years, not one vacation,
not one sick day. Now he's leaving us.
- We're all going to miss you, Mr. Pope.
- I'll miss you.
He's leaving us for good.
If he owes you some money, you better get it
quick, 'cause he's out of here next week.
A toast to the man himself.
Our hope, our savior, our Pope.
Our Pope!
Ain't much of a trick
if you can't finish it, pal.
Is that your card?
How'd you do that?
I can't tell you that.
That's why it's magic.
Slight of hand, my friend. While you're busy
watching the deck in the left hand,
the magic was happening in the right.
Not sure if I want you
handling my cards, friend.
Will you excuse me for a moment?
Dealer change.
Very nice party, Mr. Pope.
You are a very loved man.
Thank you, Mr. Tao.
Whoever said money can't buy love
clearly just didn't have enough.
This place will never be
the same without you.
I feel your absence may change
my luck at the tables.
You got nothing to worry about, Mr. Tao.
Mr. Prince will make sure the Swan's tables
are still the luckiest in the city.
That's all I needed to hear.
- Sorry. Good to see you.
- You need some water?
I'm okay. I just need
a minute in the office.
Mr. Pope? Mr. Pope?
What do you need?
- I'd like to have a word with him.
- Not tonight.
You've reached Sydney.
Please leave your name and number
and I'll get back to you as soon as possible.
Hey, Syd, it's me.
I was really hoping to see you tonight.
I know you're busy, but...
give me a call when you get this. Bye.
Carol.
- Hey.
Any changes?
No.
Jesus, Luke. It's not going to cover
what we owe on last month's bill.
I'm doing the best I can, Julie.
What? What is it?
I'm sorry, Mr. Vaughn,
but we've given you ample time.
There comes a time
when we have to accept reality.
So what? I'm supposed to sit by helplessly
and watch my little girl suffer?
We're talking about my little girl here.
You give me until the end of the week.
You understand? You give me
until the end of the week.
- I'll get you every penny by Friday.
- Mr. Vaughn.
- Just listen to me.
- Mr. Vaughn...
Every penny by Friday.
You keep her name on that list.
She's going to get that surgery.
I will get you every penny.
Please.
Friday, Mr. Vaughn.
Friday.
Hey. Talking about Princess Riley here
and her best friend Monkey.
And they were going to go into...
was it a very enchanted magical forest
or was it a very scary forest?
- Scary forest.
- Oh, my goodness. Of course it is.
Okay, so Princess Riley
and her best friend, Monkey...
Stop.
I don't want to be the hero tonight.
But you're the bravest
little girl I know.
I want you to be the hero.
I want you to save me.
Okay. I think that is a great idea.
Princess Riley and Monkey,
they got to the very creaky bridge.
And there's an ogre that comes out
from underneath the bridge.
- What do you think the ogre's name is?
- Luke.
Smoke?
- Nah, I quit.
- Health?
- Money, actually.
- This one's free.
Thank you.
Vaughn, right?
Heard you've been
working here a long time.
- Too long.
- Bet you've seen some crazy shit.
Yeah, man, I've seen some crazy shit.
Been here about three
or four months myself.
And I've seen some crazy shit.
Like this fat Chinese guy
who comes in every week...
biggest fucking loser, this guy.
This guy drops a buttload of money
every Thursday, just like clockwork.
Well...
you play long enough,
the house always wins.
It's the way this guy loses...
making all the wrong bets,
holding when he shouldn't,
not splitting when he should.
Fuckin' guy wants to lose.
Shitload of money, every Thursday night.
Nobody's got that kind
of fuckin' money to burn.
You know what's ever crazier?
Every Friday night, a different Chinese guy
comes to the high-rollers table,
plays roulette, and wins fuckin' huge.
I'm talking statistic-anomaly
fuckin' huge.
Every Friday night,
like fuckin' clockwork.
Why don't you just cut to the chase
and tell me what's on your mind?
The way it appears to me,
is they're taking in a shitload
of money every Thursday night
and laundering it out
through the casino.
You're telling me this because?
Put 'em in an awful bad spot, if someone
were to rob them of that money.
It's not like they're going
to go crying to the police
about someone stealing their dirty cash.
Well, sounds like
you've got this all figured out.
I do, except for one piece.
I need a guy who's been here too long,
smoking habit he can't afford,
and access to the vault.
- Thanks for the cigarette.
- So any thoughts on the matter?
Yeah. Stealing from the Pope...
is suicide.
The number you have reached
is not in service at this time
and there is no new number...
Yeah?
Got that address you wanted.
Also a Luke Vaughn wants a meeting.
All right, send him in. Shit.
Luke Vaughn.
What can I do for you? Sit down.
I was wondering if we
could have a word in private.
Everything we say here is private.
How are you, sir?
I'm still breathing, Vaughn.
Still breathing.
Well, that's good. I suppose
that's more than some can say.
Oh, indeed.
How's that pretty little wife of yours?
- Ex-wife now, actually. She's...
- Well, fuck her. I hope you traded up.
Listen, Mr. Pope. I...
I'm here to ask a favor, a big one.
- How big?
- $300,000 big, at least.
What do you need $300,000
at least for, Vaughn?
You remember my daughter Riley.
She's sick, in the hospital.
- Needs an operation.
- Insurance?
Insurance doesn't even
cover the treatments.
Been paying out of pocket
for a month and I'm behind.
So far behind that if I don't come up with
money by Friday, she's gonna lose her spot.
You know I don't run
a charity here. Rule number 3.
"It's not a business
if you give the money away."
I remember the rules.
This isn't charity. It's a favor.
$300,000 that I'm never going to see
again sure sounds like charity to me.
No, sir. I will pay it back.
I sign your paycheck, Vaughn.
Who are you kidding?
- Mr. Pope, you're my only option.
- I don't make exceptions.
Let me ask you something...
what if it were you?
What if you were in my shoes
and your kid was sick?
- Hey, hey, time's up.
- What if Sydney was sick?
- Nobody's talking to you.
- That's all the time you get.
- No, it's not all the time I get.
- Mr. Pope already answered your question.
I don't accept his fucking answer!
God damn it, get your fuckin' hands off me.
I don't care what you don't accept.
Get the fuck out of here.
What about the shit
that I've done for you?
What do you want? A fuckin' cookie?
What you did for me? You didn't do shit for me.
You fuckin' ran away. I let you go away.
You wanted to start a new life, you found God.
I didn't want my little girl
growing up hating me
- for the man I'd become!
- Get out of here.
You've got what you want,
I got what I want. Go!
- Like you, God damn it! Fuck!
- Move it!
- You're a bad bet!
- Get your fuckin' hands off me.
- Hey!
- Damn it, don't touch me!
You're fuckin' fired.
Get him the fuck out of here.
- That was awkward.
- Yeah, well...
What's with that guy? What's his deal?
That guy would have been you, but he
found love or religion, some bullshit.
He just left everything.
He turned it all down.
I don't know, Derrick. What do you think?
Maybe I should have just given him the money?
I don't think the younger you
would've even considered that an option.
"Don't let sentiment
cloud your judgment.
"Relationships come and go,
but principles...
"principles are here to stay."
Frank Pope.
Glad someone was listening.
Hey, ladies. Looking good.
I'm in.
But I was just fired,
so if you want the vault codes,
it's pretty much going
to have to be tomorrow night.
Let's do it.
Who the fuck are these guys?
My boy Dante.
Mickey.
Hey, man.
This isn't what we agreed to.
I've known this guy since we were kids.
His favorite color is blue.
He lost his virginity to Becky McCormick.
Of course, I fucked her first.
Anything you want to know, just ask.
What's his dick taste like?
Relax. Dante's bringing the guns.
- Mickey's got the car.
- Who said anything about guns?
Feel free to leave yours
with your fuckin' mommy.
I'm not walking in there
with just my dick in my hand.
You do know
who we're dealing with, right?
We go in there with guns,
Pope catches us, we're dead.
It's my operation, Vaughn.
The guns stay.
You don't like it,
take a fuckin' walk right now.
Otherwise, nobody else here
has a problem with it.
So we good?
What's your plan?
Walk in there just after closing,
stick our shotguns in their fuckin' faces.
They'll be all tired and shit.
They're not going to do anything.
Grab the green stacks,
walk the fuck out by dawn.
- Keep it simple.
- Yeah.
Well, simple is usually the best,
but what you've got here
is the simplest way for us
to get our asses shot off.
You got a better fuckin' idea,
we'd love to hear it.
- Swan?
- Swan.
You got the vault, transformer room.
Pepper's the vault.
- Sugar should be the vault.
- What?
It's sweet. Everybody wants it.
Makes sense for the money to be the sugar.
Fine. Sugar's the vault.
Cox, you're the ketchup.
Mickey is Sweet'N Low. I'm the salt.
Dante, you're the pepper.
- Why do I got to be the pepper?
- 'Cause I'm running out of fuckin' condiments.
- Dante, shut the fuck up.
- Nobody steals from the Swan.
But that's because they're afraid
of the Pope, not because it's Fort Knox.
The way I see it,
we've got three things going for us.
One, we have the access codes.
That's on me.
Two, we have the inside man. That's you.
Three, we have knowledge
of a certain security guard
that likes his donuts and coffee
and precisely 3:25 every night.
- Every night?
- Every night. Everybody with me so far?
Mickey, you following me?
Yeah, I'm following you.
This is you with the car. Can I trust
the car won't link back to us?
You're going to pick Dante and I up
right here at this bar at 3:00 a.m.
- Where am I?
- You're at work.
You finish your shift,
clock out, don't leave.
Find your way to the transformer
room and wait.
- Until?
- 3:30.
There'll only be a few employees
hanging around by then.
You... you're going to be
parked up here.
Right by the scrambled eggs. Cool.
This gives you a straight direction
south on the freeway.
- Don't fuck it up.
- You said you got a straight shot,
- not we got a straight shot.
- There is no "we."
We make it out of the Swan alive,
I'm on my own.
You have a problem with that?
As long as we got our money,
I don't give a rat's ass where you go.
Let me know if you need
a quick tutorial.
Where'd you learn to do that?
Fort Beginning for Boys.
- Army?
- Yeah. I served.
The only thing I served
is fries, my friend.
I'd never have guessed.
Dante and I will lock-bump our way
onto the Swan's main floor.
The main casino floor's empty at the time
of night. Everyone goes below to close out.
Go, go, go.
As long as I've known him, good old
Jerry likes to take a leisurely stroll
to the break room for a stale donut
and coffee right at 3:25.
All the inner doors are maglocked
with a three-point security seal.
The vault itself is on a secure circuit.
The rest of the system
is hooked into the ship's old wiring.
So wait for me and Dante
to get into position.
At exactly 3:30 a.m.,
you kill the power.
Let's go, let's go, let's go.
From the time the lights go out,
we have 10 minutes to get in and out
before back-up generators come on
and lock down the ship.
Come on, let's go. Move.
Let's go, let's go.
Quick, come on. Let's go.
This way. Let's hope
this fucking code works.
All right, you motherfucker, unlock.
- What?
- Can you come back later, please?
Thank you.
Let's go!
Move.
Green bags only, dirty stuff.
Let's go, in the bags. Hurry.
No, we're good.
Come on.
- Let's do this.
- Come on.
Come on, come on, come on.
Come on, guys, come on.
- Fuckin' A!
- Let's go! Quit fuckin' around.
- Let's go, come on. Get the bags.
- That's right.
- That's nice, get out.
- Let's get out.
- Let's get out of here.
- Let's go.
Shit.
If something goes bad, what's plan B?
Plan B is run for your fucking life.
Let's go, let's go, let's go!
Shit, shit.
Motherfuckers!
Ready? Go!
Dante!
I got you, man.
I'm getting the fuck out of here.
Come on! Get out of here, Mickey.
Come on, get out of here.
Get the fuck out of here.
What the fuck? Un-fuckin' believable!
- This way, follow me.
- Asshole!
This way! Fuck! Come on.
Let's go, buddy. Come on.
- Fuck!
- Come on, man! Let's get out of here!
- This way!
- Go, go, go, go! Here!
- Morning.
- Yes, it is.
- Ma?
- Hi, honey.
- Mom, what are you doing awake?
- I couldn't sleep.
- Your medication isn't working?
- I haven't taken it yet.
I was thinking of taking
the dog out for a walk.
It's 4:00 a.m., Ma.
- I worry about you.
- I'll be fine.
God damn it, run.
Come on!
All right, I love you.
Good night.
Come on.
Go.
Please, please.
Open the fuckin' door!
Let's go!
Close the door and drive.
Everybody be cool.
We'll be out of here in a second.
Cops!
Take your mask off. We gotta blend in.
Fuck.
Everybody act normal, nobody gets hurt.
This is Officer Bauhaus.
Multiple shots fired. I'm in pursuit.
Fuck.
- She wants me to pull over!
- Keep driving.
Fuck this!
Shots fired. In pursuit
of at least one armed suspect.
Don't ever put
your fucking hands on me again.
Pretty sure shooting a cop
is not very good for our situation.
I'm in charge!
- Please describe the bus, over.
- Bus number 657. I repeat, 657.
- I'm in charge.
- Noted.
I'm gonna make this
real fucking simple for you.
Lose that cop,
or lose your goddamn life.
Whatever you say. We're cool.
Calling all units,
possible hostage situation.
Commuter bus... bus number 657.
I repeat, bus 657.
- Head I-10 west.
- Cox, what are you doing?
Improvising. Head I-10 west!
Go that way!
Suspect appears to be headed
towards Interstate 10 onramp, over.
You can't let them get on the highway.
All units, we have suspects
headed towards the Russell onramp.
Set up stingers just west of Waterloo,
right before the onramp.
So what do you suppose
they're up to now?
- Setting up a roadblock.
- How the fuck do you know?
Stop your vehicle.
We're setting up a roadblock.
There's nowhere for you to go.
I need a phone. Who's got a phone?
Who's got a lipstick?
Thank you.
- What's your name?
- Rebecca.
All right, Rebecca.
What's your phone number?
- Get me the fuckin' cops on this thing.
- ...0-1...
- Get me the fuckin' cops on that thing!
- All right, all right, all right!
Dispatch, this is 657.
Put me through to PD.
- Please stand by, bus 657.
- I can't stand by! Patch me through to PD!
- Do you need assistance?
- The fuckin' cops! Quit fucking around!
- I can't wait!
- Hey. I'm gonna need you to back off.
- You know I can't do that.
- Why?
'cause I'm the cop, and you're the robber.
That's the game. It's pretty black and white.
- No gray area?
- No.
Come on. There's always
a gray area, Officer...
- Bauhaus.
- All right, you got a first name?
Cops, now!
- Patch me through to the police.
- Quit fuckin' around!
Kris, I need you to clear the roadblock.
- I need you to pull over.
- Tell them to clear the roadblock!
- Just give me a second. I'm working on it.
- Clear the goddamn roadblock!
Listen to me.
I'm going to need you to trust me.
Kris, I can't help these people on the bus
if you don't give me this one.
Stay right there. Keep your eyes on us.
But I need you to clear that roadblock.
- We gotta get on the Interstate.
- Tell them to clear the roadblock.
- They gotta clear the roadblock!
- You do this for me,
and I promise you, I give you
my word, no one gets hurt.
Tell them that people
are going to start dying.
Captain Michaels,
I need you to remove all roadblocks.
I repeat...
removal of all roadblocks, over.
Negative, Bauhaus,
I'm not letting them on the Interstate.
- But, sir, I have one of...
- The roadblock stays, Bauhaus.
- It's out of my control.
- Kris,
I've got at least 10 people on this bus,
including a little boy and a pregnant girl.
- Tell them to clear the fuckin' roadblock!
- This lunatic?
- I can't control him if this bus stops.
- Tell 'em to clear the roadblock!
You'd better keep your fucking word.
Look out, look out!
Go there!
Kris, are you there? You okay?
Eat a dick.
- You ever try a real cigarette?
- I only smoke vapor, baby.
Used to just roll tobacco in paper,
then enter the filter,
now this vapor bullshit.
If and when you ever have kids, they won't
even know what a real cigarette is.
They'll just think it's something
from old movies.
What are you saying, baby?
Everything dies.
From the moment
something's born or invented,
we're on a one-way course
with obsolescence.
Obso-what?
Yeah?
- Sorry to call you so early.
- No one calls with good news at 5:00 a.m.
Derrick, there's no right way
to break bad news. So how bad is it?
- How much?
- Three mil.
I'm sorry. Maybe I just had
a stroke on my way over here,
'cause I thought
I just heard you say $3 million.
- Yeah.
- Tell me it wasn't the house cash.
- Who?
- Vaughn, two others.
- You sure?
- Positive.
- Where are they?
- They're on a bus.
Let's recap.
A man we fired yesterday
stole $3 million,
that, if recovered by the police, implicates
us in connection to money laundering
for some of the city's most well-known
criminal families. And...
- you let them get on a bus?
- No, I didn't let them. They hijacked it.
The cops got involved.
Then I had to pull back.
- So what are you going to do about it?
- I'm gonna find 'em.
The money will be back
in this vault by tonight.
Good, Derrick.
I believe you.
Now I want to speak with Vaughn
before we finish this.
All right, we are following
this situation of a runaway bus.
Suspected hijackers are on this bus
and there is a very heavy police presence
following the bus down the highway.
Sorry, kiddo.
Bus 657, please respond.
- Bus 657, bus 657? Come in, please.
- Turn that goddamn thing down.
Are you fucking kidding me?
What the fuck is wrong with you?
Give me your goddamn phone.
Did you take my picture, bitch?
- No, I swear.
- Everybody give me your goddamn phones.
Give me your fuckin' phones.
Give me your fuckin' phone.
Give me your goddamn phone.
Put your fuckin' phone in the bag.
No, no, no, me no speak "Engrish."
Oh, no? You speak English now?
Okay, fine, sorry.
Just my whole life is on there, man.
- Give me your phone.
- I'm looking.
- Give me your goddamn phone.
- I'm looking, I'm sorry! I don't know where...
I got it, I got it.
Go ahead, go to him.
- Oh, what the fuck?
- The kid's scared, all right?
I don't give a shit.
Don't move anybody else.
Jesus Christ. You're a real pleasure
to be around, you know that?
All right, everybody,
just stay calm, all right?
I know this isn't
how you want to start your day.
You work with us here, I promise you,
you're going to get off this bus safely.
- How do you feel?
- I'm pretty cold, paisan.
Put some goddamn pressure on it.
All right, listen up!
Anybody here a doctor?
Nurse? EMT? Anybody got any kind
of medical knowledge whatsoever?
I'm a veterinarian student.
- Yeah, bring her up.
- Bring her up? What the fuck?
"Engrish," get your ass
up here and help her.
Okay, okay. I...
Honey, I know this is really scary.
We're going to get off this bus.
They're not going to hurt us.
Is that a rabbit? Does he have a name?
- Big Ear.
- Big Ear?
He used to be Big Ears,
but my sister ripped it.
Well, I think he still looks adorable,
one ear or not.
What's your name, sweetheart?
- Joseph.
- Joseph?
Honey, why are you
all alone on this bus?
- Just keep breathing.
- I can unfuck this.
I know this guy in Texas.
Runs one of those small dirt airfields.
It's right on the border. It's perfect.
We get there, we jump on a plane.
He can take us wherever the fuck we want
to go. South America, Central America.
- Hey.
- What are you doing, man?
- You're going to get us all killed.
- There's three of them and 10 of us.
If we charge them,
they don't stand a chance.
- They've got guns. I'm in a beaver suit.
- So?
- Mexico?
- I didn't say Mexico.
Just on the border. Jump on a plane,
go wherever. It's a plan.
- Why don't we just fucking drive into Mexico?
- We're not going to Mexico.
I'm going to get us out of this shit.
Cox's Sucker!
Jono?
- Sorry we put you in this situation.
- Me too.
- Remember that time you fucked my sister?
- No!
Yeah, that's 'cause it never happened.
If you want it to happen,
you'll do me a favor.
- Is he okay?
- He ran away from home.
His sister picks on him and his parents
take her side every time, apparently.
I hear that.
Move slow, a-hole.
This is not going to end well for you.
Go ahead. Take the shot.
No, I'm not fucking kidding you.
Big-ass bags of money.
Be the hero, man. What if you miss?
Cox is going to turn around,
he's going to shoot immediately.
Maybe he misses, maybe he doesn't.
What if he hits...
- What's your name?
- Pauline.
She for sure is going
to be collateral damage.
And the mascot guy? He's dead.
You're not going to do this.
Be seeing you soon. Three hours out.
- What's your name?
- Eric.
Eric?
Sit in your fuckin' seat.
We're on our way.
- What's going on?
- We need to head to Galveston, Texas.
Galveston? I'll take you
wherever you want, chief.
But we're not even going
to make Slidell on these fumes.
- Cops, this is robbers.
- What the fuck are you doing?
We're out of fuel.
We're ready to make a deal.
Hang tight, man.
You disobeyed a direct order,
endangered not only your life
and the life of your fellow officers,
but dozens of citizens' lives as well.
Anyone dies on that bus and it's on you.
- Hand over your badge and gun.
- But, sir...
I think we're a long fucking way
from "but, sir," Bauhaus.
I hope I'm not interrupting anything.
But which of you decided to...
endanger a bus full of civilian hostages
with an unauthorized roadblock?
- You must be he.
- Who the fuck are you?
Detective Marconi, lead investigator
on this little shit show.
I was sent here
by Deputy Chief Braddock,
and chief outranks captain,
so... I officially release you
of your duties and responsibilities
and I officially reinstate you,
Officer Bauhaus.
- Grab your shit, come with me.
- But, detective...
I think we're a long fucking way
from "but, detective," Captain.
That took balls doing what you did.
Why'd you do it?
There's a little kid on that bus, sir.
I hate to be the bearer of bad news,
but there's still a little kid on that bus.
When I spoke to one of the kidnappers,
there was something protective in his voice.
It was almost like he was thinking
straight, like a cop or a soldier.
Or a sociopath.
- I don't think so, detective.
- You don't think so?
- Call it a gut feeling.
- How many are we dealing with?
At least two, the psycho
and the soldier. Possibly more.
- Great.
- Sir, why did you reinstate me?
I didn't. The hijackers did,
requested you personally.
- Can you drive a fuel truck, Bauhaus?
- Does it have wheels?
You're a real fuckin' moron,
you know that?
Driving the same car to your job
as you drove to a crack house?
- I don't want...
- Shut up. You made it easy for me.
Where they headed?
Did they have an escape plan?
- Some friends? I'm talking to you.
- It's not my...
I'm talking to you.
What you got here? Let me see
what you got. Oh, look at that.
Let me see.
Man, what the fuck...
I'll do...
I don't fuckin' know. I don't know!
I don't fucking know.
- Okay?
- Go ahead.
- Okay.
- Shut up.
- What?
- He doesn't know anything.
What was that?
- Cox, Cox, Cox, Cox!
- Jason Cox?
- Cox said he's going to kill you?
- Cox is going to come.
- Please don't hurt my baby.
- Cox said he's gonna kill him?
Relax, relax, relax. Hey, hey.
Relax. Shut up.
- Please don't kill me.
- Get on your knees, get on your knees.
Please. I'll do anything. Please...
All right, boys. That bus is going
to stop on that fuckin' bridge.
- So what are our options?
- We could hit 'em hard with tear gas.
I'm not ready to gas civilians
on live television, but thanks for playing.
- Full-on assault.
- Civilian casualties?
Inevitable in that scenario,
but manageable.
- Snipers?
- We're going to need two clean shots,
lined up from the air.
But it's going to be risky.
All right, start mapping out
the assault just in case.
In the meantime, get our best guys in that
chopper. They get a clean shot, we take it.
- Roger that.
- You heard him. Let's move.
All right, Bauhaus! You good?
You're working the hell out of that vest.
Stay alert, stay alive...
make note of anything useful.
And if you can,
get us a clean visual on the gunman.
Copy that.
No. Hell no. Give 'em old man death
and that green-haired hooker back there.
Look, we give 'em the kid
and that woman,
they think we're reasonable, they see it
as a victory, it buys us more time.
No. If we keep
the pregnant chick and the kid,
it gives us more leverage
if shit goes bad.
We have one medical emergency
onboard already.
If that chick goes into labor,
they storm the bus, hostages be damned.
All they're going to give a crap about is
saving that baby in time for the 6:00 news.
We're at the bridge!
Talk to me, Forbes.
You got your boys in position?
We have eyes on the prize, sir.
Bus is heading into position.
- This is all you, Bauhaus.
- Copy that.
Bus has stopped. Bus has stopped.
Three people leaving the bus.
One suspect, one woman and a kid.
You got a clear shot?
Negative, too many bogeys,
too many bogeys. Come back around.
Suspect one by the fuel tank.
That's too risky. May ignite.
So what's the big plan?
I don't know that I have one.
Maybe start a bus company
and go head-to-head with Greyhound.
Or you could turn yourself in and let
the rest of the people off the bus.
I can't do that yet, Kris.
Hopefully soon.
What about their families?
What about your family?
There's got to be someone
out there that cares about you.
I could find them, bring them here.
I just need your name.
Good try, officer.
All right. Well... well, at least
let me check out the hostages.
You keep putting the gas in the tank,
you can do whatever you want.
They're heading into the bus, sir.
No visual on the second gunman.
What the fuck are you thinking,
bringing a cop on the bus?
Relax. She just wants to make sure everybody's
all right, we haven't hurt anybody.
- One of yours?
- Yeah.
He needs medical attention.
Let me take him out of here.
You're not taking him anywhere.
You're going to get your ass off the bus.
I always thought there was nothing sexier
than a woman who fought back.
Make one more fuckin' move.
D...
if this bitch shoots me,
kill her and everybody else
on this fucking bus.
- You got it, pal.
- All right, Kris.
Tell your boss that everybody's okay.
Fucking bitch.
Sir, suspect one and Officer Bauhaus
have exited the bus.
You got eyes on the other perp?
Negative, sir. But we have
a clean shot at suspect one.
I don't know why you're doing this,
but let me help you.
- Let me help you with your problems.
- You have no idea what my problems are.
Come on! Let's get the fuck out of here!
If you get a minute and have a chance,
will you let me know how the girl is?
Sir, should we take a shot?
It's now or never, sir. I have him.
Abort. Abort, let him go.
Go for Marconi. This is Officer Bauhaus.
Well done, Bauhaus.
What have you got for me?
...proceeding toward Texas.
Here you are. There you go. Enjoy.
Can I help...
You're a hard girl to find, Syd.
- What are you doing here, Dad?
- What? A father can't look for his daughter?
And then find her in some grimy shelter?
- Missed you at the party.
- I was busy.
- You know I'm leaving town?
- Good for you.
- I'm not sure how long.
- Need me to water your plants, feed the cat?
I was hoping to give you something.
This says you own 51% of the Swan.
Derrick will run the whole thing.
You won't have to lift a finger.
The money will just be in a trust,
with you as the sole beneficiary.
You can't buy me.
- I don't want your money.
- Sydney...
Dad, I know how this money is made.
Oh, come on, don't be so naive.
Nothing's that black and white.
- This money's as clean as the rest.
- Oh, that's bullshit.
This empire you've carved out
for yourself...
- For you.
- For yourself, it has a price.
- It cost you your wife and it cost you me.
- Sydney, please, just sign the paperwork.
- I just want you to have it.
- Why the urgency? Why now?
What?
- What's the trick?
- There's no trick. It's in my...
Are you dying?
It's in my lungs, my blood, my bones.
Nothing they can do, so...
And you're leaving, and you think
this might be the last time you see me.
You always were a smart one, Syd.
Then you should hear this
before you walk out that door.
You want to give me your empire,
your beloved Swan?
That place, that boat,
that's been a cancer for me
and for Mom and for everything
good inside of you.
That's what you're going to be
leaving behind in this world.
That's your legacy. If you love me,
if you ever really loved me,
you would take it and you would
burn it all to the ground.
You're not making any sense, Syd.
- This is real...
- Love is built on sacrifice,
not dollars.
What can I do to fix it?
Oh, my God! Joseph! Joseph!
So, are there any names you can remember?
Any details at all?
Yeah, they kept calling the one guy,
the... crazy one, Cox.
Cox? Did they mention
anything about a destination?
- Maybe why they hijacked the bus?
- I think they were being chased.
- Chased by who?
- I don't know.
Did you see anyone chasing them?
I didn't, but they were
running and sweaty,
and they kept looking out the window.
So, I mean, I don't know. Maybe I'm wrong.
How's that?
- That's perfect. What do you think?
- It's pretty... it's pretty close.
- I'll go run a search.
- Thanks, Dan.
Listen, is this going to take much longer?
There's just somewhere I really need to be.
All right. Well, yeah, we're done here.
We'll be in contact if we need
anything else. So thank you for your time.
- Of course. Anything I can do to help.
- Okay, bye.
Hello there, soldier boy.
Is that your kid?
Yup. Two tours, Iraq, one Afghanistan.
He's a company commander now,
stationed in Italy.
That's a good assignment.
You serve?
I did, a long time ago.
I thought they trained you guys
to be heroes.
Well, I seem to letting everyone down
in that department lately.
Everything's going to be okay.
I need you to keep breathing, okay?
- What's your name?
- Rebecca.
Thank you.
- If I die...
- You're not going to die.
I just...
I'm sorry.
I'm gonna be right back.
Tom, apply pressure here.
So... where's my apology?
You got tits?
- No.
- Then go fuck yourself.
My name is Jason Cox. My bill was
slightly higher than usual this month.
I believe my son has been using
my cell phone to call his girlfriend,
who unfortunately moved to Texas.
Have there been any outgoing calls
to Texas within the past week or so?
I'll just need the last four
of your social in order to proceed.
Sure, no problem. One-one-two-zero.
Yes, sir. Several calls to Galveston,
Texas. 405-5...
Yeah. Tell me something good.
Looks like they're headed to Texas,
making a run for the border or some shit.
Cliché.
I'm gonna send one of our guys
out to pick up Vaughn's daughter.
- That way we can do an exchange.
- No, no, no, no.
- What, no exchange?
- No daughter, Derrick. No daughter.
Mr. Pope, I think this is
just our best chance to...
Let me make this clear, we are not going
to kidnap a bedridden little girl
with fucking cancer. You're not going
to touch a hair of her head.
If there's any fucking hair left
on that poor little girl's head.
You're gonna leave her alone,
you're gonna leave her mom alone.
And if she has a fucking teddy bear, you're
going to leave the teddy bear alone as well.
Our problem's with Vaughn, not them.
Is that understood?
- Understood.
- Now get me my money back.
Galveston Air Cargo, Jono speaking.
Anyone there?
Hey, cocksuckers, someone pick up.
Pick up, pick up,
pick up, pick up, pick up.
Detective?
So how about it? A little
mano-y-mano meet and greet?
What makes you think we want to do that?
I hear your compadre
isn't doing too good.
Word on the street is he's having
a serious allergic reaction to bullets.
Come on, let me get him some medical
supplies. At least give him a chance.
Get back to you in a minute.
- How's he doing?
- He's fucking dying.
He needs blood. If not blood, he needs
fluids, IV, something, or he's gonna die.
- He needs a hospital, man.
- Not going to the fucking hospital.
- You want him to die?
- What the fuck you just ask me?
You listen to me, motherfucker,
that guy, dying,
we grew up together. He's the only
fucking friend I've ever had.
So don't fucking ask me
if I want him to die!
I don't want to die, man.
I don't want to die.
If we get you the shit you need,
can you keep him alive?
Hey, fucking IV shit? We get it,
can you keep him alive? Yes or no?
Definitely for longer,
but I don't know how long.
You there?
Yeah.
All right, we need to get IVs,
pain meds, bandages, clotting agents.
Can you do that?
I can get all that for you.
I just need to deliver it in person.
Of course you do.
Here's the catch...
we're not stopping the bus.
I can work with that.
Go for Marconi.
- Detective Marconi, this is Officer Bauhaus.
- What you got?
I've got an ID on one of the hijackers,
a Luke Vaughn.
Looks like he did some time
in Bibb's Correctional
- and served in the army.
- You get an address?
I'm actually standing out front right now.
Looks like he was evicted.
- Neighbors say he moved in with his sister.
- Any ID on the sister?
No, no one...
no one knows anything about her.
Well, it's a start. Anything else?
I was thinking about
heading over to this Swan Casino.
Vaughn works there. I don't know.
Ask a few questions, check it out.
No, no, no. I'll send one of my guys.
Okay? You just...
You've had a rough one, Bauhaus. Just...
hang at the station.
I'll hit you back when I need you.
- Get started.
- Okay. Okay. Tom?
- Nice little party you got here.
- Hold this.
- Lucky there's a doctor on the bus.
- She's not a doctor. She's a vet student.
Not so lucky then.
What's this?
- Pain meds.
- Right. Okay.
Careful. I have thin veins.
- Holy shit, he's dead!
- Oh, my God! Oh, my God!
What the fuck do you mean, he's dead?
- What the fuck did you do?
- Ask the vet.
- What the fuck you do, bitch?
- I didn't do... I didn't do anything!
- I didn't do anything!
- Well, you'd better do something!
- Do CPR, something! Work on him!
- It wasn't her.
Okay, what's in the bag?
Tom, check his pulse!
I think it's for you.
Don't die.
Mr. Pope?
You know, I see you every day, every day
on that floor for the past five years.
And every day I think to myself, "Today's
the day Luke is going to come to the office,
ask to come back."
That day never comes.
This isn't how I wanted it to go down.
I know, but we do have a bit of a situation
on our hands. Wouldn't you say?
Yeah. There doesn't seem
to be a whole lot of out.
Well, here's one you might not
have considered. Put a bullet in Cox,
throw yourself and my money
into the man standing in front of you.
Everyone gets off the bus. No one knows
about my money or its origins.
You get carted off to jail.
Except you never make it.
Instead, you disappear
with enough cash to save Riley
- and start a new life far away from here.
- I wish I could believe you, Mr. Pope.
But you and I both know
you're a man that lives by his rules.
I'd make an exception for an old friend.
But this is a right-now,
one-time deal only, pal.
You need to fold your hand,
walk away from the table,
- or I'm taking your whole stack.
- I appreciate the out.
You and I both know
that's a sucker's bet.
You don't make exceptions.
Sorry. No deal.
Me too.
No deal.
- What the fuck's going on?
- Detective Marconi here...
is in Mr. Pope's back pocket.
What'd you do?
What the fuck did you do?
Did you kill my friend, you piece
of shit? Is that what you did?
You kill my fucking friend?
Fucker!
- What the fuck are you doing, Vaughn?
- No, you can't kill him. Just listen to me.
To us, he's Pope's errand boy.
To the rest of the world, he's a cop.
We kill a cop, the whole world
comes crashing down on us.
Get him off this fucking bus
or I'm gonna kill him!
Something is happening.
This is the bus 657 hostage situation.
It appears that the bus
is slowing down now
and the doors are opening.
We're seeing now... Oh, my goodness.
Catch these motherfuckers!
- We've got a problem.
- What do you see?
SWAT bikes.
Everybody get down! On the floor!
Coming up on both sides.
Gas! Get on the floor!
I can't see anything!
Everybody get down!
- They're on the roof!
- They're on the fucking roof!
- Motherfucker!
- Get behind the yellow line!
Get off the road!
I can't hold it!
He blew out a tire!
- I can't control it!
- Go left!
Bus 657 has crashed just outside
of Galveston, Texas, as the police...
Oh, fuck!
Stay below the window line.
Stay down.
What the fuck are you doing?
- Let's go! Come on!
- Move, move!
We're surrounded. We're sitting ducks.
Oh, what'd you do now, boy?
Black out the fucking window, man.
You got any more paint?
Flies around shit.
...to interrupt here,
but we do need to go to a live...
So what's the plan, detective?
One wrong move,
we're 10 million hits on YouTube.
Call your sniper section. I want
your boys in position 10 minutes ago.
Roger that. Snipers, get in position.
Get the the fuckin' news on the phone.
Get the fuckin' news on the phone!
- Cox, what the fuck are you doing?
- I want my 15 seconds of fame.
Cox, Cox, what the fuck are you doing?
- You don't have to do this!
- What are you doing?
- Shut the fuck up!
- You got 'em?
- Please, Mr. Cox...
You got 'em? They on the phone?
Cox, what are you doing, man?
- I think you need to see this.
- ...bus 657 hostage situation
where we have one of the hijackers
on the line, ready to speak with us.
Go ahead, live on the air.
Tell the cops to back off!
I'll kill this motherfucker!
I'm gonna kill him and everybody
on this goddamn bus!
He's not going to kill a hostage
on live TV. Prepare to board the bus.
- Sir?
- Do it!
Please, don't. Please.
- Shut up, shut up.
- Come on, man. Please.
- Cox...
- Tell the cops to back off!
- Shut the fuck up.
Cox, we're not going to play it this way.
We can't do this. You can't kill him!
- Please, please.
- Shut the fuck up!
Don't shoot me.
- You got a clear shot?
- Negative, sir. I only see the hostage.
This death is on that man's conscience,
not mine!
- No. No.
- I'm in charge. I'm in charge!
Oh, my God.
Fuck!
All units withdraw.
I repeat, all units withdraw.
I would like to apologize
to our viewers for that.
I do not know what to say.
- It's a very... grave situation.
- This is unprecedented.
- We will continue to learn more on this.
- We apologize.
That should have never happened.
- Hello.
- Hi, Daddy.
Princess.
What are you doing? Is everything okay?
I'm fine, Dad.
The nice policewoman said over here
that you're being a real, real hero.
I'm proud of you, Dad.
I love you so much. You know that?
All Daddy wants to do...
is to make everything okay for you.
I just want you to feel better.
If I could take all your pain away
and make it mine,
I would. You know that?
I know that, Dad. I love you too.
- I'm gonna see you real soon, okay?
- Okay.
I know about the bills.
I know about the surgery.
You're not going to be able to get
that money here on time, Vaughn.
She is going to lose her spot.
I'll have that money there by 7:00.
You and your psycho friend
just killed a hostage.
So for the sake of your daughter...
give yourself up.
You have no idea
what's really going on here.
- It's not what it seems.
- Yeah, well, it all seems pretty fucked.
And unless that bus grows wings, you ain't
got a hope in shit to make it anyways.
The only way off that bus
is with your hands up, man.
The wheels on the bus go round and round
Round and round
All day long
God damn it!
Get me off this fuckin' bus!
Fuck! God! Fuck!
Get me out of here!
I got an idea.
All right, detective, here's the deal.
No more games. You fix the tire,
I release all the hostages but one.
Once I get where I'm going,
I release the last hostage.
Nobody follows us.
I see someone follow us...
choppers, police escort...
I kill another fucking hostage.
What do you think, detective?
This gonna work for you?
Deal.
Sending in a mechanic,
the bus is being repaired.
And it appears we're close
to a resolution.
Go.
I spoke to your guys and they're
in position. So once the bus pulls out,
it'll just be me
and your guys out there.
We'll take the bus,
I'll put a bullet in Vaughn.
I'll get your money.
Sounds like a plan. Don't fuck it up.
All right, it appears that some of
the hostages are coming off of the bus now.
One hostage remains on the bus,
which now appears to be departing.
The police have ordered
news choppers not to follow.
That'll be $1.25, gentlemen.
Hey, Cox's Sucker!
She's ready and waiting, my brother.
He's a little indisposed at the moment.
Wanted me to call and tell you
we'd be there in 10, 15.
And there could be a change
in destination.
Roger that. She got enough fuel
to get you anywhere you want to go.
Hello?
Anybody here?
Put it down.
You hungry?
Eat rock salt, motherfucker.
Marconi, please respond.
This is a fuckin' shit storm. I'm done.
All right? I gotta get out of here.
I'm sorry, Mr. Pope,
but if we'd done this sh...
Anyone seen Marconi?
Welcome back, Vaughn.
I'd make this painless
for old time's sake.
Bullet-in-the-head kind of deal,
but we had a lot of cleaning to do.
What time is it?
7:15.
What are you laughing at?
You remember that card trick you used
to do all the time when I was a kid?
The one I could never figure out
'cause I was so busy watching the hand
that was holding the deck when the magic
was really happening in the other hand?
What the fuck you talking about?
I needed to get the money
to the hospital by 7:00.
That was the deadline.
Pay everything off by 7:00,
Riley continues her treatments,
she gets her surgery.
So why are you smiling? You missed it.
Are you sure about that?
Or you been too busy watching
the hand holding the deck?
Check the bag.
Where's the money?
You forgot your own trick, Mr. Pope.
You were watching the wrong hand.
You forgot the magic.
Morning.
- Open the door!
- There is no "we."
We pull this off and get out
of the Swan alive, I'm on my own.
That pregnant chick, she goes into labor?
They storm the bus. Hostages be damned.
That was great, sis.
I still don't understand
why I have to be pregnant.
Come on, who's going to suspect
a pregnant woman?
Where's the money?
Is this going to take much longer?
There's just somewhere I really need to be.
Yeah, I'm her aunt, father's side.
Your money's going to save
a little girl's life.
- What about your life?
- That was a trade I was willing to make.
You're a fucking hero. Saves your little
girl's life by sacrificing your own.
I'm touched. You see, you see...
that's $3 million.
So you know what I'm going to do?
First, I'm going to light a match
and I'm going to watch you burn.
Then I'm going down
to the hospital personally
and I'm gonna see your little girl.
And guess what?
I want you to think about
her suffering. Suffering...
- You're not going to touch my girl.
- I'm gonna touch her. You better believe it.
What are you doing? What are you doing?
What are you trying to tell me? Yeah.
See how it's not funny, bitch?
Stealing $3 million is not
so fucking funny now, is it?
Rule number 1 is
you never steal from us!
If you do, we'll make
an example out of a thief!
Make sure you really know
that you can't steal from us or me!
I'm gonna fuckin' light your ass up.
Fuck all. Time to light you the fuck up!
This ain't on my family.
This ain't on me. Don't touch my girl!
What a fuckin' day.
You gonna be okay?
You know, my mother, she was a nurse.
Good woman. Strong.
She used to say when people were...
dying, on their last breaths...
deathbed shit...
they'd open up with regrets,
things they wished they'd done different,
stuff they were desperate to put right.
So she had this saying.
"Regrets in death
meant you'd lived life wrong.
"Don't live life wrong, Frank."
Dogs me to a tee,
would have made
the same mistakes I made.
I can't fix what I did,
but I can stop it from happening again.
I should go see my daughter.
You're a good dad, Vaughn.
Thanks.
Yeah.
I didn't expect you to answer.
I thought you might be...
Dead?
Yeah, me too.
Strange? You gonna arrest me,
Officer Bauhaus?
Well, the weird thing is, I could've sworn
there were three hijackers.
But everybody on the bus
said there were only two.
Well, that is strange.
They're prepping Riley now.
Vaughn.
Best news I've had all day.
What do you want me
to tell her when she wakes?
You tell her Daddy's coming home.
Someone needs to stop Clearway Law.
Public shouldn't leave reviews for lawyers.