Unit
Christmas rations must be
picked up by 0900 hours.
Armor group tree
decoration team report
to the Engineering Depot.
My son will you turn off
that wretched puppet?
Brush your teeth.
Don't call him a puppet.
I beg your pardon.
Look he's not a puppet.
Howdy Doody's real.
Well...
He's real.
Mr. Deedee
Doodoo will have
to say good night.
Oh no.
And remember
you have to be asleep
when he comes
down the chimney.
It's not even a chimney Pop.
He has his ways.
Then I want to wait up.
Watch him do it.
Nonsense.
Okay.
I want a story then.
Oh no no no.
No stories tonight.
Just one.
And then I'll go to bed.
Right away.
Then I'll brush my teeth
I promise.
"It is said that
at the dawn of time
"man beast and all magical
beings lived together under
Aiglin the Father Tree.
"But man had been created
with a hole in his heart
"a hole that no
possession power or
knowledge could fill.
"And in his infinite greed
"man dreamt of
expanding his dominion
over the entire Earth.
"The blood of many an elf
ogre and goblin
was spilled in
their war with man.
"And King Balor
the one-armed
king of Elfland
"watched the slaughter
in dread and despair.
"But one day the master
of the goblin blacksmiths
"offered to build the king
a golden mechanical army
"seventy times 70 soldiers
"that would never know hunger
and could not be stopped.
"Prince Nuada begged
his father to agree.
"'Build me this army'
the king said.
"So a magical crown
was forged
"that would allow
those of royal blood
"to command the Golden Army
if unchallenged.
"'l am King Balor
leader of the Golden Army.
"'ls there anyone
who disputes my right?'
"And in his throne room
no one challenged his word."
But wait
what if someone could
challenge him?
Would they have a fight?
Well most likely.
A challenge must
be answered.
But do you want to hear
the end of this story or not?
Yes please.
Right.
"So the world was changed
and the next time
the humans marched
"they felt the earth
tremble beneath their feet
"and saw the sky darken
with monstrous shapes.
"The Golden Army
had no remorse
felt no loyalty or pain.
"And King Balor's heart
grew heavy with regret.
"So he called a truce
and divided the crown
in three pieces
"one for the humans
and two for himself.
"ln exchange
man would keep
to the cities
"and the magical beings
would own the forests.
"This truce would be
honored by their sons
and the sons of their sons
"until the end of time.
"But Prince Nuada
did not believe in
the promises of man.
"And it is said that
he went into exile
"vowing to return
the day his people
needed him most.
"So the Golden
Army lay dormant
"locked inside the Earth
waiting.
"And there it is to this day
"awaiting the day the crown
is made whole again.
"Silent
still and indestructible."
Wow. What does it
mean "industrable"?
Indestructible.
Indestruct...
It means no one
can destroy them.
Wow.
Go to sleep my son.
But it's just
a story right Pops?
Is it now?
Yeah come on.
Those guys
they can't be real.
Well my son
I'm sure you'll find out.
How long have you
been there my friend?
They're over there.
I bought them today.
I haven't fed them at all.
I will go up first.
You will follow.
And remember Mr. Wink
don't be shy.
Next lot. Number 776.
This is an important
votive figure
a fertility goddess
dating approximately
15000 to 10000 B.C.
This was found
in a loess deposit
in a terrace about
30 meters from
the Shannon River.
And we'll open the
bidding at $300000.
Three hundred thousand.
Three hundred and
twenty-five thank you.
Three hundred and fifty
thank you.
Three seventy-five.
Three hundred
and seventy-five.
Going once.
Going twice. Sold.
And now we move on
to our next item
lot 777
a piece of the Royal
Crown of Bethmoora.
The origin of this
piece harkens back
to the saga of
the Sons of the Earth
and the creation of
the fabled Golden Army.
And here it is
our next item.
Lot 777.
Ladies and gentlemen
please keep your seats.
The auction will
restart shortly.
I'm sure this is just
a temporary loss of power.
Now for the first
time at auction
a piece of the Royal
Crown of Bethmoora
coming to us from
a long lost culture.
Lost?
Not at all.
Forgotten by you
perhaps
but very very much alive.
Who are you sir?
Sir please identify yourself.
You can't just...
I am Prince
Nuada Silverlance
son of King Balor.
And I am here sir
to reclaim what
is rightfully mine.
Security. Call security!
What do you think
you're doing?
This is outrageous.
Take what you want.
Please leave.
Anything take anything.
Be quiet.
Sit down!
Proud empty hollow
things that you are.
Let this remind you
why you once
feared the dark.
Fishstick. We have to talk.
Undercover.
Can't he get the
meaning of the word?
Look we are still
government-funded.
We are still a secret
although a dirty secret
if you ask me.
Officially we do
not exist you see.
So that's the problem
when we get these.
Subway. Highway. Park.
And he posed for this one
and gave an autograph.
I suppress each photo.
Cell phone videos.
They cost me
a fortune and they
show up on YouTube.
God I hate YouTube.
Well he just
wants the world outside
to know what we do
what he does.
He loathes me.
I don't think so.
No?
Target practice.
Oh dear.
And then he
posts them around.
Do you know how
that makes me feel?
What's going on?
Oh it's Friday.
I tell you Fishstick
he hates me.
He's out to destroy me.
My street cred is low.
Street cred?
My mojo.
Washington
they're wondering
if I've got the stuff.
You think I have
an easy job?
Do you think
I enjoy being
a pain in the neck?
I am medicated.
I mean
this is not candy.
This is...
It's an antacid.
Yes it's an
over-the-counter
medicine
but this is medicine.
You see I worry
because you know
I mean I am
we are after all
we're just humble
public servants.
It's not about you.
He's acting out.
Things are a little
tense with Liz.
Tense? How tense?
Tense how?
Well you know the usual.
A new couple
making adjustments.
They argue.
They argue huh?
Sometimes.
How bad?
Like everybody else.
They have good days
and bad days.
I'm not done with you.
Hey Abe.
Red come back here!
Manning.
Pick up your clothes!
Yeah yeah yeah.
Put away your things!
Watch it
boys she's on fire.
Then again there are
the really bad days.
I'm not afraid
of you you know.
You should be.
Look at this mess.
Look around.
I have one rule.
Don't touch my stuff.
Oh I get it.
That's your rule. Okay.
The one and only.
I'm easy.
How's that even possible?
Everything is your stuff.
The same CD  LP.
It's Al Green.
You can't listen
to Al Green on CD.
But it's good to keep.
And an eight-track.
An eight-track Red?
Yeah well one day
the world's gonna
realize its mistake.
Eight-track was
the way to go baby.
Come on kids
you can come out now.
That's right
it's all over.
That's right.
And what about me Red?
I need some space.
At least enough to
find my toothbrush.
Toothbrush? Wait a minute.
It's right there.
Red! I can't
live like this.
Security breach
central Manhattan.
Oh damn.
Gotta go.
We all gotta go.
It's an emergency right?
Security breach.
Let's go.
Red. Red!
All personnel
to garage area.
Hold on a sec.
Oh jeez it's Manning.
Watch yourself Liz.
Red. Red!
Listen.
Manning.
Hi.
We're going to
downtown Manhattan.
Yeah it'll be fun.
Downtown.
Very dangerous.
Dangerous for you.
And for me.
Now I know
you dream of
the outside world
but trust me
it's not that great.
It's savage as a
matter of fact. Bad.
Come on fellas
let's get this out of here.
These on the
other hand are good.
Mmm.
Cuban.
Good.
Being seen?
Bad.
Exactly.
I confiscated a box of these
and I'll get you some more.
But you've gotta do me
a little favor tonight
out there.
You have to be...
You have to be very very...
Discreet.
What? Thank you. Yes.
You're welcome.
Discreet.
Invisible. In and out.
Really?
Hey.
Hey I can be
discreet if I wanna be.
I followed you
and Myers didn't I?
And then you had him
transferred to Antarctica.
That's very discreet.
He said he liked the cold.
Like a shadow.
Red team Red team.
Like a shadow
in the night.
US Customs
discovered a few
illegally imported items.
It's a minor infraction.
And a gas pocket.
They detected
a gas pocket up there.
Now FBI agents
under my command
are going up there right now
with special gas equipment.
Jeez it stinks in here.
This is worse
than my room.
Waiting for
a report on that.
Say "cheese."
Let's go.
Whatever they
called us for is over.
We had over 70
guests reported.
We have no survivors
no bodies.
Same story here babe.
Don't call me "babe."
"Abe" I said.
"Abe." Wrong channel.
Abe I think Liz is
still mad at me.
Still the same channel.
Oh!
Can l ask
you a question?
No.
Now listen.
When we get home later
I'm gonna clean up
my whole mess.
That's not the problem.
What is it?
Not now.
Abe what have you got?
Oh this is interesting.
Both boxes have
the Royal Seal.
Only delivered
at a time of war.
Red? We have company.
Come on Blue
give me something
to work with here.
Burrowing creatures.
How many of them?
Many.
There are no corpses
because there
are no leftovers.
Have you noticed the floor?
Oh crap.
Precisely.
All these things
do is eat and eat.
Then poop
and then eat again.
Remind you of anyone?
Damn it Abe.
What are these things?
English English.
Oh they're Tooth Fairies.
Ha!
No no. Third century
Black Forest.
Feed mostly on calcium
bones skin organs.
But they do go
for the teeth first.
Hence the name
Tooth Fairies.
I bet you they don't
leave money either.
Oh my God.
Liz you're pregnant.
No I'm not.
Yes you are.
What have you got Marble?
Think I may have found one.
But he's kind of cute.
Don't go near it!
It's biting me!
Marble.
It hurts! It hurts!
Red we need you here!
Marble.
Nasty little...
Keep firing Abe.
Keep firing!
Damn.
Sorry lady.
You should be running.
There's a safe upstairs.
How do we get there?
We need a clearing.
Run!
Up to the safe now!
Abe. Up the stairs.
Come on Liz
burn them all.
Go. Go!
Yes we're going!
Get in the safe Abe.
Get in the safe!
Oh no no.
No no no!
Steel!
Damned beasts.
Fire is mine.
Fire is in me.
Red stay away
from the window!
Fire is me.
Stop biting me!
World here I come.
What have you done?
Guess we're out.
Hey Hellboy
over here.
Your Royal Highness.
Before entering
the council chamber
you must surrender
your weapon.
I will not.
It is protocol
sire for peasant
and prince alike.
For you Sister
anything.
According to multiple eye
witnesses lives were
in fact endangered.
There you have it Hellboy.
But is he really
on our side?
Do you have superpowers?
Well yeah.
But really all
l wanna be is just
an ordinary person
just like you and
you and everybody.
Hey guys.
You're missing this.
We're on TV.
Liz. Liz
are you all right?
Yeah I'll be out
in a minute.
You don't need to do that.
You can trust me.
My readings are
quite accurate.
Shut up Abe.
Get your damn hand
away from the door.
You have nothing to fear.
In spite of appearances
I believe Red
would be an excellent
father figure.
And what about this guy?
Walking around
with a toilet
seat on his head.
A toilet seat!
It's quite obvious it's
a breathing apparatus.
Hey I think we gotta
lose the garbage truck.
Sends out the wrong signal.
You think that's
our problem?
Transportation?
And this girl we
definitely have to find out
what's wrong with her.
She's cute though.
We should get
her on the show.
I hate it when
people stare at me.
Makes me feel
like a freak.
You had no right Red.
It's Manning. Could you...
How many times do
l have to tell you?
lt's a gas pocket.
And a gaseous
phenomenon that occurred...
Gas pocket.
What an idiot.
You've murdered me.
You have murdered me.
You have ridiculed me.
And you have brought
this unto yourself.
What?
Washington is sending
down a new BPRD agent.
A new guy?
Why?
To look after you.
Sire please.
To set us free.
All of us Father.
A truce based on shame.
The humans have
forgotten the gods
destroyed the Earth.
And for what?
Parking lots.
Shopping malls.
Greed has burned
a hole in their heart
that will never be filled.
They will never
have enough.
Honor?
Look at this place.
Where is the honor in it?
Father you were
once a proud warrior.
When did you
become their pet?
I have returned
from exile to wage war
and reclaim our land
our birthright.
And for that I will
call upon the help
of all of my people.
And they will answer
the good the bad
and the worst.
Perhaps I am.
Perhaps they made me so.
We will not fade.
It is.
I am sorry Father.
And you Sister
are you at peace with
your king's verdict?
I am my brother. I am.
Then very well.
Death it is.
Now for the final piece
my sister.
Where is she Wink?
Where is she?
Go find her.
Now! Find her!
Elevator
arriving now to section 42.
Elevator arriving
now to section 42.
Pardon me boys.
Excuse me. Excuse me.
Is he here?
Not yet.
I'm telling you
we don't need this guy.
Well I think we do.
Evidently this
guy's quite the big
shot in Washington.
What's his name?
His name is Johann Krauss.
Johann Krauss?
Sounds German.
He's the top man in...
Ectoplasmic.
Yes thank you.
Ectoplasmic research.
Comes highly recommended
by our European liaison.
Johann Krauss.
"Liaison."
I love that word
don't you?
It's so hoity toity.
I don't like Germans.
No fingerprints.
Here he comes.
Germans make me nervous.
No photo. Dossier says
and I translate
"He has a nice open face."
Oh my God.
Damen und Herren
Johann Krauss
at your service.
I like him.
Look at that.
Poor little thing.
Bought and sold on
the black market.
Crammed into
cargo containers.
Smuggled abused.
He has very
expressive hands.
The seal on the box
worries me also.
A warring emblem.
Yes from the Bethmoora clan.
The Sons of the Earth.
Your file says
you're the brains
of the operation
and I must admit
I'm impressed.
In my file you'll see
Mr. Krauss
that I worked
very closely with Abe
in his training.
Ja okay.
Let's see what our little
friend here can remember.
Memory gets a little
sketchy right after
you've burned to death.
But maybe Saint
Malachy can help.
Oh no no.
No amulets
Mein Herr.
Teleplasty.
Plastic. Very modern.
Teleplasty by which
an ectoplasmic medium
such as Dr. Krauss
can control inanimate things
organic mechanical
dead or alive.
Take it take it
all in mein Junge.
There we are. Get up.
Get up. Get up.
Now I have full control
of its limbic system.
Let us see how long
I can hold it.
What?
Hey you chewed off
the tip of my tail.
Yeah you you little...
It says you're rude brutish
und not very bright.
Wow!
It seems our
little friend here
remembers market
sounds and voices.
And a peculiar
troll language spoken
in the last place
his cage was opened.
The troll market.
The troll market?
Come on.
No one's ever found it.
That's because
it doesn't exist.
Mr. Krauss? Dr. Krauss sir.
Our little informant there
doesn't look so good.
Back inside you.
There we are.
So now we know
where to begin.
Trolls dwell under bridges.
Wow. You're a genius.
By the way there's
over 2000 bridges
in New York City.
But Vladimir Vanya
19th century
occult historian
places the troll
market directly under
the east end of
the Brooklyn Bridge.
We've already looked there.
Yes you have
but not with me Agent.
Not with me.
We're moving in.
Keep it coming
keep it coming.
Hold it.
"Not with me Agent."
What an ego.
I like him.
Well you can keep him.
I mean am I the only
one that thinks this
guy is full of...
No no no no
don't lean.
Lot 336 the Schufftein
glasses. Could it be?
The three surviving
pairs
and we will use them to
locate the troll market.
Dr. Krauss what a coup.
The Schufftein glasses.
You're my hero.
Hey. You Hellboy?
Yeah.
You're ugly man.
Two more on
the wall in front of me
and then three on
the alleys facing that way.
What do you think of
Mr. Know-It-All?
Don't know
too early to tell.
Hey you're Hellboy.
I know I'm ugly.
Forget it.
We'll talk about it later.
He's sure of himself
and I think maybe
you're intimidated.
Intimidated. Huh?
Keep us up to
date on the cameras
Agent Sherman. Over and out.
What's this?
Normally we can't see
fairy folk and trolls.
They generate a cloaking
aura called "glamour."
But in 1878
Emil Schufftein designed
and built these.
Four crystal diopters
that penetrate that effect
and reveal the true
nature of things.
Oh Dr. Krauss they're more
beautiful than I'd imagined.
You must try
them on then.
Oh yes.
Try them on Agent.
They'll look good.
I love these tight
little leather straps.
Intimidated?
Mr. Kraut? Sir?
Krauss Agent.
With a double "S."
S-S. Right right.
Listen those gizmos?
How do you know they work?
l have a suspect.
Give me a vector
Agent Sherman. A vector.
B-12 the alley northbound.
Well track the target.
We're coming down.
Keep an eye on her.
I'll be right back.
This little old lady?
Come on.
It's a Fragglewump
an ugly Scottish troll.
They're afraid of canaries.
Oh my God. Canaries huh?
What about the kittens?
She feeds on them.
Come on then.
Kitty kitty kitty.
That thing is a "she"?
Down you fools.
What do you think
you are doing?
She's gonna eat the cat.
You'll make her
aware of our presence.
We should use
the canary now.
She's gonna eat it!
We should use
the bird Dr. Krauss.
The bird.
She's going to eat the cat.
You will stay put
and follow my orders.
I can't sit by here...
You are directly
under my command
and you have to obey.
Stay put!
Oh screw this!
Hey! Lucy.
Come back here.
I'm home.
Oh yes dearie.
Can I help you?
Give it up nasty.
We can see you.
You see me?
How? How do you see me?
We're looking
for the entrance
to the troll market.
Any clues?
Come any closer and
I'll rip your heart.
We're gonna have to get
a little old-school Abe.
Give me the bird.
Not a canary.
What you're afraid
of this little guy?
Who'd know?
No more no more.
I'll take you there.
Come on let's go
you dirty old troll.
Let's go.
Agent Sherman
we are going into
the troll market.
Keep communication
to a minimum.
Over und out.
I like him.
You see this is
a man who takes charge.
You think?
Yeah. He's efficient.
He's precise.
You add "resistant" to that
you got yourself a new watch.
Dr. Krauss is aware
of the chain of
command and he...
Oh brother!
He seems to like me.
OLD Here we are.
Wow that's some door!
It's a complex
combination lock.
What do you think
Agent Sapien?
Not good.
With the number of symbols
on the combination
we'll be here for days.
Well not necessarily.
Let me try my technique.
Open it Lucy.
I will not.
Pretty please.
Do as you may demon.
Release the yellow beast.
Tear my eyes out.
Rip my insides and
my legs and my tongue
but I will never
open that door.
Is that your
investigative technique?
It said "never."
It's unconscionable.
That means
he didn't like it.
What?
So what you're
gonna show us
how it's done
Mr. By-The-Book?
Is that it?
Yes I think I will.
There we are.
Let me see. Yes.
Gentlemen welcome
to the troll market.
Red there's
something really important
that l need to tell you.
Oh Liz you should
be here. You'd love it.
Nobody's looking at us.
We blend right in.
Agent I said keep
communication to a minimum.
You'll blow our cover.
You know?
I think he's right.
I'm bringing you
here for sure babe.
The fishbowl wants
radio silence. So...
Over and out.
The Royal Seal.
Brother Red.
Red do you read me?
Yeah I read you Blue
but I'm watching
Sherlock at work.
I'll get back to you.
Excuse me sir.
Sir excuse... Pardon me.
Sir may I ask a...
I gotta tell
the boys that one.
Excuse me gentlemen.
Have you seen anyone
purchasing this
type of Tooth Fairy?
No one sells them
down here pal.
Over in Jersey maybe.
Well what about this then?
Do you recognize this seal?
Make him go away.
No. We don't.
Please dear sir.
You'd better go. Now!
We'll make it
worth your while.
Don't waste your time.
We will not talk!
What are you doing?
You're absolutely
sure about that huh?
Absolutely.
You won't talk eh?
Never.
Never huh?
Never ever ever.
Feeling a little
chattier now?
We'll never talk.
Yes yes.
We will only don't
hit me anymore.
Chicken.
Who bought
the Tooth Fairies?
Prince Nuada.
They say Prince Nuada
broke the truce
and now there is
talk of war
a war with
the human world.
Sorry kid.
That's all right.
Nice baby.
I'm not a baby.
I'm a tumor.
Yes Red. I am
following a lead
right now.
It may turn out...
It may turn out
to be nothing
but I will let you
know soon enough.
What do you want?
Tell me your name.
Follow me.
Your father
left you this map.
In it he said
lies the secret
to the location
of the Golden Army.
Move away!
Quickly Your Highness.
Can I help you
with something?
No thank you.
I'm just looking.
You can't go in there!
Sir why
are you following me?
I...
I was just hoping
to find an old map
chart of Algiers.
Why are you following me?
I was not.
Did my brother send you
to steal the crown piece?
Your brother?
Oh you're sorely
mistaken I assure you.
Then answer me truthfully.
Why were you following me?
My name is Abraham Sapien.
There is no such name.
Oh I don't like
it either but I...
Enough.
Give me your hand.
Your hand.
You are an agent
for the Bureau of Paranormal
Research and Defense.
And your name is...
Oh...
Horrible I know.
I'm Nuala
Princess Nuala.
Yes I know.
Forgive me
Your Highness
but as you were
learning about me
I couldn't help
but learn a bit
about you myself.
I know that you
need our help.
I'm afraid it's
the other way around.
The window. Out now.
I will take care of this.
Oh dear.
Go! Now go!
Get out of here Blue.
Yes. Come with me
Your Highness.
You.
Let me put this to you
as delicately as I can.
My cigar it was Cuban.
Now you pissed me off.
Oh crap.
Whoa!
Now stay down!
Damn.
A tooth. Happy?
Give it up pal.
It's over.
I wouldn't do that
if I were you.
Wow. Told you.
Oh mein Gott
what have you done
Agent Hellboy?
Look at this!
Now we have to leave.
Red. This is Princess Nuala.
Lady.
We should leave.
Now. Now!
Let's go.
To wage his war
my brother needs this
the final piece of
the Crown of Bethmoora
and this map to the location
of the Golden Army chamber.
The Golden Army.
The harbingers of death.
The unstoppable tide.
Howdy Doody.
Your Highness if you hand
the crown piece over to us...
No. Where it goes I go.
My father died to uphold
the truce with your world.
You must honor
his noble intention.
The lady's
in dire danger.
I take it you're
vouching for her
Agent Sapien?
Most emphatically.
Yes I am.
Even so.
I am sorry but we
simply cannot assume
such responsibility
on our own.
The lady just
lost her father.
What more do you want?
You may not care
but there are
procedures rules
and little handbooks...
She's coming with us.
You got that Gas Bag?
What did you call me?
You.
You will pay
for what happened
to my friend down there.
Yeah right.
You take checks?
Demon.
Born from a womb of shadows.
Sent to destroy their
world and you still
believe you belong.
Are we gonna
talk all night?
'Cause I'm really sleepy.
No Brother no!
Kill him.
It's just a jumping bean.
It's going for water. Hurry.
Oh dear.
No. No no no no. No.
What the hell is that?
Excuse me!
Stay back.
Hey what's going on?
We've got
target in sight.
It's an Elemental
a giver of life
and a destroyer.
What?
A Forest God.
A Forest God eh?
I'm gonna get me Big Baby.
Somebody help!
My baby's...
Help! Help!
How can I help you ma'am?
My baby's inside!
Come with us
dear lady please.
There's nothing
to worry about.
We've got everything
under control.
Please. My baby's
still in there! Please!
Hey little guy.
Homing in on target.
Hang on kid.
Agent Hellboy.
Reach higher ground
and shoot the weapon.
Shoot the weapon!
First praise the tail kid.
You must shoot it in
the energy ganglion.
The what?
The energy ganglion.
Scheisse. The head!
Shoot it in the head!
Whoa!
Oh crap.
You gotta trust me
little buddy. Okay?
You woke up the baby.
Agent Hellboy
take the shot!
Right now! Take it!
That's an order!
Take the shot.
That's an order
Agent Hellboy.
Shoot it!
Shoot the gun!
Demon.
What are you waiting for?
This is what you
wanted isn't it?
Look at it.
It's the last
of its kind.
Like you and I.
You destroy it
the world will never
see its like again.
Shoot it!
You have more
in common with us
than with them.
It's breaking free.
You could be a king.
You will not
disobey a direct order!
Shoot it!
It's getting loose!
If you cannot command...
It will
destroy everything!
That's an order
Agent Hellboy!
...then you must obey.
Shoot it now!
Damn.
Shoot it!
Move back.
Step back step back.
It's beautiful.
...and this huge
monster just came
out of nowhere!
Yo give the
baby back man!
Oh what have you
done to my baby?
The baby's fine.
You freak!
Hellboy
what'd you do to that baby?
The baby's fine.
Don't move.
Hands in the air! Up!
He's got a weapon
in his hand.
That is his hand.
Miss stay away from him
for your own safety.
He was trying to help.
Don't you see?
He was just trying to help.
That's all we do.
That's all we've
done all these years.
She's touching
his hand!
We've just tried to
help you. You.
You're a goddamn freak.
We don't need
you around!
What a freak.
Liz.
Let's go home.
...investigation of the
BPRD and its promotion of
intra-species marriage
seen by many as a threat
to traditional families
fuelled by federal funds.
I didn't touch you yet.
You did a good job
out there.
Then tell me why
don't I feel so good?
I mean I killed that thing.
And for what?
They don't even like me.
I mean they're afraid of me.
What do we do with that?
Red I don't want
you to freak out.
I'm gonna leave
for a little bit.
I need time to think.
About what?
Can't you do your
thinking right here?
Look I'll be really
really quiet.
I'll get rid of the cats.
Red why are you with me?
Do you need
everyone to like you?
Everybody?
Or am I enough?
Think about it.
You stay.
We belong dead.
It's blank.
No coordinates.
"Be near me
when my light is low
"When the blood
creeps and the nerves
prick and tingle
"And the heart
is sick and all
the wheels of being slow
"Be near me when the sensuous
frame is wracked with
pangs that conquer trust
"And time a maniac..."
Tennyson
"In Memoriam."
A beautiful poem.
Forgive me I didn't
mean to startle you.
Oh no. No no.
I borrowed this book.
I hope you don't mind.
Oh no no. Please
this is your home now.
You are safe here.
My brother will find me.
He always does.
How could he?
Our location is a highly
classified secret.
Yes but I know of
it now which means
that he does too.
We're twins.
Even as children
a link has bound us
one to the other.
Something I cannot explain.
No need.
You look different.
Oh do I?
Perhaps my hair?
No.
It's your eyes.
I can see your eyes.
Yes. Just trying
a new look.
Is that a map?
Yes it was in the cylinder.
There are no coordinates.
Perhaps there's
a watermark.
You were very brave
vouching for me.
How do you know
I'm not the enemy
bringing me here?
It's as you were
saying just now.
From intuition maybe
a link.
Normally I'm
able to read others
quite quickly
but I've never met
anyone like you.
Nor I like you.
Good night Abraham.
Good night Princess.
Your Highness.
Your Majesty.
Your... Ma'am.
Ma'am?
Gute Nacht
Agent Hellboy.
Look Agent
I know you don't like me
but I could take
away your badge.
Never had one.
Kept asking though.
You will learn to
obey me follow protocol
and stay fockused
at all times.
Oh that word "fockused."
Yeah with your
accent I wouldn't
use it that much.
I knew Professor Broom
young man.
You didn't know
Professor Broom.
Yes I did.
After my accident...
Shut up. Shut up.
...he designed
this containment suit.
A wonderful man.
And even then
he was worried
about your future. He...
Hey Gas Bag stop it!
Right now.
Or what?
Are you threatening me?
Because I think
I can take you.
Excuse me?
You heard me.
I couldn't hear you
from all the way over there.
I can take you
because you have
one fatal flaw.
Oh I wanna hear it.
No you don't.
You can't take criticism.
Try me.
Can't take it.
What's my flaw?
Your temper.
It gets the best of you.
Makes you weak.
Makes you vulnerable.
Oh crap.
Johann.
Johann? Johann?
Hey Johann?
Come on pal.
Hang in there
will you?
Johann? Johann?
Damn.
Ow!
There we are.
Your temper
it makes you sloppy.
Try to control it
Agent Hellboy.
Before it controls you.
Glasshole.
Mmm.
Huh?
Hello Red.
Well you're up late.
What are you listening to?
Vivaldi.
ll cimento dell'armonia.
I particularly
like the last...
Hey hey. What's that?
Just a remote.
This? Yes.
"Popular Love Songs."
Oh Abe.
You fell for the Princess.
She's... She's like me.
A creature from
another world.
You need to get out more.
She's alone in the world.
I wanna help her.
I need to care for her.
You're in love.
Have a beer.
Oh my body's a temple.
Well now it's an
amusement park.
No no no.
The glandular balance of...
Just shut up and
drink it would you?
What track?
Eight.
Can't Smile Without You.
I know.
Yep I'm gonna need
a beer too.
Well see I love this song.
And I can't smile or cry.
I think I have
no tear ducts.
I wish Father were here.
He'd know what to tell
you. Us.
l can't smile without you
l can't laugh
and l can't sing
l'm finding it hard
to do anything
You see
l feel sad when
you're sad
l feel glad when you're glad
lf you only knew
what l'm going through
l just can't
smile without you
You came along
Just like a song
And brightened my day
Who'd have believed
that you were
part of a dream?
Now it all seems
light years away
And now you know l can't
smile without you
l can't smile without you
Nuala.
Good dog.
Security detail
for the front gate
immediately.
It's the last one.
Look at her.
She's it Abe.
She's it.
She's my whole wide...
You know?
Yeah. Yeah.
I would give
my life for her.
But she also wants me
to do the dishes.
I would die
and do the dishes.
Why is she mad at me?
It's not because
the room is dirty.
Something else.
Well ask her then.
No.
Listen Abe.
Yeah.
When a woman's
mad about something
but she's really mad
about something else
you can't ask because
then they get angry
because you had to ask.
Do you know what I mean?
Never mind
don't answer
that question.
You gotta just...
Yeah.
...find out.
Very quick of you.
The parchment.
It was of no importance.
The cylinder is
very interesting.
We will find
the Golden Army here.
As for the crown piece
I know it's here.
I can feel that
much from you.
Father always tried
so hard to shield your
heart from mine.
But it's in one of the books
and I will find it.
Blue.
You always look
so beautiful in blue.
Blue.
Poetry. "Love.
"Found then lost."
Only words.
I will find it.
Listen listen Red.
I know what's
going on with Liz.
Red.
Abe.
I'm sorry.
He has to know.
Abe!
Know what?
Why?
Stay back.
I'll go first.
Abraham. No don't...
He'll kill you.
Princess?
Abraham?
No!
I will kill you Abraham.
And anyone else
if that is necessary.
Well?
Then why don't you
just start with me
Your Royal Assness?
Whoa whoa whoa whoa.
Who put those there?
And your weapon of choice?
Five-fingered Mary.
You move and I'll kill
your Abraham first.
Red you mustn't
harm the Prince.
What?
If you hurt him
you hurt the Princess.
You've gotta be kidding me.
Will you give me
the crown piece?
No.
The piece.
Abe?
Red I'm so sorry
but they're linked.
What's going on?
Red.
Liz.
Red behind you.
You may have
mused in the past
"Am I mortal?"
You are now.
Abraham
many people have
died for this crown.
He will too.
If you want to save him
and see her again
you will find
the missing piece
and bring it to me.
Jesus Abe pull the
damn thing out!
I cannot.
Every time I touch it
every time I
come close to it
it moves closer
to his heart.
I don't know
what else to do.
The wound will not heal
until the spear is removed.
We're running out of time.
Then we go after the Prince.
And we make him
take it out.
Hey Liz.
You were asking me.
Don't talk.
No no let me tell you.
I know what's important.
It's you.
Red.
I could turn my back
on the world all of it
as long as you stay with me.
I'll stay with you.
You're the best man
I've ever met.
"Man."
"Be near me
when my light is low
"When the blood creeps
"And the heart
is sick and all
the wheels of being slow"
The cylinder
yielded coordinates
to County Antrim
Northern Ireland.
The Giant's Causeway.
Right about here.
Great. So we know
where he is.
What are we waiting for?
We should get going.
The Prince will
demand the crown piece
Agent Sherman.
So we give it to him.
Dr. Manning?
I'm afraid it's not
as simple as that.
Hold on here
what are you saying?
The Golden Army
must not awaken.
So what?
You're just gonna let
him die is that it?
I'm sorry.
We called Washington.
We have our orders.
And what about you?
He saved your life.
I know.
I know this is
difficult for you but...
Well I won't
let him die.
Agent Sherman
may I remind you
that I am the leader
of this team.
Oh there's no doubt
about that sir.
That is what you
are Dr. Krauss.
And if ever you were human
that time is long gone.
What's wrong
with her?
You want me to
call her back sir?
Let her go.
I understand.
What about you?
You find anything?
No. Nothing yet.
Well keep looking.
Absolutely sir.
All of you.
But don't worry
sir we know it's here
and we're gonna find it.
When Tom Manning
gets on the case
things get done.
They get done.
They get done!
100%. I guarantee that.
Even without the piece
we have to get
him out of here.
We'll go to
Antrim and we will
find the Prince.
Keep looking.
I ask you everybody
keep looking.
Abe.
Just the two of us.
Yes. Yes.
Let's go.
We need to leave now
before they run our
clearance upstairs.
Guten Abend
meine Freunde.
Do you have authorization
to take that plane?
You're not gonna
stop us Johann.
On the contrary
I've been giving
it some thought
and we should be able
to save Agent Hellboy.
You say I'm not
human anymore
but you are wrong.
I understand your
pain all too well.
A long time ago
I lost the woman I loved.
And that was in fact
the source of my
present misfortune.
I will tell you
about it one day.
But for now the tactical
advantage is ours.
Consider this
the Prince lacks
the crown piece
and without it
his army poses
no threat.
So we have clearance then?
Agent Sherman Liz
screw the clearance.
We will take that plane!
It should be here someplace.
The entrance should be here.
I don't understand.
Perhaps there's
a mistake on the map.
Hello there!
I bid you welcome strangers.
How can I be of assistance?
We seek safe
passage to Bethmoora.
And what does a nice
little girl like you
want in the nightlands?
We are looking
for Prince Nuada.
Him I know.
Trade me something
and I'll take you to him.
Here. I have a shiny belt.
But I have no pants.
Look a wonderful
set of magic eyes.
I already have binoculars.
But I see something special
something shiny
underneath the bandages.
I want that.
No you can't take it out.
Not without killing him.
Maybe I know someone
who can.
Will you trade me then?
All right.
Very well.
Keep going. Keep going.
Oh my God.
You should have
seen this city
when it was alive.
What happened to it?
Curse.
As soon as
the Golden Army
was stored here
a plague of silence
and death befell us.
And the world left us behind.
For a long time
I alone dwelled in the dust.
All right little girl
the two of you come inside.
The rest of you
wait out here.
Hello old friend.
I have brought you visitors.
And I have
a favor to ask you.
I owe no favor to
you goblin. Leave.
But I have done
so much for you.
I have brought
you many souvenirs.
And he has something shiny.
Red.
Something mine.
Red!
Anung un Rama.
You know that name?
And yours.
Elizabeth Sherman.
At last.
I have been
waiting for you both
many a winter moon.
I am his death
and I will meet him
at each crossroads.
Good. But when can I have
that which is mine?
Can you save him?
It is for you to decide that.
It is all the same to me.
My heart is filled
with dust and sand
but you should know
it is his destiny
to bring about the
destruction of the Earth.
Not now not tomorrow
but soon enough.
Knowing that you still
want him to live?
So child make the choice.
The world or him?
Him.
The time will come
and you my dear
will suffer more than anyone.
I'll deal with it.
Now save him.
It is done.
I have done what I can.
Now give him
a reason to live.
Hey friend what
about that which is mine?
Don't forget about me.
What about me?
Friend?
Shiny.
Listen to me you big ape.
You have to get up.
'Cause you're
gonna be a father.
I become
father?
Well all this is
very touching
but if you still
want to meet Nuada
we have to leave now.
Ready.
Here we are.
And there they are.
Seventy times 70 soldiers.
Sometimes I wish
I'd never created them.
Bim-bam went the hammers!
Whoosh went the furnaces!
And one of those fires
took my legs off now.
This is as far as I can go.
I'm not very
good with steps.
But if you're here to
stop him the Prince
I wish you luck then.
The Golden Army
must not awaken.
Undo what we did.
We will.
You're here.
So I assume you brought
the remaining piece.
No. We didn't
but we should discuss...
I'm not addressing you
Tin Man.
Abraham.
Abraham?
My sister is well
as I promised so...
Abe?
What the hell are you doing?
You would do
the exact same for Liz.
Agent Sapien no!
I am Prince Nuada
Silverlance
leader of the Golden Army.
Is there anyone here
who would dispute my right?
Kill them.
But...
He lied to us.
Abe old buddy
if we ever get out of
this we gotta talk.
Open wide!
Industrable my ass.
Hey! Throw me a bone here!
Oh crap.
Well
I'm out of ideas.
I got one.
I challenge Prince Nuada
for the right to
command this army.
You challenge me?
Who are you
to challenge me?
You are nobody.
You are not royalty.
Yes. Yes!
He is Anung un Rama
son of the Fallen One.
He has the right.
A challenge must
be answered.
Very well then.
Red please.
Red. Think about it.
Guys. Guys!
He will kill you.
Don't do this Red.
Don't worry babe.
I'm not gonna kill him Abe.
But I am gonna
kick his ass.
Whoa!
Red.
Hey!
Nice ride huh?
You jumpy slippery bastard.
I got you now.
Kill me. You must
for I will not stop.
I cannot.
Sorry pal.
I win.
You live.
Nuala.
The humans
they will tire of you.
They have already
turned against you.
Leave them.
Is it them or us?
Which holocaust
should be chosen?
I never had a chance
to tell you how I felt.
Give me your hand.
It's beautiful.
We die
and the world will
be poorer for it.
Nuala my sister.
All that power.
Don't even think about it.
No. No it's nothing.
I told you
it's a dead end.
What are you doing?
Go away.
Check the belt locator.
Check the belt locators
over there.
Over there.
You you took that plane
without an authorization
young man.
Hey. Manning.
Here to help as always.
What's going on?
I quit.
What? Are you serious?
Looks that way
doesn't it?
What's wrong with you?
You can't all just quit.
Watch us.
On second thought
I think I'll keep this.
Come on. Come on!
Johann they can't do this.
Stop them.
Dr. Manning suck my
ectoplasmic schwanzstucker.
So what you said before
about us living anywhere.
Guys. Guys!
Anywhere. You and me.
Come on back.
Let's find a place
in the country.
I said come on back.
Clean air.
Green hills.
A yard with lots
of room to grow in.
It'll be great
for the baby.
Babies.