Watch Movies, TV Series and Live Sports
Signup Here -> WWW.ADMITME.APP
(music)[Mariachi]
- Hey, Pete, are you sure
this is the place?
- [Chuckles]
You saw the letter.
This is the place.
Don't you think it's a little
funny, I mean, your uncle
giving you this race car?
- Sentimental reasons.
- Yeah.
Would a cracked block
be a sentimental reason?
- All we got to lay out is the
storage fee. You got the money.
- I got the money.
All finished!
- Shine?
- No, thanks.
You are personally connected
to a Puerto Vallartan.
Show you plenty good time!
- What do you think, Pete?
- It's not in the budget.
No, thanks, son.
Where do you want to go?
Paco'll show you. Free on the house!
- "Taller mecanico avenida. '"
- Cardenas.!
No problem.
I show you exactly.
I like Americans.
Americans very smart people.
- Someday, I go to America.
- When you do, you look up
Pete Staniczek here.
- He'll put you up, show you
the best ice cream parlors.
- That sounds good!
You see down there?
That's Avenue Cárdenas.
Turn left, that way.
Go two blocks, you'll find Mecanico.
- Thanks.
- De nada. Anytime!
Welcome to Puerto Vallarta.
- Gracias.
- See you later, alligator.
Cute kid, d'ya know
what I mean?
- Well mannered, polite,
didn't have his hand out.
- [Chuckles]
An endangered species.
- That light area, right around 400.
- I can see it.
- And you say this is Inca.
- You're the expert, you tell me.
Did anyone else spot this?
They were looking for oil.
And where is this?
[Chuckling]
In the jungles.
South America.
Mr. Shepard, there's nothing
to be gained by our playing games.
This could very well be
an undiscovered Inca city.
And you know what that means:
Pre-Columbian artifacts.
- And gold, Mr. Prindle.
- And what do you want?
Cash.
And plenty of it.
'Cause they're gonna throw
the key away if they find us
stealing that stuff.
Yeah, it's a national
treasure, or something.
- Is there another print of this?
- That's it.
Gentlemen,
we're in business.
There's gotta
be some mistake.
Ah, no, senores.
No, senores.
This is not a mistake.
This is senor Douglas' car.
And you're telling me that this thing
won the Monte Carlo Grand Prix?
That is what senor Douglas
told me.
He say he'd have won
the Baja race too...
but his girlfriend...
did not make the curve.
Herbie, he see it, he stop.
He no finish the race.
Senor Douglas say,
"it's here."
Let's turn it over.
La llave, senor.
[Engine Starting]
- Okay, so it runs.
- Let's take it.
It's transportation home.
- Senor.
- Si, senor?
Mind if we take it
around the block first?
Okay, senor.
Cute kid, huh?
Doesn't have his hand out.
He doesn't have his hand out
because it's in your pocket.
You check that side.
See if you can
find us a taxi.
- I'll get you a taxi, senor!
- Get lost, kid. Taxi!
All right, 1200,
the National Hotel Bar.
I'll be there.
- Carry your bags, senor?
- Move along, sonny.
- No trouble. I carry your bags cheap!
- Put the bags down.
- I said, put the bags down!
- Hey, kid!
- Come on, get away from me, will ya?
- Taxi.!
Very sorry, senores.
Please, you forgive me!
He said he liked Americans
and put his arms around us.
Then took us to the cleaners.
Never mind reenacting the crime.
Just look for the little...
There!
See that grubby little foot
out behind that box?
- A cold beer says it's
attached to Paco the dip.
- Shh. Shh.
[Door Squeaks]
Come back here,
you little bandit!
- We need that worse than you do.!
- Don't scare him.! Talk to him nicely.!
Ooh!
Yee! Ah!
- [Speaking Spanish]
- Buenos dias.!
- [Continues Speaking Spanish]
- Oh!
I'm sorry, lady.
We're looking for a little kid.
Did you see a little kid?
I'm sorry.
Me too, lady.
You look that way.
[Dog Barking]
- What took you so long?
- It's not easy in this town.
Mr. Prindle, if you want
to get in touch with me before,
you can use this number.
- My wallet's gone.
- Maybe you left it up in the room.
It was that kid.
That crummy little kid!
Buenos dias.!
[Both Grunt]
I don't know.
He must've skipped town.
No, he didn't.
This time we sack him.
You take him low,
I'll take him high.
- Oh, no, you don't!
- Is that yours?
- No!
- Is it ours?
- Si.!
- Grab loose of that.
- Nah, looks like that's all he got.
- I'll take over, dipstick.
I oughta tan your bottom!
(music) Oh, I got another one (music)
Look, there he is!
- [Whistling]
- Hold it, kid!
- Wait a minute!
- Wait!
- Why? What we want's in that mailbox.
Let's get the kid first,
just in case. Come on!
Somebody, stop that boy!
Stop that kid, someone.!
Hey, you, grab him.! Anybody.!
[Siren Wailing]
He's over here,
come on!
- [Speaking Spanish]
- [Whistle Blowing]
[Speaking Spanish]
Look up there!
Over here too!
[Baby Crying]
- Busca alla arriba.
- Si.
[Speaking Spanish]
[Continues
Speaking Spanish]
[Car Horn Honking]
Well, like you said,
transportation.
Let's close the deal
and get out of here.
[Engine Starts]
There he is!
In the car!
[Screeching]
[Both Yelling]
What, are you planning to sleep
over at the local jail, lead foot?
I'm not doin' anything!
- Maybe this bug did win the Grand Prix!
- We got ourselves a race car.
- This your wallet?
- Yes, Officer, thank you very much.
- Is something missing, senor?
- No, everything's fine.
It's all here.
We will continue looking
for the car and the boy, of course.
Thank you, Officer.
We'll catch up with you.
Film's gone.
- Why would a kid take it?
- I don't know, we gotta
get it back, though.
I'll never get
another one.
Steady, boys! That's the car that's
going to win the Grand Primeo at Brazil!
- Something's weird about that car, D.J.
- I know!
It's dynamite and it'll blow the doors
off anything in the race.
[Man Speaking Spanish On P.A.]
Attention, please. Sun Princess
will be embarking in 20 minutes.
We blew it.
The car's on the ship;
the boy's on the ship.
- That thing's going to Rio.
- Its first stop is Panama.
When it gets there,
we'll be waiting for it.
The booty was taken aboard
the man-o'-war and
the enemy vessel scuttled.
The women were then
turned over to the crew...
the select ones going
to the officers, naturally.
The wenches were escorted below
and, believe me, there was
no poetry or "by your leave'"...
or "how lovely you look, madam. '"
One got to the matter at hand
in short order.
Each captive seaman
was given 100 lashes with the cat...
- spread-eagled on the rigging.
- My dear Captain Blythe.
[Hisses]
They didn't last long
in those latitudes, I can tell you.
In no time at all, they were bloated
carrion for the birds of prey.
Yah!
Oh, do have some
of the green turtle soup, Mrs. Purkiss.
It's the chef's specialty.
- [Pop]
- [Gasps]
Well, they'd no sooner
broken out the grog...
- then the entire Spanish armada
was closing on them.
- Everything looks so tempting.
Yes. [Sighs]
Doesn't it?
They were met with stiff resistance
as they clambered aboard.
- It was parry and thrust,
thrust and parry.
- [Screams]
- Uh, permit me.
- Thank you.
- Anyone else?
- Oh. No, thanks.
Where was I?
Well, the deck was awash with blood!
What are you gonna have?
I think I'll have
that captain...
on a bed of roses.
Blast of grape
might sweep the deck clean.
- Aunt Louise, you're incorrigible.
- I know! [Giggling]
I've never regretted
a moment of it.
Right this way,
gentlemen.
My goodness,
what a pleasant surprise.
Two handsome young gentlemen as our
dining companions. I'm Louise Trends.
- DavyJohns.
- Pete Staniczek.
Pete, this is
my niece Melissa.
Well, sit down,
sit down.
Oh, just lucky,
I guess.
- You gentlemen going to Rio?
- Not exactly, ma'am.
Oh, I was telling Melissa...
Rio is a city
of romance.
You really, to get the most out of it,
have to share it with someone.
- Wasn't I, Melissa?
- Aunt Louise.
Well, personally, I won't have much time
for that sort of thing.
I'll be utilizing every moment
I have copying down material
for my doctorate.
You're gonna be a doctor?
Yes, of Latin American
cultures.
Celery? [Giggles]
Cool it with the doctor bit.
Well, so what does take
you gentlemen to Rio?
Actually, we're headed further
south. We're entering a car
in the Brazil Grand Primeo.
Pete here handles the wheel.
The rest is my lookout.
- You're a race driver.
- Yeah.
Oh, isn't that fascinating!
- Oh, I love race cars,
don't you, Melissa?
- Not really.
Well... hungry?
(music) [Humming]
Ah! [Muttering]
Ahh.
[Muttering In Italian]
Ah! Here we go.
[Singing In Italian]
[Speaking Italian]
Buon appetito, eh?
[Chuckling]
- Ah! [Speaking Italian]
- [Phone Ringing]
[Continues Speaking Italian]
[Sighs]
[Phone Ringing Continues]
But I checked the pressure
five minutes ago. Everything is fine.!
Number one, okay.!
Yes, I know how Capt. Blythe is...
but I tell you, the dial is right
on the nose. I see it for myself.
[Muttering In Italian]
[Muttering Continues]
Who take-a my chicken?
[Faint Chewing Sounds]
Aha! So you think you can steal
Armando's dinner and get away with it?
We're gonna see about that.
Oh, yes.
Okay. Open up.
Open up, little car.
No car's gonna eat my dinner.
Open up. I tell you!
Open up!
[Yelling, Muttering]
[Muttering In Italian]
Aha! Heh-heh-heh!
Open up.
[Grunting]
[Man] You can't drive
that car down here.
This is the number one hold.
Some of your cargo, it's-a broke loose!
Send your officer watch down here fast,
no, but I mean real fast! Si.
- Hey, what's going on?
- That car has no driver!
Better notify
Captain Blythe!
[Officer Whispering]
Shh.! All right, men.
Spread out and be careful.
Psst!
[Whistling Quietly]
Now.!
[Grunting]
And I am to believe
that this... car...
ate your chicken dinner?
Eh, and then he spit out the bones!
[Spitting]
- Who is this?
- Wiper, third class,
Armando Moccia, sir.
Do you know the penalty
for drinking on duty...
wiper, third class?
[Muttering In Italian]
Armando not touch one drop. No, please!
The car ate my apple.
I know because I hear with my own ears!
Eh! Muncha-muncha-munch!
Muncha-muncha-munch, eh?
- Do you know what I'm going
to do with your ears?
- [Chuckles Nervously]
- Uh, where is the car now?
- Went for a drive after dinner.
Oh. And was it smoking a cigar
and drinking a brandy?
The perpetrator of this little jest
will receive 50 lashes...
- before ship's company
and set adrift in a...
- [Gasps]
Perhaps you'll be good enough
to tell me about your grandson
Snooky another time.
- [Gasps]
- Wiper, third class, Armando Moccia?
- Aye-aye, sir.
- [Crashing]
[Men Yelling]
[Car Accelerating]
[Car Braking]
Ah!
[Grunting]
Okay, men, secure it.
Get the blocks and make it good.
Capitane.
Muncha-muncha-muncha! Si.!
See? Hah!
[Grunts, Snorts]
Now.
- How did you want to handle that?
- You mean pay for it?
Or did you plan to, uh,
reassemble the stemware yourself?
- It's not our responsibility.
- [Whip Cracks]
I'm your captain, judge and jury.
I'll decide what's your responsibility!
Captain!
The, uh, the cargo manifest
states unequivocally...
that you, Peter Staniczek,
are the sole owner of the car.
You are the consignor
and the consignee.
Your car did damage, ergo...
- Yeah, but Pete wasn't driving...
- Stow it!
I, uh, I have been advised
by our public relations department...
to waive all charges
of kidnapping...
and smuggling illegal aliens
into a foreign country.
- Where is that kid, anyway?
- In the storeroom...
where he'll remain until
the ship reaches Panama...
at which time he will be turned
over to the port authorities...
and returned
to his native country.
In the meantime,
your automobile will be impounded...
until your obligations
are met.
Captain.
Uh, gentlemen...
I do hope you've been
enjoying the cruise so far.
Remember, we have
a shuffleboard tournament
on main deck at four bells...
and, uh, disco lessons
in the lounge at six bells.
Thanks, anyway.
We can write the captain an
I.O.U. And pay him out of our
winning at the Grand Primeo.
There's no way we can raise
that kind of money.
Maybe we should chalk it up
to experience and work our way home.
- Maybe Aunt Louise will bail us.
- You are a dreamer, D.J.
Wait a minute.
She likes cars and she's trying
to get her niece hooked up.
Yeah?
- No!
- Wait a minute.
All you gotta do is keep the doc
enthralled with tales of derring-do...
while I initiate Aunt Louise
into the delights of Formula One racing.
- I don't like it.
- Come on, man! Nothing good comes easy.
Lots of charm,
lots of charm.
You may not believe this,
this is an exact replica,
down to the last button...
of the uniform worn by Lord Nelson
when he defeated the Spanish armada.
- Seems like it belongs
on me, doesn't it?
- I love a uniform.
It gives a man a certain...
[Blows]
- At ease, madam!
- Captain!
Excuse me, I must circulate
among the cargo... uh, passengers.
Anyway, like I was saying,
it's the thrill of a lifetime...
when you see that car that
belongs to you streak across
that finish line a winner.
Not only that, you're part
of the technological advancement
of the automotive world.
- Oh, really.
- Mm-hmm.
I wonder...
where the kids are.
Now isn't that...
(music)In my heart and my hand
(music)I've never seen
- They seem to be enjoying themselves.
- Yeah, they're hitting it off.
Pete's a great guy.
He's what I call a beautiful person.
(music) With your head up in a cloud
(music) Where you belong
(music)Please look at me
(music)lf I stay around
(music)Maybe something good
will happen
(music)Like you'll
look into my eyes
(music)And realize
- My kind of racin'.
- [Chuckling]
Oh, pardon me.
That's the third time I've done that.
Who's counting?
I'm having a great time.
- Are you really?
- Yeah.
(music)And so
Usually when we race,
a good time means towing
the crew across Texas...
in the middle of August,
looking for a Denny's...
then bedding down
in some fleabag motel.
Now here I am...
soft lights, sweet music...
pretty girl.
Uh, Mr. Staniczek, you don't
really have to say those things.
Oh, I know that. It's just that you're
different than other girls I've known.
- I can well imagine.
- No, no, it's a compliment.
For one thing, you don't giggle
when there's nothing funny.
And you listen when I talk.
A man looks a long way
for a girl like that.
And, uh...
(music)And maybe then
- Our fingers touch
- You are pretty, Melissa.
(music)And you'll thrill me
oh, so much
(music)A lovely dream
(music) That's meant to be
(music)lf you would give
(music) One look
(music)At me
Ah, this is it.
I just want to thank you
for this evening.
- L-I really enjoyed myself.
- Me too.
Well, good night.
Melissa?
- This is the pits.
- Did something go wrong?
We went wrong
when we got into this.
I don't like playing games
with people.
Come on, just a couple more days.
I already got the money.
Aunt Louise gave me a check.
We got the car out of hock.
And get this, kiddo.
She's gonna sponsor us all the way.
We name it, she buys it.!
All you gotta do is keep making
like Burt Reynolds.
- So, that's the deal.
- Well, I sorta read it
between the lines.
Anyway, the important thing
is we're back in the running.
Ahh! Nothing's gonna
stop us now.
[Weak Honking]
- [Weak Honking]
- Hi!
- That captain sure was mad, wasn't he?
- Honk!
- What is he gonna do with you?
- Honk-honk-honk.
They will send me back where I live...
with the orphans.
But it's okay.
They put me back, I run away again.
- Can we be friends?
- Honk.
- What's your name?
- Honk-honk.
- Que?
- [Slower] Honk-honk.
- I just call you "Ocho," okay?
- Honk-honk.
[Whistling]
Atta boy, Ocho!
Thanks, Ocho.
I'll pay you back.
But you better go back where you were,
so you won't get in trouble.
[Footsteps]
- Oh-oh!
- [Engine Starts]
There it goes!
Don't let it get out of this hold, men!
Check over
by the elevator, men.!
[Running Footsteps]
In those days,
a captain was a captain.
And a ship was a ship,
not a floating carnival.
And the only women aboard
were dragged there by
the scruff of their neck!
Whoo, gives me goose bumps
just thinking about it.
The captain is having
a little jest with you ladies.
I'm only telling it
like it was.
[Quietly]
Or should be.
Yes, when you talked about
liberation in those days...
you were talking
about battles...
nations, empires.
[Crashing]
Oh! Oh!
[Louise] Oh, Captain.
Oh, my word.!
Sorry!
[Groans, Spits]
But, Captain, how can a car
release a boy with a key? Explain that!
I can't explain that
any more than I can explain
the Bermuda Triangle, madam.
- Nor do I intend to try.
- Captain, I am the sponsor
of that little car.
It's going to win
the Brazil Grand Primeo.
If you can bring that off,
I will not only part the Red Sea...
I will tint it magenta.
Oh, oh, Captain.
I appeal to you as a woman...
a desperate, helpless...
single woman.
- Spare that car.
- Lorelei and her sirens could
not make me veer one degree!
- My course is set!
- Oh!
Ship's company!
Stand to to witness punishment!
Sir, the passengers
might not understand.
I am simply abiding
by the traditions of the sea...
Chief Steward.
By the powers vested in me
as the captain of this ship...
I hereby deem this vehicle
a menace...
to life and limb and the very
safety of the vessel itself.
I herewith commit it
to the sea...
a fate well-deserved.
- Doff hats!
- [Drum Roll]
Seamen... do your duty.
[Weak Honking]
- [Weak Honking Continues]
- [Crowd Gasping]
- You too?
- Oh, bag and baggage.
Anyone remotely associated with
that little car is being put ashore.
If it hadn't been for that steward,
we'd have been keelhauled.
- Sorry it turned out like this.
- If I decided to get out
of needlepoint...
and into racing,
it was my choice.
- Actually, there's more
to it than that.
- Steady, steady.
We needed backing, so D.J.
Pitched you on the car while... l...
Pitched my niece
on the fantail.
I've got too much mileage
on me not to recognize...
an operation
when I see one.
You mean you knew that?
Well, I was hoping that...
something might happen
between you and Melissa.
She's really
a wonderful girl.
- She's terrific but...
- A little klutzy for someone
like yourself.
Not everybody's
made for each other.
I really like her and I
don't want her to get hurt.
I plan to tell her but maybe
you can smooth things over.
- Here's your bag, miss.
- Thank you.
Melissa, there you are!
I was just looking...
- You meet such
interesting types on ships.
- Melissa!
Sorry, boys.
Come on, pal.
How do you say
in Panamanian...
we need a job?
Excuse me. I don't know
where you're taking this boy,
but I have prior claim on him.
- Are you from Juvenile Authority?
- Yes, I am.
- No, he's not!
- Aah!
We'll handle this!
- Grab that kid!
- Stop that kid!
He's wanted by the police!
We gotta get that kid!
We'll get him.
Tom, you better come
take a look at this.
- What the devil is that?
- I don't know. Supposed
to be the Major Maroux.
[Soft Honking]
Ocho?
- [Honking]
- Ocho!
I'm coming, Ocho,
I'm coming!
- Ayudame, andale.!
- Vamonos.!
[Honking]
[Speaking Spanish]
[Grunting, Laughing]
[Laughing Continues]
What is the matter,
muchacho?
- It's an old wreck.
- But he was my good friend.
Your friend is good for nothing
but junk. [Laughing]
Hey, even junk...
worth something.
[Cackling]
Bye, Ocho.
Vaya con Dios.
[Rattling]
Ocho!
Come on, Ocho,
you can do it. Try, try!
- Please, Ocho, come on!
- [Backfiring]
Don't give up now,
please, please.!
Try, try!
I help you!
[Speaking Spanish]
It's those men.
Come on, you gotta start!
You're whippin'
a dead horse, muchacho.
We gotta get outta here!
This is our car now!
Go play someplace else.
Sal de ahi, muchacho.
Ay.!
[Engine Roars]
[Men Coughing]
You feeling better, Ocho.
(music)A friend
(music)It takes one to be one
(music) Takes some time 'til
the light starts shinin'
(music) On a friendship
(music)A friend
(music)Step up if you need one
(music)Stick out your hand
(music) They should understand
it's a friendship
(music)A buenos dias
Come on, try
(music)A pat on the back
A wink of the eye
(music) That's what friends are for
and remember this, charro (music)
(music) They'll stick with you
today and tomorrow
(music) Amigo (music)
(music)It's nice if you've got one
(music)But it's nicer
if you're not one to stop
(music)From lookin'for more
(music) The world is full of people
who need you so much
(music)A million hearts there
to touch
(music)And I bet you a banana
(music) Manana you'll have
a new friend
(music)And I bet you a banana
(music) Manana you'll have
a new friend
(music)A friend
(music)It's nice when you see one
(music)But it's nicer
when you be one
You look good, Ocho,
like a real taxi.
Now we're gonna make
lots of money.
Then Paco will never have to
take nothin'from nobody again.
[Door Closes]
[Prindle]
Just relax, sonny.
- Now, where is it?
- Where's what?
There was some film in the wallet
you took from us in Puerto Vallarta.
When we got it back,
it was missing.
- Where is it?
- I don't know. Maybe it got mixed-up.
- What do you mean, "mixed-up"?
- With the other man's wallet.
He's lying.
Maybe, maybe not.
Now you listen to me.
I want that film back.
I don't care how you do it,
just get it back!
Because if you don't...
he's gonna cut this car of yours
up into tiny, little pieces.
You understand, kid, huh?
Little strips to hang on
your Christmas tree?
Comprende?
Si.
You know, Pete,
I was just thinking.
Do you realize that that car
could've put us in the big time?
We could've been
international celebrities.
You know what I mean?
Endorsements,
groupies chasin' after us.
It's that kid.
Murphy's Law took over from
the time we ran into that brat.
Hi, guys.
Speaking of
four-foot crime waves.
I come to say, I sorry
if I make trouble for you.
Yeah, well, fine.
See you around.
Paco go. I just want you
not be mad at me.
[Crying]
Now don't start that.
Nobody's mad.
It's water over the dam.
I'm sorry.
Please, you forgive me?
Fine, kid,
no hard feelings.
Forget it.
[Whispering]
Straight back there,
through that hallway and to the right.
Gracias.!
Gloriosky! Just makes you
feel good all over.
He did it again.
Come back here,
you little bandit!
- [Honking]
- [Pete] Hey, that's our car.!
- How can that be our car?
- I don't know. Let's get him!
We better get outta here,
or those guys are gonna get you back!
[Tires Screeching]
Shepard's ready.
He's got the plane.
Good.
Here comes the boy.
[Tires Screeching]
Why, that little,
double-crossing... Come on!
[Whistle]
Taxi!
Taxi.!
Let me get in here.
It's a little tight.
Pardon moi, senor.
[Grunting]
- Pier 6, the Sun Princess.
- Pier 5, the Windsong, please.
- You!
- I'm terribly sorry,
- I'm terribly excited...
- but it's imperative I return
to my ship immediately.
- I'd be so pleased...
- You can have the cab after that!
- Thank you.
- The Sun Princess.
- The Windsong, please.
We're in real
trouble now, Ocho.
[Blythe]
And full steam ahead.!
Where in blazes
are you going, driver?
No comprendo, senor.
You people comprendo enough
when you want to!
Wait a minute.
[Gasping]
It's that same kid!
And here's the biggie:
I think it's the same car.
It's a ghost.
Let me outta here!
- Let me outta here, or it's
the yardarm for you!
- Can't stop now, senor.
- Look!
- Oh! Uh...
- Melissa! Melissa!
- Help, help!
Help!
I'm being shanghaied!
Help, Melissa.!
Help!
I'm being shanghaied!
The kid,
he robbed us again!
- He shanghaied them.
- Shanghai?
Senor, stop!
Could you please stop?
Por favor, alto.!
Por favor, alto.
Please stop.
[Brakes Squealing]
Por favor, senor.!
Muchas gracias.
- How much?
- How far you want to go?
No, how much
for the whole bus?
Huh?
Is $340 enough?
Lady,
you got yourself a bus!
Next bus, please.
Todos para fuera.
Acabo de vender el bus.!
[Laughing]
[Passengers Complaining]
[Blythe]
Now, listen to me, son.
If you don't release me
this instant...
I'll have you tied to a cannon
to be discharged at sunset.!
[Paco]
I can't stop.
Two men said that they would
cut up Ocho in little pieces...
and two other men
are very mad at me.
[Bus Engine Clattering]
[Melissa]
Is that banging noise new?
[DJ.]Just louder.
It might throw a rod.
- Uh, is that serious?
- Not if it happens in front of a hotel.
[Backfires]
Are we still in Panama?
- Panama's long gone, capitan.
- What? Let me out of here.!
Can't, capitan.
There's some men after me!
No, Ocho,
not in there!
- [Spectators] Olé!
- What was that?
We're at the bullfights,
capitan.
Oh, this is exciting.
- I think it will be, senora.
- What did he mean by that?
- [Sneezing]
- God bless you.
Turn in there!
- This can't be right.
- Back up!
[Spectators Cheering]
Oh!
We're goin'in.!
[Spectators Cheering]
[Bellowing]
[Snorting]
- What are we gonna do?
- Just ignore him.
[Booing]
Saquen esos carros
de la plaza.!
Vamonos, hombre.!
Pero saquense de aqui. Estan locos.
Pero orale,
afuera, hombre.!
[Spectators Booing]
[Snorting]
Come on,
get it off the car!
[Cheering]
[Grunting]
Come on!
[Spectators Cheering]
[Shouting, Booing]
Oh... Oooh!
Alto, ya parenle,
basta, ya basta.!
Please get us
out of here, kid.
I'm not asking for myself,
but I'm very worried about this lady.
- How thoughtful!
- Just shut up!
- Pasen por esa puerta, rapido.!
- Si, senor policia.
[Blythe]
That first gangway.! Move it.!
Aaah!
Get goin Ocho.!
Ay, que viene el toro.!
- We're stopped. Where's the bull?
- There he is.
What a magnificent animal.
- I think you can see him
better from here.
- Aaah!
Aaah!
Hey, Ocho, we gonna let him
get away with that?
Yes, you are!
Let's get out of here!
[Spectators Cheering]
[Blythe]
Scat, scat, scat.!
Ocho, he's gonna kill ya!
You just can't stand here doin' nothin'!
You gotta fight!
Take a good look at him!
[Paco]
He's a killer.!
[Engine Revving]
- He is going to fight.
- That-a-boy, Ocho!
I can't believe this.
Thirty years at sea,
and I'm going to die in a bullring.
[Paco]
Hey, toro, toro.!
Toro.! Hey, toro.!
Toro, toro.!
- No toros! Shhh!
- Toro.!
Toro, toro.!
Andale, toro, aqui.!
Hey, toro.!
Good, Ocho!
That-a-boy, Ocho!
Stay with him!
Ole, Ocho.!
[Snorting]
[Spectators Cheering]
Atta boy, Ocho!
You take him now!
Look, son, I want you to know
that I think of you as my son.
If you get us out of here, I'll make you
first mate of the Sun Princess.
You and your little car
can stay in a nice suite...
and eat at my table
every night.
The big boat will take you
anywhere you want to go, okay?
Don't worry, capitan,
we got him now!
[Groaning]
Over here, toro.!
Over here!
Ole.!
Hey, toro, toro.!
That-a-boy, Ocho!
He's getting
awfully close, Ocho.!
- Aaah!
- I'm going to be sick.
They got voodoo down here,
you know that?
[Spectators Cheering]
[Cheering Continues]
[Spectators]
Ole! Ole!
[Snorting]
He's had enough. Let's go.
Come on.
They want us to take a bow,
all of us!
[Spectators Cheering]
Oh, wait.
Come out.
- Nothing in this world will
induce me to go out there.
- They'll be disappointed.
Don't pull on me!
Don't do that!
[Not Audible]
Mmm! Ahhh!
[Cheering Continues]
You too, capitan.
Take a bow!
[Wild Cheering]
[Engine Starts]
Oof!
[Honking]
What's wrong, Ocho?
Oh!
[Tires Screeching]
Wait a minute!
- I told you.
- Let's get Shepard and the plane!
Captain, the boy!
That boy's in trouble!
Help him! Help!
- Can't we go any faster?
- We could, but we'd have to walk.
The fact that we're
moving at all violates...
- every principle of the
internal combustion engine.
- Hey, wait a minute.
[Melissa]
It's Aunt Louise.
[DJ.]
And Captain Blythe?
Aunt Louise,
are you all right?
Ecstatic.
Well!
[Louise] We just fought a bull,
and brought it to a standstill.
[Pete]
Looks like you lost, Captain.
[Blythe]
Reverse your course.
[Louise] We have to find that boy.
There's some men after him.
What if he
doubled-back on us?
We'd have seen him.
There's only one road around here.
Just keep looking
for that crazy car.
[Louise]
He doesn't understand "bracket."
All right, then,
get some wire.
- Wire, wire.
- Wire?
- Wire, uh, wire.
- Wire.
Sounds like "fire."
Ah, si.!
Fuego, si.
- He's gonna get some.
- Thank you.
- Uh...
- Fuego.
Um, senor, no.
Mm-mm.
- The Sun Princess.
- Como se llama?
Tell the mate I've been
stranded in Timbio.
No puedo.
No le entiendo.
- The Sun Princess! It's a ship!
- Sheep.
- Now... No, not a sheep. It's a ship.
- Princesa es sheep.
Not sheep. That's "baa-baa"!
This is "toot-toot"!
- No comprendo, no.
- What do you mean, "no comprende"?
In St. Augustine,
not far from here...
they have monolithic
statues that are...
Well, they go back
to 500 B. C...
but nobody knows who made them
or where they came from.
I wish I could help you.
I'm sure you'd find a cold
six-pack much more exciting.
Oh, now, have I hit on something
that you hold dear and sacred?
Look, I led you on.
I apologized.
Oh, please, don't.
Well, I'll just have an
electrocardiogram when I get home.
But I can assure you,
there's been no damage.
We're wasting
valuable time bickering.
[Louise] Who knows what's
happened to that boy by now?
I'll just see what's
holding up the captain.
Why are you all
staring at me?
It's a conspiracy!
What?
Si, sesenta centavos.
Siesta centavos.
Don't go away.
I'll get it for you.
- Siesta centavos.
- Sesenta centavos, senor.
- Three minutes more
cost you more money.!
- Siesta centavos.
Oh, here.
Yes, we're getting it for you.
I beg you, don't hang up.
Yes, I'll be
right with you.
I love your country.
It's very colorful.
Your children have
such expressive faces.
Look alive with
that change, woman!
Please don't go away.
I'll get it for you.
Are you still there?
Hello?
Hello!
She's gone.
It took me two hours
just to get the operator...
and she's gone,
just like that.
- Oh.
- Hello?
Oh, yes, de nada.
How will I explain this
to the company?
You just tell Aunt Louise
all about it.
- They'll take away my command.
- Yes, oh.
- They'll take away my sheep.
- Oh, your sheep.
[Paco] I think we lost 'em,
but one thing I still can't figure out
Why would those men want
a picture like this, Ocho?
It's kinda lonely
around here, huh, Ocho?
Honk-honk.
When we're safe
from those men...
- we'll go back where there's
lots of people, huh, Ocho?
- Honk!
[Quinn]
We've got him.!
Why don't we
force him off the road?
Because we just might
come off second best.
Well, what's a bug
and a kid gonna do?
Something quite unexpected,
I assure you.
We'll wait 'til it stops.
[Plane Engine Buzzing]
[Engine Clattering]
Will it make
Chiclayo?
Not a prayer.
- How long do you give it?
- About a minute.
We should alert the captain.
He'd want to know about this.
[Pete] He'll be alerted,
any second now.
Sound general quarters!
- Captain!
- It's every man for himself!
Have you put out
distress signals?
Oh, we will.
Five of them.
Maybe we can go to Santiago
and work there, Ocho.
Those men'll
never find us there.
Don't worry, Ocho.
I'll take care of ya.
Oye, nino. El senor
en la cantina necesita un taxi.
- Andale, pronto. Apurate.
- Si.!
Wake up, Ocho!
A man in the cantina needs a taxi.
We can siesta later.
- Someone want a taxi?
- Just the driver.
Ow! Let go!
Let me go.!
No! Let me go!
Aaah!
Ocho!
Let me go.!
Help.!
Ocho!
Bye-bye.
How's it going?
I'm telling them not to hold
the ship at Port au Spain...
but go directly to Tobago,
where I'll join them there.
I hate to think of what's happened
to that ship in my absence.
Get this off immediately.
It goes to the Communication
Center of the Sun Princess.
Are you certain that
the pigeon understands that?
Si, senor capitan.
He certainly knows
his pigeons.
There's an airport in Chiclayo,
about 12 miles further on.
But there's no transportation
from here to Chiclayo.
[Engine Revving]
[Louise]
It's the same car.!
I was so worried.
Thank heavens.!
It's the same car,
but where's the boy?
- [Honking]
- I think he wants to tell us something.
It's a car, woman,
not Lassie.
- Where is Paco?
- Honk-honk-honk.
I know something terrible's
happened to him. Come on.
Get in, everybody.
Get in!
I am not getting into
that sardine can again!
- It's a 12-mile walk to Chiclayo,
so make up your mind.
- And hurry!
- Get in here!
- Ow!
Oh! Aaah!
[Prindle]
What about that down there?
Yeah,
that could be it.
[Shepard] Gentlemen,
we're right on the money.!
[Thunder Rumbling]
[Prindle]
Together now, pull.!
[Grunting]
[Thunder]
What do you think?
Gold.!
Probably pure gold.!
[Laughing]
More than that,
it has tremendous archaeological value.
- Do you think there's more?
- Plenty.
[Quinn]
What do we do with it?
I say we get this
outta here now...
then come back with tools
and do it up right, okay?
You got it.
- What about me?
- Get outta here!
Aaah!
[Shepard] I don't like leavin'
that kid back there.
[Quinn] Don't worry about him.
He's not goin'anywhere.
Does anyone know
where we are?
The car does.
I'm sure of it.
Well, ask it, will you?
I would, but we're not
on speaking terms.
[Melissa] This is ridiculous.
Somebody ought to do something.
- We'd better just sit tight.
- Easy for you.
[Thunder Rumbling]
[Shivering, Crying]
[Animal Screeching]
Aaah!
[Animal Growling]
[Honking]
Ocho!
Paco, what are you doing here
in the middle of the jungle?
- We were worried sick about you.
- Those men, they were stealing gold.
Big gold, like this.!
- [Pete] Where'd they get gold?
- Right there. It looks like Inca ruins.
Si. It's Inca. They will
fly away the gold and they
will melt it. I hear them.
I'll see that the matter
is brought to the attention
of the proper authorities...
when we put in at Rio.
That might be too late.
Go, Ocho.!
- [Engine Revving]
- What's that?
Come on, give us a hand!
Let's keep movin'!
Oh, no.!
It's that car.!
It ate it.!
It ate the gold.!
[Quinn]
How'd it get out here?
- There goes a million bucks.
- No way.
[Sighing]
Seven hundred miles on
a banana boat with wheels.
I'll be laughed off
the Caribbean.
It worked, didn't it?
Those men in the airplane,
they couldn't find us.
It was a good idea, Paco.
How much farther?
We're practically there.
Okay, get ready
to peel off.
Hmm, sorry.
[Melissa] We're looking for
Dr. De Moraes'offce.
[Pete] He's upstairs,
in the main building.
I'll call the police.
Hello.
You go on.
I'll wait here.
Aaah!
May I use your phone?
It's very important. Oh, thank you.
Hey!
Are you going towards the sea?
It's vitally important
I return to my ship!
Wait, wait!
[Knocking]
Dr. De Moraes?
Yes?
Oh, Dr. De Moraes...
you have no idea what
we've gone through to get this to you.
And what we've gone through
to get it from you.
When we couldn't
find you on the highway...
we decided that you'd either gone
to the nearest police station...
or to the world's foremost
authority on Inca civilization.
I guessed right.
Nice, ripe bananas.
They're good for brains.
Get 'em while they last.
Very cheap.
Nice, ripe bananas.
Let's make a deal on a peel.
Let's do
this thing together.
We don't want this
to get away from us.
[Engine Cranking]
Ocho, listen. Sounds like
the airplane those men had!
Let's go see!
[Brakes Squealing]
They can't do anything.
Come on.
Ocho, what are we gonna do?
They're taking the gold!
Atta boy, Ocho!
Wh-Wh-Whoa!
Sorry, boss.!
Get this thing off of me!
Hit 'em again,
Ocho!
You idiot!
- Hey, come on! Hurry up!
- Get this thing off of me!
[Groaning]
Give me that thing!
[Mumbling]
I can't get a grip on it.!
Let's do this
scientifically.
Pull! Push!
Cut it out, will ya?
[Grumbling, Groaning]
Get off of my foot!
Help me get it
to the plane.
I can't see!
Whoa!
[Groaning]
Hurry up, pilot!
Ready... fire.!
Say what you want
about voodoo...
but where I come from,
cars don't throw bananas.
Just get it
in the plane!
Ocho, they're getting away.
Hurry!
[Tires Squealing]
Come on, let's get
this thing outta here!
With this extra weight, I'm gonna need
the whole field to take off!
Well, hurry up!
Here it comes again!
[Quinn] You think he's gonna
try and hijack us?
[Prindle]
Anything's possible with that thing.
Get 'em, Ocho!
Stay with 'em!
- I wonder what it's gonna do now.
- I don't know.
Well, take off!
- Come on, take off!
- I'm trying!
- Right on our tail.
- I think he's tryin' to chew it off.
Do we need one?
Now, Ocho, get him!
Don't let go!
That-a-boy!
Shake 'em, Ocho!
Shake 'em, man.
I can't take off with all that
weight in the tail. Go get it!
- Catch it when I raise the tail.
- Gotcha.!
Aaah!
Go for it, Ocho, now!
Hang on!
Shake it off!
Come on, Ocho, you can't give up now!
They're getting away!
[Shepard]
He's going to ram us.!
- Aaah!
- Do something!
- Why are we going in circles?
- Because he broke my tail, that's why!
Now get in front of'em!
Make 'em stop!
Get this thing
off the ground!
We're gonna hit him!
Pull up!
She's stalling.!
They're still going, Ocho!
- What's the matter?
- The throttle jammed open!
My wings!
- You hurt, Ocho?
- [Weak Honk]
You don't sound so good.
Don't quit now.
You can do it!
- Can you step it up?
- I'm hurrying.
- Move your feet forward.
- I got it, I got it.
Uh, uh...
Policia.!
I'm so glad you're here.
I was the one who called you.
Stay with 'em!
Go, go!
[Police Sirens]
Can't you make this thing
go any faster?
The oil pressure's down.
I don't want to ruin my plane.
[Police Sirens]
They got the gold!
[Paco]
Stop! You'll never get away!
[Louise]
We're right behind you!
Okay, Ocho, you got 'em now!
Give it to 'em!
Whoa!
- You did it!
- Paco, Paco.
That's him!
Paco, are you all right?
Ocho and me, we okay.
You ought to see those other guys.
No se muevan.
Quedense ahi.
Todos ustedes,
salganse de ahi.
Salganse de ahi, les digo.
Yno se muevan.
(music)[Dance Music]
Gorgeous!
Just magnificent.
I've always felt, Captain,
that you have a...
deep appreciation for beauty.
I've never seen
anything like it.
Any man of the sea who wouldn't
want her rolling under him...
is ready for dry dock!
Wow!
Magnificent!
I'm not admitting the kid's
a better driver than I am...
but he sure can get more
out of that car than I can.
- And they're really...
- Simpatico.
Yeah, simpatico.
Well?
If I had billowed out
like a schooner under full sail...
I might have...
shivered his timbers.
- I hope we win this one.
- Don't you worry, Aunt Louise.
This is the car that's gonna win
the Grand Primeo of Brazil.
That's right.
Drivers,
start your engines!
[Clapping]
Paco,
muy bueno.!
[Clapping]
[Engine Starts]
Looking good, Ocho!
Why do you keep
calling this car "Ocho"?
"Ocho" means eight.
Can't you read the numbers?
Sure I can read the numbers.
Five and three are eight.
Anyone knows that.
[Laughing]
Let's have a toast.
To victory in Rio.
[Everyone]
Victory in Rio.!
(music)A friend
(music)It takes one to be one
(music) Takes some time 'til
the light starts shinin'
(music) On a friendship
(music)A friend
(music)Step up if you need one
(music)Stick out your hand
(music) They should understand
it's a friendship
(music)A buenos dias
Come on, try
(music)A pat on the back
A wink of the eye
(music) That's what friends are for
and remember this, charro (music)
(music) They'll stick with you
today and tomorrow
(music) Amigo (music)
(music)It's nice if you got one
(music)But it's nicer
if you're not one to stop
(music)From lookin'for more
(music) The world is full of people
who need you so much
(music)A million hearts there
to touch
(music)And I bet you a banana
(music) Manana you'll have
a new friend
(music)F-R-E-N-D
Friend
5@y3
Watch Movies, TV Series and Live Sports
Signup Here -> WWW.ADMITME.APP