23.976 English
sync © 03.07.2021
Watch Movies, TV Series and Live Sports
Signup Here -> WWW.ADMITME.APP
No! No!
Cord (2000)
Also Known As: Hide and Seek
You're okay. Just relax.
Just try to relax, okay?
- Hey... how you doin'?
- Good, thanks.
Look, we have a visitor.
She just woke up.
Where am I?
Good morning. Good morning!
Sleepy? Hello.
Where am I? Who are you?
Helen, could you get
the phone, please?
- Oh, okay.
- Thanks, baby.
Can you raise this arm up?
No.
I couldn't get your ring off,
so I had to remove a
little tissue.
I used the anesthetic
so it wouldn't hurt.
- Here.
- Thanks, baby.
Sorry about that.
Where's Jack?
He's right over here.
Look!
Yeah, right.
- Helen...
- What?
Please be quiet, baby.
Don't tell me to shut up.
I didn't tell you to shut up.
I just said to be quiet.
Tell her what
happened to her head.
- He dropped you.
- You're not really helping.
Well, you did.
He dropped you on your head.
- Helen, could...?
- Oh, right. The number.
- Thank you.
- The number.
I'm going to call up your husband.
I don't want you...
What do you want?
Let's call.
Mr. White?
Who I am is not important.
Just do exactly as I say...
or...
or I'll kill your wife.
Okay, go ahead, here.
Tell your husband you're okay.
Go ahead, say hello.
- Jack?
- Go ahead. I'm okay.
- Help, Jack.
- Tell him.
- Jack...
- Okay, I'm okay.
I'm fine, I'm fine.
I'm okay.
Okay, that's it. That's it.
So there you have it, sir.
If you don't do exactly
as we tell you, then...
we'll have to kill somebody.
Be smart...
very, very smart.
Bye.
Good, honey.
Now we just can wait.
The waiting game.
Coffee?
I want some coffee, yeah.
Do you want some coffee?
Are you crying?
Don't cry.
You're very pretty.
Okay.
We'll see you in a while, okay?
Bye-bye.
You're going to have
to come by the house soon.
You won't even recognize it.
I turned his office
into a game room.
Excuse me one minute.
I got the house, he got the crap.
- Jack?
- Hey, speak of angels.
- Anne!
- Hi, Emily.
- Hi, how are you?
- Good, thanks.
I heard about your miscarriage.
I'm sorry.
My sister went through two in-vitro
trials before she succeeded.
Are you going to try again?
Well, we're...
we're talking about it.
Jack, Uncle Bob is leaving.
Oh! Oh, okay.
Would you excuse
us for a second?
- Thanks.
- Bye.
Jack?
Hey, Jack?
Come with me.
Okay...
Do you know where we are?
No... Wha...
- Okay.
- Wha...
- Open?
- Open.
Wow...
Oh, it's so beautiful.
What... what's this?
You're too much.
Like it?
I can't wait to have this baby.
I just can't wait.
Honey, what's the matter?
Honey?
You okay?
You're so hot.
I think I'm pregnant.
Really?
- I think so.
- Really?
I think so.
You don't want to
kiss me right now.
Anne, wake up.
Time to wake up.
Right now, I'm going
to release you from
those nasty handcuffs, okay?
Do I have your permission?
What?
It's very, very important
that we trust each other.
Trust makes everything
move more smoothly.
Am I making sense?
Good.
So...
can we trust each other?
Yeah.
What?
Yes, what?
We can trust each other?
Okay, then.
You'll feel better when
you see what I have for you.
Look at that.
Ta-da!
It's veal.
I made it especially for you.
Go on.
Take a bite.
Mmm... Mmm...
It's good, isn't it?
I don't eat veal.
You know what it is, don't you?
What veal is?
It's baby cows.
Little baby cows.
Haven't even had a chance
to walk yet.
Eat up.
Hello? Hello.
Oh, geez, no, no...
I ordered...
Oh!
Oh, poor little Anne!
I'm sorry, it wasn't my idea.
Frank didn't feel like
he could really trust you.
Not just yet.
Come back to bed.
You shouldn't be
galloping all over anyway.
Here you go, nice and cozy.
Here, nice veal.
For you.
What's going on?
Have you heard from my husband?
Good girl.
Finish up.
Okay, I'll just be
right up here, on the phone.
If you want anything, call.
You're just...
not pregnant.
Are you sure?
Because...
- I... I've had...
- She's been vomiting at home.
- Several at home pregnancy tests.
- Yes.
- They've both come up...
- She's been positive on every test.
- I've been sick every night.
- Right, right.
I could run another
series, but, uh...
Frank Benton,
Anne and Jack White.
Hi, how you doing?
- Hi.
Frank, you did cross check
these tests, didn't you?
That's right,
Dr. Webster.
So we, you'd know if there
was something happening.
That's correct, sir.
You know, the symptoms
you've been experiencing...
are probably due to
a number of hormonal changes.
It's perfectly natural to go through
these fluctuations from time to time.
If you've been under severe stress,
you know that can really
wreak havoc on your system.
You may even read positive
on a home pregnancy test.
I can tell her if I want to...
and you can't stop me.
I've seen it before and
I know what to do.
Yeah, and look how you
solved that one.
I could tell her if I want to.
You can't stop me, honey.
You can't tell me what to do...
- You're not the boss of the family.
- I can stop you, I can stop you.
- I'm the boss of the family.
- What are you doing?
Stop being such an animal.
This is a civilized house.
I want you to cut it out.
She's not ready to be told yet.
No! Let go of me.
Let go of me!
I can tell her if I want to.
You get away from me.
- What are you going to do?
- Get away from me.
- Anne! I have something...
- No.
- No!
- Cut it out!
Just relax.
- I am relaxed.
- Just settle down.
- I am settling down.
- Come on.
- I am settling, I...
- Come on, baby, come on.
You're going to fuck it up.
I need an aspirin.
Do you have some aspirin?
I need a little...
Anne!
Shit!
Don't you tell her!
No! Leave me alone!
Anne, help me!
- Let go of me!
- Cut it out.
- Cut it out...bitch.
You have a big mouth.
Anne, you're pregnant and
you're going to have my baby.
Cut it out. Cut it out.
Go upstairs.
- Stop it. It's too late, moron.
- Go upstairs.
- I told her.
- Yeah?
Anne, you're going
to have my baby.
She was just kidding.
She's just making things up.
You're a jerk, Helen.
I know you.
You work at the clinic.
Dr. Cordon's office.
Right?
Oh, my God!
I am pregnant.
I'm pregnant, and you...
My husband.
Oh, my God!
Where's Jack?
He doesn't even
know you're here.
The ransom and the...
What about the ring?
There's no ransom,
and nobody knows you're here.
You're going to have that baby
and you're going to give it to us.
So get some sleep.
You're going to be here a long time.
I can tell her if I want to...
Honey, are you there?
It's me.
I guess you're not
home from work yet.
I don't know if you
got any of my messages.
Well, my flight schedule is the same,
so I'll see you in the morning.
I'm gonna keep you up all night.
I love you.
Annie!
Anne!
Anne?
Honey, are you there?
It's me.
Annie?
I guess you're not
home from work yet.
I don't know if you got
any of my messages...
The car went off a cliff about
three miles north of Point Bonita.
It looks like she just lost control.
I mean, they've taken the car in...
to check for the possibility
of brake failure, but...
there's just no solid answers yet.
I want to see her.
- Look, I can understand you...
- Look, don't give me that shit.
Don't give me that shit.
- I want to see my wife.
- There's nothing to see.
The fire burned very hot.
I'm very sorry.
Well, how do you know it's her?
I mean, how can you be sure that...?
You identified the ring
and the chain.
If you've got any questions or
if you're unsure about this...
You didn't find the pendant.
- You don't have the pendant.
- The chain was broken.
The chain was broken
when we found it.
The pendant probably flew
off away from the wreckage.
There's nothing left.
I do wish there
was more that I could tell you.
If you need to talk,
you know where to reach me.
You'll be the first one to
know if we find out anything new.
Good morning, good morning.
It's time to get up
in the morning.
Anne!
Anne?
There you are!
You scared me.
What are you doing, all scrunched
up in the corner like that?
Look!
Look what I have for you.
It's something different.
It's a delicious macrobiotic shake.
I made it myself.
Mmm, mmm...
I'm not hungry.
Well, how about I'll just
put it over here, by the table...
and you can eat it over here,
sitting up like a real person.
Would you like that?
Come on, Anne.
I went to a lot of trouble
to make this milkshake.
It's got nutrients and things
that you need for the growing baby.
Don't be so selfish. It's not like
you're just eating for yourself.
You're eating for the little
one inside. It's very im...
Anne...
Anne, I'm afraid I have to
insist that you drink this milkshake
and then we can
get on with our day.
Okay, drink some milkshake.
Drink it.
Drink it, Miss Sensitive Stomach.
Drink the fucking milkshake.
I'm not hungry!
All right, this behavior
will not be tolerated!
It will not be tolerated.
This is not acceptable behavior.
You...
Frank!
Frank, she's crazy!
She's...
- Psycho bitch.
- Cut it out!
See, what did I tell you?
Frank, do you want me
to get the pump?
Shut your mouth! Shut your mouth.
Get it. Get it.
Get the pump?
Okay.
Get over here.
Got it, I got it, I got it.
She was upsetting me.
This is out of control.
What's your problem?
You don't want to eat?
You know something?
When I was a kid,
my father got me a job...
on a farm that made
pate de foie gras.
In French,
it means paste of fat liver.
And there was this old guy, who'd
go around three or four times a day,
force feeding the ducks.
And my job was to clean up
after the ducks that would explode.
Really.
And they would make
this terrible sound...
just before they would explode.
- Helen?
- Yeah?
How did it go?
They'd quack! Like that.
Like it Louder.
like quaack. Quack!
- Helen?
- Hmm?
Help me out.
Come on,
give me the hose.
Why didn't you just eat?
No...
Helen, give me the pump.
Help me out. Help me out.
- It's okay.
- You don't want to eat?
No, it's okay.
I'll drink it.
- You'll drink it.
- I'll drink it.
- You sorry?
- Yes.
Say you're sorry.
Say you're sorry for me.
I'm sorry.
You're sorry?
Sorry?
Yeah.
You're going to eat
everything from now on?
You're going to be
good from now on?
- Promise?
- Uh-huh.
I'm ready, Frank.
Don't upset my wife.
- Okay, here, baby.
- What?
- Here.
- I'm going to drink.
No, Frank.
No, she has to learn a lesson.
She can't disrespect
her hosts like that.
We have to teach her a lesson.
We have to do it once
so she learns a lesson, Frank.
She said she'd eat it, Helen.
So just relax.
If you don't do it, God dammit,
if you don't do it...
I'm going to do it.
I know how to do it.
All right.
Listen, cut it out.
I'll do it, you little wuss.
Calm down.
I said all right.
Give me the hose.
Give me the goddamn hose.
Can I do the pump part?
Can I do the pump part, Frank?
You don't have to do this.
I'll drink it.
I'll drink it, yes.
Come on, swallow it.
Swallow it, swallow it!
Is it coming up?
Is she drinking it?
Open up, swallow it,
swallow it.
That's enough. That's enough.
That's enough!
Give me a bowl.
Here.
- Okay.
- Eew.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Relax. Okay, let me
show you something.
Let me show you this.
OK, look it. Look it.
Look at that.
Do you see that?
Can you see that?
Did you read that?
Some matches, a car...
a cliff, and this was really easy.
The only hard part
was finding a body...
for the accident, you know?
I love you, Frank.
- Sorry, I didn't mean...
- It's okay. It's okay.
You know,
it's like I can feel her.
- Yeah.
- It's as though, as though...
Look, Jack, if you...
if you need to talk,
or if you need anything,
I'm here, okay?
- Okay, thanks.
- Okay.
Frank, I've gained two pounds.
I can feel the skin
stretching over my tummy.
Look, honey.
Look. Look.
Look, Frank, you can see it.
Look.
Yeah, I can see it.
This morning, I felt
a little bit queasy, too.
- Yeah.
- What else should I be feeling?
Five weeks, five weeks,
five weeks...
Fi...
Heartbeat!
Heartbeat.
Five weeks.
Five weeks: the mother should be
feeling a little bit of a heartbeat...
- That's right.
- And the baby should be about...
- Four mm's.
- Millimeters.
- Four mm's. The baby's...
Four millimeters in length.
Heartbeat.
Frank, I think I can feel it. See?
See if you can feel it, Frank.
Come on, Frank.
All right, all right,
all right, all right.
Yes, feel it. Can you feel it?
Listen to it.
Put your ear down...
here.
Frank, that's... not.
It's up...
I think it's a girl, baby.
I can smell it better from here.
No, no, I don't...
Frank, you're too late!
I'm already pregnant!
- Oh, man, come on.
- You know the rules.
There's absolutely
no sex during pregnancy.
You know the rules.
Come on, don't you think you're
taking it a little too far?
No, I'm not taking it
a little too far.
A baby is a very fragile thing.
It doesn't want things coming and
banging at it while it's trying to grow.
You're gonna set yourself
up for a big disappointment.
I'm not setting myself
up for a disappointment.
We're doing everything right
this time, so nothing can go wrong.
I think I should perform
an amniocentesis.
I think it would be...
No! What?
No, no!
No amniothesis!
Okay, okay.
I take it back.
But I just want you to understand,
things can happen, okay?
- I know.
- You just be very careful.
Okay.
Okay?
It's gonna be fine, okay, baby?
- All right.
- It'll be fine.
- Okay.
- We'll have our baby.
You know, I read somewhere
that you should have sex...
while you're pregnant.
All the medical books...
You did not.
- Mm-hmm.
- You're making that up.
I'm not making that up.
Look, I don't wanna take
any unnecessary chances.
- Let me explain.
- But if you...
need to jerk off, I could...
do a little dance or something
for you, to turn you on.
Why should I have to jerk off
when I can help the baby?
No! Frank!
No, you'll confuse the baby.
No!
Frank...
Frank, are you there?
- Yeah?
- Could you come into my office?
Can it wait?
I'm in the middle of something.
I've got Jack White on the phone.
It's about his wife.
I'm coming in a second, all right?
Shit.
Mr. White, I have
Frank Benton with me now.
Mr. Benton, hi.
It's.. it's Jack White.
Um... what can I do for you, sir?
Well, I... I really need
to find out something,
I mean, anything about
what happened to her,
and I'm wondering if
you can remember anything...
from the day
that we came in,
anything unusual that might help...
Did-did you call the police, sir?
Well, yeah.
I'm just trying to get any
information that might help them.
I think you were having
your third child, right, sir?
Or...
- your second child?
- Uh, no.
You know, sir, it was a really,
it was a-a long time ago.
It's a little bit of a blur
for me now, sir.
I can't really help you out
that much, sir. I'm really sorry.
Okay, thank you.
Thanks very much.
Sorry. I won't take up
any more of your time.
- Okay.
- Thanks.
Are you all right, Frank?
You look a little flushed.
Yeah, I'm fine.
I'm just really hot today, you know?
I'm gonna go back to work.
I'm, I'm...
Good morning, Anne.
It's a lovely day outside.
Wake up.
I have a little surprise for you.
You'll love this.
I've been thinking, Anne,
and I think there's been
entirely too much hostility lately.
There's no reason
you and I can't be friends.
And so, I was thinking...
perhaps the reason why
you're so cranky all the time
is because you look so bad.
I myself find that, when
I'm a little bit depressed,
it's always nice to put on makeup.
It cheers your spirits right up.
Oh, you look pretty.
So, this is fun, isn't it?
Anyhow, I think you should
tell me a little bit about yourself.
Of course, I know little things,
medical things.
I know you had chicken pox when
you were four, didn't we all?
And you came about this close
to getting breast implants
with Dr. Marshall.
I myself don't need implants.
I'm naturally buxom like my mother,
but I can understand where you
would feel inadequate,
and perhaps, you know, want
to augment yourself,
but anyway...
You know, Anne, it'd be nice
if you tried to engage
in a little bit of conversation.
For example, you could say something
like "Good morning, Helen"
when I come in, or
"Lovely day, isn't it?"
or, "Isn't the weather beautiful?"
Little things like that.
It kinda helps lubricate
a relationship.
Look.
Look how cute you are.
Fuck you.
What?
What did you say to me?
You little bitch!
After all I've done for you!
Well, I guess I can't really
expect much from you, can I?
Little Miss Trailer Park Trash.
Now I know you and I disagree
on a lot of things.
In fact, I'm willing to wager
that there's not one single thing
that you think we agree on.
Am I right?
But there is.
There is, Anne.
There's one very, very, very
important thing that we agree on.
You know what it is? We both
want what's best for the child.
It's my child.
Frank and I, we've wanted this
baby for a long time, Anne.
I was pregnant once, but then
Frank ran some tests
and he found out that, it,
that the baby was deformed.
So Frank performed an abortion, and
something really terrible happened...
and now I can't have
babies again. Ever.
It wasn't Frank's fault.
I told him.
I said, "Frank, it's not your fault."
Things can go wrong, you know?
He's been trying
to make it up to me.
It was very hard
on our relationship.
You see,
he did want a baby.
He wanted a baby almost
as bad as I did.
Just not that one.
It had the same deformity that
Frank's little brother Alex had,
his... lobster hands and...
lobster feet.
That won't happen again,
not this time.
I just want what's best
for my baby.
- Are you going to kill me?
- What?
After I have the baby,
are you going to kill me?
Please...
Helen, please.
Oh, Anne. I wish I could tell you
how beautiful it feels.
Something is growing inside of me.
I can almost sense its pulse.
What will it look like,
my little baby?
Will it be a boy or a girl?
Will it look like me?
I'll tell you a secret, Anne.
You remember...
when Frank took out your eggs,
and he fertilized them,
and he put one back?
He threw away yours.
Yes, and then he put back my egg.
My baby.
Isn't it wonderful?
The wonder of life.
Anne, before,
you didn't know me then,
but I was angry.
I was a victim.
Now, not a day goes
by when I don't ask, why me?
Why am I so lucky?
Ah!
Oh, my God!
All right, let's work on
the lower extremities.
Try something where you
lay down on your belly.
Gentle, Anne.
Gentle, okay?
You need to work your lower back.
This is really important.
- Right here.
- I can do it myself.
I know you can do it yourself.
I don't want you to
overwork yourself.
Helen and I aren't going to
take any chances with you.
I mean, if you were to...
have a miscarriage,
she would be very upset.
And that would upset me.
Just relax.
These exercises are for
the baby, okay? It's all for the baby.
- Don't touch me!
- Enough.
What did you say?
Don't upset me, all right?
Just relax.
Try some where you clamp against
my fist here with your thighs.
This is an important exercise
for delivery. Okay?
Clamp down on three.
All right? One, two, three.
What's going on down here?
Hey, baby, just doing
a little exercise here.
- Come up here.
- Well, it's about time.
She was getting a little flabby.
Do some push-ups against the pole.
Right here,
it's a little squishy.
Can you see that, honey?
Here, where it's squishy?
You look so pretty today, baby.
Thank you.
I'm going to town.
Okay, keep working that lower back.
That's it, work this muscle in here.
That's easy.
I could do that.
- Helen?
- What?
- I'm working with her, okay?
- Okay.
- I'm concentrating, all right, baby?
- All right.
That's a nice dress.
Thank you.
I'm going to the store.
Do you want me to get you anything?
No, baby, no, thanks.
We're okay.
All right.
Love you.
I love you.
Don't over do it.
See you in a little while, okay?
I love you.
Go on the bed.
In a loving way,
you turn my night into day...
In a loving way you have chased
the blues away
When I was oh, so alone...
Fuck!
In a loving way, we
will find a love nest, too.
And we will...
Shut up.
You're going to be nice.
You gonna be nice?
You're going to be nice to me.
Frank!
Fuck!
I forgot my purse.
That was quick.
Finished, already?
- She was tired.
- Frank, what's that smell?
What smell?
Ahh, it's right, it's like a
flowery smell mixed with...
I don't know.
You can't smell it?
No, baby, I don't smell anything.
You telling me you
can't smell this smell?
Come over here.
You can smell it over here.
It's really strong.
Over here, where I was standing.
Come on, come here.
Smell this.
All right, here.
It's really strong.
It's like flowers and something else.
Pungent, like stinky.
Listen, baby, listen.
What?
I don't... I don't smell.
Maybe it's her sweat.
- Wait, I smell it here.
- You have to be quiet.
- Here's where I smell it.
- Be quiet.
What?
She's sleeping.
Eew! Right here.
It's really strong. Frank.
Frank?
Did you empty the port-a-potty?
Not yet.
- Nooo?
- Nooo. Not yet.
I don't know you think you can
just mask that
with all kinds of air freshener?
You can't fool me.
I can smell smells.
I have a very strong nose.
You can't just come in here and
make promises like you always do
and say you're going to
empty the port-a-potty
and then mask...
mask it with air freshener smell.
- Listen.
- Wha...
Didn't I say I'd do
it by the end of the day?
Didn't I say by the end of the day?
Yes, you said by
the end of the day.
Is the end of the day here yet?
Has the day ended yet?
- It's almost.
- Well, it's not over yet.
- Now come on, let's go.
- It's almost over.
It's not over yet
and I will do it today.
Now come on, let's go...
The whole house is stinky.
You didn't give
me a kiss hello, nothing.
- It's just not enough.
- She never left the house without it.
If there was more to
go on, maybe...
What more do you need?
She never took the thing off.
Why did I find it in our house?
The chain was found at the crash site.
It broke.
She took it with her.
I mean, there's a thousand different
ways that this could happen.
Something is going on.
I'm asking you find out what it is.
Jack, really. I think we've
done all that we can for now.
Look, I'm going to
ride you until you help me,
so you might as well help me.
The best help that
I can give you right now
is to recommend a
good therapist.
Fuck you!
Don't you fucking patronize me.
What if that wasn't her in the car?
What if she's still alive?
You're going to do nothing?
For your sake, I hope
that she's still alive, okay?
I really do, Jack.
I'm very sorry.
April showers, Easter Bunny,
la la flowers...
Frank?
Frank, I found a very large
Easter egg outside the front door.
A very large Easter egg.
It was outside the front door.
La di la la. Summer's here.
Time to eat watermelon
and drink some beer.
October, the most
fertile month of the year.
October, October's almost
gone now that it's been here.
Frank, want to hear
my October song?
I love my little baby.
Aw, what's that?
You're hungry.
Would you like some milk?
We're out of fresh milk,
but look, I have a bottle.
Some. I don't care.
I don't care. Drink it.
Drink, drink, drink,
drink, drink, drink.
I'll cut you out.
Frank will cut you out
if you're not good.
I can't stand you.
It's so hard being a mother.
Arms out!
Come on, hut, hut. Come on...
Arms out. Keep going, Anne.
Come on, one, hut, hut, hut,
two, three, hut, two, three.
Come on, Anne. Come on.
Arms out, hut, hut, hut.
Come on, hut, hut.
Keep going, Anne. Come on.
Arms out, arms out, hut, hut.
All right, keep going, keep going.
Don't stop, Anne.
Frank! Frank! Frank!
Someone's coming.
Frank! Frank!
Hide Anne.
Get down, get down!
Down, stay down.
Stay down.
Stay close.
Shut up.
Hello?
Hi, Happy Bottoms at your service.
Happy Bottoms?
Diaper service.
I'm Dana, your diaper
technologist engineer.
Well, I'm afraid
there must be some mistake.
You see, I haven't even
had my baby yet.
Well, there was an information
card you filled out at the market.
- I did?
- I'm here to drop off some samples.
Ahhh!
You bit me!
- Shit.
- Excuse me?
Come on in. Hurry it up.
I haven't got all day.
The kitchen's usually the best place
for the Happy Bottoms' diaper pail.
So, when are you due?
Oh...
- Real soon now.
- Is this your first?
Uh, yes, it's our first
darling little treasure.
- Well, congratulations.
- Thank you.
I think you're going to
be real pleased with our service.
Anne, cut it out.
Watch the baby.
Wait!
Wait, what about samples?
Oh, I can leave these here for ya.
Oh, okay.
- This could be it.
- Oh, my God, how exciting.
It's going to be okay.
Everything's okay.
I'm here for you.
Okay, breathe. I'm here for you...
- It hurts.
- It's going to be okay.
- Breathe. Breathe in, out...
- Hot towels.
- Water. Give me water.
- Out, oh...
Oh, God!
Push. Breathe.
Get the fuck away
from my baby, you bitch!
What the fuck is
the matter with you?
You think you can put your hands
all over me just because I'm pregnant?
Wait, wait, wait.
I want those diapers.
So, um, I guess we'll
get the matching ones.
You know, the matching ones?
And the weekly delivery.
Look, look, I'm really
sorry about what happened.
I'm my hormones are raging.
I'm pregnant, you know?
Hey, lady,
I said we'd get the diapers.
Hey, baby.
It's okay.
You, shut up.
Hey, baby.
Everything's okay.
It's okay.
Don't worry. Don't worry.
Shut up!
I have an idea.
Why don't we go to the zoo
or the park, or the museum,
or something?
Just get away.
Are you kidding?
I got, I've, I've...
- Come on.
- I've got meetings till 8:00.
I've presentations to prepare.
Come on.
What, you're
not having fun now?
What have we been doing
for the past few months?
Meeting for lunch.
Let's fuck.
Let's fuck?
Yeah.
Don't you miss loving?
Yeah, yeah, I do, but I...
I can't do this.
You know, Jack,
you just don't get it.
What's going on?
What time is it?
It's late.
How are you feeling?
What does it matter?
Oh, go away.
Go away. Go away.
I've got a surprise for you.
What?
It's called an amniocentesis.
It tells me if the baby is healthy,
and what sex it is.
I'm just going to remove a
small bit of fluid with this needle.
- No, no, no, no, no.
- It doesn't hurt.
Listen to me.
Listen, Anne...
No, it's too late for that, Frank.
It doesn't hurt at all.
You'll just feel a little coldness...
No, no.
- Listen...
- I don't want this test, Frank.
I'm going to do the test.
The father would like to know
the baby has ten fingers and ten toes.
I'm gonna need you to be
very, very still.
You're going to have to force me
because I don't want this test.
- Okay.
- I'm not going to let you do this.
I'm gonna do it,
so don't make it difficult, okay?
I don't wanna hurt the baby.
I just have to do this test,
'cause I have to know.
And then I'll stay here with you...
till you feel better.
I can lay down with you here,
if you want.
Would you like that?
Yes?
I'd like that.
Helen! Helen!
What the hell's going on down there?
You get away from there.
You get away from there,
you stupid bitch.
Get back there.
Honey, honey, what happened?
What did she do to you?
You bitch!
You get away from him!
You stay away from him.
You bastard!
You son of a bitch!
This was my baby!
It was my egg! It was my egg!
It was my egg!
It wasn't your egg.
What?
It wasn't yours.
You bastard! You bastard!
You...
You lied to me!
You fucking bastard!
You bastard!
Bastard!
I just wanted a baby, Frank.
Why couldn't you let me have a baby?
That's all I wanted.
I love you.
Honey...
Keys, keys, keys...
So many keys.
It's this one.
It's gonna be better.
Every day it's gonna be all right.
Every day is gonna be better...
...everything
is gonna be all right.
- Anne?
- Yeah?
I have, I brought some sheets
and I brought you a night-gown.
And here, it's your breakfast.
You sure know when it's time to eat.
Well, I should.
I'm the one who set your schedule.
It was Frank that didn't follow it.
I've never met
anyone like you, Helen.
Well, there's nobody like me.
That's probably why.
I really think you are going
to make some kind of mother.
- Really?
- Really.
You know what sticks out in my mind
the most about you though?
What?
That you want this baby so badly,
more than anyone could ever imagine.
I do.
I really want this baby.
I could... I'm going to love
this baby so much,
I'm just gonna, I'm gonna
take really good care of it.
And this house!
This is a good house for a kid,
'cause there's lots
of little nooks and crannies,
and you can run around,
and I was thinking maybe
to get a dog, name it Gopher.
And we could...
and perhaps get a pony,
but maybe that would
be later on when it was big,
so it didn't fall off
and break its little neck.
I was thinking, I have lots of plans,
lots of, you know,
but first I want to make
sure the baby's happy...
just being a baby in the crib.
Good.
Can I tell you something else?
What?
I think it's gonna be a boy.
A little boy?
- How do you know?
- I think.
Is it like,
how it kicks inside the womb,
and is it really aggressive?
Or...
A mother just knows, right?
You just know.
A little boy!
I'll call it Joey. Or Brandon.
I'll call it,
I don't know.
I have to think about it.
Anne?
I'll be back down at lunchtime.
A boy!
Anne?
Oh, my God!
What happened to you, Anne?
What happened?
Get up.
Oh, my. Come on, Anne.
Get up, all right?
Here, you're gonna be fine.
Everything's gonna be fine.
All right.
You really shouldn't
be so clumsy, you know?
You're not just walking for one.
Ahh! The baby! It hurts!
Right here?
Where? Here?
All right. I'll just,
I'm gonna, uh, I'll get, I'll...
Okay. I'm going to call
for a doctor, all right?
You stay right here.
Don't move.
He's here.
Now, Anne, I'm sure you understand
this is a very tricky situation.
It's very important there
be no talking of any kind.
You understand me?
I know how you hate
when I give you the hypodermic...
but I can't take
any unnecessary risks.
I don't need anymore.
I'm your friend...
Anne, I can't trust you.
I'm sorry.
Yes, you can.
I'm your...
Hi, you must be the doctor.
Come on in.
Thank you very much.
I'm really glad to see you.
Can I take your coat?
- Oh, thank you.
- So what was your name again?
- Gardner.
- Oh, Gardner.
I'm sorry I didn't hear that.
So glad to see you.
It's kind of an emergency.
You seem awfully healthy.
Oh, no.
Nah, it's not for me.
It's for my sister.
She's upstairs.
She's in bed.
She's incapacitated.
- What's her name?
- Susan.
- Susan... wake up.
- She won't wake up, doctor.
She took a painkiller earlier.
She insisted.
She's a very headstrong girl.
- What's she on?
- Demerol.
It shouldn't
put her out like this.
So I don't know maybe that affected
her stomach a little bit,
perhaps you should
check it out.
Pull her blankets back.
I'll listen to her vitals.
Okay.
- Ma'am?
- You know, I was just thinking...
Perhaps it's better you don't
do a whole thorough examination.
You see,
we don't have medical insurance
and we won't be able
to pay you for the bill.
Don't worry, there'll be no charge.
Excuse me...
Aren't you nice?
So... you hear anything?
Did she have any
symptoms before her fall?
No, no symptoms at all.
As a matter of fact, doctor,
between you and me,
I think she might be
faking it a little bit.
You see,
she's kind of a hypochondriac.
I am very concerned
about her stomach.
Oh, no, doctor.
I think it's very important...
that you don't
examine her stomach.
You see, she had a nasty
botched Caesarian a few years ago,
and she's very sensitive
about anybody seeing the scarring.
I know she's unconscious,
but I think it would be...
a violation of her personal
rights if you were...
to peel back her clothing
and look at the most intimate,
disgusting part of her body.
Oh, here she comes.
What?
I can't hear you, Susan.
I don't think she's
really saying anything.
You've got to tell me where.
That's enough, doctor!
I think that...
Excuse me, I'm going to get that.
Excuse me, one second.
Hello?
Yeah, it's...
No, no,
Frank isn't here, he's gone.
A family emergency.
Look, I really can't talk right now.
Yes, goodbye, doctor.
Great news!
That was her doctor!
Her real doctor.
He's on his way over here right now.
He'll be here in ten minutes.
I really, really, really
appreciate your coming out.
It's very, very,
very kind of you.
- What was her doctor's name?
- Benton.
- Benton?
- No, it's Smith.
I'm bad at names.
Listen, I don't mean
to sound inconsiderate, but...
You don't sound inconsiderate.
Believe me.
- Your sister should have X-rays.
- I understand that, doctor.
She might have a concussion.
Yes, I understand you took
some kind of Hippocratic oath
and you feel it's your
duty to take care of my sister,
but I really think you should go now.
Thank you very much.
- But...
- Thank you, thank you. Goodbye.
So, we're back, are we?
Back to something
you're familiar with.
What's the matter, Anne?
Too many drugs for you?
As you know, Anne, we have
many rules in this household,
and no fucking
secret messages is one of them.
You got that?
Does that sink in?
No notes, no messages.
Answer me!
Fuck off!
Bitch!
Mother fucker!
After all I've done for you!
Have you ever heard
of a Caesarian, Anne?
I think I could do that.
What do you think?
Of course, I'm not a skilled physician
like the dearly departed Frank,
but I do have very sharp scissors.
Frank?
Anne!
Hello!
Hello, anybody in there?
Okay, be home. Be home.
I'm not in right now, if you leave
your name and your number
I'll call you back as soon as I can.
Thanks. Bye
Jack, Jack, are you there?
Pick up the phone.
Jack, please, pick up the phone.
It's Anne.
Jack, I need you.
Please pick up the phone.
I need your help.
I need you to come and get me.
Jack... Jack...
Jack, pick up the phone.
Please... pick up the phone.
Please, pick up the phone.
I'm in the country somewhere...
Who is this?
Jack!
Jack, Jack!
This is a sick joke.
Who is this?
It's your wife.
Jack, it's me, please...
Jack, it's Anne.
What?
It's Anne.
- Anne?
- Yes.
It's me.
I need you...
I need you to help me out.
I'm in the middle of
the country somewhere and I don't...
I've been kidnapped.
Oh, my God!
Where are you?
By a road.
I'm in a phone booth...
There's no phone book.
Oh, okay, wait,
I'm at, I'm at 555..
- Oh, Jesus!
- There's tractors.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
There's a farmhouse.
I've been in it.
Okay.
- Okay, it's uh...
- The number, honey, the number.
It's 555-0194.
555-0194.
Please come and get me.
Okay, listen.
You call the cops right now.
Call 911 right now.
They'll be able to get there right away.
Anne!
What's going on?
Anne! Anne!
Anne!
Come to mama!
Anne, where are you?
Anne!
Anne, wait, wait.
Wait!
Anne, wait!
Anne!
Stop!
I said stop!
You're making me mad.
Bitch!
Don't make me mad!
No, fuck that!
You calm down!
She's not dead,
for Christ's sake!
She... listen to me...
God damn you!
Come to mama.
Anne, where are you?
You psycho bitch!
Oh, you bitch!
You bitch!
Wait! Stop!
No, stop, stop.
Please, help.
Help!
No!
What the hell?
Where is she?
You got her?
Well, someone smashed
up the phone booth all right.
- You haven't got her?
- Well...
Someone may have already
given her a lift somewhere...
- Maybe...
- Oh, Jesus Christ!
Maybe just some kids.
All the officers have her description.
What do you want me to do?
Officer Williams,
report to dispatch.
I'm on my way.
Come to mama!
Anne, where are you?
Come, little birdie.
Where are you?
Any improvements yet, Karen?
Well, her heart rate's
picked up a bit, but not much.
Okay, thanks.
What is your story, my friend?
Curious sensitive fella, ain't you?
Oh, come on, doctor.
Get off the bed.
It's highly unprofessional.
Good news, Anne.
We're checking out early.
I'm turning the light on now.
Anne!
I have a surprise for you!
Come on, Anne.
I have a birthing day
surprise for you.
You have a visitor.
Wake up, asshole.
Wake up.
Don't you recognize him?
Look!
It's Jack!
What?
I thought you said
he was good looking.
God, what an annoying voice!
Jack, are you all right?
Jack, can you hear me?
Jack, can you hear her?
You should answer her, Jack.
Communication is very
important in a marriage.
Come on, Jack.
I'm fine, dearie.
Why don't you stop?
I could have killed him.
I was gonna kill him.
But then I had a thought.
I thought,
"maybe it will comfort Anne
to have her husband
around for the big moment."
You know what my motto is:
"Whatever is best for the baby."
Oh, I have something
else I want to show you.
Look here. Look what I did!
Look, look.
Look!
See? I came downstairs
when you were asleep...
and I was gonna cut the baby out.
And I could have too.
Except for, when I started,
I thought I heard
my baby crying out.
"No, mommy, no.
You'll put out my eye."
I almost hurt my baby trying to
get it out of your disgusting body.
But then, all of a sudden,
the contractions started,
and I thought to myself,
"Helen, just wait.
It's not gonna be long now.
You can wait."
You know?
It's just a matter of time.
And I've got plenty of time.
The waiting game, huh, Anne?
Oh-oh.
Blow, Anne. Blow.
Blow. Blow. Blow.
Breathe, Anne. Blow.
Blow. Blow.
Fuck you!
See?
It won't be long
until I separate you from my baby,
and then, after that...
Goodbye, useless tissue matter.
Oh! Oh, no!
Oh, shit!
This could be it.
All right, calm down,
don't get all hysterical.
The baby's not going
to pop out all of a sudden.
All right, all right.
- It's coming out.
- Just breathe.
Push, push.
Oh, Jesus.
How did you do that?
All right, settle down.
You're not helping me here.
Push, push.
Push, you lazy bitch.
God damn you!
You fucking bitch!
You psycho bitch!
You drop it!
You drop...
Anne!
Anne, what are you doing?
What are you doing?
I'm gonna kill myself
and I'm gonna kill the baby too.
No. Anne, no.
Don't do that.
It's a little baby.
Drop it, or I'll kill Jack!
If you want this baby, drop the gun.
I'll kill your yuppie husband.
Drop the fucking gun.
All right, Anne.
Anne, Anne, I'm...
Okay, Anne.
Okay. Okay.
All right.
You got your way.
- Look, look, Anne, look.
- Put it down.
I'm putting it down.
Are you looking?
I'm going to put it down.
Look, Anne, be careful.
I'm putting it down.
Here goes.
Down on the floor.
I'm putting it down.
Look, it's on the floor.
Look, Anne, look.
I'm putting it down.
Look.
All right.
- Down on the floor.
- You bitch!
Bitch. You little bitch.
Die! Die!
You fucking bitch!
I wanna walk.
We're okay.
We're okay, sweetie.
Jack.
Oh, Jack.
Watch Movies, TV Series and Live Sports
Signup Here -> WWW.ADMITME.APP