(SINGING)
(LAUGHS)
(LAUGHS AWKWARDLY)
FRED: You're looking at
the many noble rabbits
who have served as
the Easter Bunny.
I you've ever
gotten a basket of candy
and colored eggs
on Easter morning,
you have them to thank.
Yes, even that guy.
See, every bunny
dreams of holding the title,
but not just anyone can do it.
You have to be majestic.
You have to be dignified.
You have to be, well, a bunny.
Or, at least you did.
Hi. I'm Fred O'Hare,
the first human Easter Bunny.
Sounds insane, you say?
It'll make sense once you know
how it all went down.
(PLAYING DRUMS)
E. B.'S DAD: E. B.?
E. B.?
Where are you?
Hi, Dad!
Woohoo!
Oh! There you are.
Son! I was thinking.
You are gerring so big,
you're practically
a foot tall.
Over a foot,
if you count the ears.
I always
count the ears.
(LAUGHS)
So, how would you Iike
to go to work
with me today?
Would I?
That sounds awesome.
I said the same
thing when my father
first took me to the factory.
I didn't use
the word "awesome," but...
Down, please.
(ELEVATOR BELL DINGS)
Thank you.
Go ahead, Son.
Take a look.
Whoa!
Look at all that candy.
Come on, come on.
See you.
This is so cool!
Oh, careful! E.B., welcome
to the Easter Factory.
This is where we make
all the candy and eggs
rhat I deliver to
the children of the world.
It's pretty impressive,
isn't it?
It's amazing, Dad!
I'm glad you like ir,
because someday
this will all be yours.
Really?
Now, come on, Son.
There's so much ro see.
E.B.: Daddy, what do you
call that thingamajig?
Ah, rhe Marshmallow
Chick Machine.
Loved them since
I was your age.
When your grand-dad,
the Easter Bunny before me,
took me on this
very same tour...
Hello.
Hello, little bunny.
What are you doing?
We don't eat the candy.
We make the candy!
But I thouhht...
E.B.
This is my second-in-command,
Carlos.
It's fine, Carlos.
E.B. was, uh, taste-testing.
Isn't that right, Son?
Yup, I'm taste-testing.
It's great.
Oh, dear me. No, no.
Son, we're going to have
to work on your taste.
Carlos, too much marsh,
not enough mallow.
Exactly, señor,
I was just going
to say that.
Phil! Too much marsh,
not enough mallow!
(POP MUSIC PLAYING)
CARLOS: Phil! Phil!
Phil!
Hi, boss.
No dancing on the job!
It's forbidden.
(MUSIC STOPS)
Yes, sir. I'm very bad.
(EXCLAIMING)
I am so sorry, señor.
I will dea with
this personally.
Yes. Easter is
right around the corner,
Carlos.
There is no room for error.
Sí, señor.
Remember this, E.B.,
we can't make any mistakes.
The entire world
is counting on us.
This seems hard, Dad.
And I don't know
if I can do it.
Oh, come now.
Don't you worry, Son.
Yes, it's
a big responsibility,
but you'II be ready.
You'll have to be.
Why, in a few years
you will pick up
the Egg of Destiny
and receive the magical powers
of the Easter Bunny.
Now, Iet's move on.
E.B.: Bye, Carlos.
Okay, ciao.
See you Iater.
Enjoy your life of privilege,
little bunny.
(WINGS FLUTTERING)
HENRY: So, how are
my kids doing?
I had rehearsals for
the Easter play today.
Oh.
They usually cast
a boy as Peter Cottontail,
but they made
an exception for me
on account of my
singing voice is so strong.
HENRY: (LAUGHS)
That's great, honey.
Sam, how about you?
(CLEARS THROAT)
Well, I'm up for
a big promotion at work.
Really? That's terrific.
Good to hear
that two of my kids
are working so hard.
So, Fred. How did
that job interview go?
I don't know
about that place, Dad.
I just don't know
if it's really
what I'm Iooking for.
HENRY: Really?
Did they pay money?
Then it's exactly
what you've been looking for.
Well, that's just crass.
What are you nodding for?
"Dear Fred,
as your mother I
have always Ioved you,
"and it hurts me
to have to tell you
"in this way,
but there comes a time
"when every young
man musr grow up
and leave the nest."
You all prepared statements?
Fred, we're just doing this
because we love you, Son.
The Sadeki family
down the street went
through the same thing
with their son Jordy.
He just laid on
the couch all day
watching court shows,
but then they had
an intervention,
and now he
works in a pharmacy,
and has an apartment.
I don't really want
to work at a pharmacy, Mom.
Well, you need
to do something.
You need to get a Iife.
You need to get a job
and you need to move out.
Especially that last one.
But I did move out.
And I had a job.
Is ir my fault
the company downsized?
Fred, that was
over a year ago!
You have ro get
back on the horse.
And you have so
much potential.
Thanks, Mom.
Sometimes I
think you adopted me
because Fred was
such a disappointment.
Wow.
Alex, that is
a very hurtful statement.
You're not denying it.
Eat your dinner.
Mom, Dad, I'm trying, okay?
I go on job interviews.
I had one today!
Yes, but it wasn'r
what you were Iooking for.
It's always something.
You didn't like the commure.
The parking lot
was too far away
from the building.
The man in the cubicle
next to you smelled.
He smelled.
Fred,
nothing is ever
good enough for you.
You don't want me
to settle, do you?
Settling is fine.
Dad, when I was a kid,
you said that
when I grew up I was
going to do something great.
Yes. But now I'm telling you
that you should
forget about "great,"
and settle for
getting any job.
We should have nudged you
out of the nest
a Iong time ago.
Baby birds get a nudge.
Giant birds who never Ieave,
they get shoved.
(ROCK SONG PLAYING)
E.B.!
Hello, Dad.
So, what do you think?
Uh, what did l...
It was great! Really kicking.
But, E.B., shouldn't you be
rehearsing your speech?
You're about to be
crowned the Easter Bunny
in front of
3,000 of your peers.
Uh, yeah, about that.
Yes?
Look, Dad, (CLEARS THROAT)
ever since I was
yea big, it's been,
"The Easrer Bunny
wouldn't do that" and
"The Easter Bunny
has to be perfect."
But I'm not perfect.
I know that, Son.
But you'II get there,
eventually.
But I'm...
Lisren.
You want me to be this.
But maybe I'm not this.
Just maybe, maybe I'm this.
A sock? (SNIFFS)
Ugh.
Yeah, that's right.
I might be
a metaphorical sock.
I might not be
a good enough egg,
but I mighr be
the best sock ever.
I might not cut it
delivering Easter baskets,
but I might be
great at something else.
Oh, the drums!
Why, I think that's fine.
I think ir's really
nice that you have a hobby.
Everyone should have a hobby.
It's not a hobby, Dad.
I want to drum in a band.
I want to see the world.
E.B., rhe Easter
Bunny sees the world.
Every country in one night,
making people of
the world happy.
Really, Dad?
The whole world?
What about China?
(WOMAN YELLING IN MANDARIN)
No!
Look, it's candy, woman!
Madam, please.
AII right. So,
we haven't cracked China yet.
But, for all
those that do believe,
you will be there.
No, Dad. I don't want
to be the Easter Bunny.
Now, Iisten to me.
Four thousand years of
tradition doesn't end
jusr because one selfish bunny
doesn't feel like doing it.
Look. Dad...
No, E.B., you look!
You are going to
be the Easter Bunny!
Now you need to
get it together,
get rid of these drums,
and get your
priorities straight!
I'll see you out there!
No, I don't think you will.
Destination.
Where dreams come true.
In-flight snack preference.
Any baggage?
Just emotional.
I'm sorry, Dad.
(WHOOPING)
(GRUNTS)
Ow!
I did it.
E.B.: Hollywood.
Right.
First order of business,
find a place to stay.
Perfect.
Fred, wait, wait, wait! Fred.
Did you know
about this, Sam?
Oh, uh...
You did.
Okay, Iook.
The rules of this
intervention state
that I am not
supposed to help you, okay?
So you can't tell anyone
what I'm abour ro do.
No! I'm not going to
take money from you.
Wasn't going to
give you money.
We can call it a loan.
Fred, Iook,
I got you a job
interview tomorrow
at my friend's company.
I'm a lirrle
slammed tomorrow.
I know you're not.
I'm pretty busy.
No.
Look, it's an
entry-Ievel position.
Entry-level?
At a video game company!
Okay. That's kind of cool.
I know.
All right, look,
if it means that much to you,
I'II swing by.
No, Fred.
You don't '"swing by.'"
Okay?
You shower,
you shave, and you show up.
The three "shs."
Come on, Fred. You've
got to start your Iife.
Think of this
as a reboot.
Right!
It's rime.
Yeah. You know what?
You're right.
In a couple of months,
couple of weeks,
you're gonna see
a whole new Fred.
Yeah. By Easter.
Easter is in two weeks.
By Easter,
I'm going to have a new job,
a new place, a new Iife.
Great!
Okay.
Now if you'll excuse me,
I'm going to go
sleep in my car.
Fred, listen.
My boss is on
vacation for a few weeks
and he asked me to house-sit.
Nobody ever asks
me to house-sit.
I know.
It's so weird.
Anyway, he has dogs,
and you know I'm
scared of dogs,
so take over for me.
Wait.
Your boss Iives in
a big mansion, right?
Yes, in Beverly Hills.
And he Ioves his house
more than he loves his kids.
So you have
to behave. Okay?
Do not touch anything.
Do not break anything.
Do not go upstairs!
Wait, what's upstairs?
Fred.
Okay.
And do nor forget
to feed the dogs.
Got it!
Thank you, Sam.
You're welcome.
I pur the address
on the paper.
Okay.
Bur, Fred?
Yeah?
If you screw up,
I'll kill you.
(AWKWARD LAUGH)
Okay.
HUGH HEFNER: Listen to me.
This is the Playboy Mansion.
It's not a hotel.
Yeah, right.
But it says here
that ever since 1 971,
rhe Playboy
Mansion has been home
ro sexy bunnies
from around the world.
Friend, I can't see you.
Please step forward.
Now, I'm telling you
that I am both a bunny,
and incredibly sexy.
I don't have time for this.
Hello? Hello?
Maybe this is the rags part
of my rags-to-riches story.
(BALLAD PLAYING)
FRED: All right,
Iet's see here.
54 Broadway Terrace.
Whoa!
Look at this!
Hello, Fred's new crib.
Maybe this is
a good thing.
All great artists suffer
before they become famous.
That lady wrote
Harry Potter in a ditch.
Bur it's the hunger,
the loneliness
and exhaustion
that gets you really.
How could this
night get any worse?
I see.
Car accident. Thank you!
(THUD)
Ow!
Why?
Oh, ow!
It's still alive.
I've got to help him out.
This will do.
Don't you worry,
little friend.
I'm going ro end
your suffering.
(GRUNTING)
No!
Who said thar?
E.B.: Well, who do
you think said it?
Your latest victim.
You know whar? We can
Ieave the insurance
companies out of this.
I could just, maybe,
come Iive with you
for a couple of months.
(GASPS)
(SCREAMING)
No, no, no!
Not real. Not real. Not real.
(PANTING)
Excuse me?
(EXCLAIMS)
You left your car back there,
with the Iights on.
I'm just saying!
(DOOR OPENING)
(CLATTERING)
(FOOTSTEPS)
(YELLS)
Say something. Talk again.
I'm E.B. And you are?
I'm Fred.
Well, Fred, I am so hungry.
Have you got anything
in the old snack department?
Okay.
Here you go.
Oh! Oh! That's...
(EXCLAIMS IN DISGUST)
What is this?
What? It's Turkey Jerky.
First,
you hit me with your car,
and then you try and poison me
with a meat stick.
Why do you hate me?
Okay. Is there
something you'd rather eat,
you weird Iittle thing?
Well...
Carrots!
He's a genius.
One carrot. Okay.
Time ro hop away
out of Fred's life
back to the Enchanted Forest.
You're kicking me out?
Yeah. It's a bad time.
Yeah. Did some jerk
just hit you with his car?
That kind of bad time?
No, I'll tell you what.
It's fine.
Oh, me Ieg. Ow.
I mean,
you can't be expected to help
every innocent
creature you wound.
And I'm sorry if I
dented your bumper
with my face and body.
Do you want me
to Iook for some
baby aspirin?
No, no! You save it.
You might run over a baby.
Just pray that
sweet messenger of death
visits quickly.
Is that the icy hand now?
Okay, wait!
On the off-chance
that you're really here
and I'm not completely crazy,
and I did run you
over and you're hurt...
I guess you can stay.
Thanks, mate.
And I could bunk down
anywhere. Seriously.
West wing, master suite,
guest bedroom. I'm not picky.
Right. Okay.
What's this space, then?
This is a place for you
to stay for the night.
I'm not a car.
So why would I
need to stay here?
Look, it's not my house.
I'm not even
allowed to go upstairs,
and I'm human.
Sorry. What are
the newspapers for?
Because I'm nor really
a voracious
reader or anything.
You know, you're an animal.
So, we all know animals...
I understand.
I'll just sleep down here,
among my poo and
pee like a pig.
If you like,
you use it as well.
Sorry.
No, don't reproach yourself
for these medieval conditions.
Yeah, whatever.
I'm going to go to bed
where, hopefully,
I've been all along.
So, good night.
Oh, okay,
I'II just stay here then.
By myself.
In the dark.
With the door closed.
(E.B. SIGHS)
Señor. Señor,
I have news.
Operations are
running at full capacity.
With my supervision,
we are right on
target for Easter.
Fine, fine.
But is there any
report on my son?
Yes, I have the report.
The Sun will be shining,
foggy times are Iifting.
Easrer will be
clear sailing, señor.
Not the sun.
My son, E.B.!
That son.
Yes. I almost forget.
The rabbit hole was used
for an unscheduled trip
earlier this evening, sir!
What? You mean he ran away?
And at the heighr
of our busiest time.
It's almost unforgivable.
But how could he
just take off Iike this?
It's just not Iike him.
PIease, señor.
Don't be too rash.
It's way too
early to disown him.
But I wasn't going ro...
Wait a minute.
Are you hopping?
Am l?. I didn't notice.
It just comes
so naturally.
(PANTING)
Anyway, señor, considering
your obvious
distraction with this,
wouldn't it be wise
to pass the mantle to,
I don't know, somebody else?
Hmm.
Let's see.
It would have to be
someone you trust.
Someone who is
comfortable giving orders.
Phil! Keep doing that,
but do it faster!
Faster. Gotcha.
CARLOS:
And stop dancing!
No dancing. Yes, sir.
Carlos, you're right.
I'm totally right.
Assemble
the Pink Berets at once!
I'm sorry. What?
We need to find E.B.
The Pink Berets?
But they're only to be used
in a situation of
extreme emergency.
This is prerry exrreme,
Carlos. The Pink Berets
will find E.B.
They have to!
You can't ignore me
forever, Señor Bunny.
(POP SONG PLAYING)
(RABBIT EXCLAIMS)
(SNEEZES)
(EXCLAIMS)
(SIGHS)
Freeze!
(BEEPING)
(GRUNTS)
(SNIFFING)
HEFNER: Who's there?.
Is this the same guy?.
Don't make me come down there.
(EXCLAIMS)
MAN ON RADIO: 101 is
blocked due to an overturned
ttactor trailer
at the Burbank entrance.
Weather is
a cool 72 degrees...
(RADIO TURNS OFF)
Rabbit.
Hello?
Talking rabbit?
(CHUCKLES)
Okay. Wow.
Dude, you are stressed.
Hi, Fred O'Hare.
Hey, Fred O'Hare.
Nice to meet you.
I'm Fred O'Hare.
You need me for this job.
You're going to
hire me for this job.
(WHISTLING)
Oh! The dogs. Right.
"Sam, until Daisy and Baby
are accustomed to you,
"please wear the safery suit
in the hall closet
when you feed them."
Safety suit?
Daisy! Baby! Come here.
(CLICKING TONGUE)
Let's go.
I'm on a schedule here.
(GROWLING)
Oh!
(BARKING)
(SCREAMING)
No!
No! Heel! Sit! Sit!
(SIGHS)
That's fine.
Okay, it's all good.
(LOUD ROCK MUSIC PLAYING)
No, no, no!
(GROANING)
Look, Fred!
Can you believe it?
They've got
a drum kit in here.
What do you rhink?.
Never had one formal lesson!
I am the Extreme Rock Master!
I know what
you're thinking.
(MUSIC STOPS)
No, you really don't.
Hey, Fred, what's wrong?
You look a bit put out.
Why are you still here?
You can'r be up here.
You're in the forbidden
part of the house.
Yeah, but so are you.
Pick this up, man.
You've destroyed the place!
I wouldn't say, "destroyed."
I was just
getting comfortable.
Whar about your injury?
Huh?. Your Ieg?.
You're hurt, right?.
Yeah, exactly.
I needed a sofr bed
in which to convalesce.
Oh, I see. So, you climbed
a flight of stairs...
Struggled up each
stair is more Iike it.
Worth it, though.
That Jacuzzi
loosened me right up.
Jacuzzi?
(BUBBLING)
(FRED EXCLAIMS)
E.B.: Oh, yeah. You might
want to rurn it off.
It was creating
a lot of bubbles.
No!
(ROCK MUSIC RESUMES)
My sister is
going to kill me!
Don't worry.
We'll clean it up together,
as soon as I've
beat my high score.
Hey, Fred!
Come on, your turn.
Pick up a guitar, mate.
E.B.: (MUFFLED)
Fred, I think we
got off on the wrong foot.
You said some things,
I flooded some things.
Let's start over again.
Fred?. Why am I in a box?
This seems like
the sort of thing
a serial killer might do.
Is this going
to be a surprise?
All right,
come on. Out.
Oh! Are we
going for a hike?
Better!. We're
releasing you into the wild.
The wild?
(RATTLING)
(GROWLING)
(SHRIEKING)
Oh, no, no, no. I'II just
stay with you, I think.
This place seems to be
dominated by carnivores.
Get out. Let's go.
What are you doing?.
You're going to leave me here?
Yeah, there's lots
of rabbits out here.
You'II feel right at home.
E.B.: Fred, are we
Iocked in
a destructive relationship?
FRED: Get out.
Fred. You're
making a scene!
Get out!
Move along.
Look, Fred.
(ExCLAIMS)
Goodbye!
But I want to stay with you!
Fred, please don't go.
I'm already Iate. So go away.
Come on, man.
Fred, mare.
I'll behave.
I'll clean up my mess.
I'll do the dishes.
Nor your problem.
There are no
dishes in the wild.
No. Fred.
But I'm special.
Well, we're all special.
(EXCLAIMS)
You're not getting it.
I don't mean special as in,
"everybody's special."
I mean, I'm really special.
(CLINKING)
What're you doing?
See?
FRED: Jelly beans?
E.B.: Mmm-hmm.
So what?. So you talk
and you poop candy.
Could you do it in
someone else's life?
No, you're right.
It's not your concern.
And in two weeks,
maybe you can explain
to the children of the world
why rhey didn't get
their Easter baskets.
Easter?
What, Easter?
No way.
Yes, Fred.
I am the Easter Bunny.
(EXHALES)
Hop in.
Yes!. I knew it! I knew it.
I knew you were real.
I knew it!
What are you talking abour?
Of course I'm real.
No.
When I was a kid,
I saw you on Easter morning.
You did?
Yeah.
That was you,
right?
Absolutely. No question.
Okay. Because you do
Iook a Iittle different.
Was it...
I don't know,
have you Iost weight?.
Or maybe it's the clothes.
You're talking
about the old guy.
Yeah. We got rid of him.
He didn't understand children.
Ah.
He didn't get that
children sometimes
just want to drum.
I mean, dream.
Sometimes they
just want to dream.
Children dream.
Yeah. So he had to go,
anyway, this guy.
Right.
Well, it's a good thing
you got rid of him, then.
Exactly.
So... Wait a minute.
Why are you here now?
Jusr doing
a little last minure recon
for Easter deliveries.
Finding ideal egg
hiding Iocations.
There is one. That's perfect!
Compiling a Iist of kids
with chocolate allergies.
That kind of thing.
It's all very technical.
I see.
Okay.
Oh, man. I'm really Iate.
Late for what?.
What are we doing?
I have a job interview.
You're staying here.
But here is boring.
Let me come with you.
I could be a job reference.
Thank you, I appreciate that.
Look, I really need this job,
and I don't think anyone
there is going to be
able to handle you.
I'm not sure I can handle you.
So, just do me a favor?
Wait in the car.
Fred, I don't want
to get your hopes up,
but I think you're
definitely going
to get this job.
Be good.
Yes, sir.
I'll stay here and
guard the vehicle.
RECEPTIONIST:
2UP Games.
Yes, sir. I'll put
you through to Mr. Hill.
Hi, I'm Fred O'Hare.
I'm here for a 1 0:30 with
Mrs. Beck.
You're a half-hour lare.
I know. I called.
That doesn't make
you any earlier.
Uh-huh.
You know, you're the first
impression people get when
they walk in here.
In many ways,
you are the face
of the company.
Fill rhis out.
Yes, ma'am.
(PHONE RINGING)
2UP Games.
Yes, sir. Can I help you?
(E.B. SNORING)
(ALARM BLARING)
(MUTTERING)
What is that alarming noise?
Oh, no!
Pink Berets!
(EXCLAIMS)
(GRUNTING)
RECEPTIONIST:
2UP Games. Please hold.
I'm sorry, sir.
Who did you
want to speak to?
Fred.
What are you doing here?
I told you to wait in the car!
This is serious.
I really need your help!
I need your help!
You can't be here.
You've got to go!
Fred?
Yes.
(EXCLAIMING)
Get me out of here!
Ah!
Mrs. Beck.
Yes.
How are you?.
I'm well. I can't say thar
I'm that impressed with your
punctuality, though.
Yeah, I have
half a dozen excuses.
But I'm just going to go
with a straight apology.
I'm really, really sorry.
Okay. CIean slate, then.
Thank you.
So, Iet's begin, Fred.
I'II show you inside.
(E.B. GRUNTING)
Whoa!
So, recent
employment history.
You haven't
worked in a year?
Yeah, my parents
have moved in with me.
That has sort of
been a full-time jjb.
Mmm-hmm.
It's fine.
It just gets in the way
of writing my novel, is all.
You're writing a novel?
What is that about?.
It's about a crippled soldier
who, in the future,
goes to another planet
and he becomes
one of the indigenous people
who are blue and
live in the forest.
That's not Avatar?.
Not really.
So, why don't
we take a walk
and I can tell
you a Iittle bit
about the company?
Okay.
So, the good news is,
we tend to
promote from within.
But you'd be
starting in the mailroom.
Mailroom.
Is that a problem?.
No, no, I love mail.
I get lots of mail.
E-mail,
snail mail, chain mail.
I am male.
(LAUGHS)
Speaking of mail,
that's Cody. Let me
introduce you to him.
He is being promoted to
junior exec and you would
be replacing him.
Wow. Congratulations.
Question.
I need 30 copies
of something, collated,
stapled, bound
and on my desk
by yesterday.
What do you do?
I would make 30 copies,
and I would do what
you said with them.
(SNIFFS)
I smell potential.
Oh, Mrs. Beck, I was
wanting to talk
to you about my Iunch.
(WHISPERING)
Fred. Fred!
What is wrong with you?
This is
an extreme emergency.
You're ruining this for me.
You really need to go.
You're righr.
I'll create a diversion
and ee'II escape in
the ensuing chaos.
E.B., no! Get back here!
Fred?.
Yeah.
I got a good
feeling abour this place.
Where to next?.
(BLUES MUSIC PLAYING)
Sounding good to me.
But where is Ricky?.
We need to put
a back beat behind that.
A back beat.
I think Ricky
went out for coffee.
(DRUMS PLAYING)
I guess he's back.
How you feeling, Ricky?
Yeah, I'm smashing.
(IN DEEP VOICE)
I mean, I'm fine.
I'm just fine, daddy-o.
(SCATTING)
Well, then let's do it.
(SONG RESUMES)
Okay, so this our sport...
Oh.
This is our sports-game
motion-capture studio.
Mmm-hmm.
In here?.
Yeah.
Ah!
Hockey.
It's golf.
And this is our
sound recording studio
for our music games.
We've done
Extreme Rock Master,
Extreme jazz Master,
and now we're doing
Extreme Blues Master.
Sounds like a cool idea.
Whoa,
you got the Blind Boys of...
(SOFTLY) Quit it!
I'm going to kill you
so bad! Get out!
Okay, Fred,
Iet's try and keep moving...
I'm all of a sudden
not feeling so good.
Oh.
Do you have a restroom?
Yeah.
Where is thar?
(IN OWN VOICE)
That was brilliant!
(IN DEEP VOICE)
I mean, that was tight.
Sounded all right.
But I know my
drummer when I hear him.
So, who are you, boy?
Okay, I admit it.
I'm not a blues man.
My name is E.B.
I'm just some
guy off the street
wirh two sticks of
wood and a dream.
I understand if
you throw me out.
I get it if you don't
want to give me a break.
Hey, slow down, friend.
You know, we have a buddy
who is always on
the lookout for new talent.
And the man is a genius.
He is the godfather
of entertainment.
And he's having
auditions tomorrow.
The Hoff?
You mean he can help me?
If he like you.
Wow. Thanks, Blind Boys.
Good Iuck, Iittle rabbit.
Wait,
how did you know I was...
Mmm!
CIever gents.
E.B.:
So, Fred, how'd it go?
FRED:
Don't say a word.
(GRUNTING)
FRED: Can I get a Iittle
clarification, here?
Is this what
the Easter Bunny does now?
He just goes house to house,
messing up people's Iives?
Well, that
is just hurtful.
Besides, you're
selling yourself short.
They were going to
shove you in the mail room.
Well, excuse me,
but I happen to think
you're better than that.
You don't know me, okay?
We just met.
I can tell.
You give off this aura
of untapped potential.
I do?
Don't pull that
with me, rabbit, okay?
I'm too smart for you.
But, Fred, I'm serious.
You're destined to
do something great.
I just know it.
I've heard rhat one before.
You'll find an awesome job.
Hey. Look, what about this?
Dog walker?
No.
TSA Officer?.
What about this one?
It looks exciting.
Wind in your hair,
hot babe on your arm.
That's a car ad.
You should buy that car, then.
(SIGHING)
(KNOCKING ON DOOR)
Ah! Señor.
How you doing, jefe?.
Am I disturbing?
It's never been
this quiet in here.
Yeah, it's so depressing.
You should clear this out.
Make a new den or a clubhouse.
Like a man-cave!
It'll be fun.
I called his
dreams ridiculous.
What kind of
father does that?.
No, no, señor.
I will not permit you
to beat yourself up over this.
Anybody would be lucky
to have a father such as you.
Thank you, Carlos.
I miss him.
Me, too, señor.
A son is very
difficult to replace.
Difficult, but
not impossible.
Carlos...
What the...
What's that on your head?
What?. My new earmuffs?
It's a cold spring
this year, you know? Brr!
Oh.
Anyway, what am I going to do?
I know,
how can you deliver Easter
with this tremendous burden
on your old, frail shoulders?.
Hey, hey,
hey, easy
with the "old."
No, I'm just saying,
like, compared to me.
Surely you're not thinking
of making the trip yourself?
What choice
do we have?
We can improvise. I mean...
Does it even
have to be a bunny?
Whar?
I suppose,
given these troubled times,
even a humble
chick could do the job.
(LAUGHING)
Really, Carlos.
(LAUGHING AWKWARDLY)
Wow. I mean,
that is funny.
Can you imagine that?.
A chick delivering Easter?
That's ridiculous.
Oh, dear me.
But I appreciare
you trying to
cheer me up, though.
Please. It is my pleasure
to amuse you, señor.
(LAUGHING)
A chick delivering...
Fred, I was wondering if...
Are you doing
anything tomorrow?
Tomorrow I get to
start my new job
at the video game company.
Wait a second.
No, that didn't work out.
I know. I know.
I'm sorry about that.
But do you know whar?
Every cloud has
a silver Iining.
And behold this
silver lining, Fred!
The Hoff?
Yes, please.
I just need a ride.
Mmm.
No.
Come on, Fred.
This iS my one big chance.
I'll do anything.
Even get out of your life.
I take you to
Hoff Knows Talent,
and that's it, we're done.
Bunny's honor.
(SPITS)
Right here, mate.
It's okay.
A verbal agreement is fine.
Now, you realize,
you can't talk.
No. I can.
No, what I mean is,
you shouldn't talk.
What? Like, ever?
Yeah,
"ever" would be wonderful.
But from now on,
especially not in
front of other people.
They might freak out
and want to
dissect your brain.
Dissect? That's
a bit extreme.
There's an easy explanation
as to why I can talk.
It's a simple combination
of cuteness and magic.
Okay. Here we go. One BLT.
And one order of
carrot cake a Ia mode,
topped with, quote,
Whatever candy you have
Iaying around back there.
Unquote.
Uh, excuse me.
Is that a cough drop?
Yeah. It's cherry.
It counts.
It's a peculiar garnish.
Can I get some
chocolate syrup?
Sure, doll.
E.B.:
Thanks, Iove.
It seems my brain is
still intact, Fred.
E.B.: Fred,
I've just had an idea.
When I'm a famous rock srar,
I'm going to buy
a mansion just Iike this
and make you
sleep in the garage
in a topsy-turvy switcheroo.
What do you think?
Oh, man. My sister is here.
You never told me
you had a sister.
There's still so much
we don't know
about each other, Fred.
If she goes upstairs,
I'm dead.
Why?
Why?.
Let me take you
back to this morning
when you flooded
the bathroom and
you trashed the bedroom.
You remember thar?
Fred, leave this to me.
I'll smooth ir out with her.
Ow!
Hey!
Look at me.
One word out of you,
and it's rabbit season.
You got it?
Okay, I'm going to
run interference.
I need you to sneak upstairs
and clean up, quietly!
(DOOR CLOSES)
Sam!
Hi!
Hey, it's not a good
time for me right now.
I was just Ieaving.
But you just got here.
I know, right?
Hey, what are these?
Oh!
There you are.
(CHUCKLES) Mmm!
I'm on this North Beach diet.
It's carrots only.
That is why rhey're
all over the house.
I was going to
clean them up, though.
Okay, Fred,
how did the interview go?
Yes?.
Oh! Thank you for asking.
Amazing! I aced it.
Really?
Yeah.
No way!
Why are you so surprised?
Fred, that's awesome!
PIace could use me, too.
Don't get me wrong,
it was great.
It was good.
It was all right.
I just... I don't know
if it was for me, really.
It just didn't gel.
Something felt a Iittle off
about the whole thing.
I didn't get it.
Oh! What? What happened?
It's kind of hard ro pinpoint
any one specific thing.
Oh, Fred.
I know. I know. I'm sorry.
(WHIRRING)
What is thar?
I wouldn't know
because I'm not
allowed to go up there.
And I haven't
been up there once.
Hmm. Okay.
Sam, no, you're not
allowed up there, either.
Don't go up there!
Sam, I'm begging you!
I can explain.
(GASPS)
Oh, my God!
Look at this.
(EXCLAIMING)
Look how cute this
stuffed bunny is!
Wow! Yeah. Oh.
So cute!
Isn't he?
Yeah, you know whar?
Maybe we shouldn't
be playing with him
because we're not really
supposed to be up here in
the first place. So...
He's just so lifelike.
You think?
It's a little
freaky-Iooking to me.
Oh! Oh, he's so soft!
(MOUTHING)
And cute, and cuddly,
and warm.
Okay!
Why don't we put him back
before things
get uncomfortable?.
No, I'm not uncomfortable.
Well, I'm
uncomfortable because
I'm Iooking after the house
and it's my responsibility.
There we are.
All right.
(E.B. IMITATING WIND-UP TOY)
Oh, my God!
Wow! Look at that.
He's a wind-up toy.
That is so adorable!
Yeah, I think
he might be broken.
Yeah, you're a broken
little guy, aren't you?
Hey... Ow!
(SIGHS)
Fred, I am really
worried about you.
Hmm!
Don't eat that.
You might not like the flavor.
Fred, relax.
Watermelon.
Can we go?
Look, Sam, I don't
want you to worry, okay?.
I'II get something.
Look, Fred,
I just thought it would make
tomorrow night a Iot easier
if you could tell Mom and Dad
that you had a job.
Whoa! What's
tomorrow night?
Alex's play!
The one she's been
talking about for weeks.
Oh, that is easy.
I'm not going.
Oh, yeah, you are.
Fred, come on,
she's your sister.
All right.
Wear something nice.
I'II wear something nice.
7:00.
7::00.
Don't forget, I love you.
I Iove you.
Put gas in your car. 7::00.
Bye.
Nice. Is she
seeing anyone?
No, she's single,
and she's looking
for a rabbit.
(SNARLING)
Wow! There's a lot
of people here, Fred.
Way more than I imagined.
You nervous?
Well, a little.
It's just...
I'm starting to
feel a bit sick, Fred.
I've never actually played
in front of anybody.
Come on. This could be
your big opportunity.
I know it's my big chance,
but what if I blow it?.
Relax. I'II give you
a good intro.
I'll ser you up,
you knock them down.
Yeah?
Yeah.
Really?
Mmm-hmm.
Thank you, Fred.
No problem.
Now, if you could please
remove your claws
from my shoulder.
Sorry about that.
That's my nerves.
Thanks.
(HIP-HOP MUSIC PLAYING)
Thank you.
Next.
(CIRCUS MUSIC PLAYING)
(WHINING)
(ASIAN FOLK MUSIC PLAYING)
Next.
(PLAYING)
Mr. Hasselhoff.
Yes.
May I call you The Hoff?
Fantastic.
Sir, I realize that
you have seen it all.
But this...
This will stretch the limits
of even your vast experience.
What you're about to
see will mystify you.
It will challenge
the very scope...
Cut to the chase, my friend.
Okay. Uh...
I give you E.B.
(SWALLOWS)
(SOFTLY)
Come on, Iet's drum.
(EXHALES)
(POP SONG PLAYING)
Stop! Stop!
Stop, stop.
I don't want to hear anymore.
Come on! Mr. Hoff,
we've been waiting all day.
Give the guy a chance.
I gave him a chance.
I didn'r like it.
I loved it!
Woohoo!
Yes!
Hoff knows talent,
and that rabbit's got talent!
Thank you, David Hasselhoff!
I will not let you down.
This is a golden opporrunity
and one I intend
to realize fully!
Hey, wait.
You're not surprised
that I'm a talking rabbit.
Little man, my best
friend's a talking car.
Can you make it
to a Iive taping
of the show Saturday night?.
I'll send a limo.
Did you hear him?.
Did you hear The Hoff?
I'm on my way, Fred!
It sounds like
The Hoff really dug you.
I mean, he is a good acror,
but I think he was sincere.
Thanks, mate.
And don't think I've
forgotten our deal.
You've done your part.
And now I'm ready to
get out of your life.
Good. Yeah, good.
We've had some
good times, eh?.
Haven't we, Fred?
Yeah, there were a few.
You validared my
whole childhood dream.
And then, what else?.
(GASPS)
Let me think.
Good times.
Well, maybe jusr one
good time. But the
main thing is
I got to meet the guy
on my second grade lunchbox.
Hasselhoff, wow!
E.B.?
Psst! Fred!
What are you doing?
Pink Berers.
Pink what?.
There is nobody here.
Oh yes, there is.
If they see me,
rhey'll take me
back to Easter lsland
and I'll never get
my chance to drum!
Pink Berets? Huh?.
Sounds super fierce.
Don't be fooled by
their adorable name.
They're the Easter
Bunny's Royal Guard!
But you're the Easter Bunny!
Aren't you?
Of course I am, technically.
What do you mean,
"technically"?.
I'll explain Iater.
Just get in the car.
Look, I was supposed
to take over this year,
but I ran away.
What are you, crazy?
Who wouldn'r want to
be the Easter Bunny?
That's, like,
the greatest job ever!
Yeah, you'd think so.
But it's what my
dad wants, not me.
He expects so much.
What's lefr for me to do
but let him down?
Sounds familiar.
Sometimes fathers
just don't get it.
He told me I only
ever think of myself.
Other times,
they hit the nail
right on the head.
Come on, Fred.
I know we said
we'd go our own
separate ways,
but please,
you've got to protect me.
Look, I'm sorry,
but I can't really
leave you places,
I can't really
take you places.
And I've got to go to
my sister's play tonight.
Oh, I Iike plays.
We should go see a play
that my sister's not in
and that my family will
not be attending.
I understand.
Just drop me off
ar the bus station.
I'm sure I'll be fine.
I could be one of
those street drummers,
wirh a bucket!
Hi. How you doing?.
Good.
Who's your kid playing?
An egg.
An egg?
Yeah.
Wow, that's something.
My kid is the Easter Bunny.
The one that
makes it all happen.
All right, Dad,
all the roles are
equally important.
Sure, sure.
SAM:
Fred!
ANNOUNCER ON PA:
Please get to your seats.
The play is about to begin.
Hey, guys. Mom, Dad.
(AUDIENCE APPLAUDING)
(MUSIC PLAYS)
(SINGING OFF-KEY)
Here comes Peter Cottontail
Hopping down tje bunny trail
Hippity hoppity,
Easter's on its way
Bringing every girl and boy
Baskets full of Easter joy
Ugh! What is that
dreadful sound?.
(CONTINU ES SINGING)
Oh, no! They found me!
Run for it!
It's the Pink Berets!
(AUDIENCE GASPING)
Oh! Never mind, everyone.
False alarm.
Please continue with
your awful singing.
(AUDIENCE GASPING)
How did that
rabbit just talk?
Um...
Fred has been
studying ventriloquism.
Yeah! I might
do it professionally.
Woohoo!
(AUDIENCE LAUGHING)
You're being ridiculous.
Stop it! Sit down!
You should be
nicer to your son.
It's just a thought.
Who wants ro hear a song?
We'd Iove to
sing a song for you.
No, we wouldn't.
(ALL CHEERING)
Stop making a fool
of yourself! Sit down!
Absolutely.
(SINGING) I want candy
I want candy
Take it, kids.
I know a girl
who's tough but sweet
She's so fine
she can't be beat
She's got everything I desire
He's really good!
I can see his lips move.
Sets the summer sun on fire
I want candy
I want candy!
E. B. :
Just the proud moms now.
I want candy
Now the grumpy dads.
All I want is your candy
All I want is your...
Chewy
Fun to eat
So darn sweet
Candy
We're a hit!
They love us!
Here.
Are rhose for me?
Mmm-hmm.
Thank you. So sweet.
AIex. Good job tonight!
Wasn't she
a good Easter Bunny?
Jerk!
(GROANING)
Oh! Hey, Dad.
I was just Ieaving.
Fred, seems Iike we made
quite an impression
on you the other night.
Is this your new career?
Upsraging grade-schoolers
with your
ventriloquist puppet?
No, no, I got lots of
other stuff going on.
Yeah.
There it is.
What?.
That look.
The complete and
utterly disappointed Iook.
Well, I'm sorry, Fred,
but can you give me just,
I don't know,
one reason not to
be disappointed?
Well...
Just one.
Yeah.
Fred?
Fred, where'd you go?
Yeah, I'm right here.
I jusr remembered
I have a really great
solid Iead, actually.
You do?
Yeah, a great job.
Tell me about it.
I can't really
tell you about it.
But it's big.
You're going to Iove it.
It's really big!
E.B.: Hey, what's with
rhe "Mr. Serious"
all of a sudden?
Wait, is this where
you tell me you
want to see other rabbits?
Because I'm
open-minded, Fred.
E.B., I have
the most amazing idea.
When I was a kid,
I told everyone
that I saw
the Easter Bunny, right?
No one believed me,
even though
he left me this.
This chocolate bunny,
which I kept.
Oh, dear.
And tonight, it just hit me.
I realized that it was
my destiny to see him.
Just like it was my
destiny to meet you.
It's all been
leading up to this.
Up to what?
You don't want to be
the Easter Bunny, right?
I know who can
take your place.
Who?
Me!
I'm sorry, Fred.
Would you mind repeating
that in my good ear?
I want to be the Easter Bunny.
What was that for?
That is for people
who have gone loony!
A human Easter Bunny?
Come on, Fred!
It doesn't make sense.
A bunny makes no sense.
You deliver eggs.
If you wanna get all logical,
bring logic into this,
you should be
an Easter Chicken.
What? Come on.
People might resist it
at first. But, hey,
change can be a good thing.
You don't want the job anyway.
The pressure is ungodly!
It did a number on me.
Do you know there was
a period of roughly
nine months
where rhe sight
of a colored egg
made me want to vomit?.
And rabbits are
physically unable to vomit.
So it was just hours of...
(RETCHING)
Nothing coming out.
I don't care.
Imagine that, Fred.
Don't care.
If you can be a drummer,
I can be the Easter Bunny.
Fred, you can't just
be the Easter Bunny.
My dad has to give
you special powers.
Eh.
Besides, rhe Easrer
Bunny has got to be fit.
Ow!
And you're a little scrawny.
Finally, the Easter Bunny
has got to have
Iightning-fast reflexes.
Hi-ya!
Knock it off.
I'm serious.
I can do this.
I will be the Bunny.
The stubborn old bunny
refuses to crown anyone else.
This can only mean
one thing, my friends.
We are going to
have to take matters
into our own hands.
(ALL CHIRPING)
Um, um, um.
Carlos?. Carlos?.
Yes, Phil?
(STAMMERING)
We don't have hands, per se.
No, it's a figure
of speech, Phil.
Right. Got it.
Too long have we labored
under the yoke of
the bunnies' tyranny.
Well, no more!
It's time for
the Easter Chick to rise!
(ALL CHEERING)
Um, um...
Yes, Phil?.
Just thinking out loud.
But wouldn'r ir be
easier just to wait for E.B.?
I mean, he can fix this.
Phil, if you love
E.B. so much,
why don't you marry him?
E.B. is gone, okay?
Oh.
There is a new boss.
Really? Who is ir?
Is it me?.
(HONKING)
Are you being serious?.
Yes. Hi.
Just rehearsing
for the big
Easter sing-a-Iong.
Okay, everybody,
this time sing
a lot more better.
And one, and two.
And three and four.
It's me.
Me, you idiot.
I'm taking over.
Oh. I see.
But first,
I must get in shape.
I will be the Bunny.
You know,
I've been thinking, Fred.
Oh!
Hey, E.B., what's up?
Fred, listen.
You helped me
become a drummer.
And how do I repay you?
I jellybean all over
your dream. Well, no. No.
I've changed me mind.
I've seen the light.
We're going to do this.
And nice job on the eggs.
I told you I was serious.
Seventy-two.
Conditioning is a must, Fred.
Seventy-three.
This is fun.
Just a couple of dudes
hanging out, getting buff.
I could do this
all day!
Me, too, Fred.
I feel great.
(GRUNTING)
Phil, how am I doing?
Be honest.
E.B.: Next up,
speed and agility, Fred.
I want you ro run so fast
that you"re just a handsome
blur with great hair.
Ready? Go!
(EXCLAIMS)
Fred, that was awesome!
For a couple of seconds,
you touched greatness.
I can feel rhe burn!
But it's good.
It's a good burn.
Phil, too fast!
Too fast, Phil!
(SCREAMING)
Sorry, sir.
Come on, Fred!
Keep hopping!
Woohoo!
That's the spirit!
The student is
becoming the master.
The Padawan is
becoming the Jedi!
The human being
is becoming
the Easter Bunny.
I can feel myself
getting stronger.
Phil? How do I
look from back there?
My buttocks,
they are pretty firm, yeah?
It's a wonderful
butt, Carlos.
Sí, sí, I know.
That's very good,
in a crude, primitive,
offensive-to-me-personally
kind of way.
(BLOWS WHISTLE)
What do you think?
Uh...
CARLOS: It's a Iittle too
hot for the kids, no?.
(EXCLAIMS)
Very impressive!
But I can bet you
can go even faster.
Way to go!
Stay calm, Fred.
Dogs can smell fear.
And you have nothing
to fear but fear itself,
and this dog I'm riding on.
Wow!
Nice work, Fred.
(YAWNS)
(SNORING)
(GLASS SHATTERING)
(GASPS)
Oh, no. Not today.
(SNEEZES)
(GROWLING)
(DOGS WHIMPER)
(EXCLAIMS)
(MUFFLED DANCE MUSIC)
(MUSIC GETS LOUDER)
Ah!
(GASPS)
What abour Fred?
He'II be all right.
(WHISTLES)
(GASPS)
(GASPING)
Whoa.
Hey, I know you guys.
You're the Pink Berets,
right?. Ha!
E.B. said you guys
were so scary,
but you're really...
You're really adorable.
Oh.
(GROANING)
Easrer Island.
Oh.
They brought me here
to Iead them in all things
Easter, of course!
Hello, my fellow Easter-teers.
I am truly, truly humbled
by your choice in me.
And as I stand
before you, I...
(CHIRPING)
Oh.
Is rhis part of
the coronation ritual?
Phuh!
Murderer!
Picking up a little
tension in the room.
Carlos!
What's going on?
Who is this person
and what's he doing here?
Wow, you're him.
The big guy.
I'm Fred O'Hare.
I met you...
Well, I didn't meet you.
I saw you when I was a kid.
You look great.
Señor Bunny,
brace yourself.
This heartless human,
he has killed your son!
Whar? E.B.?
Did you say "kill"?
No, I didn't kill E.B.
Oh! Liar!
This can't be so.
Where are the Pink Berets?.
(GASPS) No!
Wait a minute.
That's not...
Silence, human!
Can't you see
you have broken
his poor old heart?.
Are you kidding me?
OId friend,
I share your sorrow.
E.B. was like
your son to me.
I'm trying to
keep it together.
But don't you worry,
I will take care of Easter.
Whoa, whoa, whoa! Does
anyone care that that's
a Butterball turkey?.
No, no, that is E.B.
He has the same
shirt and everything.
My deepest condolences.
Attention, all bunnies.
There will be
a service for E.B.
in the egg painting room.
Carrots and coffee to follow.
Carlos. What are you up to?
It's called
a coup d'état.
Which is French
for coup d'état!
(LAUGHING OMINOUSLY)
But, Carlos.
You've been my most trusted
number two for years.
Guess what?. I am sick
of doing number two.
It is our time
for number one!
Yeah?. We the bosses now.
All hail Carlos!
We the bosses!
Woohoo!
E.B.'S DAD:
Pink Berets!
(GRUNTING)
(CHOCOLATE HARDENS)
Seize him!
Woohoo!
Hey! Don't do that.
He's a beloved holiday icon!
No!
(E.B.'S DAD SCREAMING)
You can do rhis.
You are rhe world's
best rabbit drummer.
You are a superstar.
You are a jerk
for abandoning Fred.
Hey, I don't need
that kind of voice
in my head!
Yeah, well, you
should have thought of that
before you abandoned Fred.
Look, you better tell me
something positive about me.
I can'r.
You abandoned Fred.
(KNOCKING ON DOOR)
Oh! Hello,
who is this
gorgeous devil?.
Is Eb in here, please?
"Eb"?
It's "E.B." That's me.
Oh, all right, well, E.B.,
you're wanted on
stage in two minutes.
(AUDIENCE CHEERING)
Welcome to Hoff Knows Talent.
You guss look great.
There are all kinds of
exciting acts tonight.
HASSELHOFF:
There he is.
How's my little guy?
Acrually, David Hasselhoff,
I've got a problem.
Hmm.
Is it the jitters?
Believe me,
even I used to get them.
Now, I find a good way...
No, ir's not
the jitters, David.
I'm starting to realize
I might be
a really selfish rabbit.
Look, I love drumming.
But when my
friend needed me most,
I lefr him in a house
full of highly
trained ninja bunnies.
What am I going to do?
Hmm.
A dilemma as old
as time itself.
I know rhat if
I Ieft right now,
I'd be giving up fame.
And untold riches.
And all the bunnies
you could ever want.
Yes, and all the...
You're not really
helping much, David.
Like, at all!
And Fred could be
in real trouble.
Go to him.
ANNOUNCER:
Give it up for
Mt. David Hasselhoff!
It's The Hoff!
Fred?
Anybody home?
Uh-oh.
CARLOS: The Easter moon
is on the rise.
At midnight,
her radiant beams
will fill up the Egg
of Destiny with magic.
Then, at Iast, Señor Bunny,
I will be Easter's new king!
Carlos, I'm
warning you!
The Egg of Destiny
is too dangerous in
the hands of a chick.
Its power can only
be wielded by a bunny.
Oh, yes?.
Well, Iool at me wielding.
I'm wielding!
Ooh-ooh. I'm wielding
it again. Okay?
Oh, Carlos, can I wield
the Egg of Destiny?. PIease?
No.
Can I at least touch it?
Ow!
There, you touched it.
That was harsh.
But, Carlos,
rhink of the children.
Yes, but I am! The childrens.
They don't want
candy and chocolate.
From now on,
their baskets will be filled
with clumps of bird seed,
dried crickets,
and the world's finest worms!
Mmm! Mmm! Mmm!
ALL: Mmm!
Have you
completely Iost your mind?
Silence! You see,
this is why he must go.
It's this lousy attitude
of his. Well, no more!
The more sensitive
chicks in the room
may want to avert their eyes.
What about
a compromise, okay?
The bunny gers Easter
one year and the chick
gets it the next.
Enough of the chitty-chatty.
Bye-bye, Easter Bunny.
Hello! Hey, everyone.
I'm back. Yep,
ir was all a big mistake,
but I'm alive.
Hey, Larry, Kyle,
what are you doing in there?
E.B.'S DAD:
E.B.! You're alive!
E.B.!
Dad? Fred? What's going on?
Gummy cannons! In position.
Fire at will!
(E.B. SCREAMING)
That hurt!
Put him on the belt, boys.
Dice him, slice him,
and pulverize him!
(LAUGHING OMINOUSLY)
That is a bit excessive.
Oh, no! E.B.!
Son!
The reign of
the bunny is over!
Oh!
Somebody help!
Help us!
What are you doing?
Don't worry, Dad, Fred.
I'II be right there.
To the Egg SIeigh!
And step on it!
(SNIFFING)
Are these ropes made
of black Iiquorice?
Yes, yes, rhey are.
Horrible stuff!
We can eat through them.
(GROANS IN DISGUST)
I suppose you can.
You see, my friends?
It is just Iike
I told you, no?.
Oh, tonight is going to
be a very big night!
(EXCLAIMING)
I'm flying!
Wirhout even
flapping my tiny wings.
Everything is
coming up Carlos!
(LAUGHING)
Got it!
Good man, Fred.
Hop on.
All right. Let's go!
I'm starting to get a sense
of impending doom now.
Ow! (GASPS)
(EXCLAIMS)
No!
(EXCLAIMING)
(EXHALES)
(EXCLAIMS)
I made it!
All right. Here we go!
Come on, Fred!
FRED: Whoa!
Look, Fred!
There he is. It's E.B.!
E.B.!
The Egg SIeigh!
You've got to stop Carlos!
Don't worry, Dad!
I'm on it!
(LAUGHING)
The power is
surging through my veins!
(LAUGHS)
It's good to be the king.
(LAUGHING) Eh?
(GRUMBLING)
What is happening to me?
(EXCLAIMS)
Uh-oh.
(GRUNTING)
Whoa!
Come on out, Carlos.
It ends here!
You think you can
just take over Easter?
Well, guess what?
(LAUGHING OMINOUSLY)
I actually think
you're on to something.
You're a bright man,
you're an innovator.
I like it.
Give it a whirl.
(YELLING)
(PANTING) One second. Hey!
You finish?
Um... Not quite.
(EXCLAIMING)
Take rhat!
(LAUGHS OMINOUSLY)
E.B.: Get off!
Whoa!
Incoming!
Why?
Bunny slam!
Ow!
You father was a fool
to think you would ever
amount to anything.
(LAUGHING)
(SINGING) Here comes
Carlos Yellowtail
Hopping down tje chicky trail
Easter is coming your way
Okay, Phil,
initiate take-off procedures.
PHIL: Aye-aye, Captain!
Chicks, fall in!
Attention!
PHIL: Here we go.
Right flaps!
Left flaps!
Okay, we're good to go!
(DRUMMING)
Let's go, Phil.
Easter is waiting.
Righty-o.
Uh-oh.
Oh, boy.
Phil, let's get
this bird in the air!
Yeah!
CARLOS: Phil!
Knock off the dancing!
Yes, sir. Sorry.
Lifting off!
No way! The show is not over.
CARLOS: Phil!
What are you doing?
Fly us straight!
(DRUMMING CONTINUES)
No, no, Phil!
Knock it off!
Keep her level!
No, Phil.
Phil! Phil!
Phil! Please, Phil!
Phil!
Phil, I'm feeling a little...
Will you please stop dancing?
CARLOS: Phil!
Woohoo!
Yeah, that's right!
(GRUNTING) This is not over!
Ah-ha!
Thank you very much.
Dad!
E.B.!
I was so worried, Son.
I'm so sorry for
all the things I said.
Me, too, Dad.
And your friend, here.
He saved my life.
He was magnificent!
Well, l...
I kind of was.
Hey, thanks, Fred.
Well, Easter's in a few hours.
I have to get going.
Whar?
Dad, I'm ready.
But, E.B.,
what about your dream?
I'm still going to
be a drummer, Dad.
But I can be
the Easter Bunny, too.
There's just one thing.
(WHISPERING)
All right, then.
Fredrick O'Hare.
Yes, sir.
Please step forward.
Down on one knee.
Left or right,
doesn't matter.
And now, place your forefinger
on the Egg of Destiny.
Oh...
E.B., you as well.
By the power vested in me,
I pronounce E.B.
and Fred O'Hare
co-Easter Bunnies.
Hear, hear!
(ALL CHEERING)
Wow!
(CHEERING)
Now go forth and deliver!
Woohoo!
(FRED WHOOPING)
Wonderful brunch, Bonnie.
Thank you, dear.
It is delicious.
Torally agree.
This is amazing, Mom.
You should open a restaurant.
I'm serious.
That is a very nice
thing to say, Fred.
And can I say that
I love your costume?
I think it is so cheerful.
Thanks, Mom.
But it's a uniform.
(SIGHS)
I'm so tired.
Yeah, you were up very late
delivering pizzas.
Easter baskers.
Every time you say
'"Easter baskets,"
I hear "pizza."
It just helps me cope.
Guys,
can we not do this today?
(DOORBELL RINGS)
Oh, they're here.
This is exciting.
That is my
co-Easter Bunny.
Hey, why don'r you
guys come see me off?
It'll be fun.
Well, that's weird.
Who do you think it is?
I don't know.
Wow.
HENRY: Fred.
Fred, wait.
This is
amazing!
I know, right?
It's pretty cool, huh?
(SIGHS) I'm sorry I gave
you such a hard time.
Aw, Dad, come on.
You don't have to...
I'm proud of you.
Thanks, Dad.
Easter Bunny.
Wow!
The one who
makes it all happen.
Say the words, Fred.
Bring it home.
Happy Easter ro all!
And to all,
a good mid-to-Iate morning.
FRED: On Cheepers! On Peepers!
On Biscuit and Buzzy!
On Chucky! On CIucky!
On Feathers and Carlos.
E.B.: Yeah, come on, Carlos.
Put your back into it.
I've been flapping all night,
so just cut me
some slacks, okay?
One Iittle coup
and suddenly I'm
everybody's chump.
(BOTH SPEAKING MANDARIN)
Fred, whar did she say?
Was that about me?.
(SPEAKING MANDARIN)
You speak Chinese?
Just when I think I
can't Iove you any more...