Watch Movies, TV Series and Live Sports
Signup Here -> WWW.ADMITME.APP
I C E   A G E   3
DAWN OF THE DINOSAURS
It's happening!
Wait up, guys!
The baby is coming! The baby
is coming! I'm having a baby.
- Code blue, code blue.
- Or pink, if it's a girl
Coming up baby! Coming up baby!
I'm coming, Ellie!
We got it.
- Ellie, Ellie! Where are you? Where am I?
- Manny!
I told you! It was just a kick.
Oh... right! Right... Oh, wow!
Oh, you really gave daddy a scare!
Daddy got silly.
Daddy fall down cliff and go
boom, boom, boom. Silly daddy!
Sorry, folks. False alarm.
It was just a kick.
- Do you know who I want to kick?
- That's the third false alarm this week.
Allright show's over...
break it up, break it up!
Oh, I see someone else
who has a bun in the oven?
I'm not pregnant!
Too bad.
You'd make a wonderful mother.
Manny, I know you're excited.
I am too.
But you're getting a
little carried away.
Okay, okay...
Boy, you're starting
to sound like Diego.
Wait a second... Where is Diego?
My hooves are burning, baby!
They are burning!
Oh, look at this! I got to tiptoe!
I got to tiptoe! Eat my dust, dingo!
- Huh, can I look now?
- Easy, don't freak out the baby.
The baby is fine. It's the freaked
out daddy I'm worried about.
Ah, uh, uh! No peeking.
- Voila! Playground for junior...
- Oh, wow!
It's amazing.
- Oh, Manny...
- I made it myself. Our family.
Hey why aren't I up there?
- You can be on ours.
- You'd fit right in.
Of course, it's still work in progress.
Few rough edges, here and there.
I don't believe it!
You're trying to baby proof nature.
Baby proof nature?
Get outta here.
That's ridiculous.
Manny, this is the world our baby's
gonna grow up in. You can't change that.
Of course I can, I'm the
biggest thing on earth.
Okay big daddy, I can't wait to see,
how you handle the teen years.
Come on, Sid. I don't want you
touching anything. This place is for kids.
Are you a kid?
Don't answer that.
Diego, there you are.
You missed the big surprise.
- I'll check it out later.
- Okay. See ya!
You know, I think there's
something bothering, Diego.
No, I'm sure everything's fine.
You should talk to him.
Guys don't talk to guys,
about guy problems.
- We just punch each other on the shoulders.
- That's stupid!
To a girl, but for a guy, that's
like six months of therapy.
Okay, Okay I'm going.
- Hey!
- Oww!
- Why'd you do that?
- I don't know.
So, listen! Ellie thinks theres
something bothering you...
Actually, I've been thinking, that soon,
it might be time for me to head out.
Okay. So, I'll just tell her that
you're fine. It was nothing.
Look, who are we kidding, Manny?
I'm losing my edge.
I'm not really built for
chaperoning playdates.
What do you talking about?
Having a family, that's huge.
And I'm happy for you, but...
- It's your adventure, not mine.
- So, you don't want to be around my kid?
No, no, no... That's...
You're taking this the wrong way.
No, go! Go find some adventure,
Mr. adventure guy!
Don't let my boring domestic life
hit you on the bottom, on your way out.
Isn't Ellie supposed to be the one
with the hormonal imbalance?
Manny, wait! No one has to leave.
- So?
- That's why guys don't talk to guys.
- Why? What happened?
- Diego's leaving.
Whoa, whoa! This should be the best
time of our lives. We're having a baby.
- No, Sid. They're havin' a baby
- Yeah, but we're a herd. We're a family
Look things have changed.
Manny has other priority's now.
Face it, Sid. We had a great run,
but... now it's time to move on.
- So, it's just the two of us.
- No, Sid. It's not the two of us.
Crash and Eddie are coming with us?
Just Crash?
Just Eddie?
Goodbye, Sid!
Okay, calm down. Calm down.
I'm good at making friends.
I'll make my own herd.
That's what I'll do!
Hey! "Me amigo's. Que pasa?"
Well, at least you still got your looks.
Oh, great!
Anybody here?
Hello?
Oh, poor guys! I know what
it's like to feel abandoned.
Don't worry,
you're not alone anymore.
There you go.
Stay here! You take care
of your brother now.
Momma's coming right back.
Momma's coming, baby!
I got you.
What did I just tell you kids?
Oh, thank you,
thank you, thank you!
Bad eggs, rotten eggs!
A heart attack you almost gave me.
Oh, I'm sorry, darling!
It's just that I love you so much.
Hello!
I'd like to present, Eggbert,
Shelly and Yoko.
Sid, whatever you're doing.
It's a bad idea!
Shh! My kids will hear you.
They're not your kids, Sid.
Take them back.
- You're not meant to be a parent.
- Why not?
First sign: stealing
someone else's eggs.
Second sign: one of them
almost became an omelet.
Sid, someone must be
worried sick looking for them.
No, they were underground, in ice.
If it wasn't for me they'd be...
Egg sickles.
Sid, I know what you're going through.
You're gonna have a family too someday.
You gonna meet a nice girl, with... with low
standards, no real options, or sense of smell...
- What Manny means to say is...
- No, I get it. I'll take them back.
You have your family and I'm
better off alone. By myself.
A fortress of solitude.
In the ice, for ever!
Alone, lonely loner..
- That's a lot of aloners.
- Precisely!
- Sid, wait.
- No, no, it's ok.
He'll bounce back, it's one of
the advantages of being Sid.
Why should I take you back.
I love kids.
I'm responsible, loving, nurturing.
What do you think?
I knew you would agree.
Oh, oh, don't cry!
I'll find a dry place.
Let me just dry you off.
I don't know, being
a parents, a lot of work.
Maybe I'm not ready.
Mamma, mama, mama!
I'm a mommy.
Where's mommy?
Here I am!
There you go, nice clean faces.
I got it! I got it!
Stop it, no.
Hey, no biting!
I'm sorry, no, it's okay, it's okay.
Don't cry! Why you still crying?
Are you hungry? Maybe you're hungry.
I know just the thing.
...this is animal
I am your baby and this is my milk
Ahhhh!
I thought you were a female!
I'm sorry, but you can't go in.
Manny says, It's just for kids.
Wait a minute...
You are kids!
Just don't break anything!
- The Sloth says the playground's open!
- No, wait. Not for everyone!
No, no. Don't touch that!
- What are they?
- Who cares? Their fun!
Mommy, his not sharing.
- Aren't you gonna do something.
- Why my kid had it first.
- Did not!
- Did to!
- What is the matter with you?
- I'm a single mother with 3 kids.
I could use a little compassion.
- No don't!
- No, don't! Stop!
- Ronald!
- Whoa! That's insane.
Stop! Stop! Stop!
- Hold on, little Johnny!
- I'm trying!
You know, experts say that you should
let the kids eat whatever they want.
- Do you think my ankles look fat?
- Ankles. What ankles?
Ronald, where did you come from?
Oh, no!
Okay, come on! Spit him out!
If you don't spit out little Johnny,
we're leaving the playground
this instantly... One...
Two... Don't make me say "three".
- There we are! A picture of health.
- That's not little Johnny.
- Well, better than nothing.
- Madison!
- Come on, barf him up!
- Sid!
- Hello, Manny!
- Little Johnny!
Oh, wait... No! No!
Oh, I'm really sorry.
This place is totalled.
- And we didn't reck it.
- We're losing our touch bro!
The important thing is that no
one got hurt. Except for that guy.
And, and those three... and her.
I told you to take them back, and
you kept them! Now look what they've done.
Okay granted, we do have
some discipline issues.
Eating kids is not
a discipline issue.
- But he spit them out!
- Well, that's super! Lets give him a gold star!
They don't belong here, Sid.
Whatever they are, wherever
you found them, take them back.
Manny, I'm not getting rid of my kids!
Earthquake!
It's Okay, It's okay, mamma's here!
Do earthquakes, shriek?
- I thought those guys were extinct.
- Well then, that is one angry fossil. Sid!
Come on, inside, inside, inside.
Nobody move a muscle!
No, no, no, don't cry.
We are poor little lambs
who have lost our way.
Baah, baaah!
Ahhhh!
- Sid! Give them to her. She's their mother.
- How do I know she's their mother?
What do you want, a birth
certificate? She's a Dinosaur!
Well I've put in the, blood,
sweat and tears to raise them.
- For a day! Give them back, you lunatic!
- Look, these are my kids!
And you're gonna have to go
through me to get them!
- Sid!
- Help!
- Run!
- Don't you have anything better to do?
- Help!
- Sid?
- Sid must be down there.
- Well, his dead! Real shame.
- He will be missed.
- Oh, no, no, no! Not so fast!
Okay. Ellie, this is where I draw the line.
You, Crash and Eddie back to the village.
Yeah that's gonna happen.
Ellie! You saw that thing?
This is gonna be dangerous.
Talk to the trunk.
Oh, great! After we save Sid,
I'm gonna kill him.
- Ladies first!
- Age before beauty!
- No pain, no gain!
- What pain?
- Sid?
Oh, no, no, no! Not good. Not good.
Ellie! Ellie! Wait up!
Okay look, if you feel anything,
even if it's nothing...
...you gotta tell me.
And we're outta here.
We need a code word.
Yeah, something that says, "the baby's coming. "
Hmm. How about "Aaah! The
baby's coming!" How's that?
Nah, too long. We need something
short and punchy, like, uh... "peaches"!
Peaches?
I love peaches, they're
sweet and round and fuzzy.
- Just like you.
- You think I'm round?
Uh... Round is good.
Round is foxy!
Stay close.
- Are you guys havin' the same dream I am?
- We've been living above an entire world.
And we didn't even know it.
Run for it! Hurry.
- Diego, what are you doing here?
- Sight seeing. Looking for Sid, same as you!
Well aren't you noble.
This is not the time guys.
We need all the help we can get!
Never mind!
Here, boy. Here, come on!
Are you nuts! We're
not getting on that thing!
It's either this
dinosaur, or that one!
Pregnant lady, wants a lift.
Yabba, dabba, Do!
Don't ever, yabba, dabba, do that again!
- I feel so... puny.
- How do you think I feel?
Ouch!
Take cover!
Dude, you're awesome!
You're like the brother I never had! Me too.
Can we keep him?
- Buck.
- What?
The name's Buck.
Short for Buckminster.
Long for "Buh!".
A little dull.
- What are you doing here?
- Our friend was taken by a dinosaur.
Well, his dead. Welcome to my world.
Now, uh, go home.
- Off you pop!
- Not without, Sid.
Ellie wait, maybe the
deranged hermit has a point.
Manny! We came this
far, we're gonna find him.
I got tracks.
Let's go.
If you go in there, you'll find
your friend... in the AFTER-LIFE!
How do you know, oh, great
and wisely, weasely one?
Mummy dinosaur carrying three babies,
and... some floppy green thing?
Yeah, we're friends with
the floppy green thing.
You got all that from the tracks?
No, not really. I saw 'em come through
here earlier. She's headed for Lava Falls.
That's where they care, for the newborns.
To get there! You got to go
through the jungle of misery.
Across the chasm of death.
- To the plates of wow.
- Wow!
Okay! Good luck with the slow decadence
to madness, we're gonna go now.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa!
What you... You think this is
some sort of tropical getaway?
You can't protect your mate, mate!
What are you gonna do with
those... those flimsy tusks?
When you run into the Beast?
I call him "Rudy".
Oh good. Good. I was worried it was
something intimidating, like Sheldon or Tim.
Wait! You mean there's something
bigger than Mommy Dinosaur?
Aye!
- Aye?
- Aye! Aye!
- He's the one that gave me this.
- Whoa! He gave you that patch?
- For free? That's so cool.
- Yeah, maybe he'll give us one too!
Welcome to my world!
- Abandon all hope, he who enters there!
- Alright we get it.
Doom and despair.
Yadda, yadda, yadda!
Sounds like a jungle of misery to me.
- Hold on.
- Why? What's wrong? Peaches?
- No, it's just I got a funny feeling.
- You're hungry, low blood sugar!
- There's some fruit.
- No, Manny!
I wouldn't do that, if I were you.
This isn't exactly your playground.
Like I'm going to be afraid
of a pretty flower.
- Bet you didn't see that coming?
- Manny?
For the record, I blame you for this.
Stop eating our friends, plant!
- That's it, I'm tearing it up, from the roots.
- Do that and it'll clamp-shut forever.
Alright, preggers.
Don't get your trunk in a knot.
I'll have them out of
there before they're digested.
Digested?
They'll be nothing
but bones in 3 minutes.
- Well maybe 5 for the fat one.
- I'm not fat!
I feel tingly.
Don't say that, when you're
pressed up against me.
- Not that kind of tingly.
- I can feel it too.
- Help, someone help us!
- Hurry!
It's time to get... Buck wild.
Who's fat now?
No!
- Tourists.
- Puked on by a plant. Awesome!
- Say something.
- Thanks for saving us.
Will you help us find
the floppy green thing?
- That's not necessary.
- Yes, it is.
Alright, I'll help ya. But I got rules.
Rule number one:
Always listen to Buck.
Rule number two:
Stay in the middle of the trail.
Rule number three:
He who has gas, travels
at the back of the pack.
- Come on then! Chop, chop!
- We should all have our heads examined.
That's rule number four.
Now, let's go find your friend.
Oh, it's okay, it's okay.
Don't worry, we're gonna be fine.
Please swing a little more to...
See, she's putting us down...
No! I'm too young to be eaten.
Wow! Nice mucus. And I
don't care for, everyone.
Listen these things get complicated.
Maybe we can work something out.
I can have them on Sundays to Tuesdays?
Wednesdays to Fridays? Weekends!
It's okay, mommas okay!
If you eat me, it will send a bad message.
Ha! Score one for the sloth!
And the scores all tied up.
- Do you think the beast will find, Sid?
- Or, more importantly, us?
Rudy? Are you joking? He's relentless.
He knows all, sees all eats all.
So, that's a "yes".
Hey, get off my lawn! Go on shoo!
I knew that guy when he was a caterpillar.
You know, before he came out.
So, you're just living down here by your wits!
All on your own, no responsibilities?
Not one! It's incredible.
No dependence, no limits,
the greatest life a single guy can have.
Did you hear that?
This is my kind of place.
Hello? No, no. I can't really talk right now.
I'm trying to recover a dead sloth.
Now, they're following me!
I know, they think I'm crazy.
Okay... We're going into the Chasm of Death,
I'm gonna lose you. I love you too.
- Alright. Goodbye, goodbye, bye.
- Okay, follow me!
That's you in three weeks.
- So, why do they call it the chasm of death?
- Well we tried, 'big smelly crack'.
- But, that just made everybody giggle.
- Well now what?
- Madam...
- She is not doing that.
Rule number one.
Come on, mammoth.
You supposed to have a good memory.
Always listen to Buck.
Now! Eyes forward!
Back straight... and... uh, yes...
Breathe in the toxic fumes
and you'll probably die.
Toxic fumes.
- Just another day in paradise.
- Wait!
Geronimo!
- Ellie! You okay?
- You have to try this.
Alright now pile on
everyone, couldn't be easier.
Don't panic! Just some, technical
difficulties. Keep holding it in boys.
- I can't take it anymore.
- He breathe it. And now I'm breathing it.
- Hey we're not dead.
- You sound ridiculous.
Me? You should hear you.
Alright, alright.
And one, and two...
- Christmas, Christmas time is here...
- Are you crazy?
It's not poison.
It's so disturbing.
- Stop laughing, all of you!
- "Stop laughing, all of you!"
What's rule number one?
They're just laughing,
what's so bad about that?
They died laughing.
- Stop laughing!
- Do you know what's funny though?
We're trying to save Sid
and now we're all gonna die!
- And I don't even like Sid.
- Who does? He's an idiot!
Thanks for getting me into this mess.
It's the most fun I've had in years.
Thank you, for deserting the herd.
That was totally super.
Stop that! Don't you see?
We're all gonna die.
We gotta do everything, huh?
- Sometimes I wet my bed.
- That's alright. Sometimes I wet your bed.
I'm not sure how much
of that you could hear?
Oh, I heard all of it.
- You wet my bed?
- That was gas talk, dude.
- Well, we better get moving.
- Aren't we forgetting something?
I'm so lonely.
Okay. Here you go guys...
Muncher, muncher.
What? You're not gonna
eat your vegetables?
How you going to become
big and strong dinosaurs?
No... I raised them vegetarian.
It's a healthier lifestyle.
I mean look at me.
Excuse me. I'm trying to
have a conversation here.
No, no, no! That's not for us kids.
Way to feathery, and fleshy, and...
...and alive!
No, no, no!
We do not eat live animals, period.
Now go, fly. Be free.
Little flightless bird.
My bad.
Hey, where you going?
This is how you resolve a conflict?
No wonder you're single.
Oh, come on!
Am I talking to myself here?
I say they're vegetarian.
You say "Grrr".
I say "Can we talk about this?".
- I don't call that communication.
- Grrr!
See? That's your answer to everything.
Grrr!
What are you afraid of?
You're the biggest thing on Earth.
Aren't you?
- They'll never survive. It's dangerous by day.
- But it's even worse at night.
- Plus the guide is a lunatic!
- What? You mean Buck? Oh, he's whacko.
I am not.
- Totally bonkers!
- And his feet smell.
- Shut up!
- You shut up!
Oh, you little...
- He's strangling his own foot.
- Shouldn't we get moving?
- And give Rudy a midnight snack? Not likely.
- The skulls right, take a load of mammals.
We'll camp here. Now, who's hungry?
I am. You don't need the calories!
There I was... My back
against the wall. No way out.
Perched on a razor's edge of oblivion.
Staring into the eye, of the great white beast.
- Were you killed?
- Sadly, yes. But I lived.
Never had I felt so alive, than
when I was so close... To death.
Just before, Rudy could
suck me down his gullet.
I grabbed hold of that, roast pink fleshy thing
that dangles at the back of the throat.
I hung on to that sucker,
and I swung back and forth, back and forth.
Back... and forth and back. Until finally
I let go and shot right out of his mouth.
I may have lost an eye that day.
But I got this.
Rudy's tooth...
It's like the old saying: "An eye for
a tooth". A nose for a chin. A butt for a"...
It's an old saying. But
uh, it's not a very good one.
You are super-weasel.
- Ultra-weasel.
- Diesel-weasel.
What? He is.
Now let me tell you about the time I used
to sharpen, clam-shell to turn a T-Rex.
- Into a T-Rachel
- Yes, master.
Wow, that's enough
fairy-tales for one night.
- Come on, Ellie. You should rest now...
- Pff.. Life at the party.
Alright, you guys get some
shut-eye, I'll keep watch.
Don't worry, Buck, we got this.
- Night time is possum time.
- Yeah, we own the night, baby.
Good night, Rudy.
Wait, wait. What about me?
Sleep well, kids. We have a busy
day tomorrow. Forging, Hunting...
Missing my friends.
Probably are not missing me.
What...
You're a real softie, you know that?
Manny?
Crash? Eddie?
What's going on? Are you okay?
I'm sorry. I just wanted
to keep you safe, and
Now you're in the most
dangerous place in the world.
This isn't your fault. It's bigger than
both of us. We have to get, Sid.
Yeah, but If I had been a better friend
to him... we wouldn't be here.
Better friend?
Are you plucking my whiskers?
You risked your life, your mate,
and your baby to save your buddy!
Not the best husband or father,
but... a damn good friend.
Everybody stop!
I smell something.
Hmm, it smells like
a buzzard's butt fell off.
- And then got sprayed on by a bunch of skunks.
- That's, Sid.
Mammal's, we have ourselves a crime scene.
Half eaten carcass! Hunk of... Oh, no!
Broccoli!
Here's what I think happened:
Dinosaur attacked Sid, Sid fights back
with piece of broccoli.
- Leaving dinosaur, a vegetable.
- Are you nuts?
Sid's not violent,
or co-ordinated.
- Yeah, and where's the dinosaur?
- Alright, alright. Good point.
Theory two:
Sid's eating broccoli. Dinosaur eats Sid.
Dinosaur steps on broccoli.
- Leaving broccoli, a vegetable.
- Buck, when exactly did you lose your mind?
Umm... 3 months ago. I woke up
one morning married to a pineapple.
An ugly pineapple.
But I loved her.
Uh, Buck! I think you
missed a little clue over here.
Your friend might be alive.
But not for long. Rudy's closing in.
Wow...
You got it. The plates of, wow.
Or whatever's left of them.
Single file everyone.
Head for, Lava Falls.
- What's that sound?
- It's the wind. It's speaking to us.
- What's it saying?
- I don't know. I don't speak "wind".
Ellie?
I'm fine, don't worry about me.
I'm just taking my...
Ellie! Whoa!
- Manny!
- Get to the ledge!
- Ellie!
- Ellie, where are you?
- It's okay, I'm up here.
- Hang on, Ellie. We'll be right there.
Wait! Sloth down!
Wait... Time out. Hold up.
Jeez, you guys are getting fast.
It's not so bad down here.
Nice weather, friendly neighbours.
Hi, neighbour!
- Rudy...
- Rudy!
- Never heard that kind of dino before.
- That's Sid.
We'll have to move fast.
Manny, pineapples!
- Pineapples?
- She gets cravings.
- Pomegranates, grapefruits, nectarines.
- She's ordering a fruit cocktail.
- Come on, think. Peaches!
- Peaches? Peaches!
The baby!
What, what, what now!
- This not good.
- The baby is coming!
- Can you try to hold it in!
- Can somebody slap him for me?
- Just sit tight, we're coming!
- There's only one thing to do.
Opossums, you're with me.
Manny, you take care of Ellie,
until we get back.
What? No, you can't leave now.
She's off the trail.
What about rule number 2?
Rule number 5 says, you can ignore
rule number 2, if there's a female involved.
Or possibly a cute dog. I just
make up these rules as I go along.
Yeah, but, but, but...
She's... You have to!
- Manny, it's alright. I got your back.
- Now you're talking. Come on, lads!
- Take care of our sister, Mr.
- No pressure.
What does that mean, "I've got your back"?
I'd rather they cover the front.
That's where all the
good stuff is, isn't it?
We gotta move!
Okay! Alright. It's okay.
Daddy's, daddy's coming.
I gotta say sweet heart,
you really got timing...
Go away! Go away! Shoo!
Afraid of danger! Afraid of danger!
Don't worry, it's just lava. Deadly,
Violent lava!
- Boys, are you ready for adventure?
- Yes, sir!
- For danger?
- For death!
- Uh, can you repeat the question?
That's right. Come on!
- Have you ever flown one of these before?
- No, first time actually.
There she is.
- Ellie!
- Manny!
I need to get to her.
Listen, I'll protect, Ellie.
You stop those guys.
Manny, if they reach her, it'll
be to late. You have to trust me.
Alright, let's do it.
My paws are burning, baby!
They burning!
I gotta tiptoe, tiptoe, tiptoe...
- Excuse me, twinkle toes. Giving birth here.
- Oh, right. Sorry! You're okay?
Am I okay? Do you know
anything about child birth?
No, not really, but Manny's coming..
- Diego, I'm scared! Can I hold your paw?
- Yeah, of course...
Just go with the pain.
It's just a contraction.
- Look! He's right there.
- Roger!
- No, Sid.
- I know. Roger!
How about we get Sid first,
and then go back for Roger.
Oh, never mind.
Oh, Buck.
- Wait, wait! Sid's that way!
- Tell that to them.
Bring it on, you chicken headed freaks!
Don't worry about a thing.
You're doing fine.
It's going great.
Ah, excuse me.
- Just keep breathing.
- Diego!
Just breathe, that's the important thing.
Grab that ammo.
- Bogey at 3 o'clock.
- Fire!
This is awesome!
Light it up!
- Yeah!
- Hasta la vista, birdie!
Let's get our...
Mayday! Mayday!
We're losing altitude! Hold these.
- That tastes like fish.
- Okay. That's just weird.
- I love you, bro!
- I know!
Snap out of it, come on! Pull!
This is the end of Sid, the sloth.
- Help!
- No, Sid. It's me.
- And me!
I don't want to panic anybody,
but who's flying this thing?
No, no, wait, my kids!
I never even got to say goodbye.
- You can do it. Push! Push!
- I can't do it.
Just one more big push.
You have no idea what I'm going through.
Okay forget I said that. Let's do this together.
I liked you guys better,
when you were extinct.
Oh, I'm getting dizzy.
Manny. Come on buddy.
I think we're getting close.
She's perfect.
I think we should call her, Ellie.
- Little, Ellie...
- I've got a better name... Peaches.
Peaches?
Why not? She's sweet, and round,
and covered with furs.
I love it.
I saw that, tough guy.
No, no, that last dino
caught my eye with a claw and...
- Alright, so I'm not made of stone.
- Incoming!
It's Sid!
Oh, it's a boy!
- That's its tail.
- It's a girl.
Hi, sweetheart!
It's uncle Sid... Yes, it is.
Oh, you're so beautiful.
Oh, she is...
She looks just like her mother.
Thank goodness!
Oh, no offence, Manny. No offence.
You're beautiful on the inside.
It's good to have you back, Sid.
Never thought I would say
this, but... I missed you, buddy.
Now I wish my kids were here.
You could have been friends.
Ellie!
- I promised myself I wouldn't cry.
- I didn't.
I forgot what it was like
to be part of a family.
What about you? Ever
thought about having kids?
Alright, mammal's. Let's get you home.
This is it, mammal's. Right where
you started. This was fun.
- We could make it a regular thing.
- I don't know about that.
Right, Right. Yes cos' of all
the uh, mortal peril. Of-Course.
- Oh, well, the Buck stops here!
- We couldn't have done it without you.
Well obviously. But, good
times just the same...
We're not alone, are we?
Hello, Rudy!
Run!
Over here you colossal, fossil!
Looking for something?
Why don't you come and
get it? To the cave! Go!
- Stay with the baby.
- We'll be fine. Go!
Wuss!
Pop, goes the weasel!
Shoo, shoo! Come on! Move!
Diego... Catch!
Through the hole, over the valley.
One more loop...
Come on, lads! Heev!
Better luck next time, snowflake.
This isn't gonna hold him long. Let's go!
Hold up, guys!
Way to go, Mom-Zilla!
Come here, kids. Well let me tell you
something. You're where you belong now.
And I'm sure you're gonna grow
up to be giant, horrifying dinosaurs.
Just like your mother.
Momma...
...take good care of our kids.
- You were a good parent, Sid.
- Thanks!
- Can I baby-sit for you?
- Not a chance.
- Oh, come on! I work cheap.
- Alright. I'll think about it.
- Yes!
- Never happened.
- He's gone. What am I supposed to do now?
- That's easy.
- Come with us.
- You mean... up there?
I never thought of going back. I've been
down here so long, it feels like up to me.
I'm not sure I can fit-in
up there anymore.
So, look at us.
We look like a normal herd to you?
Ouch!
So long, big guy!
That's our queue. Come on, Peaches.
He's alive.
Buck...
- I... I gotta...
- Yeah...
Besides this world should
really stay down here.
- Take care of 'em, tiger.
- "Always listen to, Buck. "
We're almost out.
- Is everybody okay?
- Where's Buck?
Don't worry.
He's where he wants to be.
Is he going to be okay?
Are you kidding?
Nothing can kill that weasel.
It's Rudy I'm worried about.
I know this baby thing isn't for you.
But whatever you decide to do...
I'm not leaving, buddy.
Life of adventure... It's right here.
Well, I got a whole speech here.
I've been working on it.
How can I show
you that I'm strong and...
...sensitive? Noble, yet caring?
Thanks!
Ah, they grow so fast, huh?
Look at my kids.
Seems they were born one
day and then gone the next.
- They were, Sid.
- Yeah, it was a lot of work.
It's right, sweetheart.
Welcome to the Ice Age.
@hamIL
Watch Movies, TV Series and Live Sports
Signup Here -> WWW.ADMITME.APP