Created and Encoded by --  Bokutox -- of  www.YIFY-TORRENTS.com. The Best 720p/1080p/3d movies with the lowest file size on the internet.
(HORSES NEIGHING)
Dismount!
SCOUT: Herman's horse-sick!
SCOUTMASTER:
Chaps, no one wander off.
Some of the passageways
in here can run for miles.
HERMAN: I don't think
this is such a good idea.
(DIGGING)
(LAUGHTER)
What is it?
(DIGGING CONTINUES)
FEDORA:
Alfred, did you get anything yet?
- Nothing.
- Then keep digging.
The kid's got something!
(WHOOPING)
I got something, Garth!
I got something...
I got something right here.
(WHOOPING)
Oh, look at that!
- We're rich! We're rich!
- Shut up. Shut up.
Well, we're rich, ain't we?
Indy...
Indy?
What are they doing?
Indiana? Indiana?
(SHUSHING)
HALF BREED: Hey, we got to find
more stuff to bring back.
It's the Cross of Coronado.
Cortez gave it to him in 1520.
MAN: Oh, boy!
ROSCOE: I'm thinkin' about
raisin' my dead mama, dig down
and put it on her bony finger!
That cross is an important artifact.
It belongs in a museum.
Run back and find the others.
Tell Mr. Havelock
that there are men looting in the caves.
- Have him bring the sheriff.
-(HERMAN SHUDDERING)
It's only a snake.
Did you hear what I said?
Right. Run back...
Mr. Havelock... The sheriff...
What, what are you gonna do?
I don't know.
I'll think of something.
FEDORA: Dig with your hands,
not with your mouth.
He's got our thing!
- Get him!
- Get off me!
Mr. Havelock! Anybody!
Everybody's lost but me.
There he is! Let's go! Let's go!
(WHISTLING)
'Hey! Hey, you!
- Dang it!
Hey! Come back here!
(WHISTLING)
Come on! Get him!
Hey, come back here!
(GRUNTING)
(GROWLING)
(HISSING)
(SHOUTING)
(INDY SCREAMING)
Here, let me.
(ROARING)
Holy smokes!
Come on, kid.
There's no way out of this.
-(ROARS)
- Hey!
Toss up the whip.
You got heart, kid,
but that belongs to me.
It belongs to Coronado.
Coronado is dead,
and so are all of his grandchildren.
This should be in a museum.
Now give it back!
(HISSING)
A snake! Snake!
FEDORA: Don't let him get away!
INDY: Magic?
Hold it.
Make sure he doesn't double back.
Okay, kid, out of the box, now.
Son of a...
Damn.
Dad!
Dad.
- Dad...
- HENRY: Out.
- It's important.
- Then wait. Count to 20.
- No, Dad. You listen to me.
- Junior!
One, two, three, four...
HENRY: In Greek.
(COUNTING IN GREEK)
(BUGLE BLOWING)
HENRY: "May he who illuminated this,
illuminate me."
I brought the sheriff.
Just the man I want to see.
Now, there were five or six of them...
- It's all right, son.
- They came after me...
- You still got it?
- Well, yes, sir.
It's right here.
I'm glad to see that
because the rightful owner of this cross
won't press charges if you give it back.
He's got witnesses, five or six of them.
(WHOOPING) Yeah!
Good day.
You lost today, kid,
but it doesn't mean you have to like it.
Small world, Dr. Jones.
Too small for two of us.
This is the second time
I've had to reclaim
my property from you.
That belongs in a museum.
So do you.
Throw him over the side.
(GRUNTING)
Grab him, he's getting away! Stop him!
INDY: Archeology is the search for fact...
...not truth.
If it's truth you're interested in,
Dr. Tyree's philosophy class
is right down the hall.
So forget any ideas you've got about
lost cities, exotic travel,
and digging up the world.
We do not follow maps
to buried treasure,
and "X" never, ever, marks the spot.
Seventy percent of all archeology
is done in the library.
Research. Reading.
We cannot afford to take mythology
at face value.
(BELL RINGING)
Next week, Egyptology
starting with the excavation of Naukratis
by Flinders Petrie in 1885.
I will be in my office
if anybody's got any problems,
for the next hour and a half.
Marcus, I did it.
You've got it!
You know how long I've
been looking for that?
All your life.
All my life.
Well done, Indy. Very well done, indeed.
This will find a place of honor
in our Spanish collection.
We can discuss my honorarium
over dinner and champagne tonight.
- Your treat.
- Yes.
My treat.
(STUDENTS CHATTERING)
- GIRL: Dr. Jones!
- Dr. Jones!
(ALL TALKING TOGETHER)
Shush!Shush!
Dr. Jones, I am so glad you're back.
Your mail is on your desk.
Here are your phone messages.
Dr. Jones, you promised...
This is your appointment schedule,
and these term papers
still haven't been graded.
Okay. Irene, put everybody's name
on a list,
get the order they arrived...
- Oh, come on, Dr. Jones.
- Dr. Jones.
...And I'll see each and
every one of them in turn.
Venice, Italy
ALL: Dr. Jones!
MAN: Dr. Jones?
Dr. Jones.
I trust your trip down
was comfortable, Dr. Jones.
My men didn't alarm you, I hope.
My name is Donovan. Walter Donovan.
I know who you are, Mr. Donovan.
Your contributions to the museum
over the years
have been extremely generous.
Some of the pieces in your collection
here are very impressive.
Well, like yourself, Dr. Jones,
I have a passion for antiquities.
Have a look over here.
This might interest you.
INDY: Well, it's sandstone.
Christian symbol.
Early Latin text.
Mid-12th century, I should think.
That was our assessment, as well.
Where did this come from?
My engineers unearthed it
in the mountain region north of Ankara
while excavating for copper.
Can you translate the inscription?
(READING LATIN)
"...who drinks the water
I shall give him, says the Lord,
"will have a spring inside him
"welling up for eternal life.
"Let them bring me
to your holy mountain
"in the place where you dwell.
"Across the desert
and through the mountain
"to the Canyon of the Crescent Moon,
"to the temple where the cup that...
"Where the cup that holds the blood
of Jesus Christ resides forever."
The Holy Grail, Dr. Jones.
The chalice used by Christ
during the Last Supper.
The cup that caught His blood
at the Crucifixion
and was entrusted to
Joseph of Arimathea.
The Arthur legend.
I've heard this bedtime story before.
Eternal life, Dr. Jones!
The gift of youth
to whoever drinks from the Grail.
Now, that's a bedtime story
I'd like to wake up to.
An old man's dream.
Every man's dream,
including your father's, I believe.
Grail lore is his hobby.
He's a teacher of medieval literature.
The one the students hope
they don't get.
Walter, you're neglecting your guests.
DONOVAN: Be along in a moment, dear.
Hard to resist, isn't it?
The Holy Grail's final resting place
described in detail.
What good is it?
This Grail tablet speaks of deserts
and mountains and canyons.
It's pretty vague.
Where do you want to start looking?
Maybe if the tablet were intact,
you'd have something to go on,
but the entire top portion is missing.
Just the same, an attempt to recover
the Grail is currently underway.
Let me tell you another
bedtime story, Dr. Jones.
After the Grail was entrusted
to Joseph of Arimathea,
it disappeared,
and was lost for a thousand years
before it was found again
by three knights of the First Crusade.
Three brothers, to be exact.
I've heard this one, as well.
Two of these brothers
walked out of the desert
150 years after having found the Grail
and began the long journey
back to France,
but only one of them made it.
And before dying of extreme old age,
he supposedly imparted his tale to a...
to a Franciscan friar, I think.
Not "supposedly," Dr. Jones.
This is the manuscript in which
the friar chronicled the knight's story.
It doesn't reveal the location of
the Grail, I'm afraid,
but the knight promised
that two markers
that had been left behind would.
This tablet is one of those markers.
It proves the knight's story is true.
But as you pointed out, it's incomplete.
Now, the second marker is entombed
with the knight's dead brother.
Our project leader
believes that tomb to be located
within the city of Venice, Italy.
As you can now see, Dr. Jones,
we're about to complete a great quest
that began almost 2,000 years ago.
We're only one step away.
That's usually when the ground falls out
from underneath your feet.
You could be more right than you know.
Yes?
We've hit a snag.
Our project leader has vanished,
along with all his research.
We received a cable from his colleague,
Dr. Schneider,
who has no idea of his whereabouts
or what's become of him.
I want you to pick up the trail
where he left off.
Find the man,
and you will find the Grail.
You've got the wrong Jones,
Mr. Donovan.
Why don't you try my father?
We already have.
Your father is the man
who has disappeared.
BRODY: Your father and I have been
friends since time began.
I've watched you grow up, Indy.
I've watched the two of you grow apart.
I've never seen you this concerned
about him before.
Dad?
He's an academic, a bookworm.
He's not a field man.
Dad?
Dear God.
BRODY: What has the old fool
got himself into now?
I don't know, but whatever it is,
he's in over his head.
Dad?
It's today's mail, and it's been opened.
Mail.
That's it, Marcus.
Venice, Italy.
BRODY: What is it?
INDY: It's Dad's Grail diary.
Every clue he followed.
Every discovery he made.
A complete record of his search
for the Holy Grail.
This is his whole life.
Why would he have sent this to me?
I don't know,
but someone must want it pretty badly.
Do you believe, Marcus?
Do you believe the Grail actually exists?
The search for the Cup of Christ
is the search for the divine in all of us.
But if you want facts, Indy,
I've none to give you.
At my age, I'm prepared to
take a few things on faith.
Call Donovan, Marcus.
Tell him I'll take that ticket
to Venice now.
I'll tell him we'll take two
All right, tell me what's going to happen
when we get to Venice.
Don't worry, Dr. Schneider
will be there to meet you.
- Schneider?
- I maintain an apartment in Venice.
It's at your disposal.
Oh, well, that's good. Thank you.
Dr. Jones, good luck.
Now be very careful.
Don't trust anybody.
Signora ? Signorina ?
- Ah, Venice...
- Yes.
How will we recognize
this Dr. Schneider when we see him?
I don't know. Maybe he'll know us.
WOMAN: Dr. Jones?
INDY: Yes?
I knew it was you.
You have your father's eyes.
And my mother's ears,
but the rest belongs to you.
Looks like the best parts
have already been spoken for.
- Marcus Brody?
- That's right.
Dr. Elsa Schneider.
How do you do?
ELSA: The last time I saw your father,
we were in the library.
He was very close to tracking down
the knight's tomb.
(LAUGHS) I've never seen him
so excited.
He was as giddy as a schoolboy.
INDY: Who? Attila the Professor?
He was never giddy,
even when he was a schoolboy.
Fréulein, will you permit me?
- I usually don't.
- I usually don't, either.
- In that case, I permit you.
- It would make me very happy.
But I'm already sad.
By tomorrow, it will have faded.
Tomorrow I'll steal you another.
I hate to interrupt you,
but the reason we're here...
Yes. I have something to show you.
I left your father working in the library.
He sent me to the map section
to fetch an ancient plan of the city.
When I got back to his table,
he'd gone, with all his papers,
except for that scrap,
which I found near his chair.
Roman numerals.
ELSA: Here is the library.
INDY: That doesn't look
much like a library.
BRODY: Looks like a converted church.
In this case, it's the literal truth.
We are on holy ground.
These columns over here
were brought back as spoils of war
after the sacking of Byzantium
during the Crusades.
Now, please excuse me.
The library's closing in a few moments.
I'll arrange for us to stay a little longer.
Marcus, I've seen this window before.
Where?
Right here, in Dad's diary.
INDY: You see?
Look, Indy. The Roman numerals.
Dad was onto something here.
Well, now we know
the source of the numbers,
but we still don't know what they mean.
Dad sent me this diary for a reason.
Until we find out why,
I suggest we keep it to ourselves.
Find something?
Yes. Three, seven and ten.
That window seems to be
the source of the Roman numerals.
My God, I must be blind.
Dad wasn't looking for a book
about the knight's tomb,
he was looking for the tomb itself.
Don't you get it?
The tomb is somewhere in the library.
You said yourself it used to be a church.
Look.
Three.
Seven.
Seven. Ten.
And ten.
Now where's the ten?
Look around for the ten.
INDY: Three and seven.
Seven and seven
and ten.
Ten.
"X" marks the spot.
(LOUD BANGING)
Bingo.
You don't disappoint, Dr. Jones.
You're a great deal like your father.
Except he's lost, and I'm not.
Lower me down.
Look after this for me, will you?
Come on.
Pagan symbols. Fourth or fifth century.
Right.
600 years before the Crusades.
The Christians would have
dug their own passages
and burial chambers centuries later.
INDY: That's right.
If there's a knight of
the First Crusade down here,
that's where we'll find him.
(BRODY GRUNTS)
What's this one?
The Ark of the Covenant.
- Are you sure?
- Pretty sure.
Watch out.
It's petroleum.
I should sink a well down here
and retire.
Give me the lighter.
Oh, rats.
(SQUEAKING)
(SCREAMS)
Come on.
INDY: Come here.
Look, it... it must be one of these.
ELSA: Look at the artistry
of these carvings, and the scrollwork.
It's this one.
This is it. We found it.
Look.
The engraving on the shield,
it's the same as on the Grail tablet.
The shield is the second marker.
What's that?
INDY: It's a rubbing Dad made
of the Grail tablet.
Just like your father,
giddy as a schoolboy.
Wouldn't it be wonderful
if he were here now to see this?
He never would have
made it past the rats.
He hates rats.
He's scared to death of them.
(WHOOSHING)
(SQUEAKING)
Get back! Back against the wall.
Quick! Under it! Air pocket!
- Don't wander off.
- What?
What?
(SCREAMING)
I think I've found a way out.
Deep breath.
(EXCLAIMING)
Ah, Venice.
Are you crazy? Don't go between them!
Go between them? Are you crazy?
I said go around!
You said go between them!
I said, don't go between them!
No!
Why are you trying to kill us?
Because you're looking
for the Holy Grail.
My father was looking for the Holy Grail.
Did you kill him too?
KAZIM: No.
Where is he?
Talk or you're dead.
Damn it, tell me!
Tell me!
If you don't let go, Dr. Jones,
we'll both die.
Then we'll die.
My soul is prepared. How's yours?
This is your last chance.
No, Dr. Jones, it's yours.
INDY: All right, where's my father?
KAZIM: If you let me go,
I will tell you where he is.
Who are you?
My name is Kazim.
And why were you trying to kill me?
The secret of the Grail has been safe
for a thousand years,
and for all that time,
the Brotherhood of the Cruciform Sword
have been prepared
to do anything to keep it safe.
Let me off at this jetty.
Ask yourself, why do you
seek the Cup of Christ?
Is it for His glory, or for yours?
I didn't come for the Cup of Christ.
I came to find my father.
In that case,
God be with you in your quest.
Your father is being held
in the Castle of Brunwald,
on the Austrian-German border.
INDY: How's the head?
BRODY: It's better, now I've seen this.
It's the name of a city. "Alexandretta"?
The knights of the First Crusade
laid siege to the city
of Alexandretta for over a year.
The entire city was destroyed.
The present city of lskenderun
is built on its ruins.
Marcus, you remember
what the Grail tablet said,
"Across the desert
and through the mountain
"to the Canyon of the Crescent Moon."
But where exactly?
Your father would know.
Your father did know.
Look. He made a map.
He must have pieced it together
from clues scattered through
the whole history of the Grail quest.
A map with no names.
Now, he knew there was a city
with an oasis due east, here.
He knew the course turned south
through the desert to a river,
and the river led
into the mountains, here.
Straight to the canyon.
He knew everything
except where to begin,
the name of the city.
Alexandretta.
- Now we know.
- Yes. Now we know.
Marcus, get hold of Sallah.
Tell him to meet you in lskenderun.
What about you?
I'm going after Dad.
Elsa?
(MUSIC PLAYING ON PHONOGRAPH)
Elsa? Elsa?
(GASPS)
- My room...
- Mine, too.
What were they looking for?
This.
- The Grail diary?
- Uh-huh.
You had it?
You didn't trust me.
I didn't know you.
At least I let you tag along.
Oh, yes.
Give them a flower,
and they'll follow you anywhere.
Knock it off. You're not mad.
No?
No. You like the way I do things.
It's lucky I don't do things the same way.
You'd still be standing
at the Venice pier!
Look, what do you think
is going on here?
Since I met you,
I've nearly been incinerated,
drowned, shot at,
and chopped into fish bait.
We're caught in the middle
of something sinister here.
My guess is Dad found out
more than he was looking for.
And until I'm sure,
I'm going to continue to do things
the way I think they should be done.
How dare you kiss me!
Leave me alone. I don't like fast women.
And I hate arrogant men.
(GONDOLIER SINGING)
Ah, Venice.
(THUNDERING)
What do you know about this place?
I know the Brunwalds
are famous art collectors.
What are you going to do?
Don't know. I'll think of something.
(KNOCKING)
Yes?
(IN SCOTTISH ACCENT)
And not before time!
Did you intend to leave us
standing on the doorstep all day?
We're drenched!
(FAKES A SNEEZE)
Now look, I've gone and caught a sniffle.
Are you expected?
Do not take that tone with me,
my good man.
Now buttle off and tell Baron Brunwald
that Lord Clarence MacDonald
and his lovely assistant
are here to view the tapestries.
Tapestries?
Dear me, the man is dense.
This is a castle, isn't it?
There are tapestries?
This is a castle,
and we have many tapestries.
But if you are a Scottish lord,
then I am Mickey Mouse!
How dare he?
(INDISTINCT CHATTERING)
(TELEPHONE RINGING)
Nazis. I hate these guys.
(THUNDERING)
This one. I think he's in here.
How do you know?
Because it's wired.
Indy?lndy?
Don't worry. This is kid's play.
I'll be right back.
Junior?
Yes, sir.
It is you, Junior!
Don't call me that, please.
Well, what are you doing here?
I came to get you. What do you thi...
(VOICES APPROACHING)
Late 14th century, Ming dynasty.
It breaks the heart.
And the head. You hit me, Dad.
I'll never forgive myself.
Don't worry, I'm fine.
Thank God.
It's fake.
See, you can tell by the cross section.
No!
Dad, get your stuff.
We've got to get out of here.
HENRY: Well, I'm sorry
about your head, though,
but I thought you were one of them.
Dad, they come in through the doors.
Good point.
But better safe than sorry.
So I was wrong this time.
But, by God, I wasn't wrong
when I mailed you my diary.
You obviously got it.
I got it, and I used it.
We found the entrance
to the catacombs.
Through the library?
Right.
I knew it.
And the tomb of Sir Richard?
Foundit
He was actually there?
You saw him?
Well, what was left of him.
And his shield,
the inscription on Sir Richard's shield?
"Alexandretta."
(EXCLAIMING) Alexandretta! Of course!
On the pilgrim trail
from the Eastern Empire.
Junior, you did it.
No, Dad. You did.
Forty years.
If only I could have been with you.
There were rats, Dad.
Rats?
Yeah, big ones.
What do the Nazis want with you, Dad?
- They wanted my diary.
- Yeah?
I knew I had to get that book
as far away from me as I possibly could.
Yeah.
Dr. Jones.
BOTH: Yes?
I will take the book now.
BOTH: What book?
You have the diary in your pocket.
(CHUCKLING) You dolt!
Do you think my son
would be that stupid
that he would bring my diary
all the way back here?
You didn't, did you?
- You didn't bring it, did you?
- Well...
You did.
Look, can we discuss this later?
I should have mailed it
to the Marx Brothers.
Will you take it easy?
Take it easy?
Why do you think I sent it home
in the first place?
So it wouldn't fall into their hands!
I came here to save you!
Oh, yeah?
And who's gonna come
to save you, Junior?
I told you...
...don't call me Junior!
Look what you did!
I can't believe what you did...
Elsa? Elsa?
That's far enough.
Put down the gun, Dr. Jones.
Put down the gun, or the Fréulein dies.
- But she's one of them.
- Indy, please!
- She's a Nazi.
- What?
- Trust me.
-Indy,no!
I will kill her!
- Yeah? Go ahead!
- No! Don't shoot!
Don't worry. He won't.
Indy, please! Do what he says!
And don't listen to her.
- Enough! She dies!
-(CRYING OUT)
Wait! Wait...
I'm sorry.
No, don't be.
But you should have
listened to your father.
She ransacked her own room,
and I fell for it.
How did you know she was a Nazi?
She talks in her sleep.
I didn't trust her. Why did you?
MAN: Because he didn't take my advice.
Donovan.
Didn't I warn you not to trust anybody,
Dr. Jones?
I misjudged you, Walter.
I knew you would sell your mother
for an Etruscan vase,
but I didn't know you would
sell your country and your soul
to the slime of humanity.
Dr. Schneider,
there are pages torn out of this.
This book contained a map,
a map with no names,
precise directions from the unknown city
to the secret
Canyon of the Crescent Moon.
So it did.
Where are these missing pages,
this map?
We must have these pages back.
You're wasting your breath.
He won't tell us,
and he doesn't have to.
It's perfectly obvious
where the pages are.
He's given them to Marcus Brody.
HENRY: Marcus?
You didn't drag poor Marcus along,
did you?
He's not up to the challenge.
He sticks out like a sore thumb.
We'll find him.
The hell you will.
He's got a two-day head start on you,
which is more than he needs.
Brody's got friends
in every town and village
from here to the Sudan.
He speaks a dozen languages,
knows every local custom.
He'll blend in, disappear.
You'll never see him again.
With any luck,
he's got the Grail already.
Does anyone here speak English?
Or even ancient Greek?
Water? No, thank you, sir.
No. Fish make love in it.
Goodness me. Thank you so much.
No, I don't like that.
No, I really don't want...
No, no, thank you very much.
No, thank you, madam. I'm a vegetarian.
Does anyone understand
a word I'm saying here?
Mr. Brody!
Sallah. What a relief.
Marcus Brody, sir.
- But where is Indy?
- He's in Austria.
A slight detour.
You are on your own?
Yes, but don't panic.
Everything's under control.
Have you, have you
arranged our supplies?
Yes, of course.
But where are we going?
This map will show you.
It was drawn by...
Mr. Brody.
Welcome to lskenderun.
The director
of the Museum of Antiquities
has sent a car for you.
Well, your servant, sir.
And I am his.
Follow me, please.
My reputation precedes me.
There is no museum in lskenderun.
Papers, please.
Papers? Of course.
- Run.
- Yes.
Papers. Got it here.
Just finished reading it myself.
- Run.
- Yes.
Egyptian Mail, morning edition. Run.
Did you say...
Run!
Okay, okay, quick, quick, quick!
Find the back door! Find the back door!
Intolerable.
Dr. Schneider. Message from Berlin.
You must return immediately.
- A rally at the Institute of Aryan Culture.
- So?
Your presence on the platform
is requested at the highest level.
Thank you, Herr Oberst.
I will meet you at lskenderun.
Take this diary
to the Reichmuseum in Berlin.
It will show them our progress,
ahead of schedule.
Without the map,
I'm afraid it's no better than a souvenir.
Let me kill them now.
No.
If we fail to recover
the pages from Brody,
we'll need them alive.
Always do what the doctor orders.
Don't look at me like that.
We both wanted the Grail.
I would have done anything to get it.
You would have done the same.
I'm sorry you think so.
I can't forget how wonderful it was.
Thank you.
It was rather wonderful.
VOGEL: Dr. Schneider.
Your car is waiting.
That's how Austrians say good-bye.
And this is how we say good-bye
in Germany, Dr. Jones.
(GROANS)
I liked the Austrian way better.
So did I.
Let's try and get these ropes loose.
We've got to get to Marcus
before the Nazis do.
You said he had two days' start.
That he would blend in. Disappear.
Are you kidding? I made that up.
You know Marcus.
He got lost once in his own museum.
Can you try and reach
my left jacket pocket?
HENRY: What am I looking for?
My lucky charm.
Feels like a cigarette lighter.
INDY: Try and burn through the ropes.
Very good.
(HENRY EXCLAIMS)
I ought to tell you something.
Don't get sentimental now, Dad.
Save it till we get out of here.
The floor's on fire.
- See?
- What?
And the chair.
Move! Move it out of here! Go!
HENRY: It's scorching the table! Fast!
- Move!
- Okay!
(SPEAKING GERMAN)
Well, we have Marcus Brody,
but more important, we have the map.
(SPEAKING GERMAN)
"By the personal command
of the Fuhrer.
"Secrecy essential to success.
"Eliminate the American conspirators."
Germany has declared war
on the Jones boys.
(SPEAKING GERMAN)
- Dad!
- What?
Head for the fireplace!
(COUGHING)
INDY: I think I can get these ropes off.
(RUMBLING)
Whoops!
(SPEAKING GERMAN)
Our situation has not improved.
Listen, Dad, I'm almost free.
(SHOUTING) Alarm!
(ALARM RINGING)
This is intolerable.
I'm out, Dad.
Well done, boy.
(ALL SHOUTING)
(SPEAKS GERMAN)
Come on, Dad.
Dead end.
There's got to be a...
A secret door or a...
Passageway or something.
I find that if I just sit down and think...
(SCREAMING) Dad!
...The solution presents itself.
Great. More boats.
You say this has been
just another typical day for you, huh?
(GRUNTS)
No! But better than most.
Come on, Dad. Come on.
What about the boat?
We're not going on the boat?
Jones!
(SPEAKS GERMAN)
(GUNSHOTS)
Halt! Halt!
(GROANS)
- HENRY: Stop!
- What?
Stop! Stop!
You're going the wrong way.
We have to get to Berlin.
Brody's this way.
My diary's in Berlin.
We don't need the diary, Dad.
Marcus has the map.
There is more in the diary
than just the map.
All right, Dad. Tell me.
Well, he who finds the Grail
must face the final challenge.
What final challenge?
Three devices of such lethal cunning.
- Booby traps?
- Oh, yes.
But I found the clues that
will safely take us through,
in the Chronicles of St. Anselm.
Well, what are they?
Can't you remember?
I wrote them down in my diary
so that I wouldn't have to remember.
Half the German army's on our tail,
and you want me to go to Berlin?
- Into the lion's den?
- Yes.
The only thing that matters is the Grail.
What about Marcus?
Marcus would agree with me.
Two selfless martyrs.
Jesus Christ.
(GASPS)
That's for blasphemy.
The quest for the Grail
is not archeology.
It's a race against evil.
If it is captured by the Nazis,
the armies of darkness
will march all over the face of the Earth.
Do you understand me?
This is an obsession, Dad.
I never understood it. Never.
Neither did Mom.
Oh, yes, she did.
Only too well.
Unfortunately, she kept
her illness from me
until all I could do was mourn her.
(CHANTING)
(BAND PLAYING)
(INDISTINCT SHOUTING)
My boy, we are pilgrims
in an unholy land.
(CLAMORING)
Fréulein Doctor.
- Where is it?
- How did you get here?
Where is it? I want it.
You came back for the book? Why?
My father didn't want it incinerated.
Is that what you think of me?
I believe in the Grail, not the swastika.
But you stood up to be counted
with the enemy of everything
that the Grail stands for.
Who gives a damn what you think?
You do.
All I have to do is squeeze.
All I have to do is scream.
I've got it. Let's get the hell out of here.
(SPEAKING GERMAN)
- What did you get?
- I don't know.
First available flight out of Germany.
Good.
Well, we made it.
When we're airborne,
with Germany behind us,
then I'll share that sentiment.
Relax.
(SHOUTING)
(SPEAKS GERMAN)
Tickets, please.
Guten Tag, Herr Jones.
(BOTH SPEAKING GERMAN)
Tickets, please.
(PEOPLE MURMURING)
WOMAN: We should get out of here.
No ticket.
Ticket.
MAN 11 Ticket!
MAN 21 Ticket!
- Ticket!
(SHOUTING IN GERMAN)
You know,
sharing your adventures is
an interesting experience.
That's not all we shared.
It's disgraceful.
You're old enough to be her fa...
Her grandfather.
Well, I'm as human as the next man.
I was the next man.
(CHUCKLES)
Of course. Well...
Ships that pass in the night.
Do you remember the last time
we had a quiet drink?
I had a milkshake.
What did we talk about?
We didn't talk.
We never talked.
Do I detect a rebuke?
A regret. It was just the two of us, Dad.
It was a lonely way to grow up.
For you, too.
If you'd been an ordinary,
average father,
like the other guys' dads,
you'd have understood that.
Actually, I was a wonderful father.
When?
Did I ever tell you to eat up? Go to bed?
Wash your ears? Do your homework?
No. I respected your privacy,
and I taught you self-reliance.
What you taught me was
that I was less important to you
than people who'd been dead
for 500 years in another country.
And I learned it so well
that we've hardly spoken for 20 years.
You left just when
you were becoming interesting
Unbelievable.
- Dad, how can you...
- Very well.
I'm here now.
What do you want to talk about?
Well, I...
(STUTTERING)
(CHUCKUNG)
I can't think of anything.
Then what are you complaining about?
Look, we have work to do.
When we get to Alexandretta,
we will face three challenges.
The first, "The Breath of God.
Only the penitent man will pass."
Second, "The Word of God.
"Only in the footsteps of God
will he proceed."
Third, "The Path Of God.
"Only in the leap from the lion's head
will he prove his worth."
What does that mean?
I don't know. We'll find out.
We're turning around.
They're taking us back to Germany.
INDY: Well, I thought it would
take them a lot longer
to figure out the radio was dead.
Come on, Dad. Move!
Come on, Dad. Come on!
I didn't know you could fly a plane.
Fly, yes.
Land,no.
(GUN FIRING)
Dad, you're going to have to
use the machine gun.
Get it ready.
Eleven o'clock!
Dad, eleven o'clock!
What happens at eleven o'clock?
Twelve, eleven, ten.
Eleven o'clock, fire!
Dad, are we hit?
More or less.
Son, I'm sorry.
They got us.
Hang on, Dad. We're going in!
- Nice landing.
- Thanks.
Those people are trying to kill us!
I know, Dad!
Well. It's a new experience for me.
It happens to me all the time.
This is intolerable!
This could be close.
Faster, boy! Faster!
Well, they don't come
any closer than that!
Dad, he's coming back!
(CLUCKING)
(PILOT SCREAMING)
I suddenly
remembered my Charlemagne.
"Let my armies be
the rocks and the trees
"and the birds in the sky."
DONOVAN: These pages are taken from
Professor Jones' diary, Your Highness,
and they include a map
that pinpoints
the exact location of the Grail.
As you can see,
the Grail is all but in our hands.
However, Your Highness,
we would not think of crossing your soil
without your permission,
nor of removing the Grail
from your borders
without suitable compensation.
What have you brought?
(SPEAKS IN GERMAN)
Precious valuables, Your Highness,
donated by some of the finest families
in all of Germany.
Rolls-Royce Phantom Two.
Four-point-three liter, 30 horsepower,
six-cylinder engine,
with Stromberg downdraft carburetor.
Can go from zero to
100 kilometers an hour
in 12.5 seconds.
And I even like the color.
The keys are in the ignition,
Your Highness.
You shall have camels, horses,
an armed escort, provisions,
desert vehicles and tanks.
You're welcome.
We have no time to lose.
Indiana Jones
and his father have escaped.
We go this way.
Get that camel out of the way.
What happened to Marcus, Sallah?
They set out across the desert
this afternoon.
I believe they took Mr. Brody with them.
Now they have the map.
And in this sort of race,
there's no silver medal
for finishing second.
Care to wet your whistle, Marcus?
I'd rather spit in your face.
But as I haven't got any spit...
Must be within three or four miles.
Otherwise we are off the map.
Well, Marcus,
we are on the brink of the recovery of
the greatest artifact
in the history of mankind.
You're meddling with powers
you cannot possibly comprehend.
(INDY EXCLAIMS)
INDY: I see Brody.
He seems okay.
They've got a tank.
Six-pound gun.
What do you think you're doing there?
Get down!
Dad, we're well out of range.
(EXPLOSION)
That car belonged to my brother-in-law.
Come on, come on!
I can't see anyone up there.
Maybe it wasn't even Jones.
No, it is him, all right.
He's here somewhere.
Put Brody in the tank.
Well, in this sun,
without transportation,
they're as good as dead.
(GUNSHOTS)
It's Jones, all right.
- Now, who are all these people?
- Who cares?
As long as
they're keeping Donovan busy.
Dad, you stay here while Sallah and I
organize some transportation.
(SCREAMS)
- I'm going after those horses.
- I'll take the camels.
- I don't need camels.
- But, Indy...
No camels.
Who is he?
A messenger from God.
For the unrighteous,
the Cup of Life
holds everlasting damnation.
- Marcus!
-(SHOUTS)
"Genius of the Restoration..."
"Aid our own resuscitation."
Henry, what are you doing here?
It's a rescue, old boy. Come on.
Search him.
What is in this book?
That miserable little diary of yours.
We have the map. The book is useless.
And yet you come all the way back
to Berlin to get it.
VVhy?
What are you hiding?
What does the diary tell you
that it doesn't tell us?
It tells me that goose-stepping morons
like yourself
should try reading books
instead of burning them.
DONOVAN: Colonel!
Jones is getting away.
I think not,
Herr Donovan.
Not that Jones, the other Jones!
Sallah, I said no camels!
That's five camels. Can't you count?
Compensation for
my brother-in-law's car.
Indy, your father and Brody...
Where's my father?
They have them.
In the belly of that steel beast.
(SPEAKING GERMAN)
Fire!
(HORNS HONKING)
(SCREAMS)
Dad! Dad!
- Dad!
- Junior?
Junior?
Junior!
(COUGHING)
(SHOUTING)
Dad!
Dad! Get out!
(SHOUTING)
(GRUNTING)
(SPEAKING GERMAN)
Henry, the pen...
- What?
- But don't you see?
The pen is mightier than the sword.
Look what you did.
It's war.
Didn't I tell you it was a rescue?
(SHOUTING)
- Dad!
- Yeah?
You call this archeology?
Get out of there, Dad.
How does one get off this thing?
Where's Marcus?
(HENRY SCREAMING)
Dad!
Hang on, Dad!
Father of Indy, give me your hand!
Sallah!
Get Dad!
SALLAH: Give me your hand!
Junior!
(RUMBLING)
Indy!
Oh, God.
I've lost him.
And I never told him anything.
I just wasn't ready, Marcus.
Five minutes would have been enough.
I thought I'd lost you, boy!
I thought you had too, sir.
Well...
Well done. Come on.
Let's go, then.
Why are you sitting there resting
when we're so near the end?
Come on, let's go!
The Canyon of the Crescent Moon.
(MAN SPEAKING GERMAN)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
DONOVAN: Helmut, another volunteer!
(MEN CHATTERING)
(SPEAKING GERMAN)
I never expected to see you again.
I'm like a bad penny, I always turn up.
Step back now, Dr. Schneider.
Give Dr. Jones some room.
He's going to recover the Grail for us.
(SCOFFS)
Impossible? What do you say, Jones?
Ready to go down in history?
As what? A Nazi stooge like you?
The Nazis?
Is that the limit of your vision?
The Nazis want to write themselves
into the Grail legend,
take on the world.
Well, they're welcome.
But I want the Grail itself.
The cup that gives everlasting life.
Hitler can have the world,
but he can't take it with him.
I'm going to be drinking my own health
when he's gone the way of the dodo.
The Grail is mine,
and you're going to get it for me.
Shooting me won't get you anywhere.
You know something, Dr. Jones?
You're absolutely right.
(GUNSHOT)
Dad?
Junior...
- No!
- Get back!
You can't save him when you're dead!
The healing power of the Grail
is the only thing
that can save your father now.
It's time to ask yourself
what you believe.
INDY: "The Breath of God.
"Only the penitent man will pass."
"The penitent man will pass."
The penitent man will pass.
The penitent man...
"Only the penitent man will pass."
The penitent man will pass.
The penitent, penitent...
The penitent man...
The penitent man... The penitent...
The penitent man is humble before God.
Penitent. Penitent...
The penitent man...
Penitent man is humble,
kneels before God.
Kneel!
I'm through!
We're through.
He's all right.
No.
The second challenge:
"The Word of God."
"Only in the footsteps of God
will he proceed."
The Word of God...
The Word of...
Proceed in the footsteps of the Word.
-"The Word of God..."
- BRODY: No, Henry. Try not to talk.
The name of God...
Jehovah.
But in the Latin alphabet,
Jehovah begins with an
J...
Oh, dear.
Idiot!
In Latin, Jehovah starts with an
"I."
"E."
"H."
"O."
"V."
"A."
"The Path of God."
"Only in the leap from the lion's head
"will he prove his worth."
Impossible, nobody can jump this.
(MOANS)
BRODY: Indy!
Indy, you must hurry!
Come quickly!
It's a leap of faith.
Oh, geez...
You must believe, boy.
You must believe.
(GASPS)
I knew you'd come,
but my strength has left me.
Who are you?
The last of three brothers
who swore an oath to find the Grail
and to guard it.
That was 700 years ago.
A long time to wait.
You're strangely dressed, for a knight.
I'm not exactly...
A knight? What do you mean?
I was chosen
because I was the bravest,
the most worthy.
The honor was mine until another came
to challenge me to single combat.
I pass it to you who vanquished me.
Listen, I don't have time to explain, but...
Which one is it?
You must choose,
but choose wisely.
For as the true Grail will bring you life,
the false Grail
will take it from you.
DONOVAN: I'm not a historian.
I have no idea what it looks like.
Which one is it?
Let me choose.
Thank you, Doctor.
Oh, yes.
It's more beautiful
than I'd ever imagined.
This certainly is the cup of
the King of Kings.
Eternal life.
(GASPS)
What is happening to me?
(SCREAMING)
DONOVAN: Tell me, what is happening?
(WIND BLOWING)
He chose
poorly.
ELSA: It would not be made out of gold.
That's the cup of a carpenter.
There's only one way to find out.
You have chosen wisely.
But the Grail cannot pass
beyond the Great Seal.
That is the boundary
and the price of immortality.
(SIZZLES)
(MOANS)
(MAN SPEAKING
FOREIGN LANGUAGE)
Drop your guns. Please.
Dad, come on, get to your feet.
We have got it. Come on!
Elsa! Elsa, don't move!
It's ours, Indy, yours and mine.
INDY: Elsa, don't cross the Seal.
The knight warned us
not to take the Grail from here.
(RUMBLING)
HENRY; Junior!
Junior!
Elsa...
Elsa, don't. Elsa...
Give me your other hand, honey.
I can't hold you!
I can reach it. I can reach it.
Elsa, give me your hand.
Give me your other hand!
Elsa!
(SCREAMING)
Junior, give me your other hand!
I can't hold on.
I can get it.
I can almost reach it, Dad.
Indiana...
Let it go.
Dad...
Please, Dad.
Elsa never really believed in the Grail.
She thought she'd found a prize.
What did you find, Dad?
Me?
Illumination.
And what did you find, Junior?
"Junior"? Dad...
Please, what does it always mean,
this... This "Junior"?
That's his name: Henry Jones, Junior.
I like Indiana.
We named the dog Indiana.
May we go home now, please?
The dog?
You are named after the dog?
I've got a lot of fond memories
of that dog.
- INDY: Ready?
- Ready.
Indy! Henry! Follow me. I know the way!
Got lost in his own museum, huh?
Uh-huh.
After you, Junior.
Yes, sir.