Created and Encoded by --  Bokutox -- of  www.YIFY-TORRENTS.com. The Best 720p/1080p/3d movies with the lowest file size on the internet.
Come on, let's go! Let's go!
Hey! Hey, guys!
Faster!
Hey, what you got under there?
- Hey, you want to race?
- Oh, please.
- Come on!
- Come on, let's go!
Come on!
- Please?
- Come on! Let's go! Come on!
Come on. Let's go.
Go faster! Faster!
Sorry, gentlemen.
This whole area is closed for
weapons testing for the next 24 hours.
That includes all on-base personnel.
Good afternoon, sir.
I'm afraid that goes for you,
too, Colonel, sir.
The Pentagon sent out revised ...
Russians.
This ain't gonna be easy.
Not as easy as it used to be.
- Well, we've been through worse.
- Yeah? When?
Flensburg. There was twice as many.
- We were younger.
- I still am young!
We had guns.
Put your hands down, will you?
You're embarrassing us.
Bet you 500 bucks
we can get out of this.
Let's call it 100.
You recognize building, yes?
Drop dead.
I'm sorry.
I meant drop dead, comrade.
- Where was he found?
- In Mexico.
They were digging in the dirt,
looking for this stuff.
You're not from around here, are you?
Where is it you would imagine
I am from, Dr. Jones?
Well, the way you're sinking your
teeth into those wubble-u's,
I should think maybe Eastern Ukraine.
Highest marks.
Colonel Dr. Irina Spalko.
Three times
I have received Order of Lenin.
Also medal as Hero of Socialist Labor.
And why?
Because I know things.
I know them before anyone else.
And what I do not know, I find out.
Now, what I need to know now
is in here.
- You are a hard man to read, Dr. Jones.
- Ouch.
So, we will do this, what is
expression, old-fashioned way.
You will tell us.
You will help us find what we seek.
This warehouse is where you
and your government ...
have hidden all of your secrets, yes?
This is a military warehouse.
I've never been here before in my life.
Object we seek,
rectangular storage container,
dimensions 2 meters by 0.5 meter
by 66 centimeters.
Contents of box, mummified remains.
This is no doubt familiar to you.
What makes you think I've got any
idea what box you're talking about?
Because 10 years ago ...
you were part of the team
that examined it.
Look ...
Even if I knew
what you were talking about ...
You will help us find it.
Compass. I need a compass.
You know, north, south, east ...
West.
No compass?
I need your bullets.
The contents of that box
are highly magnetized.
I need gunpowder.
You want my help or not?
Don't toy with me, Dr. Jones.
What is the point of all this?
If it's still magnetic,
the metal in this gunpowder
should point the way.
Shells. Give me some shotgun shells.
Pliers.
Drop the guns,
or Colonel Dr. Spalko is dead.
Why, Mac?
Well, what can I say, Jonesey?
I'm a capitalist, and they pay.
After all those years
we spent spying on the Reds?
I thought we were friends, Mac.
I've had a run of bad luck
with the cards lately, mate.
Awful. Bloody awful.
I can't go home empty-handed again.
No defiant last words, Dr. Jones?
I like Ike.
Put down gun.
You got it, pal.
Damn, I thought that was closer.
Come on. Come on.
He's not to get out of here alive!
Block the exits!
Don't get clever, Boris.
You don't know him.
Know him. Know him.
You don't know him!
You don't know ...
You did well.
Hello? Hello?
Hello!
Hey. I knocked.
You guys got a ...
Wait a minute.
Come on, gang!
Oh, that can't be good.
All personnel,
it is now one minute to zero time.
Put on goggles or turn away.
Do not remove goggles or face burst
until 10 seconds after first light.
That can't be good at all.
Wait! Wait!
Wait, wait, wait! Wait!
Sure! Great! Don't wait for me!
Minus 15 seconds.
Minus 10 seconds.
Niner, eight, seven, six,
fiver, four,
three, two, one, zero.
I had no reason to believe
that Mac was a spy.
He was Ml6 when I was in OSS.
We did 20, 30 missions together
in Europe and the Pacific.
Don't wave your war record
in our face, Colonel Jones.
We all served.
No kidding?
What side were you on?
I don't think you recognize
the gravity of your situation.
You aided and abetted KGB agents ...
who broke into a top-secret
military installation ...
in the middle of the
United States of America, my country.
What was in the steel box they took?
You tell us. You've seen it before.
You mean that Air Force fiasco in '47.
I was tossed into a bus
with blacked-out windows ...
and 20 people
I wasn't allowed to speak to.
Hauled out in the middle of the
night in the middle of nowhere ...
on some urgent recovery project
and shown what?
Pieces of wreckage ...
and an intensely magnetic shroud
covering mutilated remains?
None of us
was ever given the full picture.
And we were threatened with treason
if we ever talked about it.
So, you tell me,
what was in the box?
Indy, thank God.
Don't you know it's dangerous
to climb into a refrigerator?
Those things can be deathtraps!
Good to see you, too, Bob.
Relax, boys.
I can vouch for Dr. Jones.
What the hell is going on?
KGB on American soil?
Who is that woman?
Describe her.
Tall, thin, mid-30s,
carried a sword of some kind,
a rapier, I think.
Yeah, that's her.
You sure she's here?
Here and gone. Who is she?
Irina Spalko,
she was Stalin's fair-haired girl.
His favorite scientist, if you
can call psychic research science.
General Ross ...
She's leading teams from the
Kremlin all over the world.
Scooping up artifacts ...
she thinks might have
paranormal military applications.
- General Ross!
- Back off, Paul.
Not everyone in the Army's a Commie
and certainly not Indy.
What exactly am I being accused of,
besides surviving a nuclear blast?
Nothing yet.
But frankly your association
with George McHale ...
makes all your activities suspicious,
including those during the war.
Are you nuts?
Do you have any idea how many medals
this son of a bitch won?
A great many, I'm sure.
But does he deserve them?
Dr. Jones, let's just say for now
that you are of interest to the Bureau.
Of great interest.
Grooved Ware in the beginning
of modern drainage practices,
which we also see in Skara Brae
on the west coast of Scotland.
Skara Brae dates from 3100 B.C.
and was continuously occupied
for 600 years ...
until it was apparently
abandoned in 2500 B.C.
There's no clear evidence
as to why its occupants ...
decided to abandon a perfectly
healthy environment. Yes?
- May I have a moment, Professor?
- Yes.
Open up Michaelson.
Review Chapter 4.
When I come back we'll discuss ...
the difference between
migration and exodus.
What?
You have no idea the pressure
coming from the Board of Regents.
The FBI showed up this morning,
ransacked your office,
searched all your files!
You're the dean of the college.
Why didn't you stop them?
They have no right.
They had every right!
They weren't vandals.
They were federal agents
with search warrants!
The university isn't gonna get itself
embroiled in that kind of controversy,
not in this charged climate.
So you're firing me.
A leave of absence is all.
An indefinite leave of absence.
- You are firing me.
- During which ...
they've agreed to continue to pay
your full salary for a period ...
I don't want their money!
Please don't be foolish.
You don't know what I had to go
through to get that for you.
You went through? What exactly
did you have to go through, Charlie?
Henry ...
I resigned.
Where will you go?
Train to New York,
overnight to London, for starts.
I might end up teaching in Leipzig.
Heinrich owes me a favor.
I'll wire you when I get settled.
You can send on
the rest of my things.
I suppose
there's nothing to keep you here.
I barely recognize
this country anymore.
The government's got us
seeing Communists in our soup.
When the hysteria reaches academia,
I guess it's time to call it a career.
How did Deirdre take the news?
How does any wife take such things?
The look on her face was
a combination of pride and panic.
I never should've doubted you,
my friend.
No, you have reason to question
your friends these days.
Brutal couple of years, huh, Charlie?
First Dad, then Marcus.
We seem to have reached the age
where life stops giving us things ...
and starts taking them away.
Just another half glass.
Hey!
Hey, old man!
Professor, hello! Hey!
Are you Dr. Jones?
You're running out of platform, kid.
Are you a friend of Dr. Oxley's?
- Harold Oxley? The archeologist?
- Yeah.
What about him?
They're going to kill him.
I haven't talked to Harold Oxley
in 20 years.
He's a brilliant guy.
He could put you to sleep
just by talking.
Yeah. Yeah. When I was a kid,
that's how I did get to sleep.
Oxley's voice was better than
a glass of warm milk, you know.
The name's Mutt, Mutt Williams.
- Mutt? What kind of name is that?
- Yeah.
It's the one I picked.
You got a problem with it?
Take it easy.
What was your relationship to Oxley?
My dad died in the war.
Ox kind of helped my mom raise me.
You were saying
somebody's going to kill him?
Six months ago,
my mom gets a letter from the Ox.
He's down in Peru.
Found some type of skull,
a crystal skull.
Like the one that guy
Mitchell-Hodgkiss? Hedgkiss?
- The one he found.
- Nice jacket.
The Ox and I were obsessed with
the Mitchell-Hedges skull in college.
How do you know about it?
Are you kidding?
It's all he talked about.
He'd talk about that thing
till the cows come home.
What's it? It's like an idol?
Deity carving. Mesoamerican.
There are a number of crystal skulls
in the world.
I saw one in the British Museum.
Interesting craftsmanship,
but that's about it.
All right, well, laugh if you want.
Oxley said he found it this time.
He said this was real and he was off
to a place called Akator with it.
- Akator? He said that? You're sure?
- Yeah.
That's what he said.
He said Akator. What is it?
It's a mythical lost city
in the Amazon.
Conquistadors called it El Dorado.
Supposedly, the Ugha tribe were
chosen by the gods 7,000 years ago ...
to build a giant city
out of solid gold.
It had aqueducts and paved roads ...
and technology that wouldn't
be seen again for 5,000 years.
Francisco de Orellana disappeared
into the Amazon looking for it in 1546.
I almost died of typhus
looking for it myself.
I don't think it exists.
Why would Ox
want to take the skull there?
The legend says that a crystal
skull was stolen from Akator ...
in the 15th or 16th century,
and that whoever returns
the skull to the city temple ...
will be given control over its power.
Power. Right. So there's some
kind of power. What's the power?
I don't know, kid.
It's just a story.
No.
From his letter, my mom thought
the Ox was off his rocker.
You know, smog in the noggin,
so she goes down there to find him,
only he'd already been kidnapped.
Now they've got her, too.
Now, Ox said
he hid that skull someplace,
and if my mom doesn't come up with it,
they're gonna kill them both.
Now, she said you'd help me.
Me? What's your mom's name again?
Mary. Mary Williams.
You remember her?
There were a lot of Marys, kid.
Shut up! That's my mother
you're talking about!
All right? That's my mother.
You don't have to get sore all the
time just to prove how tough you are.
Sit down. Please. Sit down.
She said if anybody could find
the skull, it's you.
Like you're some type of ...
Like a grave robber or something.
I'm a tenured professor of archeology.
Oh, you're a teacher.
Well, that's gonna be a big help.
Anyway, she called me
two weeks ago from South America.
Said she'd escaped,
but they were after her.
She said she'd just gotten
a letter from the Ox ...
and mailed it to me
so I could give it to you.
Then the line went dead.
I opened it.
I mean, the thing's pointless,
though. It's just gibberish.
It's not even English lettering.
See?
See those two bricks over there,
at the counter?
I don't think
they're here for the milkshakes.
Who are they?
Don't know. Maybe FBI.
Come quietly, Dr. Jones.
Make that KGB.
- And bring letter with you.
- Letter? What letter?
Letter Mr. Williams just give you.
Me? Do I look like a mailman?
We don't ask again.
Come now or we'll ...
Or what?
Nice try, kid, but I think
you just brought a knife ...
to a gunfight.
Outside now.
- Hit this guy.
- Who?
Joe College. Hit him hard.
- Here, hold this.
- What?
That's my boyfriend!
Take it outside!
Get that greaser!
Your mom didn't escape.
They let her go,
so she could mail the letter ...
and you could bring it to me
and I could translate it!
Get on, gramps!
Go, go, go, go, go!
Better dead than Red!
This is crazy!
Somebody's going to get hurt!
Left! Go left! Left!
Move, move! Move!
Split, split! Split, split!
- You're going too fast.
- That's a matter of opinion!
- Excuse me, Dr. Jones.
- Yes?
I just had a question on
Hargrove's normative culture model.
Forget Hargrove.
Read Vere Gordon Childe
on diffusionism.
He spent most of his life
in the field.
If you want to be
a good archeologist,
you got to get out of the library!
Who is that?
Francisco de Orellana,
the conquistador.
Remember, the guy who got lost
looking for the skull.
And just as I thought.
Koihoma.
What's that?
It's an extinct Latin American language.
Pre-Columbian syllabic base.
See. Diagonal stresses on the
ideograms. Definitely Koihoma.
- You speak it?
- Nobody speaks it.
It hasn't been heard aloud
in 3,000 years.
I might be able to read a bit though
if I walk it through Mayan first.
You know, for an old man,
you ain't bad in a fight.
Thanks a lot.
What are you, like, 80?
It's a riddle.
Leave it to Ox to write a riddle
in a dead language.
"Follow the lines in the earth
only gods can read ...
"which lead to Orellana's cradle ...
"guarded by the living dead."
- He's talking about the Nazca Lines.
- What are those?
Hold on here.
Geoglyphs. Giant ancient drawings
carved into the desert floor in Peru.
From the ground,
they don't look like anything.
But from the sky,
only the gods can read them,
because only gods live up there.
Oxley's telling us
the skull is in Nazca, Peru.
Finally. They saw him.
Ox wandered into town a couple of
months ago, raving like a madman.
Police locked him up
in the sanitarium. It's this way.
I took Spanish and I didn't understand
a word of that. What was it?
Quechua, local Incan dialect.
- Where'd you learn that one?
- Long story.
I got time.
I rode with Pancho Villa.
A couple of his guys spoke it.
Bullshit!
- You asked.
- Pancho Villa?
- Technically, I was kidnapped.
- By Pancho Villa?
It was the fight
against Victoriano Huerta.
- How old were you?
- About your age.
Your parents must've had a cow, huh?
It worked out.
Things were a little tense at home.
Yeah, me and my mom
aren't on the best of terms, either.
Treat her right, kid. You only get
one and sometimes not for that long.
It's not my fault. It's hers.
She just got P.O.'ed
because I quit school.
She thinks I'm some
kind of goof or something.
- You quit school?
- Oh, yeah. Sure. Tons of them.
Fancy prep schools
that teach you how to debate
and chess and fencing.
I'm great with the blade.
I just think it's a waste of time.
- You never finished.
- No.
Just a bunch of useless skills.
Wrong books.
'Cause I love reading.
Me and Ox used to read all the time.
But now I can pick them myself.
You get me?
- What do you do for money?
- Fix motorcycles.
Gonna do that
for the rest of your life?
Maybe I will, Teach.
You got a problem with that?
No. Not if that's
what you love doing.
Don't let anybody tell you different.
This is it. Sister.
She says Ox isn't here.
She doesn't know where he is.
Some men came and took him away,
men with guns.
She says he was obsessed, deranged.
Drew pictures
all over the walls of his cell.
This riddle in Oxley's letter
doesn't make any sense.
"Follow the lines that only the gods
can read that lead to Orellana's cradle."
Cradle, cradle, birth.
Orellana wasn't born in Peru.
He was born in Spain.
He was a conquistador.
He came here for the gold.
What happened to him?
He disappeared along with six others.
Their bodies were never found.
He must have lost his mind.
Ox, man, what happened?
What happened?
This is not the Mitchell-Hedges skull.
Look at the elongated cranium.
And the same word ...
in different languages,
over and over again.
Return.
Return where?
Or return what?
You mean the skull?
Seems to have been on his mind.
Where was he supposed to return it to?
- Sweep.
- Yeah.
Ox didn't mean Orellana's birthplace.
Cradle has another meaning in Mayan.
Literally, it means "resting place,"
as in final resting place.
Ox meant Orellana's grave.
This drawing scratched into the floor
is the cemetery where he's buried.
You said Orellana vanished
and nobody ever found his grave.
Well, it looks like Harold Oxley did.
"Grave robbers will be shot."
Good thing we're not grave robbers.
- What are we looking for?
- I don't know yet.
Maybe an antechamber
off one of these barrows.
I think I just saw something!
Oh, you're jumping at shadows.
This way down.
- This way up.
- Yeah.
Those darts are poison!
Stay there.
You're a teacher?
Part-time.
Dead end.
Maybe.
What are you doing?
Put that thing away.
Give me some light over here.
Bring it over here.
It's just a thing.
Dance on your own dime, will you?
One of the scorpions just stung me!
Am I gonna die?
- How big?
- Huge!
- Good.
- Good?
When it comes to scorpions,
the bigger the better.
A small one bites you,
don't keep it to yourself.
Their skulls.
Look at their skulls, man.
Like the drawings in Oxley's cell.
Means we're getting closer.
That's crazy. Why is it like that?
Nazca Indians used to
bind their infants' heads with rope
to elongate the skull like that.
- Why?
- Honor the gods.
No, no.
God's head is not like that, man.
Depends on who your god is.
You're going nowhere fast.
Professor, this really
is a dead end. Look.
Hey!
Come on, genius.
Bring the backpack.
- This is incredible.
- Unreal.
Don't touch anything.
Footprints. Somebody's been here.
Recently.
Two sets of prints.
Same size, could have been
the same person twice.
Not bad, kid.
One. Two.
Three. Four. Five. Six.
Seven.
Orellana and his men might've
made it out of the jungle after all.
Give me some light.
You don't have a knife, do you?
Looks like he just died yesterday.
It's the wrappings.
They preserved him.
What just happened?
He's been wrapped up for 500 years.
Air doesn't agree with him.
Thanks.
I don't want to keep
borrowing yours all the time.
- That's fine.
- I was going to put it back.
Is this one open already?
It's him.
It's Orellana himself.
They called him The Gilded Man.
His lust for gold was legendary.
It's odd.
Somebody's been here and gone.
But they left all this gold
and all the artifacts.
What were they looking for?
- Hold this.
- No. No.
Unbelievable.
No tool marks.
A single piece of seamless quartz.
Cut across the grain.
It's not possible, even with
today's technology, it would shatter.
Crystal's not magnetic.
Neither is gold.
What is this thing?
Maybe the Nazca Indians thought
this was their god.
- You think this is the one from ...
- From Akator.
Maybe the Spaniards found this skull
along with all this other loot.
They were headed for their ships
along the shore.
Maybe the Indians
caught up with them,
or they got to squabbling
amongst themselves ...
over their prize,
kill each other off.
The Indians wrap them up
and bury them.
A couple of hundred years later,
Oxley shows up here, finds the skull.
Takes it away, maybe to Akator.
But then he returns it here.
Return.
Return, like he wrote
on the walls of his cell.
He put it back
where he found it. Why?
- Hello, Jonesey.
- Hello, Mac.
You're lucky I turned up, Jonesey.
Dovchenko there wanted
to blow your brains out.
That's the third time
I've saved your life.
Unshackle me.
I'll give you a big hug.
You had a Luger
pointed at the base of your skull
the first time we met.
I had the situation under control.
- You owe me.
- What do you owe them?
After the war, when you turned,
how many names
did you give the Reds?
You're not looking
at the big picture here.
How many good men died
because of you?
Eventually, they're gonna
let me out of this chair, comrade,
and when they do,
I'm going to break your nose.
"Comrade"?
You think this is about flags?
About uniforms? You think
this is about lines on a map?
It's just about money, isn't it?
No. Not only money.
A gigantic pile of money.
Don't worry about
what the Russians will pay.
It's nothing compared
to what's at Akator.
An entire city of gold. It's what
the conquistadors were after.
For God's sake, Jonesey, we'd be rich!
Richer than Howard Hughes!
Blood money, every nickel.
I need you to see
the angle here, mate.
Be smart. Do the right thing.
Just like in ...
Like in Berlin. Got me?
Just like in Berlin.
You want me to trot off,
or should we sing a song?
How fortunate our failure
to kill you, Dr. Jones.
You survive
to be of service to us once again.
Well, you know me,
always glad to help.
"Now I am become death,
the destroyer of worlds."
You recognize those words?
It was your own Dr. Oppenheimer
after he created the atomic bomb.
He was quoting the Hindu bible.
It was nuclear intimidation.
But now this next level of weapon
is ours to have,
yours to fear.
Weapon? What weapon?
A mind weapon.
A new frontier of psychic warfare.
That was Stalin's dream.
Now I know why Oxley put the
skull back where he found it.
He knew you were looking for it.
That skull is no mere deity carving.
Surely you knew that
the moment you laid eyes on it.
It was not made by human hands.
Who made it, then?
Come on.
The body we found in New Mexico
was not the first.
We'd already dissected two others
from similar crash sites in Soviet Union.
Saucer men from Mars.
The legends about Akator
are all true.
Early men could not have
conceived it, much less built it.
It was a city of supreme beings ...
with technologies
and paranormal abilities.
You got to be kidding me.
Why do you choose
not to believe your own eyes?
The New Mexico specimen
gave us hope.
Unlike the others we'd found,
its skeleton was pure crystal.
A distant cousin, perhaps. Maybe they,
too, were sent to find Akator.
Perhaps we're all searching
for the same thing.
- There is no other explanation.
- There's always another explanation.
The skull was stolen from Akator
in the 15th century.
Whoever returns it ...
Returns it to the city temple
will gain control over its powers.
I've heard that bedtime story before.
It's a legend.
Why do you think Akator even existed?
You should ask your friend
that question.
We're certain he's been there.
Oxley?
Ox, it's me, Indy.
Ox?
Ox, you're faking it, right?
"Through eyes
that last I saw in tears ..."
Ox, listen to me, pal.
Your name is Harold Oxley.
You were born in Leeds, England.
You and I went to school together
at the University of Chicago.
And you were never this interesting.
My name is ...
My name is Henry Jones, Jr.
What have you done to him?
We ain't done a thing.
It's the bloody skull.
He is the divining rod
that will lead us to Akator.
But we need someone
to interpret him for us.
His mind, it seems, is quite weak.
Let's hope yours is stronger.
The skull's crystal stimulates an
undeveloped part of the human brain,
opening a psychic channel.
Oxley lost control of his mind
by staring too long into its eyes.
We believe you can get through to
him after you have done the same.
I've got a better idea.
You look at it.
The skull does not speak
to everyone, it seems.
Surely you're not afraid,
Dr. Jones.
You've spent your entire life
searching for answers.
Think of the truth behind those eyes.
There may be
hundreds of skulls at Akator.
Whoever finds them will control
the greatest natural force ...
the world has ever known.
Power over the mind of man.
Be careful, you might get
exactly what you wish for.
I usually do.
Imagine.
To peer across the world
and know the enemy's secrets.
To place our thoughts
into the minds of your leaders.
Make your teachers
teach the true version of history,
your soldiers attack on our command.
We'll be everywhere at once,
more powerful than a whisper,
invading your dreams,
thinking your thoughts for you
while you sleep.
We will change you, Dr. Jones,
all of you, from the inside.
We will turn you into us.
And the best part?
You won't even know it's happening.
Return.
Return?
That's enough.
If he dies, we can't get there.
Cover it.
Henry.
You all right, Jonesey?
- You broke my nose!
- I told you.
Enough! You will speak to Oxley
and lead us to Akator, yes?
Take him outside.
- You all right, kid?
- They left my bike at the cemetery.
- Yeah, but you're all right?
- They left my bike.
Whoa! Whoa, whoa.
Wait, wait, wait. Stop, stop, stop.
I'm ready.
Don't give these pigs a thing.
You heard him.
Clearly I have chosen
the wrong pressure point.
Perhaps I can find
a more sensitive one.
Get your hands off me,
you rotten Russki son of a bitch!
Indiana Jones.
About time you showed up.
- Mom!
- Sweetheart.
"Mom"?
What are you doing here?
Forget about me. Are you all right?
- "Mom"?
- Young man, I specifically told you ...
not to come here.
- Marion is your mother?
You never wrote that. You never
said that in any phone calls.
Marion Ravenwood is your mother?
For God's sake, Indy,
it's not that hard.
No, I mean, I just never thought ...
I would have a life after you left.
- That's not what I meant.
- A damn good life!
- Well, that's fine.
- A damn good, really good life!
- Well, so have I!
- Yeah?
You still leaving
a trail of human wreckage,
or have you retired?
Why? You looking for a date?
With anybody but you.
So, Dr. Jones, you will help us?
A simple "yes" will do.
Oh, Marion, you had to go
and get yourself kidnapped.
Not like you did any better.
Same old, same old.
Henry Jones, Jr.
- Henry Jones, Jr. ...
- That's right, Ox. Listen to me.
"To lay their just hands
on that Golden Key ...
"that ope's the Palace of Eternity."
- Palace of ...
It's from Milton.
He's said it before. Why?
Ox, you got to tell us
how to get to Akator ...
or they're gonna kill Marion.
"Through eyes that last I saw in tears,
here in death's dream kingdom ..."
Harold, they're gonna kill
Abner's little girl.
You got to tell us how to get there.
We need ...
Get me paper.
Something to write with.
Autowriting!
I should have seen this.
- Henry Jones, Jr.
- Right. That's right, Ox.
Three times it drops.
The way down.
- Three times ...
- Pictographs.
Ideograms.
Good, Ox. Good.
Ox?
It's me, Ox.
It's Mutt, Ox. Hey, look at me.
Look at me. It's me.
It's me.
The wavy lines mean water, of course.
Closed eyes mean sleep.
The sun with the arc over the sky
stands for time, duration.
The word "now" is "until."
These two close together,
the horizon and the snake,
mean one thought.
The horizon stood for the world,
but it didn't mean the Earth.
It meant big, great.
"The water sleeps
until the great snake."
These aren’t just drawings,
they're directions. Get me a map!
The great snake is the Amazon,
of course,
but "sleep," what water sleeps?
Here! Sono.
The Portuguese word for "sleep."
Yes, good. Exactly.
He wants us
to follow this curve of the Sono ...
down to where it meets the Amazon
to the southeast.
After that, I'm not sure.
Kingdom of dreams, tears and eyes ...
I have no idea what he means.
This could be the route, though.
It's a completely unexplored part
of the canopy.
Go, go, go, go, go! Come on!
- Kid, what the hell are we doing, kid?
- They were going to kill us!
- Well, maybe.
- Somebody had to do something!
- Something else would have been good.
- At least I got a plan.
This is intolerable.
Harold, for God's sake, keep up.
Mom?
- Stay back!
- Stop! Stop! Stop! Don't move.
Moving makes space,
space will make you sink.
No, I think I can get out
if I can just ...
Stop it!
You're pulling against a vacuum.
It's like trying to lift a car.
Just stay calm.
Okay, I'm calm.
- What is it? Quicksand?
- I'm calm.
- No, it's a dry sand pit.
- I'm sinking, but I'm calm.
Quicksand is a mix of sand,
mud and water.
And depending on the viscosity,
it's not as dangerous ...
as people sometimes think.
- For Pete's sake, Jones,
we're not in school!
Don't worry. There's nothing
to worry about unless there's a ...
A void collapse.
I'll go get something
to pull you out.
Ox, don’t just sit there.
For God's sake, man, go get help!
- Help?
- Help!
Help?
Help! Go!
Mutt can be a little impetuous.
It's not the worst quality
in the world.
Keep your arms above the surface.
When the kid comes back, grab on.
- Indy, he ...
- He's a good kid, Marion.
You should get off his back
about school.
- Mutt, I mean ...
- Not everybody's cut out for it.
His name is Henry!
Henry. Good name.
He's your son.
My son?
Henry Jones the Third.
Why the hell didn't you
make him finish school?
- Mom, grab on! Grab it!
- Yeah.
I got it.
Come on, Mom!
Pull, pull, pull, pull!
Pull!
Grab on.
- Grab it.
- Just grab it, Indy.
It's a rat snake!
- Rat snakes aren't that big.
- Well, this one is, all right?
It's not even poisonous.
Now grab on!
- Go get something else.
- Like what?
Like a rope or something.
There's no Sears and Roebuck here!
Grab the snake!
- Maybe I can touch the bottom.
- There's no bottom. Now grab it.
No, I think
I can feel it with my feet.
- Grab the snake!
- Stop calling it that!
It's a snake!
What do you want me to call it?
- Say "rope."
- What?
Say "grab the rope."
- Grab the rope!
Hold tight. It's slimy.
Pull!
Get rid of that thing, will you, Son?
Afraid of snakes.
You are one crazy old man.
Why do you have to do everything
the hard way, Jonesey?
Good work, Ox. Thanks.
Help.
No. No, he was British.
My dad was an RAF pilot.
He was a war hero,
not some schoolteacher!
No, sweetheart.
Colin was your stepfather.
We started dating
when you were three months old.
He was a good man.
Wait, wait, wait. Colin?
As in Colin Williams? You ...
You married him? I introduced you!
I think you gave up your vote
on who I married ...
when you decided to break it off
a week before the wedding!
I think we both knew, Marion,
it wasn't going to work.
You didn't know that. Why didn't
you ever talk to me about it?
Because we never had an argument
I won!
It's not my fault
if you can't keep up!
I didn't want to hurt you!
For love of God, shut the hell up!
Didn't you ever wonder years ago
why Ox stopped talking to you?
He hated that you ran away.
Would you two just stop?
Yeah, Marion, let's not let
the kid see mom and dad fight.
- You're not my dad, okay?
- You bet I am.
And I got news for you.
You're gonna go back
and finish school.
Really? What happened to,
"There's not a damn thing
wrong with it, kid,
"and don't let anybody else
tell you any different"?
You don't remember saying that?
That was before I was your father!
- You're not my father!
- Oh, yes, he is your father.
You should have
told me about the kid, Marion.
I had a right to know.
You vanished after that.
- I wrote.
- A year later!
By then,
Mutt was born and I was married!
Why are you bothering
to tell me now?
Because I thought we were gonna die!
Not yet!
Got it?
Oh, shit.
I'm sure I wasn't the only one
to go on with my life.
There must've been plenty of
women for you over the years.
Yeah. There were a few,
but they all had the same problem.
Yeah? What's that?
They weren't you, honey.
We got to get Oxley back,
get our hands on that skull ...
and get to Akator before they do.
Grab the wheel.
What's he gonna do now?
- I don't think he plans that far ahead.
- Yeah.
- Scooch over, will you, Son?
- Don't call me "son." Don't.
I think I'd cover my ears
if I were you.
Duck! Duck!
Move, move!
Pull up next to that duck.
Henry Jones, Jr.
Jones!
Come on! Come on!
Get down!
Ox has got the skull.
Marion, take the wheel.
That's not fair.
She drove the truck.
Don't be a child.
Find something to fight with.
Jonesey!
- Jonesey!
- Hi, Mac.
- Indy. Indy! Indy!
- Shut up! Shut up!
- You stupid son of a bitch! I'm CIA.
- CIA.
I almost screamed it at you in the
tent. I said, "Just like Berlin."
What were we in Berlin, mate?
- Double agents!
- The skull!
Throw me the skull!
Riposte.
Get on your front foot. Riposte.
It's not a match, Mom.
You fight like a young man,
eager to begin, quick to finish.
Mutt, disengage!
Hey! Hey, I got the skull!
- Throw the bag! Throw it!
- Throw the bag!
- Gun!
What are you looking at, Daddy-o?
She's getting away!
This is very dangerous.
Do svidanya, Dr. Jones.
Jones!
Whoa.
Whoa!
Turn!
- Siafu.
- What?
Big damn ants! Go!
Run to the river!
Get to the river!
Jump in! Come on! Come on!
Mom, there's a cliff!
- Jonesey, come on!
- Get in, Jones!
- Mom, stop.
- Mom, slow down.
- Honey, stop.
- Slow down, Mom.
- You're gonna go off the cliff.
- That's the idea.
- Bad idea. Give me the wheel.
- Trust me!
Slow down!
- Don't ever do that again.
- Yes, dear.
Three times it drops.
Reverse. Put it in reverse!
Full reverse!
- I'm trying! I'm trying!
- Whoa, whoa, whoa, Mom!
The way down.
He means by land.
He came by land.
- Three times it drops?
- Three times it drops.
What is he talking about?
He means one!
Two!
Three.
You okay? Babe? Let go.
"Through eyes that last I saw in tears."
"The golden vision reappears!"
Gold. I'm in.
Through eyes ... Through eyes in tears.
We got to go through that waterfall!
The skull has to be returned.
I'll do it. Nobody else has to come.
Who cares?
It's brought us nothing but trouble.
Look what it did to him.
- I have to return it.
- Why you?
Because it told me to.
- Ochre, iron oxide, charcoal.
- Oxy, stay with us.
How old is this?
Four or five thousand years.
Old as the pyramids.
Look, sun worshippers,
like the Egyptians.
This is fresh.
These were just used.
More worshippers.
Yeah, but that's not
the sun they're worshipping.
Someone came ...
and taught the Ugha farming.
Irrigation.
Ox, what is it?
I think I understand, Ox.
Someone came?
Are they the same?
There were more. Look.
Thirteen in a circle.
Show us the way, Ox.
- Let's go. Go, go, go! Run! Run, go!
- Go!
Indy!
Jonesey!
Oxley!
You were here before.
How did you get past them?
Come on, Mac. Come on!
Come on, Mac.
Come on, come on, come on.
"To lay their just hands
on that Golden Key ...
"that ope's the Palace of Eternity."
- Come on, Ox.
You did good, Ox. You did good.
City of gold.
So where's all the gold?
Look at the state of this place.
What a stupid legend.
What a waste of my time.
Ox was here before, but he
couldn't get into the temple,
so he took the skull back
to the cemetery, where he found it.
"To lay their just hands
on that Golden Key ...
"that ope's the Palace of Eternity."
Key that ope's the palace.
The obelisk.
The obelisk is the key?
What are you looking for, Ox?
What are you doing?
You figured this out in your cell,
didn't you, Professor?
Excuse me, Professor.
Well done.
Go get your own.
Listen.
Hear that?
Get up! Move! Ox, move!
Faster! Faster!
Faster!
This is not good. Move, Ox! Move!
Quick! Quick! Quick!
I don't like this!
I don't like it!
- Mom, come on!
- Jonesey!
He dropped it.
He dropped the skull!
Okay?
Hold this.
Ox, you okay?
Lovely.
All right, let's go.
This way?
Now that's more like it.
There are artifacts
from every era of early history.
Macedonian.
- Sumerian.
- This place is the mother lode.
Etruscan. Babylonian.
There isn't a museum in the world that
wouldn't sell its soul for this lot.
Early Egyptian.
Dozens of museums.
Hundreds of them, Jonesey!
Collectors.
They were archeologists.
How do we open it?
I'll give it back, Ox. I promise.
No more forever waiting.
Soon now.
Sorry, Jonesey.
So what are you, a triple agent?
Nah, I just lied
about being a double.
Look at them!
Still waiting for the return
of the one who was lost.
They are a hive mind.
One being physically separate,
but with a collective consciousness.
More powerful together
than they can ever be apart.
Imagine what they could tell us.
I can't imagine.
Neither could the humans
that built this temple,
and neither can you.
Belief, Dr. Jones,
is a gift you have yet to receive.
My sympathies.
Oh, I believe, sister.
That's why I'm down here.
- Mayan. He's speaking Mayan.
- What does he say?
He says he's grateful
and he wants ...
It.
It wants to give us a gift.
A big gift.
Tell me everything you know.
I want to know everything.
I want to know.
I've got a bad feeling about this.
Indy?
The eyes.
What are they? Spacemen?
Interdimensional beings,
in point of fact.
Welcome back, Ox.
What the hell is that?
A portal!
A pathway to another dimension!
I don't think we want
to go that way.
I want to know.
Tell me. I'm ready.
Mac! Mac! Come on!
Mac!
Mac, damn it, now!
I can see.
I can see!
Grab it!
Use your legs, Mac.
I can't do it alone.
Jonesey!
I'm going to be all right.
No more!
Cover it. Cover it.
Go!
Enough!
Go! Go!
Like a broom to their footprints.
Where did they go? Space?
Not into space.
Into the space between spaces.
I don't understand.
Why this legend of a city of gold?
The Ugha word for gold
translates as "treasure."
But their treasure wasn't gold.
It was knowledge.
Knowledge was their treasure.
What? We're just going to sit here?
Night falls quick in the jungle, kid.
You don't want to
climb down the mountain in the dark.
No?
I can. Who's coming with me?
Come on.
Why don't you stick around, Junior?
I don't know. Why didn't you, Dad?
Dad!
Dad?
Somewhere your grandpa is laughing.
Marvelous! Perfect! Make the
letters bigger, much bigger.
Henry Jones, Jr.,
and Marion Ravenwood,
insomuch in that you two have agreed
to live together in holy matrimony,
have promised your love for
each other by these vows ...
the joining of your hands
and the giving of these rings,
I now declare you
to be husband and wife.
Whom God hath put together,
let no one tear asunder.
"How much of human life
is lost in waiting!"
Congratulations.
You may kiss your bride.
Well done, Henry!
- Thanks, Ox.