- = ***** =-
Spell Checked by
HxHPRC
HxHPRC: Enjoy your hours!
Watch Movies, TV Series and Live Sports
Signup Here -> WWW.ADMITME.APP
We're going to do
a Christmas tune for you now.
You got to trust me. This one's
just a little bit different.
It combines the Christmas
colors, red...
...green...
...and blues!
Frosty the Snowman
Was a jolly, happy soul
He was smoking his pipe, baby
His two eyes were made of coal
And Frosty the Snowman
Is a fairy tale they say
He was made of ice and snow
Then he came to life one day
Frosty the Snowman
Was as bad as he could be
And the children say
He could laugh and play
Just the same as you and me
Man, check it out.
It's the Jack Frost Band.
They're digging it. They're loving it.
We gotta sign these guys.
There must've been some magic
In the air that night
For that old silk cap they found
For when
They laid it upon his head
He began
To hootchy-koo around
And Frosty the Snowman
Is a fairy tale they say
He was made of ice and snow
Till he came...
...to...
...life...
...one day
That was Medford's own Jack Frost Band.
Best band no one's ever heard of.
That's recorded live last night
at Denver's Music Hall.
Don't ask how we got the tape.
They are due for a break.
We got more music coming
from the '70s and '90s.
No '60s. No '80s. I promise.
Central Colorado's classic rock.
School's out!
No running. Feet are for walking.
Merry Christmas, everybody.
See you next year!
Merry Christmas, Miss Moon.
Hey, Charlie.
Happy vacation, Charlie.
Snowball fight!
- The brain's here.
- What's going on?
The 7th graders have us pinned down.
They're using the heavy artillery!
Come on, how bad could it be?
Two, three, launch!
What was that?
Bull's-eye!
- We tried to tell you.
- Rory Buck.
Alexander!
Help him!
Natalie, help!
Eat snow, you little wieners.
Huddle up. Come on.
Remember what we learned
in history class?
- No.
- Not really.
If you want to stop an army,
stop the general.
You're taking on Rory Buck?
Trust me, Tuck, all right?
You draw their fire.
Good luck, man.
Fire!
Get him!
I dare you to hit me.
Load me up.
- Are you all right?
- No.
Come on. Give me your best shot.
Can't you do better than that?
Okay, that was a good one.
Go now! Go, run!
Wait!
Come on, Alexander!
What did you do that for, butthead?
That little twerp's getting away!
Run like the wind, Alexander!
Are you okay?
I'll take care of this one myself.
Hold your fire.
Rory's pissed!
Well, well, well.
Little Charlie Frost.
- Hanging with the second graders now?
- Get off, Rory.
I got a present for you.
Nail him, Rory.
Good, I like presents.
Can you say, "brain freeze"?
Brain freeze.
Way to go, buddy.
All right, Charlie.
This isn't the end of it, Frost.
Oh, yeah! Way to go!
Shut up!
You okay? Good man.
Thanks, Charlie. You're amazing.
No problem.
See you at hockey, Charlie.
- See you, Natalie.
- Good job, dude.
See you later.
Hey, Chester.
Come on, boy.
Dad?
Hi, Mom.
It's a long drive from Denver.
You know he won't be back until late.
This drain, I don't get it.
Sometimes it works.
Sometimes it doesn't.
So?
So not turning over your report card
right away is a bad sign.
Here.
I'm going to play hockey
in the driveway.
Running away. That's another bad sign.
You may have your father's looks,
but you get your brains from me.
Good work, Charlie.
Wait till your dad sees this.
Excuse me, miss?
Listen, my car broke down back here.
Can I borrow a couple of bucks
till I get to a gas station?
Money? I'm sorry.
My husband's a musician.
Really?
- Is he any good?
- Yeah.
Really?
You know, I also left
my lip balm in the car.
So I'm out, and I think
I'm feeling a little...
Chapped?
I wonder if I could
borrow some lip balm?
I don't know if you'll like what I got.
Do you mind if I try?
- You like it?
- You know, I can't tell.
Let me just...
- I missed you.
Okay, that's for you.
What's for me?
I hope you brought me chocolates.
Yes!
He waited as long as he could.
- Let's get him up.
- No. Don't get him up.
Come on.
He's got the whole vacation to sleep.
Dude? Charlie-boy?
Charlie-boy.
Dad?
Get up, man.
I was just resting my eyes.
You were?
You looked asleep. Didn't he?
You looked like you were asleep.
- Exactly like you were sleeping.
- No, I was waiting up for you.
Okay, you can go back to sleep.
I just wanted to say hi.
I want to give you
a weather update too.
It's snowing!
Can I, Mom?
Dad, not another fathead.
He's not a fathead.
He's just smart, so he needs
a big cranium for his brain.
Now what?
Nose. Come on, nose.
I said "nose"!
I thought you said "hose".
Sorry.
Scarf.
Give me your hat.
Thank you.
Yes. Perfect.
How's he look?
He Looks like you.
He does?
Only a little cuter.
Good one, Mom.
Really?
Really.
Cuter than this?
Don't even...
You are...
...so dead!
You know what?
You throw like a girl.
Welcome home, Jack!
Now go to sleep!
Sorry, Mrs. Wilkins.
Hey, seriously, from this angle...
...she looks hot
in that flannel nightgown...
Pulling an all nighter?
Get your skinny little butt
in that bed.
Nice work on that snowman, dude.
Thanks.
- Except you made his head way too big.
- I did?
You put the bottom ball
on the top ball.
- How you doing?
- Good.
- How was Denver?
- Denver's pretty cool.
Cool. How're the guys?
They're great.
Everybody says hi.
So?
Is there anything you need to show me?
Like?
Like something in the shape...
...of a present.
Like from the gig?
Like those plastic swords they
stick through the olives and onions?
Yeah, Like for the martinis
Mom packs in my lunch.
Mom's making you martinis?
- I'm up to two now.
- Good.
Two a day.
I brought you this.
One of your harmonicas?
That's one of my old harmonicas.
Sure you want me to have this?
Absolutely I want you to have it.
Where'd you get it?
Where'd I get it?
I got that from...
...an old famous blues player named
Sonny Boy Wayne.
- Yeah, right.
- I did.
Sonny Boy Wayne.
He was 9 feet tall and could play, man.
There was a white light around him.
And he gave you this?
He did. He said,
"Son, I want you to have this.
It'll give you the power".
Come on, seriously.
Where'd you get it?
You want to know?
I got that...
...the morning you were born.
Really?
Little music store
across from the hospital.
I walked out in a great mood,
bought myself that harmonica.
And I never had a harmonica
that played better.
My favorite one.
- Now it's yours.
- Thanks.
You're welcome. Now go to sleep.
Son...
...I want you to go to sleep now.
It's awesome!
Okay, see you in the morning.
We play hockey tomorrow.
Can you come?
Yes, sir. Wait a minute, I can't.
We have to go into the studio.
Well, the game's not till four.
And it's against
our arch rivals, the Devils.
You're 1 1. You already have arch rivals?
Four. Yeah, what am I thinking?
I'm there. I'm there.
Definitely.
Great.
You know another thing about this
harmonica? It has magic powers.
Yeah, right.
I'm serious.
When you play that,
no matter where I am...
...I can hear it.
Right.
I'm telling you.
Good night.
Love you. Go to sleep.
You looking for the power?
Just testing it.
A major label? What do you think
of this Kaplan kid?
I Like him. He's smart.
He really knows music.
And you know what?
I think this guy really gets us.
Oh, good.
How's things at the bank?
How's that new guy
in the loan department?
Glenn? He's a nice guy.
He hit on me.
Really?
How about that? Guys don't even
check for rings anymore.
Relax. He's 63.
I straightened him out.
You straightened him out?
What exactly does that mean?
Stop it.
No wonder he hit on you.
Look at you.
I don't wear this to the bank.
You're barely wearing it here.
Sing me a smile.
Well, the driver on the bus says,
"Move on back..."
No, sing me the other one.
My song.
Every time
We say goodbye
I die a little
Take off your boots.
Every time
We say goodbye
Oh, man, if I had one hit song...
You will.
I'd make you guys proud of me.
We're already really proud of you.
- Buy you a nice big house.
- I'd settle for a new sink.
I can get you a new car,
like a Porsche.
Anything but a Jeep is a sissy car.
I'd get you some diamonds.
All I need is you.
I love you, Gab.
I Love you too.
'Cause when you're near
There's such an air
Of spring
About it
I bet you would Like
a snow blower, though.
Lift it up.
I don't remember you hanging
this many lights last year.
That's because I didn't hang this many.
Little straighter.
Yours is crooked on that side.
If you come down a bit at your end...
You've come too far now.
See, you've gone too far there...
Be careful, Mac.
You don't want to be on the wrong end
of that left hook.
Bye, baby.
I'll be in the car.
Front of the goal, shoots.
Hit the post.
A little wide. But nice shot.
Who taught you that shot?
Coach Gronic.
Dicky Gronic?
Dicky Gronic is your coach?
He can't play hockey.
Dad, Sid Gronic.
Sid Gronic's good.
Sid Gronic's very good.
He's one of the best,
if he could stay out of prison.
What was that?
That's something I call the "J-shot".
- Teach me.
- Come here.
You're big enough to handle this now.
- We got to go.
- Be with you in one second.
Hold on a minute.
Say the guy's coming down
right here, defensive man.
Bring it on the stick's toe.
Back to the heel.
Now cut loose.
There you go. Nice shot.
Very good.
- I still don't get it.
- I'll show you when I come back.
But I need it for today's game.
Teach you when I come back.
But, Dad, I want to...
"Butt Dad"?
Did you just call me "Butt Dad"?
Is that the kind of thing
Coach Gronic teaches you? Butt Dad?
By the way, that would
make you Butt Boy. Bye.
Bye, Butt Family.
See you in a while.
Love you guys. Bye.
All right.
Oh, man.
First period's behind us.
Forget about it.
God knows I'm going to try.
I know you're just kids.
And we're really here to teach you...
...fair play and sportsmanship
and all that crap.
But I am so tired of Looking
up at that scoreboard...
...and seeing that we're behind
the Devils again...
...and again...
Lighten up, Dad.
Sorry.
History is made by winners.
Conquerors.
Barbarians.
Now, I want you to go out there...
...and wipe the ice
with their filthy butts!
All right?!
Play clean.
Have a good game.
Come on, guys.
Let's whup them!
Hey, Rory.
Hey, sweetheart. Miss me?
Let's nail it this time. You're
getting tighter. We're almost there.
Come on, Charlie!
Oh, man. Oh, man. Oh, man.
- Good luck, Jack.
- Afraid I'm going to need it.
- See you Later.
- All right, man. Thanks.
I hope it's not bad.
How bad is it in there?
Yeah, that's what I thought.
- Something smells good...
- You promised him.
Why'd you go and do that, Jack?
I've told you. If you're not going
to be there, don't say you will be.
You know how I knew you promised him?
He kept Looking at me up in the stands.
And after about the 40th time...
...I realized he expected you
to be there.
I don't care if you get too busy
or you flake out on me.
Well, I care, but I chose it.
I married you. I'll deal with it.
He didn't choose this.
One of these days,
Charlie will score his first goal...
...and you won't see it.
Like you never saw his measles...
...or the time he jammed
Fig Newtons into the projector.
Those things only happen once.
Don't, Jack. You said enough.
Hey, buddy.
How'd you guys do?
Got killed. Eight-zip.
I'm really sorry I didn't make it.
I'm really sorry, man.
Hey, look...
I got to talk to you about something...
...that's really important.
You know how you always wanted to be
the next Wayne Gretzky?
I always had a dream too.
Ever since I was about your age...
...I just really wanted
to be a great musician.
I just wanted to be a real player.
I wanted to make a living
doing what I Love.
And I really want to make
a nice Living for you, me and Mom.
Well, see...
...that might be...
...kind of starting to happen.
That's good, Dad.
Yeah, it is good.
And it's really, really good
for you to have a dream.
Tricky part here is sometimes...
...if you're not careful, you can...
...I don't know, kind of turn
into kind of a...
Selfish jerk?
All right.
Yeah.
So are all musicians really flaky?
Yeah, basically, I think.
All the drummers.
Okay, here's an idea.
I've thought about this one
for a while.
You, me, Mom,
we go to the cabin up at Pine Top.
We have a real Christmas vacation,
just us.
No phone, no TV, no band, nothing.
What do you think?
Really?
Will you teach me the J-shot?
I will teach you the J-shot.
Hold on a second. No TV?
Yeah, I know.
I was thinking about that too.
Maybe a Little TV.
Okay, cool.
So, eight-oh...
How bad was it?
I think Coach Gronic popped a vein.
- Here, hon, let me get that bag.
- I forgave you last night.
- Then can you grab one of these?
- Nope.
What's in there, a dead body?
No, it's just, like, Gameboy,
batteries, food, clothes...
We'll only be up there
three days.
We could get snowed in for months.
You'll thank me.
Grab the phone, will you?
Hello?
Yeah, sure, hold on a second.
It's for you.
John Kaplan?
I'll meet you in the car.
I just got this...
...kind of unbelievable phone call.
The record company heard our tape...
...went nuts.
Oh, honey!
Dad, this is awesome!
That's great!
- You think?
- What's the matter?
Well, the head of Asylum
has to see us.
He'll only sign one act.
There's 3 other bands...
...and he'll only sign us
if we go to his party in Aspen.
When?
Tomorrow.
Christmas?
I know.
There's got to be another time
he can see you.
According to Kaplan,
there is no other time. This is it.
Don't worry. Forget about it.
It's too hard, because...
Hold on a second.
I don't even want to go.
Let's see if we can work this out.
I mean, how Long
do you have to play?
I don't know. That's a good point.
Could maybe play a half an hour.
Don't play a whole set. They can tell
how you sound in a few songs.
Get out...
Maybe I could borrow Mac's car.
I could drive back.
That way I could be back
by Christmas night.
But I'll miss Christmas Day for sure.
Here.
What's this?
I gave this to you.
I don't want it.
This is going to be a great gig, man.
We'll rock this guy's house and
blow it apart. He'll have to remodel.
This is the one. I'm telling you.
This is a good thing.
- So when do you want me to pull over?
- Right now. Over here.
What am I, crazy? I got a great wife.
I got a great kid.
I'm not living this life anymore.
I'm going home.
Good.
You're making the right decision.
If they like us now,
they'll like us next week.
It's Christmas.
They can mail us the contract.
- How do I explain this to the guys?
- Are you nuts? Watch this.
Hey, guys.
- The gig's off.
- Thank you, Santa.
Nobody wanted to come. Lou's mom
wants to cook Christmas dinner.
Yes, Merry Christmas, boys.
I'm going to see my family.
This is great! I'll take
the 40 to Highway 2, and then...
Why don't you take the car?
It'd be so much faster that way.
Oh, man!
Now, where did he say that spot was?
There it is.
Come on, Mac.
Merry Christmas.
Have a great vacation.
Thanks.
Feet are for walking!
Frost. You big butthead.
Forget it, Rory.
He's no fun to pick on anymore
since his old man died.
Yeah? Well, it's time
he gets over it.
I never even met my old man.
- Want a lift home?
- No, I'm not going home.
You shouldn't walk in the road.
No one's around. It's all right.
Okay, well, I'll see you tonight.
Why?
I'm baby-sitting.
Well, not baby-sitting.
You're not a baby.
We can hang out
while your mom Christmas shops.
All right.
See you later, Charlie.
Sorry, dude!
Damn it!
I can drive through it.
I can get it.
Really, it's okay.
No, it's not okay. Hold on.
It's okay. It's okay.
Charlie, it's okay. It's okay.
I miss him too. I miss him too.
It's going to be okay, honey.
I promise.
Here you go.
Thanks.
How you doing, little bear?
Fine.
I'll stay home. We'll hang out.
No, Mom, I'll be fine.
I've done my Christmas shopping.
I'm good.
No, me and Mac'll be fine.
Want a marshmallow?
What do you want? One?
Two?
Maybe four?
Maybe all 500?
Thanks, Mom.
Your dad loved this guy.
They even played together
a couple of times.
Nice to know he had
time for someone.
Come on, Dad, put the head on.
Now, okay, Natalie,
pack some snow in there.
Let's go in the house.
Come on. It's getting cold.
I'm going to get you now.
Gotcha!
I'm home!
Hey, I'm home.
Man, it's cold!
Could you open up?
Charlie, it's me.
It's Dad!
Could you get the door?
What?!
No.
No way!
Can't be.
What is that?
Hey! Come on!
That's disgusting!
Chester, it's me.
It's me. It's Jack!
- Chester just peed on a live snowman!
- No cranberries.
What?
This is not happening.
This cannot be happening!
Can you let me in?
Charlie, look...
I'm having kind of a bad day here.
Come on, Mac.
This ought to do it.
Kiddo, it's getting cold!
That's my branch!
Okay, come on.
Come on. Come on!
This is unbelievable.
When I was a human, nothing.
Now all of a sudden
you want to play?
Come on, Chester...
That's the coldest wedgie
I ever had.
Well, look what we have here.
Let me pick up my...
...arm.
Is that a snowplow?
Excuse me. Hello!
I'm on the front of your plow,
Mr. Snowplow Driver!
Big headache!
Wonderful service.
Thanks for the lift.
Come on, shake it off.
It's just snow.
Great.
Talk about your separation anxiety.
Hey, you!
Ball number two.
Don't just sit there.
Give me a hand.
Okay, that's it.
Come on, no.
Get the mitten out of my eye.
No, that's my nose.
That's my cork!
There we go.
Got it. Got it.
Now watch it.
Okay, one, two...
...three!
I'm getting dizzy.
Man!
Something's missing.
Nice work, ball number three.
Man, it's bad enough
my ticket got punched...
...but to come back like this!
It's embarrassing.
I've put myself back together
after some rough nights...
...but this is ridiculous.
Don't panic.
Just act real casual.
Yeah, just act casual.
Wait a minute. I'm a snowman.
There you go.
Hello there.
Maybe Charlie's snapping out of it.
It's good to see these again.
Let's get you bundled up.
It's going to be a cold one.
Back off!
- What's going on?
- I'm so glad to see you.
Have you been watching
the Sci-Fi Channel again?
Gabby, you're back.
Charlie's been great all evening.
- What happened here?
- I was thinking the same thing.
It's the snowman.
I saw it. Terrific job!
No! Mom, he's alive!
Well, I'd better be going.
Not so fast.
Honey, are you sure you're okay?
I swear, he came to life,
waddled into the street...
...and a snowplow took him away!
Well...
...I guess it got a cab back, then.
What?
How...?
Thanks, Mac.
You're welcome.
Good work!
You look good.
Oh, man...
...I never did fix that.
Oh, man, why me?
Why a snowman?
I mean, could the universe
really be that unoriginal?
I don't know.
Is it the name Jack Frost?
Because if that's it,
that's not even clever.
I should accept it.
I'm a frozen freak of nature.
I just want to know why.
I'm just...
Could you just give me...
Could I just have some kind of sign?
What the...?
Well, at least it's not a snowplow.
Sid? Sid Gronic?
Sid, is that you?
Been hearing great things about you.
Seriously.
Sid, come here!
Wait, wait, wait!
Where you going?
Wait.
Thanks for the help, Sid!
All right, wait a minute.
I just have to pull this together.
When I saw my reflection, I denied it.
That was my denial period.
I go off on Sid.
Clearly, I've had my anger period.
That's what they say you do.
First you deny, then you go into anger.
I just have to accept it.
I accept I'm a snowman.
Sid!
All right.
Come on.
Just a regular snowman, huh?
We'll see about that.
Who are you and what do you want?
Talk, or I'll
turn you into a puddle.
I know you're alive.
So you better...
...start...
...talking.
That thing's hot.
What are you doing?
I'm your father.
Okay, you're grounded.
Come here.
Charlie, it's me! Dad!
Honest.
- I can explain everything.
- Get away from me!
I can't explain the part about
me being a snowman, but...
Go pick on someone as dumb as you.
As dumb as me?
- Good one, Rory.
- Give it back!
Spin move.
Right here, right here,
right here.
Oh, look.
It's our little hero.
Don't worry about him anymore.
He's not even in the game.
You're so immature.
Come on, give it back.
Give it back.
Did you guys see that?
So you do want a piece of me.
Thought you learned your lesson.
Kid, how's it going?
What are you doing here?
Guess it's time for a
refresher course.
Okay, snowball fight?
You picked the wrong area
to mess with me, and that's snow.
Three balls, two sticks,
one cork nose. Snowman? No.
Much, much more.
I am the Wizard of Blizzard!
Now run!
Run, you little mountain goats!
Boy, the old Wizard
could use a nap.
I'm out of gas.
Run!
Let's get him!
Hold up.
He's not going anywhere.
Where are you going to go now, Frost?
Be careful!
Help!
Just hold on!
I'm coming. I'm coming!
I'm coming, Charlie!
I can't hold on!
Hold on. I'm coming.
What are you doing?
Don't you worry. I'm coming!
Told you I was coming.
You know, sometimes
it's good to have a big butt.
Let's get out of here!
There he is!
Let's get him!
Come on, guys.
Go, go, go!
You steer.
I'll scream.
Do something!
Zap them into ice.
Zap them into ice? Get real!
I don't even have pockets.
Duck, Charlie!
That'll cool him off.
Hold on!
I am holding on.
You the man!
No, you the man.
I'm the snowman.
We're safe!
Okay, we're not safe.
What's going on?
Nothing.
I don't think so.
All right!
Look out!
Time to split.
I'll see you at the bottom.
I slimmed down!
Shredding.
Big air!
Right behind you, Frost.
Pull your vehicle over.
Snowman!
Perfect.
Here we go.
Catch some air, baby!
This is awesome!
Look out.
Look out for the trees!
- Carving time!
- I'm behind you!
Big carves.
- We were ripping!
- That was cool.
- That was great.
- Did you see that?
One time, thank you.
Did you see me going down?
The nice thing about big...
...balls, excuse me, is look how
you can move around them.
I like the roundedness.
You can throw your weight over
on this side of the board.
- Better than being skinny.
- Hold on.
- You almost got me killed.
- I saved your butt too, pal.
So I'm supposed to believe
you're my dad?
Do me a favor. Go easy on me.
Because I'm having trouble
dealing with it myself, okay?
You know...
...he died a year ago.
I know. I was there.
You're nuts.
Great. He doesn't believe me.
It's not enough I got...
...these stick arms
and this humongous butt.
And that dippy walk.
What's wrong with my walk?
Is it that bad?
All right.
So you're my dad, huh?
How did my hamster die?
Your hamster? Heart attack.
Vacuum cleaner.
Well, yeah, but...
I'll bet it had a heart attack
on the way in.
All right.
What's my hockey position?
That's easy. Right wing.
- Wrong.
- What? You're a wing.
They moved me to defense last year.
Oh, man, Charlie-boy.
I'm sorry. Defense is a good position,
but you're a natural winger.
Hold on.
What'd you call me?
I said...
..."Charlie-boy".
That's what I always call you.
Charlie-boy.
Dad?
Dad!
It is me, Charlie.
I'm back.
Hold on.
This is really weird.
I just hugged a snowman.
You played on the magic harmonica.
What? Magic harmonica?
I thought you made that up!
So did I.
You know what?
Let's go home and talk, okay?
You know, catch up on stuff.
And you know something?
I'm hungry.
Boy, your mom is going to be jazzed
we fixed that sink.
Snow peas.
You should like these.
Level with me. How is she?
She's good.
She moved a picture
of you next to her bed.
What's that?
Mom's home.
She can't be!
She can't see me like this!
Nobody can see me like this,
but especially her.
Just a minute, Mom!
Honey, why are all the windows open?
Please, you gotta help me.
It's freezing in here.
Charlie, what's going on?
Science fair project.
You're kidding.
Why is the floor wet?
Well, the science fair project...
...it's about what it's like
to live in an igloo.
And Eskimos have
wet floors, Mom. Duh.
It's freezing in here.
What's going on?
And what's with all the food?
I got kind of hungry.
Three bags of veggies?
I got real hungry?
What?
There's something I need to tell you.
Well?
This science fair thing?
It was Natalie's idea.
Okay. Just tell Natalie
the next experiment's at her house.
Grab some towels and help me
with this, okay?
I think I need a day off.
Frosty the Snowman
Had to hurry on his way
But he waved goodbye
Saying, "Don't you cry,
I'll be back again some..."
You said the snowman spoke to you?
Yes, he did.
And he knew my name.
Were there any other witnesses?
There wasn't any other witnesses.
In the Rocky Mountain states...
...folks may not be in for
a white Christmas after all.
Charlie, honey,
did you fix the sink?
Why is the snowman facing this way?
I turned him...
...to even out his tan.
Was that Sid I heard talking on TV?
What was he talking about?
Nothing, really.
I saw him yesterday at the bank...
...and he told me
that you quit the team.
Charlie, you didn't tell me.
You want to talk?
About what?
I don't know.
This hockey thing...
...or how you're doing in school.
You tell me.
I'm trying to watch the weather.
Gabby, it'll be all right.
I'm here now.
Well...
...sort of.
Oh, boy.
I invented the backdoor escape,
okay? What's up?
Since you showed up, Mom thinks
I'm nuts, Rory Buck wants to kill me...
...and I'm pretty sure
my dad's a snowman.
So what's the problem?
I know yesterday was a rough day.
Things'll get better.
Quit following me.
You're a snowman!
People will see you and cut you up
into ice cube trays.
If that's the danger of hanging out
with you, I'll take the chance.
- Fine.
Really fine.
Fine as wine...
What?
I can't believe
I let you talk me into this.
I think we look kind of...
...you know, cute.
Somebody's going to hear you.
Check it out.
What's up with that?
Dude, he ditched us for a snowman.
I saw on the Geology Channel...
...they can actually turn pine cones
into a homemade explosive device.
How's your science
project coming?
What science project?
- The one about what it's like...
- Isn't that Charlie?
Hey, Mac.
Finally come in for
some Christmas lights?
I need a cup of that house paint
you call coffee.
You got it.
So what's going on?
Know when I promised not to bother
you for any talks with Charlie?
I lied.
I need you to talk to Charlie.
Nobody knows about this place.
I come here to think.
Well, it's really cool.
I've been here a lot this year.
You know, Dad, I'm sorry
I gave you back the harmonica.
Don't worry about it.
You were mad. I'd be mad too.
Can I ask you why you
quit playing hockey?
- Hockey's not that great.
- Yeah, right.
The last person you see every night
is Wayne Gretzky on your wall.
Tell you what. We're here.
Let's work on the J-shot.
I don't think so.
I see. It's like that.
Looks like I'm working
out by myself...
...even though I haven't
played hockey in...
...a year.
I'll find a rock to use as a puck,
seeing as I'll be playing...
...all alone.
All right, all right, I'll skate.
Just stop bellyaching.
We'll get our nice balance.
We'll get set up.
Man, this was a lot easier
when I had legs.
We're going to stay nice and relaxed.
Real loose.
We come through. We snap our wrist.
Just before we do that...
...I make this little move here.
That goalie could sue me
for whiplash.
That's pretty cool.
A little thing I call the J-shot.
Now, let's play some hockey.
Are you looking for the power?
Then bring it, son.
That's a J-shot, dude!
- I did it!
- That's you! That's all you!
But I didn't score.
Life is full of setbacks.
Look at me.
I'm a snowdrift with arms.
You can give up, or you can
keep firing the puck, bud.
What do you think?
All right, give me the puck.
There's a lot of wood!
Fakes left, fakes right.
Man, nice shot. All right!
You got the...
All right!
- Dad, are you okay?
- Yeah, I'm good.
I think you got the J-shot.
I think you got the J-shot down.
All right, come on.
Let's go home.
Come on, come on.
You played great.
Thanks for teaching me the J-shot.
I want to see you use it.
You got to get back on the team.
- No, I don't think so.
- I do.
You're letting your friends
and yourself down.
- But wait a second...
- No "buts".
Let's talk about schoolwork.
What about it?
I saw your report card.
You've got serious jamming to do.
What's this, a lecture?
Now you're giving me a lecture?
See? It's kind of scary.
Think how the snowman must feel.
And I'm worried about your mom.
- Why?
- Has she hung any Christmas lights?
Not a lot.
Yeah, I know. Hardly any.
Why are you telling me this?
You've got responsibilities now.
You'll just have to face them.
You got to watch out for Mom...
...and straighten things out
with your friends.
I'm only 1 2 years old.
I can't take all this!
I might have pushed it
a smidge too hard.
Hey, hon.
I'm heading to the Shiverfest.
You want to come along?
No, thanks.
Or if you'd rather,
you can come with me.
I'm going to go caroling with
Mrs. Wilkins and the neighbor ladies.
They did a good job this year.
Do you like the tree?
Want a balloon or anything?
Or pretzels? They've got...
Wow! Check out these snowmen.
Finals of the father-son snowman
building contest begin in 5 minutes.
Five minutes.
Mom thinks I'm going nuts, doesn't she?
No, no, no.
She's just a little concerned,
that's all.
So...
...what's going on?
You wouldn't believe me
if I told you.
Come on, let's check out the band.
Talk about a tough gig.
It's freezing out here.
Why don't you play music anymore?
I kind of lost the groove.
The groove?
Playing with your dad, I never
thought about what music was.
Music was life. It was...
...just...
...like breathing, really.
So natural.
After he died...
...music became...
...a job.
You know, Jack always said to me:
"It should never feel like work".
He was your best friend, huh?
Your dad was the real deal.
Do you think he wanted me
to be a musician?
More than anything, he wanted you to be
whatever you wanted to be.
He didn't care what that was.
Just whatever made you happy.
Really?
Really.
Think you'll get the groove back?
Someday, maybe.
I hope so.
Man, you got your shopping done, folks?
You got 10 hours till Christmas Eve...
...and it's already 55 degrees.
Could get up to 70 today.
Snowplow drivers got a day off.
It's hot enough to melt a snowman.
Although, you know,
good news for Sid Gronic.
Speaking of hot,
here's a little Billy Idol for you.
"Hot in the City"
on central Colorado's classic rock.
Hey, man. Good morning.
I've been doing a lot of thinking
about what you said.
You're right.
The J-shot,
it wasn't just about hockey, was it?
What do you think?
There's something I got to do.
Hey, guys.
Hey, Coach.
I'd like to get back on the team.
What?
You ditched us, Charlie.
Remember?
Do we have to bring
your snowman buddy along too?
There'll be no mention of snowmen
in this car.
I don't know, Charlie.
Well, I do.
I say we let him back on the team.
Everybody deserves a second chance.
Go get your stuff.
Go, Charlie!
They let me back on the team.
Listen, Dad, about last night, I...
It's okay, buddy.
What time they drop the puck?
- 1 1 :30. But you don't got to come.
- I know that.
He's talking to the snowman again.
What'd I say, Tuck?
Shake it, Charlie!
Remember...
...arms and wrists.
Straight but relaxed.
Thanks again, Dad.
See you after the game.
Man, this sun is brutal.
I mean, I am literally
melting my ass off.
I didn't come
all the way from the hereafter...
...to miss another one
of my kid's hockey games.
Chet, listen.
Chet, I know
we've had our differences...
...but I got a game to catch.
I really could use your help.
So how are we going to do this?
Go. Yes, Frost!
He's good.
Come on, okay. Here we go.
Come on.
Maybe you got some friends
who are Huskies.
You know a Saint Bernard?
Score! One-nothing.
And here we go again.
That's right, Chet.
Take your time.
Wonder if there's gonna be any
cute poodles there.
That's what I thought!
Good pass, Charlie!
Go, Spencer! Go!
He scored!
Score by Spencer Jordan,
with an assist by Charlie Frost.
Mountaineers, one.
Devils, one.
Okay, so far, so good.
Stay cool.
Almost there.
All right, Frost!
Get it back!
Go, Charlie. Go!
Yes, Frost. Go!
One hundred yards
of piping-hot asphalt.
Bad day to be a snowman.
This could really sting.
Okay, baby steps, baby steps.
Man, this is getting hot.
This is hot.
This is hot on my tootsies.
My tootsies is burning.
Holy habanero!
This is hot.
Let's speed her up!
Leaping Lawrence of Arabia!
I am so hot!
All right, all right, Frost!
All right, Charlie!
Turn it around!
Frost, yes, go!
The J-shot, Charlie-boy, come on!
Arms and wrists.
Straight but relaxed.
Nice going, butthead!
Outstanding! Yes!
My man! Yes!
You got the power!
Way to go, Charlie.
The ice is now open
for all free skates.
Outstanding game.
What can I say?
You rock, dude.
You're melting.
You gotta be crazy to come here.
I couldn't miss your big game.
Let's get you on the ice
so you can cool off.
That's not going to work.
I got to get you someplace cold.
I won't lose you again.
I'll be back!
Someplace cold.
Mom?
No cutting!
It's okay, ma'am.
He's my son.
You need to drive us somewhere
right now.
- Honey, I'm working.
- You've got to!
What's wrong?
- He's melting.
- Who's melting?
The snowman's melting.
That's just the way it is.
If you drive us to the mountains,
he won't melt.
I'm not driving you
and your snowman anywhere.
I know this has been hard for you.
You don't understand, Mom.
Dad's the snowman.
What?
I'm sorry, but he made me promise
not to tell you.
Honey, he died a year ago.
You'll just have to accept that.
No, Mom, you don't understand.
It's gonna be okay, Dad.
Do me a favor.
Watch out for snowplows.
Charlie's run away with the snowman.
Really.
Oh, my!
Look out! Move, move!
Excuse me. Look out.
- He could be anywhere.
- Mac, it's a kid and a snowman.
You and me.
Once and for all.
I'll fight you any other time.
Just not now.
I don't know who's more stupider,
you or your snowman.
Excuse me.
Did you just say "stupider"?
What kind of word is "stupider"?
Who said that?
I did...
...you little baggy-pants snow punk.
What the heck is it?
Not what. Who.
And he's my dad.
I knew it!
Mitch and Pudge thought I was crazy.
But I saw you that day.
You throw a mean snowball.
Okay, okay, okay.
Just chill, kid.
Don't have a meltdown.
Look, Rory,
it's too hot down here.
If I don't get him up to
the mountains, I'll lose him.
He does look pretty bad.
Come on.
You know what it's like
not to have a dad.
It sucks.
It sucks big time.
All right.
Snowdad's better than no dad.
Let's go.
Come on.
Come on, let's go!
That was good.
Merry Christmas.
Come on.
- Good Luck, Charlie!
- Thanks!
Okay, what's the snowman look like?
Like a snowman.
He looks like a snowman.
Three balls, two stick arms,
a cute cork nose.
What do you think he looks like?
I'm trying to do my job, that's all.
Can you help me?
Five-eight.
White.
Caucasian.
Stocky. He's sort of well-built.
I'd say 500, 550 pounds.
Could you estimate an age?
We're here!
Ready? On three.
I'm with you, buddy.
One...
...two...
...three!
Fresh powder. My favorite!
My balls are freezing.
I never thought I'd say that
with a smile.
Come on, Dad, let's go.
Let's go get you warmed up, buddy.
I was so busy trying to make my mark
on the world, I didn't...
You are my mark on the world.
Did you find him?
Charlie's sleeping.
He had one heck of a day.
Who is this?
Where's Charlie?
He's right here at the cabin.
Why don't you come get him?
Jack?
It's Christmas!
Merry Christmas, Dad.
Merry Christmas to you, bud.
You know what?
I think this is
the best Christmas I ever had.
You know that night you came back?
It was because of your harmonica.
I wished it.
I wished you would be here
for Christmas.
Thanks for giving me a second chance
to be your dad.
Now, there's something
I have to tell you.
It's time for me to go.
What?
No. I'm not going to let you.
You've got to get on with your life.
No, come on.
It'll get cold again, Dad.
You'll see.
Winter's just barely started.
And when it gets warm?
We'll go to South America.
Summer here is winter there.
What about Mom?
Mom needs you.
What if I need you?
I will always be there.
I promise.
As long as you hold someone
in your heart...
...you can never lose them.
Ever.
You let me back into your heart,
and that took real courage.
You did it. And if you can
do that, you can do anything.
I'm so proud of you.
If you ever need me,
I'll be right here.
You just call me.
Here.
I love you, Dad.
I love you, Charlie.
You're gonna be a good man.
Okay now, let me go.
Oh, honey!
- I'm sorry I didn't believe you.
- It's okay.
Oh, my God!
You look so...
You look so great.
Sing me a smile, Jack.
Every time
We say goodbye I cry a little
I love you so much, Gab.
I love you too, Jack.
Goodbye.
Goodbye, Jack.
Charlie-boy...
...we had us a time, didn't we?
Yeah, we did.
Love you.
Bye, Dad.
Goodbye.
Bye.
I will always hear you.
Watch Movies, TV Series and Live Sports
Signup Here -> WWW.ADMITME.APP