HAM:
I can't believe the show starts
in half an hour
and Achmed's late.
Maybe he drowned trying
to visit Bin Laden's grave.
(laughing)
Security.
That's my name.
Don't wear it out.
Bubba J?
Yeah. Well, gotta go.
Beer break.
Wait. Achmed's late.
Keep an eye out for him.
Which eye?
Where could he be?
He went from dead terrorist
to Hollywood diva.
I'm telling you,
the fame went to his skull.
Achmed? No way.
(engine revving)
(evil laughter)
-== [ www.OpenSubtitles.org ] ==-
(cackling)
Huh?
(growls)
(bleating)
Ah.
(engine revving)
(evil laughter)
Achmed's here.
I'll go park his car,
since there's
no law against drunk parking.
Thanks, Bubba J.
Good job.
(loud belch)
(belching continues)
Whoa. Is that a hybrid?
It's the AchmedMobile,
you idiot.
Just be careful parking it
or I keel you.
Didn't hurt.
And whatever you do,
don't touch the red button.
Got it. Touch the red button.
Yes.
(alarm blaring)
(gasps)
ANNOUNCER:
Ladies and gentlemen,
please welcome to the stage,
Jeff Dunham!
(cheering and applause)
Thank you.
Thank you so much.
(cheering continues)
Ladi and gentlemen,
it's absolutely great to be here
in lovely Richmond, Virginia.
(cheering)
And, you know, we--
I've been doing this show
all over the country,
just having a blast
here, there and everywhere.
The fans are great.
But we've also been taking
my show around the world.
We've been doing shows
in South Africa, Australia,
three tours of Europe
and the U.K.
Now they're talking
about taking me to China.
Wha-What?
(laughter)
How am I going to do
my show in China?
All I know is, if I do
do my show in China,
there's a big chunk of my act
I'm going to have to leave out.
(laughter)
You'll recognize it when I do it
here this evening.
(laughter)
But it is interesting going to
some of these foreign countries
and doing press interviews,
because some of the reporters
have done their
homework and care,
others just don't.
For example, I was in London
talking to a guy
and he was like,
(British accent):
"All right, so ventriloquism--
have you eliminated every other
possibility of employment?"
And I have to go, "No, this is
what I've done my entire life."
I've never wanted to do
anything else.
I started very young.
I was eight years old,
I was in the third grade,
Christmas, 1970.
Got my first dummy.
There's Mom and Dad and me
under the tree right there.
You can see how
proud my father is.
(laughter)
But for years
I'd look at that picture
and I'd think, why does he have
that expression on his face?
And then if finally hit me, duh,
look where the dummy's hand is.
So...
(laughter)
Yeah, that's creepy.
So I started doing shows
very early.
All the way through
elementary school, junior high,
high school, college.
And this is what I wanted to do.
This was the future I saw.
I saw it.
There were a few people
that didn't see it.
For example, girlfriends.
They'd realize I was sincere
about wanting to talk
to dummies the rest of my life
and they would dump me
immediately.
I couldn't see what they saw
until a few months ago.
I was sitting down
with my three daughters,
and we were looking
at the yearbooks
from my junior high
and high school years.
My daughters were horrified.
Why? Let me explain.
I started getting paid for doing
my shows in the seventh grade.
And I knew
that if I was going to be
a professional ventriloquist,
I needed a professional photo.
Now, my parents were supportive,
but they weren't going
to shell out the cash for that.
So I thought, how am I going
to get a professional picture
of me and the dummy taken?
And then it finally hit me--
school picture day.
(laughter)
(applause)
Don't believe me? There's
seventh grade right there.
There it is.
(cheering and applause)
Look at that. That is
Justin Bieber hair, damn it.
(cheering)
So ninth grade came along and
I decided to do the same thing.
This was the bicentennial year
in our country-- 1976.
I was a patriotic lad,
but I didn't want to dress
like Uncle Sam.
No, apparently I wanted
to dress like
a Fourth of July
picnic table cover.
(laughter)
(applause and cheering)
You know, the funniest thing
to me
about that photo is the fact
that I have braces.
Why is that funny?
Well, the rest of my life
I'm going to be talking
with my mouth shut,
so what's the point?
(laughter)
I know most of you look
at these photos and think,
this is the saddest human being
we've ever met.
Did he have any friends?
Yes, I did.
Here we are sitting
in my bedroom one day.
So now I had about 15 minutes
in my show.
I knew I wanted to add
something else-- some variety.
I thought, music? Yes.
Something cool.
Rock and roll guitar?
No, something cooler.
I'll play the trombone.
(laughter)
There is so much wrong here,
ladies and gentlemen.
Let's start
with the least obvious,
and that's my dummy
up in the corner
listening to me play
the trombone, but...
Now let's talk
about fashion, shall we?
(laughter)
How did my mother even let me
out of the house?
And this wasn't some accident
on a Saturday morning
where I accidentally threw on
the wrong clothes.
This was an outfit I wore
to school regularly.
I don't know why I didn't get
beat up on a regular basis.
I must have gone to the store
and said,
"Do you have any pants that
don't even go with themselves?"
(laughter)
This next photograph--
I don't remember
how it happened.
All I know is that we went to
the professional portrait studio
and this was the family portrait
that hung in our living room
this big, for years.
(laughter)
(cheering and applause)
(whistling, cheering, applause)
You know, maybe... (laughing)
And the weird part is my parents
had family and friends over
for parties a lot.
And this was hanging right there
in plain view.
No one ever said anything.
They must have thought,
"Well, the food's good.
Let's go to the mentally
ill people's house."
And now it's time
to move on to college
and the intellectual years.
I don't even,
I don't even know why.
You know, the photographer
should have
just fallen over laughing.
I don't...
I looked like Sherlock Holmes
with a dummy.
I don't know what that is.
You know, I love my parents
very much,
and they have been married
for 56 years now.
(audience cheering)
And they are a perfect example
of how a marriage can work.
On the other hand, I've recently
gone through something
that I never thought I'd go
through, never considered it,
never even thought it
a possibility.
I'm recently divorced.
I'm a single father now,
but I always try and look
for the silver lining
in the dark clouds, and one
of the silver linings
about getting divorced is that
I got to pick out my own house
because someone else has
the other house now.
As for my act,
there's an old guy,
who long before I got married,
warned me of the institution.
And now I guess he can say,
"I told you so."
Ladies and gentlemen,
please help me welcome
my oldriend Walter.
(audience cheering)
Holy crap, will you shut
the hell up?!
(Jeff chuckles)
You, too.
Are you all right?
No!
What's wrong?
I'm pissed.
Why?
I have no idea.
Well, have you ever
thought about being happy?
Yeah.
What happened?
It pissed me off.
What would happen
if you were happy?
Your show would suck.
(laughter)
You know, Walter,
just once
I think you should
try being happy.
You're an idiot.
(chuckles)
See? What the hell
is wrong with you?
When I call you
an idiot, and you smile,
like I gave you cake.
Do you want to be
in a good mood?
Not if I'd look like a moron
like you, no, thank you.
I've seen you walk by
perfect strangers
and go, "Oh, hello.
How are you?
Hoo-hoo-hoo!"
So?
That makes mothers hide
their children from you.
You don't think
I should be nice
to strangers?
You know, even dogs
sniff (bleep) first.
(howling with laughter)
Well, I'm just happy
to be here tonight.
Not in the winter. Holy crap.
I don't know.
I hate being cold.
I even got cold
in Vegas last week.
Oh, Vegas, yeah. You
took your wife there.
Oh, yeah.
You know, Vegas
has become
a great vacation
spot for families.
Oh, yeah, sure, yeah.
That makes sense.
Take the family to Vegas.
Yeah.
'Cause kids love whores.
(laughter)
"Look, Mommy,
there's a place with poles
like where you used to work."
(laughter)
So, Walter, you been
doing anything fun
since we got here?
Uh, yeah. What did I do today?
I did something fun.
What?
I signed up Achmed
to be an organ donor.
Oh, that's funny
as hell right there.
I'm getting sick
of that guy.
I think all this fame
is going to his head.
Why?
He's been doing all
the typical Hollywood stuff.
Like what?
He's been dating
a goat half his age.
Oh, yeah, an actual goat.
He even got her fake teats.
Oh, yeah, all six of 'em.
Walter, a goat
only has two.
(chuckles)
How sick is it that you
actually know that?
What, are you so lonely now,
you're checking out
barnyard animals?
You know, they're
called "petting zoos,"
not "heavy petting zoos."
Come on.
What's her name?
(bleating):
Ma-a-argaret.
Will you...?!
(laughter)
Can we change the subject?
Sur-ur-ure.
I'll change the subject,
all right.
I heard you talking
about something
you hadn't really discussed
onstage yet.
Right.
Okay.
So you're talking
about the divorce now.
Yeah.
All those years
of being married,
and now it's over.
Yeah.
So, all those years
of raising the girls,
and now the family's
broken up.
Right.
So, no more marriage?
Nope.
No more wife.
No.
What's it like?!
(loud, uncontrollable laughter)
Oh, please let me live
vicariously through you!
(laughter)
Walter, divorce is
not a good thing.
Oh, you can't lie
to me, (bleep).
So what happened?
What happened, Walter,
is that, unfortunately,
in our country these days,
more than 50% of marriages
now end in divorce,
and sadly, mine
was on that side
of things.
(voice breaking):
You know, Jeff, I never thought
I'd say this to you,
but you're my hero!
Come on.
What's it like
to wake up in the morning
and not hate your life?
To not think,
"Uh-oh, here she comes!"
Ugh!
You can leave your toilet
seat up all the time!
I'd hot-glue mine open,
for God's sakes...
and then (bleep)
in the backyard.
Just because I could.
Walter, divorce
is painful.
Oh, yeah, like
a deep-tissue massage.
(screams)
(sighs contentedly)
So how long's it been?
Almost three years now.
Oh, okay. So, you
dating anybody now?
Matter of fact, I am.
Oh, good. Female?
Well, you never know.
Sometimes that's the problem.
"Honey, I got bad news
and I got good news.
"Bad news is,
I want a divorce.
Good news is, I'm
on your team now!"
(audience laughs)
Come on, let's knit, Mitch!
So this girl you're dating,
is she the same age as you?
No.
Oh. So she's older.
(gasps)
Younger.
Yes.
How much younger?
It doesn't matter.
Yes, it does.
Come on. Does she
have nice boobs?
That don't hang down
past her knees?
¶ Do your boobs hang low,
do they wobble to and fro? ¶
(audience laughs, whistles)
¶ Can you tie 'em in a knot? ¶
¶ Can you tie 'em in a bow? ¶
¶ Can you throw 'em
o'er your shoulder ¶
¶ Like a Continental soldier? ¶
¶ Do your... ¶
All right!
Where do you hear
a song like that?
I didn't hear it,
I wrote it, dumb(bleep).
Bet you never sung
it to your wife.
Every morning!
(wheezing laugh)
That's not funny.
Oh, even the dog
laughs at that.
(imitates dog howling)
(imitates dog whining)
That last part was me.
I know.
You know, I saw an old photo
of you and your wife.
Your wife's quite beautiful.
You saw an old photo.
Yeah, I'm kidding, I know.
I married a petite,
young, beautiful thing.
Yeah.
She was eventually eaten
by the woman I live with now.
(à la Fat Albert):
Hey, hey, hey!
You're just flat-out saying
your wife's overweight.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no.
She's under-tall.
Have you ever had
a weight problem?
Only when she sat on me.
Will you...?
Aah!
Get off of me!
Actually, it's more like this:
(imitating an echo)
Hello? ...o...o...o...
It's dark in here!
...here...ere...ere...
I found your keys!
...keys...keys...keys...
I am not kidding.
Then she farted and
unlocked the car doors.
What does your wife think
when you do things like this?
I don't care.
Well, I know you care
enough about your wife
to take her on some
of these trips.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, she loves
going on these trips.
I know she loves
window shopping.
Not in Amsterdam, she didn't.
(cackles)
Ha! Because in Amsterdam,
there's hookers in the windows!
I love that city. Did you
know that in Amsterdam,
you can legally
purchase marijuana?
I, uh... yeah...
I did know that.
Do you know where?
Coffeehouses.
Coffeehouses!
It's my favorite
coffee place ever!
I'd like a latte and a doobie.
And 19 dozen donuts,
thank you.
(laughter)
(applause)
Not long after that,
we went to the UK.
You enjoyed it there.
Yeah.
Did you like the
city of London?
I don't know,
I got confused one day
standing in our hotel lobby.
Why?
Some big old black guy
walked in to me
and started speaking English
with a British accent.
I thought I was in
the Twilight Zone.
I swear, some big old black guy
walks up to me and goes,
(posh British accent):
"Oh, good afternoon, sir!"
I'm like, who the hell is making
you talk? What the hell?
Then we went to Ireland.
I got all confused there.
Why?
Everybody's last name
starts with "O."
O'Malley, O'Shea.
I think I know
a black Irish guy.
Who's that?
O'Bama.
(laughter)
I don't think Obama's Irish.
Maybe he's half-Irish,
half-African American.
I can't wait to meet him.
I'm going to walk up and go,
"Hey, top of the morning
to you there, dawg."
(laughter)
"How's your health care
hangin', yo-yo?"
"Hey, that last election
was a bee-yotch."
Say good night, Walter.
Thank you.
That's Walter.
There we go.
(cheering and applause)
Well, ladies and gentlemen,
there is a terrorist
amongst us.
(cheering and whistling)
And I don't know
how it's gotten to the point
that I can actually give this
introduction, but here it is.
Please help me welcome
the most beloved terrorist
throughout the world--
Achmed the dead terrorist.
(cheering and applause)
(evil laughter)
Greetings, infidels!
(cheering and whistling)
And for the folks who
might not know, Achmed,
you are a suicide bomber.
Yes, I am.
Don't stand too close.
(evil laughter)
And I think a lot of us
might like to know
how you feel about
the death of Osama.
(gasps)
I didn't do it.
(laughter)
I didn't say you did.
Oh, right.
Yeah, uh-huh.
(laughing):
All right, yeah, yeah.
Wait a minute.
Did you have something
to do with it?
Yeah... No!
Yes... No, no, no... no!
That Navy SEAL training
was just for laughs.
(giggling)
Wait a minute, you
trained as a Navy SEAL?
No... Ye... No! No!
How did you know?
Who said anything
about Navy SEALS?
I'm just a simple
little terrorist.
Stop interrogating me!
Damn it, you're good at this!
(laughter)
You're not going to tell
anyone, right?
Tell them what?
Oh, thank you.
I will tell you what
I do know, though.
What's that?
When Bin Laden died,
there were no 72 virgins
waiting for him.
(laughter and applause)
No?
No. It was some kind
of misunderstanding.
Turned out, it was one
72-year-old virgin.
(laughter)
Osama is stuck forever
with Bea Arthur.
(laughter)
And Osama and I agree that
that 72 virgin thing
is highly overrated.
How's that?
Who wants to hear
this 72 times?
"Ooh, ow, oh! Boo-hoo-hoo!
You're gonna call me, right?"
(laughter)
Wait a minute.
Wait a minute. You
communicate with Osama?
Of course.
How?
On Face-Shot-Off-Book.
(laughter)
So...
(cheering, applause
and whistling)
So, where... where
exactly is he?
Well, he won't say, but
I'm pretty sure it's Hell.
Why do you say that?
Well, they get cable,
but they only get one channel.
What?
The Oprah Winfrey Network.
Wait a minute.
(laughter and applause)
Come on, Achmed, a lot of people
love Oprah.
Were you ever
on her show?
No.
She doesn't love you.
And also I know why
they would not show
the photo of dead Osama.
Why is that?
It's a little
hard to explain,
but when he was killed,
he was dressed up like Cher.
(laughter)
Well, since he's dead,
do you think they're going
to come after you now?
(laughing)
Wait, what?
Well, you're
a terrorist.
Yeah, but I suck at it.
You know, the military
has the deck of cards
of the 52
most wanted terrorists.
Are you one
of those?
Yeah, but I'm in
the Go-Fish deck.
(laughter)
Well, what did you think
about them burying him at sea?
I think it's cool
that he could
end up anywhere.
What do you mean?
That is one episode
of SpongeBob I got to see.
(laughter)
(cackling)
I wrote that. I keel me.
Achmed, since you're
clearly a terrorist,
are you Muslim?
No. Scientologist.
(laughter)
But you used
to be Muslim?
No. Look at me.
I'm too extreme.
I was Catholic.
(laughter)
Really?
And Methodist...
What?
Buddhist...
And Baptist...
What?
And Capricorn.
Wait a minute.
What are you doing?
I'm trying to offend
as many infidels as possible.
(evil laughter)
And speaking of offending,
do you know what that
idiot Peanut did to me?
What?
He stole my ShamWow.
(laughter)
It's not funny!
Silence!
(laughter)
Wait for it.
(uproarious laughter)
(cheering)
I keel you!
(cheering and applause)
That's fantastic.
Let's do it together.
One, two, three...
ALL:
I keel you!
They're talking to you.
(laughter)
So, Achmed, are you
enjoying Richmond?
Oh, I love the nightlife here.
Uh, what part of
the nightlife?
They have live sex shows.
Really? Where?
In the hotel room
right next to mine.
(laughter)
What?
That's my room.
(cheering and whistling)
Next time you should
get a partner.
(laughter)
Can we talk about
something else?
I'm trying to throw up,
but I don't have a stomach.
(laughter)
So, look,
Walter and I
were talking earlier,
and you've gotten
pretty famous now
lately, haven't you?
Oh, yes.
And I think very soon,
I'm going to need
my own posse.
That's with an "O."
(laughter)
Po-o-o-sse.
P-P-oo...
..osse.
Posse.
Why are you explaining that?
In Amsterdam, they thought
I said something else.
(laughter)
I don't even like cats.
(laughter and applause)
P-P-o... P-P-o...
P-P-o...
P-P-P-o...
P-P...
P-P-P...
How am I doing that
with no lips?
(laughter)
(cheering and applause)
That's what she said.
(cackling)
(laughter)
I can't believe you did that.
That's what she said.
(laughter)
Will you stop it?
That's what she said!
I don't like this.
(squealing):
That's what she said!
(laughter)
How long is this?
(high-pitched squealing):
That's what she said!
(loud laughter and applause)
Think about it.
So you were talking
to Walter earlier?
Damn it!
Yes, and I said,
"I'm going to call
you my bee-yotch."
That means "bitch."
I know that.
I'm sorry.
I'd been watching
Pimp My Camel.
eem like you've been
in a pretty good mood lately.
Do you know why?
No.
Because like
Santa Claus,
I have been making
a list of people
to kill twice.
Santa doesn't kill people.
He does if he's
Terror Claus.
Terror Claus?
I've never heard of him.
¶ Oh... ¶
¶ He kills you
when you're sleeping ¶
¶ He chokes you when you wake ¶
¶ He knows if you are Catholic
or Jew ¶
¶ So denounce
your infidel faith. ¶
(laughter and cheers)
That's terrible.
But catchy!
Have you heard
of the Terror Bunny?
No.
He hides Easter bombs.
Look, Mommy.
(mimics explosion)
That's even worse.
I know.
Thank you for noticing.
What do you want,
more stinking knock-knock jokes?
That might be better.
Okay. Knock-knock.
Who's there?
Me. I keel you again.
(laughs)
You're such an idiot.
You keep answering
the door!
Where I am from,
the game we teach
our children is,
when someone says,
"Knock-knock,"
you shut (bleep)
and hide.
So, Achmed, did your
parents have much
to do with what you do now?
Well, uh, I guess so.
My father was
a suicide bomber.
Oh, so you guys
are a lot alike?
Well, I have his eyes.
In a box.
And I like to hide them
wherever Walter is sleeping.
That way, when
he wakes up,
it scares
the crap out of him.
WALTER (distant):
You son of a bitch,
I'll kick your
ass right now!
(applause and cheering)
Is that case locked
from the outside?
Yeah. Why?
'Cause he still scares
the crap out of me!
So, Achmed,
do you have
any good memories
of your father?
Uh, for my eighth
birthday,
he got me a puppy.
That's good.
No, it turned into a disaster.
Why?
Because sometimes my father was
a very confused man,
and that day
my mother told him
to go outside and blow up
some party balloons.
Yeah?
(sadly):
And that's how I got
a dog with no legs.
You had a dog
with no legs?
Yeah, he was great.
I had him
for many years.
Oh. So what'd
you call him?
Seriously?
Seriously.
What?
I had a dog with no legs.
What did you call him?
Seriously?
Okay, you're
a comedian, right?
Yeah.
I had a dog
with no legs.
(sinisterly): Ask me again.
What'd you call him?
I didn't call him anything
because he could never come.
It's not funny!
Achmed, that's, that's, like,
the oldest joke ever.
(voice breaking):
Yes, but in my case,
it was true.
AUDIENCE: Aw...
Thanks.
Could he do
any tricks?
He could roll over.
It not funny because if there
is any kind of an incline,
he couldn't stop himself!
He looked like a runaway
can of pinto beans
rolling down a hill.
It was the only time
I ever saw a cat
actually laugh.
Meow. (hiccups)
Meow. (hiccups) Meow. (hiccups)
(faster) Mw. (hiccups)
Meow. (hiccups)
(gasping groan)
What was that?
I killed
the (bleep) cat.
So, Achmed, when did
you know you wanted
to be a suicide bomber?
After talking
to my guidance counselor.
Your guidance counselor?
In high school.
High school?
Al Qaeda High.
Al Qaeda High?
¶ Oh... ¶
¶ All hail
to the Al Qaeda High ¶
¶ We blow up,
then we die. ¶
Everybody!
Wait, wait, wait. This is
your high school?
Who was your mascot?
The next guy
on the list.
Oh, it was, like,
"Go, team!
(mimics explosion)
Next.
So how were
the cheerleaders
at your school?
Oh, we didn't even
have girls.
No girls?
No. But for some reason,
we had a girls' restroom.
I see.
And one day, Omar and I
snuck in there to explore.
The girls' restroom?
Uh-huh.
And what'd you find?
A couple of strange
and wonderful things.
Like what?
Well, we found a machine.
And if you put
two shekels in it,
a small missile would come out.
A missile?
Well, I think it was.
It had a little white fuse.
And it must have been
a very special missile,
because it was lightly scented.
And then you could put two
shekels in the other machine
and get the bonus
accuracy package.
What?
It had wings.
And you used these missiles?
With confidence.
Really?
Always.
(laughter)
(audience whistling)
Achmed, I've never heard of
anything like this before.
Ooh, do not lie to me, infidel.
I've been to your house,
I've seen in your
cabinets and drawers,
many of these
missiles hidden away.
It looks as though you
are preparing for war.
Every four weeks, it feels
like that, I'd say so.
So your soldiers have
synchronized their time clocks.
You could say that.
Well, good luck in your
battles, my friend.
Thank you.
I fear there will
be much bloodshed.
(laughter)
What are the infidels
laughing at now?
I'll explain it
to you later.
I keel you!
, I have a surprise
to share with you tonight.
(gasps)
You're going in the closet?
No, and by the way, the, the,
the phrase is "coming
out of the closet."
Oh, congratulations!
No, I'm not coming
out of the closet.
You're going to continue
to hide the truth?
I'm not hiding in anything.
So everyone knows now?
Congratulations!
Achmed, I have a girlfriend.
(gasps)
Does she know?
Maybe she will
like this one guy.
There is no one guy.
Then there are many guys?
You are a whore.
Now, you should be stoned.
Achmed...
What would your
mother say?
I'm not a whore.
Of course your mother would
say she's not a whore.
I'm straight.
Straight, crooked,
we do not need
to know such graphic details.
(laughter)
I mean, I have a girlfriend.
Not for long.
Not when she finds out
about your many boyfriends.
Whore!
Will you please listen
to what I'm saying?
I do not talk to whores.
You are dead to me.
You're dead to all of us.
(applause and cheering)
So, Achmed...
I'm not listening!
¶ La-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la! ¶
Achmed, there's someone here
I want you to meet.
(gasps)
One of your whore boyfriends?
I think not!
No, I think this is someone
you would like to see.
(gasps)
Is it a woman?
No.
I already have a goat.
This is a surprise guest.
(gasps)
Ryan Seacrest?
Nope.
Damn it!
Look. What I want you to
do is, I just want you
to look over there while
I'm getting him out,
so you won't peek.
Okay.
Just look over there.
O... wait a minute.
When I'm not looking,
are you going to keel me?
No.
That's actually a good way
of doing it, you know.
Kinda old-school,
but effective.
It's like "Hey, look at that!"
(chokes) Aaah...
No, just look over there, and
don't look back until I say so.
Okay, whever. This is kind
of like Christmas, huh?
Yeah.
Just look over there.
Okay.
And don't peek.
Right.
Not gonna peek.
Just stay over here.
Now?
No!
Okay!
(muttering)
(applause and cheering)
(screams)
(yells)
Who the hell is that?
(British accent):
Hello, Father.
(audience whistling, applauding)
(prolonged cheering
and whistling)
It's your son, Achmed Junior.
AJ?
That's right.
ACHMED:
Wait... I thought
you were dead!
Surprise.
This is great.
Hey! What happened
to your face?
Oh, yeah.
My bad.
Achmed, he's your son.
Look at him. What do you see?
Well, he does have my eye.
(cackling laugh)
Actually, I do. Yes, I do.
Why do you sound
like Elton John?
When you were separated
after the accident,
he was raised in England.
Did my mum miss me?
Uh... yeah. I don't know.
What the hell.
How do you not know?
Oops.
What's wrong
with your leg?
Nothing!
What's wrong
with my leg?
I don't know.
Can you fix this?
No, I don't think so.
Damn it.
Don't look at me.
Sorry.
Um, we're going to get
Marnel to help us.
What?
Marnel, he works for me.
I know Mar, Mar,
Marnel!
Come fix my leg!
(murmuring)
Thanks.
(applause)
He's kind of cute.
Okay, moving on!
Wait a minute. How do you
not know who his mother is?
I had 46 wives,
you idiot.
They all dressed the same,
and their faces were covered.
How'd you tell them apart?
The numbers on their backs.
That's terrible.
I know, Mother's Day
is a bitch.
And so are most
of the mothers.
That's not funny at all.
"Atall"?
Who is "Atall"?
Was she your mother?
I don't remember
a woman who was all
bulgy-eyed like you.
Bulgy-eyed?
Well, look at him.
Well, you're not
exactly squinting.
At least my face is balanced.
You manage to look asleep and
terrified all at the same time.
Achmed, he's your son.
Well, the apple
doesn't fall far
from the tree,
and apparently this one got
run over by a (bleep) lawnmower.
You caused the accident.
Accident? It was
a huge explosion,
with great fire
and destruction.
You didn't mean for
it to happen.
I did, too!
You did not!
No, li...
Oh, (bleep).
Marnel!
Son of a bitch!
Are you talking
to me now?
Fix it right, or
I kick your ass.
Marnel!
Come back!
My arm is stuck
in my pelvis, you (bleep).
(laughter, applause
and cheering)
He can fix my
pelvis anytime.
Shut up!
Okay, look.
Okay, look. So the explosion
you were talking about,
how did it happen?
Very precise and
careful planning.
Not exactly.
I said shut up!
What happened?
Nothing.
He was putting gasoline
in his scooter.
So why was there an explosion?
(bleep) happens.
He was using his cell phone.
Really?
What?
While putting gas
in your scooter.
You know that's dangerous.
Well, it was your
mother who called.
ACHMED JR.:
Really?
I don't know.
What was her name?
42.
And you guys haven't had
any contact since?
Not much. He's a bad son.
I am not.
Tell him what you sent
me for my birthday.
It was an honest mistake.
What'd you send him?
He sent me a bottle
of skin lotion.
(laughter)
He made it worse.
What'd you do?
I sent him back
half a bottle.
(laughing)
(laughter)
You know, maybe you should
try and patch things up.
Looks like he needs more
than a (bleep) patch.
But I'm here
for a reason.
What, a skin graft?
Sorry, I'm all out.
(bleep)! Marnel!
Come fix my (bleep) leg!
Get duct tape,
you (bleep)!
(chuckling):
He actually brought duct tape.
(laughter and cheering)
He's kinky, too.
Shut up!
So, Achmed, do you know
why AJ is here?
Well... Wait a minute.
This isn't some crap about
owing child support, is it?
That bitch!
Whichever one she was.
No, that's not...
This is bad,
'cause I've seen the crap
that you're going through
and I don't know how you
can afford even a T-shirt.
Thank you.
Did I say that
just how you wrote it?
(laughter)
Yes. Thank you.
Okay. Good luck
with the judge.
I hope he's fair.
Actually the judge
is a woman.
You're (bleep).
(laughter)
Okay, listen, you...
Achmed, you're
getting hostile.
Of course I'm
I'm a terrorist,
you idiot.
You piss me off,
I keel you.
Would that really
solve anything?
Pretty much, yeah,
I think it does.
Okay...
I have nothing
in common with
my own son.
Well, just talk to him.
How?
I don't know,
like you would anybody.
Okay, W.T.F.
O.M.G.
I mean O.M.A.
(laughter and applause)
And you have no idea
why he's here?
To start his training
as a terrorist.
No, Father,
that's just it-- I don't want
to be a terrorist.
(gasps) But I want you
to be just like me.
Well, I'm not,
and I won't be.
Achmed, can you accept that?
(voice breaking):
I guess I can try.
And, AJ, what if he
doesn't accept it?
I keel you.
That's my boy!
(cheering and applause)
He's purple, he's wacky,
he's been around for a while.
Please help me welcome
my buddy Peanut!
(cheering)
How you doing, Peanut?
Doing pretty good.
How about you?
I'm fine.
That's good, that's good,
that's goo-ood.
(cheering)
Wow.
You like it here?
I love it here.
It's beautiful.
It's sold out.
The place is paid for.
We must be on
an Indian reservation.
And these are all Indians.
Look, Peanut, first of all,
the more politically
correct term these days
is Native American.
Oh, yeah.
I certainly wouldn't want
to piss 'em off.
They could try and scalp me,
but all they'd get
is a fishing lure.
(laughter)
I guess that is a little less
confusing of a term, though.
What?
Native American.
Why?
'Cause when you say Indian,
you don't know which one
the hell they're talking about.
What?
Is it the ones
that go...
(war chant):
¶ Hy-ya, hy-ya, hy-ya. ¶
or the ones that go...
(Indian accent):
Thank you for calling
customer support.
(laughter and cheering)
But in this case, I'm talking
about the ones that go...
(war chant):
¶ Hy-ya. hy-ya, hy-ya. ¶
(deep voice):
¶ Hy-ya, hy-ya. ¶
(high-pitched):
¶ Hy-ya, hy-ya... how. ¶
Do you know what
that chant means?
No, but I think it means,
(chanting):
¶ I forgot the words,
hy-ya, hy-ya. ¶
You know, we have plenty
of Native Americans
here this evening.
Oh, goody. Let's play craps.
(laughter)
What? They've got
the reservations
and the casinos
and making millions of dollars
every day hand over fist.
They're laughing
all the way to the bank.
Oh, that's what it is--
they're laughing.
(chanting):
¶ Ha-ha-ha-ha-ha. ¶
(laughter)
All right, Peanut, time
to introduce the next guy.
Oh, dude, does he have
to come out here?
Why not?
He's a talking jalapeño!
(audience cheering)
Go ahead.
On a stick-k!
So?
How random is that?
Well, José, has been in
our act for years.
I know. And when
folks see us,
do you know when
they say the best
time to watch José is?
When?
When they're drunk
off their asses.
In fact, isn't that how you came
up with him in the first place?
I don't know.
But I do know
that's when
I came up with you.
You jerk!
Just introduce him.
Ladies and gentlemen, here is
José Jalapeño on a Stick!
(audience cheering)
Good evening, José.
Hola, Señor Jeff.
How are hue...?
Whoops.
What the hell
was that?
Were you trying
to say, "How are you?"
and it came out,
"Haa-a-ah?"
Why is that we speak perfectly
and you (bleep) up?
(laughter and cheering)
I don't know.
Would you like me
to help you?
I'm fine.
Come on.
Follow me
one word at a time.
No.
Come on.
Just do it.
Do it!
Okay.
How...
are...
you-you?
Good-good.
All right.
(audience cheering)
How are you, José?
I don't know.
It took too long.
Actually, I'm
excited, señor.
Why are you excited, José?
Probably 'cause
you're holding
his stick.
Do you have
to do jokes like that?
It's just weird to me
that in front of everyone,
you're holding
José's stick-k.
Any suggestions?
You should at least
take him out to dinner first.
It's just a stick.
Maybe it's actually a handle.
A handle?
Yeah, you could use José
as a weapon.
To hit with?
Yes!
I want to go back in the box.
No, this is awesome!
"What happened to Frank?"
"He got whacked
by a jalapeño."
On a stick.
Yes!
Think about it.
You'd be wielding
a Mexican whacker.
On a stick.
Yes!
Look, you know how
Batman had his sidekick Robin
and one of their weapons
was a batarang?
Yes, of course.
Oh, dude.
What?
You just showed
your geek.
(sniffs)
And it smells
like loser.
You're not
a loser, señor.
Thank you, José.
Suck-up.
Muppet reject.
(laughter)
Hey, he can drop you,
and then I'll throw down
a couple avocados.
and we got guacamole!
I could still burn your ass.
Good point.
All right.
(chuckles)
Look...
Wait!
The Batman thing just made me
think of something.
What?
If this comedy business
doesn't work out for you,
Yeah?
you can be
a crime fighter.
A crime fighter?
Yes. You could be
Dunham Man...
with José, your trusty
sidestick. (chortles)
I see. So you're saying
I would be a superhero.
Mm, ...ish.
"Ish"? It this
like Jewish?
No, José, you're not Jewish
'cause then you wouldn't be
José Jalapeño.
You'd be Hymie Jalapeño.
On a Bagel.
(laughs)
Where would you
hold him, then?
(chortles)
In the hole.
I am not touching that.
No, you probably never have.
(audience gasps)
Okay.
This sucks!
So we're a crime-fighting
team, señor?
Yes!
What kind of crime
do we fight?
Illegal aliens.
I think there's
a conflict of interest.
Look, so you find the illegals,
whack 'em on the head with José,
and every time
José hits someone,
he yells...
Olé.
Yes!
Pretty cool, huh?
I guess so.
But, um, do I get
a costume?
What?
Anything from those
earlier photos.
I'd go with the
red shorts, señor.
Yeah, then you'd be
Ugly-Ass Crackerman.
(laughs)
Okay, look, for this
crimefighting thing,
how's José gonna dress?
Well, he needs
a disguise.
Is difficult to
hide a big stick.
I'm not saying
anything.
Of course not.
You're still holding it.
José, I don't know how
you put up with this.
I have nowhere else
to go, señor.
What?
He was evicted.
Evicted.
Really?
Yep.
Sí.
You were evicted?
Why didn't you come
to my house?
(snickering)
JOSE:
Ask Peanut.
Why didn't he come
to my house?
We told him you loved
eating Mexican food!
I was afraid for my life.
So where'd you take him?
Taco Bell!
(laughter)
That was really mean.
I know!
Hey, look. What about moving
all of José's stuff?
Achmed tried to
rent a truck.
No bueno.
(chuckles)
So did Walter help?
He couldn't because
of his war injury.
Walter has a war injury?
Yeah, he strained his thumb
playing Call of Duty: Black Ops.
So you and Achmed
did everything.
Yep. José didn't lift a finger.
(laughing)
(laughing):
'Cause he doesn't have any!
Hey, ever met José's sister?
Don't do it.
She's really hot.
(shrieking with laughter)
I'm just kidding, José.
I know. You're
more into fruit.
Hey!
Hang on, you guys.
No, you hang on.
What?
Why are you
laughing at him?
'Cause he's funny.
Oh, he is, is he?
I know what you're doing.
I'm not doing anything.
You're giving José
the better insults.
I'm just listening.
Don't give me that crap.
We all know
this is all you.
If you get any closer, he's
going to whack you with me.
Whack.
Olé!
And that's José Jalapeno
on a Stick!
(applause and cheering)
Hey.
Wait a minute!
I... I forgot to
tell José something.
Open the box back up.
Immigration!
Stop it!
Well, he pissed me off.
Well, Peanut, it's about
time to end the evening.
No way!
What?
I got one more thing to do.
No, the show's about over.
No, it's not!
I got one more thing.
What?
Okay, look.
Just trust me on this.
I have a new hobby.
A new hobby?
Yes.
What is it?
I am now a ventriloquist, too.
No, you're not.
Yes, I am.
That was...
that was pretty good.
I know. Compared to me,
you suck.
Really?
Let me show you
how it's done.
Well, you need a dummy.
He's in the box.
You have a dummy?
Over here, señor.
He's... in the box?
Yeah.
Right next to José.
Can I get him out?
Yep.
JOSE:
Don't touch my stick.
Careful!
What?
(whispering):
He's really ugly.
JOSE:
He is ugly, señor.
He is nasty-looking.
JOSE: He's so scary,
I wet my stick.
But he's right here.
He's the only
other guy in there,
check it out,
look, look, look!
All right, let's see
this, here we go...
(cheering and applause)
I thought
you said he was ugly.
He is!
He looks a little like me.
No... he looks
a lot like you!
This isn't funny.
Then why is everyone
else laughing?
JOSE:
I laugh, too, señor.
I laugh so hard
I crack my stick.
Do you know how to work this?
Of course I do.
You know there's a little
lever down there...
I know.
You grab onto the lever....
and you pull on it...
I know!
Now, do you have
a hold of the lever?
He's got a hold of something.
See, I can do this, too!
Fantastic.
How are you,
little ugly Jeff?
Not good.
Wait, wait, wait a minute.
You're going to
call him Ugly Jeff?
Oh, no, no, no, no.
Little Ugly Jeff.
Is there any other name?
Uh, Little Ugly Ass Jeff?
I like that.
JOSE:
Me, too, senor.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Wait a minute.
I would prefer you didn't
use the word "ass."
Oh, I didn't really.
It's all one word.
Little Ugly Ass Jeff.
Ass Jeff, Ass Jeff,
I am Ass Jeff.
See? It's good.
JOSE:
Bravo!
Gracias.
De nada.
This is ridiculous.
(cheering)
So, how are you,
Little Ugly Ass Jeff?
I'm sad, Handsome Peanut.
Wait, wait a minute.
Handsome Peanut?
Yes, Peanut is very handsome,
unlike you, Ugly Ass Jeff.
He is me.
Good point.
I hate my ugly-ass self.
All right.
He said he was sad.
I heard him.
Why are you sad,
Ass Jeff?
Because I'm a loser.
Yeah, that is sad.
And he's ugly.
And I'm ugly.
Thank you.
Is okay.
Will you stop this?
That's a shame,
Little Ugly Ass Jeff.
I have no idea how I
made it this far in life.
Me neither.
No one does.
I suck.
All right.
Maybe you can make up
for your loserness
by having a good personality.
No.
Doubtful.
No way.
I'm sorry.
Me, too.
Okay, look.
You guys really
think this is funny.
Oh, yes.
Sí.
Definitely.
The truth hurts.
Okay.
I'll tell you what, Peanut,
you think that's funny?
I have something here
that you're going to like.
What?
Just trust me.
You're going to love this.
What the (bleep) is that?
Hi, look at me!
I'm a little idiot!
(high-pitched giggles)
That is not funny.
Yes, it is!
No, it's not!
I think it is.
JOSE: Me, too.
LOL.
Shut up!
You guys have been awesome.
Thank you. Good night.
(rock music plays)
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org