All were transported?
You have my car...
THE BOOGEYMAN
Peace.
Can a man like you know peace?
Why not?
Peace.
Enjoy your retirement...
Ciao, John.
Santino.
May I come in?
Of course.
Happy hunting!
Welcome to the Continental of Rome.
How might I be of assistance?
I would like a room.
You are here for the Holy Father?
Good morning, Mr. Wick!
FORTUNE FAVORS THE BRAVE
Excuse me, miss.
Mr. Akoni is waiting.
Thank you for seeing me.
Why dont you go to
entertain our guests...
while I freshen up my makeup.
Okay, Signora.
What could I do without you,
Cassian?
Having a tough night?
Can I buy a drink?
Not him... me.
Be seeing you.
Not if I see you first.
Sorry, I fucked up.
My God, John.
You dont get it.
.
Go. I'll finish this.
Be seeing you.