Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
Subtitles by explosiveskull
Resync by GoldenBeard
[OCEAN WAVES CRASHING,
SEAGULLS SQUAWKING]
[DRUMS BEATING RHYTHMICALLY]
[DRUMBEATS STOP]
[♪♪♪♪♪]
[KNOCK ON DOOR]
MAN:
Hey, kiddo.
- What?
- MAN: I found something.
- You gotta check this out.
- [SIGHS]
"Jumanji."
Board game?
Who plays board games?
[SCOFFS]
[SIGHS]
[♪♪♪♪♪]
[MAN ON TV SCREAMS]
[GUNFIRE ON TV]
[GAME CRACKLES]
[DRUMS BEATING RHYTHMICALLY]
[DRUMBEATS STOP]
[♪♪♪♪♪]
[GAME CRACKLING]
SPENCER:
Parry. Parry.
Evade. Blam.
Uppercut.
Head slam. You're dead.
Strike. Strike.
Counterstrike. Head slam.
- Ka-pow.
- [PHONE BUZZES]
MAN [IN GAME]:
Get ready. Fight.
I got it.
[MAN IN GAME
READS ON-SCREEN TEXT]
[PHONE BUZZES]
[SCOFFS]
"...Benjamin Franklin,
"and it was this sense
of national exceptionalism
that fueled the spreading
wildfire of westward expansion."
Spencer? Honey?
Aah! Mom, what did we say
about the knocking?
I'm late for work. You going
to your father's after school?
- Yeah, probably.
- Don't forget your EpiPen.
Please, remember,
the world is terrifying.
Be careful of everything.
I love you
more than life itself. Bye.
- See you Sunday night.
- Okay.
[♪♪♪♪♪]
- Later, Mama.
- FRIDGE'S MOM: Eat something.
I can't.
I gotta go meet Spencer.
- Spencer Gilpin?
- Yeah, Spencer Gilpin.
He's, uh...
He's been tutoring me.
- He's helping get my grades up.
- I love to hear that.
- Little Spencer Gilpin.
- Yeah.
- Your grades gonna be okay?
- That's why I'm getting help.
I'd hate for you
to get dropped from the team...
I'm not gonna get dropped
from the team.
It's... It's gonna
be fine. Okay?
Mm.
[CAMERA CLICKS]
Okay.
That's cute, right?
Yeah.
[♪♪♪♪♪]
- Yo.
- Hey, Fridge.
Why you wearing a raincoat?
- What do you mean?
- I mean, it's not raining.
Oh, well, it might.
I mean, you never know
what's gonna happen.
- [SQUIRREL SQUEAKS]
- [SPENCER SCREAMS]
- Oy vey.
- What the hell, man?
Do you mind?
Can we speed this up?
Freak House makes me
very uncomfortable.
Here you go.
- You proofread everything?
- Yeah, I proofed it.
And I gave it a beginning...
and an ending
and s-some in the middle.
I would've done it myself,
if I had the time or whatever,
- but...
- Yeah, it's no big deal.
Hey, man, I was thinking, so...
I mean, it's been really fun,
doing your papers
and your homework and stuff,
but I don't know
what you're doing this weekend.
- I was thinking maybe we could...
- This weekend. Yeah, ah...
- Hey, Fridge.
- Hey.
You need a ride?
- I'm going with her.
- You know what?
That's actually better for me,
scheduling-wise, too, so...
See you later, Refrigerator.
Sorry. Sorry.
What up, girl?
Whatever.
It's not like
I was your best friend
for your entire childhood.
- That's fine.
- MAN: What'd you say?
[GASPS]
Uh, nothing, sir.
Oh, that guy is super weird.
That poor man.
So awful what happened
to those people.
I was talking about the kid.
What are you doing out here?
I was just talking
to my friend.
You should be more careful
where you loiter,
you hear me?
Yes, Mr. Vreeke. I hear you.
This world swallows up
kids like you.
[♪♪♪♪♪]
[PEOPLE CHATTERING INDISTINCTLY,
BELL RINGS]
BETHANY: It's been over two
hours since I've posted,
and he hasn't commented.
He hasn't even liked it.
- You saw it.
- LUCINDA [ON PHONE]: Yeah, gorge.
I don't know
what his problem is.
Thank you. It's not like
I post all the time,
just enough
to stay relevant.
But it's cute enough
for Noah to...
Hey, there's
some rando behind you.
- Hi.
Bethany, did you just make
a call during a quiz?
Yeah. But I finished
my quiz already.
Oh, okay. Well, have you noticed
that other people haven't?
- So?
- Oh, I'm sorry. Let me back up.
You're aware there are other
people in the world, right?
[STUDENTS CHUCKLE]
Look, um, you know,
I'm dealing with something
right now,
and I'm no happier
about it than you are.
I'm having a crisis,
and Lucinda, I mean,
she's supporting me
as a woman,
and it feels like
maybe you should too.
- Just hang up the phone.
- Okay, I'll wrap it up.
- Bethany, hang it up now.
- Two minutes and we're done.
And that's detention.
[♪♪♪♪♪]
TEACHER: All right, keep
those arms pumping.
Let's go!
Bethany, you're late.
Sorry.
I heard she broke up
with that football guy.
This could be
your opening, Fussfeld.
- [WHISTLE TWEETS]
- We're gonna practice
catching and throwing.
So partner up and grab
a football. Let's move!
Hey, Martha.
Martha. You can't
play catch by yourself.
Pair up.
Come on. Let's go.
No. No, I'm good.
Okay.
[STUDENTS CHATTERING
INDISTINCTLY]
You have to participate
just like everybody else.
Otherwise,
why are you even here?
It's a requirement.
- Martha...
- I think it's pointless.
Gym class is not gonna get me
into Princeton,
and I don't understand
the obsession with throwing
a ball into a hoop
and, "Touchdown, five points!"
Okay. There's a lot wrong
with that, but first of all...
It's physical activity,
which is good for you.
With other people,
also good for you.
And if you try it,
you might even have some fun.
Fun. That's what
we're doing here? Fun?
This is school.
We are supposed to be
learning things that matter.
- Okay, Martha...
- We don't have
a lot of time in this life,
and I personally
don't wanna waste it on being,
like, a gym teacher.
- That... That came out wrong.
- Yeah, it sure did.
That's detention.
That was hard-core.
Badass.
Spencer Gilpin?
Have a seat, Spencer.
Miss Mathers?
"And it was this sense
of national exceptionalism
that fueled the spreading
wildfire of westward expansion."
Does that sound familiar,
Mr. Gilpin?
- It does not.
- It's the last sentence
of Anthony's paper
on westward expansion.
And, coincidentally,
it's the last sentence
of your paper on westward
expansion from last year.
That's interesting.
MATHERS:
Is it?
I think so. I mean,
what are the odds of that?
Slim.
MATHERS: Yeah, you also
used the same metaphor:
"the spreading wildfire,"
in your papers
on the Boston Tea Party,
the Battle of Gettysburg,
and the women's suffrage
movement.
It's so hot in this room.
Anthony, I know how much
you need to pass my class,
but this is not
how you do it.
- I will not tolerate cheating.
- Cheating?
I didn't... I didn't...
I didn't cheat.
It was my fault.
I made him do it.
You made him...
have you write his paper?
Yeah.
Mm-hm.
[PEOPLE CHATTERING INDISTINCTLY]
Look.
I'm sorry, okay?
No, no,
it's not okay.
What the hell, man?
You got me kicked off the team.
Yeah, well, you could've
gotten me expelled.
It's not like you're the only
one who's living dangerously.
- Living dangerously?
- SPENCER: Yes.
This is the most dangerous thing
I've ever done in my life.
And now look at me.
I'm paying the price.
[BELL RINGS]
PRINCIPAL:
Well...
isn't this a fun group?
Welcome to detention.
Yes, Spencer?
I wanna say that I'm sorry.
- Thank you.
- Bentley, all I did was make...
Bethany, please.
You're all here for a reason.
You know what it is.
But this is what
you should be thinking about:
Who you are...
in this moment in time,
and who you want to be.
You get one life.
You decide
how you're gonna spend it.
[♪♪♪♪♪]
Fortunately...
there is no better place
for self-reflection
than detention.
Get up, everybody. Let's go.
[SWITCH CLICKS]
We are turning this
into a new computer center.
But before we do,
it has to be cleaned out.
These old magazines are bound
for the recycling plant.
But they have to be prepped
before they go.
It seems all the staples
must be removed.
Whatever you don't finish today,
you finish tomorrow.
- Tomorrow's Saturday.
- Because I wouldn't play?
- I don't think that'll work.
- That's fair.
- Shut up.
- So I suggest you get started.
Choose your weapons.
Hey, what the hell
they need with a bowling ball?
[GROANS]
Seriously, no reception?
- Okay, can today get any worse?
- Are you gonna help?
Or are you too pretty?
I'm too pretty.
[SIGHS]
Hey. I was watching you
with Coach Web today.
I wasn't watching you,
I wasn't...
Not, like, in a weird way.
I just...
I was in the room.
We're in the same class.
Um, but I thought you were
saying some really smart things
about why P.E. sucks
and, um...
about other subjects.
Thanks.
Yeah.
Yo. What's this?
[♪♪♪♪♪]
- I don't know.
- FRIDGE: What is it, like,
some type of old-school
Nintendo or something?
I don't think so.
I don't recognize it.
[GONG PLAYS
ON TV]
"A game for those
who seek to find...
"a way to leave
their world behind.
[MUSIC PLAYING ON GAME]
Jumanji."
Staples, people. Staples.
"Jumanji"?
What does that mean?
I have no idea.
Never heard of it.
[GAME CHIMES]
Hm...
Uh, which one do I pick?
I don't know. I don't
think it matters that much.
"Jefferson 'Seaplane' McDonough.
- Pilot and rascal."
- [GAME BEEPING]
- It's not working.
- Okay, try another one.
"Franklin 'Moose' Finbar."
Hm.
He sounds like a badass.
And he's a zoology expert,
which is awesome.
[GAME CHIMES]
- You pick.
- Okay.
"Dr. Smolder Bravestone."
[GAME CHIMES]
Bethany, you in?
[SIGHS]
Fine.
I'll be...
Shelly Oberon...
the curvy genius.
[GAME CHIMES]
Hey, yo, Staples, come on.
It's your turn.
Uh, no.
- No, thanks.
- Wait. Just for a few minutes?
It'll be fun.
She's not big on fun.
Okay. Fine.
[SIGHS] This may be the
lamest thing I've ever done.
I highly doubt that.
[GAME CHIMES]
[JAGUAR ROARS,
ELEPHANT TRUMPETS]
MAN [IN GAME]:
Welcome to Jumanji!
[DRUMS BEATING RHYTHMICALLY]
[MONKEY SHRIEKS]
What's going on?
[ELEPHANT TRUMPETS]
[ELECTRICITY CRACKLES]
I think it's shorting out.
[WHIMPERS]
GIRL:
Unplug it!
[ELECTRICITY CRACKLING]
- [ALL SCREAM]
- Whoa!
What's going on?
What's happening to your hands?
- BETHANY: What's wrong with you?
- I don't know.
[YELLS]
Spencer!
Oh, my God!
MARTHA:
Oh-oh-oh...
[WHIMPERS]
Aah!
[SCREAMS]
What the hell, man?
Oh, no.
Holy shit...
[♪♪♪♪♪]
SPENCER:
Whoa!
[GRUNTS]
Aah.
[BIRDS CALLING]
[PANTING]
[VARIOUS ANIMALS CALLING]
Guys?
Guys? Why do I
sound like this?
Where's my hair?
[GASPS]
- What the...?
- [BIRD SCREECHES]
Oh, God!
[BOTH SCREAMING]
Ow, unh.
- [GASPS]
- [GRUNTING]
[GRUNTS]
Huh?
Oh...
What kind of stupid-ass...?
- Who are you?
[GASPS]
Who is she?
[PANTING]
Who are you guys? Huh?
- Okay, what the hell?
- [SCREAMING]
- [SCREAMS]
- BETHANY: God! Oh, my God!
- FRIDGE: Get off of me!
- I am suing...
- What's wrong with my voice?
- FRIDGE: Get off of me!
- Where am I?
- You're crushing me! Get off!
FRIDGE:
Get...
[FRIDGE EXCLAIMS]
What the hell?
What happened to the rest of me?
What is this?
What is this on my back?
Oh, my God.
Fridge?
Yeah, I'm Fridge.
Who are you?
I'm Spencer.
What? The hell you are.
What is going on? Huh?
I think...
we're in the game.
- Sorry, excuse me?
- What are you talking about?
Somehow, I don't know how...
I think we got, like,
sucked into the game.
And we've become the avatars
that we chose.
So it's me, Spencer,
but yet I look and sound...
like Dr. Smolder Bravestone.
You're telling me
that you're Spencer?
Yes, yes, yes. That's it.
Fridge, I'm Spencer.
Which means you're Moose Finbar.
It says it right there
on your vest. And...
- Martha?
- Yeah.
You're Ruby Roundhouse.
And, Bethany,
you're Professor Shelly Oberon.
Only Shelly must be
short for Sheldon.
What are you talking about?
Oh, my God.
Oh, my God, he's right.
And you...
you're Spencer? You?
Yes. Guys, I'm telling you.
- I am Spencer. I'm... Aah!
- [BIRD CALLS]
Yep, that's Spencer.
Whoa. Whoa!
So that means I...
I'm...
FRIDGE: Wait, Bethany.
Bethany, don't!
[GASPS]
No!
I'm an overweight,
middle-aged man.
Uh, I have a tattoo.
My mom always said she'd
kill me if I ever got a tattoo.
FRIDGE:
What is this?
I have one too.
Sometimes.
Wait a second.
Where's my phone?
[MOSQUITO BUZZES]
Aah.
Why am I wearing this outfit
in a jungle?
Tiny, little shorts
and a leather halter top.
I mean, what is this?
I look like a living
garden gnome. Where is my phone?
- Who cares?
- We are in different bodies!
It doesn't seem like
the most pressing concern
- at this moment.
- Really? You don't think
this would be a good moment
to make a call
or text somebody
or change your status
to "stuck in
a video game"?
All I'm saying is,
I don't have my Claritin, okay?
And I'm allergic to
almost everything.
Oh, no.
You got allergies,
Spencer? Huh?
I don't have the top two feet
of my body!
You guys, this can't
actually be happening.
Maybe we're all in a coma.
Together?
We're all in a coma together?
It's the only explanation.
That old game machine
must have electrocuted us,
and now we're...
- [HIPPO BELLOWS]
- [ALL SCREAM]
- MARTHA: Oh, my God, Bethany!
- FRIDGE: Oh, my God, oh, my God!
MARTHA:
Stop it!
[WATER SPLASHES]
[GASPS]
Oh, my God! You better get
in there and go save her.
I'm not getting in there!
You get in.
I'm not going anywhere.
I got a backpack on.
You don't get in water with a
backpack. Everybody knows that.
[GAME CHIMES]
[GAME RUMBLES]
Ow!
FRIDGE:
What the...?
- MARTHA: Bethany!
- FRIDGE: What just...?
Are you okay?
That was so intense.
I, like, can't even
with this place.
- What just happened to you?
- I got eaten by a rhino,
and then I fell, like,
a thousand feet from the sky.
Yeah, that's what
it looked like.
That was a hippo.
They're omnivorous.
They're fast as a horse
over short distances,
and they have the bite force
of 8100 newtons.
How do I know this?
You're an expert in zoology.
- What?
- I'm still an old fat guy, right?
- I'm afraid so.
- FRIDGE: Wait.
Why is everybody okay with this?
I mean, she fell out of the sky.
Um, guys?
- [HIPPO BELLOWING]
- [SCREAMS]
Bethany, get up.
Bethany, get up. Get up!
[ALL SCREAMING]
Go, go, go!
[JEEP HONKS]
Ah! Dr. Bravestone!
Welcome to Jumanji!
Don't just stand there.
In you go.
- FRIDGE: Go, go, go.
- Yeah.
[♪♪♪♪♪]
Dr. Bravestone.
Famed archaeologist
and international explorer.
Known across
the seven continents
for your courageous exploits.
Is there a seat belt?
I can't tell you what an honor
it is to finally meet you.
I'm not embarrassed to say
you're more dashing in person.
Um, thanks.
Who are you?
Nigel Billingsly
at your service,
Ruby Roundhouse,
killer of men.
Welcome to Jumanji.
I've been so anxious
for your arrival.
As you know,
Jumanji is in grave danger.
We're counting on the four
of you to lift the curse.
- Curse?
- What curse?
Excuse me.
Have you seen my phone anywhere?
Professor Sheldon Oberon.
Welcome to Jumanji.
Nigel Billingsly
at your service.
I've been so anxious
for your arrival.
[WHISPERS]
What's with this guy?
I think he's an NPC.
A what? English, please.
A non-player character.
He's part of the game.
So anything we ask him,
he only has his programmed
series of responses.
Got it. It's all clear now.
Franklin "Mouse" Finbar.
Welcome to Jumanji.
It's Moose. It's not Mouse.
No, good sir.
I'm quite sure it's Mouse.
- Mouse?
- A nickname given
for your diminutive stature
and adorable manner.
I knew you'd be here.
Dr. Bravestone
doesn't go anywhere
without his trusty sidekick.
Sidekick?
Ever since Dr. Bravestone
rescued you
from the clutches
of a warlord
in the jungles of Peru,
you've never left his side.
Right.
Can we go back
to the curse thing?
It's all documented
in the letter I sent you.
Perhaps you should
read it aloud.
I don't have a let...
Whoa.
Right, uh...
"Dr. Bravestone,
I am writing to you
"regarding
the desperate situation
NIGEL & SPENCER: in Jumanji.
We need your help at once."
- MARTHA: Whoa... Guys?
- BETHANY: What's happening?
FRIDGE:
What the hell is going on?
SPENCER: It's a cut scene.
A lot of games have them.
It's like a little movie
to tell you the back-story.
NIGEL: My name is
Nigel Billingsly,
Jumanji field guide.
I was hired
by your former partner,
now nemesis,
Professor Russel Van Pelt
to lead
a fateful expedition.
You see,
Professor Van Pelt
had come in search
of the fabled Jaguar Shrine,
resting place
of the sacred jewel of Jumanji.
As you know
better than anyone,
the jewel was his
great obsession.
And after years of research,
he believed
that he had discovered
its whereabouts.
VAN PELT:
Could it be?
Have I finally found it?
NIGEL: Van Pelt told me that
he wanted to find the jewel
in order to document it
in his writings.
- It's real!
- NIGEL: What I did not know
was that he intended
to take the jewel for himself.
[GRUNTING]
I found it.
I found it!
NIGEL: Legend tells that the
Jaguar watches over Jumanji
and anyone who dares
to blind him
will be consumed
by a dark power.
Van Pelt assumed dominion
over all
of Jumanji's creatures,
possessing them,
controlling them.
And a terrible curse befell
this once-placid land.
I begged him
to put it back,
but once he had it
in his grasp,
he could never let it go.
So I waited
till they slept that night,
and I made my move.
[SNORES]
[BIRD SHRIEKS]
[GUNSHOT]
Bring me that jewel!
And slaughter anyone
who tries to stop you.
Right, then. Here you go.
With the invaluable help
of your associates,
you must use your
complementary skills
to return the jewel
to the Jaguar's eye
and lift the curse.
I'm sure you'll want
to get started right away.
- Actually, I think...
- NIGEL: Good luck!
The fate of Jumanji
is in your hands.
- [DOORS WHOOSH]
- [GASPS]
- What? Oh...
- And remember:
The goal for you,
I'll recite in verse
Return the jewel
and lift the curse
If you wish
to leave the game
You must save Jumanji
And call out its name
Good luck! The fate
of Jumanji is in your hands.
- And remember:
- He's saying the same thing over.
NIGEL:
I'll recite in verse
Return the jewel
and lift the curse
If you wish
to leave the game
You must save Jumanji
And call out its name
It's okay. You can handle this.
In real life, people love you.
You can hook up
with anyone you want.
Is that what you tell yourself
when you're scared?
Can you not judge me
for two seconds?
I split up with Noah,
I turned into a guy,
and I cannot find my phone.
I am allowed to be upset.
Dr. Bravestone,
here's a map of Jumanji.
You must go to the bazaar
and find the missing piece.
- The bazaar.
- MARTHA: Missing piece of what?
- Cheerio!
- FRIDGE: You can't give us a ride
- to the statue?
- NIGEL: And remember:
If you wish
to leave the game
You must save Jumanji
And call out its name
- You want to, uh, put this in there?
- No.
Come on, you're the only one
with a backpack, Fridge.
So what? We have a map.
So now we're supposed
to go and find...?
The bazaar, I guess?
So we return the jewel
to the Jaguar statue,
and then we go home.
No problem.
Why can't we just leave,
stop the game,
without doing
all this stuff?
We have to finish the game.
I think...
I think we
have to save Jumanji.
Damn, that is a man
right there.
[INHALES SHARPLY] Don't
cry, don't cry, don't cry.
Don't cry.
- [MOSQUITO BUZZES]
- Ah...
There are so many diseases
out here.
It's hot.
Okay, this is
what I'm good at.
Playing video games.
It's what I do.
It's literally
the main thing that I do.
Play a game like this,
there'll be levels.
In order to finish, you gotta
complete all the levels.
Levels are gonna get harder
as we go along.
- We complete the levels...
- Do you
even know
where we're going?
- Kind of.
- Kind of?
Oh, that's good, then.
We're in good hands.
Okay, the missing piece,
I'm guessing.
That must be
what we're looking for,
the missing piece
of the map.
The problem is,
there's nothing here.
What do you mean?
It's a map, just like he said.
It's a map of Jumanji.
Cartography.
- What's that?
- The study of maps.
It was one of
Professor Oberon's skills.
Yes. That's right.
Oh, so you can't see this,
but I can?
The characters we chose,
we all have certain skills.
So there's gotta be
a way to access our...
- [GAME CHIMES]
- [GASPS]
Oh!
Wow.
What'd you just do?
"Strengths:
Fearless. Climbing.
Speed. Boomerang.
Smoldering intensity."
[SMOLDERING]
What the hell are you doing?
- What just happened?
- Um, you just smoldered.
"Weakness.
None"?
How'd you do that?
That, uh, list?
Well, I just... I think I just
pressed my enormous left pec.
FRIDGE: It's like the boob area.
Let me show you.
Get away from me.
At least press it
in front of us...
- [GAME CHIMES]
- ...so we know exactly how...
"Strengths: Karate. T'ai chi.
Aikido. Dance fighting"?
Dance fighting?
Is that even a thing?
"Weakness:
Venom."
[GAME CHIMES]
Seriously?
"Paleontology."
What does that even mean?
Study of fossils, I think.
- That's kind of cool.
- Says the gorgeous karate badass
to the old fossil guy
who doesn't have any endurance.
[GAME CHIMES]
I hate this game.
"Weakness: Cake."
Yes, cake is my weakness.
Along with speed
and strength.
Huh...
Strength is my weakness.
Hey, can I...?
Quick question.
How is strength my weakness?
Somebody explain that to me.
And why would I need speed?
Why would I need to be fast
when I'm being chased
by an enormous killer zebra or
some shit in this dumb-ass hat?
You're also
a good weapons valet.
- What does that mean?
- Well, I think it means
you carry my weapons
in your backpack,
and you give them to me
when and if I need them?
You guys. The map,
it's changing.
MARTHA:
What do you mean?
- What's it say?
- Okay, well,
there's not
a lot of information.
But a minute ago, it didn't
say this and now it does.
It says,
"The Mighty Roar."
[DRUMS BEATING RHYTHMICALLY]
I don't like that.
- I'm done.
- What else?
Okay. And right here,
it says "From The Deep."
The hippo came from the deep.
The one that...
Yes, the thing that did
the thing. That's it. Moving on.
So if "From The Deep"
is the first level,
then "The Mighty Roar" must be
the second level.
Which way?
Okay.
If that is that...
and that is here...
Right here, I think.
[MISSILE WHISTLING]
[ENGINE REVVING]
What is this game?
Run!
Wait!
- [MISSILES WHISTLING]
- Ha!
Come on, legs!
[SHOUTS]
Why am I running so slow?
[BETHANY SCREAMING]
Oh, my God, oh, my God,
oh, my God!
[GRUNTS]
Aah!
This sucks!
[BOTH SCREAM]
Split up!
[GRUNTS]
Oh, my God.
[GROANS]
[ENGINE REVVING]
Aah!
Whoa.
[CHUCKLES]
Come on!
- Those guys have huge guns.
- Oh, really?
Is that what
those are, Spencer?
- Let me see your backpack.
- For what?
Inside your backpack,
you have my weapons.
Get down.
Got your weapons?
I can't feel no...
What's this?
Oh, yes. Boomerang,
it's one of my strengths.
What are you gonna do with it?
I don't know.
Kill them, I guess.
Kill them with that?
You got a better idea?
Oh, watch yourself.
Watch this.
[GRUNTS]
[BOOMERANG WHOOSHING]
- FRIDGE: Nice work.
- There!
Want me to see
if I got a hacky sack
for you to throw
and do nothing with?
Oh!
- SPENCER: Wait, wait.
- FRIDGE: Oh, no.
[BOOMERANG WHOOSHING]
[GASPS]
It worked.
Here they come. We gotta go.
I can't outrun those guys.
We gotta go now!
- Get on my back.
- I would rather die.
- Jump on my back!
- Nope. I'll die.
Put me down!
Spencer! Put me down!
[FRIDGE SCREAMS]
[GASPS]
Whew!
[SCREAMS] You have got
to be kidding me.
Oh, no, no, no!
[GUNSHOTS WHISTLING]
- We have to jump!
- Are you out of your mind?
I would rather do
anything else now but that.
Jump!
- Martha!
- Jump!
- [EXCLAIMS]
- FRIDGE: We gotta jump!
SPENCER: We don't know
how deep that water is.
- FRIDGE: We gotta go!
- SPENCER: No, no!
- You gonna jump. Jump!
- No!
[BOTH SCREAM]
BETHANY: Oh! I think
I'm having a coronary.
I'm having difficulty
breathing.
FRIDGE: That was the most
humiliating moment of my life.
- [GROANS]
- FRIDGE: Don't you do that again.
I took in a lot of water.
[GASPING]
They got me.
Oh, no.
Martha?
- Wait, what just happened to her?
- Is she dead? Did she die?
- Wait a second.
- [GAME CHIMES]
- [GAME RUMBLES]
- What the hell is hap...?
FRIDGE:
Ow!
- Get off of my back!
- Are you okay?
- I think so.
- FRIDGE: Off of me!
- Goodness gracious, get off!
- I'm getting off of you.
Anybody care if I'm okay?
What am I,
a human landing pad?
That's what I thought.
We each have
three lives, guys.
These little tattoos
on our arms...
Jesus, would you look
at the size of that thing?
- Spencer!
- What?
- You were saying?
- It's our life count.
Bethany got eaten by a hippo,
so now she only has two lines.
He's right.
Wait. What happens
if we use up all our lives?
Well, usually
that would mean...
...game over.
What do you mean,
"game over"?
Are you saying that
we can actually die in here?
I mean, I don't know
for sure, but...
You're not sure?
You're not sure,
- Mr. Video-Game-Genius?
- I've never been stuck in one!
So I'm not certain, but, yes,
I'm afraid we all could die.
[♪♪♪♪♪]
That is my big concern
right now.
We better find
the missing piece, then.
Okay.
It looks like
there's a village
on the other side
of this mountain.
Maybe that's the bazaar.
- Let's do it.
- FRIDGE: Wait.
I gotta take a leak first.
[SIGHING] I've been
dreading this all day,
but so do I.
Can I come with you
and you show me how it's done?
I may need your help.
Uh, yeah, sure.
Yeah, I'm... I'll help you out.
[CLEARS THROAT]
So how do we do this?
Uh. Easy.
You just, uh...
You unzip, take it out,
fire away.
Remember to aim.
It's very important.
[GASPS]
My God, you guys,
there is literally a penis
attached to my body
right now.
Martha,
come look at my penis!
MARTHA:
No, thanks.
- This the first you've seen it?
- Yes. I didn't wanna look.
I looked at mine
the first 20 seconds here.
I'm happy to report
that I was able
to bring one thing
from the outside world.
Are you...? What are you doing?
- Are you looking?
- Sorry.
FRIDGE:
You don't look over!
Yeah, you never look.
It's a thing.
Okay, good boy.
We're gonna take this
nice and slow,
and nobody's gonna get hurt.
- Now what?
- Now blast off.
And aim.
Don't forget to aim.
What is with you and aiming?
What happened?
Can we not talk about this?
Wow, wow, wow!
Oh, this is
so much easier!
[LAUGHING]
It's cool, right?
Yeah, because you have,
like, a handle.
The fact that I'm not
Instagramming this
right now is insane.
[♪♪♪♪♪]
- MAN 1: This looks all right.
- MAN 2:Up ahead!
[PEOPLE CHATTERING
INDISTINCTLY]
Bravestone.
Him and that whole lot.
They got away?
We lost them in the jungle.
I should have known.
H-how do you mean, sir?
I will summon every creature
and every soldier
to hunt them down.
Reclaim what is mine.
Find them.
[BIRD SCREECHES]
SPENCER: Be careful
of the ground, guys.
It's uneven. I'd hate
for anybody to twist an ankle.
- I did that once...
- FRIDGE: Please stop talking?
- SPENCER: Okay, sure. No problem.
- FRIDGE: Please!
- Can I borrow your jacket?
- Yeah, sure.
- Thanks.
- What are you doing?
I feel like I'm wearing
a bikini at school.
I did that once.
They sent me to the office.
Of course.
Noah likes it
when I show some skin.
It's like the key
to our relationship.
Ew.
Judgy much? Seriously, I can't
even open my mouth around you.
You don't even know me, but you,
like, decided you hate me.
Oh, wait a minute.
I don't hate you.
- You don't?
- No.
Look, I just think
you live in, like,
the "hot popular girl"
bubble.
Where everybody
either treats you
like a princess
or like an object.
Maybe it makes you a little...
self-absorbed or something?
[SIGHS]
That's fair.
But do you think maybe
the reason why you're
so judgy is because
you're, like, afraid that
people aren't gonna
like you,
so you decide
not to like them first?
No.
Maybe. Maybe.
Okay, then.
I'm just saying,
you're a babe. Own it.
Thanks.
I guess.
[♪♪♪♪♪]
FRIDGE: So sick of this game.
Just stay out of my way, Spencer.
SPENCER:
What are you mad at me for?
FRIDGE: Why? Are you
seriously asking me that?
You got me
kicked off the team.
Then you got me stuck in
whatever... Whatever this is.
And you wonder
why we not friends no more.
This is why
we're not friends anymore?
You didn't wanna get stuck
in Jumanji? I don't think so.
We're not friends
because I'm not cool enough
to hang out with you,
so you pretended
not to even know me anymore,
until you needed me
to do your homework because
you couldn't do it yourself.
No wonder
you don't know anything
about westward expansion.
Okay, you see that?
You know what?
I'm not stupid,
Spencer.
I asked you to do me
one simple favor.
Do my homework, so I don't
get kicked off the team,
and you messed that up.
Now I can't do the one thing
that I'm good at,
and it's all your fault.
I should kick
the shit out you right now.
I'd like to see you try.
What did you say?
Oh, okay.
I see what's going on here.
Guys.
You think because you...
You, what, 6'4 ", 6'5",
270 pounds of pure muscle,
I'm supposed
to be afraid of you?
Is that what you think?
Maybe.
FRIDGE:
Let me tell you something.
You're still
the same annoying kid
I've been trying to shake
since seventh grade.
Ain't nothing changed.
Don't let this new body
get your butt whupped.
[BOTH GRUNT]
[♪♪♪♪♪]
Dumb-ass.
[YELLS]
[SPENCER SCREAMS]
- BETHANY: No!
- Spencer!
Spencer!
- You killed him!
- Fridge, you lunatic!
Chill out. He'll be back.
[GAME CHIMES]
[GAME RUMBLES]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
Don't call me a dumb-ass.
Don't push me.
Or what, Spencer?
Or I'll push you back.
[FRIDGE GRUNTS]
- [GRUNTS]
- [SCREAMS]
- Oh!
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
Did you just smack me?
You gonna smack me?
- Fridge, no.
- Yeah, yeah.
Huh? You wanna smack...?
[FRIDGE SCREAMING]
BETHANY:
Oh, no, no, no!
Enough.
We can't waste lives.
We need each other.
Like it or not,
we have to do this together.
[SMOLDERS]
Could you say that
one more time, please?
- We have to do this together?
- But with the smolder.
Do you have control of that,
or does that happen naturally?
It just happens naturally.
[SMOLDERS]
[♪♪♪♪♪]
[PEOPLE CHATTERING
INDISTINCTLY]
What are we supposed
to be doing?
Looking for
the missing map piece.
So we just start
asking for it?
No, I think we look around,
scope the place out,
but most importantly, guys,
be discreet.
Rations! Get your rations!
Does anyone have any money?
I'm literally starving.
Rations! Get your rations!
Rations!
Guys, I think the game
is trying to tell us
to keep our health up.
[SMOLDERS]
We need to eat.
Okay, stop doing that.
Oh, my God, this is so good.
I haven't had bread
since I was, like, 9.
Are you serious?
How do you think
I got these abs?
FRIDGE:
Let me try some of that.
Mm.
Wait, what...?
What is this?
That's my famous pound cake.
[♪♪♪♪♪]
Cake?
Bethany, you said
this was bread.
It's been so long,
I forgot what it tastes like.
How do you forget what...?
What's hap...
Something happening to me?
- No.
- Am I... Am I shaking?
- Huh-uh.
- Am I breaking out?
No.
- Am I still black?
- Yes.
Okay. Okay, right?
We're fine.
Everything is fine.
Yeah, no, no, no,
it's okay.
It probably just meant
that I love cake.
That I couldn't resist it.
Yeah.
Hey, it's all good...
[PEOPLE SCREAMING, GASPING]
[GAME CHIMES]
[GAME RUMBLES]
[FRIDGE SCREAMING]
[PEOPLE GASPING]
FRIDGE:
God!
Oh! Ow!
What the hell? Ugh!
Like I said,
important to be discreet.
Hey, you also said eat.
Rations!
Get your...
You better
shut your ass up!
Dr. Bravestone.
Thank goodness you're here.
Jumanji needs you.
Uh. Thanks. Good to be here.
Ask about
the missing piece.
Oh, right.
Hi. I'm Bethany.
I mean...
Professor Shelly, something.
I'm a map doctor,
and I have this map that,
like, has a missing piece.
Dr. Bravestone.
Thank goodness you're here.
Jumanji needs you.
Rude.
We need to find
the missing piece.
[♪♪♪♪♪]
[BIRD SCREECHES]
What you need
is in the basket
One false move,
you're in a casket
Trust one another,
and never blink
The missing piece
is not what you think
Oy vey.
Good luck, mighty hero.
- Jumanji needs you.
- Jumanji needs him. We know.
You said it several times.
SPENCER:
So thinking there's a, um...
A snake in there
or something?
Yep.
Sounds like
a Bravestone thing to me.
Why would this be
a Bravestone thing?
You're the hero.
You heard what he said.
"Jumanji needs you."
Now, get.
[PANTING]
[DRUMS BEATING
RHYTHMICALLY]
I don't wanna do this!
Just go.
[♪♪♪♪♪]
Black mamba!
- [SCREAMING]
- FRIDGE: That's a black mamba.
A quarter milligram of its venom
is enough to kill an adult.
You'll feel a tingling
in your mouth and extremities,
followed by a fever, foaming
at the mouth, and ataxia,
which means
loss of muscle control.
- How do I know that?
- What do we do?
- See anything else in there?
- I didn't have time.
- Oh, my God.
- SPENCER: Okay.
"Trust one another
and never blink." Never blink.
You guys, I think
it's a staring contest.
- What?
- What are you talking about?
- Think about it. "Never blink"?
- Guys, I think she's right.
At camp,
they used to tell us
if you see a rattlesnake,
don't move. I think someone
has to make direct eye contact
and not blink.
And then Spencer
will reach in and grab
- whatever else is in there.
- What? Why me again?
- Because you're Bravestone.
- Okay, fine.
Who's good at staring
and not blinking?
I'm amazing at it.
Then this is your moment.
[♪♪♪♪♪]
Come on, Bethany.
Okay.
Just say when.
Now.
- [HISSING]
- [SCREAMS]
[SCREAMS]
- Oh!
- [WHIMPERS]
What do we do?
You gotta defang it.
I gotta what?
You gotta pull
his mouth back
from the blind spot
to disorient it.
But be very careful
of the venom gland
and the exposed
secondary venom duct.
Then you gotta
snap its teeth...
[WINCES]
...out of its head.
Oh, oh!
I guess it wasn't
a staring contest.
"Trust each other
and never blink."
You trusted me.
You trusted me,
and I defanged the snake.
I did it.
I did that.
Yeah.
Yeah, you did it.
Thank you.
Oh, yeah. Sure.
BETHANY:
You guys?
This does not look like
a piece of a map.
The missing piece
is an elephant?
Oh, wait, there's something
written on the wrapping paper.
"When you see me,
begin the climb."
"Begin the climb"?
When you see an elephant?
I defanged a snake.
[LAUGHS]
BETHANY: So keep your eyes
peeled for an elephant, I guess?
That's, like,
the next level of the game?
[MOTORCYCLE REVVING]
Hey!
Run!
Oh, God.
Watch out!
MARTHA:
Jump!
- BETHANY: Jump.
- FRIDGE: Go, go, go!
Hey!
I have to warn you, I think
I'm a very strong puncher.
Parry.
Parry. Parry. Evade. Block.
Uppercut.
[MAN GRUNTS]
Oh. Oh.
Duck! Head smash!
[MAN YELLS]
[BOTH GRUNTING]
Kerpow!
[LAUGHS]
Duck! Block!
Ka-blam!
Evade! Punch!
Wall toss!
That is insane.
Let's do this.
Do what?
Put... Put it
in my backpack.
Dodge! Head slam!
Throw through ceiling!
[MAN SCREAMS]
[GRUNTING]
- Ah! - Ah!
- Ah!
[PEOPLE SCREAMING]
Hello, doctor.
Been a long time.
I believe you have something
that belongs to me.
We just wanna go home.
[GUNS COCKING]
[GASPS]
MAN:
Come on! Come with me! Hurry!
Get him!
[GUNS FIRING]
Come on.
Down here.
Come on. Quick!
[FOOTSTEPS, MEN YELLING]
Shh!
Okay.
I need you to follow me
and do exactly as I say.
Let's move.
Oh, my God, you guys,
I am so stoked you are here.
- You have no idea. So stoked.
- You are?
MAN: I mean, I saw you
guys in the bazaar,
and I thought
to myself, "No way."
Then I was like,
yeah, that's...
Backs against the wall!
FRIDGE:
Oh, my goodness!
Let's keep moving.
- Watch your step in here.
- Um, who are you?
And who do you think
we are?
Right.
Sorry, okay, my bad.
Um. Let me back up
a little bit here.
Wait, are you the pilot?
"Seaplane" somebody?
- Yeah, that's me.
- FRIDGE: Wait a minute.
You're the other
character that was taken.
- So you're in the game too?
- MAN: Stay off the white bricks...
- What?
- MAN: And freeze.
- Aah!
- Oh!
[GASPING]
So gnarly.
This game sucks.
Hup!
[CROCODILES THRASHING]
All right. Get this plank.
Follow me.
Careful.
It's a horrible way to die.
[SOFTLY]
Oh, God.
There you go. All right.
Come on.
I got it, I got it.
I just defanged a snake.
Give me
a little respect.
Okay.
[♪♪♪♪♪]
[YELLS]
[PANTING]
- Hi there.
- Hi.
[GRUNTS]
Come on.
[♪♪♪♪♪]
Anyway, I'm Alex.
Spencer Gilpin.
Martha, Fridge and Bethany.
Bethany? You're a girl?
- Woman.
- [CHUCKLES]
In real life, you'd probably
wanna hit that.
They got away.
Looks like they had help.
Seaplane.
He must've crawled out
of his hole.
I'm sorry, boss.
It won't happen again.
I know it won't.
[GAGGING]
[YELLS]
SPENCER:
What are you making?
Margaritas. It's actually
one of my strengths.
That and piloting,
although I did get shot down
by a couple orangutans
in fighter jets,
so maybe not
that great at it.
Anyway, cheers.
Ah.
- Oh. Thanks.
- Sure.
I've never
had alcohol before.
- SPENCER: Me either.
- MARTHA: Know what?
- What the hell? Woo!
- Lehayim.
[GRUNTS]
[SPENCER COUGHING]
- And I'm done with that.
- It's good.
Can I get one more of those?
- Yeah.
- BETHANY: Alex?
What's up with
all these candles?
ALEX? Citronella. One
of my weaknesses
is mosquitoes,
which is kind of a bummer
when you live alone
in an open hut in the jungle.
[CHUCKLES]
[QUIETLY]
He's single.
Who's this?
Who's Alan Parrish?
He's the guy
who built this place.
Wait, other people have
been stuck here too?
Yeah. This is Alan Parrish's
house. I'm just living in it.
BETHANY [IN NORMAL VOICE]:
So, Alex, tell me,
how long have
you been in the game?
Oh, it's tough to say.
Time is kind of funny here.
But a few months, at least.
- A few months?
- What?
Yeah,
I can't seem to make it
past the transportation shed.
Transportation shed?
What's that?
It's the next level.
First time, my hot-air balloon
wouldn't even take off.
And then there was the whole
plane thing I mentioned.
And once I got down
to my last life,
I realized I was screwed.
And that I was never gonna
get out of here by myself.
Half the stuff that came at me,
I had zero way to deal with.
You can't kill a black mamba
with a margarita.
You sure can't.
You need a zoologist for that.
[♪♪♪♪♪]
Alex, we can help each other.
You've been here a long time,
you know the game,
and between us,
we have a lot of strengths.
Yeah. We're actually
pretty good together.
I don't know, bro.
Okay, I mess up
one more time, I'm toast.
Totally freaks me out
even thinking about
going back to
the transportation shed.
I don't wanna die
in Jumanji.
We just gotta stick together.
If we do that, we can win.
I know we can.
Oh, my God.
You're our missing piece.
You were the thing
we needed to find.
So the clue was to, what,
go to the bazaar
to find the missing piece?
It wasn't the elephant.
- It was me.
- Yeah.
Dudes, let's do this.
- MARTHA: Yeah.
- SPENCER: Let's do this.
- MARTHA: Let's do this.
Hey, Spencer,
you gonna drink that margarita?
SPENCER:
I... You're done.
FRIDGE:
This is one good margarita.
[♪♪♪♪♪]
ALEX: There it is. The
transportation shed.
There's all sorts
of vehicles inside.
We gotta get one,
get across the canyon,
and get to the Jaguar statue.
Okay, I see
the transportation shed,
I see the canyon, but
I still can't see the statue,
which is weird 'cause
it's the most important thing
in Jumanji and it's huge.
That's what she said.
[LAUGHING]
You drunk, Fridge?
What are you talking about?
I ain't drunk.
- He is drunk.
- I had three little margaritas.
You're about
half your usual size.
Whatever, whatever.
Alex, what do we do?
How do we get past these guards?
Last time,
I waited till they left.
How long did that take?
- Three weeks?
- Oh, we gonna die.
Okay. Plan B.
Maybe there's
another door somewhere.
But we gotta distract
those guys first.
BETHANY:
I've got it.
Distracting guys is, like,
the main thing I do.
He plays video games,
I distract guys.
Bethany, I hate to break it
to you right now,
but you don't exactly
have the, um, the tool kit.
- Not me.
- What?
- You have to go down there and flirt with those guys...
- No.
- ...and hold their attention while we sneak in.
- No!
I can't just go over there
and flirt
with some weird soldiers
I don't know.
I know, but right now
we don't have a better idea.
You don't understand.
I actually can't do it.
[WHISPERING]
I can't talk to guys.
I'm terrible at it.
[WHISPERING]
I can give you some pointers.
[IN NORMAL VOICE] No, I'm sorry. We
have to come up with another plan.
I'm not... No. Heh.
Not doing that.
Martha, you just have to
distract them long enough
for us
to get into the shed.
I really don't think
I can, I'm not...
Like, I'm not actually
some badass girl.
What are you talking about?
You're a total badass.
You could do anything.
[BOTH LAUGH]
FRIDGE:
That's beautiful, Spencer.
Why don't I set you up
with a nice candlelight dinner?
Or do you guys wanna get
the hell out of here?
All right.
Show me how it's done.
Class is in session.
- Come on, girl.
- Okay.
BETHANY:
Watch and learn.
Hey, what did you mean by
that candlelight-dinner thing?
- What are you talking about?
- You said it, me and Martha,
candlelight dinner.
What does that even mean?
The girl is into you,
Spencer.
[LOUDLY]
What?
[GUN COCKS]
[BUG BUZZES]
[♪♪♪♪♪]
Okay, in flirting
situations,
the key is making them
check you out
without letting them know
that you know that
they're checking you out.
You're like, "Whatever."
When they try to talk to you,
you can play it
one of three ways:
dumb, super into it,
or nasty.
Which way you play it depends on
what guy you deal with.
This is like my dream and my
nightmare all at one time.
I'm not gonna
take that personally.
Now, hair is everything.
Touch it. Move it.
Play with it.
Move it around a lot.
Hypnotize them with it.
Give me a flip like that.
Okay, now angle your eyes down.
Now, head down.
Tilt up. Eyes big.
- Now sparkle.
- Sparkle?
Like an anime character.
Now sparkle.
[SNIFFS]
[SHORT GASPING]
[GASPING, WHEEZING]
Needs work.
[♪♪♪♪♪]
Do you really think
she likes me?
Why are we still
talking about this?
I mean, what if
she tries to kiss me?
Then you just
kiss her back, man.
What if she tries
to kiss me, like...
Like, without warning?
What are you talking about?
Haven't you ever kissed anyone?
Don't... You gonna tell
the whole jungle?
Guys, I found
a side door. Over here.
- Guess what I found.
- No, no, don't tell him.
Okay, let's talk about
your walk.
Take your time.
Make a meal of it.
Like a gorgeous gazelle.
Or a horse. High-step it.
One foot in front of the other.
And bring it.
Boom, boom...
That's not it.
Yikes.
Anything you can do to
draw attention to the lips.
A little nibble like this.
A nibble goes
a long way, girlfriend.
Good. That's better.
Now smile.
You look terrified.
Oh, God,
you're so funny.
- You're so funny.
- Oh, God, you're so funny.
Oh, my God,
you're so funny.
- I think I'm getting it.
- You are getting it. Go, girl.
Now, keep your lips
slightly parted, like...
Yeah, not-not gross,
just relaxed.
Touch your tongue
to the roof of your mouth.
- Like this.
- Like this?
Like this.
Like this?
I think you're ready.
[CHUCKLES]
- Cool.
- Okay, flirt
like our lives depend on it.
'Cause they do.
ALEX:
Okay, there's the door.
We just need something
to cut through the fence.
Okay, Fridge, you got anything
like that in the backpack?
Uh, yeah, I should. What...?
Here you go. I got some...
Some bolt cutters.
Does that seem like a good tool
for the situation?
Perfect, actually.
It's called backpack power,
baby.
[MAN LAUGHS]
You guys,
I think this is gonna work.
I think so too.
She's pretty fly.
And those guys don't meet
a lot of new people.
"Fly"?
Well, not like
Cindy Crawford fly,
but for Jumanji,
she the bomb.
"The bomb"?
- Cindy Crawford?
- That's your go-to?
ALEX:
I'm just saying, I'm sure
they'd like to
get jiggy with her.
[♪♪♪♪♪]
Alex.
What year do you think it is?
- What do you mean?
- Oh, no.
It's 1996.
You're Alex Vreeke,
aren't you?
Yeah, that's right.
Wait a minute,
you mean Freak House?
Wait, what are you...
What are you guys talking about?
How do you know me?
Alex, I don't know how
to tell you this...
You've been in this game
for 20 years.
That's probably not
how I would've done it.
What?
No. You guys are messing
with me, right?
No, we're not.
Alex Vreeke.
Everybody in Brantford
knows about you.
You're the kid
that disappeared.
Twenty years ago.
Twenty years?
Twenty years, man.
I don't even know
how to say this, but
Cindy Crawford, dude,
she's like 50 years old.
- But still fly.
- Eh.
Wait...
There she is.
Hey.
We're gonna get you home.
Yeah.
[♪♪♪♪♪]
[EXHALES]
FRIDGE: The hell is
going on with her butt?
Bethany, what did
you tell her to do?
Did she twist her ankle,
maybe, or...?
She's never flirted before.
Give her a break.
Hello, little lady.
What are you doing
out here all alone?
[IN DEEPER VOICE]
Hey, you guys.
I seem to be lost.
Can you guys help me?
[EXHALES SHARPLY]
Hello, little lady.
What are you doing
out here all alone?
[LAUGHS]
You guys are so
interesting and funny.
What's she doing?
What, she got a bug
in her hair?
She's forgotten
all of our training.
Let's go.
Wait! I... I... I
have to tell you
about this book
that I've been reading.
About microbiology.
Which is one of
my favorite biologies.
Hello, little lady.
What are you doing
out here all alone?
- [GUN COCKS]
- [WHIMPERS]
You are a badass.
[CLICKS]
♪ Ooh, baby
I love your way ♪
♪ Every day, yeah ♪
Hey.
You guys like to dance?
♪ ...every day ♪
♪ Shadows grow so long
Before my eyes ♪
♪ And they're moving ♪
Oh, yeah, there we go.
♪ Across the page ♪
♪ Suddenly the day
Turns into night ♪
♪ Ooh ♪
♪ Far away from the city ♪
SPENCER: Which one,
which one, which one?
[MUSIC CONTINUES, MUFFLED]
I hate this place.
♪ 'Cause your love
Just won't... ♪
Her strength is dance fighting.
SPENCER: Alex, what do you think, huh?
What's the move?
- What?
- SPENCER: What do we take?
- Which one?
- I don't know, man, okay?
- I told you, I...
- SPENCER: We gotta fly.
SPENCER:
The helicopter? We gotta fly.
ALEX:
I told you I don't know.
♪ ...light the skies ♪
[GRUNTING]
♪ With the help
Of some fireflies ♪
She's kicking their ass.
That's our girl.
Yes, queen!
♪ ...the power to shine ♪
♪ I can see them
Under the pine ♪
She is destroying them.
♪ But don't hesitate ♪
♪ La di dah ♪
♪ 'Cause your love ♪
♪ Just won't wait ♪
[BOTH GRUNT]
[BOTH GRUNTING]
♪ Ooh, baby
I love your way ♪
♪ Every day ♪
♪ Wanna tell you
I love your way ♪
♪ I wanna tell you
♪ Wanna be with you
Night and day ♪
♪ Every day and every way ♪
- BETHANY: You go, girl!
- FRIDGE: Yeah.
Woo! Woo-hoo!
Go, go!
Yes! Yes! You're my hero.
[MOTORCYCLES REVVING]
- We gotta go.
- BETHANY: You should give me
lessons in kicking ass.
Give me a hug.
- Oh, my God.
- You did it.
- I did.
- Yeah, give me a hug, girlfriend.
As great of a moment as that is,
we ain't got the time.
- SPENCER: Yeah.
- They coming.
The motorcycle freaks
is coming.
Seaplane!
We got to fly, man.
Nope. I can't do it.
Okay? I told you,
I'm not a good pilot.
Maybe we should take
the school bus.
We can't outrun no motorcycle
on no damn bus!
You picked the plane
and hot-air balloon.
Maybe pick
the helicopter.
No, I can't do it. Okay?
I don't wanna die.
I'm freaking out
a little bit.
Fine. I'll do it.
How hard can it be?
It's a helicopter.
You... You press
a button, the...
They gonna spin. Okay.
Then after that, I got my...
The... The lever.
That's how...
That's how you getting
the forward-backward action.
Once we in the air,
I'mma be all right.
This, I just gotta get...
'Cause it ain't got
no step stool, so...
Let me see something.
I can probably just...
Get in, but be careful.
- No, you're drunk.
- MARTHA: No way. Nuh-uh.
Fridge, you're drunk.
Give me the keys.
- I'm?
- Alex. Alex.
If I can fight
those guys,
you can fly this helicopter.
I know you can.
Come on.
[♪♪♪♪♪]
Alex.
This is where we need you.
Remember,
you're the missing piece.
Seaplane McDonough
reporting for duty.
Let's go, people.
[♪♪♪♪♪]
[HELICOPTER BLADES WHIRRING]
Whoa!
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
[ALEX GRUNTING]
- BETHANY: What's wrong?
- ALEX: Something's broken!
- What?
- What do you mean?
ALEX:
Hang on!
[ALL SCREAMING]
FRIDGE: Oh, my God,
we're about to die!
We're about to die!
- MARTHA: Oh, my God!
- ALEX: It won't go up!
- SPENCER: What?
- FRIDGE: What do you mean?
The collective is busted.
- What?
- It controls the plate up there,
which tilts the rotors
and controls the pitch.
It's how we go up and down.
[DRUMS BEATING
RHYTHMICALLY]
You guys?
- That can't be good.
- It's no way that's good news.
[RHINOS BELLOWING]
Albino rhinos!
They're indigenous
to Jumanji.
They're huge,
white, scary, and stupid,
- and they eat people.
- No.
SPENCER:
They're getting close!
My stomach's starting
to bother me a bit.
- MARTHA: Go up!
- ALEX: I can't go up!
I think I had
too many margaritas.
[BELLOWING CONTINUES]
BETHANY: You guys,
what are we gonna do?
I'll fix the helicopter.
- Yes!
- Tell me what to do.
You gotta connect
the flight-control rod
to the mesh plate
under the rotors.
Flight-control rod, mesh plate,
- Wait, what?
- I'll be right back.
- Spencer, where are you going?
- FRIDGE: Hurry up.
- Be careful!
- No, no, just hurry up!
SPENCER: All right, just
gonna stand on this thingy,
pull myself up towards these
deadly helicopter blades. Okay.
There's the mesh plate.
Here's that rod thingy.
[GRUNTING]
- [SPENCER GRUNTS]
- [BOTH SCREAM]
[SPENCER GRUNTING]
- Spencer!
- FRIDGE: Speed it up, Alex!
Spencer!
MARTHA:
Hurry! Come on, fix it!
[ALL SCREAMING]
- MARTHA: Oh, my God!
- ALEX: Running out of time!
- MARTHA: Fix it, please!
- No, no, no.
SPENCER:
Got it!
BETHANY: We made it! You did it!
I thought we were gonna die.
- Oh.
- BETHANY: Yes!
- Nice!
- SPENCER: Thank you.
- Thank you, guys.
- You did it. That was scary.
Oops.
What?
I dropped the jewel.
[IN UNISON]
What?
You dropped the jewel?
I leaned over,
thought I had to puke,
and I didn't.
It came out
of my backpack.
- We need the freaking jewel!
- I know.
That's-that's-that's the crazy
part 'cause I know we need it.
So we're in a pickle.
We're in a pickle.
Turn around.
We gotta go get it.
Yeah, let's loop around.
Look for it.
Everybody open your eyes.
Let's all look for it
as a group.
There! I see it!
MARTHA:
What are they doing?
It's like they're
protecting it or something.
- How are we gonna do this?
- I don't know.
Well, you gotta go get it,
right, buddy?
[RHINOS BELLOWING]
What do you need?
Your boomerang?
Maybe some scissors?
A pipe wrench?
Some shoelaces?
I'm your valet. Whatever
you need, I can get it for you.
Okay? You just say the word.
- What?
- I'm sorry, buddy.
Sorry for what?
[SCREAMING]
Ow!
[GASPS]
No.
[WHIMPERS]
[FRIDGE SCREAMING]
[GRUNTS]
SPENCER:
Turn us around.
No!
Heel! Heel! Stop!
Oh, my God!
- BETHANY & MARTHA: No!
- Alex, get ready to roll us
- to the side.
- What?
[GAME CHIMES]
SPENCER; When I tell you,
roll 90 degrees to the right.
Now!
[FRIDGE SCREAMING]
You pushed me out
the helicopter, jackass!
[HELICOPTER POWERING DOWN]
BETHANY:
Oh, wow!
- MARTHA: Spencer, you're amazing.
- SPENCER: Thank you.
BETHANY:
You are a killer pilot, Alex.
- ALEX: Thanks.
- BETHANY: You too, Spencer,
- you were incredible!
- Thank you...
- FRIDGE: Hey!
- ...but he was amazing, our pilot.
- FRIDGE: Excuse me.
- You killed it.
Excuse me.
Excuse me!
I'm the one that
was a human sacrifice.
You don't know what's on
the underside of those rhinos.
And you don't wanna know.
I've seen a lot of things.
Felt them on my face too.
Things that I will never be able
to erase from memory.
[ALL LAUGHING]
Oh, that's funny to you guys.
Go ahead, laugh it up.
Get it out.
Guys, I've been trying
to get across
this canyon for, like,
20 years, okay?
Do you realize
how huge this is?
[BUG BUZZING]
Mosquito.
No, no, no!
Alex, no, no, no!
- Alex.
- BETHANY: Alex, no, no.
SPENCER:
Alex?
Alex, talk to me.
Wake up. Here we go.
MARTHA:
Alex? He's dying.
No, we can't let him die.
We're too close!
Does anyone
know how to do CPR?
Yeah, start with three chest
compressions and mouth-to-mouth.
One, two, three.
How do I do this?
Okay, pinch his nose,
open his mouth,
- full lip-lock.
- Okay.
Ah, one breath, two breaths,
then repeat.
BETHANY:
Come on, Alex.
Bethany, stop. Your tattoo.
It looks like you're giving him
one of your lives.
I'm okay with that.
What if you need it
for yourself?
I want Alex to come home too.
[GASPING, COUGHING]
Oh!
- [GASPS]
- [BETHANY GASPS]
[GAME CHIMES]
[PANTING]
- What happened?
- Alex,
Bethany gave you
one of her lives.
Bethany, you okay?
BETHANY:
I think so.
Bethany,
is that true?
You gave me
one of your lives?
I mean, yeah, of course.
Thank you.
What? What are
you looking at?
You got a situation.
[GASPS]
Oh, my God,
these things are crazy.
[♪♪♪♪♪]
Twenty years,
huh?
Yeah,
I guess so.
You know,
I just keep thinking about
my poor parents.
And what they must've
been through.
And why, because I was sitting
in my hideout,
too afraid
to finish the game?
I'm sorry.
I don't mean to lay this on you.
I'm just...
You're really easy
to talk to.
No, I get it.
I mean, sometimes
it's easy to get so focused
on your own stuff
that you forget other people
have problems too.
That's really deep.
Thanks. I feel like
ever since I lost my phone,
my other senses have
kind of heightened.
Does "phone" mean something
different in the future?
What about you, Alex?
What are you like?
In the real world.
What's your vibe?
Full-on
metalhead.
A drummer, like my dad.
Hey.
- Hey.
- What are you doing?
I, uh, I was just
filling these up.
- Cool.
- Yeah.
I'm glad you're here.
I, uh, ahem...
- I have something to tell you.
- Yeah?
And I wanna tell you now,
just in case
the next time
that we talk
I'm no longer brave.
I like you, Martha.
I, like, like you.
[LAUGHS]
Like,
I'm fully into you.
- You are?
- I am.
And I have been
since, like,
the seventh grade.
Really?
Wowza. I don't think
this has ever happened before.
- What do you mean?
- Oh, I mean, like, I don't think
anyone's ever liked me that I...
I can't believe I'm doing this.
I never tell anyone
how I fe...
[♪♪♪♪♪]
I'm into you too,
Spencer.
- You are?
- Yes. Yes! Heh, heh!
God, you're smart
and sweet and cute.
Yeah, I'm pretty into you.
[GIGGLES]
Wait. Are you sure it's not
because of, like, all of...?
What? Oh, my God, no, no.
That is not my type.
I'm into nerds.
Really?
I'm a nerd.
[GIGGLES]
[♪♪♪♪♪]
- That was... I was so awful.
- I've never kissed anyone.
- You've never...?
- Never. That was the first time.
- I have never.
- Oh, you haven't?
- No.
- Okay. Cool.
- You can't tell, right?
- [LAUGHS]
Come on. Hey!
I don't wanna see that.
I don't, not today.
While you're down here
professing your love
for one another,
I found the Jaguar.
Let's go. God! Ugh!
[♪♪♪♪♪]
- There it is.
We'd better get walking.
[BIRD SCREECHES]
[THUNDER RUMBLING]
I think we just
follow this path.
No. It can't be that easy.
"The Defenders."
What does
that mean?
There's only one way
to find out.
Fridge,
give me the jewel.
[♪♪♪♪♪]
Spencer.
[BETHANY GASPS]
[DRUMS BEATING
RHYTHMICALLY]
Something's about to happen.
I hate those drums.
What, you're just gonna
walk in there?
No.
That's what the game wants us
to do. Follow the path.
It's a trap.
"When you see the elephant...
begin the climb."
I'll go through the trees.
- The trees?
- Yeah.
Do you think
that's what that means?
That must be it.
That's the move.
This is the final level
of the game.
And I'm pretty sure
this is a Bravestone thing.
[♪♪♪♪♪]
Did he just refer to himself
in the third person?
Um, fourth person, I think.
[SPENCER GRUNTS]
How does he do that?
Climbing is one
of his strengths.
Oh. Gotcha.
Cake makes me
explode.
[SQUEAKING]
[YELLS]
[GRUNTING]
[ROARS]
- No! Spencer!
- Oh, my God!
- [SPENCER SCREAMING]
- FRIDGE: Spencer!
Spencer!
[GROWLING]
Oh, my God, you guys.
Panthers.
No.
Those are jaguars.
[THUNDER RUMBLING]
[GAME CHIMES]
- [GASPS]
- [GAME RUMBLES]
[PANTING]
Spencer!
Oh, my God.
Are you okay?
Yeah. I think so.
You still have the jewel,
right?
- I got it.
- Oh, thank God.
Hey, what happened?
I don't wanna talk
about it.
BETHANY:
Okay, we need a new plan.
- FRIDGE: Yeah.
- MARTHA: Right.
- ALEX: Totally.
- Spencer, any ideas?
Can I speak with you
for a minute?
Now?
What's going on?
I can't do this.
- What are you talking about?
- I can't do this.
Okay, who am I kidding?
I'm not some adventurer.
I'm not actually brave.
Spencer, I just saw you
hanging out of a helicopter.
It's a lot easier to be brave
when you have lives to spare.
It's a lot harder...
when you only have one life.
[♪♪♪♪♪]
We-we always only have
one life, man.
Okay? That's... That's all
we get. That's how it works.
The question is,
is how are you gonna live it?
Which guy are
you gonna decide to be?
Did I just quote
our principal?
What the hell is this game doing
to me? I gotta get out of here.
Look.
We can do this, man.
We can do it together.
- Together.
You're a good friend,
Fridge.
All right.
Okay. I don't know
video games,
but what I do know
is football.
Now, those lightning-fast,
man-eating cats out there?
They're the Defenders.
Which means we gotta run
one hell of an offense.
You guys.
[MOTORCYCLES REVVING]
We gotta go.
All right.
Here's what we're gonna do.
We're gonna fan out
and run a play that I call:
"The Double Reverse
Refrigerator."
Bethany,
you go up the left side.
I'll go up the right.
Alex, you'll draw
the defense,
so Spencer can go
up the middle.
- MARTHA: I'll go with Spencer.
- FRIDGE: No.
There's something else
we need you to do.
[MOTORCYCLES REV]
♪ Ooh, baby
I love your way ♪
♪ Every day, yeah ♪
♪ Ooh, baby
I love your way ♪
You guys like to dance?
[GRUNTING]
♪ Shadows grow so long
Before my eyes ♪
[GROWLING]
Hey! Over here!
Come and get me!
[♪♪♪♪♪]
♪ I wanna tell you, I wanna
Tell you, I wanna tell you ♪
[GRUNTING]
[MARTHA PANTING]
No! No.
[GASPS]
[GRUNTS, GROANS]
[WHIMPERING]
- MARTHA: Thanks.
- Sure.
Get to the statue. Go!
[♪♪♪♪♪]
[GASPS]
[ROARING]
Oh, no! I...
[VOICE VOCALIZES]
[JAGUARS GROWLING]
SPENCER:
Ah, whoa, whoa.
[HEAVY FOOTSTEPS]
[ELEPHANT TRUMPETING]
Oh, man. Okay.
Stay calm, don't panic.
Stop!
It's the elephant
and the mouse.
What's up?
Mouse Finbar.
Zoologist.
Zoologist and...
And backpack guy.
[♪♪♪♪♪]
Give me the jewel,
or your friend dies.
- Don't give it to him!
- Quiet!
Stop!
[GROWLING]
Take me instead,
okay?
[GROWLING]
[MARTHA YELPS]
[BETHANY WHIMPERS]
Give me the jewel.
I can't do that.
Five.
- Four, three...
- I can't give you the jewel.
- Spencer.
- Two!
Because I don't have it!
[POUNDING FOOTSTEPS]
[TRUMPETING]
Zoology, bitch!
[GROWLING]
[FRIDGE YELLING]
No, no, no! Don't...
- [ELEPHANT TRUMPETS]
- [FRIDGE YELPS]
BETHANY:
Douche bag! You suck!
- Elephant.
- "Begin the climb."
ALEX:
Leave her alone!
Get up there,
I'll get the jewel to you.
- Martha.
- Trust me.
- I'll get it to you. Go.
- Okay.
Go, Martha!
[GRUNTING]
Alex!
[♪♪♪♪♪]
[GRUNTING]
I'll take that.
Game over.
[MOTORCYCLE REVVING
IN DISTANCE]
[♪♪♪♪♪]
I don't think so.
Venom's my weakness.
[WINCES]
Go, Spencer.
[GRUNTS]
No.
[♪♪♪♪♪]
[GRUNTS]
- Yeah! - Wow!
- Yeah.
[♪♪♪♪♪]
"Call out its name."
Call out its name!
Call out its name, everyone!
BOTH:
Jumanji!
ALL:
[♪♪♪♪♪]
[ALL GASP]
[CHUCKLES]
- MARTHA: I think we did it.
- FRIDGE: I think we won.
- BETHANY: I think we did.
- [CAR HORN HONKS]
Guys,
it's Nigel.
Nigel.
[HORN HONKS]
[ENGINE STOPS]
Well done,
intrepid adventurers!
You lifted the curse!
- All of Jumanji thanks you.
- [ALL CHUCKLE]
Your work here is done.
So, sadly,
this is where we part.
Seaplane McDonough,
let me shake your hand.
Alex.
Adieu, Professor Oberon.
Later, dude.
I'll miss you the most,
my little Mouse.
Get me the hell
out of here.
Farewell, Ruby Roundhouse.
Wait.
What if we didn't go back?
I just...
I like being like this.
With you.
Then let's be like this,
every day.
Just come home.
Dr. Bravestone.
Nigel, I'm ready to go home.
Farewell, my good man.
See you later,
Bravestone.
[♪♪♪♪♪]
[DEEP SIGH]
BETHANY:
Oh, my God.
Yes, yes, yes! Yes, yes!
I'm back, baby!
I will never complain
about my body ever again.
Oh, thank God.
Oh, I missed you.
Where's Alex?
[♪♪♪♪♪]
SPENCER:
Wait, look.
FRIDGE:
Freak House?
Do you think...?
That means, maybe...
- BOY: Grandpa!
- GRANDPA: Hey!
Come here. Come here.
Oh, that's my girl.
- WOMAN: Hi!
- GRANDPA: So good to see you.
GRANDPA: Come on. Come on
and say hi to Grandma.
- Alex?
- Hey, Dad, when you get a sec,
- could you give us a hand?
- GRANDPA: Yeah.
ALEX:
Oh, that is some tree.
- Yeah, it's not too bad.
- Yeah.
Hey, Dad, will you
give me a second?
- Oh, yeah, sure.
- ALEX: I'll be right back.
Bethany?
- Spencer?
- Yeah.
Ruby Roundhouse?
[BOTH CHUCKLE]
And that
would make you Fridge.
[FRIDGE & ALEX CHUCKLE]
I'm stoked to see you.
All of you.
- You made it back.
- ALEX: Yeah, I did.
It spit me out
right where I started, so...
1996.
And your parents
and your house?
Yeah, they... All good, bro.
You're an adult now.
You have a family.
I do, yeah.
This is Andy.
And then my daughter...
My daughter's name
is Bethany.
We named her after the girl
who saved my life.
[♪♪♪♪♪]
So stoked. Heh.
[STUDENTS CHATTERING
INDISTINCTLY]
[♪♪♪♪♪]
Yo.
You wanna
go backpacking?
Like, in nature?
Yeah, but, like, somewhere,
like, really amazing.
Next summer?
What do you think?
- Are you okay?
- SPENCER: Hey.
Oh, um,
I'll catch you later.
I'll see you after class?
- Hey!
- SPENCER: Hello.
- Hey.
- So, uh, anything...
interesting
happen lately?
No, I can't think
of anything.
Yeah. Heh.
Have you guys talked
to Martha?
Oh, I was texting her
this weekend.
Have you talked to her?
Hey. There she is.
Go get that girl,
Dr. Bravestone.
[♪♪♪♪♪]
Hi.
- Hi.
- I really...
- I really wanted to call you.
- I get it.
Sorry, I don't know
why I didn't call.
It's weird being out and,
not, like, knowing,
like, what's going on and...
[NERVOUS CHUCKLE]
What?
[♪♪♪♪♪]
Smoldering.
[DRUMS BEATING RHYTHMICALLY]
Subtitles by explosiveskull
Resync by GoldenBeard
[♪♪♪♪♪]
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today