Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
Don't worry. It's just a pack of wolves.
Come on, we're almost rid of it.
- Caleb, it's after me!
- Grab on!
Run! Run!
No, Benjamin, we have to finish this.
Come on, help me bury it.
What if someone digs it up?
May God have mercy on his soul.
- Hi, Alan.
- Hi, Miss Magruder.
- Afternoon, Alan.
- Hey, Frank.
- All yours, Alan.
- Thanks, Bill.
Get him!
Prepare to die, Parrish!
Hey, Parrish, what's the rush?
He's going to his dad's factory!
He's going to Daddy now.
Go on, Parrish! Run to Daddy.
We'll be waiting.
Hey, Carl.
Hey, Alan, my man. I gotta
show you something. Come here.
Now, I've been working on this
for almost a year.
And I got an appointment
with your father...
...to show him this.
Go ahead, take it.
So, what do you think?
You think he'll like it?
What is it?
What is it? This is the future. If I can get
Wilt Chamberlain to wear them...
...there will be a pair of those
in every closet in America.
That's gonna be the height of fashion.
What's wrong?
- Nothing.
- Alan!
Thanks, Bob. What are you doing here?
I've told you, this factory isn't
a playground. It's dangerous.
Dad, can I have a ride home?
Oh, Alan.
Is Billy Jessup picking on you again?
Son, you're gonna have
to face him sooner or later.
Look, if you're afraid of something,
you've got to stand and face it.
Now, run on, son.
Carl, you know better
than to let the boy play in here.
Sorry, sir.
Oh, what was it
you wanted to show me?
Just a minute, sir.
What the devil...?
Get an extinguisher.
Bring it over here.
What is that?
Who did this?
Well?
I did, sir.
Being a Parrish doesn't mean
you can hang around with my girlfriend.
We're just friends.
Not anymore.
Get him!
- Let's go.
- Okay, I've got his bike!
Jerks!
Neat.
Alan?
Are you home?
Oh, Alan, not again. Come on.
Hard work, determination,
cheerful outlook...
...attributes that have exemplified
the Brantford spirit...
...since our forefathers
first settled this town.
Despite the harshness of our native clime
and the granite of our soil...
...we have...
- Prospered.
- I knew the whole thing this morning.
You'll know the whole darn thing tonight.
- Right. Let's go.
- Sam, we have to talk to Alan.
Well, we're on our way.
Okay.
I told your father what you told me this
afternoon, that it wasn't just Billy Jessup.
- Look, if I'd known that, I wouldn't have...
- It's okay, Dad.
But I'm proud of you.
You faced them,
even though you were outnumbered.
And, since you took it like a man,
your mother and I have decided...
...that you're ready to go
to the Cliffside School for Boys.
- There.
- Congratulations, sweetheart.
You don't want me living here anymore?
Alan.
It's always been the plan
that you'd go to Cliffside.
I mean, Parrishes have been going
to Cliffside ever since the 1700s.
Even your Uncle Skylar went there.
Look at this. Parrish Hall?
It's the main dormitory.
This is great. Kids are on my case here
because I'm a Parrish.
Just wait till I'm living
in a building named after me.
It was named after my father.
Good. Why don't you live in it?
I did. I wouldn't be who I am today
if it weren't for my years there.
Maybe I don't want to be who you are.
Maybe I don't even want
to be a Parrish.
You won't be.
Not till you start acting like one.
- Sam...
- Get your coat.
I guess I'm not ready for Cliffside, then.
We're taking you there next Sunday!
And I don't want to hear another word!
You won't!
I'm never talking to you again!
- Sam...
- Don't.
- Sam.
- What?
Nothing. Just...
What are you doing here?
I brought your bike back.
You didn't have to.
I was going over
to Billy's to get it myself.
I told Billy to stop picking on you.
You shouldn't have wasted your breath.
We gotta talk about this some other time.
What was that?
- You heard it too?
- Of course I heard it.
Come on. I found
this really weird game in the factory.
A game?
"Jumanji.
A game for those who seek to find
a way to leave their world behind.
You roll the dice to move your token.
Doubles gets another turn.
The first player to reach the end wins."
You wanna play?
I quit playing board games
five years ago.
Sarah!
It's gotta be magnetized or something.
Alan, look.
"At night they fly, you better run.
These winged things are not much fun."
What was that?
I don't know.
- Put it away, Alan.
- Okay.
Oh, no.
The game thinks I rolled.
What do you mean, "the game thinks"?
"In the jungle you must wait...
...until the dice read five or eight."
"In the jungle you must wait"?
What does that mean?
Sarah!
Roll the dice!
I think a bed-and-breakfast is just
what this town needs.
Well, it was pretty hard to pass up.
Especially full of furniture.
Oh, boy.
I keep forgetting
how big this place is.
Judy, Peter, come look at this.
I'm gonna put a reception area
right over here.
And a bar over here in the parlor.
That sounds lovely.
I'm sure you and your kids
are gonna be very happy here.
Well...
Actually, they're my late brother's.
He and his wife passed away
just last winter.
Is this something, or what?
It sure is.
So, what do you think, young man?
Is it big enough for you?
Peter hasn't spoken a word
since it happened.
Oh, my.
I'm so sorry. How terribly awful.
It's okay.
We barely even knew our parents.
They were always away.
Skiing in St. Moritz,
gambling in Monte Carlo...
...safariing in darkest Africa.
We didn't even know if they loved us.
But when the sheik's yacht went down...
...they managed to write us
a beautiful goodbye note...
...that was found floating in
a champagne bottle amongst the debris.
Excuse me.
They were very devoted parents.
It was a car crash in Canada.
- So you'll send me those escrow papers?
- First thing tomorrow.
I'll have to get a locksmith out
for this one.
Peter, pick up your toys, please.
Peter, take this suitcase up to the attic.
Then we can all have ice cream.
And bourbon.
What? What is it?
I'm going to Motel 6.
Oh, for heaven's sake.
I don't see any guano.
He said it looked like that.
That's an African bat. Some kid said
she saw some back in the '60s...
...but we don't get bats
like that in New England.
That's what he saw.
Well, whatever it was, it's gone now.
Bats aren't what I'd worry about
in this house, anyways.
What would you worry about?
Well, personally...
...I wouldn't wanna live in a house
where someone was murdered.
- Murdered?
- Yep.
Little Alan Parrish.
I say his father did it.
There's 1001 places he could've hid
the body in this house.
Especially if he chopped it up first.
Hey up there!
You kids don't wanna be late
for your first day of school.
- Not a bat in sight, ma'am.
- Do you hear that?
There is nothing to be afraid of
in this house.
I can't believe I have to see
your principal after the first day.
What am I gonna do?
Now, let's just try to relax
and finish dinner.
Talk about something else.
We found out why you got
this house so cheap.
Twenty-six years ago, a kid named
Alan Parrish used to live here.
Then one day, he just disappeared.
Because his parents chopped him up
in little pieces and hid him in the walls.
Okay, that's it. I am sick and tired
of your lies, young lady. You're grounded.
Fine, there's nowhere to go
in this stupid town anyway.
But just for your information,
that wasn't a lie.
Did you hear anything a little while ago?
Do you miss Mom and Dad?
No.
Liar.
If you don't cut that out,
they'll send you to a shrink.
Where do you think they're gonna
send you if you don't start talking?
If I get held up at
the permit office, I'll call.
The school bus should be here
any minute.
You guys still have your house keys?
Are you guys listening to me?
Hello?
What?
Maybe I should wait with you
till the bus comes.
Did your parents used
to put you on the bus?
No... No.
Are you sure?
I could drop you off.
No, don't worry about us.
The bus will be here any minute.
Okay. Please be good today.
You do hear it.
Hear what?
Where's it coming from?
Let's bring it over here.
Weird. They're stuck.
"Jumanji, a game for those
who seek to find...
...a way to leave their world behind.
Roll the dice to move your token.
Doubles get another turn.
The first player to reach the end wins."
It's gotta be microchips or something.
You go first.
Okay.
Six.
"A tiny bite can make you itch,
make you sneeze, make you twitch."
Don't!
"This will not be an easy mission.
Monkeys slow the expedition."
What is that?
I bet those monkeys came
from the game.
The mosquitoes too.
I didn't see this part.
"Adventurers, beware."
"Adventurers, beware. Do not begin
unless you intend to finish.
The exciting consequences
of the game...
...will vanish only when a player has
reached Jumanji and called out its name."
- The monkeys are gone.
- Good.
- Put it away.
- Wait!
If we finish the game, it'll all go away.
We'd better do it,
or Aunt Nora will pitch a fit.
We should just get through it quickly.
I mean, there's no skill involved.
No, you rolled doubles.
You get another turn.
Roll.
Five.
"His fangs are sharp.
He likes your taste.
Your party better move posthaste."
I don't like the sound of that.
Judy, someone's in here.
It's not real, Peter. It's a hallucination.
Run, Peter!
I'm back.
My bike.
Somebody roll a five or an eight?
He did.
Thank you! Thank you! Thank you!
Thank you, thank you, thank you!
Thank you.
Sorry if I scared you.
I'm back!
Mom! Dad!
I'm home!
I'm back!
It's me! It's me, Alan, Mom and Dad!
I'm home! I'm back!
Are you my little sister?
No.
I'm Judy and he's Peter.
Where's Mom? Is Dad at the factory?
Are you...
...Alan Parrish?
Yeah. Who are you?
We live here now.
Where's my mom and dad?
We don't know.
This house has been empty for years.
Everyone thought you were dead.
Sorry.
...Said they're about 2 feet tall,
red fur, long tail.
- Give me that description again.
- Red fur and long tail.
Get down off of my car, please,
and get up on the sidewalk.
- What year is it?
- It was brand-new.
- No. What year is it?
- 1995, remember?
- Ninety-five...
- You got some ID?
Let me guess,
it's in your other Tarzan outfit, right?
- Twenty-six years.
- Are you from around here?
I was.
But I've been in Jumanji.
Indonesia. He was in the Peace Corps.
- Carl Bentley, the Sole Man.
- Is this man related to you?
- Yes, sir, he's our uncle.
- Does he always dress like that?
Well, yeah, he's a vegetarian.
Get out of there!
Monkeys. Monkeys.
Is he all right upstairs?
He suffered a head injury
a few months ago.
Don't you move!
Thief! Hey!
- Stop! Stop!
- Don't move, don't move.
Hey, wait a minute!
Where are you going?
To find my parents!
Come on.
Wait!
My dad used to make shoes here.
They were the best shoes
in New England.
Hey!
Sorry.
Easy, girl.
Do you know what happened
to the shoe factory?
Yeah, it folded up.
Like everything else in this town.
It's pretty cold out there.
How about some coffee?
Why would they close Parrish Shoes?
When his kid ran away, Sam put
everything he had into trying to find him.
His time, his money...
Everything.
After a while, he stopped coming to work.
He just quit caring.
I don't think anybody loved his boy
more than Sam did.
Here.
You're gonna freeze out there.
Thank you.
Are the Parrishes still around?
- I see them now and then.
- Yeah?
They're over on Adams Street.
Our parents are dead too.
They were in the Middle East
negotiating peace when...
Our dad was in advertising.
Bet you miss him, huh?
Me too.
There he goes again.
Listen, I know you're upset and all,
but we should finish the game.
We? Why do you need me?
Well, just in case
any other scary stuff comes out.
Plus there's a lion in my aunt's bedroom.
Do I look like a Ringling Brother?
She'll be home soon.
Won't she be surprised?
I hope she's not allergic to cats.
Larry, we need the wheels.
Give me a hand.
- Did we hit her that hard?
- No, it looks like another weird bite.
- Yeah, it's another one, all right.
- Jeez, over 50. What the hell's going on?
- Easy, now. Easy.
- Hey, look.
- Isn't that Mrs. Thomas?
- Who's that?
- The Realtor.
- Quiet.
Listen.
You hear that?
Hear what?
Get in the car.
Okay, think. What came out
of the game before me?
There was a lion,
a bunch of monkeys and...
That!
It's okay, it's okay.
It's just a bug, but we're safe in here.
See? We're fine.
As long as we stay low,
he can't get through there too far, okay?
Don't you worry. We're fine.
Okay. He can't get us in here.
He can't get through the glass.
We're safe.
Either one of you know how to drive?
No? Well, that's no problem.
My dad used to let me
back the car down the driveway.
Once.
So, what's the big deal?
- Buckle up.
- Here we go!
Wait a minute. What? Wait.
Alan, the top!
Piece of cake.
Yeah.
Alan.
Keep that thing away from me!
When are you gonna help us play?
We've gotta hurry.
Our aunt's gonna be home soon.
Well, good. You can inform her
that she's the ex-owner of this house.
I hope you realize, with my parents gone,
this home belongs to me.
Oh, thank you.
No more banana leaves.
Yes.
What do you think those monkeys
are gonna do to the ecosystem?
Hello?
What happened to you?
You shave with a piece of glass?
The Clampetts have a yard sale?
What do you want?
I've never shaved before.
Where are you going?
How about Peter and I play,
and you just sort of watch?
Thanks, I've seen it.
So if you're not gonna help us,
what are you gonna do?
I don't know.
Pretty much take up where I left off.
I wonder if Mrs. Niedermeyer's
still teaching sixth grade.
Come on, Judy, he's not gonna help us.
He's afraid.
What did you say?
You're afraid. It's okay to be afraid.
Let's go set it up in the living room.
You have no idea
what you're getting yourself into.
Whatever it is, we'll handle it
by ourselves. We don't need your help.
I don't think so.
You think monkeys,
mosquitoes and lions are bad?
That's just the beginning.
I've seen things you've only seen
in your nightmares.
Things you can't even imagine.
Things you can't even see.
There are things
that hunt you in the night.
Then something screams.
Then you hear them eating.
And you hope to God
that you're not dessert.
Afraid?
You don't even know what afraid is.
You will not last five minutes without me.
So...
...you're gonna help us?
I'll watch...
...but I'm not afraid.
Peter, that was very cool.
It's reverse psychology.
Dad used to pull it on me all the time.
Ready?
Yeah.
Alan, ready?
There is no "ready."
I'll try it again.
Alan, it's not working.
Oh, no.
It's not your turn.
Yeah, I rolled first. Then Peter twice
because he got doubles.
Now it's my turn again.
No, look.
Two of those pieces are yours, right?
Who's the other pieces?
The elephant was mine.
You're playing the game
I started in 1969.
I'm gonna have to play.
It's not my turn.
Whose turn is it?
Sarah Whittle.
This is where she used to live.
This place gives me the creeps.
We used to play on this porch.
I knew she still wouldn't live here.
Probably married Billy Jessup
and living in a trailer park.
- Come on.
- Let's at least ask.
- Maybe she'll know where Sarah went.
- Of course she'll know. She's a psychic.
Good point.
I remember the porch being a lot bigger.
Hello?
- Can you help us?
- Do you have an appointment?
- No, we're just trying to find someone.
- Madam Serena can't see anyone now.
Well, maybe you can help us.
What is it?
We're looking for someone
who used to live here.
No, I've lived here my whole life.
Well, then you must know Sarah Whittle.
What do you want with Sarah Whittle?
Sarah?
No, I don't go by that name anymore.
Sarah Whittle?
What do you want?
Twenty-six years ago, you played a game
with a little boy down the street.
A game with drums.
How do you know that?
I was that little boy, Sarah.
Alan?
You killed her.
Leave a message
and the doctor will call you back...
...at his earliest convenience.
Dr. Boorstein, it's Sarah Whittle. Listen,
if you could call me as soon as you can.
I think I need to have
my dosage checked.
That event we've been discussing,
the one that didn't really happen?
Oh, boy.
I'm having an episode here today...
...with the little boy
that didn't really disappear.
I'm sitting in his living room,
drinking lemonade.
If you could call me, I'd really be
interested in your interpretation.
Thank you so much.
- He'll call me back.
- While we're waiting...
- God! No, no, no!
- Sarah. Sarah.
- Oh, no, no, no.
- It's okay. Sarah. Please.
I have spent over 2000 hours in therapy
convincing myself that that doesn't exist.
What happened to you was so awful,
I made up this thing...
Sarah, it was awful. It was awful.
It was awful, it really was.
But it was real. Real.
No, no, it wasn't real, Alan. Your father
murdered you, and he chopped you up.
Sarah, come on.
My dad did that?
My father could barely hug me...
...let alone cut me into little pieces.
Twenty-six years ago,
we started playing a little game.
And now...
...we're all gonna sit down
and we're gonna finish it.
And guess what.
It's your turn.
No.
Here.
Play the game, Sarah.
- Oh, no, no.
- Fine.
Just give me the dice and you can
go home. You don't have to play.
Thank you, Alan.
Oh, my God! How could you do that?
It's the law of the jungle, Sarah.
You'll get used to it.
When I think of all the energy I spent
visualizing you as a radiant spirit...
Go on, read it.
"They grow much faster than bamboo.
Take care or they'll come after you."
Oh, great.
Oh, God. Tell me this isn't happening.
Oh, it is. Stay away from the walls.
Don't touch anything.
No quick movements.
- They're beautiful.
- Oh, yeah, they're beautiful.
Don't touch the purple ones.
They shoot poisonous barbs.
And definitely stay away from the pods.
The big yellow ones.
What big yellow ones?
Peter!
I got you! Get his arms!
Get it off me! Get it off me!
Oh, my God!
- Hang on, boy.
- Got him? I'll be right back.
Oh, my God.
Sorry, Angus.
Harvest time!
Are you okay?
Peter.
Oh, my God!
My car. Oh, my car.
Carl, come in, please.
Come in, please, Carl.
Has anybody seen Carl?
I can't believe this.
Start, start, please. Yes!
- Carl? Come in, Carl.
- Carl here.
Where in heaven's name have you been?
We've got an Animal Control situation.
Get Stan and Willy on it.
I'm heading over to the old Parrish place
to check out a suspicious character.
I should've been a fireman.
Yeah.
Sarah!
Get your hands off me!
- The game is not over yet, Sarah.
- Well, it is for me.
You are not in the jungle anymore.
Stop this!
You don't treat people like this.
Okay.
Anybody up for iced tea?
I'm gonna make some tea.
Alan, please, last time I played
this game it ruined my life.
- It ruined your life?
- Yes.
"In the jungle you must wait
till the dice read five or eight."
I was a little girl, Alan.
You disappeared.
And a bunch of bats surrounded me
and chased me down the street.
I was afraid.
I'm sorry, Alan.
No one believed me. I was all alone.
So was I, for 26 years, Sarah.
Me too.
It's okay, Sarah. We're scared too.
But if we finish the game,
it'll all go away.
What if I get stuck in the game?
You won't.
Because I won't stop playing.
And neither will I.
I won't either.
Come on, Sarah.
Please?
I knew this was gonna be a bad day.
Hey, come on, we're gonna be fine.
We just have to keep our heads.
And roll with the punches.
"A hunter from the darkest wild...
...makes you feel just like a child."
What is it?
Van Pelt.
You miserable coward!
Come back and face me like a man.
Not good enough, Sonny Jim.
Coming, ready or not.
Hey, you!
Drop your gun
and get your hands in the air!
Man, I don't believe this.
So even if Alan gets out
of this situation...
...same kind of thing will happen
over and over again.
When you carry around repressed anger,
it attracts a lot of negative energy...
...and things happen, like ending up
in the jungle. That was no accident.
There are no accidents.
Whose turn is it?
- It's my turn.
- Really? Great.
You might've told us
there was a man that hunts people.
Well, I didn't know, okay?
It's just the roll of the dice.
Is he the reason you didn't wanna play?
You didn't wanna play either?
Mr. We-Started-Something-26-Years-
Ago-and-Now-We-Gotta-Finish-It?
What's with this guy?
He's a hunter. He kills things. That's what
he does. Right now, he wants to kill me.
- Why you?
- Why me?
I don't know. You'd think
it'd be a waste of his time.
Maybe he needs something for his wall.
- A Parrish.
- It's your turn.
Have you ever talked with him
about your differences?
- Are you crazy? The man has a gun...
- Don't ever call me crazy, Alan! Ever.
Everyone's called me crazy ever since
I said you were sucked into a game.
- Maybe I should roll.
- Yeah.
I was the girl who saw you murdered.
Do you think anybody showed up
at my birthday party?
- Hello, I'm rolling now. I'm gonna roll.
- Billy who?
What are you, an owl? Come on, Madam
Serena, dig into your consciousness.
- Here, just roll.
- Find the memory...
...of your old boyfriend Billy.
- The little kid who'd steal your bicycle?
- The big kid who took you to the movies.
"Don't be fooled, it isn't thunder.
Staying put would be a blunder."
- No, you're immature. No...
- You are.
- I know you are, but what am I?
- You are. I don't have to fall for this.
Do you feel that?
Run.
It's a stampede!
- Come on.
- The game!
Don't look back!
Not the game!
Why didn't you grab the game, Peter?
Just ignore him, honey. He's a Libra.
- Where are you going?
- He'll head for water!
Here we go. Come on.
- Hello?
- It's Aunt Nora. Where have you been?
Oh, I'm sorry, dear.
You have the wrong number.
Wait for me!
- What can I do for you?
- I'll have a gross of these.
You know, they stopped
making these in 1903.
Damn. Then I shall need
a replacement weapon.
Well, there's a waiting period.
And you'll have to fill out these.
Or I could fill these out.
Louise.
Now, anyone asks,
you didn't get this here.
You're not a postal worker, are you?
Alan!
Quiet.
Okay.
Here, boy.
No!
- Peter!
- Peter, are you okay?
- That was great!
I can't believe you did that.
That was so cool.
- You gave me chills. Oh, my God.
- It was great.
Alan.
It's nice work.
Come on, give me the game. Let's go.
Oh, no.
Act natural.
Hey!
Hide the game.
I don't believe this.
Every time there's trouble, I run into you.
Me? I don't know
what you're talking about.
- All right. I'm taking you in.
- I'm not going anywhere.
Just...
All right.
Just a second. You can't take him, he's...
- Her fiancé.
- Wait. You said, he's your uncle.
It's all right. I'll be back soon.
Blast.
Remember, you said
you'd never abandon your friends.
- We'll finish the game later. Okay?
- Later?
Van Pelt. Van Pelt.
I suggest you all go home now.
Okay.
Now how are we supposed
to finish the game?
We can't.
We can't finish it without him.
Judy!
What?
What happened?
I thought I could end the game myself.
I was only 10 spaces away.
"A law of Jumanji having been broken...
...you will slip back
even more than your token."
You tried to cheat?
No, I tried to drop the dice
so they'd land on 12.
Oh, okay, honey.
Well, that would be cheating.
Peter, your hands! Look at your hands!
Come in, this is Willy.
They cleaned out Larry's Hardware.
I can't stop them.
Get the National Guard down here now.
All right. What is this about?
I know you know.
Yes, I do. But you wouldn't
believe me even if I told you, Carl.
Wait a minute. Wait a minute.
How do you know my name is Carl?
I know a lot more than that.
I know you used to work
on the stamping line at Parrish Shoes.
They used to call you Sole Man.
Sole Man, yeah, that's right.
I was in there too, man,
till old man Parrish fired me.
- He fired you?
- Yeah, man.
And I had something, I could've turned
this whole town around.
- Your shoes.
- Right.
Listen, Carl?
I know it doesn't mean much
after 26 years...
...but I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
Sorry for what?
It's me, Alan.
Thank you. Come on.
What's going on?
Well, apparently, there's a sale, honey.
You just saw three monkeys
on a motorcycle, didn't you?
- Yes.
- Good girl. Come on.
Well, maybe we can bail him out
with a check.
Thank you.
You tell that sniveling coward from me,
if he wants...
Boy!
Get out of my way!
Hey, kid! What are you doing?
- Give me that, boy!
- No!
Hey!
- Peter!
- Help me!
Get me out of here!
- It's all right.
- Oh, my God, Peter. Come on.
All right.
- There it is.
- Wait here.
Gotcha, girlie.
No.
When Alan hears of your predicament,
he'll come.
He doesn't even know I'm here.
It won't work. Your plan's ruined.
- Don't move or I'll blow your brains out!
- Okay.
- Call the cops!
- That should do the trick.
- Oh, yeah.
Price check!
If you let me go, I can stop all this.
It sounds like The Twilight Zone,
but it's true.
Please, you gotta help me on this.
I know I'm gonna regret this.
All right. Just hold still.
- Okay.
- There, I let you go.
Now what are we gonna do? Hey.
- You are gonna stay here.
- My keys!
It's for your own good. Stay there.
- My handcuff keys. Wait!
- This is something I have to do!
- Alan!
- You'll thank me someday.
Come in, Carl, code red.
Hostage situation at Sir Sav-a-lot.
A woman and two children.
Sounds like the armed perpetrator
in the pith helmet you reported.
Carl? Come in, Carl.
- Lorraine? Come in.
- What's Sir Sav-a-lot?
- It's a discount store.
- Move over.
- Wait, wait, wait. Gently, gently.
- Okay. All right, all right.
Don't worry, I've done this before.
Once.
Where's Sir Sav-a-lot?
- Monroe and Elm.
- The Episcopal church.
It's not the church anymore.
It's a Speedy Burger.
Or at least it was. I don't know
what's left of it. People are going loopy.
Judy!
We got company.
No. It's all right. That's a traffic cop.
He'll back us up.
- Here's the game.
- Come on. Get out of here.
Rats.
- Turn the siren off. Right there! Okay.
- Okay, I got it.
Stop your cringing, woman.
I could have shot you at any moment.
Then why didn't you?
You didn't roll the dice, Alan did.
There it is, there it is. Hit the brakes.
- Hit the brakes!
- I'm hitting them. I'm hitting the brakes!
- The brakes! I am hitting the brakes!
He should be here any moment.
Sarah!
- Are you all right?
- Yes.
- Where's Peter?
- I'm here.
Oh, great.
So remember, circumstances are
never, ever out of your control.
End of tape three.
Update on the extraordinary events
unfolding in Brantford, New Hampshire.
Ninety-eight people have been
hospitalized with symptoms...
...ranging from inexplicable fevers
and rashes to violent seizures.
Local resources have been strained
to the breaking point.
And state health officials are now asking
those with such symptoms to dial 911.
I got it.
Alan, talk to him. Please?
What? We don't have time for this, okay?
I know, but he's a kid
and he was trying to help.
- All right, come on.
- Thank you.
Judy, come on.
I warned you about this, Peter.
No, you wanted to play the game.
What, are you crying? You don't cry,
all right? You keep your chin up.
Come on, keep your chin up.
Crying never helped
anybody do anything, okay?
You have a problem,
you face it like a man.
Hey. Hey.
I'm sorry. Twenty-six years buried
in the deepest, darkest jungle...
...and I still became my father.
It's okay. Come here, I'm sorry.
Hey, it's all right.
Remember what you said?
It's all right to be afraid.
It's not that.
What is it?
Okay.
Ready?
Don't worry, we're gonna have you turned
back into your old self in no time flat.
Because we're gonna go in here
and together...
...we're gonna sit down,
we're gonna finish that game.
No matter...
...what.
Suddenly, I feel right at home.
Lorraine, this is Carl.
I think I know who's behind this.
I'm heading over to the Parrish place.
Give me some backup.
Lorraine?
Wait. Wait!
Now what?
Stop!
Wait! Stop!
Is there a problem, ma'am?
- Oh, can I have a ride home?
- Where do you live?
Jefferson Street. The old Parrish place.
Do you have children? A boy and a girl?
- Oh, my God. What happened?
- Get in.
I'll explain it all on the way.
Fine! Take it!
We gotta get to that house.
- Shouldn't we play someplace else?
- No.
I grew up in this.
It's out there that scares me.
- Okay, it's my turn.
- Sarah, if you roll a 12, you win.
Okay, ready? Here I go.
It's okay.
"Every month at the quarter moon,
there'll be a monsoon...
...in your lagoon."
Monsoon.
Well, at least we're inside.
Yeah, right.
Well, a little rain never hurt anybody.
Yeah, but a lot can kill you.
Come on.
This way!
- What do we do now?
- We get to higher ground.
- Okay.
- Come on! Stay together!
Peter, go!
You all right, Peter?
- Judy!
- Alan?
- What?
- What is that?
Swim! Go! Go!
- Alan!
- Judy! Swim! Go! Move!
Keep going!
Stay on the table!
Peter! Feet out of the water!
On the chandelier!
Stay with Peter!
Come on, Sarah.
Peter!
Hang on, Sarah!
Are you okay? Are you okay?
Where...?
- Alan!
Judy? Peter!
Ma'am, step back
and let me handle this, please.
It's probably nothing.
They probably left the TV on too loud.
Peter? Judy?
I always wanted to do this.
Could you step back, please?
- Alan, give me your hand!
- Alan!
- Grab my hand!
- I got it.
Alan!
Take the game.
Here. Here you go.
- You okay?
- Yeah.
Alan, you wrestled an alligator for me.
It was a crocodile.
Alligators don't have
that little fringe on their hind leg.
Come on.
My mistake.
It's okay.
Come on.
Okay, it's my turn.
I've got it.
Colonel Mustard in the library
with the wrench.
Clue.
Okay.
"Beware the ground on which you stand.
The floor is quicker than the sand."
- Alan! Okay.
- Help me!
- Help me.
- Okay. Okay. Stay calm.
Don't struggle. Stay calm.
- I'm calm.
- Alan!
- Grab on!
- Okay. Pull!
Okay. I got it. Pull!
Stay calm!
Come on!
Oh, good! All right.
I got you...
Stop giving me things that come apart!
"There is a lesson..."
All right.
"There is lesson you will learn."
Oh, I got you.
"Sometimes you must go back a turn."
- Oh, did I hurt you?
- Oh, no.
Oh, dear.
Thank you, Judy. Thank you.
That was very quick thinking.
Sarah and I would like
to get out of the floor.
So it's your turn, Peter.
Okay.
I thought I'd lost you again.
Thanks for sticking around this time.
"Need a hand? Why, you just wait.
We'll help you out. We each have eight."
What's that? What is it?
- Nothing.
- You don't go... for nothing.
Peter, my dad kept an ax
in the woodshed. Go get it!
- Okay.
- Hurry! Go, go, go!
Sarah!
Judy?
Peter?
No...
There's a...
- Peter!
- Judy! Behind you, get it!
Aunt Nora, it's me. Peter.
Sorry. I can't talk right now.
I'll explain later.
- Sarah.
- What?
It's your turn.
You can finish if you roll a seven.
- I can't roll.
- Put the dice in your mouth.
Judy! Bring the game. Hurry!
Judy!
Judy, are you okay?
I'm fine. Help them.
Come on, Judy. Come on.
- Judy!
- Judy.
Give me the dice.
"You're almost there, with much at stake.
But now the ground begins to quake."
Judy!
- Oh, my God!
- What? What?
I wish Mom and Dad were here.
So do I.
Her only chance is if we finish the game!
It's your turn!
Oh, my God!
Get the game! The game!
No, I won't let you go!
Alan!
Don't move.
Stand up.
What's in your hand?
Drop it.
End of the line, Sonny Jim.
Game's up. Start running.
No.
Aren't you afraid?
I'm terrified.
But my father told me...
...you should always face
what you're afraid of.
Good lad.
You're finally acting like a man.
Any last words?
Jumanji.
It's Jumanji.
No, Alan, no!
What...?
Forgot my speech notes.
Dad, I'm so glad you're back.
I've only been gone five minutes.
It seems like a lot longer to me.
Hey, I thought you told me
you were never gonna talk to me again.
Whatever I said, Dad, I'm sorry.
Look, Alan...
I was angry.
I'm sorry too, son.
Look, you don't have to go to Cliffside
if you don't want to.
Let's talk it over tomorrow. Man to man.
How about father to son?
Great.
Hey, I've gotta get going.
I'm the guest of honor.
Dad?
Back in 196...
I mean, today in the factory...
...it wasn't Carl Bentley's fault.
I put the shoe on the conveyer belt.
Glad you told me, son.
Thanks.
Bye, Dad.
Goodbye.
- Holy smokes! Judy and Peter!
- Alan.
They're not there.
It's 1969.
They don't even exist yet.
I'm starting to forget
what it's like to be a grown-up.
That's okay,
as long as we don't forget each other.
Or Judy and Peter.
Alan, there's something
I've been wanting to do.
And I better do it
before I feel too much like a kid.
They probably don't teach driver training
in the sixth grade, huh?
Merry Christmas.
Do you want any of these?
No, Dad. It's a new cross-trainer.
It's doing fabulous.
- No, it's not a bra, it's a shoe.
- Honey, they're here.
Listen, Dad, I gotta run. Merry Christmas.
We'll pick you up tomorrow, okay?
You'll be the best Christmas gift of all.
Bye-bye! Bye-bye.
- They're here? Let's go.
- Yeah, come on. Okay.
- Hi.
- Lisa, hi.
Pardon me.
Jim! Glad you could make it.
- Thanks. This is my wife, Martha.
- Hi, Martha. This is Sarah.
- Hi, Sarah.
- Where are the kids?
Oh, my God, there they are.
How'd you know?
A guess. A guess, of course.
They're your kids.
Well, you're right, these are our children.
Judy and Peter.
Kids, say hi to Mr. and Mrs. Parrish.
Nice to meet you.
You're just like we remembered you.
I feel like we know so much about them.
Because, you know...
- You've told Alan so much about them.
- Yeah, and I told her.
- I'll go get the presents.
- Sure, honey.
Well, we love children.
- Merry Christmas.
- Cool.
So when can you start?
We were thinking of taking a skiing
holiday up in the Canadian Rockies.
- No!
Sorry.
We... We just...
Need you to get that marketing done
on the new line, pronto.
It's no problem. You know,
I could probably start next week.
That'd be great. Let me introduce you to
the rest of the folks you'll be working with.
Come on in. Our house was your house.
Is. Anytime you'd like.
What's that noise?
Please rate this subtitle at www.osdb.link/5qcm9
Help other users to choose the best subtitles