[Man Narrating]
Let me tell you about my day so far:
Took a little nap
on Mount Kilimanjaro:
Oh, yeah, and I got digits
from this Polish chick in Rio:
And then I jumped back: : :
For the final quarter of the N: B: A: Finals-
courtside, of course:
And all that was before lunch:
I could go on,
but all I'm saying is: : :
I'm standing on top of the world:
The lighter terrain here-
[Man Narrating]
It wasn't always like this:
Once I was a normal person,
a chump just like you:
- Hey, Millie.
- Oh, hey, David.
You got a lot of cities there.
Well, if you're gonna have a dream,
might as well dream big, right?
- Right:
- [Bell Ringing]
See you later.
Hey, Millie.
Give me a sec.
Hey.
I wanted to give you this.
I picked it up at a yard sale in Plymouth.
L-I thought you'd really like it.
It's a little dinged up
and it's missing a few steps, but-
I love it.
- You do?
- I do.
[Boy]
Holy crap, Rice Bowll
- Mark.
- Hey, what's this?
- Christmas come early?
- Mark, stop it.
- Mark, give it back to her.
- Holy crapl
Look what David got Millie!
You guys like the Eiffel Tower?
Wow, if you shake this thing hard enough,
you can hear the Eiffel Tower move.
- Hey, who wants to give it a shake?
- Okay, that's enough!
- Stop it. Just give it back.
- All right.
Okay, I'm sorry.
Here.
Sorry, buddy.
Guess I don't know my own strength.
- I can't believe you're such a jerk!
- I was just playing around.
- It wasn't funny:
- [Chuckles] They thought it was pretty funny.
[Millie]
David?
David, don't go out there.
It's not safe.
David, just forget about it.
Come on, Rice Bowl!
Don't be stupid!
David, come back. Come on.
Just let it go. It's okay!
Stopl It's not worth it:
Just come back: Rlease?
Come on, David!
[Millie]
Be careful: Come on:
- All good. See?
- [Mark] Great: Now come back:
- David!
- Millie, don't go out there!
[Millie, Muffled]
Davidl Davidl Somebody-
- [Groaning, Muffled]
- [Millie] Oh, my Godl
- David- Get help!
- Millie, get back here!
[Millie]
Rlease helpl Davidl
- Call 911 I Davidl
- You can't help him!
- Millie, stop, stop, stopl
- Davidl
[David Narrating]
And that's how it happened the first time:
One second I'm a goner, and the next thing
I know I'm at the Ann Arbor Rublic Library:
Home, sweet home:
Mom left when I was five:
As for Dad, well, let's just say
he wasn't much of one:
You're late:
Supper's cold:
Where you been, anyway?
You know, when I ask a question,
I expect an answer. Okay?
Hey, hey, hey.
What happened to you?
Just kids at school.
Hey, David, get back down here,
get a mop and clean this crap up!
Davidl
Don't make me come up therel
David?
Make the right choicel
- [Door Rattling]
- David! David.
Open the door.
Did I just teleport?
Great.
I teleported to the library.
Look-No, no, no: I'm not going anywhere:
I don't care what you say:
[David Narrating]
And that's when it occurred to me:
This thing that just happened,
it could set me free:
And if she could run away,
so could l:
You're okay.
[David Narrating]
I wanted to tell her everything:
David?
[David Narrating]
I mean, who would have believed me anyway?
[Millie]
Davidl
[David Narrating]
I figured it was time to move on:
Uh, I'd like a room.
You're not gonna be any trouble,
are you? No weird stuff?
Nope.
No weird stuff.
[David Narrating]
And so there I was:
I had a million questions,
like how does this thing work?
How do I control it?
Been there.
[David] Mommy, you can see
the ocean and everythingl
If we're lucky,
maybe we'll see King Kong.
- Really?
- [Laughs]
- You got me?
- Oh, I got you. I'm not letting you go.
[David Narrating]
I was 15:
Come on:
What would you have done?
I figured I'd pay it back someday:
Is there a bathroom for customers?
Hey.
It's this way.
Yeah.
Make it quick.
No problem.
Thanks.
I'm gonna need a bigger bag.
Holy shit.
Whoo!
- Hey!
- ##[Continues]
I said no weird stuff.
Let's go- two days' rent. You owe me rent.
- [Knocks]
- Hello? Hello?
The police and the F.B.I.
Have already been through here.
- Who are you with?
- N.S.A.
They couldn't make
heads or tails of it:
The vault has a time lock,
pressure mounts, steel plates.
- This guy didn't open a door.
- Open a door?
We didn't know we were robbed
until halfway through the day.
I want the security tapes
for the whole month.
And I need the name of everyone who has
a safety deposit box in that vault.
That's confiidential.
Why do you need those names?
Whoever robbed your vault
has been in it before.
Now, I want those names,
and I want those tapes.
Today.
[David Narrating]
So the story had a happy ending:
Rice Bowl was dead,
but I had never been more alive:
So now I'm living in New York:
[Chuckles]
But why settle in one place: : :
When you can have the whole world?
[Announcer]
She floats into the river.
But as you can see, this flood became
more severe about 10 minutes ago.
The question now, Pat, is,
what will happen to these people?
It would take a miracle
to get to them:
Good afternoon, Mr: Jones:
- How they doin'?
- Down by six at the half.
Don't think you'll be
needing that umbrella.
You never know.
- [Man] Watch itl
- [David] You mind if I join you?
- [Woman] No:
- What are you drinking?
Gin and tonic.
Uh, Tanqueray and tonic.
Two of'em, please.
So, you live in London?
- Taxi!
- #So what the hell are you here for #
[Whispers]
Shit.
Dude, this totally sucks.
Hey, I thought this was where the storm
was supposed to hit.
- I heard it hit Fiji.
- Fiji, huh?
Yeah. They got,
like, 30-foot swells.
Really?
Let's go.
? Ror que?
? Ror que? Why?
Because you are an abomination.
Only God should have the power...
to be all places at all times.
One less of you to worry about.
Cut him down!
Let's get the hell out of here.
- [Rhone Rings]
- Yeah?
We have a lead on the bank, sir.
I'll be on the next plane.
Hey, Angelo.
How'd they do?
- Not so good.
- Ah.
- Told you you wouldn't be needing that umbrella.
- Yeah. You were right.
Don't run:
Eight years
we've been looking for you.
And who are you?
My name's Roland.
- What are you doing in my apartment?
- Oh, we'll get to that.
What kind of crook...
leaves a note?
- I think I need to talk to my lawyers.
- Why?
You're not under arrest.
- You mean you're not the-
- Police? Mm-mmm.
Anybody can rob a bank.
What I'd like to know is how you rob a bank
without opening any doors.
Come on:
I'm sure you can think of something:
Look, uh,
if you're not the police...
and I'm not under arrest...
I think I'd like you to leave.
- [Knob Rattling]
- You need some help with that?
Been a while
since you used a door, huh?
Oh, I know who you are.
And I know what you are.
This conversation's over-
This conversation's not over...
until you answer my question!
Tell me, how'd you
last this long? Huh?
Who's helping you?
Jumpers.
Kinda hard to jump with 1,000 volts of
electricity passing through your brain, huh?
Perfect!
Who's protecting you?
Give me an answer so I can go home.
I hateJumpers.
You think you could
go on like this forever...
living like this
with no consequences? Hmm?
There are always consequences.
Where you goin', huh?
I've got you now.
You think you can hide behind a wall,
go anywhere, do anything?
Not anymorel
David? David!
That you?
David! David!
Don't go!
Don't go. Just-Just-
Just hear me out.
Okay?
David-
l-I don't know if
I'm going crazy here or not.
I don't know a lot of things these days,
but if you can hear me-
Just wait, David! Don't go!
I gotta talk to ya!
David, if you can hear me, Son...
it's okay.
You can come home...
anytime you want:
You're not crazy.
- Telecommunications.
- This is Roland.
He got away.
We have his jump sites.
I want everybody up and running:
Everybody.
[Man On Radio, Indistinct]
Ricking up transmission:
Who is this?
May I help you?
Yeah, uh-
Hi, Mrs. Harris.
It's me, David.
David?
David Rice?
Millie was right.
You're not-
Dead. Yeah.
No, I'm not.
Actually, I was hoping
you could tell me where to fiind Millie.
Millie. She's got her own place
over on Morton.
Number 260.
- She's still here?
- Yeah, uh-huh.
She works at Houlihan's Bar
down by the campus.
- ##[Rock]
- [Man] That's itl
[Woman]
Millie, need those pitchers:
Okay, you saw her.
Holy crap!
Rice Bowl?
Mark!
Mark Kobold!
Sorry, man.
I don't know you.
Jesus Christ!
Am I seeing a ghost?
Is this some kind of
sixth-sense shit?
I don't know what you're
talking about. Okay?
Hey! Everybody!
It's Rice Bowl!
Come on, don't you wanna grab a beer
with an old buddy from high school?
- I'm not this David-
- [Millie] David?
Yo, it's the Rice Cake.
- Millie?
- Hi!
You were gonna leave
without saying anything?
Uh-
[Chuckles]
- Sorry. I didn't see you.
- No?
Weren't you just up there
staring at me for the past 45 minutes?
Yeah, David.
Why didn't you say somethin'?
- I think you're drunk.
- I'm not drunk. Okay? I'm cool.
I am totally, 110% cool.
Yeah, that was really cool. Why don't you
go fiind a bench and sleep it off. Okay?
Why don't you go make me
a drink, sweetheart? Huh?
A little splash of that.
[Laughs]
- [Grunts]
- Hey! No!
- [Crowd Shouting]
- [Man Shouting] Fightl Come onl Fightl
- Come on.
- [Grunting Continues]
- Mark!
- Come on, manl
- [Millie] Stop it, you guysl
- Yeahl
Rice Bowl goes down!
Whoo!
[Groaning, Panting]
Wh-What did you do to me?
Freak!
Guess I don't know my own strength.
Hey, wh-
- [Gasps] Hey. Are you okay?
- Hey.
Yeah.
Where's Mark?
- He took off.
- What?
Yeah, I don't think, uh, he's gonna
come back anytime soon.
Oh.
Bleeding a little.
We should take care of that.
Come on.
So, you saw me as soon as I came in?
Maybe.
I didn't know what to say.
How about, " Hi. Hello.
Been a long time. How are you?"
- Hi.
- Hello.
- Been a long time. How are you?
- I'm good.
How are you?
Why don't we skip this boring stuff?
You know, I didn't think,
uh, you'd still be here.
Where else would I be?
You had those lists, right?
And you were gonna
go travel the world and-
Things change.
We all need to grow up, right?
So what do you do?
Banking.
I'm in banking.
In banking?
How'd you get into that?
It's pretty easy, actually.
I just sort of landed in it.
Didn't you flunk algebra?
No.
- Fiona, I'm gonna take my break now.
- Yeah, sure. You bet.
- ##[Rock]
- [Clears Throat] So, you're back.
What now?
What's your plan?
Maybe gonna do some traveling.
I was thinking of maybe
checking out Rome, actually.
You were thinking
of checking out Rome?
You know that was my dream.
Don't try to rip me off. Okay?
- So come with me.
- So come with you?
- You're asking me to go to Rome?
- Mm-hmm.
I mean, only if you want to
skip the boring parts.
I got it.
I'll take it!
- Thank you:
- As you like.
Yeah, yeah.
Can you believe just 10 hours ago
we were in Ann Arbor?
Yeah.
[Man]
What does the C: L: A: Want with this?
I'm afraid that's classifiied.
Really?
Well, then I'm afraid I'm gonna
have to see a federal warrant.
'Cause I don't believe you are
who you say you are.
Certainly.
Great.
Another cop.
So, Mark, tell me
what happened at the bank.
I told them already.
You're just another suit.
You're never gonna believe me.
It says here you were
beamed into the vault.
You wanna laugh about it?
Go ahead. Have a laugh.
You hear me laughing?
The girl's name is Millie Harris.
She boarded a plane to Rome 16 hours ago,
and she didn't go alone.
So, what do you think?
I think there's something
you're not telling me.
What do you mean?
This room.
First class.
Usually in my life,
when things seem too good to be true: : :
It's because they are.
- I told you, I'm in banki-
- Banking?
See, I know
that you flunked algebra.
If you don't wanna
tell me everything, that's fine:
But just don't lie to me.
I'm not lying to you.
No?
Good.
Can't... reach it.
I could eat.
- ##[Continues]
- You know, you could've just
asked me out on a date.
- Grazie:
- # This head spins around #
- ##[Continues]
- You know, this has always been
number one on my list.
I know.
You must be pretty good
at this, huh?
Good at what?
- #Baby #
- Rookie.
- #Oh-ohh, ohh-ohh ##
- No idea.
- W-W-W-W-Wait!
- Sorry, sir.
- Sorry, sorry, sorry. No. No. It's impossible.
- What?
- It's closed.
- What do you mean, it's closed? How is it closed?
- We just wanna go inside there.
- No, it's impossible. No, no.
- It's the Colosseum. How is it closed?
- It's impossible.
David, it's okay: I got to see it from outside:
That's good enough:
- You know, she came all this way to go inside.
- Hey, come on.
Sorry, he's- I don't know.
- Ciao:
- Bye.
Milliel
- Come on:
- What?
Come on.
How about a private tour?
It's closed. We can't
break into the Colosseum.
Who said it's closed?
The door was open.
Wanna see the Colosseum or not?
Come on.
We so should not be doing this.
[Millie]
This place is amazing:
[David]
I wanted you to see this:
You've gotta admit,
it's worth the risk.
Yeah.
- [Laughing] It's so cool!
- It is.
Down here is where they used to keep
the gladiators and the lions in cages?
- We should go down there.
- Can't go down there. It's off-limits.
- Even when it's open.
- Nothing's off-limits.
What?
Psst! Millie!
Did that door just open too?
- It's open now.
- Yeah.
You're gonna want to see this.
Trust me.
Bet you that's worth something:
[Laughs]
Maybe:
I think he's telling you
do not enter.
You speak Italian?
No.
- Well, uh, I'ingresso: : :
- Uh-huh?
Means "come on in."
Oh! I thought it meant "bullshit."
Well, no, that means that you should
stay here while I go around...
and open it from the other side.
It's all right.
You'll catch on.
Mmm.
Thank you very much.
Next showing will be at 6:00.
Don't forget to tip your usher.
- Oh, uh-
- Uh, do you mind, man?
- Whoa!
- Just a little privacy, eh?
- Sorry, man.
- Big Colosseum: Guy peein'?
This isn't a fashion show.
I'm taking a piss. Do you mind?
Place is all yours.
Wouldn't open that door if I were you,
not if I wanted my girlfriend to keep breathing.
What are you gonna do anyway?
Bring her down, have a nice, romantic picnic?
Nice little tea party?
Is that what you think is gonna happen?
- If you so much as look at her wrong-
- You gonna jump me? Where?
Did you think you were the only one?
You really have no idea, do you?
You lead the life you live.
You think you can just go on a little
Roman holiday and they wouldn't notice?
Just jump
all over the place-
jump, jump, jump,
jump, jump, jump-
and nothing's gonna happen?
Well, they've noticed.
Not me.
I mean I already knew.
I'm not talking about me, but them.
Down there.
Hello, boys.
Just me, then.
- [High-pitched Charging]
- Huh. That's new.
Welcome to the war.
Just let me know if you guys
are gettin' tired.
- Close.
- David?
- [Screams]
- What's going on?
Great. Let's meet
the girlfriend, shall we?
No.
- [Grunts]
- Who are these people?
Paladins.
Paladins killJumpers.
I kill Paladins.
Class dismissed.
Rolizial Rolizial
- Rolizial
- Uh-oh.
Wait!
I just came through your jump scar.
What do you think
you're doing here? Huh?
If I were you, I'd jump right back.
You're not supposed to see
all this stuff. Get out!
So if you'd like to
kindly fuck off, as in now.
Maybe your girlfriend's still alive.
- Hey.
- What happened to you?
- Uh, nothing.
Let's go. Come on.
I think we should just get out of here.
[Millie]
That didn't sound like nothing:
You were right. Okay? I shouldn't have
gone down there. Everything's fiine.
Come on. We can
still make the museum.
- [Woman Speaking Italian]
- David?
Will you talk to me?
Rlease?
Must be a cab around here somewhere.
Why aren't you talking to me?
Please talk to me.
- I'll tell you everything back at the hotel. Okay?
- I'm not waiting for the hotel.
- Look, Millie, it's, uh- it's all fiine. Okay?
- No, it's not all fiine.
- I wasn't supposed to go back there.
- [Men Shouting In Italian]
- [Speaking Italian]
- Huh?
Uh, no comprende:
- [Italian]
- No, I think you guys made a mistake.
- Be quiet.
- You're looking for that guy over there.
- [Italian]
- I'm sorry. I know I wasn't
supposed to be back there.
Calma, calma, calma, calma:
Can't you just let us off with a warning-
Whoa! Okay, okay.
- [Italian]
- Okay, okay, okay.
- Millie, just go back to the hotel. Okay?
- No-
- No, no, we're not together:
- I'm with him!
I don't know her.
Millie, go back to the hotel.
- No. No.
- [Siren Wailing]
I told you.
I want to see Millie.
- Where is the body?
- I didn't do anything, okay?
L-I don't know how many times
you want me to tell you the same thing.
Do you know how much longer
he's gonna be back there?
We wait for magistrato:
Yeah. I know. We've been waiting for
a magistrato all night.
I don't speak your-
I don't know what you're saying.
Now you "seat," or we seat you.
- Okay.
- Seat!
I seat.
- [David] She's got nothing to do with this:
- [Speaking Italian]
Allora, the magistrate is here.
We will hold on to your passport.
Don't worry:
You won't need it where you're going:
Hello, David.
You've only got about 30 seconds before
they come through that door: You understand?
You have to get out of here.
- Ditch the girl. If she's with you, she's dead.
- Mom:
- Mom.
- Twenty seconds, David.
Mom! Mom!
Hey!
Millie.
All done. You okay?
Mm-hmm. Hey.
- I'm free to walk.
- They just let you go?
- They just let me go.
- Just like that?
Just like that.
Come on.
[Millie] If they just let you go,
why are we running?
Well, uh, they really strongly suggested
that we leave town now.
- But what did they say to you?
- Asked me some questions.
- For eight hours?
- They had a lot of questions.
I really want to trust you.
You're making it extremely diffiicult.
All right. So trust me.
Let's go.
Whoa!
Whoa! Hey.
- Can you take us? Yeah?
- ##[Car Radio: ; Rap]
Get in the cab, Millie.
Millie, get in the car.
Please.
Please get in the cab.
That's yours:
Remember how I told you you didn't
need to tell me everything?
I changed my mind.
What's in the backpack?
Where did you get that?
I don't want to lie to you.
But you don't want to
tell me the truth either.
I can't get on this flight
with you, Millie.
This is as far as we go together:
- [Woman] To Detroit?
- Mm-hmm.
[Roland]
Roland:
[Man]
We lost him, sir.
- How many did you send?
- Two men.
- I told you to send everybody.
- Well, she said two would be enough...
but, uh, they missed him.
It's like he knew we were coming.
We're searching the grid now.
Keep me informed.
I'm taking a different tack.
William Rice?
Yeah.
I.R.S.
Could we, uh, go inside and talk?
I don't have to ask.
That's a courtesy.
- [Chattering On TV]
- So, what's this all about?
Your son. David.
Why? Is he in some kind
of trouble or something?
This will go a lot swifter
if you let me ask the questions.
When's the last time
you saw your son?
Eight years ago.
Eight years?
That's right.
What about friends?
Anybody I can talk to?
He didn't have
a whole lot of friends.
I'd like to talk to
David's mother if I could.
Yeah, me too.
If you fiind her, tell her I said hello.
That her?
Mary Rice. At least that was
her name back then.
When's the last time you saw her?
She split when the kid turned fiive.
Five. Oh.
Haven't heard a word since:
If I hear anything,
I'll be sure to give you a holler.
- No, you won't.
- No. I won't.
Have you seen the special move
you can do on this new thing?
They've added this new control and, like,
you just- If you-Just double-click it. See that?
What do you say?
Whoa.
Still alive, are ya?
- [Man On TV] I'm hitl
- [Man #2 On TV] He's dead:
- What? That's just great.
- There's more of them?
Hundreds more: I'm tracking 10 right now:
What do you care? There's lots more:
- What about the rest?
Like I said, I hunt them.
- Start again:
- So who are these guys?
I told you.
They're Paladins.
Yeah, you told me their name.
You didn't tell me what they want.
- [Machine Gun Fire On TV]
- Well, it's pretty simple,
isn't it? They want us dead.
- Didn't you fiigure that out yet?
- [Chuckles] Yeah. No, I got that much.
- Good. I'm glad.
- Yeah. Thanks.
- Do you mind just, uh-
- Why?
Because we can do
whatever the hell we want.
- Now can you please just-
- I'm hit!
- He's dead.
- Great. Thanks.
You really don't get it, do you?
Paladins have been killing
Jumpers for years.
Way back since medieval times.
They're fanatics.
Religious nut jobs.
Inquisition. Witch hunts.
That was them.
Look. They're smart.
They're fast. They're organized.
No matter what, they'll kill anyone
that gets in their way.
Like your family.
Your friends.
That little girlfriend
you're traipsing around Rome with you.
They're dead.
All of'em.
Get used to it.
It's just a matter of time.
I'm gonna get some takeaway.
Do you want some?
He's your father.
I'm sorry. I talked to him,
but he wouldn't budge.
He can be so stubborn:
I don't know how my mother puts up with him:
Somebody get some help!
- Now!
- [Man] What happened?
- [Woman] What's going on in here?
- [Chattering]
- [Man] Get the paddles:
- [Shouting]
You okay? Stay still.
[Man]
I'm not getting a pulse:
What the hell happened here?
Oh!
- [Whoosh]
- Mark.
- Jesus Christ.
- What did you tell him?
- How did they know about Ann Arbor?
- Don't touch me.
- Who'd you tell?
- Stay the hell away from me.
Was it a black guy with white hair?
Was his name Roland?
Just answer the question...
or I'll drop you off the top
of Mount Everest, okay?
- What? What?
- What did you tell him?
I don't-What? Tell what?
I know you told him
about home, all right?
I know you told him about Ann Arbor.
Did you tell him about Millie?
I told him everything.
Why?
Why did you do that?
- Why not?
- [Shouts]
Who are you?
Where'd the Paladin go?
- Swimming.
- Pacific?
No. Actually, Atlantic.
Nice little shark pit round Cuba.
Uh, what do you think you're doing?
- Put that stuff back!
- Actually, I need to borrow a few things.
Just stay away from the wall!
I'll cut your eyes out.
[Grunts]
I need to fiind Roland.
No, you don't.
- I only got eight hours.
- Eight hours?
There's a girl-
Her flight lands in eight hours.
Think that stuff s gonna help?
That stuff s four years old.
Do you want me to jump you back to
high school so you can learn something?
I've been tracking him for 10 years.
Look at this. Look.
You see this?
Our fiirst round in Nepal.
You should see the one he gave me
back in Prague.
Look. Forget it.
Forget Roland.
Don't waste your time.
Just leave it to me.
- Do you mind?
- Look.
Little, uh- Little privacy here?
You know, this is
kind of my thing. Just-
Just- Get-You know, turn around.
Yeah.
I'm- I was thinking
that if we do this together...
we could get him.
What? You mean, like, you and me?
- Yeah:
- Like we team up?
- Yeah.
- [Chuckles]
Look. I'm sorry,
but I don't play well with others.
Do me a favor, yeah?
Don't be here when I get back:
Find a rock. Crawl under it.
Stay there.
Joi woo, brother.
That's "good-bye" in Chinese.
Yeah. No. I've been meaning to call.
Really. I still really want to get the tattoo.
You can't keep following me.
Actually-[Clears Throat]
I'm the one person who can:
Yeah, lucky me.
Why are you walking?
I mean, l- I know Tokyo pretty well.
I got a lot of jump sites here.
You know, l-l- I like walking for a change.
Makes me feel normal.
You, uh-You ever read
Marvel Team-up?
Yeah, I read it. And?
Two superheroes joining forces
for, like, uh, a limited run.
I see what you're trying to do, yeah?
I'm not buying it.
For your own sake, just go home.
- You live in a cave.
- It's called a lair.
And what's the point?
I'm just saying, you know.
We, uh, kind of have this common thing.
And I know where to fiind Roland.
[David]
So we doing this, or what?
Sorry. Clutch stuck.
- You're real subtle.
- Yeah, I'm not gonna get rid of you, am I?
You might want to hold on, son.
That was close.
Not bad.
This thing must be two tons, easy.
How are you, uh-
If it moves, I can jump it.
Actually, I knew this Jumper once-
crazy bastard-
tried to hop a whole building.
[Chuckles]
- Won't be trying that again.
- Why's that?
That's 'cause he's dead.
Killed him.
Still managed to shake it
a little though.
So how long you been doing this for?
- Doing what? Driving?
- No. Jumping.
- [Radio Channels Changing]
- Since I was fiive.
- Five?
- Yeah.
- ##[Radio: ; Rock]
- How'd you keep it a secret from people?
- Like your parents:
- It's pretty easy when they're not around.
- ##[Radio: ; Heavy Metal]
- Where were they?
Not around.
You know, my mom-
she took off when I was fiive.
I know what it's like
to not, you know-
My dad, he-
Did I ask about your family?
I mean, are we on
Oprah here or-
[David]
Griffin, I can't keep doing this: I gotta go:
Her flight lands any second.
I need an answer.
This is it, all right?
Marvel Team-up, now or never.
- [Horn Honks]
- A very limited run, right?
Save her, kill him, you know.
We're done.
All right, Spidey.
Hey!
[Man On R: A:]
Due to increased security measures, all bags-
- Hey!
- Detroit International Airport asks you: : :
To keep your bags in your
possession at all times:
[Woman On R: A:] Flight 427 to Cleveland
will now be boarding at Gate Number 5:
- Hey.
- The flight from Rome landed an hour ago.
Oh, no.
You didn't check on the flight?
All right. Well, we gotta fiind her,
you know.
You go fiind her. I'm gonna arm up.
Meet me back at the lair.
- All right?
- Fine.
What you looking at?
Boo!
Hey. Uh, I'm Millie's friend,
David. Is she here?
Last I checked she was with you.
Hey. Your friend came by.
- What are you talking about?
- Black guy, white hair. You just missed him.
- Jesus.
- Hey.
David, wh-
What the hell are you doing here?
I buzzed, but you didn't pick up.
- So you just broke in?
- Yeah. Well, I needed to
make sure that you were okay.
No, David: I'm not okay:
I got left in an airport in Rome:
I'm sorry.
You're sorry.
Thank you.
I think you should leave.
David, you need to leavel
[Roland] Come on: Snap to it:
We don't have much time:
- What? What are you doing?
- Uh-
- David, I told you to leave.
- Um-
- "Um" what?
- I'm not in banking, okay?
- No, really?
- I mean, the money did come
from a bank, you know.
- Yeah.
- Uh, a few banks, actually.
- Are-Are you telling me you're a bank robber?
Small part. Uh-
Will you please get out of my house?
Uh-huh.
- [Screams]
- Millie, I'm sorry.
Wh- Oh, my God. Okay.
- I'm really sorry, but we gotta go:
- Just go. Leave me alone.
Come on.
This might hurt a little bit, okay?
- It's okay.
- Where am I?
Trust me, okay?
[Echoing]
- I'm not gonna hurt you.
- Don't you even come near me.
- Millie.
- Don't even come near me.
I'm gonna explain this, all right?
I'm gonna explain everything.
In here.
Just, uh-Just stay where you are, all right?
Just stay right there.
- David?
- [Roland] Hurry up. It's closing.
Griffin:
There's something I gotta tell ya.
- Did you fiind her?
- There's something that's gonna piss you off.
- Piss me off?
- David.
What is this?
- David?
- What's she doing here?
- This isn't some kind of clubhouse, you know.
- What is going on?
- Stay inside:
- Wanna see the top of Everest?
- I was trying to tell you.
- Maybe the bottom?
- What?
- Griffiin, listen to me. L-
That's what I was
trying to tell you.
By bringing her down here, they can
follow you. They have a machine.
- It can open wormholes and keep them open.
- What are you talking about?
I'm saying they can
follow us anywhere.
And you brought her here.
- Shit.
- There's two of you?
David, what is going on?
[Panting]
Millie- Millie, stay right here.
No. No!
- What have you done?
- Griffiin-
- Where does this thing go?
- We gotta go.
David, what did you do?
Holy shit.
[Ranting]
Mom?
[Roland]
Thanks for leading me to your friend:
Wait, wait, wait, wait: Why are you
doing this to me? I never hurt you:
I never hurt anybody.
Not yet, but you will.
Sooner or later, you all go bad.
What if I'm different?
- You're not different.
- [Griffiin] I'm different.
- [Whispers] Boo.
- Move!
It's time to send you home to mommy:
- [Groans]
- David?
- Millie:
- [Gasps]
- [Grunts]
- [Millie] David?
Millie, get out of here.
Run, okay?
Millie: Millie, runl
I'm gonna get you down
so you can get me out of here.
Great.
Geez:
Can you take me now, please?
Okay.
I'll take you.
I'll leave you alone.
It was always you though.
Ever since we were fiive.
It was always you.
Please just take me.
Take a deep breath.
I got it.
I trapped them there.
Without the machine,
they're screwed:
No. Millie.
- Got her!
- No!
Millie:
Buddy: Wow:
Crap. I, uh- I didn't expect that.
L- I didn't know.
Now they have to come to us.
Let's get these fiires out.
- [Beeping]
- What's that?
- Huh? What?
- What are you doing?
Nothing. I was, uh,
thinking about going bowling.
- What?
- What? Roland's in there with his whole army.
I'm gonna go back there and end this.
What do you think?
- I'm gonna blow 'em to Timbuktu-
- Yeah, but Millie's in there.
Well, yeah, there is that as well.
- I gotta go- I gotta go get her:
- Huh?
Griffiin, it's my fault that she's there.
All right? You-
- You can't just-
- What?
We gotta get her out:
We have to get her out:
I can hear you! I'm not deaf.
I understand what you're saying.
- All right. Well-
- It's a crying shame. It really is.
But you know what? We all have to
make sacrifiices once in a while. You know.
Where's the detonator?
- [Beeping]
- [David] I don't see you making any:
You know what?
I made mine.
All right?
When I was fiive.
Came to my house
and killed my parents.
David, David.
Yeah?
Look: Before this gets out ofhand,
let's just talk about this:
[Griffiin] How about this for talking, huh?
Am I getting the message through to you?
[David]
I can't let you do this.
Look, David. You touch the safe again,
and I'm gonna kill you. Have you got it?
[Griffiin]
Give me the detonator, David!
- Give it back!
- Sorry, Griffiin!
Give it back!
Don't.
Bad move.
Oh, shit.
- God, I hate Chechnya.
- [Machine Gun Fire]
Where'd you go?
Well, then, brother,
I guess our limited run's done:
The old electricity trick:
That's a nice move:
- Thanks.
- Cut me down, and, uh, we can fiinish this, yeah?
- [Groans]
- You know, it didn't have to be this way.
There's fiive of them back there.
You go back there alone, you're dead.
You hear me?
You can't win!
Get me down, David!
You do this alone, and you're dead.
You're not a hero, David!
You're a Jumper!
You don't save the girl!
Don't you get it?
[Groans]
[Man]
Out of the wayl
- [Roland] Movel
- Watch itl
[Roland]
Got himl
No!
Shit.
- [David Grunts]
- There's some things you can't jump, David.
- Only God should have this power.
- [Electricity Crackles]
Not you, David.
- David, I'm so sorry about what I said before.
Take a deep breath.
David. Hey. Hey.
David? Hey. Hey.
David!
- [Groans] Ooh.
- Shit. I'm sorry.
- Oh, you-
- I'm sorry.
[Millie]
What's my dishwasher doing in the library?
David!
- [Roland] I'm impressed:
- Stay here, okay?
What?
You've come a long way
from robbing banks:
I told you I'm different.
I could have dropped you
with the sharks.
Hi.
[Chuckles]
Can I help you?
Is-Is Mary here?
Hey, Mom.
Honey, why don't you wait upstairs?
Okay.
You know, it wasn't
easy fiinding you.
You shouldn't be here.
So it's true.
You're one of them.
Yes, it's true.
You were five years old
your first jump:
I only had two choices:
Kill you, or leave you.
So you left.
- To protect you:
- I was fiive.
I did what I had to do.
I've never stopped thinking about you.
Not even for one day.
So I'm a Jumper.
You're a Paladin.
That's right.
What now?
I'm giving you a head start, Son...
because I love you.
Good luck.
Hey:
- You okay?
- Yeah.
You sure?
Yeah. I am.
Good.
'Cause I'm freezing.
Can we please go someplace warm?
- Where do you want to go?
- Surprise me.
##[Rock]