Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org
I left Israel in 1980,
after three years in the army.
I was desperate to escape the well-worn path.
You know, high school, university,
work, marriage, kids...
...not me. I wanted to be different,
to experience the extraordinary...
...and to enter the unknown,
discover lost tribes...
...the hidden treasures,
the darkest heart of the jungle...
...which, of course,
is why I ended up in Bolivia...
...South America.
- Thank you, sir.
- You're welcome, may God be with you.
Cheers.
Wait, wait! Wait! Wait! Wait, please!
- Wait, wait! Hey!
- Sir?
Wait, wait!
Thank you so much, sir.
- Thank you. Thank you so much, sir.
- Can I take that?
- Thank you.
- Yeah. Okay.
Thank you. Thank you so much,
everyone. Thank you so much.
- I'm sorry about the bag.
- Oh, no problem.
- Okay, good. I'm Marcus Stamm.
- Yossi Ghinsberg.
- Nice to meet you.
- And you.
Yeah.
You couldn't help but fall in love
with Marcus Stamm.
This Swiss school teacher on a sabbatical...
...had the heart of a poet
and the soul of a saint.
I'd never met anyone like him before.
This is not bad!
I told my parents I'd be back in a year
but I don't think I'm ever going back.
Well, lucky you.
- Morning.
She likes you.
No. It can't be.
Kevin? Hey!
Hey, Kevin!
Oh, my God! Hey! My God! Come here!
What are you doing here?
Marcus! How are you, man?
Hey, I thought you went home after Patagonia!
No, I decided to trek up
the Cordilleras to get some more shots.
- Hey, this is my friend, Yossi Ghinsberg.
- Hey, man. Kevin Gale.
- Good to meet you.
- Good to meet you, too.
Come here, man!
- I had already heard about Kevin Gale.
- He taught me that...
He was a legend amongst
the backpacking community...
...because he had hiked all over South
America, taking incredible photographs.
- But, you know, that's why we're here...
- I also knew...
...he was Marcus's closest friend.
I've only been in South America
for a few months.
- Really? Where were you before that?
- The glamorous world...
- ...of fishing trawlers in Alaska.
- Yeah, that sounds great.
Freezing my ass off in New York,
unloading trucks.
- Really?
- But then went to Vegas...
- ...to make my fortune.
- What happened?
- I lost everything.
- Yeah.
Well, you found this guy,
and that is... priceless.
Okay.
Where'd you just come back in from?
Well, I went up to this place called Colca.
It's in southern Peru.
I was taking shots of condors.
It's amazing.
- That's gross! Yeah.
- Bottoms up.
What is this stuff?
It's called San Pedro.
And how long does San Pedro
normally take to...
- ...kick in?
- You'll know.
Nothing's happening.
Just wait. Trust me.
I actually feel kind of light-headed.
I think it's starting.
I'm flying.
"With the long, lonely night ahead...
...and all the time in the world to decide
on the actions of a future life...
...he closed his eyes."
"It takes time to live."
That's great.
I think I should send this book to my father.
Doesn't he like you on the road?
It's not that he doesn't like it.
He just can't understand it.
And so he thinks...
...I'm throwing my life away.
I read a book once that said...
"The last human freedom...
...is to choose one's own way."
Yeah, that would be nice.
Sorry about him. He's American.
- This? Here?
- On the right, here.
- We're definitely gonna fit in, right?
- It'll be fine.
Hola.
Good morning.
Are you American?
No.
There's nothing like the jungle at night.
It's the most alive sound. Insects, birds.
All these animals around you.
It's like they're screaming at you,
pulsing like electricity.
And then suddenly... it stops.
There is nothing.
Just you and whatever you came looking for.
Between the mining and the missionaries,
there'll be nothing left.
In one generation, all of the Indians gone.
The last of the hidden world, gone.
Gone!
That's what you're dreaming of.
Right? The hidden world?
That's why you're here.
Yossi, I'm not trying to be an asshole.
I'm just saying.
Do you want to be like every other tourist?
You want to go to Machu Picchu?
Anybody can go to Machu Picchu.
But the jungle?
To see wild Indians that nobody has ever
seen before and this guy, Karl, who I met...
- ...who's very nice, he can take us there!
- How do you know he is telling the truth?
He pans for gold.
He's friends with the Indians.
He could be making all of this up,
like a spiel for him.
They know each other,
they're friends, they hang out.
Smiling with the Indians.
You met him in the street!
He showed me photos.
You can take photos of this.
Him standing there, with the Indians, right?
He says the rivers there are filled with
gold and we come back with pockets full.
How can you even trust...
please watch that, it's burning, okay?
Yes. No, that is good.
- Magical. Thank you.
- There you go!
- It's nonsense, Yossi.
- Please... meet him!
- You just... you seem very sold on the idea.
- I'm doing it! I'm gonna do it.
You'll see I'm right.
Cancel your flights home.
- And come with me.
- Cancel our flight home?
That's great.
You're being stupid, Yossi, okay?
Kevin, tell him he's crazy.
I think Marcus is right.
It sounds like bullshit.
Just meet him.
This map's useless. It's what, one to 500?
It's a joke.
It's this and it's here. I'm your navigation.
The Toromonas Indians are here.
"Río Colorado" Chico. We fly to Apolo, here.
We hike to Asariamas.
Then from here to Río Colorado, Chico...
- ...three, four days.
- I've never heard of these Toromonas.
Exactly.
- You're a photographer, right?
- Yeah.
There, you take photos, they get you
straight into National Geographic.
So, what do you say?
50 bucks a head to guide us.
That's it. To help and buy provisions.
And he says he'll pay us back
when we pan some gold.
Yeah. The gold. Yeah. Whatever happened
to talking him out of it? Like we...
No, I know, I know. Look,
I have my doubts as well, but...
...Karl seems to know
what he's talking about.
And he's right. I'd get some amazing shots.
Like, once-in-a-lifetime shots.
Kevin wants to go. Marcus, come on.
You have to come with us.
It'll be an adventure.
- Yeah, okay, fine. I'll come.
- Yeah!
Yes!
We are going to have
the best time! This is "Yes"!
Who's going to the jungle?
- Come on. Is that enough?
- We'll get more food in Asariamas.
- Don't worry. No one starves in the jungle.
- What are these?
Speed. Zippo.
It makes you feel like Superman.
- Right.
- We need a better map.
I told you, there's no better map.
It's all unchartered. Look, nothing.
We just follow the river. In the jungle,
the rivers are your best friends. Okay?
You pay for this?
- We pay for this.
- Of course.
Right, no watches...
...and no wallets.
Karl says... "There's no time in ze jungle."
- No.
- "Can't get lost in ze jungle.
- Can't starve in ze jungle."
- "Invincible, ja?"
- "It's gonna be easy."
- Ja!
I'm gonna miss all this stuff.
What's that?
This my uncle gave to me before I left.
He said it will protect me.
You believe that?
- Kevin.
- What?
I... I don't know.
I don't know,
but he carried it all his life...
...and he survived the war and the camps.
And then two days after
he gave it to me, he died.
Yeah, I think we have room for it.
This is the last frontier on Earth.
Still alive, still wild.
Not for long. We don't like wild.
We don't like untamed.
We're obsessed with control.
So...
...we ruin the whole planet...
...and pride ourselves for creating
stupid national parks...
...with stupid rangers in stupid hats...
...to protect what's already gone.
Why? 'Cause we're scared.
The jungle shows us what we really are.
We're nothing. We're a joke.
God fucked up.
These tribal cultures...
...it seems like they live
in Stone Age but in reality...
...they are far ahead of us.
Invisible. Hidden in the Madidi.
The Toromonas, they understand
that they are part...
...of a much bigger picture.
They don't want what we have. They're smart.
They're truly free.
Shit! Shit! Get it off me! Shit.
- What is it?
- Something hit me!
- What? What?
- I don't know! Like a bat or something.
Something hit me in the face,
like a bat or something.
- I thought I was being attacked.
- Yes, you were. By a killer moth.
This place is getting pretty dangerous, man.
I think we should turn back.
- Boys, go to bed.
- You're okay, though? You're alright?
I might keep watch for a bit.
Watch out. Watch out! There's killer leaves!
They're back again! It's getting you too.
Get them out of my face or you're
gonna get a killer stick up your ass!
Keep moving, guys. It's gonna rain soon.
Rain? There's not a cloud in the sky.
I thought you said the rainy season
didn't start for two weeks!
In rainy season, this is a light shower!
How did you know it was gonna rain?
- I know everything.
- I bet you can talk to the animals too, yeah?
To monkeys I can.
Sure.
Watch it! Not too close.
The threads will burn.
And the whole thing falls apart.
Don't worry. Tomorrow,
we'll find some real food.
It's right there.
It's waiting for us.
That'll be good, Papa. 'Cause you have to
provide for your hungry children, you know?
- Do you see Karl?
- He's just gone on ahead. It's okay.
- Jesus, Marcus!
- Yossi, let me look at that.
- I have something in my bag...
- No, Marcus, stop! Keep walking.
- Okay.
- Come on, go!
We need more than one machete.
Shit!
Karl!
Guys...
Kevin, what if he didn't go that way?
What if he...
- No, he said Asariamas is on the river.
- No! No. We're going to wait.
Marcus, pick up your shit.
He's not coming back. Let's go.
I'm not getting lost just because
you don't want to wait.
- Marcus, we're not lost. We're on a trail.
- You don't know. Karl?
- The river is just down there!
- Karl?
- Marcus, Asariamas is on the river.
- Marcus... stop!
- Karl!
- Why are you here, man?
- What?
I mean, seriously, you're not enjoying
any of this. Why did you come here?
- Hey! I'm enjoying myself, okay?
- Wait. Quiet.
- Quiet? Kevin, what are you talking about?
- Quiet! Be quiet! Quiet!
What is that?
Guys? Kevin, please, let's take
our backpacks off and go. Okay?
What is that?
- Asariamas?
- Asariamas.
Okay.
Hey. Next time you're gonna wander
off without us, let us know, okay?
- We thought we were lost.
- I'm sorry.
I didn't know I was supposed to
hold your hand the whole time.
I thought you wanted an adventure.
Hola!
Asariamas.
I'm sorry about before.
- No, man, I'm sorry too.
- Pass it here.
Hey... hey, guys? It looks like
we're the main show in town.
What?
Hello, everyone.
That old lady's staring at my junk.
Yeah.
It's like if you mixed puke and shit...
...it would taste better than this.
Well.
They were stolen.
- Let me help you there.
- Okay.
Yeah, of course, please.
You are so brave! You are so brave!
How old are you?
Okay. Let's go!
Hey! I found gold!
- Back off!
- Cut it out!
Keep your arms out.
Still.
Amazing.
Look at the world.
Perfectly balanced.
The problem is us. People.
We're the cancer.
We deserve to disappear, seriously.
Communism isn't the answer.
Neither is revolution. I tried both.
The solution is automation.
Mathematical Cosmo politics.
Put a freaking computer in charge.
No ego trips, no pride.
A computer program for the common good.
By the way, I got in trouble for saying that.
I made myself pretty clear.
They're still looking for me.
Monkeys.
Karl! Just shoot it! Just shoot it!
In the jungle... never waste a bullet?
It's gonna be the best meat you ever tasted.
What?
Eat, you pussies.
I'll be damned. It's good. It's really good.
Marcus.
It's just meat. It's good.
Okay.
- Marcus, it really is okay.
- But I just... I can't. I mean, it...
What did you think
you were gonna eat out here?
I'll cook him some rice.
Better keep the fire going tonight.
If there are monkeys, there are also jaguars.
They are monkey hunters...
...and for them...
...we are just big, stupid monkeys.
Okay.
Just for insurances...
- Yeah.
- Keep them dry, just keep them dry.
Every time we stop, take your
shoes off and spread your toes.
Hey, Marcus?
I'll carry some of your load tomorrow, okay?
Yeah, me too.
Thank you, guys.
You know, when the storms build up...
Karl said we have to make it out
before the rainy season...
...but we're never gonna do it
if we're going this slow.
It's Marcus.
He's acting like a... a girl scout.
Come on, it's his feet.
You and me are handling it, right?
But look at him.
Clinging on to his papa.
I guess I'll turn in.
- Yeah, I'm pretty tired too.
- Yossi! No, please... I...
I am sorry that I can't keep up.
You know this is not my fault.
My feet are not my fault!
You know, it's like... because of this...
...we are not friends anymore?
Nothing's changed.
Get some rest, okay?
So, we stay here until Marcus
can walk and... back to Asariamas.
- From here?
- Yeah.
- We're what, 3, 4 days from the Chico?
- Yes, but Marcus can't walk four days.
It's fine, we carry him.
That's fantastic, genius.
We'll watch you. It's impossible. We can't.
No, what we can't do is give up!
All right. So, you guys stay here.
I go and find the Toromonas...
...come back with them,
take you to their village.
No. You're not going anywhere.
We're not staying here without you.
Then we stay here until Marcus
can walk, and go back to Asariamas.
No! No, no, no. We are not going back.
We're not... not going back.
Come on, guys. We've come this far.
There's no way we can stop now.
- Okay. What's going on?
- Okay, so, we'll...
Karl wants to go back.
Wait. There's another way to do this.
Hey, can we build a raft here?
- What, and head downriver from here?
- Yeah. Look, if we build one here...
...we can take it down past
Curiplaya to Rurrenabaque...
...and from there, we can just fly to La Paz.
We'll still see the jungle,
maybe even the Toromonas.
Yeah, look, it's easy
with the finger on the map.
- This river is not easy.
- Is it runnable?
Is it runnable?
- I guess.
- Well, then, it's doable.
You want to at least give it a try?
I'm in. Marcus?
Yeah, okay.
Great. Three against one. We go on the river!
Fuck! What the hell is that?
It's a fire ant.
The first missionaries took Indians
who wouldn't believe in baby Jesus...
...they tied them on trees
and covered them with fire ants.
After that, let me tell you, they believed.
Yeah.
- Have some water.
- Do you have enough?
Yeah, yeah. We share, okay?
- Thanks, man.
- That's okay.
Guys, look.
What one man can't do with one knife, no?
We must work as a team, okay?
If there is calm water, we use the paddles.
When there are rapids, the poles only, okay?
You stay on the front, you in the back.
You must listen to everything I say, okay?
Yeah.
Okay?
You're the captain.
Okay. Let's go.
You okay?
Okay, guys, this is it.
- What about the rocks over there?
- It's okay, just follow the river.
- Stay in the middle, okay?
- Okay.
Okay, Karl?
Karl?
Left. Go left! To the left!
- Hang on!
- Let's go with it!
- Okay. Okay.
- To the right! To the right!
- Which way do we go?
- Go to the right!
- Karl! Karl! Listen to me. Calm down.
- Oh, my God!
- Follow the river!
- Okay!
Take the pole! The pole!
Fucking get off the pole! Follow the river!
Yossi, the rock!
- I see it!
- Be careful, be careful, Yossi, okay?
Okay, guys! Come on! Just let it go!
- The pole's gone!
- You don't know what you're doing!
- To the right!
- Karl!
Shit!
- No, listen!
- Give us one instruction!
- Go left! Go left!
- Oh, my God!
- Go left!
- To the right!
Follow the river!
- Just shut the fuck up and paddle.
- Just listen to me...
- Hey!
- Come on! Hey!
- You're gonna get us all killed!
- We're in the middle of a river.
- Okay.
- We gotta go over there!
Kevin, Yossi, please pick up
your paddles. Listen to Karl.
Shut up! Shut up!
- Go to the right bank! That's it!
- Okay.
Paddle!
Yossi, pick up your paddle.
Shit!
So now you're giving orders?
You can't just listen to Karl?
Shut the fuck up!
This is not Oregon... dude! Don't you get it?
- You have no idea what you...
- Shut up!
Karl... tell us the plan.
The plan? I'll tell you the plan.
We camp here.
Tomorrow, we schlep the raft along
the river until we pass those rapids.
I go hunting now. And Captain America
here can go and fuck himself.
Great work, Kevin. Congratulations.
The only guy who knows where we are
and what we're going to do...
- ...and he just walked away.
- What the fuck is wrong with you?
You're such a fucking let-down,
I can't even believe it.
Did you see Karl on the raft?
He was terrified.
He had no idea what he was doing.
He can't even read the river.
You know what I think?
Karl can't swim.
Holy shit.
You have to go and look for him, Kevin.
You upset him. It's not fair.
- Papa looks after us.
- Oh, enough with the Papa shit, Marcus.
Jesus.
I'll go.
Karl?
Karl? What are you doing?
- You didn't see it?
- See what?
Jaguar.
Scared it off.
Probably thought you were a stupid ape.
What, Karl?
Come on. Let's go.
Go ahead. Good luck.
I'm walking out from here.
No more river for me.
Is this... is this about the rapids?
What do you want me to say, sorry?
Don't be silly. You're the captain now.
I'm hiking to Ipurama. It's three days.
You can come with me or you can
be fish food, I don't give a shit.
Do whatever the fuck you want.
For now...
...I go and take a nice dump...
...in the world's biggest baño.
And you decide what you want to do, boss.
One against three.
Shit.
I've been on rivers my whole life...
...and I don't have a death wish.
But I am telling you, we can do this river.
I want to carry on too, but...
...what about Marcus?
He's going to want to come with us.
He'll be safer with Karl.
It's tough.
But it's wrong for him to come with us.
It's wrong for us to take him.
I'm not taking him.
He's starting to lose it.
He's gotta get out.
You okay with that?
I don't know.
I'm going to talk to him.
Hey.
What's the matter?
I've been talking to Kevin...
...and he's going to continue on the river.
Without Karl?
You know, I love Kevin but he's crazy.
That is insane.
- He can't go alone. That's going to be...
- I know, Marcus, I know. I...
...tried to change his mind.
Look, if he goes on his own,
he's never gonna make it, right?
So one of us has to go with him. And...
Marcus, your feet are bad.
You can't get back on the raft, right?
My feet are fine.
- Really?
- Yeah.
I've been bathing them every day
since we started building the raft, you know?
Okay, well, that's...
...that's good news, actually, for...
...for me. To be honest, I'd...
...I would rather go out with Karl,
just to get out in three days...
...be done with it all.
So, if that's okay with you, maybe...
...just you and Kevin go on the raft.
No, I am sorry.
But I can't go out with him alone.
I mean, you see how he is with me.
My feet, they slowed down
the whole trip, and I'm so sorry.
It's fine, I understand.
If it's okay with you, I would...
...I would really like to go with Karl.
So you're okay,
with your feet being how they are?
- Yeah.
- I...
Okay.
Really?
Yeah.
Thank you, Yossi.
Okay, we are here.
There are rapids everywhere.
Here, here, here.
This is the worst.
You'll be there probably by tomorrow.
- Mal Paso San Pedro.
- Can we make it through there?
Don't even try. There are cliffs
on both sides. No shore, no nothing.
Once you're in, you're dead.
And how are we gonna know when to stop?
There's a beach on the right side.
You have to stop there.
If you can't, jump and swim for it.
Do not go into the canyon.
Okay.
- You take the machete.
- Yeah.
- I keep the shotgun.
- Yeah. That's fine.
- And food, we split 50-50.
- No, no. You need more.
We'll be out in three days.
We reach Ipurama...
...get donkeys and food.
We ride back to Apolo like kings.
Right?
You're so full of shit.
Sure, Karl.
Man of action.
We'll be waiting for you.
Lake Titicaca.
If that captain hadn't turned back,
we would never have met.
Okay, so...
- ...good luck, Kevin.
- Yeah, you too.
And be safe.
Yeah.
Hey.
- At the hostel, we make a big meal?
- Yeah, sounds great.
Yeah? All we can eat?
Yep. And I promise, back in La Paz,
everything will be like it was before.
Yeah. Yeah.
- Ready?
- Ready.
Oar, please.
Hey, do you know what day it is?
December... 1st, maybe. I think.
Maybe I can make it home for Christmas.
Can we stop for the night soon
and try to catch a fish?
There's still an hour of daylight left.
I think we try to get closer to the canyon.
What do you think?
Oh, shit!
Kevin?
Get your paddle. Get your paddle! Come on!
Quick!
Get your paddle! Paddle, Yossi!
- I am!
- Come on!
- Paddle!
- Jeez, this is too strong!
- Kevin, what do we do?
- There's the beach! There's the beach, go!
Okay, hard! Hard!
Fuck, we're drifting!
- Come on, paddle! Push!
- We're never gonna make it!
- Push!
- I'm pushing! It's too strong!
- Come on, Yossi!
- Kevin!
It's okay!
Right, right, right!
Come on! We're gonna do this!
Oh, fuck!
- Rock! Kevin!
- Get down! Get down! Go!
Hold tight, Yossi!
Oh, Jesus!
- Kevin! Kevin!
- It's okay! Hold on, Yossi!
- Kevin!
- Hold tight!
Oh, no... No!
- Okay! Okay! I'm going across!
- What?
- I'm going over! We can't stay here.
- No! Kevin, you can't leave me!
Listen to me, listen to me! When I get
to the bank, throw me the machete!
I'm gonna cut some vine
and pull you out, okay?
- No! It's too dangerous!
- It's the only way.
- Kevin, please! You'll never make it!
- It's the only way!
I'm gonna make it, okay?
I'm gonna make it. I'm not leaving you.
I'm not leaving you, okay? Just hold on!
No! Kevin!
Yes!
Yossi, hold on!
Hurry! Hurry!
Here, Kevin, the raft's moving!
- Kevin!
- Yossi! Yossi, the machete!
Yossi!
Kevin!
Holy shit.
No.
Superman.
Kevin!
Kevin?
Shit.
I'm a man of action.
Come on!
# Pretend you're happy when you're blue #
# It isn't very hard to do #
# And you'll find happiness without an end #
# Whenever you pretend #
Fuck!
You're gonna be saved in the Curiplaya.
You have a map, and people
are coming to save you.
All you have to do...
...is keep going...
...and going and going and going.
Great. It moves.
Hey.
Yossi?
What?
Kevin?
Yossi.
Marcus? What?
Marcus!
Come on. Come on.
Hello?
Hello! Hello!
Hola!
I'm sorry.
Hello!
No.
So... this must be Curiplaya.
So, then...
...I have to get to...
...Rurrenabaque.
That is a long... way.
No.
It's not a long way
for the luckiest man on Earth.
It's just... there.
You can walk there on these feet.
Okay. Okay, Yossi. You need to do this.
You have to get them dry.
Come on.
I'm so sorry, Marcus. I didn't know.
I just didn't want to be the weakest.
I was more scared than you...
...because I'm a coward.
Because I am a coward and I deserve...
...all of this.
Kevin!
Kevin! I'm here!
No! No!
You. No!
Stupid idiot!
University.
Law school.
Papa, I know. I know
how you feel and I'm sorry.
Not one shekel!
You will not see one shekel from me.
I don't need your money.
I'm not asking for it.
It's only a year.
Stay... on the river!
Stay on the river! Stay on the river!
Karl always said stay on the river!
Oh, no. No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Okay, Yossi, just keep walking.
Keep going.
I know your type.
You just don't know when to give up.
Yossi.
No! No! No!
Look, Papá.
First of all, you'll see Captain Armando.
If he didn't drown, he wouldn't just give up.
We have to go and find him.
Hello? Wait! No! Wait! Wait, wait!
Hello! Hello! I'm here!
Down here! Hello! No! No!
No!
Hey! Can't you fly any lower?
No, I can't do that.
No!
Hey. We were so high,
we couldn't even see anything.
Listen, young man...
- You tell me to listen. You keep telling me...
- Listen, please!
It has been almost three weeks.
There is no-one to look for.
You don't know that.
You did all you could.
It's a miracle you survived. Now, go home.
Listen, I know it doesn't make any sense
to you. I know that it seems hopeless.
But I'm telling you, I know, in here,
I know in my heart, that he is alive.
I just need some... I need some help. Okay?
If you can just talk to the pilot,
just give me some kind of chance here.
Listen to me, I want to help you,
really, really, but...
- You say that. You say that.
- I can't. I can't. I can't, really.
- You can't?
- Yep, I can't.
Okay, fine. You know what?
You don't want to help me,
I'll go upriver myself.
What if you die in looking for him?
Then I die!
Okay, okay, okay.
Wait.
Come.
There is maybe... someone who can help.
Señor Tico?
Captain Armando...
...told me that you know
the Tuichi River better than anyone.
I have a friend...
...who is lost in the river.
The missing one?
A gringo lost 17 days in the jungle?
He won't survive.
Your friend is having a drink
with the Almighty up there.
No, my friend is alive...
...and I need you to help me find him.
I can't.
I've never begged for anything. Anything.
But I'm begging you now. Please.
I'm sorry.
How much for the boat?
Your boat.
How much?
- Crazy gringo.
- Yeah, loco!
But really... I need it.
Please.
No, no. Don't run! Please, don't run.
I'm not going to hurt you!
I'm not going to hurt you! Please,
don't run away. It's fine, it's fine.
My... my name... my name is Yossi.
I am lost.
Do you... do you speak... English?
No, of course you don't...
I know you can't
understand me, but... it's...
...it's good to see you.
We have to find the opening
in the river tomorrow...
...so the... when the plane comes,
they... they can see us.
I promise you, we'll be fine.
And here. I know it's not... it's not much...
...but it's better
than just the ground, you know?
Yeah, I'm not... just you, not...
So that you're safe. Keep the bugs out.
I'm going to protect you.
I'm sorry, I just have to...
I just have to do one thing.
Okay.
I'm just... just checking.
We just... have to keep heading
for Rurrenabaque...
...and never stop...
...and always keep an eye for the plane.
And the pilot's gonna see us...
...he's gonna signal to us
with a tilt of his wings...
...and we'll be saved.
And you're gonna meet my friends.
But out here, something...
...happened to us...
No, no, I'm fine, I'm fine, I'm all right.
Look.
See, I told you... we would find fruit.
It's a bit rotten, but it's okay.
You have to eat! No!
You have to eat! You have to eat!
I can't do this by myself!
You can't give up! Eat!
I'm starving too!
I am hurting too! My feet are...
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
We all... we just have to... get some rest.
And, look. Look, every night,
God sends us a tree to sleep under.
This... this is a gift from God.
We are not alone here.
God is walking beside us.
You know, He has one hand on our shoulder.
He is with us.
Lie down here, next to me.
It's fine. I'll just protect you.
We'll keep each other warm.
That's it. It's going to be all right.
Just... stay here with me.
We can sleep now.
You'll be safe.
God is with us.
It's okay. Just go to sleep.
Go to sleep.
What?
Yeah!
No.
No, no.
Okay, no, don't... don't move.
Don't move. Don't move.
May God bless you and keep you.
May God make his face shine
and show you his favor.
May God lift up his face and give you peace.
Come home alive, Yossi.
Stay with me.
Don't you fucking break. Don't you break.
Come on. Come on. Come on.
Yes.
We have to find the opening
in the river tomorrow...
in the river, so they can see us...
Yossi?
Yossi.
Yossi!
Yossi, over here!
- Come on, Yossi!
- Yossi?
Don't give up!
Come on, Yossi!
Yossi!
It's okay. It's okay.
You... are gonna live.
Yeah.
Thank you.
- What's wrong?
- We have to go back.
It's impossible.
You did everything you could.
I'm sorry.
Yossi?
Go away.
Okay, bring her around!
Keep going, keep going!
Yeah, a little more!
Wait.
Okay, keep going. Good. Go.
Kevin.
Yossi!
Turn around!
Yossi! Don't move!
Come here, come here.
I got you, buddy. I got you, buddy.
Thank you!
Hey.
- Thank you. Thank you.
- I told you I wouldn't leave you.
Hey, it's okay. Jesus Christ.
It's okay, it's okay, Yossi.
I got you, Yossi. I got you.
It's okay.
That's it.
Thank you, sir.
- Medico.
- Yeah, thank you.
You saved my life.
You saved mine.
Be right back. Okay?
Thank you.
Thank God, the one who was missing was found.
Thank God.
Added missing lines, foreign, synced and
corrected by H@w-to-kiLL @subscene.com
Please rate this subtitle at www.osdb.link/e4uy
Help other users to choose the best subtitles