Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
This is the night
It's a beautiful night
And they call it bella notte
Look at the skies
They have stars in their eyes
On this lovely bella notte
So take the love
Of your loved one
You'll need it about this time
To keep from falling like a star
When you make that dizzy climb
For this is the night
And the heavens are right
On this lovely
Bella notte
Silent as a snowﬂake in the night
Holy is the spirit of this night
All the world is calm and peaceful
All the world is bright and joyful
Spirit of love
And child of peace
Love unending
That shall not cease
Peace, my children
Of good will
Peace, be still
It's for you, darling.
Merry Christmas.
Oh, Jim, dear.
It's the one I was admiring, isn't it?
Trimmed with ribbons?
Well, it has a ribbon.
Oh, how sweet.
- You like her, darling?
- Oh, I love her.
What a perfectly beautiful little lady.
Come on, Lady. Over here.
That's a girl.
There, now.
A nice little bed for you.
But Jim, dear, are you sure
she'll be warm enough?
Why, of course, darling.
She'll be snug as a bug in a...
Almost forgot something.
There.
Good night, Lady.
Now, now, don't worry, darling.
She'll go right to sleep.
No, no, Lady.
This is where you belong, right here.
Aw, look. She's lonesome.
Don't you think maybe...?
Just for tonight?
Now, darling, if we're going
to show her who's master,
we must be firm
from the very beginning.
Lady!
Stop that now!
Stop it!
Lady! Quiet, now. You hear me?
Back to bed!
Quick, now.
Not one more sound.
Jim, dear.
Aw, Jim.
What?
Oh, all right.
But remember, just for tonight.
All right, Lady. All right.
I'm up. I'm up, Lady. I...
Oh, no!
What's wrong, Jim? What is it?
Can't you explain to Lady about Sundays?
Have you noticed, darling,
since we've had Lady,
we see less and less
of those disturbing headlines?
Yes, I just don't know
how we ever got along without her.
Say, she must be about six months old.
We'd better be getting her a license.
Hope it fits.
My, but it does look nice.
So grown up.
Won't Jock and Trusty be surprised?
Four steps straight
and then to the left
And right to the place
where I marked it
With a bonnie, bonnie bone
that I buried for me own
In my bonnie, bonnie bank
in the backyard
That's a grand sight.
Jock!
Oh, Jock!
Hello, Jock.
Oh! Oh, it's you, lassie.
Notice anything different?
You've had a bath?
No, not that.
You've had your nails clipped?
Guess again.
Well, I wouldn't a-be a-knowin'.
Why, lassie.
A bonnie new collar.
- Do you like it?
- Aye.
It must be very expensive.
- Have you shown it to Trusty yet?
- No.
We'd best go at once.
You know how sensitive
he is about these things.
He's dreaming.
Aye.
Dreamin' of those bonnie bygone days
when he and his grandfather
were trackin' criminals
through the swamps.
- They were?
- But that was before...
Before what?
'Tis time you knew the truth, lassie.
It shouldn't have happened to a dog.
But, well...
Trusty has lost his sense of smell.
' No!
' Aye.
But we must never let on
that we know, lassie.
It would break his poor heart
Which way did he go?
- Go?
- Yeah, big fella.
About six-foot-two.
No, three.
Wore a striped suit. No collar.
Why, Miss Lady.
You have a collar.
And a license.
My, my.
- How time does fly.
- Aye.
It seems only yesterday
she was cuttin' her teeth
on Jim Dear's slippers,
and now there she is, a full-grown lady.
Wearin' the greatest honor
man can bestow.
The badge of faith and respectability.
That's right, Miss Lady.
As my grandpappy,
Old Reliable, used to say...
I don't recollect if I've ever
mentioned Old Reliable before.
Aye, you have, laddie.
Oh, yeah.
It's Jim Dear.
Please excuse me.
Hello, there, Lady.
Come on, beat you home.
You win again.
Steady, now.
Steady.
Well, what have we here?
Big girl now, huh?
All right.
Ladies first.
You know, darling, with Lady here,
I'd say life is quite complete.
Yes, dear.
I don't imagine anything could
ever take her place in our hearts.
What a day!
Well, now to dig up some breakfast.
Cute little rascals.
Now. That breakfast, let's see.
Bernie's?
No. Francois...
No, no.
Nope. Too much starch.
Tony's. Oh, that's it.
I haven't been there in a week.
A beautiful day to make pizza
Hey, still we call it bella notte
Well, buon giorno, Butch.
You want-a your breakfast?
OK. The boss, he's a-saving
some a-nice bones for you.
Breakfast comin' up from a-left field.
Good catch!
Whoa, boy, whoa.
Hey.
Blimey.
Look, Peg, it's the tramp.
Hiya, handsome.
Come to join the party?
All right, all right.
No time for wisecracks.
I've got to get you out.
I'm telling you, the pressure's
really on. Signs all over town.
- Gee, thanks.
- You're a bit of all right, chum.
- OK, OK, get going.
- Hey! What's going on over there?
Scram. And be careful.
WW, you mangy mutt.
Hey. Let go. Let go of me.
Well. Snob hill!
Hi, gals. How's pickings?
Pretty slim?
Yeah. I'll bet they've got
a lid on every trash can.
And a fence around every tree.
I wonder what the leash and collar set
does for excitement.
Lassie. Lassie!
Miss Lady, ma'am.
Miss Lady!
Good morning, lassie.
'Tis a bonnie, braw, bright day...
...day.
Why, Miss Lady.
Is something wrong?
Aye. Tell us, lassie.
- If somebody's been mistreatin' ya...
- No, Jock.
It's something I've done, I guess.
You?
It must be.
Jim Dear and Darling are acting so...
- Jim Dear and Darling?
- Hush, lad.
Now, lassie,
get on with the details.
Well, I first noticed it
the other day
when Jim Dear came home.
Down, Lady, down!
Darling, darling!
Are you all right?
Of course I am.
Why shouldn't I be?
I just can't help worrying.
After all, in your condition,
alone here all day,
and walking that dog...
- That dog!
- That dog?
He's never called me that before.
Well, now, lassie,
I wouldn't worry
my wee head about that.
Remember,
they're only humans, after all.
That's right, Miss Lady.
As my grandpappy,
Old Reliable, used to say...
I don't recollect if I've ever
mentioned Old Reliable before.
Aye, you have, laddie.
- Frequently.
- Yeah.
But now Darling is... Well...
We've always enjoyed
our afternoon romp together.
But yesterday...
No, Lady. No walk today.
No, Lady.
Not now.
Lady!
Drop that, Lady.
Drop it, I say.
It didn't hurt, really
But Darling has never
struck me... before.
Now, lassie.
Do not take it too seriously.
After all, at a time like this...
Why, yes, you see, Miss Lady,
there comes a time
in the life of all humans when...
Well, as they put it...
Birds and the bees?
Or... Well...
The stork? You know... No?
- Well...
- What he's trying to say, lassie,
is Darling is expecting a wee bairn.
Bairn?
He means a baby, Miss Lady.
Oh.
What's a baby?
Well, they resemble humans.
But I'd say a mite smaller.
Aye. And they walk on all fours.
And if I remember correctly,
they bellow a lot.
Aye. And they're very expensive.
You will not be permitted
to play with it.
But they're mighty sweet.
And very, very soft.
Just a cute little bundle.
Of trouble.
Yeah. They scratch, pinch, pull ears...
But shucks. Any dog can take that.
It's what they do to your happy home.
Move it over, will you, friend?
Homewreckers, that's what they are.
Look here.
Who are you to barge in?
The voice of experience, buster.
Just wait till junior gets here.
You get the urge
for a nice comfortable scratch,
and, "Put that dog out!
He'll get fleas all over the baby."
You start barking
at some strange mutt
"Stop that racket.
You'll wake the baby."
And then!
Then they hit you in the room
and board department.
Remember those nice,
juicy cuts of beef?
Forget them.
Leftover baby food.
And that nice,
warm bed by the fire?
A leaky doghouse.
- Oh, dear.
- Do not listen, lassie.
No human is that cruel.
Of course not, Miss Lady.
Why, everybody knows
a dog's best friend is his human.
Come on now, fellas.
You haven't fallen
for that old line, now have you?
Aye. And we've no need for mongrels
and their radical ideas.
Off with you, now. Off with you!
- OK, Sandy.
- The name's Jock.
- OK, Jock.
- Heather Lad of Glencairn to you!
OK, OK, OK.
But remember this, Pigeon.
A human heart has only so much
room for love and affection.
When a baby moves in,
the dog moves out.
Let's see. That'll be about...
Oh, well.
Darling?
There isn't any way we can tell, for
sure, what it's going to be, is there?
I'm afraid not.
Nobody ever knows for certain.
All we can do is hope.
Darling, are you sure
you want watermelon?
And some chop suey too.
Chop su...
All right, darling.
- That's the cutest thing I ever saw.
- What darling little booties!
- That bonnet.
- Isn't it just too adorable?
Don't you love showers?
I've never seen you look more beautiful.
Isn't she radiant?
That's what I told Bill yesterday.
"Darling looks positively radiant.
Why, in all my days," I said,
"I've never seen anyone as radiant."
Jim, you look terrible.
Absolutely horrible.
I never saw you look worse.
Cheer up, Jim. Old Doc Jones
has never lost a father yet.
Yes, Aunt Sarah, it's a boy.
A boy. And... What's that?
Eyes?
What color are they?
Well, oh, gosh.
I forgot to look.
A boy. It's a boy, it's a... Doctor!
Doctor, it's a boy!
Yes, yes, I know.
A boy.
Oh, boy, oh, boy!
It's a boy, it's a boy, it's a boy!
Hello? Hello, Jim?
Are you there, Jim?
Central, we've been cutoff.
Hello? Hello?
Hello!
What is a baby?
I just can't understand
It must be something wonderful
It must be something grand
'Cause everybody's smiling
In a kind and wistful way
And they haven't even noticed
That I'm around today
What is a baby, anyway?
What is a baby?
I must find out today
What makes Jim Dear and Darling
Act this way?
Oh, my little star sweeper
I'll sweep the stardust
For you
Little soft ﬂuffy sleeper
Here comes a pink cloud
For you
Little wandering angel
Fold up your wings
Close your eyes
And may love be your keeper
There, now.
Little star sweeper.
Dream on.
Well, that should do it.
We've got enough here
to take us halfway to China.
Darling. Darling!
We haven't much time.
Jim, I just can't leave him.
He's still so small and helpless.
He'll be all right.
Now come on. If he wakes up,
we'll never get away.
Jim, I feel so guilty
deserting him like this.
Nonsense.
Hey. What's the matter with Lady?
She thinks we're running out on him.
Don't worry, old girl.
We'll be back in a few days.
And Aunt Sarah will be here.
With you here to help her...
There's the old girl now.
Coming, Aunt Sarah. Coming!
Sorry I'm late, dears.
Hope I haven't kept you waiting.
- Let me take your things.
- No.
No fussing. I know my way around.
On your way.
Mustn't miss your train.
Have a good time,
and don't worry about a thing.
Goodbye, dears. Goodbye.
Goodbye.
Now to see that big nephew of mine.
You adorable little...
Good gracious!
What are you doing here?
Go on, now. Shoo, shoo.
Scat. Get out of here.
There, there.
Aunt Sarah won't let
that dog frighten you any more.
No, no, no.
Rock-a-bye baby on the treetop
When the wind blows
We are Siamese if you please
We are Siamese if you don't please
Now we looking over our new domicile
If we like we stay
for maybe quite a while
Do you seeing that thing
swimming round and round?
Yes.
Maybe we could reaching in
and make it drown.
If we sneaking up upon it carefully...
There will be a head for you
A tail for me
Do you hear what I hear?
A baby CW-
Where we finding baby
there are milk nearby
If we look in baby buggy
there could be
Plenty milk for you
and also some for me
What's going on down there?
Merciful heavens! My darlings.
My precious pets.
That wicked animal.
Attacking my poor,
innocent little angels.
Good afternoon, ma'am.
What can I do for you?
I want a muzzle.
A good, strong muzzle.
Oh, yes, ma'am.
Now here's our latest.
Combination leash and muzzle.
Now, we'll just slip it on like this,
and... No! No, no, no.
Nice doggy. No, don't wiggle.
Steady, now.
Now... Now, now.
Careful, you little...
Watch out.
- Careful, doggy.
- Come back!
Get over here, I say.
Come back here.
Hey, Pige, what are you doing
on this side of the tracks?
I thought you...
Wh...?
You poor kid.
We've got to get this off.
I think I know the very place.
Come on.
Well, here we are.
- The zoo?
- Sure.
No, no. This way.
Follow me.
- Oh.
- What's the matter, Pige?
- We can't go in.
- Why not?
- The sign says...
- Yeah, that's...
- That's the angle.
- Angle?
Look. We'll wait for the right...
Here we are now.
Just lay low.
- Hey, you!
- I beg your pardon.
- Were you addressing...?
- What's the matter? Can't you read?
Why, yes, in several languages.
Oh, a wise guy?
All right, now, what's
this creature doing here?
- He's not my dog.
- He's not?
Go away. Get down.
Go on. Why, certainly not, officer.
I suppose you'll be tellin' me next
it was the dog that was whistling?
I'm certain I don't know.
Oh! So I'm a liar now, am I?
Well, you listen to me.
Resisting an officer of the law.
You're gonna pay.
Pull a knife on me, will you?
Trying to assassinate me, you are.
Carrying concealed weapons.
Come on, Pige.
The place is ours.
We'd better go through
this place from A to Z.
Apes.
No, no. No use even asking them.
They wouldn't understand.
They wouldn't?
Too closely related to humans.
Alligators. Now there's an idea.
Say, Al, do you suppose you could
nip this contraption off for us?
Glad to oblige.
Whoa. Whoa!
If anybody ever needed
a muzzle, it's him.
Timber!
Pigeon, look out!
Now what harebrained idiot would...
Hey, look. A beaver.
There's the answer to our problem.
Let me see here.
Six-foot-six and seven-sixteenth inches.
Pardon me, friend.
- I wonder if you'd do us a little...
- Busy, sonny. Busy.
Can't stop to gossip now.
Got to slide this sycamore to the...
...swamp.
Well, this will only take a second.
Only a second? Listen, sonny.
Do you realize every second,
70 centimeters of water
is wasted over that spillway?
- Yeah, but...
- Gotta get this log movin', sonny.
Gotta get it moving.
'Taint the cuttin' takes the time.
It's the doggone haulin'.
The haulin'. Exactly.
- Now, what you need...
- I'd better bisect this section here.
What you need is a log puller.
I said a log puller!
I ain't deaf, sonny.
There's no need to...
Did you say log puller?
And by a lucky coincidence
you see before you,
modeled by the lovely little lady,
the new, improved,
patented, handy dandy,
never-fail little giant log puller.
The busy beaver's friend.
You don't say?
Guaranteed not to wear,
tear, rip or ravel.
Show the customer the merchandise.
And it cuts log-hauling time 66 percent.
Sixty-six percent?
Think of that.
- Well, how's it work?
- Why, it's no work at all.
You merely slip this ring
over the limb like this
and haul it off.
Say...
You mind if I slip it on for size?
Help yourself, friend.
OK. Don't mind if I do.
How do you get
the consarned thing off, sonny?
Glad you brought that up.
To remove it, simply place
the strap between your teeth...
Like this?
Correct, friend. Now bite hard.
You see?
It's off.
Say, that is simple.
Well, friend, we'll be
on our way now, so...
Not so fast now, sonny..
I'll have to make
certain it's satisfactory
before we settle on a price.
Oh, no, it's all yours, friend.
You can keep it.
I can?
It's a free sample.
Well, thanks a lot.
Thanks ever so...
Say!
It works swell.
But when she put
that horrible muzzle on me...
Say no more.
I get the whole picture.
Aunts. Cats. Muzzles.
Well, that's what comes of tying
yourself down to one family.
Haven't you a family?
One for every day of the week.
The point is, none of them have me.
I'm afraid I don't understand.
It's simple.
You see...
Hey.
Something tells me it's suppertime.
Come on.
I'll show you what I mean.
Take the Schultzes here.
Little Fritzie, that's me, Pige,
makes this his Monday home.
- Monday home?
- Ach, ja.
Monday's is Mama Schultz
cooking der Wiener Schnitzel.
Delicious.
Now, O'Brien's here
is where little Mike,
that's me again, Pige,
- comes of a Tuesday.
- Of a Tuesday?
Begorra.
That's when they're after havin'
their darlin' corned beef.
You see, Pige,
when you're footloose and collar-free,
well, you take nothing but the best.
Hey! Tony's!
Of course. The very place
for a very special occasion.
No, this way, Pige.
I have my own private entrance.
Wait here.
Just one minute. I'm a-comin'. I'm...
What's a-matter? Somebody's
a-makin' da April Fool...
Oh, hello, Butch.
Where you been so long?
Hey, Joe, look who's here.
Well, what do you know? It's Butch.
Hey, hey, hey!
Joe, bring some bones
for Butchy before he eat me up.
OK, Tony. OK.
Bones a-coming up.
What's this?
Hey, Joe, look.
Butchy, he's got a new girlfriend.
Well, a son of a gun!
He's a got a cockerel Spanish a-girl.
Hey, she's a pretty sweet kiddo, Butch.
You take-a Tony's advice
and a-settle down with this-a one?
"This a-one?"
This one. This... Oh!
Tony, you know.
He's a-not a-speaking
English a-pretty good.
Now, first we fix-a the table.
- Here's your bones, Tony.
- OK, bones. Bones?
What's the matter for you, Joe?
I break-a your face.
Tonight, Butch,
he gets the best in the house.
OK, Tony, you the boss.
Tell me, what's your pleasure?
À la carte? Dinner?
OK.
Hey, Joe.
Butch-a, he says
he wants-a two spaghetti speciale.
Heavy on the meats-a ball.
Tony, dogs don't talk.
- He's a-talkin' to me!
- OK, he's a-talkin' to you.
You the boss.
Now here you are.
The best spaghetti in town.
For this is the night
It's a beautiful night
And we call it
Bella notte
Look at the skies
They have stars in their eyes
On this lovely bella notte
Side by side
With your loved one
You'll find enchantment here
The night will weave its magic spell
When the one you love is near
For
This is the night
And the heavens are right
On this lovely
Bella notte
This is the night
It's a beautiful night
And we call it
Bella notte
Look at the skies
They have stars in their eyes
On this lovely
Bella notte
Side by side with your loved one
You'll find enchantment here
The night will weave its magic spell
When the one you love is near
For this is the night
And the heavens are right
On this lovely
Bella notte
Oh! Oh, dear.
Is something wrong, Pige?
- It's morning.
- Yeah.
So it is.
I should have been home hours ago.
Why? Because
you still believe in that
"ever faithful old dog Tray"
routine?
Come on, Pige.
' Open UP VOW eyes.
' Open my eyes?
To what a dog's life can really be.
I'll show you what I mean.
Look down there.
Tell me what you see.
Well, I see nice homes
with yards and fences.
Exactly. Life on a leash.
Look again, Pige.
Look, there's a great
big hunk of world down there
with no fence around it.
Where two dogs can find
adventure and excitement.
And beyond those distant hills,
who knows what wonderful experiences?
And it's all ours for the taking, Pige.
It's all ours.
It sounds wonderful.
But?
But who'd watch over the baby?
You win.
Come on.
I'll take you home.
It's a beautiful night
And they call it...
Not to change the subject, but...
Ever chase chickens?
I should say not!
Then you've never lived.
- But we shouldn't.
- I know.
That's what makes it fun.
Come on, kid.
Start building some memories.
But we...
We won't hurt the chickens?
Hurt 'em? No!
We'll just stir 'em up a bit.
Just look at those fat, lazy biddies.
Why, they should've been up hours ago.
Some fun, hey, kid?
Hey, what's going on in there?
What's that?
That's the signal to get going. Come on.
- This is living, hey, kid!
- Is it?
Come on, Pige. Follow me.
You know, there's a little bit
of bird dog in all of us, Pige.
Pige? Pige?
Pige? Where are you, Pige?
Pige?
Pigeon?
Oh, Pige!
Hey. Hey, Dachsie, how we coming?
Just one more chorus and we're out.
OK. On a downbeat.
One, two...
Put her in number four, Bill,
- while I check her license number.
- OK.
All right, baby, in here.
Well, look yous guys,
Miss Park Avenue herself.
Blimey.
A regular bloomin' debutante.
Yeah. And pipe the crown jewel
she's wearin'.
Hey, whatcha in for, sweetheart?
Putting fleas on the butler?
All right, you guys.
Lay off, will you?
What's the matter, Peg?
We was only havin'
a bit of sport, we was.
Can't you see the poor kid's
scared enough already?
Pay no attention,
my little ochi chernye.
That's right, dearie.
They don't mean no real harm.
It's like Gorky says
in Lower Depths, quote:
"Miserable being must find
more miserable being.
Then he's happy-"
- Unquote.
- Boris is a philosopher.
Besides, little bublichki,
wearing license here,
that is like waving,
you should excuse the expression,
red flag in front of bull.
My license?
But what's wrong with it?
There ain't nothin' wrong with it.
Confidential,
there's not one dog here
who would not give left hind leg
for such a knick-knack.
That's your passport to freedom, honey
Without it...
Hey- Hey, yous guys, look.
Poor Nutsy is takin' the long walk.
Where is he taking him?
Through the one-way door, sister.
You... You mean he's...
Oh, well.
A short life and a merry one.
Yeah, that's what
the Tramp always says.
- The Tramp?
- Now there's a bloke
what never gets caught.
He's given the slip to every
dogcatcher in this burg.
You won't believe this, dearie,
but no matter how tight a jam he's in,
that Tramp always finds some way out.
I can quite easily believe that.
But remember, my friends,
even Tramp has his Achilles' heel.
Pardon me, amigo.
What is this "chili heel"?
Achilles' heel, Pedro.
This is meaning his... weaknesses.
The dames. Yeah.
He has an eye
for a well-turned paw, he has.
Let's see. There's been Lulu.
Yeah, and Trixie.
Und Fifi.
And my sister,
Rosita Chiquita Juanita Chihuahua.
I think.
What a dog.
Yeah. Tell us about it, Peg.
What a dog!
Peg used to be
in the Dog and Pony Follies.
He's a tramp
But they love him
Breaks a new heart every day
He's a tramp
They adore him
And I only hope he'll stay that way
He's a tramp
He's a scoundrel
He's a rounder
He's a cad
He's a tramp
But I love him
Yes, even I have got it pretty bad
You can never tell
When he'll show up
He gives you plenty of trouble
I guess he's just a no 'count pup
But I wish that he were double
He's a tramp
He's a rover
And there's nothin' more to say
If he's a tramp
He's a good one
And I wish that I could travel his way
Wish that I could travel his way
Yeah.
But he never takes them serious.
But someday he is meeting
someone different.
Some delicate, fragile creature
who's giving him a wish
to shelter and protect.
Like Miss Park Avenue here, matey?
Could be.
- But when he does...
- Yeah. I'm way ahead of ya.
Under the spell of true love...
The poor chump grows careless...
The Cossacks are picking him up...
And it's curtains for the Tramp.
It's the little cooker, Bill.
- In number four.
- OK.
All right, baby.
They've come to take you home.
You're too nice a girl
to be in this place.
Courage, man.
Courage!
But...
I've never even considered matrimony.
Nor I.
But no matter which of us she accepts,
we'll always be the best of friends.
Now remember,
not a word about her
unfortunate experience.
- We don't want to hurt her feelings
- Yeah. Yeah.
Lassie.
Miss Lady, ma'am.
Please, I don't want to see anybody.
Now, now, lassie.
Don't feel that way about it.
Of course not, Miss Lady.
Why, some of the finest people
I ever tracked down
- were jailbirds.
- Quiet!
You great loony!
Please, lassie.
We've come with a proposition
for helpin' ya.
Help me? What do you mean?
Well, now...
You see, lassie...
Neither of us is as young
as we used to be.
But we're still in the prime of life.
Aye.
And we've both got
very comfortable homes
That's right. Where we know
you'll be welcome
and appreciated, Miss Lady.
So... So, to come
directly to the point...
If you could...
...find it possible to...
To...
You're both very kind,
and I do appreciate it.
- But...
- Oh, Pigeon.
Oh, Pi...
Oh! Hi, boys.
Anything new in the kennel club set?
A little something
I picked up for you, Pige.
Looks like I'm the one
that's in the doghouse.
If this person is
annoying you, Miss Lady...
We'll gladly throw the rascal out.
That won't be necessary. Thank you.
Very well, ma'am.
You... You...
...mongrel!
Come on, Pige.
It wasn't my fault.
I thought you were
right behind me. Honest.
When I heard they'd
taken you to the pound...
Don't even mention that horrible place.
I was so embarrassed and...
- And frightened.
- Now, now.
Who could ever harm
a cute little trick like you?
Trick? Trick!
- That reminds me, who is Trixie?
- Trixie?
And Lulu and Fifi
and Rosita Chiquita wh...
- Whatever her name is.
- Chiquita...
Oh! Yes! Well, I-I...
As far as I'm concerned,
you needn't worry about your old heel.
MY heel?
I don't need you
to shelter and protect me.
- But...
- If you grow careless, don't blame me.
I don't care if the Cossacks
do pick you up! Goodbye.
And take this with you.
Stop that.
Hush, now, hush.
Stop that racket!
What's wrong, Pige?
- A rat!
- Where?
Upstairs, in the baby's room!
- How do I get in?
- The little door.
On the porch.
Merciful heavens!
Oh, you poor little darling.
No, no, no.
Thank goodness you're not hurt.
You... You vicious brutes. Back!
Get back!
Go on! Get back!
The pound. The pound, that's it.
I'll call the pound.
Come here, you. Come here!
Come on, come on.
Come along. I'll call them this minute.
I won't sleep a wink
with that brute in the house.
Hello? Hello!
I don't care if you
are alone there, young man.
I insist you pick him up immediately.
Darling, look.
If you want my advice
you'll destroy that animal at once.
Don't worry, ma'am.
We've been after this one for months.
We'll take care of him.
- What do you suppose...?
- Say, what's going on here?
Just picking up a stray, mister.
Come on, giddap.
Caught him attacking a baby.
- Good heavens.
- My baby.
Aunt Sarah!
I was certain he was no good
the moment I first laid eyes on him.
Yeah, but...
I never thought
he'd do a thing like that.
Thank goodness I got there in time.
There they were...
No, I'm sure there must be
some mistake. Lady wouldn't...
Watch out! That dog's loose.
Keep her away.
Nonsense.
She's trying to tell us something.
What is it, old girl?
What are you try...
Darling, Aunt Sarah, come here.
What is it, Jim?
A rat!
A rat?
We should've known.
I misjudged him.
Badly.
Come on. We got to stop that wagon.
But, man, we don't know
which way they've gone.
We'll track 'em down.
And then?
We'll hold 'em.
Hold 'em at bay.
Now what?
The scent. Follow the scent.
Let's face it, man.
We both know you've lost
your sense of smell.
Go on, get out of here.
Go on, get away.
Easy. Go on, get away.
Watch it now. Watch it!
Hi, Pige.
All right, everybody, watch the birdy.
Steady, now.
Hold it.
I guess I used a little too much.
Darling, visitors.
Visitors?
Why, it's Jock.
And good old Trusty.
Careful now, man.
Careful. It's a wee bit slippery.
Yes, yes.
All right, boy. We'll let 'em in.
No, no, not you, young man.
You're going to take a nap.
Well, Merry Christmas.
Come in. If you'll just
step into the parlor,
I'll see about refreshments.
Darling, where did you
put the dog biscuits?
The box Aunt Sarah sent for Christmas.
In the kitchen, Jim, dear.
No doubt about it.
They've got their mother's eyes.
Aye.
But there's a bit of
their father in them too.
Well, and I see you finally
acquired a collar.
Oh. Yes.
Complete with license.
Oh, yeah, a new collar.
Caught the scent the moment
I came in the house.
Trusty, I says,
Trusty, somebody's
wearing a new collar.
'Course, my sense of smell
is very highly developed.
Runs in the family, you know.
There'll be no livin'
with him from now on.
As my grandpappy,
Old Reliable, used to say...
I don't recollect if I've ever
mentioned Old Reliable before.
No, you haven't, Uncle Trusty.
I haven't?
Well...
As Old Reliable used to say...
He'd say...
Doggone.
You know,
I clean forgot what it was
he used to say.
Peace, my children
Of good will
Peace
Be
Still
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org