Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
To this
Small, little, not too big, little, homey
Nice, little, quaint, little, always kindly
Old New England town
Welcome
If you're new to the place
And feeling uneasy
Fret not a bit
In this always friendly
old New England town
Welcome
To our family picnic
July Fourth picnic
Independence Day
Aunt Sarah!
Will we see you at the picnic
the day after tomorrow?
Of course!
My precious kitties
love the Fourth of July.
Whether next of kin
or next-door neighbour
Happily, we pool our labour
to give our town a new face
A nifty new look!
A red, white, and a blue look!
And when we're done,
you'll never know the place
At our family picnic
July Fourth picnic
Independence
Day
There's a buzzing in the air
Children running everywhere
As all of us prepare
For that once-a-year, wonderful day
And our spirits are so high
Feels like Christmas in July
As we pray the hours fly
To that star-spangled
Wonderful, wonderful, wonderful day
We can hardly wait
to bathe and dress up
We love picnics, we confess, yup
With Darling and with Jim Dear
We've made a home
from which we'll never roam
Why would we
When we're so contented here?
In this fine, little, not too
Big, little, cosy
Warm, little, swell, little
Always loving
Old New England home
In our small, little, not too big
Little, homey, nice, little, quaint, little
Always friendly
Old New England town
Welcome
Welcome!
All right, time for a bath!
The water's hot.
Oh, excellent! I love getting a bath.
It makes my fur so silky smooth.
Yeah!
-Me first!
-No, me first!
No, not you! Wait a minute!
I hate baths.
Just the same, Scamp,
when you live in a house,
you need to be clean.
Well, then I'm glad I'm a wild dog.
Scamp, you know you're
not supposed to climb
on the furniture.
Now get down from there
before you break something.
Hey, let's do some dog stuff, huh, Pop?
You know, dig up bones, rip up flowers,
chase cats!
Scamp, come on now.
You're gonna make a mess.
-Got it!
-Dad!
Tramp?
I hope you're not making
a mess in there.
All right, whirlwind, time to settle down.
Why don't you go play with Junior?
Scamp play!
Scamp!
Look what you did to my favourite hat.
If I've told you once,
I've told you a thousand times. No!
Let's see if you
can behave long enough
for me to give you a bath.
Bad Scamp!
Scamp, stop squirming.
Bad Scamp! Bad, bad, bad Scamp!
Well, it's about time you settled down.
There. All done.
Scamp!
Play ball!
Hey, come back here!
Scamp, catch the ball!
Come back here now!
No, no, no, no, no, no!
Yay! Yay!
Scamp! Scamp!
-Play ball!
-Scamp! Oh, no!
What a mess!
This time, you've gone too far!
You've left me no choice.
Some dogs just have
to learn the hard way.
Maybe chaining you up
will teach you a lesson.
I'm sorry, pal, but I just
don't know what else to do.
-Serves him right.
-Simply incorrigible.
He brought this on himself.
Now we'll need another bath.
-Me first!
-No, me first!
Not you first!
Tramp?
Best thing Jim Dear
could have done for our boy,
chainin' him up.
Tramp, he's never
been chained up before.
He's just a pup.
He has to learn to live
by the rules of the house.
Firm discipline moulds a pup into a dog.
You turned out pretty good.
Yeah, Pidge, but I found you.
And if it weren't for you,
I'd have wound up in the pound.
I'm just trying to protect him.
He'll understand someday.
Maybe he needs to understand today.
I thought you might be hungry.
I'm sorry, pal.
You're just gonna have
to shape up a little, that's all.
I always get blamed for everything.
Sometimes it's hard
bein' part of a family.
You have to obey certain rules.
But I want to run wild and free,
like a real dog!
Son, the world out there is full of traps.
Here, you, you have
a family that loves you.
As long as I do what you say.
Pop, I just don't feel like I belong here.
Didn't you ever feel this way?
I was just like you when I was your age.
You were never like me.
You've been a house dog all your life.
How would you know?
Oh, you'd be surprised.
Scamp, I'm only trying to protect you.
By putting me on a chain?
Those are the rules, Son.
All I ever hear is, "Rules, rules, rules!"
"Don't do this!" and "Don't do that!"
What good are teeth and claws
if you can never use them?
-Stop that howling!
-I can't help it, Pop!
Wild dogs howl at the moon!
There will be no wild dogs in this family!
Then maybe I don't want
to be in this family.
Like it or not, you are
a part of this family!
And until you start acting like it,
you can just get used to
being out here every night!
Hey, Angel!
Why don't you come on out, 'kay?
I can't.
The pup is in chains!
Come back, you mangy mutt!
Hold still so I can take you in
all peaceable-like!
Hey! Where'd you go?
What the...
Hey, drop that!
Defacing a county officer's...
Oh, come on now, that's not fair.
Come on now, hand it over, girl.
Hey!
Hey, drop that!
Hey, gotcha!
It's off to the pound with you,
big fella! Huh?
You don't have to...
Boy, when I get out of here,
I'm gonna do somethin' fierce.
I'm gonna get you...
You little mutt!
You're gonna see what mad is!
I'll get you yet, you hooligans!
Oh, you! Come on!
Far from here is where I want to be
Somewhere out there,
loose and running
Nobody's leash to hold me
Nobody's hugs to crush me
Nobody's soap and scratchy comb
To bathe and brush me
A world without fences
Where I can run free
And be with real dogs
Who'll bring the real dog out in me
No walls and no boundaries
Where I can be free
A world without walls and fences
That's exactly where I want to be
This pup just won't sleep his life away
On some sofa, like his father
Too many bones to chew up
Too many smells to sample
Too many fancy flower beds
To rip and trample
No rules to control me
Stop what I want to be
A world without fences
That's the world I want for me
No rules, no responsibility
On my own, completely free
A world without fences
For me
So long, you house dogs!
You can't tell me what to do any more,
'cause I'm a wild dog!
Hey, you guys, wait for me!
Pretty good pickin's, huh?
I can see you know
your way around an alley.
It's that obvious?
Couldn't miss it if I tried.
This must be your diploma
from the school of hard knocks.
Yeah, I just graduated.
Then you must know this move.
Any street dog would.
Wow! Slick move!
-I mean, that's kid stuff.
-Yeah, right.
You've got your own style,
don't you, tenderfoot?
Listen, you don't belong on the street.
You won't last five minutes out here.
Get going, you crazy mutt!
Hey, you, get out of the street!
Scamp...
Scamp? Oh, no!
Tramp!
They're jumping on the sofa
and playing in the trash.
And breaking stuff!
If only there were hats to chew on.
Goodbye, chains! Hello, freedom!
Go, Buster!
That a way, Buster!
Bust his butt off, Buster!
So, any of you other lowlife mongrels
think you're dog enough
to take Buster on?
Don't be afraid!
Have no fear! Have no fear!
That's right, boys.
Junkyard dogs rule this town.
And Buster rules the junkyard dogs!
Angel! Angel! Talk to me.
Who's the king of the junkyard?
Oh, you are, Buster.
And it's quite a kingdom
you've got here.
That's my girl!
I'm not your girl!
I don't belong to anyone.
Hey, hey. Look here, you guys.
I'd say we got a new recruit.
The little house dog!
Hey, you got off the leash!
Yeah.
Hey! Hey, hey, hey, hey! Watch it!
Oh, be still, my heart.
I'm gettin' a bad case of puppy love.
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
Hey, Ruby.
I'm the top dog around here.
And nobody joins the junkyard dogs
unless I say so.
So, what's your name, sport?
Name's Scamp.
Well, howdy, Scamperoo.
So, you saw us having some fun
and thought you'd join right in, huh?
Yeah, sure.
Hey, I hate to break
the news to you, champ,
but not many house dogs
get to run in this pack.
-I'm not a house dog.
-Oh, you're not?
Then what's this badge of respectability
hanging around your neck?
Hey, collar boy!
How's life on the end of that chain?
No way!
I've had it with the house dog life.
Nothing there but rules, rules, rules.
I want to be wild and free,
like you guys!
I don't know, kid.
Your average house dog
ain't got what it takes.
Hey, tell him what it takes, Buster!
Tell him what it takes!
In junkyard society
We're repelled by all propriety
Humility and modesty
Good manners and sobriety
We always gulp our meat
Our coats are never neat
Alas, we lack all poise
We're full of natural noise
No pets you stroke and pat
You might as well be a cat
In junkyard society
Society
We are the mutual un-elite
An underclass from our head to feet
Our deeds are spiteful,
our mischief pure
We got a natural disorder
For which there's no cure
Down to the junkyard
Straight to the junkyard
Step to the junkyard
Society rag
That's where you're
nobody's perfumed pet
Where you can wet
where you want to wet
Where you put charity on the shelf
The only one that you'll look out for
Is you yourself
Down in the junkyard
Check out the junkyard
Doin' the junkyard
Society rag
No distemper shots from the vet
Show your temper
Mean as you can get
Down at the yard where we live and let
Chaos and trouble
Oh, we do it double
None of this play-it-safe
house dog stuff
Our days are risky, our nights are "ruff"
The peaceful life leaves us ill at ease
We're crude and loud in a crowd
And very proud of our fleas
Oh, I love this guy!
Down at the junkyard
Check out the junkyard
Step to the junkyard
Straight to the junkyard
Doin' the junkyard
Sing it, boy!
Society rag
What a blast!
I'd never get away with this at home.
So, you really think
you got what it takes
to be a junkyard dog, huh?
Oh, he's got what it takes, Buster.
I saw all his moves back in that alley.
Yeah! Yeah! Watch this slick move!
Talented as you are,
it ain't that easy, sport.
Every day out here
is like a test of survival.
A test!
Beautiful!
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah! Good!
Baby, I always get my best ideas
when you're around.
That's why you're my girl.
I'm not your girl.
Okay, Scampers, we'll give you a shot.
But you gotta pass
a little test of courage
in Reggie's alley.
-What?
-But it's never been done before!
Come here. Don't listen to them.
I got faith in you, kid.
It's just a little test
to prove you can stand
on your own four paws.
Easy. I'm not afraid of anything.
That's what I like about you, kid.
You got spunk.
-Did you call the pound?
-Yes, dear.
They haven't seen him.
Oh, Tramp.
Scamp's never been out all night.
So much could happen.
Hey, easy, Pidge.
We'll find him before he gets himself
in real trouble.
Oh, Miss Lady, ma'am!
We came as soon as we heard.
Uncle Jock! Uncle Trusty!
Scamp ran away!
What they said!
Not to worry, little ladies.
Got my grandpappy Ol' Reliable's
keen sense of smell.
Say, have I ever told
you girls about the time
I saved your father from certain death?
-No!
Yup!
Here he goes again.
I told you, there'll be no livin' with him.
That Scamp is gonna get
into so much trouble
when he gets home! Yeah!
-I don't even want him back.
-Yeah, who cares?
He should know better than to run off.
I bet he gets a slipper
right across his great, big, fat...
We really do miss him, Mom.
We'll be back with
your brother in no time.
Your old man's got twice
the speed and cunning
as any dog half his age.
Just usin' a few forgotten
muscles, that's all.
Lady! Tramp! Let's go!
Come on. No tellin' what mischief
that pup's gettin' into.
All right, Scampster. Fetch the can
outta the alley.
See ya!
It's a spook! A spook!
It's Reggie! Scatter!
Where, oh, where
Has my little dog...
Well, I'll be.
You're not gettin' away this time!
I gotcha now, you little hoodlum!
Hey! Hey, now, get off of there!
What are you, mad?
You crazy...
That'll get you
hard time in the pound, fella.
Attackin' a deputy animal
control officer's vehicle.
And a fine modern machine
like this one at that.
Two horsepower,
three miles to the gallon.
Boy, I tell you...
Hey.
You saved my life.
Nobody else here would
have dared to do that.
Wow, did you see that?
-Is it possible?
-Scamp is a canine hurricane!
You did everyone a big favour, 'kay?
Oui, you are practically the hero!
Shouldn't we go after him
or something?
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
You got it all wrong, kid.
In the junkyard,
it's every dog for himself.
I can see we're gonna have
to put you to another test.
Anything you say, Buster.
-Will somebody open this thing?
-Okay! Okay! Okay!
-Is that open enough?
-Magnifique, Mooch!
That's using your head!
Thanks again, huh?
You comin', tenderfoot?
I hit the thingy.
This is great! This is living.
I never get to do this at home.
After I pass my next test,
I'm gonna be the best
junkyard dog there ever was!
I don't think so, doll.
You may be good, but you'll
never be as good as the master.
Here we go.
Ruby's right, carnsarnit!
In my day, there was only one stray
by which all dogs was measured.
The Tramp!
Huh? What?
He taught Buster
everything there is to know
about being on the streets, 'kay?
Buster's trouble was Tramp's trouble.
And Tramp's trouble
was Buster's trouble, 'kay?
That dog was a prize.
The one that got away.
Got away from me, at least.
Got away with everything!
I heard he once stole
an entire meat wagon!
'Kay? Yeah, and then the dogcatcher
chased him all the way to the river.
No, sir. It was dogcatchers.
How many?
At least a dozen.
Two dozen. Now that I think about it,
the police and the army cavalry
were after the boy as well.
He was trapped!
But if the Tramp was gonna go,
he was gonna go in style.
So, what happened?
We never saw him again after that.
They say when the wind blows,
you can still hear the Tramp...
Wow.
All right, all right.
That is not what happened.
He met this girl, see?
Queen of a kennel club set.
Even her prissy little name
still leaves a bad taste in my mouth!
Lady.
But he met his true love.
He betrayed me!
You can't have a family
and still be a junkyard dog!
So I gave Tramp a choice.
It's either me or her.
And he picked life on the end of a chain.
Hooked up with a real powder puff!
Sleepin' on carpets!
Free room and board!
Livin' the cushy pillow life!
That's when I learned the first rule
about being a junkyard dog...
Buster's trouble is Buster's trouble.
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
The Tramp used to scratch like that.
You ain't related, are ya?
-Who, me? No way!
-Good.
'Cause if you were, you'd be kibble.
Right, Buster.
No way, Dad.
That can't be true.
You gave it all up?
I mean, what could be better than this?
You okay, tenderfoot?
Who, me? Yeah. Yeah, sure.
What are you doing out here?
Don't you have
a nice family back home?
What difference does it make?
All families are alike.
They make you take baths
and sleep in a bed,
and you have to eat
everything in your bowl,
and when it rains,
you have to come indoors.
Let's just say you're lucky
you've never had to live with a family.
Wrong again, tenderfoot.
You mean, you had a family?
Actually, I've had five families.
-I always thought one was too many.
-I could never get one to stick.
Someone would take me in,
and just when I'd start to think,
"Wow, this is my family,"
they'd move or have a new baby
or have an allergy.
Same old story... I'm out on the street.
Wait a minute.
You really want a family, don't you?
But you've got Buster.
Buster! You can't tell him. You can't!
He'll kick me out.
Don't worry. Your secret's safe with me.
I promise.
Thanks.
So, I guess you're Buster's girl, huh?
I am not Buster's girl!
I don't belong to anybody.
The junkyard dogs
aren't much of a family,
but what choice do I have?
What more do you need?
As a junkyard dog, you can stay up late
-or dig or...
-Run.
-Yeah. Or play or dig or...
-Run!
-Right. Or chase squirrels...
-No! I mean, run!
Come on!
Angel!
Angel! Angel, help!
Now would be a good time! Hurry!
Scamp? Scamp!
Scamp, where are you?
Scamp? Scamp?
Excuse me, I'm looking for...
I think I'm onto somethin'.
Aye? Are you sure?
I most assuredly got him!
-This way!
-Come on, Pidge!
-Oh, look!
-Scamp!
Oh, please.
Scamp!
Thank goodness.
A wig? You smelled a wig, man!
You're hopeless!
I'm sorry, Miss Lady.
Come on. We've gotta keep searching.
I shouldn't have been so hard on him.
-Hey.
-Scamp?
You're all right. I was so worried...
So worried?
Yeah, right.
Get over yourself, house pet.
There's gotta be a better way
to take a bath, huh?
Trust me, there is
no good way to take a bath.
Wow! That is so weird.
How'd you do that?
-Talent.
-Let me try.
Oh, that was smooth.
You really are a house dog.
Oh, yeah? Yeah!
-You're weird.
-No, you're the weird one.
-Oh, yeah?
-Scamp.
I never had this feeling before
She gives me shakes
and shivers I can't ignore
And I see that there's more now
Than just running free
I never felt my heart beat so fast
I'm thinking of him first
and of myself last
And how happy I want him to be
It's amazing someone in my life
Just might be loving me
I didn't know that I could feel this way
It's so crazy something in my life
Is better than a dream
I didn't know that I could feel this way
She makes me warm and happy inside
He smiles and I
get dizzy and starry-eyed
-All these feelings I have
-Have me asking
Can this be love?
It's crazy
-I can hardly speak
-Whenever he
-Whenever she
-Says hi
I didn't know that I could feel
I never dreamed that I could feel
-I didn't know that I could feel
-This
-Way
Nice neighbourhood. Snob Hill.
Hey, Jim Dear never
leaves this gate open.
Come on, Tramp.
Oh, no! We gotta get out of here!
Why? What's wrong?
Come on, boy.
We've done all we can for one day.
Oh, we'll find him.
You were the best street dog
there ever was,
and I still have faith in the old Tramp.
Old Tramp?
If only the old Tramp was still here.
Come on, Tramp!
We'll find Scamp tomorrow.
-The Tramp is your father?
-I... Wait, no, wait!
Angel, wait!
Did you find him?
Maybe tomorrow.
Scamp.
Bad Scamp.
Gosh, I didn't think
they'd miss me that much.
You didn't think they'd miss you?
I can't believe you'd run away
from a home like this.
Well, you don't know what it was like.
No, I don't.
Must have been horrible
having someone care
about you that much.
I need to be wild and free.
I'll never find that here.
I'd give anything to have what you have.
And I'd give anything
to have what you have.
Come on, Scamp.
We could run off together.
We don't need them.
Angel, don't you understand?
Only one more test,
and I'll finally be a junkyard dog.
-That's where I belong.
-No, you don't belong there.
You're better than that, Scamp,
and that's what I like about you.
Come on, tenderfoot, let's go.
Wow!
Wow! Look!
I really think we should keep searching.
Nonsense!
It's the Fourth of July!
Time to have some fun.
You can continue
your search after our picnic.
Aunt Sarah, we're not really
in the mood to celebrate.
Oh, come now, Scamp will be all right.
You'll find him.
But, first, let's eat.
I won't have my Fourth of July
ruined by that little Scamp.
There, there, boy.
I knew it. Beautiful.
Scampo, front and centre.
Take a look out there.
See that family?
You mean that family, over there?
No! This family, right here.
Now, as your final test,
I want you to infiltrate their picnic
and liberate their chicken
right out from under the nose
of that meek little house dog.
You don't have to prove
anything, Scamp.
Just walk away.
Since when do you care so much?
I thought you were better than this.
Pipe down, Angelcakes!
Come on, kid.
You wanna be wild and free, don't you?
All it's gonna cost you
is one juicy chicken.
Yeah. I shoulda known.
Once a house dog, always a house dog.
I'm no house dog!
Scamp back!
Oh, my goodness!
-Scamp!
-Monster!
Scamp back! Scamp back!
-Scamp wanna play!
-Scamp?
-Come back!
-Where him go?
It's chow time, boys!
You...
You little mutt! I won't forget you!
I'll lock you in the pound, I swear it!
Slick move. Lost him.
-Don't bet on it!
-What?
Hey, slow down there, whirlwind.
I'm not going home! You can't make me.
I know, I know. Easy.
I just want to talk.
So, how you doin' out here?
It's great, Dad.
The junkyard dogs have
taught me all the tricks.
I go wherever I want,
do whatever I please.
-No chains, no fences.
-No regard for someone else's lunch?
That's how it is out here on the streets.
But then, you know
all about that, don't you?
You make the rules, Dad,
but you didn't have to follow them
when you were my age.
Is that why you didn't tell me
you were a street dog?
I didn't want that life for you,
because I found something better.
I found love.
Ain't that beautiful?
I think I'm gettin' all misty-eyed here.
I see you haven't changed a bit.
So here we are again,
just like old times,
before you turned
your back on everything
that makes a dog a dog.
He says you walked out on him.
After I met your mother,
I guess Buster just got jealous.
-You ditched me!
-I fell in love!
You made your choice!
Now it's his turn to choose.
Come on, kid.
You don't know what
he's really like, Son.
-You're coming home.
-You hear that, kid?
Daddy's tellin' you what to do again.
You don't belong here.
And he's leading you
back to a life on the chain.
I'm offerin' you freedom.
-Scamp.
-Scamp!
-Make your choice, kid.
-He doesn't have a choice.
I know what's best for him!
No! You know what's best for you!
Well, I'm not you, Dad!
I'm a junkyard dog!
That's my boy.
I guess there are some things
you have to learn on your own.
When you've had enough,
our door is always open.
House dog to the end.
What'd I tell ya, kid?
You can't teach an old dog new tricks.
-Huh?
Hey, Scampski!
This is for all you've done, kid.
You did it, kid!
You're at the top of the heap now...
A junkyard dog!
I'm... I'm a junkyard dog.
You made it to the pack!
You're a doll, dollface.
I'm a junkyard dog!
-How could you do that?
-Come on, Angel!
He's your father! Go after him!
You're not like the rest of us.
You're good and decent. Kind.
The streets will beat that
out of you if you stay!
But I made it!
This is everything that
I've ever dreamed of.
Dreamed of what? This?
You have a home
and a family that loves you.
You're not like the rest of us, Scamp.
Oh, yeah, yeah, that's right.
Let's see,
he's good and decent and kind.
Is that it, Scampy?
You wanna be a widdle house doggie?
No!
'Cause you know how I feel
about house dogs.
Hey, cut it out!
She's the one who wants to be
a house dog, not me!
Oh, no. I didn't mean that.
Is that true, Angel baby?
I don't think a family's so bad.
You hear that, boys?
She wants to be a little house pet!
Oh, she want to be a little house pet!
Gonna wear ribbons.
You ain't no junkyard dog.
That's right, Buster.
I'm not. Not any more.
Oh, and... I'm not your girl.
There's going to be trouble!
-Maybe you do belong here.
-Oh, come on.
Where is your sense of humour?
Come on, Angel!
Who needs her?
Let her go find some
snivelling little family.
That's where she belongs.
Angel?
I didn't mean it, Angel!
I don't know what I was thinking!
Really!
Angel, where are you?
Just as I suspected,
out looking for Angel.
Beautiful.
Time to settle an old score.
Hold it right there, ya scoundrel!
What the...
Well, I'll be!
You're not gettin' away this time!
Great. I got everything I ever wanted,
and it stinks.
Come here, ya little hooligan!
Buster!
Gotcha!
Well, lookee here. No collar.
It's a one-way trip to the pound for you.
Oh, man, slick move.
Me without a collar.
How could I be so stupid?
Dad was right.
Buster's nothing but trouble.
I wish I was home.
Always there
To warm you in the winter
With shelter from the rain
Always there
To catch you when you're falling
Always there to stand you up again
Family
By your side
In seconds if you ask it
Arms out wide
To welcome you to stay
Near enough
To listen to your heart song
Always there
To help you on your way
Family
-Family
What is a family?
Caring and devoted hearts
With endless love to share
-Love that will follow you everywhere
Always there
To welcome you in winter
What is a family?
Arms out wide
To welcome you to stay
Right by your side
Near enough
-To listen to your heart song
Always there
To help you on your way
Family
Always there
-Family
-Scamp?
-Angel!
-Scamp!
-Get out of here! He'll get you, too!
This'll hold ya, you crazy mutt!
Thought you could outfox me, huh?
Well, that'll be the day.
Hey, kid, looks like you got thrown
in the wrong cell!
Hey, Reggie. Long time no see, huh?
Oh, I found you!
You gotta come! Hurry!
Scamp's in trouble!
-Scamp?
-He's in the pound!
-Hold on, Son!
-Dad!
Keep your paws off my boy!
Hey! Paws off my pop!
Oh, yeah! He's cashed in his bones.
He's cashed!
Dad?
Dad, you did it!
Slick move!
All right, we have to go now.
You! The one that got away.
Let go! Let go! Oh, no!
Oh, have mercy!
Oh, let... Oh, let go!
Aren't the fireworks lovely tonight?
Angel!
Come on, you two.
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey!
What about me?
Your old pal, right? Oh, come on!
After I stood by youse
all through that fight?
Hey, come back here
when you're walking away from me!
-Pop?
-Son.
I'm so sorry.
I shouldn't have run away.
Whirlwind.
Maybe I was also being
a little too tough on you.
I don't see any harm in the two of us
goin' down to the river once in a while
to bay at the moon. What do you say?
Really? You and me?
Your old man's still
got a few good howls
-left in him.
-I found him!
I found him for sure this time!
I found him!
You found nothing! Again!
So far you've found six cats,
three gophers, two rabbits...
-Go easy on him, Uncle Jock.
-No, I'll not go easy on him, Scamp!
Five flyin' pigs, a wildebeest!
Scamp?
Why, it is Scamp!
Aye, I'll never hear
the end of this one, either.
-Ready to go home, whirlwind?
-Not quite, Pop.
There's one last thing
I gotta take care of.
Do mine eyes deceive me?
Hey, Scamp! Scampadoodle!
You escaped the pound!
Yeah, no thanks to you!
Hey, come on. You know our motto.
You can keep your motto!
But not this.
I'm going home where I belong.
So long, Buster.
Hey, ya missed, Scampalooza! Huh?
-That's my boy!
-Let's go home, Pop.
I'll get... Come back here!
You can't leave me here!
You're nothin' but a house pet!
It's a good look for you, Buster.
The garbage adds some class.
Hey. Hey, someone wanna
lend me a paw here?
I think a home sounds nice.
With lots of children
and hugs and kisses!
If you dogs leave,
you're never comin' back!
Au revoir, Buster!
It has been, as you say, beautiful!
Dogs! You can't leave me here!
I was only kidding.
Buster's trouble ain't Buster's trouble.
Come on.
Buster's trouble is everybody's trouble!
What's all the commotion? Scamp?
Hi, Scamp! Scamp come home!
He's back!
Hi, Scamp, I love you!
Good job, boy.
Oh, Scamp.
It's so good to have you
back where you belong.
You reek! You need a bath.
But we'll worry about that later.
Jim Dear, I think Scamp
brought a friend home.
Hey there, girl. Come on.
Come on, girl. It's okay.
Don't be afraid.
Did you help our Scamp
out of those lonely streets?
She's a little angel.
Angel! Angel!
Jim Dear, you don't suppose...
Oh, no, Darling.
We've got enough dogs as it is.
You know we can't...
No. No. We can't. I...
Oh, what's the use?
Welcome to the family, Angel.
Angel!
In our small, little, not too big
Little, homey, nice, little, quaint, little
Always friendly
Old New England town
Welcome
Welcome!
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org