SANTORINI, GREECE
They've found another one.
There'll be no treasure left for her.
Mark the location.
That's the Frenchman.
And over there, Kristos.
They're all coming. All except one.
All right, follow Kristos.
When he dives, we dive.
Maybe we'll get lucky
and find whatever's down there.
Look at that, Jimmy. Look!
Why isn't she slowing down?
- Whoa!
- You were asking?
- I knew it!
Hello, boys. You're all wet.
Many raiders are here,
and you make us wait!
But you know I can't resist a bit of fun.
What's all this fuss about?
What do they think is down there?
I don't know what they think,
but I think it's the Luna Temple.
The Luna Temple?
My sons! If it's not on television, forget it!
- It was built by Alexander the Great.
- A Greek, if you don't know!
Alexander collected treasures
and stored them in two places.
The majority went to his library in Egypt.
But his most prized possessions
went here... the Luna Temple.
By law, no one was allowed to record
its location, and in 330 BC it was...
...swallowed by the sea.
- Destroyed during a volcanic eruption.
Lost for ever.
Until yesterday.
If even half of it is intact, it will be
the greatest find since the Pyramids.
The others are heading along this shelf.
- That's based on the currents?
- Yes.
This, Gus, is why I was late.
It's a geological,
taken two hours after the quake.
The epicentre was here,
five miles northeast of us, but...
...look at the currents
along the shelf now.
Wait! They've shifted.
So, while they're all diving there,
the ruins will actually be...
...here.
Let's go.
Something wrong?
First, Alexander doesn't record
the temple's location.
Then, God wipes it from the earth
with a volcano.
Now, even the currents change.
Lara, maybe this temple's
not meant to be found.
Everything lost is meant to be found.
Don't worry.
It's incredible!
It's unbelievable! Whoa!
- Oh, my God.
- This is huge!
Thank you.
Wonderful.
Jimmy, this is wonderful!
- Do you see what I see?
- Oh, my God!
It's incredible.
Nicky, look at this.
We're going to be rich!
Lara! What do you say
to two handsome Greek partners?
Well, when you find two, let me know!
- She's talking about you.
- No, you!
Pack the gold coins.
- Lara, what is that?
- It's mine.
What is she doing?
Lara! That column is collapsing!
Aftershock!
- I think that's a sign to leave!
- Two minutes!
- Lara, we need to leave now!
- We've got to move!
Keep packing. This thing is going
to collapse. Take those two.
- We have to hurry up.
- Go, go! Come on!
Lara!
Lara? Lara, it's us, Hillary and Bryce!
She's disorientated.
That's normal after three days.
Nice day for a dip.
Gentlemen, there is an expression:
"It's not nice to fool Mother Nature."
Yet that is precisely what I've been
doing for some time now...
...whether it be sarin gas for Mr San,
improved typhoid for Mr Krev
to use in the Balkans,
enhanced cholera for Mr Duvalier.
While these weapons
serve their purpose,
there have always been limitations.
Stable diseases aren't lethal.
Deadly ones burn out too quickly.
Mother Nature can only
be fooled so much.
Deploy my weapon, and your enemies,
however great, will collapse from within.
Rather like Mr Monza's
collapsing right now.
- What the hell is going on?
- Monza told Ml6 about this meeting.
That's why the change of location.
He was going to turn me over to them
and then seek asylum in the West.
A smart man would've known
I was on to him.
He would never have got on the plane.
But I knew you would.
You actually thought you could fool me.
That, gentlemen, is the sound
of a traitor dying.
That was an accelerated form of Ebola,
deadliest disease known to man.
Highly contagious.
However, as with all known diseases,
there exist stockpiles of antiserum
in the West.
There is no antiserum
for what I am offering you.
No treatment. No vaccine. No cure.
The world's never seen
anything like what I've uncovered.
Uncovered?
Yes. I've branched out.
Archaeology.
0-7-7-4-4-6-8-1.
That is the account
at the Landesbank in Bern.
$100 million each, if you please.
- Where's Chen Lo?
- He has the orb, but Ml6 is on to him.
- How?
- He doesn't know.
Rather than risk bringing it, he's waiting.
I have just told a cabin full of men about
Pandora. The clock cannot be reset.
Tell him to bring the orb at once.
You'll find the killers.
Don't take it out on me!
- Bryce, what have we got?
- I haven't loaded your images yet.
- What about references to an orb?
- I checked.
Inventories of the Luna Temple
do not list any orb.
I want you both to list every orb
ever mentioned in Greek history.
Every one?
That's... liable...
...to be...
...thousands.
Then we'll read thousands.
Start with that one.
Perhaps you'd like some tea
while you wait?
No, they wouldn't. Tea is for guests,
the door is for intruders!
They're from Ml6.
I can tell from their soft hands
and pressed suits.
They make decisions
and leave the dirty work for others.
- I've no interest in...
- His name's Chen Lo.
Along with his brother Xien, he runs
a ring of bandits, the Shay Ling.
They deal in guns, diamonds, antiquities
to sell on the black market.
They followed you when you arrived
in Santorini, where they killed Gus.
- Why?
- For this.
Our listening post in Malta
intercepted that fax.
It was sent from Chen Lo
to a man named Jonathan Reiss.
The scientist? Won the Nobel Prize?
He's now the foremost designer
of biological weapons in the world.
His creations have been at the heart
of bio-terror in the past 15 years.
Reiss's disdain for life is legendary.
He doesn't care who his weapons kill.
A modern-day Doctor Mengele.
We know Chen Lo followed you
to obtain the orb, and thus deliver Reiss.
We don't know why.
Candidly, that terrifies us.
Reiss is not to be trifled with.
Pandora's box.
Reiss is going to use the orb
to find Pandora's box.
The Greek myth?
Pandora opens a forbidden box
and unleashes pain into the world?
That's the Sunday school version, yes.
How do you think life began?
Shooting star? Primordial ooze?
In 2300 BC, an Egyptian pharaoh
found a place he named The Cradle
of Life, where we, life, began.
There he found a box,
which brought life to Earth.
The pharaoh opened it, but all that
was left was the Ramante, or anti-life.
The plague, the companion to life.
- Companion?
- Nature is about balance.
All the world comes in pairs.
Yin and Yang, right and wrong.
- What did this plague do?
- It levelled the pharaoh's army.
A soldier was dispatched to transport
the box to the end of the world.
2,000 years later,
Alexander the Great reached India,
where his army was ravaged
by a plague after finding a box.
India?
That's where the soldier brought it?
Alexander felt the box
was too powerful,
so he returned it to its home,
The Cradle of Life.
It has never been seen since.
- And this Cradle of Life is where?
- No one knows.
Alexander used a map with the box,
which he then hid from the world.
But the name he gave this map
was "Mati",
and the literal translation
for the word "Mati" is eye.
The orb is the map, hidden
in the Luna Temple by Alexander.
Reiss will use it to find Pandora's box,
and when he opens it,
he will unleash a weapon more
powerful than you could ever imagine.
The markings form a pattern,
but even if I figure what they mean,
we still can't read the whole map
because we've only a partial view.
- We have to figure out how to read it.
- Right. Thank you.
On behalf of Her Majesty,
recover this box before Doctor Reiss.
Oh...! Well, now that I have
Her Majesty's permission...
- Tell me where to find the orb.
- It's in China with Chen Lo.
We'll assign two of our best agents
to help.
I don't want them.
- Expertise in archaeology doesn't...
- I didn't say that I don't need help.
But you won't get me there in time.
I need someone inside the Shay Ling.
Their methods, their hideouts.
- I need Terry Sheridan.
- Not if he were the last man on Earth!
Terry Sheridan, ex-commander
with the Royal Marines,
turned mercenary and traitor.
Put that man on the trail of a weapon
he can sell to the highest bidder?
Open!
I am your host, Armin Kal.
Welcome to Fantasy Island.
Croft.
Hello, Terry.
What do you think of my new place?
It's not quite Croft Manor.
What? A key to your heart?
To a flat in Zurich.
You can pick another city, if you want.
Your record expunged,
your citizenship restored.
- By?
- Ml6.
Ml6...
Would that make me Faust,
or the Devil?
Pick one, because Ml6 will also
arrange a new identity.
- Yeah? You think I need their help?
- Having two faces doesn't count.
What do I have to do?
- Take me to the Shay Ling.
- The Shay who?
Chen Lo took something from me
and I want it back.
Is that you or Ml6?
Also, I've arranged for £5 million
when we succeed.
- Call it "second chance" money.
- Or life insurance for you.
I don't need any.
You and I, working alone?
It's easier to see through you that way.
So what if, afterwards,
Ml6 decide that me back in the world
isn't such a great idea?
Then I feel sorry for whomever
they get to come after you.
- You've authorisation to kill me?
- Any time, for any reason.
Why don't you just do it, then?
What is it they say? "Hell hath no fury..."
You're not that good.
The Shay Ling are like ghosts, Croft.
They move constantly,
and their home is the most remote
mountain region in China.
Region?
You'll have to do better than that.
Get me into China,
and I'll get you to them in a day.
No guns, no money,
no weapons of any kind.
Talk about taking the fun out of life!
They've spies all over China.
We slip in to Beijing undetected,
then we go by truck.
Truck? I was thinking
about something a little faster.
A little faster?
This is a little faster,
but the Chinese will track the pod.
- There won't be any pod to find.
- Will there be any of us to find?
- Ready? Now.
- Ready for what?
The ditching was good, Croft.
I'll give you that.
But we'll never find a vehicle
in a place like this.
Oh, it's so lovely to see you.
- Is everything ready?
- Yes.
Your clothes, guns and knives
are over there.
And I took the liberty of tuning your bike.
- May I?
- Yes.
- Lara.
- Ah!
- What is the happy couple up to?
- Accessorising.
- Where are we on reading the orb?
- All maps have a key, a legend.
The orb's key's not there,
it must've been lost.
Or somewhere in the temple.
Go through every image I took
near the orb.
The key must've been linked to it
in some way. Right, bye, then.
It's unlike Lara to take a partner.
Where are you two going?
We'll take a nice little trip,
breathe some fresh mountain air,
stop by my friends, the Shay Ling.
The Shay Ling watch all the roads,
we'll go round the back.
- We'll go straight.
- Maybe you didn't hear me.
The Shay Ling have men
on every road from here to Luoyang.
Not every road.
- A bit rusty?
- It's coming back.
I expected more from a Scot.
I don't expect anything
from an Englishwoman!
Good, 'cause you're
not gonna get anything.
The fun's over.
From now on, it's by foot.
- Best to reconsider that "no gun" rule.
- No.
OK.
And don't be looking at my ass.
- Where do I fit in?
- You're the guide.
I mean,
when you think back on the vast
scheme of your adventurous life,
where do I fit in?
Was I the love of your life
or just another bump on the road?
Was I time well spent?
Four months, more good than bad?
Come on, it had to be more
than that, am I right?
You're right.
It was five months.
- You're laughing at me.
- Because I used to find you charming.
I am charming.
You're late!
Tilt your head back. Do it!
You might see again in an hour. Maybe.
What's this? It's not there.
There's no orb.
Is there anything
you can tell me about this?
- Hello?
- You didn't like your messenger?
I didn't. But I liked the men
I lost in the temple.
You underestimated Lady Croft.
I underestimated
how much this orb is worth.
There's so many
horrible diseases in the world.
Things we are particularly
susceptible to as children.
You could be holding
little Shiho or Tai by the hand,
as a mysterious ailment
ravages their bodies.
You kill them, and I will give
your orb to Lady Croft.
She's a few miles away
from here as we speak.
I wonder how much she would pay.
I'll pay you an additional $12 million.
It will be yours once you've delivered
the orb along with Lady Croft's body.
- You don't know where they are.
- You're impossible.
You pretended to know
so I'd get you out.
This isn't a tomb, Croft,
and the Shay Ling aren't mummies.
They're killers.
But if you don't trust me...
I'm sorry to have to do this,
but you're wasting time.
You want to shoot me? Shoot me.
Personally, I'd rather you do it...
...than them.
Well, Terry,
what part of "never come back again"
didn't you understand?
You wanted to find the Shay Ling.
Come on!
The only way to get into their place
is as their prisoners.
- You might've told me that before.
- You would've believed me?
Make Chen Lo a better offer
than his buyer. He'll cross them.
Even if his buyer's Jonathan Reiss?
You might've told me that before!
- Were you really gonna kill me?
- I bet she would have.
I've seen her in action.
Didn't Terry tell you?
The last time any of us saw him,
he was riding away with a truck...
...full of my Ming vases.
And sitting next to him...
...was his sister.
How is she?
You... shouldn't have come here.
It got me out of prison.
Besides, the lady has a good offer.
- Better than Reiss.
- Really?
- Should I take it?
- Take it.
Or you and I ransom her and the thing
back to the British for triple.
Let's talk.
Not you, Terry.
Lady Croft and I.
You wait here. Catch up.
I'll be four minutes.
Terrific.
There is something
I think you will appreciate.
This is the largest group
of terracotta warriors I have found.
The King of Chin made them
for use in the afterlife.
To fend off enemies
he made in this one.
Sounds like we could both use a set.
I will be happy to sell some to you.
I hope you're as entrepreneurial
with the orb.
You lost men, I lost men. I see
no reason we should both lose again.
If I want double
what Reiss offered me...
- Is it here?
- It's worth a lot.
Then you know Reiss will kill you
the moment you give it to him.
- Your government assures my safety?
- No.
But I will.
That must hurt, saying that to me.
Take the offer.
- You presume to give me orders?
- Take the offer before it expires.
No.
- Then I will have to force you.
- Then I will have to kill you!
Has it been four minutes yet?
That was nice.
It's too bad you're on the wrong side.
Tell me where the orb is
and it spares your life.
The Flower Pagoda, in Shanghai.
9 p.m.
This is mine.
Now, we're even.
Now!
Remember that "no gun" rule?
I reconsidered.
You know there was a staircase
we could've used?
- Lara, are you all right?
- Smashing.
I'm on my way to Shanghai,
and I need you to look at something.
It was in the Luna Temple.
I'm betting it's the key to the markings.
She's holding some sort
of musical instrument.
It's sound.
- That's brilliant.
- The key must be linked to it.
I'll start decoding the images.
Get the rest. Bye.
- Miss you.
- Bye!
Oh, well.
Just like old times.
I think that's the first time
you've actually smiled because of me.
Why did you do it?
I started thinking I was tired of doing
things somebody else's way.
It'd always be somebody else's way.
So you abandon your men
and betray your country?
Leaving my men and my country,
that didn't hurt as much as I thought.
But leaving you did.
You're a hard act to follow, Croft.
You know why you and I
get along so well?
No.
We are two of a kind, me and you.
- We are nothing alike.
- I don't think we're alike.
But I do think we're a pair.
Opposite sides of the same coin.
- My men have the roof covered.
- Set down in the square instead.
My men will also have things covered.
OK, fine.
OK, Sean, let's go!
They're landing in the square.
- We're in the wrong position. Stairs?
- No time.
- Rooftops?
- No.
I've got a plan.
Stay here. Wait for my signal.
Here's the money, come and get it!
Wait for my signal, huh?
- Give me that box!
- Money first!
- Give me that box now!
- No! You first!
Christ! Get us out of here!
Take us up!
Take it up!
Go! Run her over!
- Yeah?
- We tried it your way. Now we try mine.
- Bring it to the top of the pagoda now!
- OK.
Got you!
Come on! Hold it up!
- Come closer!
- Raise it higher! Higher!
- My regards to your brother!
- Too late.
Croft, what are you doing?
Take us up!
Move! Go!
Let's go! Move!
I'm tired of you pointing that at me.
You OK?
- Never better.
- Looks like we lost the orb.
I wouldn't go vaulting
into thin air for nothing.
I've put a tracer on the crate.
Got it. Look.
Impressive.
A weapons lab
in the middle of the city? No way.
He must've dumped that crate.
No, it's here.
One of the buildings?
No.
It's exactly where we're standing.
Part of me allowed for the possibility
that Pandora's box was just a legend.
But now I know it's there.
- She escaped.
- She has no idea where we are.
We take no chances.
Have everything we need to make
an antidote transferred to the jet.
I need an out for two people.
Mid-city. Soon.
What? Are you crazy?
- Are we set?
- Piece of cake.
Hello.
- So much for easy.
- What is that?
He's already decoding the orb.
Bugger!
Headset.
You've gotta get everyone out.
What do you suggest, the fire alarm?
Not bad. But that's just the alarm.
There's no danger.
Do you think anyone here is paid
enough to take that chance?
Don't even think about it.
It's her.
Yes?
Damn!
I'm glad, Lara!
That would've been too easy!
Give me your best!
How's that?
- I'm going off-line.
- No, don't!
- Thanks.
- You're welcome.
Hello, boys.
Did you understand the medallion?
Yeah. The markings are sound waves.
We've translated all the markings,
roughly half the orb.
Let's complete the set, then.
I'll send the rest of them to you.
Then finish the translation
and transmit the sounds back to me.
We need more back-up.
Smart girl.
Move!
Don't shoot her! Not until we're sure
the computer has done its job.
You honestly believe you'll be able
to control what's in that box?
Really, Lara, you disappoint me.
Have we received payment
from all the buyers?
No, you don't want to control it at all.
You're using the buyers.
They'll release it as just another
weapon, and the world blames them.
What's left of the world blames them.
Once I have the virus,
I'll make enough antidote
to protect the best and the brightest.
Heads of corporations,
heads of state. Life will go on.
You've never thought,
"The world would be better
without certain people"?
I can certainly think of one person
I could do without.
There it is.
I'm sorry, Lara. You'd have been
welcome in my world.
Piss off.
Shoot her between the eyes.
No mistakes.
Asshole!
I'm gonna get you.
Follow me!
You're mine.
Bingo! Two one-way tickets
out of Hong Kong.
Parachutes!
Something a little faster.
Come on!
Our rendezvous point is two
and a half, maybe three miles.
You're aware that no one's ever gone
further than one mile?
- I am now.
- This way!
- Right, you go first.
- No, you go first.
I'll go first!
Holy cow!
Follow her.
Hi, Terry. Good to see you.
I suppose you want paying, then?
We agreed on $200?
No, $300! Expenses.
So this...
...rock is the map?
Yes, it is.
I've never seen anything like it.
Have you?
And it's the only way to find that box?
Just think, you could take it
and walk out the door.
No. Window's better,
off the ship faster, harder to track.
Croft, do you really think
I would do that to you?
You can break my wrist,
but I'm still gonna kiss you.
Not exactly what I had in mind, but OK.
- Why didn't you shoot Reiss?
- What?
He must have walked
right past you in the lab.
Why didn't you shoot him?
No clear shot.
I didn't know where you were.
I'll inform Ml6 of the completion
of your service.
You'll have your money and your life.
- Don't waste it.
- This is no time to split up.
Yes, it is, before you make
the wrong decision.
OK, you want to leave? Go ahead.
But don't pretend
it's to try and save me.
You're afraid
you might not pull the trigger.
Afraid of letting your guard down,
of letting anyone in.
I'm not leaving
because I couldn't kill you.
I'm leaving because I could.
Good morning.
Might I borrow your television?
It's important.
Cheers. Lovely.
- Hello, Bryce.
- Hello, Lara.
- Are you ready?
- Yes.
Right. Sending the last images
of the orb... now.
Got them.
Translating... Done.
Send the sounds.
Sending it now.
No, nothing.
Oh, well, back to the drawing board.
No, wait. The tones are being distorted.
Send me the file.
Look, Lara, I...
I really don't think that's gonna work.
Yes, it will. Ever heard your voice
on a tape recorder? Same thing.
Why are we having this discussion?
Send me the file.
- Sending it.
- Thank you.
Lara!
Africa. It's in Africa.
- Somewhere near Kilimanjaro.
- Great, Lara.
How long for Reiss
to fix his computers?
Twenty-four hours at the fastest.
Ask Kosa to meet me
north of his village.
0800 hours. Bye, then.
A bit faster than
twenty-four hours, I'd say. Out!
Africa it is.
- Kosa? How are you?
- Lara?
- You had the jeep cleaned.
- I know how you like your equipment!
- Where are you? I can't see you.
- Don't worry, I can see you.
Where are you coming from now?
Keep going straight,
keep your speed steady.
Lara! Welcome back!
Do you ever do anything the easy way?
And risk disappointing you?
I've lost my friend and
I'm not sure where to go...
Nice shirt.
She went to Kilimanjaro
to play with the elephants.
Kosa, we've never been here, have we?
We didn't come
to this area before. Why?
I've seen that mountain before.
The box is there somewhere.
The locals call it
"The Mountain of God".
There's a tribe that makes
a home on it that might help us.
Leave this object and go.
And never speak of it.
To trespass on The Cradle of Life is
to risk flooding the world with death.
Men are coming for the box.
Unlike me, they won't look at it
with fear or respect.
They will open it. They want to use it.
I'm sorry if I have to disturb your gods
to keep this from happening.
But I will do whatever I must.
Do you truly understand
what you are doing?
Are you truly prepared
for what you are about to learn?
Some secrets must remain secrets.
These are very heavy burdens,
very lonely burdens.
If you find the box,
you will have to carry them.
I am prepared, sir.
He warns that no one who has looked
for the box has come back.
He says the land beyond the canyon
belongs to the Shadow Guardians.
Shadow Guardians?
They do not sleep.
They never rest.
They move like the wind.
And anything
that walks their land will die.
And the Cradle itself?
Only with the orb can it be revealed.
Inside you will find a place of madness.
Sky and Earth are one.
Direction, meaningless.
He's going to give us twenty men
to take us as far as they can,
to The Cradle of Life
where the box is hidden.
We're getting closer.
He said you're right.
The Cradle of Life lies near the summit.
- He wants to know how you knew.
- The orb.
He says he will not turn back with
the others. He'll go as far as we go.
- He will fight the Shadow Guardians.
- You're a very brave man.
What is he saying?
That your accent is funny.
Get down!
Back! Back!
Back! Get back!
Thank you, Lara, for leading us here
and for finding the orb.
However, you have seen
the exact position.
You could save me hours, days even.
Help me, I'll make it worth your while.
No.
Think of what I'm offering you.
Let her go.
A chance to find out how it all began.
Life, Lara, the origin of what we are.
Don't tell me you're not tempted.
- That's what got Pandora into trouble.
- They told me you wouldn't do it.
And I told them you would, rather than
lose two of your closest friends.
- Take us to The Cradle of Life.
- I'm sorry, Lara.
It's your destiny to see what's inside.
He is right. It's just beyond
the canyon, remember?
Such a short walk
might save your friends.
Well, if it spares my friends...
I'm up for a walk.
I'm sure she'd understand.
You should've told her we were hostage.
He'd never have found her.
I don't suppose either of you
know how to fly a helicopter?
I can.
- What?
I've got over 150 hours between
flight simulation games, models...
And in the real thing?
- Two.
- Two?
You're only gonna fly it once I'm out,
so remember your two hours well!
It's through here?
Move, baby.
What was that?
You! Check it out!
Keep moving!
What are you doing?
Back in formation now!
Holy shit!
Don't!
They seem to react to movement.
They're gone.
We're close. I've seen it in your eyes.
Take me to Pandora's box.
- I don't know how.
- Do it now!
You were the one who wanted
to go for a walk. So start walking!
The next one will be higher.
Only with the orb can it be revealed.
All right. I'll need the orb.
Do you want to see
The Cradle of Life or not?
You tell me what to do with it.
Don't think you can outwit me, Croft.
Oh, do shut up!
So, this is The Cradle of Life...
Here we are.
It's all yours. Time to be a hero.
There it is.
Perfect, isn't it? All that power
in such a banal container.
When Pandora saw inside the box,
she cried black acid for tears.
And, as it was a woman
who found the box,
I see no reason to break with tradition.
A woman should collect the box.
Go on!
It is impossible to reach.
Now take it!
Take it!
I don't think so, Reiss!
You OK?
- I'm fine. I'm fine.
- There you go.
- You come prepared.
- I know how clumsy you are.
Hillary and Bryce?
They're fine.
Thank you.
What was that?
Let's get out of here.
Terry? What are you doing?
You're joking, right?
We're taking this with us. This is ours.
You're not walking out of here
with that box.
So you're saying we just leave it,
when it's worth a fortune?
- Put it back.
- I don't think so.
It could kill millions
of innocent people.
- Now you're being dramatic.
- Put it back.
No!
I've helped you keep this away
from Reiss. This is my reward.
I'm taking it with me.
So it's come to this, has it?
Well, you do have
authorisation to kill me.
Better do it, then.
'Cause if you think standing
in front of me is gonna be enough...
You don't have it in you to stop me.
See, all your beliefs...
...all your ideals, they're not real.
I am. And you've loved me.
You think you're strong,
but you'll not choose them over me.
- Now move.
- No.
Fine.
The box is safe now.
Some things are not meant to be found.
Didn't you ever do anything
the easy way?
I wouldn't want to disappoint you.
- Lara, are you OK?
- All right?
This is... very touching.
You know us, always making friends,
having a laugh.
Getting married...
What?
This is a wedding ceremony
and you are the grooms.
Good luck, boys!
Go!