Downloaded from
YTS.MX
Official YIFY movies site:
[fanfare]
[applause]
- Aloha.
- [all] Aloha.
Today the Galactic Council
assembles
to honor Lilo and Stitch,
who have successfully
captured all 625
of Jumba's
genetic experiments,
turned them
from bad to good,
and found each a place
where it can belong.
[applause]
To recognize the completion
of their task,
the Galactic Council
has elected to bestow
the following rewards...
[gasps]
You hear that, Jumba?
We're gonna
get prizes.
Dr. Jumba Jookiba,
we hereby return
the confiscated key
- to your laboratory.
- Hah!
With old lab back,
evil possibilities are infinite!
Agent Wendy Pleakley...
[snores]
we hereby offer you
the chair of Earth Studies
at the GACC.
Ohh.
Galactic Alliance
Community College?
Yes!
As for Stitch,
you are hereby
offered a commission
as captain of
the Galactic Armada
and commander of its
new flagship the BRB-9000.
Ooh. BRB.
What's BRB
stand for?
Big Red Battleship!
Ah-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha!
Finally, Lilo Pelekai,
you shall become our
first Earth ambassador
and return to Kauai
to be the experiments'
sole caretaker.
[applause]
You mean Jumba and Pleakley
and Stitch aren't coming home?
Stitch wants to come back
to Kauai. Right, Stitch?
Oh, uh, Kauai.
Yeah.
Maybe everybody
wants to go back?
- Right. Of course.
- Right.
Don't you have
something to say?
Oh, yeah, right.
I'm wishing to go back
to stinky water planet
and share bunk bed
with bossy one-eyed noodle.
Is this your
final decision?
[all] Um...
- Eeh.
- Absolutely.
I suppose.
Or maybe...
Then so be it.
[electricity crackles]
* Aloha
* Ohana
[foghorn bellowing]
[Lilo] Now that we're done
catching experiments,
we can do whatever we want.
I want to finish
my logbook.
It's got a picture
of every experiment,
in the one place
they belong.
What do you want
to do, Stitch?
Hmm...
[humming]
- [grunts]
- [pipe creaks]
And, uh... Huh?
- [rustling]
- [Stitch muttering]
Ee-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha!
[imitates jets roaring]
Ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha!
[gibberish]
Scale model
of Big Red Battleship.
Impressive.
[microwave beeps]
Where are you taking
the microwave?
Hah! Without
evil genius lab,
Jumba must energize
genetic experiments
with primitive
Earth popcorn maker.
You know,
the microwave oven
was invented
by Dr. Percy Spencer.
Ah, who cares?
If you were a student
at GACC you'd care
'cause it would be
on the final exam.
And what do we
call this, class?
Breakfast?
Specifically,
grain-based flakes
immersed in bovine
gland extract.
Eww!
I'm off to work.
Oh, Pleakley.
I need you to fix
Lilo's skirt for hula class.
Only if you answer this extra
credit question correctly.
Where did the native Hawaiian
hula dance originate?
- Uh, Hawaii?
- Very good, Nani!
If you were attending GACC,
I'd move you
to the head of the class.
- [imitates jets roaring]
- [crash]
[turbine backfires]
[Gantu] Blitznak!
Without the reserve engines,
this ship is stupid and useless.
- Just like you.
- [sighs] Who am I kidding?
You're right.
I couldn't hold on to a single
one of those experiments.
You still got me,
your faithful
sandwich-making pal.
Yes. I noticed the little
Earth girl never captured you.
I guessed the one place
I belonged
was with my
blubber-butt buddy Gantu.
Maybe that was
my problem all along.
What? Your blubber butt?
[chuckles]
Gantu?
So, we're taking the old
two-man shuttle, huh? Heh-heh.
Hey, you want I should fix
a picnic lunch for the trip?
There's only room for two
on the two-man shuttle,
me and Dr. Hamsterviel.
- I'm breaking him
out of prison.
- What?
This is my last chance
to redeem myself.
If I succeed,
my future is secured.
What about my future? How am I
supposed to pay the bills?
Why not make sandwiches?
It's all you're good at.
- Maybe I will!
- Fine.
You're gonna miss
my egg salad!
Not enough mayonnaise
and too much dill weed.
What did you call me?
- [generator starts]
- [beep]
- [crackling]
- [beeps]
Aagh! Primitive
Earth science.
Jumba...
...what was
your old lab like?
Ah ha ha ha!
Galaxy Defense Industries.
State-of-art
genetic accelerator.
Endless uburnium
energy supply.
Everything little boy Jumba
ever dreamed of having
in evil genius laboratory!
[laughs]
Hah... Um, but popcorn power
is good too.
[beeps]
[Pleakley]
Welcome, students,
to Earthiana 101.
Quiet, class. Quiet!
Plooka,
spit out that gum!
Lenlu, stop playing
with your antenna.
- Pleakley.
- Aah! Oh, Lilo!
Don't pay
any attention to me.
I wasn't pretending to be
a professor of Earth Studies,
just like I dreamed of
since before I could walk
on three legs.
Not at all! I was just, uh,
uh... brushing my tongues!
BRB.
Scrump, have I ever
told you the story
of the Lonely Rooster?
Once there was a rooster
named Pancake.
He was lonely.
So he went to the beach
to make friends.
He made friends
with a shell named Paula
and an empty can of soda
named Jimmy
and a piece of a broken
surfboard named Steve.
They were good friends
and had fun playing together.
But then one day a big wave
splashed over the whole beach
and washed Paula and Jimmy
and Steve away.
[wave crashes]
Pancake was sad
that his friends were gone.
But Pancake
was never lonely again,
because he could always
remember them.
The end.
Lilo, are you OK?
Scrump and I are
getting used to the way
things used to be.
So, you're letting them go.
They'll say
they want to stay,
but it's just because
they don't want me
to be sad.
They'll be OK
without me, right?
Oh, Lilo.
You're showing so much
aloha spirit letting them go.
And the aloha you give
will always come back to you.
It's like a circle.
Aloha means hello,
but it also means goodbye.
It's hard to say goodbye.
I know, baby.
Goodbye, laundry!
Goodbye, dirty dishes!
Goodbye, dust bunnies.
Goodbye, goodbye, goodbye!
Nani says that letting you go
shows aloha spirit,
and that the aloha you give
will always come back to you.
Eh, interesting theory
but scientifically impossible.
I'm estimating
23 percent aloha
- is lost in giving process.
- [beakers break]
You know, aloha is one
of those Earth concepts
I never did understand.
Come, Pleakley. Oof!
What is in here,
bricks?
Concrete, adobe,
terra cotta...
You name the brick,
it's in there.
My students are sure
to find them fascinating.
Jumba, you belong back in your
real evil genius laboratory.
But if you're ever missing
Kauai, you can play this.
It's my favorite
Elvis record.
Pleakley, you belong at Galactic
Alliance Community College
teaching Earth stuff
to aliens.
That's why I'm
giving you this rock.
Here it's just
a dumb old paperweight,
but out there it'll be
a dumb old paperweight
from another planet.
I'll keep it
with me always.
And, Stitch,
you belong...
I'll miss you too.
But you belong
out in space,
catching bad guys with
the Big Red Battleship.
This is a very
special necklace.
I kept it hidden in
a sock for three years.
It's Ku Tiki,
the god of strength.
Promise to never
take it off?
- Promise.
- You're number 626.
- Name: Stitch.
- [camera clicks]
Aloha.
[alarm blaring]
Don't worry,
Dr. Hamsterviel,
your escape
will soon be complete.
What do you mean
"complete"?
You haven't even broken me
out of my cell!
Then who is this?
That's the warden's gerbil,
you nearsighted fish stick!
[laughter]
Hmm. He looks
just like you.
[P.A.] Security command,
release portal 7.
Run! Run!
And put down
that gerbil!
I brought you
a little surprise.
- What is it?
- An Earth souvenir.
They call it an aloha lei.
It symbolizes...
Excellent!
I'm starving!
Wait! Wait!
You're not supposed to...
[burps]
Never mind.
- [clears throat] Aloha.
- Captain Stitch.
The Council has received...
You have coconut cake
on your uniform.
Oh. Sorry.
[slurps]
The Council has received
a security alert.
With the aid
of the former Captain Gantu,
Dr. Jacques von Hamsterviel
has escaped from prison.
- [gibberish]
- This is your first mission
as captain of
the Galactic Armada.
Seek out and capture
Dr. Hamsterviel.
It will also be
the maiden voyage of...
- Oh!
- ...the BRB-9000.
- [man] BRB fueling complete.
- [woman] Hatchway secure.
[man] Captain has
arrived in the bay.
Oh! Big Red...
[playing march]
Whoo-hoo! Aah!
[cymbal crash]
He, uh, went in
through the air manifold.
- [door beeps]
- Captain on the...
- [Stitch laughs]
- ...ceiling?
Big Red, Big Red, Big Red!
Huh?
[seat motor whirring]
[clicks]
Hmm. [gibberish]
[computer]
Hyperdrive activated...
Captain, you're certain
you want to engage
the H-drive
in the spaceport?
Ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha!
[boosters firing]
Well, he's certainly
enthusiastic.
Yeeow! [cackles]
Is there anything else I can
get for you, Professor Pleakley?
Why, yes.
You could give me
a great big pinch
to wake me up!
I've got a huge
corner office,
a complete set of
the Encyclopedia Earthiana,
my very own walk-in closet,
the keys to the college
carpool van, and...
...galaxy-wide fame as the
greatest Earth expert ever!
[gasp] Is that
a real Earth rock?
Why, yes.
Yes, it is.
You've actually been
to Earth?
You must tell me everything.
Of course.
But you will have to wait
for my first lecture,
"Perspectives on Earthiana:
A One-Eyed View."
Lecture?
You don't give lectures.
I don't?
Oh. Well, then, in my
first class you can always...
And you don't have
classes either.
You're a supervising
professor.
That's why you get
all this great stuff:
the office,
the encyclopedias,
your own walk-in closet
and wardrobe.
Oh, right.
Could we take a look at
that, um, new wardrobe?
Ah! Jumba's
evil scientist laboratory.
Is just as I left it!
So many wonderful memories
of evil experimentation,
ending with disgrace,
arrest and imprisonment,
but still
wonderful memories.
So much new evil
to be done. Heh-heh-heh!
Where to begin?
Antiaircraft lollipops?
Oh! Permanently stinky
bedroom slippers?
Or perhaps device to stop
evil genius talking to self.
Heh-heh-heh-heh!
Eh, silly Jumba.
It's rounds time,
Scrump.
I used to do it
with Stitch,
but you can
help me instead.
We just check to make sure
that all Stitch's cousins
are still happy
in the one place they belong.
* I lai la ua i la
* No mala hini ohana
* Welcome, cousins
Come on by *
* Aloha, e komo mai
* I lai la ua i la
* No mala hini ohana
* Welcome, cousins
Come on by *
* Aloha, e komo mai
* Aloha
* We'll find a place
where you belong *
* Ohana
* A family
to call your own *
* Where you feel at home
Everybody sing *
* I lai la ua i la
* No mala hini ohana
* Welcome, cousins
Come on by *
* Aloha, e komo mai,
nai nai nai nai *
* I lai la ua i la
* No mala hini ohana
* Welcome, cousins
Come on by *
* Aloha, e komo mai
* Aloha
* Ohana
[popping]
* Aloha *
Wow! Wasp Mummies VI
is already out.
I hope my dad will
let me go see it.
- Well, I heard...
- Aloha, Myrtle.
Where are you
taking Gigi?
I'm taking her
to the canine spa.
What'd you do
with your dog?
He's an outer space pilot
in a Big Red Battleship
- and fighting bad guys.
- [Gigi whimpers]
Is not!
You're a weirdo!
- [girls] Yeah!
- No, I'm not!
I'm done doing
all that weird stuff now.
Wanna play dolls?
No way! Once a weirdo,
always a weirdo.
That's what my dad
used to say.
- I didn't know you had a dad.
- Quiet, Yuki.
In fact, I bet that's why
your dog ran away,
and I also bet that
he's never coming back.
- [girls] Yeah!
- Just like Myrtle's dad.
Quiet, Yuki!
Hey! Wait up!
Come on, Scrump.
[Nani] Lilo! I told you
you can't stay out after sunset.
- OK.
- OK?
[groans]
You did the right thing.
- Letting them go shows...
- [muffled] Aloha. I know.
[bubbling]
Add two tablespoons
genetic material and...
Hah! I've perfected
evil genius boom-boom liquid
for saliva of new experiment.
[laughs]
Pleakley! Come look!
Pleak... [echoes]
I'm forgetting.
No Pleakley, just Jumba.
Shh! Who you talking to?
Shh! Stop that.
[glass breaks]
[Elvis] I'd like
to sing a song
that's probably the saddest
song I've ever heard.
[* Elvis Presley:
I'm So Lonesome I Could Cry]
* Hear that
lonesome whippoorwill *
* He sounds
too blue to fly *
* The midnight train
* Is whining low
* I'm so lonesome
I could cry *
* Did you ever see
* A robin weep
* When leaves began to die?
* That means he's lost
* The will to live
* I'm so lonesome
I could cry *
* The silence
* Of a falling star
* Lights up
* A purple sky
* And as I wonder
* Where you are
* I'm so lonesome
I could cry *
* I could cry *
[applause]
Perhaps other side
is less depressing.
- Jumba!
- Dr. Hamsterviel!
I see I have found you
recollecting
misty musical
recollections.
Why are you no longer on
asteroid of inescapable prison?
No prison can contain me!
I... I mean, I am fully
reformed. Out on parole.
I heard you were
opening up the old shop.
So I am thinking...
[sniffs]
maybe we could work
together again.
[sighs]
Remember the old days?
You creating
experiments,
I funding them with my
shady business deals.
- No.
- Oh, come on!
Graduating together
from Evil Genius U?
- [scoffs]
- Our first business together?
[scoffs]
What about creating
our first experiment?
You remember Shrink?
25 years of partnership,
and you did nothing
but cheat Jumba,
embarrass Jumba,
steal from Jumba,
and finally fink on Jumba
to Galactic Federation.
For you, I wouldn't create
piece of dry toast!
Very well, then.
You leave me no choice
but to forcibly force you
to make a new experiment
by force!
By force! By force!
That was your cue!
Sorry.
Now, Jumba, I will
explain this only once
and oh, so patiently.
I want to order
a new version of 626.
Make him with extra
destructive capabilities
but easy on the fluffy.
And I don't like blue.
So make him
resplendent red
to match my cape,
and make him to go!
Jumba makes genius experiments,
not fast food.
Would take years
just to create design.
Well, what about
this one?
[clock ticking]
[mutters]
Is it done?
Is it finished?
Can't be rushing
evil genius.
[telephone rings]
Answer it.
But none of your
not-so-funny funny business.
Galaxy Defense
Industries,
where DNA stands
for "Do Not Ask."
- Jumba!
- Pleakley!
- Eh, is bad time.
- I'm sorry.
It's just that, well...
I just miss you so much!
I mean, heh, I just happen to be
in your quadrant, so I thought,
maybe I'll drop by.
- Enough! Hang up!
- No.
No? But don't you miss
your Aunt Pleakley?
- No!
- I'm wearing the wig.
No! Not coming by.
Never coming by!
Never wanting
seeing you again.
Yeah?
Well, me neither!
What I meant when I said
"I miss you so much
and can I visit?" was
"I don't miss you at all
and I never ever want to see
you ever again ever either!"
- [cries]
- Is truly evil!
Making Jumba pretend
to be mean to Pleakley.
Just finish my experiment.
Hmmph.
Am putting
finishing touches... now.
[* Elvis Presley: Aloha Oe]
Why are you playing
that annoyingly folksy
folk music?
Eh, to annoy experiment.
Is making him more evil, yes?
Heh-heh.
Oh, good idea.
More evil is good.
[song ends]
- [evil cackle]
- [gasps]
[snarls]
Oh! He's so beautiful
in his ugly nastiness.
Oh, perhaps I will mimic
the little Earth girl
and name you
with your very own name.
I shall call you...
Spike!
Heh-heh. She already
used that one.
Very well. Kicks.
- Used it.
- Slugger.
- Done.
- Cannonball?
He jumps in the water,
makes awesome waves.
- [groans]
- Why not just call it 627?
- You already made 627.
- I did?
Shut up! I am naming
the naming here.
I'll think of it.
I've got it!
I shall name you...
- Leroy!
- [laughter]
What? It is a genius name.
My Leroy will be defeated
by no thing or no one,
- not even...
- [explosion]
- [all] 626?
- Aloha, Gerbil Boy.
[laughs] This is
all so perfect.
A test for my
new creation.
- Hey! Is my creation.
- Whatever.
Leroy, destroy him!
[Leroy and Stitch growl]
[growling]
[snarls]
[growls]
- Ah-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha!
- What is so ha-ha funny?
- I don't have insurance.
- Get him, Leroy. Get him!
[growls]
[crash]
Aah! Ooh!
[muffled growls]
- Ha-ha-ha-ha-ha!
- [growls]
[cackling]
- [doorbell rings]
- Is this a bad time?
[muffled growls]
[Pleakley] I just
wanted to make up.
Next time send flowers.
Now that I have
proven Leroy
to be an invincible
fighting machine...
Leroy? [laughs]
I shall proceed
with the next phase
of my oh-so-clever plan,
creating an army
of Leroy clones!
[machine humming]
[cackling]
[bell counter ticking]
And now, to dispose of you
three meddling meddlers.
[grunting]
I have cleverly
programmed this vehicle
with destination
coordinates 12-21-9-7-9.
The black hole!
We can't fly
into a black hole!
I've gotta have the van
back to the college by 6:00.
Well, you're going
to be late by about...
...forever! [echoes]
[dinging]
- Captain on this... floor.
- [growls]
[snarls]
[speaks gibberish]
Captain setting
destination coordinates.
Zero parsec?
Captain Stitch, our orders
are to return the prisoner
to Asteroid K-37.
Why are we setting
a course for Turo?
- [snarls]
- [speaks gibberish]
[gasps]
You're not the captain!
He is now!
[cackles]
[snarls]
[line ringing]
[man] Hello,
this is Cobra Bubbles.
Cobra, I want
to call Stitch.
I'm unable to come to
the phone right now.
My current location:
classified.
Estimated return time:
Have a nice day.
[sighs]
[Nani] Does Scrump
want some breakfast?
It's her favorite,
cold pizza.
She's not hungry.
She's worried
about Stitch.
Aww, Stitch can
take care of himself.
He's indestructible,
remember?
I told Scrump that,
but she gets feelings
sometimes.
She thinks
something's wrong.
so I've been trying to
get in touch with Stitch.
Oh, 'cause
you're gonna need
one of those intergalactic
communicator thingies
if you want
to contact him.
I know! But Jumba and
Pleakley's ship is gone,
and Pleakley took
his space cell phone.
Who else?
Out of my way!
- I need peanut butter!
- For breakfast?
Hello?
Hmmph, Gantu schmantu.
Who needs him?
Nothing but a pain
in the patookie anyhow.
Didn't even like
my egg salad.
"More mayonnaise,
less dill weed."
- Uh, hello?
- Sorry, we're not open.
- Open?
- I'm turning this dump
into the best spaceship-shaped
sandwich shop on the island.
- Where's Gantu?
- He left.
But I'm naming
a sandwich after him,
the open-faced
double decker blubber butt.
I won't ask what's in it.
I brought you something.
Peanut butter and jelly?
[sniffs]
Gee, nobody's ever made me
a sandwich. Heh-heh.
Hey, what do you want?
I need to call Stitch.
Sorry. Videophone's busted,
like everything else
in this dump.
- Can you fix it?
- Why should I?
Gantu's the only one who'd call,
and I ain't answerin'.
From now on, I'm lookin' out
for old number 625.
625. I never gave you
a name, did I?
A name? For me?
Let's see.
How about Patty?
Short for patty melt.
Or... Monte?
Like a Monte Cristo?
Or Pita Pita Sandwich Eata.
[chuckles]
[sarcastic chuckle]
I don't think so.
I know! Reuben.
Huh. The classic corned beef
and sauerkraut on rye.
Reuben.
Ooh, I like that.
So, uh, does this give me
official "cousin" status?
You know, full ohana rights?
All that aloha stuff?
Depends. You have to give
aloha to get some back.
So, you're gonna help me
fix the videophone?
Sure. Why not?
It's Lilo, right?
[banging on metal]
- [clattering]
- [saw buzzing]
[air wrench whirring]
Uh, you sure
that's gonna work?
You'd be amazed. Pickle juice
is a great conductor.
[humming]
- You may thank me later.
- I'll thank you now.
Mahalo, Reuben.
Heh. No problem, Lilo.
[snarls]
- [Leroy laughs]
- [beeping]
Incoming call from...
E-arth, sir.
- [growls]
- [speaks gibberish]
It must be
the little Earth girl.
Ha-ha! My Leroy will easily
dupe her tiny little brain.
Hide!
Oooh!
Aloha, Stitch.
- Stitch?
- Uh...
- Say "eeh."
- Eeh.
- Are you OK?
- No, cuter.
Think "plush toy"!
Oh, yeah, it's me.
I'm Fluffy.
That's him,
all right.
Wait a minute.
My tiki necklace.
He's not wearing it.
That's not Stitch!
- Hang up. Hang up!
- OK! Bye-bye!
- Wait!
- [explosion]
Ah. I think that went
very well, don't you?
- Actually, sir, I think...
- I didn't ask what you think!
- Actually, you did. I...
- It was a rhetorical question!
Don't you know what
a rhetorical question is?
- Yes, sir! I believe it's...
- That was rhetorical too!
[groans] Aah!
[sighs]
My genius plan
is unfolding perfectly.
Prepare for hyperspace
to planet Turo,
where I and my army
of Leroys...
- [slurping]
- Quit picking your nose.
...shall take over the
stinky Galactic Alliance!
Sir, I must point out
a weak spot in your plan.
The little Earth girl
has a special talent
for turning evil experiments
from bad to good.
And she controls
a force of over 600
of Jumba's
genetic creations.
This makes her a credible
threat to your Leroy army.
Very well. Then the
little girl's experiments
must be captured and taken
to a large public arena,
where I shall
destroy them all!
[cackling]
This is clearly a job
for my most trusted henchman.
Thank you, sir. I won't
fail you this time.
You have already failed me
625 times.
No, this time I will send
my new trusted henchman,
- Leroy!
- [growls]
[static]
Reuben,
there's a fake Stitch
driving
the Big Red Battleship.
Do you know
what that means?
It's lunchtime?
No. Stitch is in trouble,
and so is the Galactic Armada
and planet Turo
and maybe the whole galaxy!
It ain't our problem.
Look, you're number 625.
The closest one
to Stitch.
If you wanted to, you could
have all of his powers.
You just have to stop
making sandwiches
and start making
something of yourself.
- [sighs]
- I'm gonna fix this ship,
fly to planet Turo
and warn the Grand Councilwoman.
Are you with me?
I said,
are you with me?
I'm with you, sister,
but first we gotta
put this servo unit
back in the main
drive shaft.
You are as strong
as Stitch.
Now, we reroute
the ignition conduit...
And you can walk
on the ceiling.
[Reuben] Whoa-ohh!
I'm a little
out of practice.
Flazookie
and cartridge clamp.
- Here?
- Smaishy scoop.
- Is this it?
- Pickle.
- It's got a bite out of it.
- Perfect!
[rapid beeping]
[crackling]
[gulps]
- [sizzling]
- [beeping]
And please, keep Weirdlo
and her weirdness
as far away from me
as possible.
[crackles]
[rumbling]
[cackling]
[screaming]
[screams]
Black hole
dead ahead!
[grunts]
Aah! Ha-ha!
[speaks gibberish]
[computer] New destination
coordinates denied.
[growls,
speaks gibberish]
[metal creaking]
Impact with black hole:
one minute.
[Pleakley]
What's gonna happen to us?
According to calculations,
black hole will transport us
to volcano planet,
where we will be quickly
yet painfully vaporized!
- Vapor?
- Unless....
- "Unless"?
- Unless we alter destination
by disrupting event horizon
just before entry.
Is requiring
small projectile
approximately 3-inch diameter
weighing 17.2 ounces.
But we don't have...
Wait a minute!
Lilo's rock!
- [beep]
- Ay! Is 22.3 ounces.
Gimme.
Impact with black hole:
30 seconds.
Go, little monster!
Go, go, go!
Save us, save us,
from the black hole!
Yay!
[all] Aaah!
[cackles]
[croaks]
[rapid footsteps]
[growls]
[sniffing]
[grunting]
[speaks gibberish]
[gasps, speaks gibberish]
- [chuckles]
- [Nani] Lilo, I'm home.
- [gibberish]
- You in bed already?
[snoring]
Guess that answers that.
[cackles]
[* Theme to Hawaii Five-O]
It crash-landed
in my backyard.
I bet it came
to take you-know-who
back to planet Weirdlo.
Yeah. Lilo wasn't
in class today.
- Maybe it ate her.
- Maybe it's gonna eat us all.
Well, I'm not gonna
wait around to get digested.
I'm telling Officer Kaihiko.
Come on, Gigi.
[snarls]
- Nice doggie.
- [barks]
- [screams]
- Ha-ha-ha-ha-ha!
[computer] Arrival
clearance code approved.
They're
letting us land.
Miss Grand Councilwoman!
Stitch is in trouble!
He's not
in control of...
- Hello.
- Hamsterviel?
- "Hamsterveal"?
- It is pronounced Hamsterviel.
Dr. Jacques von Hamsterviel,
king, top ruler
of the galaxy.
[cackles]
I'd get down
and gloat in your faces,
but I can't get out
this chair. Gantu!
Heh-heh!
Nice cape.
- We're too late.
- Indeed.
I have taken over
the Galactic Alliance
using my army of clones
named Leroy.
- Leroy?
- What's wrong with Leroy?
Nothing. I like it.
- See?
- [growls]
You can't run
the galaxy.
That's the Grand
Councilwoman's job.
She has been demoted.
- Dr. Hamsterviel's office.
- [creature jabbering]
I'm sorry.
He's in a meeting.
It'll never work.
Stitch will stop you.
Hmm, Stitch? Sti...
Oh, you mean
that weakling 626?
The one I sent tumbling
to his doom in a black hole?
Is that the Stitch to which
you are referring to?
- Black hole?
- Oh, don't worry.
He's got
plenty of company.
That idiot scientist
and one-eyed noodley thing.
Jumba and Pleakley?
- What is it?
- Incoming call, sir,
- from a Mr. Leroy.
- Put him through!
What is the progress?
[speaks gibberish]
- Talk normal!
- All experiments captured.
Excellent!
I'm on my way.
It has taken Leroy
a paltry few hours to succeed
while you took
three years to fail.
- What is wrong with you?
- Well, I have a bad knee.
No! That was
a rhetorical question.
You don't answer it!
Now will you get me down
from this chair.
Uh, was that
a rhetorical question?
No! That one was not...
Get me down! Get me down!
[Gantu] What should I do
with the girl and 625?
- Take them to the prison block.
- Yes, sir.
Then pick up your final paycheck
and return your ID.
- What?!
- You heard me. You are fired.
Now that I have Leroy,
you are no longer needed.
But what about
my future?
How am I supposed
to pay the bills?
Well, why not write
your memoirs?
Diary of an Incompetent
Fish-headed Minion:
The Idiot Years.
[sighs]
To assure
my galactic dominance,
I am now off to Earth
to eliminate those
pesky experiments! Ah!
My years of devotion
and hard work,
and this is
how I'm rewarded?
You are right.
That gerbil treats you
like a pile of blitznak.
See, his problem is
he's got no aloha spirit.
But that will come back and
bite him in the tail someday.
'Cause you know,
the aloha spirit you give
always comes back to you.
At least that's what
Lilo says.
Though it looks like her
spirit's kind of broken.
Nani says aloha means
"hello" and "goodbye,"
but for us, it mostly
seems to mean goodbye.
You know, turns out
I'm pretty strong.
I could maybe open this.
Whoa! Ha-ha!
I am strong!
You didn't open the cell.
I did.
I'm breaking you two
out of here.
- Aloha.
- Aloha! Whoa-ohh!
[speaks gibberish]
625, when did you learn
to climb ceilings?
The name is Reuben.
Once we're through
this airlock,
it's clear sailing
to the spaceport.
- [gibberish]
- Uh-oh.
Hey, this looks like
Pleakley's rock,
with a bite
out of it.
Stitch!
- Ah!
- How did you get here?
- No time explaining.
- Hurry! Get in!
- Whaah! Gantu?
- No time explaining.
We've got to get back to Earth
and save the cousins.
Well, how will
we all fit?
I could ride
in the backety-back.
[cackling]
I wonder what they got
in store for us.
I heard Hamsterviel is
taking over the galaxy
and he brought us all
here to get rid of us.
It's OK. We're just
having a nightmare.
You know,
I had a nightmare once.
I had to take a test on
spaghetti. I studied rigatoni.
I was late for class.
I was naked, fell off a cliff,
I tried to scream
and I couldn't...
[speaks gibberish]
[growls, barks]
[cackling]
Finally! It is an evil
dream come true.
All you ridiculous
625...
Actually, 624, 'cause
you subtract Stitch and...
Whatever!
Lock cannon on target!
[machine whirrs]
Not happening.
Aloha...
as in goodbye.
[Stitch] Cowabunga!
Aaaah!
[laughs]
Heh-heh!
Who knew carpool vans
had such sophisticated
weapon systems?
My cannon! And you!
How did you escape
my imprisoning?
Gantu turned
from bad to good.
Hey, where is Gantu?
Oh. Heh. He's still
in backety-back.
[alarm chirps]
- Thanks.
- What?!
He's on the
aloha team now.
You never did understand
the meaning of aloha, did you?
Well, I think it means...
Uh, that was
a rhetorical question.
[groans]
You aren't the only one
with a team, you know.
What you forget is
that I have my own army,
and I have them riding
in the frontedy-front.
[growling]
This is bad.
I'm calculating
our odds of victory
at, eh... zero.
[speaking gibberish]
[growling]
[rumbles]
Whoaaah!
[whistle blows]
- [screams]
- [growls]
- [grunts]
- [rayguns cock]
[gasps,
speaks gibberish]
- [Leroys laugh]
- [grunts]
[gibberish]
- Whoa!
- [crash]
Yeow!
[mutters]
[giggling]
[electricity crackles]
- Nice one, cousin.
- You can talk?
- [laughs]
- Look out!
- Boyd!
- There's too many of 'em!
[growls]
- [speaks gibberish]
- [laughs]
- Huh? Uh-oh.
Aah! Uhh!
Ow, my head.
Jumba, a little
evil genius help here.
[scoffs] If Jumba
was real evil genius,
he would have programmed
shutoff switch
into original Leroy.
Wait! Jumba is evil genius!
Hawaiian folksy folk music
is tied into synapse matrix.
If Leroy
is hearing Aloha Oe,
he is shutting down like
a car wash in a rainstorm.
- Will it shut 'em all down?
- Heh-heh. I don't know.
Ahh! Eeh!
Are you thinking
what I'm thinking?
Rock 'n' roll, baby!
[humming]
Jumba, sound!
Cranking up to evil 11.
Pleakley, lights.
Bright. Very bright!
Gantu! Uh...
...fireworks?
Gladly.
- [microphone feedback]
- [clears throat]
Aloha, cousins!
[playing rock guitar]
- [string snaps]
- [gibberish]
[* Aloha Oe]
* Aloha oe, aloha oe
* E ke onaona
noho i ka liko *
* One fond embrace,
a ho 'i a 'e au *
* Until we meet again
[laughs]
- * Aloha oe
[all] * E ke onaona
noho i ka lipo *
* One fond embrace,
a ho 'i a 'e au *
* Until we meet again
[saxophone solo]
It's working!
Aloha totally rocks!
[blubbering]
Not my original Leroy!
[growling]
[all] * Aloha oe, aloha oe
I am not beach ball light.
I am hamster light!
[all] * One fond embrace,
a ho 'i a 'e au *
* Until we meet again
- [gibberish]
- * Until we meet again
Sing it, cousin!
* Until we meet again *
Aloha!
- [song ends]
- [cheering]
[applause]
It is with great joy
that I return to
the Galactic Council,
and with even greater joy
that we once again honor
- our greatest heroes.
- [applause]
How can we ever repay you?
Especially Lilo
and Captain Stitch.
No captain,
just Stitch.
Am I to understand
that you wish to resign
your commission?
Yes, please.
Stitch has found one place
he truly belongs.
On Earth, with Lilo.
That being the case,
Mr. Gantu,
would you be interested
in resuming your position
as captain of
the Galactic Armada?
Would I?! Ahem.
I mean, yes,
Your Eminence.
- On one condition.
- Condition?
I'd like to request
experiment 625...
ahem, I mean, Reuben,
as my galley officer.
No kiddin'?
I've grown rather fond
of your egg salad.
Granted. And finally,
Jumba and Pleakley.
Jumba would like to return
to Earth as well.
You would?
But what about your lab?
Jumba is finally
understanding
ohana is more important.
Don't have to be
evil genius to see that.
Well, then,
I surely don't need
a non-teaching
teaching job.
- Your point being?
- Crazy head! I wanna go home!
That's all I want too.
To go home with my ohana.
- Eeh.
- [applause]
[Lilo]
Bigger smile, Stitch.
Little closer
to Nani, David.
- Myrtle?
- I still think you're weird.
But Gigi says she likes
being part of an ohana.
OK, everybody, this is it.
For the last picture
in my book,
a group shot.
The whole ohana!
Everybody, say
aloha!
[all] Aloha!
* Aloha
* Ohana *
[* Elvis Presley:
Jailhouse Rock]
* The warden threw a party
in the county jail *
* The prison band was there
and they began to wail *
* The band was jumping
and the joint began to swing *
* You should've heard those
knocked-out jailbirds sing *
* Let's rock
* Everybody, let's rock
* Everybody
in the whole cell block *
* Was dancin'
to the Jailhouse Rock *
* Spider Murphy played
the tenor saxophone *
* Little Joe was blowin'
on the slide trombone *
* The drummer boy from Illinois
went crash, boom, bang *
* The whole rhythm section
was the Purple Gang *
* Let's rock
* Everybody, let's rock
* Everybody
in the whole cell block *
* Was dancin'
to the Jailhouse Rock *
* Number forty-seven
said to number three *
* You're the cutest jailbird
I ever did see *
* I sure would be delighted
with your company *
* Come on and do
the Jailhouse Rock with me *
* Let's rock
* Everybody, let's rock
* Everybody
in the whole cell block *
* Was dancin'
to the Jailhouse Rock *
* Run, run, run
* Sad sack was sittin'
on a block of stone *
* Way over in the corner
weepin' all alone *
* The warden said Hey, buddy,
don't you be no square *
* If you can't find a partner
use a wooden chair *
* Let's rock
* Everybody, let's rock
* Everybody
in the whole cell block *
* Was dancin'
to the Jailhouse Rock *
* Shifty Henry said to Bugs
For Heaven's sake *
* No one's lookin', now's
our chance to make a break *
* Bugsy turned to Shifty
and he said, Nix nix *
* I wanna stick around
a while and get my kicks *
* Let's rock
* Everybody, let's rock
* Everybody
in the whole cell block *
* Was dancin'
to the Jailhouse Rock *
* Dancin'
* Dancin' to
the Jailhouse Rock *
* Dancin'
to the Jailhouse Rock... **
[* Everlife: Don't Be Cruel]
* Baby, don't be cruel
* You know I can be found
* Sitting home all alone
* If you can't come around
* At least please telephone
* Don't be cruel
* To a heart
that's true, yea *
* Yeah, baby,
if I made you mad *
* For something
I might have said *
* Please let's
forget the past *
* The future
looks bright ahead *
* Don't be cruel to
a heart that's true, yeah *
* I don't want
no other love *
* Baby, it's only you
* I'm thinking of
* No other love
I'm thinking of *
* Don't stop
thinking of me, no, no *
* Don't make me
feel bad this way *
* Come on over here
and love me *
* You know what
I want you to say *
* Don't be cruel
* To a heart that's true,
yeah, yeah *
* Why should we be apart?
* I really, really
love you, baby *
* Cross my heart
* Cross my heart, mmm
* I really, really
love you, baby *
- * Baby...
- * Baby
* Let's walk up
to the preacher *
* And let us say I do
* Then you'll know
you'll have me *
* And I'll know
that I'll have you *
* Don't be cruel
* Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
* Why should we be apart?
* I really, really
love you, baby *
* I don't want
no other love *
* Baby, it's only you
* I'm thinking of
* Don't be cruel
* Don't be cruel *