- Aloha.
- What?
Bye-bye.
Stitch, why are you doing this?
Please stop.
Stop it, Stitch. Don't...
No! Stitch!
Wake up! Wake up!
Wake up, Stitch. Wake up.
Stitch, wake up.
It's all right. Don't worry.
You were just having
another nightmare.
Seems like a bad one.
You know what this means, don't you?
Very interesting.
Why don't you tell me
what happened next?
Well...
- I see.
- Then...
And then...
That's it. No more.
It's my professional opinion
that you're afraid of turning bad again.
We need to test your goodness level.
For example, someone bad would
let this Elvis Blue Hawaii lamp,
circa 1971,
smash to pieces against that wall.
Or let my favorite book,
Plastic Surgeries Gone Wrong,
drop out this window to be lost forever.
Or let his family member
fall to her painful, crushing death.
No!
See?
Look at all the good things you did.
My prognosis?
Your goodness level is extra high.
Nothing to worry about.
Lilo! Stitch!
You're gonna be late for hula class.
Except that.
Stitch!
Hurry up, you two.
Hey, can you guys help me today?
It's family night.
- I want the house clean.
- Not me.
I have very important project
I've been working on.
No more crop circles!
All the other aliens get to make them.
- What about you?
- I have a full day of Earth research.
Watching talk shows
and reading magazines?
Yeah, it takes it out of ya.
Can we take the hovercraft? Please?
It's too dangerous.
Besides, someone may see you.
- Please?
All right,
you can take it if you can find it.
Yes!
I hid it so good this time, they're never...
Thanks, Nani.
I gotta find
a better hiding place for that thing.
There's no place I'd rather be
Lingering in the ocean blue
Sorry!
I'd surf till the sun sets
beyond the horizon
Flying by
on a Hawaiian rollercoaster ride
Hawaiian rollercoaster ride
There's no place I'd rather be
Girls, I have very exciting news.
This week is our May Day...
Sorry I'm late. But wait till you see this.
I got my 'uli'uli technique down.
Lilo...
Lilo?
Lilo, we're not doing that today.
We're not doing that today.
Kumu has an announcement.
In three days
is our town's May Day celebration.
And here's the best part.
There will be a hula competition.
Each of you will create an original hula.
The one that
best expresses the aloha spirit
will lead our halau
as the winning dance.
You, you, you!
- Are there any questions?
- Kumu, I have one.
Will people who are late to class
be allowed to participate?
Mertle, I think in the spirit of aloha,
we should be tolerant of others.
Well, there's no harm in asking.
I want you to use class time today
to begin working on your ideas.
The May Day celebration is big time.
The whole town will be there.
Maybe I'll get a contract.
We can do any idea we want.
Even make our own costumes.
- Cool!
- It'll be a lot of work.
My mom knows
how to make great costumes.
My mom can sew really good.
My mom knows a lot about hula.
She can help me with it.
- I guess Lilo's on her own.
- She doesn't have a mom.
- Don't say that.
- It's the truth.
- Not everyone has a mom.
- All right, don't bite my head off.
I don't know
what costume I'm gonna wear.
Lilo, may I speak with you?
This is a book of past winners.
Do you know who this is?
It's your mother.
- My mom?
- Aye.
She won the competition
when she was your age.
She was as beautiful as an orchid
and as graceful as a rolling wave.
Here. To inspire you.
That's my mom.
She won the competition
when she was my age.
Hey, Lilo.
Maybe your dog can take a picture
of me when I win the competition.
- How do you know you'll win?
- It's pretty well known
that I'm the best dancer
in the seven-year-old division.
I don't know. I think maybe I can win.
Hello?
You're a stinky dancer, and anything
you come up with will be stinky.
You'll never be like your mom. Never.
- Okay.
- That's it!
Smile.
As you can see,
there was a little disagreement...
Again.
Next time, flush the evidence.
Why don't you come inside, Kumu?
Excuse the mess.
We have a full house.
Make yourself at home, Kumu.
I just made some lemonade.
Hey!
Nani, we're out of lemonade.
Pleakley, I just made that.
Nani. You have to come to lab
and see my new invention.
I just mopped in here!
It will improve your primitive earthly life.
Speaking of improving your life,
I've just been reading this article
called Ten Days To A Slimmer You.
Full of wonderful suggestions.
Guys, I don't have time for this.
We have a guest.
A guest? Well, let's go meet him.
Let's not. Lilo's in enough trouble.
- Trouble?
- Well, all out of lemonade.
Anyway, I know my sister
is very sorry and didn't mean it.
- Very sorry.
- See?
- But I did mean it.
- Lilo?
Next time,
Mertle Edmonds is going down.
She's going way down.
No more pro wrestling for you.
Where is she? Where is she?
There's our precious angel, who must
be the victim of a misunderstanding.
- No, no...
- Where is she?
- Jumba. What are you doing?
- Don't worry. The cavalry has arrived.
- There she is.
- No, no, no, no.
Somebody give this kid gold star,
she's so good.
I don't believe we've met.
This is Uncle Jumba and
I'm Auntie Pleakley. Enchantée.
On second thought, Kumu,
we should talk outside.
It's not polite to interrupt your auntie.
- Knock, knock.
- David.
How's it, everybody?
You remember my Auntie Pleakley
and Uncle Jumba, right?
Say something.
- Nice hat.
- Why, thank you, David.
See? Uncle Jumba
said it made me look top-heavy.
Aunt Pleakley wanted the truth.
What we want and what we need
are entirely different things.
It's true what they say.
Men are from Mars,
and women are from Venus.
- Nani.
- Yeah?
You've been stressing,
so I got movie tickets.
Movie?
David, I would love to, really,
but I'm gonna have to rain check.
- That's okay. I understand.
- Great. Thanks for understanding.
I dare you to say that's not flattering,
even on him.
Okay, I'm sure that Kumu
isn't interested in this.
- Nice to be meeting you.
- Au revoir.
Bye-bye.
Boy. Good thing we were here.
I'm not talking to you.
Sorry about the relatives, Kumu.
Yeah, sorry. Thanks for coming.
See ya at the competition.
Lilo?
I know you want to be
in the competition,
but your behavior today
makes me think you're not ready.
No. I'm ready. It's just...
Mertle pushed my buttons.
I'll be good. I mean it.
I hope so. If there's any more trouble,
you won't be allowed in the competition.
I promise. There won't be any trouble.
I promise, promise.
I triple promise.
- Okay, then.
- Thank you, Kumu.
You don't have to worry.
I've seen the error of my ways.
I will be good from now on
and be the best hula dancer ever.
You'll see. I can do it.
There's no way I can do this.
Just because my mom was
a great hula dancer doesn't mean I am.
The only thing I know
I inherited from her is, well, Nani.
What if Mertle's right
and everything I do is gonna be stinky?
Maybe I'm just stinky...
Like cheese.
But my mom was beautiful
like an orchid and graceful like a wave.
I'll never be like her.
You think I can do it?
We do together.
Let's win this thing.
- Okey...
- Dokey.
Hula ideas, take one.
Mummies.
Amputation.
Vampire bats.
Recycling.
Gossip.
Skydive.
I wonder if Elvis had these problems.
Done.
Okay, everyone,
family fun night is ready to begin.
Everyone?
Anyone?
Guys, family fun night.
Everything's ready.
Let's... What's going on?
We're increasing the flow of blood
to our brains to make us think.
- We've only got one day and 23 hours...
- And 16 minutes.
...to come up with the winning idea,
so please leave us alone to think.
Please.
You'll figure it out, and if you ask me,
it's a perfect time to take a break.
- Pass.
- I said, if you ask me, it's...
- We kinda didn't ask you.
That's it, you two.
I've been cooking for hours
and finally picked up the house
just so we can have quality fun time
like Mom used to.
You're part of this family,
so you are gonna come downstairs
and have family fun.
Fun, fun, fun!
Is everyone having fun?
Yeah!
- Great.
- Loads of fun!
- I made sci-fi snacks.
- Yummy.
We have deep-fried Martian cockroach.
Delicious.
- I think I'm gonna throw up.
- I think someone did.
Nani, what are these?
Alien eyeball dumplings.
What kinda sick joke is this?
Don't be making her mad. Eat it.
It's good.
- Cockroach?
- I'm too upset to eat.
I'm hula-less.
I'm sure you'll come up with something.
Come on. Let's watch the movie.
...are dangerous.
They'll destroy everything in their path.
The authorities are asking all...
- It's a bit redundant, don't ya think?
- I'm trying to watch movie.
It's so beautiful.
Nani, I think you did a great job
with family night.
- I know what your problem is.
- What?
I'm sorry to break it to you,
but your relationship has fizzled.
We've been only going out
for three weeks.
A fizzle is a fizzle.
According to this,
comfort plus time equals boring.
I think she's just tired.
Tired, or tired of you?
I wanted to dance
at your wedding, but...
Fine.
What?
- Stitch!
Stitch?
No.
Jumba, Jumba, slow down!
Where ya going? Include me!
Something's wrong with 626.
- What is it?
- I don't know.
Or won't tell?
My good eye!
You don't trust me.
Fine. You won't tell me what's going on.
I won't tell you something.
What an interesting secret
I have that I won't tell Jumba.
Oh, my, it's a juicy one.
- Quiet, you.
- Okay, I don't have a secret.
But don't shut me out.
Let me in. Let me...
- What's that?
- Is sample of Stitch's fur.
Now we shall see.
No. No.
Those idiot police.
I hoped this day would never come.
What are you talking about?
What is wrong with Stitch?
During his creation,
Stitch was never fully charged.
There is it.
That's not so easy on the throat.
Can it be? Have I done it?
So cute, so fluffy, even.
Where did I go wrong?
What a relief.
Your name is 626. Isn't that nice?
I know, I know.
You want to get out and wreak havoc,
but your molecules need to be charged.
That's most important part.
Meanwhile, I've got a surprise for you.
Close your eyes.
No peeking. He cheats already.
If it's too big, I have it taken in.
- Open up! Intergalactic Police!
- Is nobody home.
Check is in mail. I'm in the tub.
You are under arrest
for illegal genetic experimentation.
You idiots, you will ruin everything.
- No.
- Yeah. Tell it to the council.
You two, get the evidence.
Stop.
His molecules aren't fully charged.
No, no! No!
Warning. Warning.
Electromagnetic bonding incomplete.
No, no,
there's no telling what will happen.
Let me go. No!
What will become
of my little monstrosity?
Now his circuits are going haywire.
That's why he was freaking out.
He can't control it.
If it continues, his circuits will
burn themselves out like supernova.
Can ya fix him?
I must,
or my little Stitch will shut down...
For good.
Stitch? Stitch?
Once there was a boy with big,
puffy hair who loved meat loaf a lot.
So he put the leftovers
in his pillowcase.
But that night, a buzzard flew in the
window and tried to eat the meat loaf.
Trashed the whole house.
And do you know who that boy was?
Elvis.
True story.
I think Stitch feel better.
Even Elvis slipped up sometimes.
But he never stopped trying,
and neither can we.
- Elvis!
At ease.
When Elvis was in the army,
he got things done.
Here's a map that shows
every place Elvis went to in Kauai.
Our mission, go to these places,
where the King
will give us the idea for our hula.
To the hovercraft.
Thanks to a certain sister of mine,
we'll have to walk.
Stop, look and listen, baby
That's my philosophy
It's called rubberneckin', baby
But that's all right with me
Stop, look and listen, baby
That's my philosophy
It's called rubberneckin', baby
But that's all right with me
Some people say I'm wasting time
They don't really know
I like what I see, I see what I like
It gives me such a glow
Yeah, yeah, yeah
First thing in the morning
Last thing at night
I look, stare everywhere
And I see everything in sight
Stop, look and listen, baby
That's my philosophy
It's called rubberneckin', baby
But that's all right with me
People say I'm wasting time
But I don't really care
I see what I like, I like what I see
It gives me such a glow
Yeah, yeah, yeah
Stop, look and listen, baby
That's my philosophy
It's called rubberneckin', baby
And that's all right with...
This is the exact bench
where Elvis sat in Blue Hawaii.
Yeah. That's him.
I can't believe it.
My butt is in the shadow
of the butt of Elvis Presley.
Yes.
Okay, Elvis.
We're ready to receive
a great idea for our hula.
That's it. I got it.
Elvis is trying to tell us
to do a hula about a chicken.
No, he's not.
There's plenty of other places
on the map that we can go to.
We better hurry.
Hey, drop it!
Gotcha.
Yes!
No.
We're sunk.
I know it's hard
to keep the faith sometimes,
but if you don't give up on Elvis,
Elvis won't give up on you.
That song.
It's about the Hawaiian goddess Hi'iaka.
Hey! That's right, Lilo.
That's a great story.
Friendship, jealousy,
death by molten lava!
Do you know what this means?
- Thank you, Elvis!
We got our hula.
Stupid supercomputer.
I know, Mom,
but Jumba and I have been very busy.
- My mom says hi.
- Yeah, hi...
He's waving.
I can't talk about it, Mom. It's top secret.
- I said I was sorry.
- That's it. That's it!
I have to go, Mom. Talk to you Sunday.
I finished plans for new fusion chamber
that will recharge Stitch.
Way to go.
But we don't have alien technology
to build it.
Way to burst a bubble.
We'll have to find primitive Earth
machinery and just hope it works.
No prob. I can get
all those parts from the house.
Stitch is having another episode.
They're getting worse.
Hurry. These parts
are crucial to saving Stitch's life.
Nothing can go wrong.
Target sighted.
Gotcha.
No, it's you. I mean, hi, Nani.
- What are you doing with the toaster?
- This?
Yeah, interesting question.
- What's going on?
- I was just about to...
We have to hurry to... Nani...
- To make toast.
- Toast?
Making toast. We're making toast.
Toast. Who doesn't enjoy
nice, crispy piece of toast?
Answer, nobody.
And there's so many different kinds.
Rye, sourdough, pumpernickel.
You can put marmalade on it.
Tasty toast.
You don't know what you're missing.
- Care to try some?
- That's okay. I've gotta go to work.
And, boys?
Don't play with the toaster.
Hi, David. Gotta run.
If you're hungry, we've got toast.
Lots of toast.
- Should I make more?
- Just get rid of him.
- But how?
- You're the Earth expert.
David, David, David.
Poor, sweet David.
Trusting, naive David.
- Okay, maybe I do need help.
- You're in good hands.
For 29.95,
you can have the kayak all day long.
But, of course...
Look at her.
- Doesn't even know you're here.
- Maybe because we're hiding.
I'm sorry. Is my relationship dying? No.
Okay, okay.
What you think I should do?
Well, it's obvious
she's taking you for granted.
But she won't if
she sees another woman interested.
What other woman?
- Yeah!
- Have fun.
Oh, my, you're so fascinating and tan.
I'm so clumsy.
You've gotta be kidding me.
- I don't think...
- It's working. She's coming over.
- Hey, Nani.
- No waving. Be cool.
Is that a deltoid or a rhomboid?
Okay.
Hey, David, I'm off at 5:00.
Wanna get some dinner?
- Great.
- He has plans.
- He does?
- With me. I'm the new girl on the island.
Let me get this straight.
You came here and interrupted me
to tell me you have
pretend plans with Pleakley?
I don't know what you're talking about.
My name is Inga.
I'm a foreign exchange student.
Are you jealous?
No.
Well, you blew it.
This is how the story goes, Stitch.
Once, there was a beautiful
goddess named Hi'iaka
and a handsome mortal
named Lohi'au.
They were as close
as two people could be.
But one day, Pele,
the volcano goddess,
grew jealous of their friendship.
So she took Lohi'au and threw him
into a volcano filled with molten lava.
Stitch!
My bad.
Hi'iaka discovered his body
in a cavern by a sea cliff,
and she stayed with him,
praying to the gods
to bring Lohi'au's spirit back.
And it worked.
Her love brought him back to life,
proving that love
is more powerful than death.
I will love you always
We are ready for rehearsal.
Okay, girls, this is your last rehearsal
before tomorrow's competition.
What if I forget the moves
and Mertle laughs at me?
And I get mad and pound her?
You gotta help me, Stitch. I need you.
We do together.
Our hula is about an ancient friendship
that proves love
is more powerful than death.
Oh, brother.
The great goddess Hi'iaka... That's me!
And the brave and handsome
mortal Lohi'au.
That's Stitch.
I said, the handsome mortal Lohi'au!
Handsome mortal!
Stink-o-rama.
Stitch, get out here.
What are you doing?
Cut it out.
That's not what we practiced.
Stitch!
No!
- Stop it!
- He's crazy!
Girls, girls, get behind me.
Lilo, get control of your dog.
Nice doggy...
Lilo! Lilo!
Lilo, you will not be allowed
to rehearse at this halau again.
Lilo, I... I...
Come on.
It couldn't have been that bad.
It was.
Mahalo. Have a good one.
- You're not listening to me.
- I'm listening. I have to work.
My hula career is falling to pieces,
and you're worried about stinking work?
Stitch needs you to be patient with him.
- He did it on purpose.
- You don't mean that.
You should have seen
the way he was acting.
- Aren't you being overdramatic?
- His goodness level is at rock bottom.
I love you so
I can't let you go
Don't tell me no
I need your love tonight
Gee, the way you kiss
Sweedee, too good to miss
I want more of this
I need your love tonight
I've been waiting just for tonight
To do some lovin' and hold you tight
Don't tell me, baby, you gotta go
I got the hi-fi high
and the lights down low
Hey, now, hear what I say
You better stay
Don't run away
I need your love tonight
I love you so
I can't let you go
Don't tell me no
I need your love tonight
Gee, the way you kiss
Sweedee, too good to miss
I want more of this
I need your love tonight
Yeah.
The great goddess Hi'iaka... That's me.
And the brave mortal Lohi'au...
That's also me.
Were best friends.
Lilo, look.
- Their friendship proved...
- I'm good now. No more badness.
Sorry.
- The great goddess Hi'iaka...
- Stitch good.
Stitch, just get outta here.
Fuzzball.
- No, you out.
- No, you.
- You. You!
Fine.
I will.
- No, Stitch will.
- I'm leaving first.
- I'm leaving first! I am.
- No! Stitch first!
Who took my hair...
Who took my hair dryer?
Get back here. You'll be sorry.
- Open this door, trog.
- Who's there?
- Stitch. Open the door.
- Okay.
What is up with you two?
- Nani, it's me.
- Neither of you move.
David, I'm glad you're here...
David?
Nani, you're not the only fish in the sea.
- Tell her you have...
- Because I have a lot of...
- Tell her your options.
- Options?
Options. Really?
Are you jealous?
- She's touching me.
- I'm not touching you.
- You're touching me!
- Not touching.
- Touching me!
- It's free air.
Would you cut it out?
This is crazy. You guys are family.
- Why are you fighting?
- Because he ruins everything.
- Not my fault.
- Then whose fault is it?
You're dead meat.
That is it!
Go to your room
and make up like loving friends!
- You're gross.
- Stupid head.
Keep walking.
Stitch sorry.
We said we were gonna be good.
I needed you, Stitch.
Stitch good again.
If you promise to be good,
I'll give you one more chance.
- But I want you to promise.
- Yeah.
You get the costumes,
and I'll get the record player.
Stitch good.
Good, good, good, good, good.
Stitch good...
We are ready.
- Stitch.
- Lilo.
- Everything's ruined.
- I... I sorry.
I don't know why I ever believed you.
Something wrong with Stitch.
I know what's wrong with you.
You're bad, and you'll always be bad.
Three. Two. One.
There it is, Pleakley.
The fusion chamber,
the only thing that can save Stitch.
- It's amazing.
- Just another work of genius.
Can I switch it on? Please, please?
No, no, no. No, no, no.
That is extremely delicate machine.
It takes superior mind.
Thanks to me, crisis is over.
Jumba? Jumba?
What happened?
That's it, Pleakley.
It's over.
I can't build a new fusion chamber.
Sure you can,
like you built the first one.
I didn't build first one.
I ordered it from catalogue.
A catalogue?
And now there is no hope
for my little creation.
Jumba has failed family.
So you didn't build
the first fusion chamber.
So what?
You still built Stitch, didn't ya?
Well, didn't ya?
Yes.
And you're still an evil genius. Admit it.
No, I... I don't like to brag.
Well, see, that's why
you're the only one who can do it.
Pleakley, my wrench!
Lilo?
Hey, Lilo.
I'm not doing the hula with him.
So don't try to make me.
Okay, okay.
He's ruining my chance of winning.
Lilo, baby, it's just a contest.
- No, it's not. Now get off my bed.
- Not until we talk about this.
You're no help! I wish Mom were here.
- I'm doing the best I can.
- Well, it's not good enough.
Don't you think I know that?
Hey. Remember how she would always
make up those funny constellations?
Like Swiss Cheese Man?
Where is the Stinky Bag of Garbage
again?
Near the Sour Milky Way.
Right, near the Old Lady
with the Chihuahua on her Head.
I have to win the contest,
just like Mom did.
If I win, she'll know I'm good,
and she'll be proud of me.
Baby.
You don't have to win anything
for Mom to be proud of you.
- How do you know?
- Because I know everything.
Okay, I don't know everything,
but I think Mom would be proud of you
just for being you.
You, too.
Thanks, Lilo.
Stitch good.
Stitch good now.
A little less conversation
a little more action, please
All this aggravation
ain't satisfactioning me
A little more bite and a little less bark
A little less fight and a little more spark
Close your mouth and open up
your heart and, baby, satisfy me
Satisfy me, baby
Do you think Lilo will show up?
After that rehearsal? She wouldn't dare.
- Come on, come on
Don't procrastinate, don't articulate
Girl, it's getting late
gettin' upset waitin' around
A little less conversation
a little more action, please
A little more bite and a little less bark
A little less fight and a little more spark
Close your mouth and open up
your heart and, baby, satisfy me
- Satisfy me
I just wanted to say
I am very proud of all your hard work.
If it were up to me,
you would all win first place.
He's just saying that
so the losers don't feel bad.
Hi, Nani.
Yeah.
Okay.
Welcome to
our annual May Day Festival,
where one of our little girls
will be chosen alaka'i.
First up is Aleka,
doing the dance of the pineapple.
That should do it.
What if it doesn't work?
It will.
Maika'i, Aleka.
Next up is Mertle Edmonds.
It's a gift certificate to my daddy's store.
Hit it.
Legend tells of a man named Karl
who dreamt of offering
authentic Hawaiian collectibles
at an affordable price.
Like this costume
in seven natural colors,
and these genuine faux pearls,
each a jewel of the Pacific.
The best things in life are marked down
for clearance this weekend at Karl's.
Mertle, what can I say?
Thank you.
It's in the bag.
If Jumba and Pleakley don't get here
soon, they're gonna miss Lilo.
No.
- What's happening?
- His circuits are about to blow.
We have to get him
in the fusion chamber now!
- Shouldn't we test it?
- There isn't time.
Next we have Lilo, who's doing her hula
about an ancient friendship.
This is it.
- You'll be great.
- Stitch?
I just want to say I...
I can't talk now. I have to go on.
I know, I...
- No, badness coming on.
- What?
- I... I have to...
- Are you okay?
Stitch!
No.
- Stitch?
- No, Lilo. Too dangerous.
- Lilo, it's your turn. Everybody's waiting.
My hula is about an ancient friendship
that proves love
is more powerful than death.
I will love you, I will love you
I'm sorry, Mom.
Stitch! Come back!
- Have you seen Stitch?
- We thought he was with you.
- Lilo, baby, what happened?
- Something's wrong with Stitch.
He's malfunctioning.
And if we don't find him soon...
Stitch!
Stitch?
- Stitch! Where are you?
- Stitch.
You there, brudda, brudda?
Stitch!
No!
Hey, we'll find him.
- We looked everywhere.
- He only has few minutes left.
- The ship.
- The fusion chamber.
Stitch!
Stitch.
We have to stop him.
- I think I should drive.
- Two eyes. My car. I'm driving.
At the rate he is going, he's soon
to be accelerating into stratosphere.
If only we had way to
communicate with him.
Stitch has taken off in the ship,
and we have no way to contact him.
- Poor Jumba. He's worked so hard.
- Give me that!
Yes, yes... Yes, Mother Pleakley.
He'll call you back.
Hello. Thanks for using
the Uninhabited Planet Index,
your guide to the galaxy's
most isolated and lonely locations.
If your selection is Planet Z-13,
engage hyper-drive.
Stitch! Can you hear me? I need you.
Please come back.
Stitch can never come back.
- He's lost control of ship.
- What?
What do we do now?
It was my best hiding place.
Get him into fusion chamber
before his energy runs out.
Is only chance!
No.
Stitch?
Stitch!
No, Lilo. Too dangerous.
You're not dangerous.
We have to get you
into Jumba's machine.
No worry. I've got you, Nani.
Stitch, you're gonna be okay now.
Please be okay.
Stitch sorry.
Stitch?
Hurry, before...
No!
Jumba. Jumba, it's not working.
No.
We're too late.
- No!
- Lilo, wait. There's nothing you can do.
He's gone.
Honey, come here.
No!
Stitch.
I'm so sorry.
I kept saying how I needed you.
But you needed me more.
You're my ohana, Stitch.
And I'll always love you.
I will love you
Stitch not bad.
Stitch fluffy.
Stitch!
But how is it possible?
It's not.
Stitch okay now?
No more nightmares.
Stitch!
You look fluffier than ever.
Come here, you. Group hug!
So Hi'iaka and Lohi'au were reunited
and are together to this day.
Nani!
I will love you
I will love you always
When it's hard to stand
You can take my hand
And I will love you
I will love you always
I will love you
Mom would be so proud of you.
I will love you always