Approach. Radio check.
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org
Looks good.
All silos operational.
Ready for phase 3 deployment.
Trident I, II and III
burners are go.
Ready for deployment.
Verifying command...
Verifying Naval Command...
SSBN Ohio fleet are go.
Gold crew reporting
operationally
configured Trident II
SLBM array.
Verifying flight path
analysis...
Flight path analysis complete.
The comet's trajectory is...
Go for deployment?
We are go for deployment.
Awaiting command.
STRATCOM on standby, sir,
awaiting command.
This is the president.
Is everyone alright?
- Yes sir.
- Mr. President,
we've spoken
to Presidents Lee Zhang,
Todorov, and Rencilier.
Prime Minister Bennett has
also agreed to the initiative.
- The I.A.E.
- A confirms compliance.
This is all we can do.
This is a high price
to pay for disarmament.
Are you sure this will work?
We've run countless simulations.
At this point,
it's just a matter
of probabilities...
The force of these
nuclear warheads
should be enough to ensure
sufficient disintegration,
and the explosion
should redirect
any remaining debris.
What happens if it doesn't work?
We've already put
the local disaster
response teams on alert.
Let's do it.
Initiate launch sequence.
Launch sequence initiated.
Mr. President.
There's a problem.
Did we hit?
Yes sir.
But the blast created debris,
meteorites, sir,
and all of them are heading
towards Earth.
This was so much fun.
Thank you so much for coming.
Of course. Please tell us about
the couples' luncheon tomorrow.
I will do that Heidi.
I promise I'll call you.
And e-mail me
the prayer chain list!
I will e-mail you.
Goodnight ladies.
- Goodnight
- I'll see you next week!
Don't forget, Second Timothy!
Okay...
Mom, I need help.
It's a very nice solar
system, honey.
You did a great job.
That supposed to be...
Mercury? Mmm...
What do you think your dad's
doing right now?
Come on!
- Dad?
- Yeah?
I need help with my
Solar System project.
Not right now, honey.
David...
Kate, I'd like to get
this done before they start
the water rationing.
Maybe I should do it.
Unless you got over
your vertigo.
Very funny. I got it. Thank you.
David, come on.
Ali, honey! Alison!
Listen, as soon as I'm
finished here, I'll come
inside and I'll work with you
on your Solar project. Ok?
I promise.
Al, honey... Pinky swear?
Dad, I'm twelve.
Come on!
Good.
Okay?
This will be better
if I did this in daylight
where I have a better chance
of not getting hurt.
That's right.
Did you feel that?
It's an earthquake
I saw this big flash
over by the Valley of Fire.
It's just heat lightning
Alison. Go to bed.
Can I go online?
It's two o'clock in the
morning Alison! Go to sleep.
It's fine honey.
We should be cultivating
her interests.
She's taking after you,
you know.
Ah, let's hope not.
It's probably Mauricio.
Ah. I Bet we got
a turbidity flag 'cause
of the earthquake... Hello?
David...
I need you to come in...
Mark?
Come now.
Mark? Mark, what's wrong?
I gotta go in to work.
Why did you bother
switching to days
when you're on call
seven nights a week?
It's my job, Kate.
What do you want me to do?
Come on, David.
What do you want, honey?
I need to show you something.
Alison, go to bed.
- Dad?
- Alison.
Are you gonna come
to church tomorrow?
You promised
you'd come this Sunday.
Fine.
Good night.
Mark!!
Mark? Where are you?
What?!? Do you need water?
Did you call this in?
No, no, no.
Take it easy, Mark.
He's hot and diaphoretic.
Where did you find him?
I just found him
here on the floor.
Take it easy...
His pupils are dilated.
What did he take?
Water...
It's the water!
David! I've been
trying to call you!
Kate! Kate, are you okay?
- Yes, but...
- Listen... don't drink
the water, there's
something wrong with it.
- What?
- Yeah.
- David why?
- No matter what,
don't drink anything out
of the tap water.
I'll be home as soon as I can.
Alison, did you drink that?
- Kate.
- Alison, honey are you okay?
Kate! Kate, is there
something wrong with Alison?
There's something wrong
with the water.
The organic content readings
are higher than I've ever seen
before and I don't know why.
His blood pressure
is 225 palpitations.
Give me 5 mg of prednisone.
I can't get a line on him.
Give me the auto injector.
Here, give it on your side.
He stopped breathing.
Check the rig.
Here we go.
You know what.
That's it. Let's go.
This is the end.
I'm sorry Mark.
Come on!
I'm gonna take my own truck!!
Come on Sam, pick up. Come on!
David.
Sam! Sam, Are you okay?
Have you been hit yet?
No. They haven't hit Vegas.
But we're getting the reports
here in the lab... you alright?
Yeah, listen, I'm fine.
But I think they're affecting
the water. It killed Mark.
Yeah, he's not the first...
Any idea what it is?
I think it's a radioactive
thujone derivative.
But I'd like your systems
report so that I could verify.
Okay. Sure.
You know what the source is?
At this rate, by tomorrow
morning all the groundwater
from here to Los Angeles
will be compromised.
There's some
contaminated aquifers.
But the primary source
is Lake Mead.
This thing is deadly
up to 10 days after ingestion.
Ten days...
Survival depends on a person's
ability to make antibodies...
We've started working
on an antidote...
Depending on exposure level,
it could be a lot
quicker than that.
They're bringing people...
Sam! Sam!
Sam, can you hear me?
This area is under quarantine
by the United States government.
Hey! Hey!
Sir. I need you
to step back, sir!
I live right here.
This is my house! I need to...
I understand, sir. I understand.
But this is a quarantined area.
Come with me, please.
- Sir...
- Alright! Alright!
- Taking you into quarantine.
- Hold on.
Clearing disaster area.
- No!
- Mommy!
That's my wife!
That's my daughter!
DAVID!!!
Kate! Alison!
Kate! Kate!
Wait! Alison. No!
Alison! Please, just...
- Sir, you need...
They're gone sir.
Alison! Kate!
You've reached the
voice mail of Sam Tefton,
please leave a message.
Hey, Sam, it's David
again. Listen...
I'm on my way
to Vegas right now.
My family has been taken in the
quarantine and I just wanted
to see if you knew
anything about it...
I think my daughter is sick.
Call me back as soon
as you can. My phone is dying.
Thanks.
Yeah, traffic is all backed up,
all the way to the 210.
Yeah, and they shit down 15.
destroyed at the pass
near Wheaton Springs...
Confirmed sightings at Lowell,
Braeside, Kingsburg
and Richard...
comet... terminal flight path...
Be advised...
all residents of the area
should proceed calmly...
thesouth end of Las Vegas.
Hello?
Hey!
Wait! It's okay.
No. No. It's okay.
You're okay. You'll be okay.
Listen to me! Listen to me!
I have to give you this
shot or you're going to die!
Okay?
Ahh!
Great.
Come on!
It's okay, you're alright.
You're alright.
David, it's Sam...
I'm getting
closer to the formula...
quarantine here at
the federal complex...
This is the
emergency broadcast system.
The Department
of Homeland Security has
declared a state of emergency
for Clark County, Nevada.
We are expecting a large
scale meteor shower
event this evening in the
greater Clark County area.
Designated shelters at...
Valley Anderson, Sierra Vista...
Enterprise... the McCarran
International... Las Vegas
convention center...
and the medical center.
All residents are to avoid
drinking tap water
until further notice.
The CDC has identified an
extremely harmful pathogen in
ground water sources
near Lake Mead...
Ahh!
It's okay. Stop!
What are you doing? Stop!
Hey, listen, I'm not going
to hurt you. It's okay.
It's okay. I'm not going
to hurt you. Alright?
I'm just gonna borrow your Jeep,
to get us to Vegas,
and then I'll give it back,
okay? Okay?!
- Pull over!
- What?!
Pull over now!
Fine.
Are you okay?
Oh yeah. You're okay,
you're okay.
- Yeah. Yeah.
- Come on!
- You're okay?
- Yeah.
Hi, I'm Lynn.
- I'm David.
- Nice to meet you.
Do you have a toothbrush?
What?
Or some shampoo?
No.
Oh, yeah. Come on. Let's go
Is that for me? Thanks!
So... we're really
going to Vegas?
- Yep.
- Fantastic...
whoa. what was in
that injection thing?!
Midazolam.
Right.
So you're not into Vegas?
Got it.
I have an ex-boyfriend... recent.
Ex-job, ex-apartment,
ex-dog, ex-sister...
Nothing like the end
of the world
to put things in perspective.
So... where exactly
are we going in Vegas?
We're gonna see my friend
about the water contamination.
Maybe I could get
some answers...
Water contamination?
Yeah, that's what made you sick.
I saw a soda next to you
at the gas station.
I haven't felt like this since
I got motion sickness
on the Matterhorn
at Disneyland...
So... anyway.
I puked all over my shirt,
and Mickey wouldn't hug me...
Which is really
the story of my life,
when I think about it.
You really puked
on the Matterhorn?
Oh yeah!
Ahhh!
The engine's dead.
Come one, get out!
Ah!
Come on!
Come on.
David, wake up!
Where did you get the water?
I don't know.
Just a sip. It's good
We have a directive
from DHS control.
If we tell the staff,
this gets away from us.
If you want staff to stay staff
you'll tell them
what's going on.
I'm not going to let
bureaucracy step on my team.
We'll lose operational
control...
You call this control?
Since they put us under
the DHS, we put
5,000 non-contagious people into
quarantine. In the middle of
the biggest catastrophe since
the ice age, the Secretary of
the DHS wants to detain the sick
instead of fight the disease.
We both know the protocol.
If a waterborne pathogen
gets in the water...
It's high school biology.
These guidelines
are just a study in politics
trumping science.
The meteorites fell and
the Secretary blinked. She ran
it by the book to cover herself.
So we're gonna throw the book
away and save these people.
As Deputy Director
I have to report you
to the Secretary of the DHS.
She'll have
to remove me by force.
Everybody give me your
attention please! Listen up!
By now you probably have
heard the rumors...
Now I'd like to
give you the facts.
Several days ago NASA
revised its estimates
on the trajectory
of a long period comet.
And they discovered it was on
a collision course with earth.
All of the nuclear armed
countries launched
their nuclear warheads and ICBMs
but it backfired.
Hundreds of meteorites have
collided with the planet
and thousands more
are on their way.
As you already know most
of central Las Vegas
has been destroyed... the strip,
downtown, McCarran Airport.
So we need to move fast.
The CDC building hasn't been
hit. Is that right, Sharon?
Yes, that's correct.
The building is intact, but the
power's out and the water's
down... there's no way they can
deal with our quarantine.
Deaths?
Several. All from the water.
Do we know anything
about the diseases?
About the fatalities?
- Mr. Pitts?
- Go ahead, Candace.
Their toxicology team
is telling me that
if a significant amount
is ingested...
About four ounces... then
the pathogen is fatal.
Depending on the amount,
it could be hours to days...
seizures followed by death.
We need to get those people
rushed into treatment.
Vegas can't handle it,
so we got to get them
some place that can.
We're going to do it
right this time. I don't
care how many meteors come...
We can't just throw
these people away.
Our nearest facility is
in Los Angeles, so let's send
these people there ASAP.
Donny, can you
do a transpo evac?
We got to get them
outta there quick.
Can we get security?
I'm getting reports of
heavy looting by armed gangs...
Someone get on that.
Candance, do we have
anything from the labs?
Cures, vaccines?
Get with them
at the L.A. Metro DHS.
And see if they got
rooms to handle these
people at their facility.
Harvey, we keep
getting calls from the DHS.
They're calling every line,
even the secure connection...
I think it's urgent.
Don't pick up.
They'll threaten you
like they threatened me.
I want to get these people
out of Vegas
before they can stop us.
Are you okay?
It's strangely liberating.
We don't know for sure.
The body could build up
its own immunity...
I'm a pessimist.
Maybe my friend Sam
can help you.
He's working on an antidote.
Here.
Yeah. Just a sec.
Come on. Let's go.
Kate! Alison!
David, what are we doing?
Alison!?
David, who are we looking for?
My wife, my daughter
were taken here
after the meteors fell...
I have got to find my friend.
Yeah, it's the place.
What is this place?
It's the Vegas federal complex.
I think we're
in the CDC building.
One of my colleagues works here.
He knew about the quarantine
before they took my family.
So I think he should know
where I can find them.
Oh, this must be
the departments, okay...
Customs and Border Protection...
FEMA...
- Federal Water Quality Agency.
- 194.
It's right there.
He's sick and you can fix him!!!
Now give it to me!!
It's not finished...
NO! I need it NOW!!!
Use this if you can.
Get up! GET UP!!
- Hey!
- DON'T MOVE!
It's okay. I can help.
I've got information here
that she needs.
I just need to see the formula.
Okay? Where is it?
It's on the counter.
- Okay.
- Okay. Cool.
STAY THERE!
Yeah, I'm working on it.
I'll be right down.
I need some saline.
Aah, It's above
the sink. It's labeled.
Quick!
- Quick!
- Alright!
DAVID!
There are more of them.
They're coming back.
Here. 20 mililiters.
Are you sure this
is going to work?
Yeah.
Okay. This should
neutralize the contaminants.
Can you make more of this?
Yes, I'm gonna go
to my other lab,
I should be safe there.
Here you go.
What happened to all the
people that were quarantined?
Uh, Everyone here
at the federal office
went to L.A.
I'm going to L.A.
I'm not staying here.
Wait. The antidote
hasn't been tested.
If we had the equation
wrong... it could be fatal.
Come on.
Oh, sh...
It's locked.
Right there... We need to jump.
We have to jump...
I can't! This is too...
this is too high.
David! On 3.
1... 2...
No! No. I can't!
David!
No, I'm afraid of heights.
Then we have to go back.
Hey!
Back here. Come on.
Alright, come on.
David!
Come on, we got to keep moving.
We'll get you some water.
You alright?
What are you doing?
This is the antidote Sam
was working on.
No. I'm gonna wait.
Come on! You're getting sicker!
You got to take it now!
What, so you can test it?
Make sure it works
for your daughter?
No. Come on...
David, it's okay.
Look. You hold on to it.
Okay Lynn?
In case you change your mind.
I'm gonna go look for some
water. Try to figure out
a way to get back to L.A.
Lynn!
Here...
Did You hear that?
You said you heard something?
Wait a sec... what's this?
She's still alive.
Cops.
Cops, cops, cops, cops.
FBI! Drop your guns! Get down.
Get out! Drop your weapons now!
FBI! Drop your weapons!
DROP YOUR WEAPONS! FREEZE!
Hey! Hey! I'm unarmed!
- Hey! Hey!
- I'm unarmed!
- Stop right there!
- I'm unarmed! Don't shoot!
Turn around! Turn around!
Put your hands behind your head!
Lock your fingers!
Now, on your knees!
Down! Down! Now!
Okay! Wait!
Stop right there!
Stop right there! Down on
the ground! On the ground!
So... what is this?
I'm just trying to get to
L.A. I'm looking for my family.
They were detained.
Taken in the quarantine.
Please, sir.
I think my daughter is sick.
And I know where
there's clean water.
Take 142. It's safer.
When the meteorites
started to fall
Homeland Security had
no clue what to do.
I mean people were sick, so what
happens? Some bureaucrat yells
quarantine, and the next thing
you know
northwest Clark County
gets cleaned out.
Why L.A.?
Well, 'cause after
Vegas got hit,
they didn't have
the admin support.
They had to move the operation
over to Los Angeles.
All the quarantined
people are packed in
at the Metro Detention Center
at downtown L.A.
But wasn't L.A.
affected by the meteorites?
I heard something on the
radio about a comet...
- No.
- Are you sure? Cuz I heard...
No!
Alright, so you want
to tell me about your...
your goodie bag there?
Midazolam injectors?
Yeah, I took a peek.
That's what I do.
Southbound 4529
we are in pursuit of a...
Repeat 10-0
on the Southbound I-15.
Relax. Enjoy the sunshine.
10-0 southbound, do you copy?
Yeah. 10-1 on that.
10-9. I repeat, 10-9.
Southbound I-15.
I repeat, 10-0 on Southbound...
request directive from
Incident Command...
This is Special
Agent Jake Nielson.
Would one of you Clark County
thick-necks
tell me what the hell
is going on?
Looks like someone told them
about our water!
No. No. Run 'em down!
Run 'em down!
Tell me about the meteors.
LEMME OUTTA HERE!
Never!
TELL ME!
A comet is going
to wipe out the city
of Los Angeles in three days.
My son is there.
Just leave the car
and the water. Get out!
I didn't want Munez to know.
There's only one gun.
This is a de facto arrest.
I need to hear my rights...
Harvey Pitts is going to
be reassigned to the field.
I am now the Director of the
Center for Disease Containment.
You are not allowed to
communicate with anyone
about the activities
at the CDC or the DHS.
Is that clear?
I want to retroactively
terminate all operations
that Pitts initiated in
the last twelve hours.
The Secretary of the DHS
has told me,
and NASA has confirmed, that
a comet is going to destroy
the city of Los Angeles
in three days.
You need to be prepared
to coordinate a response
with the other offices
around the country.
The slower the information leak,
the easier it is
to coordinate a response.
David... we have to keep moving.
How much water do we have left?
Less than half a bottle
You'd better drink it.
No. You first.
I haven't seen you drink
since yesterday morning.
My wife would call
this a Kingdom moment.
What's that?
I don't even know.
I think your wife
is probably right.
I hear the highway over here.
Come on, let's keep going.
We can't leave them all
at the Metro Detention Center!
The faster you process,
the faster they leave!
We can't process 5,000 people
before that comet strikes!
Hello?
Candace, it's me, Harvey Pitts.
They have me
coordinating California.
From what they're saying,
it could be a death sentence.
Harvey, Peter's really
hurting our operation.
He's cutting into everything...
I have a plan for
saving those people. I have
autonomy with our equipment and
personnel here, but it'll take
some logistics from your end.
And you have to hide it
from Peter.
Okay.
You are sentencing them
all to death.
I don't have
jurisdiction over that facility!
If I could wave a magic wand,
I would.
Do not jump the barricade.
Hey!
Where's the Metro
Detention Center...
I think it's destroyed.
How do I get there?
Right there!
David! We should find
the rendezvous point...
Come on!
We should at
least figure out where it is...
Last evacuation
from rendezvous point...
Excuse me. Detention
Center is right here?
Yes.
You sure this is it?
This is it.
This is where they went.
Why don't you go on...
why don't you go on
and find the rendezvous point.
NO!
Go on!
You're so selfish.
Selfish? I have thought
about nothing but my
wife and daughter
for days now...
I have been risking
my life for them...
And I'm risking my life for you!
Lynn!
I'm sorry. Okay?
Hey! What are you doing?
You want to get shot?!
You don't know about the curfew?
No ma'am.
Lord have mercy...
She's sick.
Come! Come! Help me. Help me.
Come.
Come on. Drink some.
Come on!
You're all coming with me.
Come on! Let's go!
Just around the corner.
This is the only
rendezvous point in the area.
And we're being evacuated
in the morning.
I'm looking for my wife
and my twelve-year-old
daughter. They're from Nevada.
They're probably at one
of the refugee camps
east of the city.
Then that's where
I'm going to go.
They'll shoot you if they
find you on the street.
Nobody's supposed to
be out past curfew.
I don't care.
You're not going to be any good
to your family if you're dead.
You're staying with us tonight.
Evacuation is first thing
in the morning.
David!
Thirsty?
- Yeah. Thank you.
- Mm hmm
Ah.
- Can't sleep?
- No.
Miss your family?
Yeah.
It seems pretty natural to me.
Never used to be to me...
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
What about you?
Where's your family?
How come you're not with them?
I am. This is my family.
There's a proverb that says
"Do not go to your brother's
house when disaster
"strikes you...
Better a neighbor nearby
than a brother far away."
You know, when I was younger,
I used to think
there was nothing
more important in life
than to take care
of me and mine.
You know, look out for myself.
Yeah.
'Cause no one else was...
But then I found somebody.
Shh... David! Wake up!
OW!
Okay. Hurry, hurry.
They're not going to wait.
Sorry.
I haven't relapsed yet.
Yeah. You look better.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
Well, they're going to
evacuate soon.
What if they are not
at the camp?
David. We have to go...
What if they're waiting for you?
We'll be ready.
Somebody help her please!
Somebody help her, please!
Please! Somebody help her!
Please! Please!
She's sick...
She started having another
attack... I...
How long she's like this?
I don't know! Maybe an hour.
It's never been this bad.
Okay, we need to lay her flat.
I can give her a shot
to stop the seizures.
Please... please... please...
It's not working
I don't want to give
her more of this
because it could stop her heart.
Shh... shh...
David.
Please help me through this.
You praying, Pastor?
Always!
I have a cure here, but it
hasn't been tested...
There's a good chance
that this could...
That this could kill her.
- What's her name?
- Madeline.
Madeline. Madeline!
Sit up, Madeline.
Hold this.
You gotta drink this.
It's gonna save your life.
Open your mouth, honey, come on.
Gotta force it in.
Open your mouth.
Open up.
Good, good girl. Good girl.
Good girl. Slowly.
Honey. Oh God, please.
Oh she's... Okay baby, come on.
Come on baby girl. Come on.
Get her to move.
Baby, come on. Come on, come on.
Oh!
Thank you. Thank you. Thank you.
Oh, thank you.
Thank you, thank you so much.
Ma'am, you the rendezvous
point coordinator?
Yes.
There are two vans ready.
We have to hurry.
Oh, okay.
Do you have children?
Yeah. A daughter.
A few years older than her.
Where is she now?
She's with my wife.
They were both taken
into quarantine
about three days ago...
So were we. They took
us to Singing Springs.
We came back on foot,
but a lot of people couldn't.
We didn't want to risk it.
There's another quarantine?
I only knew about
the one at the Metro
but where is this one?
The mountains northeast of L.A.
Ma'am. We got to go.
Yeah, it's far, but you might
be able to make it on foot.
There's a ravine
three miles in...
- Thank you.
Hurry... Hurry... Hurry.
Mommy!
We have two more!
- Mommy!
- Go with your daughter.
One more.
Who else? Let's go!
We're staying.
Now you go with them.
Go with them!
Jesus help us!
- Come with us.
- No, I gotta help everybody.
We got to get them out!
Evac has been confirmed.
Will take place in 0200 hours.
David...
What? Come on.
Come on.
We don't have much time.
I think that's the ravine,
right up there.
Just keep moving.
Just a little bit more.
Sit down.
Okay, this is the last one.
You finish it.
Come on. We got to climb.
Let's go.
- I can't.
- Yes you can. Come on!
David... I can't.
Okay. You stay here.
And I'm going to try
and find an easier way.
Any luck?
No.
- Hey?
- Yeah?
Why didn't you leave me
at the gas station?
Why am I still here with you?
No. I can't
I'm going to go look
for another way.
Lynn? Lynn!
Lynn!! Lynn!!
Lynn! Lynn!
Come on, you have
to take the antidote now.
Come on, Lynn!
- No. David. No. No.
Save it for your daughter...
Lynn, come on!
No. Lynn! Lynn! Please!
Please help me.
Yes, there are still
some sick among the group.
Yes. Medevac
as well as transport.
Yeah... yeah...
Can you hold?
Effective as of now, we
are no longer devoting resources
to quarantine detainees.
We still have a group
at Singing Springs.
You're telling us
to leave them stranded?
They've been waiting for an
evac team like everyone else.
What about their support staff?
They're government employees...
People are going to die
no matter what we do.
We'll withdraw our guys
when we can. You know,
all the cities around the
world are going to be hit
in four hours. We don't have
time to save people in L.A.
We have to devote resources
where they're effective.
Look... you either do it now
or you wait for the reprimand.
Okay. Thank you.
Harvey, we're clear on my end.
Cross your fingers, Candace.
We've got one chopper left,
and I'm not sure
how the blast will affect it...
Hey!
Hey! Where is the detention
center?
- It's gone.
- It's gone...
Everything is destroyed.
There are only a few of us left.
We were waiting for the
evacuation but it never came.
Did you bring a helicopter?
No. I'm looking for
a woman and a little girl.
There are still two more
people up the trail.
Up here?
Hey!
David!
Kate!
I heard... I heard your voice.
Oh.
Kate, I'm sorry. I'm sor...
Shh...
Alison, she's...
Alison! Alison!
Prop her up.
I have something
I need you to take, okay?
I need you to drink this.
- Shh...
It's going to make you better.
Have some.
Alison!
Just tell me what we can do.
We've been waiting on
a directive throughout
this crisis, and
it's never come!
There's nothing we can do!
Yes there is...
I love you.
I love you too.
Hey!
We got 'em!
And we're getting
them outta there!
Please rate this subtitle at www.osdb.link/9j6xb
Help other users to choose the best subtitles