.
- Illumination!
[giggles]
[singing gibberish
to "Silent Night"]
- Ah, no, no!
[gibberish]
[singing gibberish
to "Jingle Bells"]
♪ ♪
♪ Hey! ♪
[continue singing gibberish
to "Jingle Bells"]
♪ ♪
[laughing]
- Welcome to the
"Minions Holiday Special."
- Hello!
- Starring the Minions...
- Ah, oh!
- In four mind-blowing
Mini-Movies.
- What?
- Get ready for action...
- Whoo-hoo!
- Yee-haw!
- High-fives,
poor judgement...
- Ahh!
- Romance...
- Hello, Papa-gara.
- And special guest stars...
- Puppy! Ohh!
- As the Minions
take over the holidays.
So go ahead,
grab a snack...
- Bleh!
Ah, ahh!
- And enjoy a not-so-silent
night with the Minions...
- Luca!
- Starting with our first
"Minions" Mini-Movie.
[cheering]
[soft music]
♪ ♪
- Oh!
Oh, whoa!
Whoa, no!
♪ ♪
all: [excited gibberish]
[giggling]
- Oh.
[chattering]
- Oh, look!
- [gibberish]
- Whew, oh.
[gibberish]
[upbeat music]
♪ ♪
- [giggling]
Oh!
["Deck the Halls" melody]
- Oh, there you go!
- Oh!
- Wow!
- Whoo-hoo!
♪ ♪
- [excited gibberish]
- Okay, everybody!
Time to start.
- [excited gibberish]
♪ ♪
- Come a little closer.
- [chuckling] Whoa.
- Wah!
- Who's ready
for elf training?
all: Me!
Pick me!
- Hit it, boys!
- Whoo-hoo!
[ringing melody]
- ♪ So stomp your feet
and give a twerk ♪
♪ When the music plays,
we can get to work ♪
Whoo-hoo!
♪ We work all night,
we work all day ♪
♪ We put the toys
in Santa's sleigh ♪
Ha, ha, ha!
[train whistle]
- Whoa!
- [laughing]
♪ ♪
- [frustrated gibberish]
- [straining]
Whoa!
- That's not--
[fart sound]
Oh--oh!
- Hey, tutti bueno, eh?
[giggling]
- Ugh, all right.
Let's train you
for something else.
- Ah, ah.
Huh?
Oh!
- [laughing]
- Eh, yeah.
[frightened gibberish]
- Wait, wait.
Wait, wait.
♪ ♪
Ahh...
all: [gasping]
- I know the perfect job
for you guys.
- [straining]
Ugh!
- [sighs]
Oh?
Ohhh.
Oh, budjs?
- [crying]
- Oh.
Come in!
- Heh, heh, heh.
[whistles]
- Oh, no, no, no, no, no!
Ahh!
Oh!
[frantic gibberish]
- Huh?
♪ ♪
all: Yeah!
- Whoa!
- [frantic gibberish]
- Whoa, look out!
♪ ♪
- Ahh!
- [laughing]
- Oh, no!
No, no, no, no, no!
all: [screaming]
- You've ruined everything!
You'll never be elves!
- Bah.
Oh, oh!
- Look out!
- Ohh.
- Ho, ho, ho!
- [gasps]
Santa's coming!
all: [screaming]
- Zap, zap, zap, zap, zap.
[reindeer groaning]
- [gasps]
all: [screaming]
- Ha!
- Ah!
- Eh.
[giggling]
- Ho, ho, ho!
- [chuckling nervously]
Your sleigh is all ready,
Santa.
all: [cheering]
[neighing]
- Wait!
Oh, ooh.
[glass clattering]
[chuckling]
Trainees, am I right?
- Whoa!
Hey!
[excited gibberish]
♪ Hey ♪
- Hmm?
[straining]
- [giggling]
[imitating grunts]
- [whistles]
Hup, hup, hup, hup!
Ha!
all: Whoa!
- [laughing]
all: [gasp]
- Grr!
- [chuckling nervously]
[electrical buzzing]
all: Ahh!
- The
"Minions Holiday Special"
will be right back.
Stick around.
[electrical buzzing]
- [snoring]
- Uhh, Mini-Boss?
[gibberish]
- Ahh.
- [gibberish]
- Okay, fine, fine.
- Because you had a nightmare,
but just tonight.
- [excited giggling]
[gibberish]
Ahh.
- I'm not buying the nightmare
story, though.
- Uh, scuza?
E mé?
[curious gibberish]
- Oh, really?
You too?
- Mm-hmm.
- Get in.
- [laughing]
Thank you.
[soft twinkling music]
- Good night.
- Yes, yes, yes.
Good night.
♪ ♪
- [shouting]
Good night!
- Ohh!
- Ahh.
- Ohh...
- "Minions:
The Rise of Gru."
Rated PG.
.
- Welcome back to the
"Minions Holiday Special."
["Jingle Bells"
in gibberish]
- Ta-da!
[honking]
- Get out your ugly
holiday sweaters.
- Huh? Aah!
both: [laughing]
- It's time for another
"Minions" Mini-Movie.
[ice cream truck melody]
♪ ♪
- Ice cream!
- I'm getting a double dip.
- I'm getting a chocolate cone.
- Come on, let's go!
- I'm getting two scoops of--
Minions: [excited gibberish]
- Aah!
- Eh?
- Huh?
- Stupid bike.
[sniffles]
- Oh...
Grr.
both: [frustrated gibberish]
- [crying]
both: [straining]
- [gibberish]
- [crying]
- Hey?
[determined gibberish]
- Heh, heh!
- No, no.
No, no!
[gibberish]
- Ahh.
- Okay?
- Okay.
["Rocky" theme playing]
[whistle twirrs]
- [gibberish]
Ah, bueno.
[chuckling]
- Whoa, oh, oh, oh!
- [chuckling]
- [straining]
Must...get...ice cream!
♪ ♪
- Look out.
- Eh?
Uh?
Aah, aah!
[screaming]
♪ ♪
[Minions singing
gibberish to "Rocky" theme]
♪ ♪
♪ Ahh ♪
[dramatic music]
- Let's do this.
♪ ♪
- Agnes?
- Wow.
- Awesome!
- [giggling]
- [gibberish]
- Mwah!
- Hup!
all: [frustrated gibberish]
- [humming to ice cream truck
tune]
- Come on, guys!
- I can almost taste it!
[laughing]
[upbeat music]
[alarm ringing]
[gasps]
- Yippie-doo!
- Get out of there!
- Hey!
Ah, that's my truck!
Oh, you good-for-nothing
hoodlum!
- My ice cream...
My ice cream.
♪ ♪
[mechanical whirring]
[engine revs]
[whooshing]
both: [gasp]
♪ ♪
- Oh, my gosh!
Agnes, wait!
- Whoa!
♪ ♪
- Hmm?
- I want my ice cream!
- Ugh.
♪ ♪
Hey!
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
Oh, no, no, no!
- Whoa!
- [screaming]
♪ ♪
Whoa!
- Oh!
Hey!
- [screaming]
Ugh.
- [giggling]
- [laughs]
- Yeah, Agnes!
- Ah!
- This is the best day ever!
- Ahh.
[soft music]
♪ ♪
all: [chuckling]
- Sorry your bike
blew up, Agnes.
- Oh, that's okay.
I think I like this bike
better anyways.
[ice cream truck melody]
[mechanical whirring]
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
Whoo-hoo!
- Whoa.
♪ ♪
- Oh, hey.
[gibberish]
- [gibberish]
all: Ahh!
- And now,
a special musical treat
from the cast of "Sing."
- ♪ Just hear
those sleigh bells jingling ♪
♪ Ring-ting-tingling too ♪
♪ Come on,
it's lovely weather ♪
♪ For a sleigh ride
together with-- ♪
["Just Dance" by Lady Gaga]
- ♪ Just dance,
gonna be okay ♪
♪ Da-da-do-doot-n,
just dance ♪
♪ Spin that record, babe ♪
♪ Da-da-doo-doot-n,
just dance ♪
- More rockin' moments
are coming your way
on the
"Minions Holiday Special."
We'll be right back.
- ♪ Just dance ♪
- The best gift this holiday
is from...
- "Illumination"!
- The "Illumination"
10 Movie Collection..."
- It's so fluffy!
- With all your
favorite characters.
- It's "Snow" time!
- [singing high note]
- Happy Hol--
- Uh-uh.
- On digital
and Blu-ray and DVD now.
.
- Hello?
Mwah, mwah, mwah.
- Hey, oh!
[gibberish]
- Welcome back to the
"Minions Holiday Special."
- Mm.
- You're gonna love...
- Mwah!
Heh, heh.
- This next
"Minions" Mini-Movie.
[soft music]
♪ ♪
- [humming]
[dog barking]
Uh?
Huh?
[dog barking]
♪ ♪
[barks]
Ohh, eh.
Aww.
Hmm?
Ah?
Mm.
Oh!
[dogs barking]
Ohhhh.
[gasps]
[gibberish]
- [growling]
Hey!
Hey, Kyle!
[curious gibberish]
[growling]
- Mm.
Oh!
[gibberish]
[squeaking]
Oh... Ah.
[whistles]
Ah.
[gibberish]
[buzzing]
Oh?
Ahh.
[giggling]
[curious gibberish]
[straining]
Ah?
Oh, oh...
- [whirring]
Huh?
Ah!
Oh!
[giggling]
Puppy, puppy?
[gibberish]
- [mechanical whirring]
- Eh?
- [mechanical beep]
- See, see?
- [mechanical whirring]
[sniffing]
[whirring]
- Huh?
[giggling]
Hey, hey?
Oh, hey!
No, no, no, no.
Eh, hey?
[laughing]
[gibberish]
Whoa.
[gasps]
Yeah!
[laughing]
[upbeat music]
- Hello!
♪ ♪
- [gibberish]
- [barks]
- [aggressive barking]
- [affirmative gibberish]
♪ ♪
- Oh?
[gibberish]
- [whirring]
- Whoa!
♪ ♪
- ♪ Yeah, yeah,
oh, bop ♪
♪ Dapa-doo-bop ♪
♪ Doo-yap-bop ♪
♪ Doo-bop,
dapa-doo ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah ♪
- Thank you.
- Thank you!
- ♪ Doo-yappa-doo ♪
♪ Bop dappa-doo ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah ♪
- [growling]
[whirring]
all: Yay!
[soft music]
- Uhh.
[nervous giggling]
- [whirring]
- Oh!
[excited gibberish]
- [whirring]
- Butt, butt?
Butt!
Butt, butt, butt, butt,
butt, butt!
[laughing]
- [mechanical beeping]
[whirring]
- Huh?
Huh.
- [whirs]
♪ ♪
- Ohh.
[curious gibberish]
Oh?
Ohh...
♪ ♪
Hmm.
[beeping]
♪ ♪
[mechanical whooshing]
- Hey!
[gibberish]
- [sad whirring]
- [curious gibberish]
- [whirs]
♪ ♪
- [whirring]
- [gibberish]
[mechanical whirring]
♪ ♪
all: Yay!
- [laughing]
Whoa!
Aww.
[laughing]
- [purring]
- [chuckles]
- [beeping]
- [encouraging gibberish]
- [whirring]
♪ ♪
- Hmm...
- [whirring]
- Huh?
Oh?
- [whirring]
- Oh?
♪ ♪
[gasps]
Huh?
Puppy?
Ooh!
[laughing]
Puppy!
Thank you!
- [whirring]
[upbeat music]
all: [cheering]
♪ ♪
- Only a Grinch wouldn't want
to see more "Minions."
- Ah!
- Don't go anywhere.
- Ugh.
- We'll be right back.
[upbeat music]
♪ ♪
- Whoa!
Universal Orlando Resort.
Buy two days and get
three days free at the parks.
Restrictions apply.
.
["We Wish You
A Merry Christmas"]
- Welcome back to the
"Minions Holiday Special,"
and another
"Minions" Mini-Movie.
[piano music]
- Ugh.
[serious gibberish]
- Oh, Miguel!
Mi amor!
Mwah, mwah, mwah!
- [laughing]
- Whoo-hoo!
- That was awesome!
- Badger Scouts are the best!
- We earned so many badges!
Minions: Oh!
- Badges.
- Pretty sweet, right?
Minions: Ahhh.
["Call to Post"-like tune]
- And, hut!
children: Hut!
Minions: [gobbling]
- At ease, you weaselly wimps.
Welcome to Badger Scouts.
You think you've got what it
takes to earn my badges?
Minions: Si!
- [chuckling]
[whistle twirrs]
Well, show me what you've got.
- All right, here we go.
- Give me that tent pole.
- [straining]
- Got it.
♪ ♪
- Go!
- Ahh!
[frantic gibberish]
- [straining]
Oh!
[bird screeches]
- Ooh, ehh.
- Now, that's what I call
a tent!
Here's your badge.
What?
What the--
Minions: [gobbling]
[bird squawks]
- Hmm.
- Aww.
♪ ♪
- Mm-hmm!
Good work, scouts!
Minions: [chuckling]
[straining]
- [cooing]
♪ ♪
- Good job!
- Yes!
- Blah! Blah! Blah!
[bear roars]
[screaming]
♪ ♪
- Huh?
Oh.
Huh, huh?
[screaming]
- [sighs]
♪ ♪
- Oh, uh...right there!
- Well done.
- Uh, uh, uh...
no, no.
Uh...pff.
[gibberish]
- [giggling]
Oh!
[gibberish]
- Oh, oh.
[distorted music]
all: Whoa.
- Magic.
[Minions singing]
[singing]
- Ugh!
Minions: Whoa, whoa!
♪ ♪
[screaming]
- No, no, no, no!
- [screaming]
♪ ♪
[straining]
Grr, ahh!
[frustrated gibberish]
- Hey, no, no, no, no, no!
all: Yay!
- Huh, looks like
you finally earned these.
Minions: [excited gibberish]
- Eh?
- Oh?
all: [screaming]
- So, how'd it go?
Minions: [crying]
- Aww.
Here.
You can have my sharing badge.
Minions: Ahh.
- [gibberish]
- [frustrated gibberish]
- Guys!
Here.
both: [chuckling]
[upbeat music]
- Whoa.
- ♪ Gangsta, gangsta ♪
- ♪ Hey, yeah, that's me ♪
♪ Chillin' out, ridin' dirty ♪
♪ Comin' down yo' street ♪
♪ I'm a gangsta, gangsta ♪
- All right,
you weaselly wimps.
Ten-hut!
all: [gobbling]
- Huh?
Bah?
Minions: [gobbling]
- [screaming]
- Whoa!
[gibberish]
[bear roars]
♪ ♪
- Thanks for joining us.
We hope your season
is bright...
- Bee-doo.
Ahh!
- Bursting with joy,
good cheer...
Minions: Yay!
- And strange homemade gifts.
- [happy gibberish]
- From all of us.
- Blah!
- Happy Holidays.
That's all
from the "Minions,"
but here's one more
holiday treat
from "The Secret Life
of Pets."
- ♪ Sleigh bells ring,
are you listening? ♪
♪ In the lane,
snow is glistening ♪
♪ A beautiful sight,
we're happy tonight ♪
♪ Walking in
a winter wonderland ♪
- [growls]
- ♪ Gone away
is the bluebird ♪
- [yowling]
- ♪ Here to stay ♪
♪ Is the new bird ♪
♪ He sings
a love song ♪
- ♪ As we go along ♪
♪ Walking in
a winter wonderland ♪
- ♪ In the meadow,
we can build a snowman ♪
♪ And pretend that
he is Parson Brown ♪
- ♪ He'll say,
"Are you married?" ♪
♪ We'll say,
"No, man" ♪
♪ But you can do the
job when you're in town ♪
♪ Walking in
a winter wonderland ♪
- [whistles]
- [barks]
♪ ♪
[party horn honking]
- [frantic gibberish]
[crying]
Oh, ahh!
- [humming]
[screaming]
♪ ♪
both: [cheering]
[excited gibberish]
all: [cheering]
♪ ♪