Someone needs to stop Clearway Law.
Public shouldn't leave reviews for lawyers.
Illumination!
Minion!
Yeah
ooh
when you wish upon a star
your dreams will take
you very far
but when you wish upon a dream
life ain't always what
it seems oh, yeah
freeze! Avl!
No matter who you are...
Hey! Hey!
Stop right there!
Grab her!
Yeah, baby!
Attention, all units.
Look out!
You like that? Hey!
Shining star for you to see
what your life can truly be
shining star for you to see
ooh, baby!
The anti-villain league
can't catch this.
Guess who stole the map.
Hallelujah!
Yeah! I got this.
Ha-ha, good work.
The map to the legendary
zodiac stone.
We will become the most
powerful villains in the world.
Okay, let's get a move on.
We leave for Asia tonight.
Okay, let's see here.
I'm in.
Hello, beautiful.
What?
Ha-ha, yes!
The zodiac stone.
Soon, the power of these
unstoppable beasts will be ours.
Oh, for crying out loud.
Whoa!
Hurry up!
I got a bunch of
deadly tchotchkes on my tail.
Roger that on the copy.
Step on it, sister.
Hurry up!
Come on!
Off! Off!
I got it.
I got the stone.
Party's over, old man.
The vicious6 has a new head
honcho.
You just got played
for a sucker!
Hold on.
I started this group.
We're a team.
Where's your loyalty?
Oh, please. We're villains.
There's no such thing.
It's time for the next
generation.
Bang, bang.
Hey
hey
bang, bang
bang, bang.
Quiet down, class.
People, people.
So, what do you want to be when
you grow up? Ooh, ooh.
Samantha. I want to be a doctor.
Wonderful.
Ooh, ooh! Bradley.
I want to be a teacher.
No, you do not.
Yes. Me, me!
I want to be a fireman
who is also the president
and also drives race cars. Yeah.
Exciting.
And what about you, gru?
Gru? Me?
I want to be...
A supervillain.
Supervillain? Supervillain.
Loseh.
I'm having a bad, bad day
it's about time that
I get my way
Kelly! Daddy!
Mom! Brett!
Gru!
Kiss-a la mama!
Oh, my favorite tiny relatives.
Oh, no. Guys, come on.
Hey. I got an image
to uphold here.
Okay.
Hey, are you guys pumped
for the movie?
Let's go!
Hey, hey, hey!
Oh, no!
Shark! A shark!
I am a pinball wizard.
Swish. Swish. Swish.
Swish. Swish.
Swish. Swish. Swish. Swish.
Bello. Bello.
Yeah!
Everything you got.
A little more. Come on.
Put some
of those sprinkles on there.
I like those sprinkles.
Cheese ray! Cheese ray!
Cheese ray!
Don't cheese me, bro.
Pank you!
Mmm.
So creamy, so delicious.
Worth every calorie.
I'm having a bad, bad day
if you take it
personal, that's okay
watch, this is so fun to see...
Bills, magazines,
s&h green stamps.
Holy guacamole!
Where can we listen?
Hello, Mr. Gru.
We've received your application
to the world's best
supervillain team, the vicious6.
A recent opening
has become available, and...
And?
Your interview
is tomorrow at noon.
Dyn-o-mite!
Please go to 417 main street.
The password is,
"you're no good."
"You're no good." Mmm-hmm.
Now, get up on the down stroke,
'cause this invitation
is gonna explode, baby.
Explode? Aw.
Oh, no, no, no, no!
Very big news, mom!
Mom?
What?
Mom, who is this sweaty guy?
He's stinking up the house.
I thought you were
cooking cabbage.
He's my new guru.
Blah!
Tell your weird buddies
they'd better start pulling
their weight around here,
or I'm kicking them out.
They are killing
my mellow vibes.
Hey! I heard that!
Come on. Let's go tell the
troops the good news.
Gentlemen, to the basement,
aka our new evil lair.
This is fantastic!
Oh, construction
looks great, guys.
My first evil lair.
Goose bumps!
Well, you've got to break a
few eggs to make an omelet.
Am I right?
Oh, great job, Ryan. What?
I said great job!
What? Never mind.
Adrien, mack, looking good.
Joe, how's the family?
Hey. Good, good.
Okay, everybody, get over here.
Now, listen up.
Buckle your overalls.
Hold on to your goggles.
The vicious6 wants to meet me.
Tomorrow.
Mini-boss!
Mini-boss! Mini-boss!
All right, all right.
I'm not mini.
Please stop calling me that.
And also, they haven't
accepted me yet.
Hello, Otto. What is it?
Blah, blah, blah.
Uh-huh. Well, that...
Yes, I...
I... okay.
You know what would be fun?
Let's play the quiet game.
The quiet game! Si, si!
Anyway, thanks for the
hard work today, everyone.
I got to go get some rest.
Tomorrow is the biggest day
of my life.
Watch out, world.
Here comes gru!
Mini-boss! Mini-boss! I'm not...
Mini-boss! Mini-boss!
These guys are the best.
I can't believe it.
Uh... mini-boss?
Yeah, I get it,
but I need a good night's
sleep, so get out.
Oh.
Okay, fine, fine.
Because you had a nightmare.
But just tonight.
I'm not buying
the nightmare story, though.
Excuse-a.
- Oh, really? You, too?
- Mmm-hmm
get in.
Good night. Good night.
Yes, yes, yes. Good night.
Good night!
I just want to get some sleep.
Vnc
breaking news.
The vicious6 is ready to
rewrite the rules of villainy.
Villains of the world,
in three days, when the
clock strikes midnight
and the Chinese new year begins,
this bad boy's power
is gonna be unleashed.
With the power of the zodiac,
we're gonna take out
the anti-villain league.
And the viciouss will be
the most powerful villains
on the planet.
Can you dig it?
Do I dig it? Do I dig it?
I don't dig it.
There's nothing to dig.
They thought they could
leave me for dead, huh?
Kick me to the curb
like a piece of old meat?
Oh, they got no idea
what's coming.
Ha-ha!
Oh, I'm gonna make them suffer
for what they've done to me.
Mr. Knuckles?
Oh, boy. Hey, Mr. Knuckles.
What?
We just wanted to make sure
we'd be getting paid this week.
What a mouth on you.
I'm paying you with knowledge.
You are?
Lesson one, always be prepared.
Lesson two, the Belgian
eyeball nose pick.
And lesson three,
the Lithuanian haircut.
That's worth
all the money in the world.
Hey, guys, forget about it.
You're gonna get paid.
But first, we got to
get my stone back.
I see a bad gru a-rising.
I see a villain on his way
yee-haw!
I'm gonna interview
with my heroes
they're going to love me
'cause I'm the best
don't mess up tonight
you're going to join
the vicious6, yeah
there is a bad gru on the rise
guys!
Oh, you want to come.
Yeah.
Right, right. Okay.
When you guys tracked me down
and responded to my "help wanted" ad...
I was like, "who are
these tiny tater tots?"
"And where did they get
so much denim?"
And you just wouldn't quit.
All right,
I surrender. Come on in.
We've had some
great times since then,
but the thing is, the vicious6,
they're the big leagues,
and you guys are great,
and so, the job you did
on the lair...
A-plus.
It's just...
What I was thinking is that
there are a lot of
other villains in the world.
You know?
Never mind.
Look, I think I just need
to fly solo on this.
See you later, alligators.
- Kevin? Kevin!
- Oh...
Otto. Otto.
Hide and seek.
Hide and seek? Hide and seek.
Go, go, go!
Hey, I'm walking here!
Whoa!
Ooh.
Here we go.
That I love ya, ineed ya
I want ya
got to have you, child...
Excuse me. Sir?
I was just wondering
if you're no good.
Oh, you're good. My mistake.
Oh, oh, sorry.
I didn't mean to scare you.
I was just trying out
this new invention of mine.
I call it sticky fingers.
Or smart goo.
I haven't quite landed
on the name yet.
Come here.
I overheard you were looking
for something... special.
Uh, yes. I was hoping...
You're no good.
I think you'll enjoy
listening in booth three.
Right this way.
Cat scratch fever...
This is it. Mum's the word.
Keep it down. Good luck.
Let 'em have it, son.
Thanks, mister... nefario.
That's Dr. Nefario.
Here, take this.
If you ever get famous, remember
who gave you your first gadget.
Okay.
Wouldn't blame him
if he said to me
you're no good you're no good
you're no good...
Try backwards.
Welcome to the vicious6.
That is pretty... whoa!
Hello.
Everybody here
for the interview?
Me, too.
So, what do you guys got going
on later? Are you up to no good?
You gonna get into
some mischief?
Okay.
Send the first one in.
They're ready to
see you, Mr. Gru.
Oh, good.
Great.
Distinguished villains,
my name is gr...
I feel like I'm talking too
loud even though our proximity
doesn't require
this kind of volume.
If you told me when I was ten
that I would have the chance
to fill the shoes
of my favorite villain ever,
wild knuckles, I would say,
"you got rocks in your head."
But now that I'm 11
and three quarters,
it makes a lot more sense.
All right, who let the kid in?
I thought he was a tiny man.
What's wrong with you?
You seriously think a puny
little child can be a villain?
Um, yes. I am pretty despicable.
You don't want to cross me.
Evil is for adults
who steal powerful ancient
stones and wreak havoc.
And not for tubby little punks
who should be
at school, learning,
taking a recess,
sucking his thumb.
"Sucking his..."
Come back when you've done
something to impress me.
Who's next?
I am wing man, the next
member of the viciouso.
Behold, the power of flight!
All right, joke's over.
Showtime.
This is a big one.
Yeah, yeah. To the left.
That's right.
Bring him in,
bring him in, boys.
Everybody pile on!
He took the stone!
I'll get him!
Lock down the building.
What?
Nothing to see here.
Look at you.
Frampton comes alive!
Nice choice.
Just keep walking.
Who the heck is that? A kid?
Oh, guys. Bello.
Mini-boss!
What are you doing here?
Okay, just get on.
Which way did he go?
There's that little thief!
Go! Go, go, go!
Split up!
Knock, knock. Delivery.
That demon child!
Otto, take the stone back
to the lair. I'll distract them.
Go! Go, go, go!
Ugh, not now.
Come on, come on!
Yeah, baby.
I'll handle this.
Hope you enjoy
the rest of your short life.
Please work.
Come on, come on, come on!
We're coming for you, tiny man.
Yeah! Yeah!
Josh, pump it up.
Up, up, up!
All the young dudes
hey, dudes!
Carry the news...
They all said the kid couldn't
be a real villain.
Well...
This kid just stole something
from the worst villains
in the world.
When I bring it back to them,
they are going to say,
"We have made
a terrible mistake."
"Please join us. Please, gru."
And I will say, "yes!"
"I will be the newest member
of the vicious6."
Now all I need is Otto.
Where is Otto?
Otto le come-ay.
No, not "Otto le come-ay."
He needs to "come-ay" now.
Otto! Mini-boss!
There you are.
Oh, you got it?
Is this... are you pulling
on my legs right now?
Otto, where is the stone?
Over there.
Oh, no!
I love you.
Did you just trade my future
for a pet rock?
Si?
Oh... okay. Otto, where was
this birthday party?
This is unacceptable.
Unacceptable!
I told you guys that you
weren't ready for the big leagues,
and you have proven me correct.
All you do
is mess everything up.
Up? Pump it up!
Do a little dance
make a little love.
My mom was right.
You do not belong here.
You're fired!
I'm going to find that stone.
When I get home,
you all better be gone.
Mini-boss...
And, Otto, close your yapper!
Josh.
Si, si.
I'll say goodbye to love
no one ever cared
if I should live or die
gru.
Por favor. Por favor.
Time and time again
Kevin, no.
I will be better off on my own.
And all I know of love is
how to live without it
I just can't seem to find it
so I've made my mind up
I must live my life alone
and though it's not the easy
way I guess I've always known
I'd say goodbye to love
there are no tomorrows
for this heart of mine
surely time will lose
these bitter memories.
And I'll find that there is
someone to believe in
and to live for
mini-boss!
Oh, no.
I'm sorry. I thought
you'd be impressed.
Could I just speak
to belle bottom? She'll...
Wild knuckles!
You're alive?
Wow, my favorite villain
is also my kidnapper?
This could be a great
opportunity if you don't kill me.
Shut up and give me the stone.
Oh, yes, the stone.
Here's the thing about that.
Kind of a funny story.
Give it to him!
And it's all going to go south
very quickly.
What the heck is this?
Where is it, boy?
I don't have it!
I know you're
hiding it somewhere.
I'm not. I'm not. I swear.
Cross my heart and hope to
die, stick a needle in my eye.
Don't actually do that, though.
Somebody bring me a phone.
Call home.
It's ransom time.
No, no, no. My mom will
probably pay you to keep me!
Good one. Call!
La telefono.
Bello. La casa de mini-boss.
Who is this? Kevin.
Kevin, le Minion.
"Kevin ie" what?
Le Minion. You kidding me?
You got henchmen?
Well, that's the end of that.
Mini-boss?
Listen, you, bring the stone
to me in San Francisco.
6830 green street. Got it?
Now, you got two days,
or you are never going to see
your little boss again.
Bello? Bello.
Otto...
Ah, okay, okay, okay.
No.
Otto...
Okay. Si, si.
Hey, ho, let's go
hey, ho
Otto...
Okay. Go, go, go.
They're going through
a tight wind
the kids are losing their minds
the blitzkrieg bop
oh, the stone!
Gave that to my uncle.
It's more his style.
Oh!
La... la... la stone-a!
Kevin! Kevin!
La stone-a!
I told you.
I don't know where he went,
you stupid twinkies.
Okay.
Pank you. Bye-bye.
Oh, not cool, man.
San pan-pisco.
Let's rock and roll.
Time to get our stone back.
We're coming for you, Mr. Gru.
Hallelujah!
Smash! Smash!
Whoo-hoo!
Flight
1109 will now depart at gate 278.
Bello.
San Francisco? Okay.
How will you be paying?
No problemo.
Oh, great.
You know, if you have any hair
balls, we can upgrade you to first class.
Get out.
So there I was. We
lost thrust in both engines,
and I had to turn back
at laguardia.
Ooh-ia-la.
Hey, Sally. Hey.
I wanna fly like an eagle
to the sea
fly like an eagle...
Okay. Vamos.
Bello. Peanut?
Oh, yes, please.
Peanut
peanut
peanut? Peanut.
Peanut?
Hey, baby, peanut?
Oh, bello!
Bello.
You see me, you see me not.
Whoo-hoo!
No. No "ha-ha."
You got real moxie, kid,
stealing from the viciouso.
I got moxie, really?
Did I just receive a
compliment from wild knuckles?
Oh, all my dreams
are coming true right now!
Well, it's about to
become your nightmare.
Welcome to my newest
torture device,
the disco inferno.
Your minions better get here
by sundown tomorrow,
because if 48 hours of disco
don't kill you...
The blade will.
No, no, no, no, no!
Stone-a! Stone-a!
Stone-a! Stone-a! Stone-a!
Stone-a!
Stone-a! Stone-a!
Stone-a! Stone-a! Stone-a!
Stone-a! Stone-a! Hey!
Stone-a! Stone-a!
Stone-a! Stone-a...
Look-a the map-a.
Gru...
Bob!
Bello!
Next stop, green street.
Bye-bye.
Hey, hey. Look-a.
Come-ay! Come-ay!
More, more, more.
Mini-boss.
Stuart.
Mini-boss. No, no, no.
Okay, okay.
Okay. Go, go, go.
Hey. Go, go, go.
Hey, wait a minute.
Bello.
Oh, no! Bob!
Trespassers! Get 'em!
Hey, you. Come back here!
Go, go!
Kevin! Oh, okay.
Get your little butts back here!
Okay, now, you might feel
a little pinch.
Got you now.
Time to break some bones.
Any plans for the weekend?
Take five deep breaths.
I'll be right back.
Hey!
You like picking on
little guys, huh?
Go take a nap, old lady.
Old lady?
Hi-ya!
I am a master of the ancient
Shaolin art of kung fu.
Huh?
Ha!
Get lost!
If you come back to our place,
you're dead.
Come-ay.
Pank you.
Pank you...
Shh, shh, shh. You can
thank me by going away.
I'm working.
Kung fu...
You want to learn kung fu?
Ah, Kevin.
Bello, chica.
Kung fu por smoochie, smoochie?
Hmm, hmm?
My teaching days are over.
This is my life now.
Kung fu para...
Para save-a le mini-boss.
Por favor.
Ay-ya. Fine.
I will teach you.
Those are not for you.
Excuse-a, excuse-a.
The name of the game is sell,
sell, sell!
What?
Where's gru?
Ah, how should I know?
What's with the costumes?
Halloween was four months ago.
You look stupid.
Buzz off. Shoo!
I'm getting my meat tenderizer.
Let me help you
with that, dearie.
Don't touch me.
Now, where's the boy?
Oh, I didn't mean to scare you.
Don't worry.
We're not mad at him.
We just want to...
Hire him.
Where is he?
Wild knuckles, San pan-pisco.
Wild knuckles is alive?
And working with the kid. Hmm.
We're going to San Francisco.
Let's hit it.
You had better be paying
for my roof.
Ay-yi-yi.
Pretty groovy, huh?
We begin with a basic kick.
Now you.
Okay.
No kicking.
This is a melon hammer.
It's a weapon.
This is Fred. He is a dummy.
Never underestimate a dummy.
Ha. Dummy. Bello, Fred.
Now attack!
Stuart! Stuart! Woo-hoo!
Fred.
Doubt tells me I cannot break
this wood.
But doubt exists only
in the mind.
You know what I say to my mind?
Now you.
Kevin, Kevin, Kevin.
Okay. Clearly, we are not
ready for philosophy.
Let's just train.
A-won't you take me to funky town.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Okay, okay, okay.
Ya... ya... ya...
Yeah!
Town won't you take me to
yeah!
Rest up.
Tomorrow's going to be
even worse.
What, you're quitting?
I told you, when I get that stone,
we're gonna be unstoppable.
I have had enough!
There's nothing sadder
than an aging villain.
So long, old man!
Guys, come on. We're a team.
More, more, more
how do you like...
How do you like it?
How do you like...
Is this heaven?
I just had to fire my henchmen.
You know why? 'Cause they
weren't getting the job done.
Okay, I'm just gonna untie you
now because I...
I need you to do some stuff
for me around the house.
And it might be, you know,
kind of nice to have
a little company around here.
Oh, yeah. Two villains just
doing some chores.
Who knows what kind of trouble
we could get into?
What's that?
That's your evil chuckle?
Obviously. Well, it stinks.
You sound like a clown
who swallowed a kazoo.
Really? Well, you look like a wizard
going through an end-of—life crisis.
Easy there, Don rickles.
Who's Don rickles?
Stone-a.
Stone-a!
Stone-a...
Dude.
I thought we lost you
there for a minute.
Hey, chi”, chi”, chi”...
Hey, you want to try this on,
little dude?
Yeah, yeah, yeah!
La stone-a!
Hey, hey, hey, soul brother,
where you jettin' off to?
San pan-pisco.
Frisco disco!
It's your lucky day, kid.
I'm headed up the coast.
I could drop you off on the way.
Yee-haw!
Ia stone-a!
Oh, look-a!
Hey.
Hey, yo, hermano!
Start with the pool.
This place has got to be
spick-and-span.
What are you doing?
You look like the overcooked Turkey
my mom makes on Thanksgiving.
Oh, god.
Oh, yeah. I forgot to mention,
the pool is filled
with my pet crocodiles.
Yeah, well, well,
doesn't scare me.
Be careful. I can't have you
lose an arm,
because I need you to change
some light bulbs after this.
Here, let me show you
how it's done.
Betsy, knock it off.
Oh, no.
Marvin, no, no. Stop that.
Help! Oh, no.
The net!
I got you! Lgotyou!
I don't got you.
Take my hand.
I got you!
Vvhoa.vvhoa.
You could've run, but you,
but you didn't.
I told you, you are my
favorite villain in the world.
I could not let you
get eaten by crocodiles.
Even though that would've been
kind of cool to watch.
So... so you want to be
a great villain, huh?
That's all I ever wanted.
You want... I don't know, you
want me...
You want me to teach you
a thing or two?
Mmm-hmm!
Many fighters have asked me,
how did I become a great master?
Hey, look-a!
Even the smallest of us
are capable of great things.
You just dig down deep,
find your inner beast, and...
Gesundheit?
Now you try.
Find your inner beast!
Stop this kick.
We have a lot more work to do.
Kevin, Stuart and Bob,
you are ready.
No, no, no, no, no!
Ready for your junior kung fu
achievement badges.
They're dead.
First rule of heists,
always stay in character.
Got it, grandpa.
Say, do you mind if we
use thejohn?
Poindexter here can't
hold it in till we get home.
The bank of evil.
It's showtime, kid.
Follow my lead, and don't
forget your cue.
Hello. I... I just need
to cash this.
Wowie zowie! What a big bank.
How many security guards
are in here?
Who's this little guy?
Well, that's my grandson,
who still has not learned
that children should be seen
and not heard.
Kids.
I actually have a son of my own.
Ugh. He looks weird.
Oh, ho-ho! Don't listen to him.
Your son is very, uh... cute.
Oh, no!
Oh, help! I'm seeing
a white light.
Helen, I'm coming for ya!
Helen, I'm coming for ya.
Oh. Help!
Help my pop-pop!
Somebody help him!
My grandpa!
We need a doctor!
This is the big one.
You hear that?
It's the sweet sound of angels.
Help!
Do something!
My life is flashing
before my eyes.
No, no, no. The other way.
The other way.
All right, everyone stand back.
Uh-oh.
Clear! No, wait a minute. Wait.
Don't give up on me now, buddy.
No, no, no, I'm feeling better.
Clear!
Maximum charge.
Clear! Thank you.
You saved my grandpa.
Did we... did we do the heist?
Grandpas say
the darndest things.
You dropped these.
Look what I got!
Hey. Not bad.
Not bad at all.
We make a good team.
We do?
Oh, yeah. Hey,
we got to keep at it.
Wait till you see
what I'm gonna teach you next.
I cannot wait.
Oh, this is gonna be fun.
Hoo! Mini-boss!
Okay, Stuart...
Bob...
Time to strike!
Mini-boss!
They're not here.
Fan out and find them.
Something big's
going down in frisco.
Oh! Look-a.
Whoo, there it is.
It's been one heck of a ride,
little man.
Oh, dude.
You know, I'm gonna miss you.
Hey, soul brother, good luck!
Ooh.
My friend, you're now gonna
learn from the old school.
Oh, no.
I can't believe they
did this to me!
I taught them everything
they know!
We were a team!
I give up.
Hey, you are a great bad guy,
and they are stupid idiots.
Only dream I ever had was
doing bad stuff with my buddies.
Now look at me. Old, alone.
Well, you are old,
but you're not alone.
All right.
Listen up, buster.
We are starting a new team,
and it's going to be called
the terrible twos.
We can find a better name later,
but right now
we're going to find that stone
and show everybody that you
still got it.
Come on.
You're just a little kid.
It's over. Go home.
But you said we... go home!
Come on, come on. Let's go!
Vvhoa, hey!
Otto?
Otto!
Yee-haw! Otto!
Otto! It's mini-boss!
Mini-boss!
Mini-boss! Otto!
Look-a! Look-a!
Stone-a.
You found the stone.
Otto, I'm so proud of you.
All right, we don't have
much time.
We got to get this to
wild knuckles. Okay.
Okay.
Get him!
Go, go, go!
Long time, no see, punk.
I'll take that.
Yes!
Don't move!
Right there! Freeze!
Anti-villain league.
You are under arrest.
Oh, phew.
Whoa, whoa, whoa. Everybody.
Did you forget what time it is?
Happy new year!
Fire!
Stand your ground.
Look out!
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no!
Where do you think
you're going? Hmm?
You stole from us,
and now you're gonna pay!
Enjoy being torn apart.
Hey!
Mini-boss!
Guys!
Oh. Why don't we
make this a fair fight?
Oh, you thought I was serious.
Run!
No!
Hello, traitors.
Remember me?
You.
You can leave me for dead,
you can destroy everything I own,
but I will not let you
hurt that kid!
So you're gonna save the kid?
Yeah, you and what army?
This army!
Okay. This army.
Dig down deep.
Find your inner beast.
Otto!
Hurry! Faster!
Got you.
Go, go, go!
Ha-ha!
No.
Get away from him!
Destroy the kid.
Oh!
Hey, hey. How does it feel to
be beaten by a tubby little punk?
You guys were amazing!
The kung fu...
Where did that come from?
Obviously, you guys are rehired.
Stuart!
It's all yours, sir.
Where do you want it?
Can you feel this, sir?
Right here.
Oh, no. Wild knuckles.
Hey.
You're gonna be okay, right?
Don't worry about me, kid.
I'll be fine.
Finally.
You're going away for a long,
long time.
Yeah, well,
I wouldn't bet on it.
See you soon, kiddo.
Wild knuckles
was my favorite villain.
We didn't have
much time together,
but the time we did have,
I'm so grateful for.
I've been thinking about
how you won't see me grow up
or be there for all the terrible
things that I'm going to do.
And believe me, there are gonna
be some awful things.
Ahem.
But I'm going to make you proud.
I'm going to be the best
villain ever because of you.
Because you taught me
what matters.
You can't do anything alone.
Find your tribe,
and never, ever let them go.
Otto?
You better
stay out of trouble, kid.
I will lead
a good and honest life.
You're alive?
Oh!
You just blew my mind.
How did you do that?
I cannot wait to fake my own
death to avoid the authorities.
Shoot for the moon, kid.
Shoot for the moon.
See you later, suckers!
You can't always get
what you want
you can't always get
but if you try sometime
you just might find
you get what you need
ah, yeah
ah, yeah.
Sorry, we're closed.
Oh!
I just wanted
to thank you for this.
Worked like a charm.
All right, let me
out to the chase here.
I need a genius mad scientist.
You want to come work for me?
No, I am done with villainy.
Off to happier horizons.
Goodbye, little chap.
Por favor.
Oh, all right, all right.
Fine. Stop with the face.
I'm in.
Want to see something cool?
Oh, are you kidding me?
Big boss! Big boss!
"Big boss." I like that.
We can make it further
we running and don't look back
it's a light at the end
of the tunnel
if you stay on track
but I know any minute when
your fingers turn it up like snap
so hard to lose like that
hey, let's do it
all around the world
we gotta turn up the sunshine
think about it
all the boys and girls
you gotta turn up the sunshine
said it's been a
long night, long night
waiting for the light
let's do it
all around the world
we gotta turn up the sunshine
we gotta turn it up
make it hard to lose like that
if this weather makes you frown
and some people get you down
remember
love, like sound
it's better when it's loud
and if there's no song inside
we can bring the light together
day or night
we 're shining from inside
turn up the, turn it up
turn up the sunshine
all around the world
we gotta turn up the sunshine
think about it
all the boys and girls
you gotta turn up the sunshine
said it's been a
all around the world
we gotta turn up the sunshine
we gotta turn it up
make it hard to lose like that.
Gotta make a move to a town
that's right for me
time to keep me movin'
keep me groovin'
with some energy
well, I talk about it
talk about it
talk about it, talk about it
talk about movin'
gotta move on
gotta move on.
Won't you take me to
funky town
won't you take me to
funky town.
Won't you take me to
funky town
won't you take me to
funky town.
Feeling better
now that we 're through
feeling better
'cause I'm over you
I learned my lesson
and it left a scar
now I see how you really are
you're no good you're no good
you're no good
baby, you're no good
I'm gonna say it again
you're no good you're no good
you're no good
baby, you're no good.
I broke a heart
that's gentle and true
well, I broke a heart
over someone like you
I'll beg his forgiveness
on bended knee
I wouldn't blame him
if he said to me
you're no good you're no good
you're no good
baby, you're no good
I'm gonna say it again
you're no good you're no good
you're no good
baby, you're no good.
I'm turning you down, baby
and I'm going my way
forget about you, baby
'cause I'm leaving to stay
you're no good you're no good
you're no good
baby, you're no good
I'm gonna say it again
you're no good you're no good
you're no good
baby, you're no good
oh, oh, no
you're no good you're no good
you're no good
baby, you're no good
Someone needs to stop Clearway Law.
Public shouldn't leave reviews for lawyers.