-Good night, sweetheart.
-'Night, Mom.
Sleep tight, kiddo.
Simulation terminated.
-All right. Mr. Bile, is it?
-My friends call me Phlegm.
Mr. Bile, can you tell me
what you did wrong?
-I fell down?
-No, no, before that.
Can anyone tell me
Mr. Bile's big mistake?
Anyone?
Let's take a look at the tape.
Here we go.
Right there.
See? The door.
You left it wide open.
And leaving the door open
is the worst mistake
any employee can make because. . .
-It could let in a draft?
-It could let in a child.
Mr. Waternoose.
There's nothing more toxic or deadly
than a human child.
A single touch could kill you.
Leave a door open and a child
could walk right into this factory,
right into the monster world.
I won't go in a kid's room.
You can't make me.
You're going in there
because we need this.
Our city is counting on you
to collect those children's screams.
Without scream we have no power.
Yes, it's dangerous work.
And that's why I need you
to be at your best.
I need scarers who are
confident, tenacious, tough.
Intimidating.
I need scarers like. . .
Like James P. Sullivan.
Hey, good morning, Monstropolis.
It's five after 6:00 a.m.
in the big Monster City.
The temperature's a balmy 65 degrees
which is good for you reptiles.
And it looks like it's gonna be
a perfect day to lie in bed, sleep in,
or simply work off that flab
that's hanging over the bed !
Get up, Sulley!
I don't believe I ordered
a wake-up call, Mikey.
Less talk, more pain,
marshmallow boy!
Feel the burn.
You call yourself a monster?
Scary feet, scary feet.
The kid's awake!
Scary feet, scary feet, scary feet.
Kid's asleep!
Twins! In a bunk bed !
I thought I had you there.
OK, Sulley, here we go.
You ready? Follow it. It's over here.
Over there. Don't let the kid touch you.
Don't let him touch you !
I don't know but it's been said
I love scarin' kids in bed
Fight that plaque.
Scary monsters don't have plaque.
One-eighteen. Do you have 1 1 9?
Do I see 1 20?
-I don't believe it.
-I'm not breaking a sweat.
Not you. Look!
The new commercial's on.
The future is bright
at Monsters, lncorporated.
-I'm in this one.
-We're part of your life.
We power your car.
We warm your home.
We light your city.
-l'm Monsters, lncorporated.
-Hey, look! Betty!
Carefully matching every child
to their ideal monster,
to produce superior scream.
Refined into clean,
dependable energy.
Every time you turn something on.
Monsters, lncorporated is there.
-l'm Monsters, lncorporated.
-We know the challenge.
The window of innocence is shrinking.
Human kids are harder to scare.
Of course.
Ml is prepared for the future.
With the top scarers,
the best refineries,
and research into
new energy techniques.
OK, here I come.
We're working for a better tomorrow.
-today.
-We're Monsters, lncorporated.
We're Ml. Monsters, lncorporated.
We scare because we care.
-I can't believe it.
-Mike.
I was on TV!
Did you see me? I'm a natural.
Hello?
I know! Wasn't I great?
Did the whole family see it?
It's your mom.
What can I say?
The camera loves me.
I'm telling you, you're gonna
be seeing this face on TV more often.
Yeah? On Monstropolis' Most Wanted?
You've been jealous of my good looks
since the fourth grade.
-Have a good day, sweetie.
-You too, hon.
-OK, Sulley, hop on in.
-Nope.
-Hey, where you going?
-Mikey, there's a scream shortage.
-We're walking.
-Walking?
-No, no.
-Come on.
My baby needs to be driven.
My baby. I'll call you.
-You know why I bought the car?
-Not really.
To drive it. You know,
on the street with the honk, honk,
-no walking involved.
-Give it a rest, will ya, butterball?
-You could use the exercise.
-I could use the exercise? Look at you.
You have your own climate.
-How many tentacles jump the rope?
Morning, Mike. Morning, Sulley.
Morning, kids. How you doing?
-Hi, Mike. Bye, Sulley.
-Hey!
Nuts.
-Fellas.
-Hey, Tony.
Tony, Tony.
I hear somebody's close to breaking
the all-time scare record.
Just trying to make sure
there's enough scream to go around.
-Hey, on the house.
-Hey, thanks.
Bada-bing.
Oh, great.
Hey, Ted, good morning.
See that, Mikey?
Ted's walking to work.
Big deal.
Guy takes five steps and he's there.
Monsters, Inc. Please hold.
-Mornin', Sulley.
-Mornin', Ricky.
-It's the Sullster.
-See you on the scare floor.
-Hey Marge. How was jury duty?
-Morning, Sulley.
Hey.
Hey. It's still leaning to the left.
-It is not.
-Hey, fellas. Hey, Jerry.
-Hey, Mr. Sullivan.
-Guys, I told you, call me Sulley.
-I don't think so.
-We want to wish you good luck today.
Hey, hey, get lost, you two.
You're making him lose his focus.
-Sorry.
-See you later, fellas.
Go get 'em, Mr. Sullivan.
Quiet.
You're making him lose his focus.
-Oh, no. Sorry!
-Shut up!
Monsters, Inc. Please hold.
Monsters, Inc. I'll connect you.
Miss Fearmonger is on vacation.
Would you like her voicemail?
-Schmoopsie-pooh.
-Googly bear.
-Happy birthday.
-Googly-woogly, you remembered.
-Hey, Sulley-wulley.
-Hey, Celia-wheelia.
-Happy birthday.
-Thanks.
So are we going
anywhere special tonight?
I just got us into a little place
called Harryhausen's.
Harryhausen's? But it's impossible
to get a reservation there.
Not for googly bear.
I will see you at quittin' time.
-Not a minute later.
-OK, sweetheart.
Think romantical thoughts.
You and me
Me and you
Both of us together
You know, pal, she's the one.
-That's it. She is the one.
-I'm happy for you.
Thanks for hooking me up
with those reservations.
They're under the name "googly bear."
Good. . .
You know, that wasn't very funny.
-What the. . .
-Wazowski.
What do you know?
It scares little kids
and little monsters.
I wasn't scared.
I have allergies.
-Sure.
-Randall, save it for the scare floor.
I'm in the zone today, Sullivan.
Gonna do serious scaring.
-Putting up some big numbers.
-Randall, that's great.
That should make it more humiliating
when we break the record first.
Do you hear that?
It's the winds of change.
"You hear that? It's the winds of. . ."
What a creep.
One of these days I am really
gonna let you
teach that guy a lesson.
Chalooby. Baby.
Good morning, Roz,
my succulent garden snail.
-Who would we be scaring today?
-Wazowski.
You didn't file your paperwork
last night.
Oh, that darn paperwork.
Wouldn't it be easier
if it all just blew away?
Don't let it happen again.
Yes. Well, I'll try to be less careless.
I'm watching you, Wazowski.
Always watching.
-She's nuts.
-Always.
All scare floors are now active.
Assistants, please report
to your stations.
OK, people,
Eastern Seaboard coming online.
We got scarers coming out.
They are so awesome.
Hey, may the best monster win.
I plan to.
We are on in seven, six, five,
four, three, two. . .
You're the boss.
You're the big hairy boss.
I'm feeling good today, Mikey.
Attaboy. Another door coming right up.
You're still behind, Randall.
-Maybe I should realign the scream. . .
-Get me a door.
Door, yes, door.
Well, Jerry, what's the damage so far?
We may actually
make our quota today, sir.
First time in a month.
-What happened?
-The kid almost touched me.
-She got this close to me.
-She wasn't scared of you?
-She was only six.
-I could have been dead.
-I could have died.
-Keep it together, man.
Hey, we got a dead door over here.
-I'm coming.
-Look out.
Excuse us.
We've lost 58 doors this week, sir.
Kids these days.
They just don't get scared
like they used to.
Let her rip.
-Sir?
-What?
Look.
Attention.
We have a new scare leader.
Randall Boggs.
Look at those numbers.
Slumber party.
Never mind.
Hey, watch it.
Well, James,
that was an impressive display.
Just doing my job, Mr. Waternoose.
'Course I did learn from the best.
If I don't see a new door
in my station in five seconds,
I will personally
put you through the shredder.
Hey, Wazowski, nice job.
Those numbers are pretty sweet.
Are they?
You know, I hadn't even noticed.
-And how's Georgie doing?
-He's doing great.
I love working with that big guy.
Keep the doors coming.
I'm on a roll today.
George and I are like brothers. 231 9!
We have a 231 9!
Red alert.
Red alert, red alert.
-Red alert.
-George Sanderson.
Please remain motionless.
Prepare for decontamination.
Duck and cover, people!
Not the CDA.
-Go, go, go.
-Coming through. Stand aside.
Clear the contaminated area.
-A 231 9 in progress.
-Coming through. Watch yourself.
Stand back. Careful.
All clear. Situation is
niner-niner-zero. Ready for decon.
-Thanks, guys, that was a close one.
-OK.
Take a break. We gotta shut down
and reset the system.
An entire scare floor out of commission.
What else can go wrong?
-What a day.
-We're just going through a rough time.
Everyone knows
you'll get us through it.
Tell that to the board of directors.
James, this company's been
in my family for three generations.
I would do anything
to keep it from going under.
So would I, sir.
-I could use your help with something.
-Anything, sir.
We've hired some new scare recruits,
and frankly, they're. . .
-Inexperienced?
-They stink.
I thought maybe
you might come by tomorrow
and give them a demonstration.
Show them what it takes
to be our top scarer.
I'll start out with the old
Waternoose jump and growl.
Now that's my boy.
Let's go, everybody.
All doors must be returned.
No exceptions.
I've never seen anything like you today.
You were on a roll.
Another day like this
and that scare record's in the bag.
That's right, baby.
As if dinner wasn't enough,
I'm taking her to a monster truck rally.
-Nice.
-What's on your agenda?
-Work out some more.
-Again?
There's more to life than scaring.
-Can I borrow your odorant?
-I got smelly garbage or old dumpster.
You got low tide?
How about wet dog?
Yep. Stink it up.
I am so romantic sometimes
I think I should marry myself.
-Give me a break.
-What a night of romance ahead of me.
Tonight is about me and Celia.
The love boat is about to set sail.
I gotta tell you, that face of hers,
it just makes my heart go. . .
Hello, Wazowski.
Fun-filled evening planned for tonight?
Well, as a matter of fact. . .
I'm sure you filed
your paperwork correctly,
for once.
Your stunned silence
is very reassuring.
My scare reports.
I left them on my desk.
If I'm not at the restaurant in five
minutes they'll give our table away.
-Schmoopsie-pooh.
-Googly bear.
-Want to get going?
-Do I ever. It's just. . .
-What?
-It. . .
-A small. . .
-I don't understand.
I forgot about some paperwork
I was supposed to file.
Mike was reminding me.
-Thanks, buddy.
-I was?
I mean, I was. Yeah.
-OK. Let's go.
-We're going.
The pink copies to accounting.
The fuchsia ones go to purchasing
and the goldenrod ones go to Roz.
Leave the puce.
Pink copies to accounting,
fuchsia ones to Roz.
The fuchsia ones go to purchasing.
The goldenrod ones go to Roz.
Man, I have no idea what puce is.
Oh, that's puce.
Hello?
Anyone? There's a door here.
Hello? Hey.
Anybody scaring in here?
Hello. Yo.
Kitty.
No, no, stay back.
Hold it, hold it.
Michael, I've had a lot of birthdays. . .
Well, not a lot of birthdays.
But this is the best birthday ever.
What are you looking at?
I was just thinking about
the first time I laid eye on you,
-how pretty you looked.
-Stop it.
-Your hair was shorter.
-I'm thinking about getting it cut.
No, no, I like it this length.
I like everything about you.
Just the other day someone asked
who was the most beautiful monster.
-You know what I said?
-What did you say?
I said. . .
-Sulley?
No, no, that's not what
I was gonna say.
You're not making sense.
-He's handsome. He's rugged.
-What a coincidence, running into you.
-I'm just gonna order something.
-Michael.
-What's good?
-You're ruining everything.
I went to get your paperwork
and there was a door.
What?
-A door?
-Randall was in it.
Randall? That cheater.
He's trying to boost his numbers.
-There's something else.
-What?
Ooklay in the agbay.
-Look in the bag.
What bag?
They don't have anything
I like here. Take care, Celia.
-What's going on?
-Celia, please try to understand.
-I have to do something !
-Michael?
On three. One, two. . .
-A kid !
-Boo!
A kid !
There's a kid here.
A human kid !
Googly bear!
Come on.
Let's get out of here.
Please remain calm.
This is not a drill.
7835 in progress, please advise.
-Michael? Michael !
-Celia!
-Come with me.
-Stop pushing.
Get your hands off
my schmoopsie-pooh.
Ready for decontamination.
I don't think that date
could have gone any worse.
lf witnesses are to be believed,
there has been a child security breach
for the first time in monster history.
We neither confirm nor deny
the presence of a human child here.
Well. a kid flew right over me and
blasted a car with its laser vision.
l tried to run. but it picked me up
with its mind powers
and shook me like a doll.
It's true.
l saw the whole thing.
It is my professional opinion
that now is the time to panic.
It's coming. It's coming !
Boo!
No, no, no, no!
Come here, kid.
Don't touch those, you little. . .
Those were alphabetized.
It's OK.
As long as it doesn't come near us
we're gonna be OK.
You like this? Fetch.
Hey, hey. That's it.
No one touches Little Mikey.
Mike, give her the bear.
Oh, no!
Make it stop, Sulley.
Make it stop!
Here, look. See bear?
Nice bear.
Sulley!
Bear, he's a happy bear.
He's not crying, neither should you.
We'll be in trouble
'cause they're gonna find us,
so please stop crying now.
Good. Good, Sulley. Keep it up.
You're doing great.
He's a happy bear.
He has no. . .
-It touched me.
-Sulley, the bear!
The bear. Give her the. . .
What was that?
l have no idea, but it would be
really great if it didn't do it again.
How could I do this?
How could I be so stupid?
-This could destroy the company.
-Who cares about the company?
What about us?
That thing is a killing machine.
It's waiting for us to fall asleep
and then wham !
We're easy prey, my friend.
We're sitting targets.
OK, look, I think I have a plan here.
Using mainly spoons,
we dig a tunnel under the city
and release it into the wild.
Spoons.
That's it. I'm out of ideas.
Air balloon, too expensive.
Giant slingshot, too conspicuous.
Enormous wooden horse, too Greek.
No. Can't think. Can't think.
-Flatliner. Flatlining.
-Mike?
I think she's getting tired.
Well, then why don't you
find someplace for it to sleep
while I think of a plan !
Are you sleepy? Wanna sleep?
Is that what you want?
OK. I'll make a nice little area
for you to. . .
No. Hey, that's my bed.
You're gonna get your germs all over it.
Fine.
My chair's more comfortable anyway.
What?
It's just a closet.
Will you go to sleep?
Hey, that looks like Randall.
Randall's your monster.
You think he's gonna
come through the closet and scare you.
Oh, boy, how do I explain this?
It's empty.
See?
No monster in here.
Well, now there is.
But I'm not gonna scare you.
I'm off duty.
OK.
How about I sit here
until you fall asleep?
Go ahead. Go to sleep.
Now. Now go.
You go to sleep.
Mike, this might sound crazy,
but I don't think that kid's dangerous.
Really? Well, in that case,
let's keep it.
I always wanted a pet
that could kill me!
What if we just
put her back in her door?
-What?
-Mike, think about it.
We send her back,
everything goes back to normal.
Is that a joke?
Tell me you're joking.
Sulley, I think that given
the circumstance
I've been extremely forgiving till now.
But that is a horrible idea.
Are we gonna march in public
with that thing?
Then I guess we waltz
right up to the factory, right?
I can't believe we are waltzing
right up to the factory.
Sulley, a mop, a couple of lights
and some chair fabric
are not gonna fool anyone.
Think about names.
Loch Ness. Bigfoot.
The Abominable Snowman.
They all got one thing in common.
Banishment!
-We could be next.
-Don't panic. We can do this.
-How you doing, Frank?
-Hey, guys.
Everything's going to be OK.
Number one wants this
dusted for prints.
-Careful with that.
-l got a good view.
A little lower.
This was recovered at the scene.
-Don't panic.
-Don't tell me not to.
-Keep it together.
-It's not OK.
-Boo.
-Could be contaminated.
Gentlemen, safety
is our number-one concern.
If there's anything that. . .
Not now. I'm. . .
Oh, hello, little one.
-Where did you come from?
-Mr. Waternoose!
James, is this one yours?
Actually, that's my cousin's sister's
-daughter, sir.
-Yeah, it's. . .
Bring an Obscure Relative
to Work Day.
Must have missed the memo.
Well, listen, James,
why don't you stop by the simulator
after lunch
and give us that scare demonstration?
Yeah. Oh, sir. . .
-Mr. Waternoose?
-Yes, yes. I'm coming.
I'll see you this afternoon, James.
That is, if these gentlemen
haven't shut us down.
-Oh, boy.
-A scare demo.
That is great.
Why am I the last to know?
We could bring your cousin's sister's
daughter. She'll be a big hit.
Halt.
Hold him down.
Come on. The coast is clear.
OK. All we have to do
is get rid of that thing.
So wait here while I get its card.
She can't stay here.
This is the men's room.
That is the weirdest thing
you've ever said.
Look. It loves it here.
It's dancing with joy.
I'll be right back with its door key.
That's a cute little dance.
It almost looks like you've got to. . .
Are you done in there?
Sorry, sorry.
OK. You're finished now, right?
Hello?
Boo.
Where did she go?
Did she disappear?
Did she turn invisible?
I just have no idea.
Gotcha.
Boo.
Hey, you're good.
Be relaxed. Be relaxed. Be relaxed.
Roz, my tender oozing blossom.
You're looking fabulous today.
Is that a new haircut?
Tell me, it's a new haircut.
New makeup. You had a lift.
You had a tuck. You had something.
Something has been inserted in
your skin that makes you look like. . .
I need a favor. Randall was working
late last night on the scare floor.
I need the key
for the door he was using.
Well, isn't that nice?
But guess what? You didn't turn in
your paperwork last night.
He didn't. . . No paperwork?
This office is now closed.
Ready or not, here I come.
I'm getting warmer.
Any second now.
-Fee, fi, fo. . .
-What are you doing?
I'm looking for the kid.
-You lost it?
-No, no. She was just. . .
Here she is.
Hey. What's the matter?
-I already told your buddies. . .
-All right. Carry on.
Randall. Thank goodness.
What are we gonna do about the child?
It's on the front page.
The child. The one you were after.
Be quiet. Don't you think
I'm aware of the situation?
I was up all night trying to find it.
I did a calculation factoring in
the size of the sushi restaurant.
The child may have escaped !
Until we know for sure
we're gonna act like nothing happened.
Get the machine running.
I'll take care of the kid.
When I find whoever let it out,
they're dead.
Why are you still here?
Come on, go! Move! Now!
I'm not here.
They're gone.
This is bad, so very bad.
What were they talking about,
machine?
Who cares?
All we have to do
is call her door and send her home.
Right. We're just two regular Joes
on our way to work.
We will blend right in.
-Top of the morning.
-What's shakin', bacon?
Did you lose weight?
Or a limb?
-You have her card key, right?
-Of course.
I told you I'd get her card key.
I went and got it.
Now I have her card key.
OK. Here we go.
Take care of yourself. Try not to
run through any more closets.
-Mike, that's not her door.
-Of course it's her door.
No. Her door was white
and it had flowers on it.
It must have been dark last night
because this is its door.
Hey, you hear that?
Sounds like fun in there.
Send me a postcard, kid.
That's Mike Wazowski, care of
22 Mike Wazowski,
you-got-your-life-back Lane.
Very good. Now bon voyage.
Bye-bye. Look at the stick.
See the stick? Go get the stick.
-Go fetch.
-Mike, this isn't Boo's door.
-Boo? What's Boo?
-That's what I decided to call her.
There a problem?
Sulley, you're not supposed to name it.
Once you name it,
you start getting attached to it.
Now put that thing back
where it came from, or so help me. . .
Hey. We're rehearsing a scene for
the upcoming company play called. . .
Put That Thing Back
Where It Came From or So Help Me.
It's a musical.
Put that thing back
where it came from or so help me
So help me. so help me
And cut.
We're still working on it.
It's in progress, but we need ushers.
Sulley, I've had enough.
Say goodbye to. . . Where did it go?
-Where is she?
-She got away from you again?
Well, that is just. . .
Wait a minute. The sun is coming up.
This is perfect.
She's gone!
Where are you going?
Sulley, don't blow this.
We're so close to breaking the record.
Somebody will find the kid.
It'll be their problem.
She's out of our hair!
-What are you two doing?
-They're rehearsing a play.
She's out of our hair
Can it! So, what do you think
of that kid getting out, Sullivan?
-Pretty crazy?
-Oh, yeah, crazy.
Word is the kid's been traced
to this factory.
-You haven't seen anything?
-Well. . .
No. No way.
But if it was an inside job,
I'd put my money on Waxford.
-Waxford?
-The one at station six.
-He's got them shifty eyes.
-Hey, Waxford.
-Sulley!
-Michael Wazowski !
Last night was one of the worst nights
of my entire life, bar none!
-I thought you cared about me.
-Honey, please.
-I thought you liked sushi.
-Sushi ! Sushi !
You think this is about sushi?
Wazowski.
Michael !
Men.
Breathe. Keep breathing.
-Where's the kid?
-Kid?
-What kid?
-It's here in the factory, isn't it?
It never would have gotten out
if you hadn't been cheating last night.
Cheating? Cheating. Right.
OK. I think I know
how to make this all go away.
What happens when the whistle blows
in five minutes?
-I get a timeout?
-Everyone goes to lunch.
Which means the scare floor will be. . .
-Painted?
-Empty.
It'll be empty, you idiot.
You see that clock?
When the big hand is pointing up
and the little hand is pointing up,
the kid's door will be in my station.
But when the big hand points down,
the door will be gone.
You have until then to put the kid back.
Get the picture?
Boo!
-No.
-Hey. you. Halt.
He's the one.
-The one from the commercial.
-That's him.
-Can we get an autograph?
-Oh, sure. No problem.
Make that out to Stephanie.
my daughter.
Yes. Let's see.
"From your scary friend.
Best wishes. . ."
So, then I said, "If you talk to me
like that again, we're through".
-What'd she say?
-You know my mom.
-She sent me to my room.
-See you guys later. Take it easy.
Bottoms up.
Boo!
Hi.
Well, hello, there.
What's your name?
Mike Wazowski.
Sulley!
Oh, Sulley.
OK, Sulley, come on.
Hey! You guys seen Sulley anywhere?
-Nope, sorry.
-Sulley!
Boy, Wazowski
looks like he's in trouble.
231 9! We have a 231 9!
Oh, dear.
Sulley!
Sulley. Great news, pal.
I got us a way out of this mess,
but we gotta hurry.
Where is it?
Sull, that's a cube of garbage.
I can still hear her little voice.
-Mike Wazowski.
-I can hear it too.
-Mike Wazowski !
-How many kids you got in there?
Mike Wazowski !
-Kitty!
-Boo!
Boo, you're all right.
I was so worried. I was. . .
Don't you ever
run away from me again, young lady.
But I'm so glad you're safe.
My, what an affectionate father.
Actually, she's my cousin's sister's. . .
-That's enough. Let's go.
-Mike Wazowski.
Yeah. Step aside, kid.
We're in a. . .
-Will you stop making Boo laugh?
-I didn't. Come on.
I still don't understand.
You got Boo's door?
I'll explain later. Run.
Let's move, let's move. Come on.
Please be there. Please be there.
-There it is, just like Randall said.
-Randall?
Wait a minute. Boo, hey.
One, two, three, four,
get the kid through the door.
-The nightmare is over.
-It's OK, Boo. What's the matter?
-It's time to move.
-Mike, what are you thinking?
-Randall's after Boo.
-Who cares? Let's go.
-This is a limited-time offer.
-No. I don't like this.
Sulley, you wanted her door
and there it is.
-Now let's move.
-No, Mike.
You want me to prove
everything's on the up and up?
-He wants a door, I get a door.
-Wait.
Paranoid delusional furball.
Mike!
Hey, Sulley, where you been all day?
Sulley? Sulley!
Mike? Mike?
Where are you?
Are you in there?
Where are you, buddy?
Mike?
Where are you?
Boo, way to go.
It's OK.
Randall, did you have to. . .
-Yes! I got the kid.
-Oh, huzzah !
-Great news. Not that I was concerned.
-Get over here and help me.
Come on, while we're young here,
Fungus.
The kid needs to take off a few pounds.
Wazowski ! Where is it,
you little one-eyed cretin?
It's cretin. If you're gonna
threaten me, do it properly.
Second, you're nuts if you think
kidnapping me
is gonna help you cheat!
You still think this is about
that stupid scare record?
Well, I did.
Right up until you chuckled like that.
Now I think I should get out of here.
I'm about to revolutionize
the scaring industry.
When I do,
even the great James P. Sullivan
is gonna be working for me.
Well, somebody's certainly
been a busy bee.
First I need to know where the kid is
and you're gonna tell me.
-I don't know.
-Sure.
I don't. I don't.
What's that? Wait.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
Come on. No, no.
Come on. Hey, hey.
Hey, hey. This thing is moving.
I don't like big moving things
that are moving towards me.
No. Come on. Hey!
-Randall !
-Say hello to the scream extractor.
Hello.
Where you going?
We'll talk. We'll have a latte.
Come on. We can talk about this.
What is that thing?
Wait, wait, wait.
No, no, no.
No. Come on.
Help. Help! Help, help!
For. . . What did you do wrong this time?
-I don't know. I calibrated the. . .
-Go check the machine.
There must be something wrong
with the scream intake valve.
Fungus? Fungus? You like cars?
I got a really nice car. If you
let me go, I'll give you a ride
in the car.
Please, Fungus.
I'm sorry, Wazowski,
but Randall said I'm not allowed
to fraternize with victims
of his evil plot.
What happened?
Where's Wazowski?
Where is he?
-Come on.
-This is crazy. He's gonna kill us.
That could be contaminated.
We gotta get out of here now!
We could start a new life far away.
Goodbye, Monsters, Inc.
Goodbye, Mr. Waternoose.
-No, Mike, wait.
-Hey, what are you doing?
-Follow me. I have an idea.
-No, no, no, no, no.
-Simulation terminated.
What was that? You're trying
to scare the kid, not lull it to sleep.
I was going for a snake/ninja approach
with a little hissing.
How many times do I have to tell you?
It's all about presence.
-About how you enter the room.
-Mr. Waternoose!
James, perfect timing.
No, no, sir. You don't understand.
-Show these monsters how it's done.
-I can't.
-Sir, you have to listen to me.
-Pay attention.
You're about to see
the best in the business.
-Reset the simulator.
-But sir!
-Good night, sweetheart.
-'Night, Mom.
-Kitty!
-No, Boo, no!
-Give us a big loud roar.
-There's no time for this!
-What are you waiting for? Roar.
-But, sir. . .
Roar!
Well done. Well done, James.
-Boo?
-All right, gentlemen.
-Right this way.
-I hope you've learned a lesson today.
Boo.
Boo, it's me.
-The child !
-Sir, she isn't toxic.
-It sounds crazy, but trust me.
-Boo?
No, no, no, no, it's OK.
I was just. . . No.
No, don't be scared.
That wasn't real.
It's just a. . . I was just. . .
-Boo.
-. . .test it out on that sweet girl.
-. . .have her, he is trying to kill us.
-This is Randall's fault.
-Randall?
We can take you to his secret lab
in this factory.
How could this happen?
Does anyone else know about this?
-No, sir.
-Good.
This company can't afford
any more bad publicity.
Now, before we do anything else,
let's take care of the child.
I never thought
things would come to this.
Not in my factory.
I'm sorry you boys got mixed up in this.
Especially you, James.
But now we can
set everything straight again.
For the good of the company.
Sir? That's not her door.
I know, I know.
It's yours.
No!
Boo!
No! No! No, no, no, no!
It's too late.
We're banished, genius!
We're in the human world.
What a great idea,
going to your old pal Waternoose.
Too bad he was in on the whole thing.
All you had to do was listen to me.
Just once!
But you didn't, did you?
You're still not listening !
Take that!
Welcome to the Himalayas.
Abominable. Can you believe that?
Do I look abominable to you?
Why can't they call me
the Adorable Snowman
or the Agreeable Snowman,
for crying out loud?
I'm a nice guy.
Snow cone?
No, don't worry. It's lemon.
How about you, big fella?
Snow cone?
Did you see the way she looked at me?
Poor guy. I understand.
It ain't easy being banished.
Take my buddy, Bigfoot.
When he was banished, he fashioned
an enormous diaper out of poison ivy.
Wore it on his head like a tiara.
Called himself King Itchy.
It won't be so hard for you guys.
How lucky can you get?
-Banished with your best friend.
-He is not my friend.
I just assumed you were buddies.
When I saw you in the snow hugging. . .
Look at that big jerk.
Ruined my life. And for what?
A stupid kid !
Because of you I am now stuck
in this frozen wasteland.
Wasteland?
I think you mean wonderland.
How about all this fabulous snow?
And wait till you see
the local village.
Cutest thing in the world.
I haven't mentioned the free yaks' milk.
-What did you say?
-Yaks' milk.
Milking a yak ain't exactly a picnic.
Once you pick the hairs out
it's nutritious.
No, about a village.
Are there kids in it?
Kids? Sure. Tough kids, sissy kids,
kids who climb on rocks.
-Where is it?
-At the bottom of the mountain.
-A three-day hike.
-Three days?
We need to get there now.
You wanna go to the village?
Rule number one out here,
always. . . No.
Never go out in a blizzard.
We need to get to Boo.
Boo? What about us?
Ever since the kid came in,
you've ignored everything I've said,
and now look where we are!
We were about to break the record.
-We would have had it made.
-None of that matters now.
None of it matters?
Wait a second.
OK. No, good. Great.
So now the truth comes out, doesn't it?
Would you look at that?
We're out of snow cones.
Let me just go outside
and make some more.
Sulley, what about everything
we ever worked for?
Does that matter?
What about Celia?
I am never. . .
Never gonna see her again.
Doesn't that matter?
And what about me?
I'm your pal. I'm your best friend.
Don't I matter?
I'm sorry, Mike.
I'm sorry we're stuck out here.
I didn't mean for this to happen.
But Boo's in trouble.
I think there might be
a way to save her if we can just get. . .
We? Whoa. We?
No. There's no "we" this time, pal.
If you want to go out there
and freeze to death,
you be my guest.
Because you're on your own.
Hey, I got more snow cones!
Come on, George.
I know you can do this.
I picked out an easy door for you.
In Nepal. Nice, quiet Nepal.
You know, you're right.
Here. Take this.
Go get 'em, Georgie.
Look out. Coming through.
-Sorry, George.
-Hey, you can't just. . .
Twenty-three. . .
Out of the way!
Finally. I never should have
trusted you with this.
Because of you,
I had to banish my top scarer.
With this machine,
we won't need scarers.
Sullivan got what he deserved.
Sullivan was twice the scarer
you will ever be.
Kitty!
-Kitty!
-Sullivan?
-Sorry, Boo.
Stop him !
Let's get you home.
Finish him off!
You don't know how long
I've wanted to do that, Sullivan.
Mike?
-It's not that I don't care.
-Mike, you don't understand.
Yes, I do.
I was just mad, that's all.
I needed some time to think, but
you shouldn't have left me out there.
-I'm being attacked.
-I'm not attacking you.
I'm trying to be honest. Hear me out.
You and I are a team.
Nothing is more important
than our friendship.
I know. He's too sensitive.
Come on, pal.
If you start crying, I'm gonna cry.
And I'll never get through this.
I'm sorry I wasn't there for you,
but I am now.
Sulley, I am baring my soul here.
The least you can do is pay attention.
Look at that. It's Randall.
Come on.
Get up. There can't be any witnesses.
There won't be.
I'm glad you came back, Mike.
Somebody's gotta take care of you,
you big hairball.
-Schmoopsie-pooh, I can't talk.
-Come on.
Michael, if you don't tell me what's
going on right now, we are through !
Here's the truth.
The kid? Sulley let her in. We tried to
send her back, Waternoose had a plot,
and now Randall's trying to kill us!
You expect me to believe
that pack of lies, Mike Wazowski?
Mike Wazowski.
I love you, schmoopsie-pooh !
-Hey!
-Idiots.
Look out. Coming through.
Make way. Move it.
Hurry up, hurry up.
-There they are.
-Attention. employees.
Randall Boggs has just broken
the all-time scare record.
No, I didn't.
Get out of my way.
Go get 'em, googly bear.
There it is.
Get off my tail. Let go.
-What are you doing?
-Grab on, Mike.
Are you out of your mind?
-Sulley, what are we doing?
-Get Boo's door and find a station.
What a plan.
Simple, yet insane.
-Whoa.
-Oh, boy.
Hold on !
Don't look down !
I'm gonna be sick.
Oh, no.
No!
-Boo's door.
-There it is.
How are we supposed to get to it now?
It's a dead end, Sulley.
-There he is.
-Make her laugh.
-Sulley!
-Just do it!
-Get it open.
-Here he comes.
Give me that kid.
-Why couldn't we get banished here?
-We gotta find another door.
Look! Boo's door.
-There he is. Hurry up!
-Give me your hand.
-Come on, it slides.
-Right. Right.
Jump. I'm right behind you.
Come on.
Hurry up. Keep moving !
Get inside.
That was weird.
Mike?
-Sorry, buddy.
-OK.
I hope that hurt, lizard boy.
Great job, buddy. We lost him.
Boo!
No!
Nice working with you.
-Get it open !
-I'm trying !
-Open the door!
-Come on, get in here.
Boo!
There they are!
Sulley, what are you doing?
Sulley!
-Looks like we caught the express.
-Do you see them?
Straight ahead.
-Kitty.
-Boo.
Look at everybody's
favorite scarer now.
You stupid, pathetic waste.
You've been number one for too long,
Sullivan. Now your time is up.
And don't worry.
I'll take good care of the kid.
No!
She's not scared of you anymore.
Looks like you're out of a job.
OK, over the plate.
Let's see the old stuff.
Chuck him, baby.
Here's the pitch and he is out of here.
-Mama, another gator got in the house.
-Another gator?
Give me that shovel. There!
Get him, Mama. Get that gator.
-Care to do the honors, Mikey?
-With pleasure.
That's right, Boo. You did it.
You beat him.
Come on.
OK, Boo, it's time to go home.
Take care of yourself
and be a good girl, OK?
-Oh, no.
-The power's out. Make her laugh.
I got a move here
that'll bring down the house.
-Sorry. She didn't see that.
-What?
What, did you forget to check
if her hood was up, you big dope?
Uncle Mike, try not to yell
in front of her.
-You know we need her to laugh.
-Right.
Hey, Boo. Just kidding. Look.
Funny, right? See, with the. . .
These are the jokes, kid.
What's happening?
Hold on.
When the door lands in the station,
cut the power.
You'll have the child and the criminals
responsible for this whole mess.
Great. A welcoming committee.
What are we gonna do?
This is the CDA. Come out slowly
with the child in plain sight.
OK, OK, you got us.
Here we are. Here's the kid.
I'll cooperate, but before you
take us away, I have one thing to say.
-Catch.
-231 9.
We have a toxic projectile.
-After the suspect.
-Stop him !
-Come on.
-Don't let them get away.
Wait. Come back.
He has the child.
Sullivan. Sullivan !
Give me the child. Give her to me!
Open this door.
Open this door!
Stop it.
Don't do it.
-Come on.
-Don't go in that room.
I think we stopped him, Boo.
You're safe now.
You be a good girl, OK?
-This has gone far enough, James.
-She's home. Leave her alone.
I can't do that. She's seen too much.
-You both have.
-It doesn't have to be this way.
I have no choice. Times have changed.
-Scaring isn't enough anymore.
-But kidnapping?
I'll kidnap 1 ,000 children
before I let the company die.
And I'll silence anyone
who gets in my way!
No!
-Night, Mom.
-Night, sweetheart.
-What is this?
Simulation terminated.
Well, I don't know
about the rest of you guys,
but I spotted several big mistakes.
But how did. . .
You know what? Let's watch
my favorite part again. Shall we?
l'll kidnap 1 .000 children
before l let this company die.
-Come with us.
-What are you doing?
Take your hands off.
You can't arrest me.
I hope you're happy, Sullivan.
You destroyed this company.
Monsters, Incorporated is dead !
Where will everyone get their scream?
The energy crisis will only get worse
because of you !
Stay where you are.
Number one wants to talk to you.
Attention.
Hello, boys.
-Roz?
Two and a half years of
undercover work were almost wasted
when you intercepted that child,
Mr. Sullivan.
Of course, without your help,
I never would have known that
this went all the way up to Waternoose.
Now, about the girl.
I just want to send her home.
Very good.
-Bring me a door shredder.
-What? You mean. . .
You mean I can't see her again?
That's the way it has to be.
I'll give you five minutes.
-Well, so long, kid.
-Mike Wazowski.
Yeah.
Boo.
It's been fun.
Go ahead. Go grow up.
But, Boo. . .
Boo.
Look at that. You know. . .
That's cute. Yeah.
Boo. . .
Well, that's very nice.
Come here, you !
Oh. he's a happy bear
Nothing's coming out of your closet
to scare you anymore, right?
Yeah.
Goodbye, Boo.
Kitty.
Kitty has to go.
Boo.
Kitty?
None of this ever happened,
gentlemen.
And I don't want to see
any paperwork on this.
Take him away.
I bet we get the rest of the day off.
You idiot.
They're gonna shut down the factory.
When that wall went up, you should
have seen Waternoose's face.
I hope we get a copy of that tape.
Are you all right?
Come on, pal.
Cheer up. We did it!
We got Boo home.
Sure, we put the factory
in the toilet and
hundreds of people
will be out of work.
Not to mention the mob that will
come after us when there's no power,
but at least we had some laughs, right?
Laughs.
ls this thing on?
Hello? Hello? Testing.
Good evening. Nice to see you.
lt's great to be here in your room.
Where are you from?
You're in kindergarten. right?
l love kindergarten.
Best three years of my life.
Of my life.
But l love sports.
Dodgeball was the best.
l was the fastest one out there.
Of course. l was the ball.
l was the ball, see...
All right.
Thanks a lot.
I'll be here all week.
Remember to tip your waitresses.
Great job, Mikey. You filled your quota
on the first kid of the day.
Not bad. Only somebody
with perfect comedic timing
could produce this much energy
in one shot.
And the fact that laughter
is ten times more powerful than scream
had nothing to do with it?
Googly bear, come here, you.
-Schmoopsie-pooh !
-Googly.
Girls, stop, stop, stop.
Michael, you're such a charmer.
-Did you bring the magazine?
-A whole box.
Let me see it!
Sulley and I made the cover, right?
I don't believe it!
Googly bear.
I'm on the cover of a magazine!
This is great.
-Hey, Sulley.
-Hey, Mike.
-I was. . .
-There's something I want to show you.
Close your eyes. Follow me.
Come on. No peeking.
Keep coming, keep coming.
-Come on.
-Mike!
Follow the sultry sound of my voice.
OK, stop.
Open 'em.
Mike, is that. . .
Sorry it took so long, pal.
There was a lot of wood to go through.
It only works if you have every piece.
Boo?