Provided by SilverStark & explosiveskull
https://www.instagram.com/vishal_sahani21
Someone needs to stop Clearway Law.
Public shouldn't leave reviews for lawyers.
Check it's tight.
Close your hand.
That feel good?
- Good.
- Yeah.
You made it.
Always rely on Cole Young,
human punching bag.
Who am I fighting?
Fighting? No, no, no, Cole.
Fighting requires
both attacking and defending,
not just throwing punches.
You should try it sometime.
All right,
don't get sensitive.
You're fightin' Ramirez.
Yeah, he's experienced, fast.
Good fighter.
Who's your cornerman?
What? You're fucking serious?
You don't like it,
find someone else
who will do this
in an hour's notice for $200.
You sticking around
for this one'?
You know I don't
watch him fight anymore.
Yeah, well...
Give the people
a good show, huh?
Or they won't
stick around either.
Throw your uppercut.
You got him.
That's it.
No! Get up!
Take control!
Come on!
Don't tap out.
It's done! Done!
- Back it up, Eddie.
- Yes!
The prophecy is upon us
which means we could lose
the tenth tournament.
There is no prophecy.
Hanzo is a ghost.
I killed him centuries ago.
Winning Mortal Kombat
can not be left to chance.
There will be no tournament
because there will be
no opposition left to fight.
We will already be victorious.
Go now and kill
Earthrealm's champions...
Bi-Han.
I am no longer Bi-Han.
I am Sub-Zero.
Cole!
I am your blood.
Damn, Young.
- Hell of a fight, man.
- Yeah, you too.
- Respect you.
- A'ight.
Ready to go?
In a sec.
What you got there?
It's a strength bracelet.
- Just made this?
- Yeah.
That's pretty cool.
You want me to put it on?
My hand.
Now we got one each.
You're sure you're okay?
Yeah. I guess I should have
thrown the uppercut, huh?
Cole Young.
The man that took the belt
from Eddie Tobias.
Yeah, that was a long time ago.
Have we met?
No.
Name's Jax.
Nice to meet you, Jax.
Could've won today.
Had you controlled the cage.
Told you so.
She's smart.
All right.
Well, time to go eat, yeah?
One more thing, champ.
That dragon logo you got,
I dig that, man.
It's unique.
Where'd you get it from?
He was born with it.
- What do you mean?
- It's a birthmark.
You serious?
Pretty cool.
Show him.
Well, ain't that something?
Nice chatting with you.
See you around, champ.
- Hey.
- Hi, Mom.
Still in one piece.
How'd it go?
He was this close
to beating him.
- This close?
- Close.
You sure you're okay?
Standing.
- Let's go order.
- Yeah.
Got my eyes on him
right now.
He's got the mark,
I saw it.
He's with his family.
Ally, come take a look at this.
It's snowing.
But it's July.
- Emily!
Stay calm, stay calm!
Get in the truck, Cole! Now!
Get in the car!
Come on, come on! Let's go!
- Move, move, move!
- Go, go, go!
Blade, I got him.
I'll see you at base at 2300.
What the fuck is that thing?
Funny, that didn't
sound much like,
"Thanks for saving my ass."
Whatever that was back there,
it's after both of us. Look.
That's... That's impossible.
It's not a birthmark, Cole.
Means you've been chosen.
Chosen? For what?
To fight.
You got the wrong person,
all right'?
I'm not the fighter
that I used to be, okay?
No shit. But they don't have
the marking.
So, like it or not, Cole,
you're the guy.
And as long as you got
that marking,
they're coming for you.
And they will kill whoever
they have to to get to you.
Take the truck.
Get your family to safety.
Cole.
You need to get to Gary,
Indiana. Find Sonya Blade.
806 West Washington Boulevard.
Are you sure?
We can take him out together.
You want your family on
a fucking slab in the morgue?
Now, get out of here.
Hold on tight, guys.
So, you wanna play
hide- and-seek?
I've done six tours,
motherfucker.
She's finally asleep.
I should go.
You'll be safe here, Ally.
You heard what Jax said.
That thing is hunting people
with the marking.
It's after me.
And if I stay here
and it shows up,
it could kill us all.
I'm not gonna let that happen.
Jax could have killed it.
We have to be sure.
The name he gave me.
Sonya Blade.
Hopefully,
she'll have some answers.
Master.
Sub-Zero tracked and killed
another one
of Earth's champions.
But another has escaped.
Have our assassins
double their efforts.
What of Lord Raiden?
If he discovers
we're breaking rules
set in stone
by the Elder Gods...
Leave the Elder Gods to me.
We didn't win
nine straight tournaments
by following the rules.
Mileena, let's finish this.
Send in the reptilian Syzoth.
What are you doing here?
Wait. I'm looking
for Sonya Blade. Jax sent me.
Where is it?
Where's what?
The marking.
I'm Sonya.
Jax hasn't checked in.
Where is he?
He stayed behind to fight.
Close the door.
Jax, where are you?
Come on.
You guys are military?
Special Forces.
What is this?
We needed a safe place
to run our operation.
Well, this looks, uh,
pretty safe.
Looks like you're ready
for anything.
This is where we keep
all we've learned
about the dragon markings.
First learned about this
seven years ago.
Jax and I were
on a mission in Brazil
to capture a wanted fugitive.
When we got there,
the target
had superhuman abilities.
Tore through our unit
in seconds.
The target had
the same marking you do, Cole.
When Jax finally took it down,
the dragon marking transferred
directly onto his skin.
I've spent years trying to
figure out what it all means.
Seems that throughout history,
different cultures
all over the world,
they reference
a great tournament.
But my research shows
that there's realms
and species that we didn't
even know existed.
That dragon marking,
it signifies that you've been
chosen to fight for Earth.
It's an invitation
to fight for something known
as Mortal Kombat.
Did you make that last part up?
It just kind of
sounds like you made it up.
And look,
they spelled it wrong.
Hey, you listen to me.
I think there's
another tournament coming.
That's why you're here.
That is why Jax and I
have been tracking you.
Because we need to find
every last champion
before it's too late.
And FYI, most of them
are dead already.
There's more to this, Cole.
I know it.
And I swear to God, I'm going
to get to the bottom of it.
I hate to interrupt
your bullshit, Blondie.
Well, I gotta piss again.
Hat is this?
You have a visitor?
Careful. He bites.
Oh, hello, sunshine.
Who are you?
That's Kano.
Kano?
Kano what?
Kano
None-of your-fuckin'- business!
Was that Russian?
Do I sound Russian to you,
you fuckin' idiot?
He's a mercenary
with the Black Dragon Clan.
Arms dealer, drug runner,
murder-for-hire,
scum of the Earth.
I also give
really good foot massages.
You have a marking.
Actually,
that's kind of a funny story.
You wanna tell him?
I was tracking another champion.
I was lucky enough to
find Kano here instead
right after
he slit the guy's throat.
Yeah, well, next time,
be more punctual.
You were never chosen.
Fate has better standards
than you.
Lucky for you,
I don't have any standards.
Let's see if you're
a natural blonde.
Not bad.
Almost felt that one.
What about you?
Where's your marking?
I don't have one.
Come on!
Hey, hey, new guy.
New guy.
Get me out of here.
I can help you.
Just sit tight.
I was about to go for a stroll,
but maybe I'll stick around,
you fucking idiot!
Fuck!
What the fuck was that?
That was my knife, too!
Fucking poetry.
Where is it?
- Where?
- Shh!
Did you shoot it?
I think I clipped it.
Sonya! Are you okay? Yeah.
Come on.
All right. I'm outta here.
Kano! Use the flare!
There you are.
Knife.
Kano wins.
You fuckin' beauty.
Fucking A.
Years of research
just destroyed.
So, do you believe me now?
Yeah. What's the plan?
There is none.
Oh...
Make yourself at home.
Yeah, I have.
Oh, by the way,
your beer is shit,
and you're almost out of it.
What are you doing?
Just working
on a Kano graphic novel.
I fancy myself
a bit of an artist.
He's a psychopath.
Well, all the best artists
are a little twisted, mate.
Well, I'm Off!
You're trying to get to
Raiden's Temple, aren't ya?
That should be fun.
You know where that is?
What's Raiden's Temple?
Yeah, I used to run guns
through there.
Locals wouldn't shut
the fuck up about it.
The legend says
champions used to train there
for Mortal Kombat.
Ah, for fuck's sake...
No one knows where it is.
Well, they do now.
Excuse me.
Where is it?
Uh, you got a pen?
You wanna write this down?
"Get fucked."
As if I'm gonna help you.
You kidnapped me.
You tied me up.
You threw a knife
in my fucking leg on purpose!
And then, that lizard thing
took off half of my face.
- Yeah.
- Lucky for me,
you can hardly notice it.
So, yeah,
it's a hard pass for me
on the "helping you" thing.
Now, get out of me fucking way.
Okay.
There you go.
Everyone's got a price.
Name yours.
You can't afford me.
Two million.
That's good.
You live in this shithole,
and you got two million dollars?
Pig's arse.
I have lived here my whole
life, you piece of shit.
You watch your mouth.
Two million dollars.
Yeah. Nah, fuck ya.
Fuck it.
Three million.
That's my final offer.
And anything I find
inside that temple, I keep!
No fucking splitsies!
Plus, if you're bullshitting me,
I'll fucking kill ya.
It's no skin off my sack.
Great!
Sounds like we got a deal.
I was gonna head there anyway.
Ya fuckin' idiot!
How are you planning
on getting us there?
Oh, I got a friend with a plane.
- You got friends?
- Hey, fuck you, pretty boy.
I'm a popular guy.
Everyone loves me.
Whoo!
Ah, bloody garden gnomes.
They give me the creeps.
You're gonna give that guy
three million dollars?
Fuck no.
I live in this shithole.
You think I got
three million dollars?
Unleash me...
There I was,
trying to shove
this guy's nuts down his throat.
And all I kept
thinking about was
what I should get me mum
for Christmas.
Your mum's been dead
for 30 fucking years, mate.
Kid can dream, can't he?
Hey!
You were out of it.
You okay?
Yeah.
All right.
Thank you for flying Air Kano.
I know you had fuck all choices.
Tray tables up. Time to jump
out of this shitbox.
Come on.
Let's go.
First time?
Yeah, what gave it away?
You'll be okay.
You just gotta jump,
count to three,
and pull this guy.
All right, simple.
But how do we know when to...
We don't got all day, princess.
What?
You're fucking kidding me.
So, how close are we?
It's 27, 28 Ks.
What?
Maybe 30, to be safe.
Let's round up to 32, eh?
We say 35,
there'll be no surprises.
Ah, shit...
Fuck this. I need a break.
You just took a break.
Too many beers, huh?
Give me that GPS.
I'm taking point.
Uh-uh. Let's look at
the scoreboard, shall we?
I got us the plane.
I know how to find
your precious little
mountain retreat,
or whatever it.
I killed the lizard man, huh?
Any of you ripped
anyone's heart out?
Hey!
I think I know
what's going on here.
Are you jealous, girly?
Of me little marking?
Hey! I'm talking to you.
If you want it so much,
all you've gotta do is kill me
and take it.
Ah, come on,
what do you say?
You wanna dance?
It's your blood.
Attagirl.
Hmm.
Go on, then.
Take it.
You're so close.
Just take it.
Take it!
Nah.
Yeah, that's why you don't
have one of these.
'Cause you don't have
the mongrel in ya!
You good?
At last.
Okay, that's far enough,
MC Hammer.
I'm not your enemy.
I'm Liu Kang from
the Shaolin Order of Light.
You're one of the champions.
Yes. From Earthrealm.
Finally, you have come
to seek out Raiden's Temple.
Fuck the Temple. Wait...
You just shot a fireball
outta your hand.
How'd you do that?
Hang on.
Hang the fuck on.
Does that mean I'm going to
get superpowers at any point?
It does, doesn't it?
There's much to learn.
The fuck?
But not here.
Follow me.
Ugh.
Hey, David Copperfield,
hang on,
just teach me how you do it.
There it is.
What you've been searching for.
It wasn't always like this.
For thousands of years,
this temple was a holy place
of worship.
It is essential
that we begin your training
for the next tournament.
This doesn't feel
like a tournament.
So far,
it feels like an ambush.
We don't have much time.
We will not see
another full moon
before the tournament begins.
Come, come.
Through here.
Now, what?
You gonna make a door appear
out of nowhere?
Ah.
I'll give you that.
It's pretty good.
Wow.
I knew it.
It's all real.
These murals are the living
history of Mortal Kombat.
Now, this one
really speaks to me.
This is Outworld.
Yes.
The most brutal and murderous
of all the realms.
Our greatest enemy.
Bi-Han!
Unleash me!
We must start training now
before our mortal enemies
in Outworld come for us.
The fate of Earthrealm
is in our hands.
There are not many of us
with the marking left.
So, you must train harder
and faster.
Because if you fail to
discover your inner power,
you will never defeat
your opponent.
They will ravage
everything you hold dear.
There will be no mercy.
You must fight without question.
The dragon has swallowed
many before us.
Now, put that back.
Put what back?
Jax! Hey! Jax?
Hey!
Oh, God...
It has been my charge
to gather
all the champions of Earth.
By the time I found Jax,
I was too late.
Well, is he gonna live?
The ice,
it cauterized his wounds.
We have sourced every realm
to find a way to heal him.
What can I do?
Be patient.
Give them time to do their work.
We must go.
He awaits.
The great protector,
Lord Raiden.
My lord.
I have gathered the remaining
champions of Earth.
This is what I have
to work with'?
You are in no physical
or mental shape to fight.
You don't even have a marking.
Oi, hang on!
What about me, Gandalf?
What does my fortune cookie say?
Powerless.
Arrogant.
The time has long passed.
Our enemies have claimed
nine straight victories.
One more victory
and Outworld will gain control
over Earth forever.
And Shang Tsung will enslave
the entire human race.
Sorry, what'd I miss?
They tried to kill my family.
Help us.
There is nothing for you here.
Only death.
Well, I'm willing to die
for my family.
Let's see if you have
what it takes.
The time has come to end this.
Take whatever trophies
you desire,
but their souls are mine.
Silence!
I have come to claim your world.
You're too late, Raiden.
It is forbidden to claim victory
until the tournament begins.
You are correct, Thunder God.
But conflict outside of
Mortal Kombat
is not forbidden.
Besides, the other gods
are too lazy to stop me.
I have come for your souls.
You will leave this place
at once, sorcerer.
These are your champions?
Kill them.
You think these tricks
will protect you forever?
Only a matter of time.
All right. Just circling back
on those superpowers.
I think I get it now.
It's kinda like
a box of chocolates.
You never know
what you're gonna get.
Is it gonna be fireballs?
Is it gonna be lightning? Huh?
Could be shit. Could be
a Frisbee hat, you know?
No offense, whoever you are.
The name is Kung Lao,
descendant of
the Great Kung Lao,
the Grand Champion
of the Order of Light.
Never heard of him.
Listen carefully,
your training has begun. Come.
Your inner power
comes from your arcana.
A gift from the marking
of the dragon.
The point of your training
is for you to unlock that power.
Without it, defeating Outworld
will be impossible.
Kung Lao and I have discovered
our arcana.
In the fight pit,
you will discover yours.
You may enter.
Let's do the damn thing.
I hope I get fireballs.
There is no guarantee.
So, look,
instead of fireballs,
what else can I shoot
out of my hands?
Like knives or guns or.
Hey, do you ever shut up?
You're welcome
to stay with us, Miss Blade.
But the training area
is for the chosen ones only.
Fucking whoops!
Oh, hang on.
We wouldn't be here
without her. She's one of us.
A fighter without a marking
can never achieve their arcana.
And a fighter without an arcana
is a liability to the others.
Yeah. Liability.
All right, bye-bye, Blondie.
All right, guys!
Little less of this,
little more of this. Come on.
Be still and listen.
Fucking hell.
Jax!
Hey, hey, hey.
I'm here.
Hey, buddy.
It's okay, it's okay.
It's okay.
You just lay down.
What happened?
All you can do now
is test your might.
We have no time to lose.
You must unlock your arcana.
In Mortal Kombat,
talent will only get you so far.
Well, that was great.
Really. Good stuff.
You know, maybe your arcana's
getting your ass kicked
by a hat.
Huh.
Fight!
No Harry Potters hit,
all right'?
Cute.
Real cute.
I'd like to see you
try that again.
Is that the only move
you know, mate?
Ahh! Oh, fuck.
Yeah, yeah. Put a fucking
shirt on, Magic Mike.
It seems as though we have
our work cut out for us.
I was just warming up.
Let me see your wound.
Liu,
how do I find my arcana?
It must come from your soul.
Whatever it is that drives you.
So, how did you find
your arcana?
Unlike Kung Lao,
I was just a worthless stray.
For reasons beyond my ken,
Master Bo' Rai Cho found me
half-dead in the gutter
and brought me...
...to the Wu Shi Academy.
There, I was given a purpose.
A brother.
Kung Lao.
And I met Lord Raiden
who Kung Lao and I
have served together.
Upon graduation,
I was given the name of a man.
He was a purveyor
of rare things.
Children.
Orphans
like me.
He had a marking.
So, I chose to take it from him.
And in that moment,
my arcana came forth.
Fuck.
Come on, Major,
I've seen better than that.
Again.
Again. Again.
Come on, you got this.
God damn it!
These don't work.
These are not me.
I'm useless.
Why even bring me here?
I can't help.
My first day of training
and we had to run 20 miles.
I thought I was gonna die.
I wanted to quit.
But all I ever wanted
was to be accepted by you
as an elite fighter.
You remember what you told me?
"Either you keep going
and you prove to yourself
that you can do this
or regret it
for the rest of your life."
Are you trying
to tell me something, soldier?
Get off your fucking ass, Major.
Miss Sonya. Sit, please.
Here, eat.
Thank you.
Cole, how's your arm?
Uh, it's healing up.
Eat more, heal fast.
More training tomorrow.
You're fucking kidding me,
aren't ya?
Oh, fucking hell.
Is he on our side?
No, those are great, mate.
They make those in men's sizes?
Topknot! At the end.
What's his name? Kung Pow?
Pass us a fucking egg roll,
would ya?
You rears
painted on, mate'? Egg roll.
There you go.
Good boy.
Maybe you should lay off
the egg rolls,
seeing how you wouldn't be
ready to fight
if you had 100 days to train.
I'll dumb it down for you.
Fat Lazy pig...
What did you say?
Terrible fighter.
Zero skill.
You got a death wish, mate?
Combat takes intelligence.
But you...
you're like a dog.
A dog who fails
his training classes.
Well, how about I take that
stupid fucking sombrero
you're wearing
and shove it so far up your ass
you start speaking Spanish?
How does that sound?
You can try.
I just fucking might!
Let me ask you this.
Why would you jeopardize
the goodwill
of the only chance
of your survival?
Princess, why don't you try
being one of them silent monks?
No, no, you misunderstand.
He is here to save you
because you cannot
save yourself.
Oh, fuckin' here we go.
You're like
an aggressive little bunny.
Soft and useless.
Angry, mentally, physically.
You should be on your knees
before this man.
I got a better idea.
How about you two
get on your knees
and take turns sucking my sack?
Do you have any fucking idea
who you're talking to?
I'm wanted
in over 35 countries for shit
you fuckin' ballerinas
couldn't even imagine.
You're angry.
Oh, fuckin' nothing gets
by you, does it?
Good.
You should be.
You failure.
"Failure"?
Fuckin' "failure"?
Let me educate you,
motherfucker. I'm Kano!
Of the Black fuckin' Dragon!
And who are you two, huh?
You're some
fuckin' cave-dwelling hippie
twirlin' his anal beads
taking orders
from this Wu Shu wanker
who wears a hubcap as a helmet.
Now sit down, shut up
and pass me a fuckin' egg roll!
That was it, wasn't it?
You all saw that?
A laser beam!
It's better than fireballs,
ya pussy!
Come on, Kano!
I knew I'd get mine first.
We are running
out of time, Cole.
Focus on what you can't deny.
Find the truth in you.
Pain is the ultimate catalyst.
Again.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, hold on.
Does it have to be him?
I met a...
You know, I see a little bit
of arcana there.
Give me one more crack at it.
Focus on the pain, Cole.
I'm focusing! Nothing's
happening. It just hurts!
Oh, stick with it.
Again.
Yeah, you're right. Nothing's happening.
Could always laser you.
What you looking at?
Mmm. They're beautiful.
You're a lucky man.
Thanks.
You have failed
to find your arcana.
Without it, you are
a liability to the others.
So, where did this come from?
And why am I the only champion
that had the marking
since I was born?
Your marking comes from
your lineage, Cole.
Lineage?
I'm an orphan from
the South Side of Chicago.
You're a descendant of one of
the greatest ninjas
to ever walk the Earth.
Hanzo Hasashi.
He was murdered along with
his wife and eldest son
by the same assassin
that hunts you now.
Sub-Zero.
The moment he died,
Hanzo descended
into the Netherrealm.
The farthest reaches of Hell,
endlessly searching for revenge.
But his bloodline lived on.
I rescued Hanzo's
only surviving child
and hid her in the one place
he wouldn't think to find her.
For centuries,
the Hasashi marking
has passed down
through your ancestors.
I had hoped
the power in your bloodline
was still strong in you.
Now, I know that's not the case.
Go!
Be with your family.
Cole, do not give up on this.
I'm sorry.
Welcome.
The great hunter Nitara.
She's beautiful.
Isn't she?
Yeah. That screech
is a real turn-on.
My loyal warriors.
Kabal.
General Reiko.
I have seen the so-called
champions of Earthrealm
and they're no match
for all of you.
We are on the precipice
of victory
and taking Earthrealm forever.
But we must strike now.
Raiden has prevented entry
into his temple.
I must find away
to bring his shield down
in order to obliterate
our opposition.
I think I can help.
Did you see a guy down there,
complete fucking asshole,
answers to Kano?
Kano?
Yeah, he's the reason
I live in an iron lung.
He's a low life
piece of shit scumbag.
You're gonna love him.
Prince Goro!
It is an honor to have
Shokan blood on our side.
Now, we shall end this
prophecy once and for all.
Well, well, well.
You backstabbing, two-faced,
ugly motherfucker.
Kabal.
Hey, Kano,
it's been a while.
You getting enough sleep, mate?
Your eyes are a little redder
than usual.
You've got a big mouth
for someone who's standing
on the wrong side of
the electric fence, tough guy.
You working for
the other fellow? That wizard.
Working with him,
not for him.
And trust me,
it has its perks.
Like what?
This is fucking tragic.
Look at yourself.
You used to be someone to fear.
You've fallen a long way
since you led the Black Dragon.
You don't tell me
about the Black Dragon.
I am the Black Dragon.
Which one's your boss?
Let me guess, the blonde?
Is that mask cutting off your
air supply, you dumb prick?
I don't take orders
from anyone, Kabal.
Then you're on the wrong side.
Fight with us and you could
have more money
than you know what to do with.
Hell, you could turn
this whole temple
into your own casino
if you wanted to.
Just name your price,
then double it,
then double it again.
What are you waiting for,
asshole?
So, what would I need to do?
Just wait here.
What is that?
You know the problem
with these new lightning sticks?
They just don't make 'em
like they used to.
What, you didn't think you'd
actually change me, did ya?
The undoing of the prophecy
has begun.
Back inside.
Dad!
Get back inside!
Cole!
Hey!
I'm the one you want!
You see that?
Come get it!
Finish them!
Damn, your breath stinks!
This is not the blood
of a chosen one.
Your death has no worth.
Ah, girls can be so mean.
Don't worry, darling.
You're still good enough for me.
Want me to slow down a little?
You're beneath me.
Now destroy him, my beauty.
Flawless victory.
- Dad!
- Cole!
Now, I tear out your spine,
champion!
Fuck this.
Mom!
Get in the truck.
Get in the truck!
Come on, come on, come on!
No, no!
Mom!
- Dad, help us!
- No!
No, Mom!
Cole!
Allison!
Get off me!
Dad, use your uppercut.
You Okay?
We're fine.
Are you okay?
Yeah.
Badass suit, Dad.
Blade!
Help!
What is that?
It's okay.
It's a door way back.
It's not over.
Impossible.
Thank you for helping
my fighter find his arcana.
After 4,000 years,
the Hasashi bloodline
still lives on.
Bi-Han.
Stop him!
Your soul is mine.
Liu!
He's about to get
his soul sucked.
I love the scream
right before they...
Liu!
Got ya!
No!
Where are we?
We are in the Void.
It is the realm
between your world and mine.
Shang Tsung
cannot follow us here.
If we were to die,
it was supposed to be together.
I am sorry, Liu Kang.
Without Kung Lao,
Earthrealm is lost.
Lord Raiden.
Why couldn't you save him?
Elder Gods are forbidden
from engaging in one realm's
war against another.
It is my job
to protect Earthrealm,
but I cannot save
every soul within it.
No.
It's not over.
We still need to fight.
Cole.
The blood on this blade
is your ancestor's.
Hanzo Hasashi's.
I took it from him
the day he died.
Use it, and the spirit of
Hanzo fights with you.
So, what's the plan?
We need to fight smarter.
We need to control the fight.
How?
I mean, they're better trained
and better prepared.
Plus, they don't mind
breaking the rules.
We need to split them up.
Lord Raiden, can you send
anyone anywhere?
Well, they don't want
a tournament.
Let's give 'em one,
but let's do it our way.
Give me Reiko.
I got a score to settle.
Hey, big boy.
Sonya...
Please tell me I get the bitch
with the teeth.
You get to take out
your old buddy Kano.
I know I've seen you
kick his ass before,
but he's got a laser now.
Watch out for that.
Oh, I got an idea.
Honey, I'm home.
Liu and I will take
Mileena and Kabal.
I know this is personal for you.
Are you ready?
You again.
What about Sub-Zero?
Nobody's taking him out
one-on-one.
Yeah.
We save Sub-Zero for last.
We take him out together.
As a team.
Yeah, these motherfuckers work.
God damn it!
I'd come out if I were you!
Fucking bitch.
Hey!
You owe me
three million dollars!
There you are. Come here.
There we go!
Fuckin' hell.
That was a bit harder
than I thought.
Tell me, Blondie,
how does that feel, huh?
Feels fucking amazing, mate.
Oh, I'm sorry,
did I cut you?
What the fuck?
Oh, shit!
Fatality.
For Kung Lao.
Shit.
A little nap?
That's pretty cool.
A little parting gift from Kano.
Okay, I'm almost
ready. How about you?
You sure Dad's gonna be
able to find us?
Completely sure.
Look, I just want to get us
out of here.
Fuck another four-armed
monster showing up.
Emily!
No!
Emily! No!
Allison!
Finally, the Hasashi bloodline
will end.
Now, you will die
with your family.
The blade of Hanzo.
Get over here.
For the Lin Kuei.
Dad. I got you.
I got you.
Hasashi Hanzo, Scorpion.
Dad.
These are my friends.
I am Liu Kang.
Sit. I will warm you.
I'm impressed.
I thought you said
you couldn't get involved.
Shang Tsung!
The prophecy has been fulfilled.
Has the blood on your hands
told you nothing?
No matter how many of my
people you put in the ground,
there will always be another
to take their place.
Today, you have killed
my warriors
and you think you have won,
but death
is only another portal.
Next time I see you,
I will not bring fighters.
I will bring armies.
You will return
to Outworld at once.
Earth will...
He talks too much.
What happens next?
Today, we are victorious,
but there are other enemies
to fight.
We can not let our guard down.
I'll assemble
a new list of champions.
You must find them.
Who's first?
My man!
Was just about to call you.
I need you.
Tomorrow night.
Sorry. My days fighting
for 200 bucks are done.
Ah, you're finally
quitting, huh?
Yeah, uh, something like that.
Where you gonna go?
Hollywood.
Hollywood?
What the hell's in Hollywood?
Not what. Who.
It's been fun.
Hollywood.
Provided by SilverStark & explosiveskull
https://www.instagram.com/vishal_sahani21
Test your might.
Mortal Kombat!
Fight!
Final round.
Finish him!
Fight!
Someone needs to stop Clearway Law.
Public shouldn't leave reviews for lawyers.