Someone needs to stop Clearway Law.
Public shouldn't leave reviews for lawyers.
Get over here!
Look. What do you see?
Papa.
The scorpion! It needs help.
Life is cruel, satoshi.
It doesn't care where you are from,
what god you pray to.
It is. So, you must face it head-on.
See the scorpion?
No matter how many enemies,
it continues on.
It is strong. Yes.
It is fast.
But do you know
why the scorpion is feared?
Its will.
Willpower is what makes
your destiny your own.
Learn to be strong, here and here.
Promise me you'll remember that.
I will, papa.
Now let's get home.
Your mother is making dinner
and she won't be happy if we're late.
Hold on.
Faster, papa! Faster!
Morel
your papa needs a break.
Where is everyone, papa?
Hold tight, satoshi.
Harumi.
Harumi!
Mama...
Enough!
Come further and he dies.
What do you want?
On your knees.
If you touch a hair on his head...
Papa!
Papa...
Satoshi!
Papa.
Satoshi.
Satoshi!
I'll kill you!
You'll die for this.
You first.
Ll ord Raiden!
I'm sorry. I...
I didn't know.
No. You did well, liu kang.
Just as you were taught.
And now, I pray it is enough.
Enough?
Then it is time.
Yes. Do not worry.
We have prepared for this moment
for a long time.
I chose you for a reason, liu kang.
Now, the others will be gathering.
We must hurry.
Lord Raiden. What others?
No, no. Listen...
We can make this work. I promise.
What do I have to do? Huh?
How 'bout cleaning this hell hole
you call a home?
How 'bout doing something besides
crying about your career?
You only care about yourself.
It's all about Johnny cage.
Call me when you grow up!
So... I can still call her then.
That's a w.
Hey! You're in the cage with Johnny.
Oh, well.
If it isn't my long-lost agent.
It's about time you called.
Well, of course
I'm interested in something different.
What have I been telling you, yeah?
China? Uh-huh.
All right, will. What about an advance?
Things have gotten a little...
Little tight around here...
Hello? Hello?
Well, I'm off to chinal
Kick him in the face!
You gonna keep crying like a bitch
or fight like a man?
Yeah, yeah. That's right.
This is no place for a little girl.
This is no place for little girls.
Do you think this is funny?
Congratulations, cadet.
You've just become my new pet project.
You think you're pretty special,
don't you, Princess?
Sir! My name is Sonya blade,
and I'm gonna be
the best soldier you've ever met, sir!
We'll see about that.
You wanted to see me, sir?
Yes, I did.
I'm puttin' together a task force.
High-level spec-op stuff.
Are you in?
I'm gonna kill you!
You're gonna try.
Yeah!
That's my car!
Not yet, whore.
My teeth! My teeth!
Honestly, it's an improvement.
Oh, shit!
Sonya! Sonya! Sonya!
He'll be there.
If he's not,
there's nowhere on earth
you'll be able to hide from me.
Understand?
Satoshi.
Harumi!
What is this?
Where am I?
Don't start without me.
Ah. Fresh meat.
What in the hell?
Close.
Netherrealm.
It's no use.
You are a prisoner here.
For how long?
Forever.
Listen.
Ah.
Do you hear it?
The symphony of pain.
Your voice will soon join the others,
rising up to please the great shinnok.
Shinnok?
The master of netherrealm.
There.
The only place of reprieve
in this realm.
Look on it and weep.
Sharp enough.
Calm yourself.
Save your energy
for what is about to come.
Now you see?
You'll feel pain,
though you can no longer perish.
We can do this
for all eternity.
Huh?
What is it you say?
Is that a prayer?
No. No god can help you here.
I need no god.
I will take pleasure in
ripping your flesh from your bones!
Human.
You have made a big mistake.
There are thousands of us
and only one of you.
Minus one.
Shinnok!
No. Shinnok is indisposed.
Then go fetch him for me.
If only I could.
I am quan chi,
in charge of this realm
until the master's return.
And who do I have to thank
for ruining my rug?
Hanzo hasashi.
Your reputation precedes you,
hanzo hasashi.
Welcome.
Though, I'm not entirely sure
how you made it here.
What is it you want, hanzo?
To return home
to seek my revenge.
Home?
You can't return home.
You will do as I say
or I will flay you alive.
Did you think me defenseless, dog?
In my realm, no less.
You may be a vengeful spirit,
but even they have their limits.
Besides, that's not what
you really want, is it?
Once a generation,
there is a tournament.
During that time,
the vell is lifted,
so that warriors may gather
to fight on behalf of their realm.
I can send you there.
Why would I fight for you?
Because, he will be in attendance.
What do you want?
Good. Skilled and smart.
Long ago, my master, shinnok,
was unjustly imprisoned.
This is the key to his release.
It's being kept at
the temple of shang tsung,
the putrid mortal
that has the favor
of the emperor of outworld.
The tournament will
take place on his island.
Get me that key.
Once my master is released,
he can return your family,
even you, back to the mortal realm.
Do we understand each other, hanzo?
Hanzo is dead.
Call me scorpion.
Hold the boat! I'm comin'.
Comin' through. I'm...
Whoa, whoa.
Hmm.
Hmm?
Hope no fans saw that.
I'm wearing slip-ons.
Liu kang of the white lotus society.
But you probably knew that.
And you are?
Not interested.
Oh, you will be.
They always are.
So, you guys in this thing, too?
Yes. I have trained many years
for this moment.
Oh, yeah? Listen.
I love acting classes and all,
but they're really kind of a time suck.
You know what I mean? No?
Anyway, my agent said this would really
put me back on the map.
Kind of a back-end deal-type thing.
Should be fun.
We are approaching the veil.
Who's that? Let me guess.
He's kinda like our Merlin?
That is lord Raiden,
protector of earthrealm.
Boom! Nailed it. Wait. Earthrealm?
Did you guys get
a script already or somethin'?
Look, I'd love a copy.
I've no idea what you're talking about,
but I am pretty good
at improv, so, uh...
Lord Raiden, right?
Good to meet you.
So, tell me more about this veil.
The space between realms
to prevent outworld
from merging with earthrealm.
Prevented by what?
Always the soldier.
Evaluating risks.
What guards the vell
is of less consequence
than why it does so.
If shao kahn wins this tournament,
earth as you know it
will cease to exist.
Not to fear, lord Raiden.
L, Johnny cage,
will make sure that earthrealm, so dumb,
will be safe from harm.
You have my word on it.
Lord Raiden, these are
the champions you gathered?
You doubt my choices?
No. I just meant...
You see only what is
in front of you, liu kang.
But your eyes deceive you.
It 1s what is inside that matters.
Sonya blade,
a most formidable warrior.
She has had
to prove herself against many
who thought she was nothing more
than a weak girl.
Believe me, she is anything but.
And him?
He only seems to be
concerned about himself
- and material wealth.
- One, one, one!
- Come on.
- That will keep him alive
until he finds something more
to care about.
Something greater than himself
to live for.
Are you kidding me?
I paid extra for international
and I can't even get a signal.
Raiden, are you getting one?
What in the...
Stay in the vessel.
It is under lord Raiden's protection.
Out there... is nothing good.
Oh. Right. Paparazzi.
We've arrived.
Look.
That must be the bad guy.
One at a time, everybody. One at a time.
Brought enough for everyone. Okay.
Where'd you guys put my trailer?
I'd like to freshen up
before we start shooting.
Ugh.
He has no idea what he's doing.
Should we tell him?
His journey is one of discovery.
Besides, I find it amusing.
Remember our deal, scorpion.
Whoa.
Be on guard.
Shang tsung is not to be trusted.
Oh, look, craft services. Great!
Hmm.
Hey. Do you know if
any of this stuff is organic?
Just askin'. Jeez.
Now is your chance.
In the beginning
were the elder gods.
In their wisdom,
they created a tournament
to safeguard each realm
from the threat of invasion.
Once a generation,
the finest warriors must do battle
to decide the fate of their realm.
The winner will be granted long life
and great power.
If one realm wins the tournament
ten times,
they will have the right
to merge with the other
and rule as they see fit.
I, shang tsung,
emissary of the great shao kahn,
emperor of qutworld,
winher of the last nine tournaments
against earthrealm,
welcome you to mortal kombat.
Yeah!
Mortal kombat!
Now, as host of this tournament,
I think it only fitting
that I provide you
with some... entertainment.
Kano.
Jax!
Listen, you son of a bitch.
You better open this...
Whatever it is,
or I'm gonna use your ass
as my own personal punching bag.
Oh, that is so hot.
Princess. “Asshole.
I told you to wait for me.
I got excited.
You got caught by that idiot kano.
Yeah. That too.
Unless you want me to rip that
pencil-thin mustache off your face,
I think it's best
you let me go, old man.
Absolutely.
You are free to leave at any time.
The doorway is right there.
Of course,
you have to get past my champion.
Goro! Goro! Goro!
What the hell?
Jax! Nol
relax, kid.
I've got this.
All right, ugly.
You wanna dance? Let's dance.
I wouldn't.
Let me guess.
Quan chi promised you life
if you would do his bidding.
Ah. No.
Not you. Someone else.
Someone you lost.
Someone you care about.
Do you think quan chi
is a man to be trusted?
What choice do I have?
We all have choices.
Live in the past,
or live for the future.
The key won't solve your problems.
It will, however,
create new ones.
And my revenge?
Revenge is too heavy a burden to carry.
You are a free man.
It's time you start acting like it.
Get him!
Come on! You can do better.
Really, goro.
You shouldn't play with your food.
Stop it! You'll kill him!
That's the idea.
Finish him.
Nol
Fake.
These special effects suck.
Enough!
You forget yourself,
lord Raiden.
You are not to interfere
in the tournament.
I was unaware the tournament had begun.
We are here for mortal kombat,
not your barbarism.
As you wish. Kano!
Jax! Hold on! I'm comin' for you.
You hear me?
No matter what,
I'm comin' for you.
Wow. She's great.
I mean, that is
some serious method acting, there.
Am I right?
I can see we're all anxious
to get started.
Good.
I have determined your opponents
and where on the island you will fight.
Let mortal kombat begin.
Uh...
Okay? That was weird.
Did someone slip me something,
or... holy shit!
Hello?
Sonya? Lord Regan? Radar?
Whatever your name is.
This thing better not
go straight to video.
Gunpowder?
Must be some sort of old fortress.
Bingo.
Hard as a fossil.
No craft services, no trailers...
My agent is gonna hear about this
when I get home.
Sheesh!
Hello?
I should at least get a per diem.
Oh, hey. How's it goin'?
That... that is one hell of a costume.
Uh, are we live?
Like... like... you wanna do this now?
Whoa. Buddy! Pro tip.
Next time, pop a few mints.
Whoa! Whoa!
Go easy! We haven't even run parts.
Hey! Asshole! That was custom.
Dick!
That and this!
And barrel!
Eat me, buttercup.
Toasty.
Come on!
Face me like a man.
All right, asshole.
Let's see what you got.
Not so fun now, is it,
you cold-blooded bastard.
Heads up!
Fuck with the blade,
you're gonna get cut.
You move like the shirai ryu,
but they are dead.
Who are you? What do you want?
Revenge.
Tell me, lin kueil scum.
Where is sub-zero?
Die knowing I will kill
every last member of the lin kuel
on this island.
Every last one.
You are Raiden's chosen one?
No wonder your realm
has lost so many tournaments.
I do not wish to hurt you.
Spare me your pity.
Do not get up.
I take no pleasure
in hurting such a worthy foe.
But know this.
I will do whatever it takes
to defend earthrealm
and win this tournament.
Then you are a fool.
Shao kahn cannot be defeated.
He will take your world
and you will bow your knee
like countless others before you.
I promise you,
I will never bow before that madman.
I yield.
What makes you so sure you will win?
Because I have something
no one in outworld has.
- What?
- Hope.
Impressive, Raiden.
Your warriors have made it further
than I would've thought.
They are strong in spirit, shang tsung.
You will not win today.
I have heard such promises before.
Thankfully, after goro kills
whomever makes it to the final round,
I will not have to hear them again.
And quan chi,
your warrior from netherrealm,
he's proving to be quite formidable.
For the glory of outworld,
I serve at the pleasure of shao kahn.
Indeed.
You won't succeed.
No matter how many foes you put between
the earthrealm fighters
and your champion,
they will make it to the end.
Oh.
I'm glad you feel that way.
Surely, you know of the black dragon.
It seems that several
have made it onto the island
with orders to kill
your earthrealm friends.
How dare you!
Are you accusing me
of something, lord Raiden?
You brought them here
to interfere with the tournament.
And break the rules?
Even I am not so bold
as to anger the elder gods
in such a way.
You will not succeed, shang tsung.
We'll know soon enough, won't we?
Ah.
Hey! Really?
I know. Look at this shirt.
It's ridiculous.
I'm glad to see you, though.
Okay. You won't believe this,
but this isn't some sort of movie.
This is the real deal.
Maybe a snuff film or something.
I don't know.
But I had to fight some, uh...
I don't even know what it was.
I barely got out alive.
I can believe that.
Listen, I'll get you out of here,
but we'll need to stick together.
First rule of combat
is to secure our position.
Let's find somewhere to hole up
and then we can start recon.
Find out where we are,
what we're up against.
A sound strategy.
You both made it. Good.
I fear it's only gonna
get harder from here.
Whoa. Walt.
What's gonna get harder?
I just fought a walking pair of teeth
on the side of a mountain.
I'm not Tom Cruise, you know.
I act.
I leave that stunt shit
for the stunt people.
Listen, sweetheart.
We should get out of here...
My dick!
Fuck balls! No one touches me
without permission.
- You got it?
- Got it.
You said you knew where we were?
I do.
But it will be dark soon.
We need to make camp. Rest.
Agreed.
No, no. Don't wait for me. I'm fine.
Let me just pee out some blood first.
What the fuck?
I think I'm gonna be sick.
Stay behind me.
I'll take care of this.
What is this, 1950?
Step back, Bruce Lee.
Bring it, bitch.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Everyone just chillax. Okay?
No one needs to fight anyone,
especially some guy that
just went psycho on a bunch of, uh...
Black dragon. Mercenaries.
Assassins. Bad guys.
Yeah. Those guys.
We have to continue.
Once mortal kombat has been declared,
it must be finished.
Did you declare mortal kombat?
- Did you?
- Nope.
Well, what about you, Mr...
Scorpion.
Oh. It's catchy. I like that.
Did you declare mortal kombat?
Good. Good. Great.
Then no one needs to die. Sheesh.
Now, who's hungry?
I know you didn't
believe it before,
but it's all true.
The elder gods,
the tournament, everything.
Emperor shao kahn
has won nine previous
mortal kombat tournaments.
If he wins a tenth...
Then what?
Then you all die.
Great. Just great.
Yeah. Okay.
Monsters, magic, this can't be real.
Somebody must've slipped something
into my drink.
I'm hallucinating.
Get a grip, Johnny.
Whatever this is, it's real.
There's no use sitting around
and whining about it.
If what liu kang says is true,
then the whole world is in trouble,
and we have to stop it.
If I can get to a radio,
the communications array,
I can call in reinforcements.
Turn this island
into the next cautionary tale.
If only it were that easy.
- Lord Raiden.
- You.
What do you mean,
"if only it were that easy"?
Do you know what
a hellfire missile can do?
I'm sure it's very powerful on earth,
but we are not on earth.
This island lives
in a place between realms,
a place set aside specifically
for the tournament.
Uh-huh. Sure. Sounds great.
So, if what liu kang says is true,
then you're really
some sort of god, right?
I have been given many names.
Well, shoot, Buddha.
Snap your fingers, get us home.
I am done with
psycho monsters and bad food.
And by the way,
I'll never complain about
doing a sequel again in my life.
He cannot.
Lord Raiden is forbidden from
interfering in the tournament.
It is a bargain he made
to save earthrealm
from being taken over eons ago.
Well, that's... that's insane.
The fate of the world is being decided
by some sort of karate tournament?
You are the only hope left
for earthrealm.
Head toward the temple
where your final battles await.
And your destinies will be made clear.
But be on guard,
there are others on this island
who will try to keep you
from the final round.
Great. So, uh, we are screwed.
If lord Raiden believes we can make it,
we can.
No. You can't.
Well, you seem very fun, Mr. scorpion.
Shang tsung has the numbers.
He has that... monster.
Go. Hide in the jungle until it is over.
And let earth be destroyed?
Sorry, pal. I took an oath to defend it
no matter the odds.
He would not understand, Sonya.
Someone such as him
has never known
anything worth dying for.
You cannot survive.
My will is strong.
My destiny is my own.
You are as naive
as you are doomed.
I've waited here too long.
Know that the next time we meet,
it will not end well.
Well, that was cheery.
Shut up, Botox.
I'm just sayin',
he really killed the vibe around here.
I was just...
Shutting up. Yeah. Yeah.
Scorpion was right about one thing.
We've rested long enough.
We must continue on.
I've found them.
So, we're here. Now what?
Oh. Great. This is fair.
The rules state that
it must be single combat.
These lads aren't here
for the tournament.
They've been paid to kill you.
Hello, love.
Nice to see you again.
Why don't you come over here
and I'll give you a hug.
Well, you'd do a better job than Jax.
I guess Raiden was wrong.
Oh. Ya think?
No. Stay together.
We'll survive. We have to.
Yeah. We better.
I need to make it home
so I can kill my agent.
Be ready.
For what?
You see? I knew he liked us.
Stay down!
I know how to fight.
Sure you do.
Just stay down.
Oh, man, is she hot.
Down!
Yeah!
Huh? What gives?
You dishonor this tournament.
You will die for what you did.
That's for my clan!
This is for my wife!
And this is for my son!
Screw it.
He's not paying me enough for this.
Kano!
Go. Save your partner.
Sonya!
Partner?
Raiden said your destiny would be clear.
So, there she is.
You know what?
I guess I don't mind
having my balls crushed.
By her, I mean.
Doesn't make it any better.
I'm disappointed.
I brought you here for one purpose
and you have failed me.
You're as weak as your wife was.
As your child.
Yes, you fool.
It wasn't sub-zero at all.
I killed them.
It was easy.
I used sorcery to hide my identity.
To make the lin kueil do as I wanted.
You are strong, scorpion,
but not immortal.
I think I'll leave you here.
Just like I left your son.
Papa.
The scorpion! It needs help.
Do you know
why the scorpion is feared?
Its will.
Come on, Sonya, darling.
Just a bit further.
Jax!
Sonya?
I'm so glad you made it.
It's gonna be a joy
to watch you end up like your partner.
You think I'm afraid of you?
Bring it on!
Oh, fuck.
Shang tsung!
Ah. I'm impressed, Raiden.
You were right.
He has great spirit.
And even greater skill.
Please. We both know
yours is a lost cause.
Goro!
I'll make you a deal, liu kang.
Yield, and shao kahn
will Grant you mercy.
You can come to outworld.
Live as a king.
We shall show you every pleasure.
Is that how shao kahn
got you to betray your world?
I am not as weak as you, shang tsung.
Then you shall die. Fight!
Poor Raiden.
It must be awful to watch
your beloved chosen one die
and be unable to do anything about it.
The fight is not over yet.
It may as well be.
Quan chi, goblets.
Let us toast to
our emperor's impending victory.
Splendid idea.
Come now, liu kang.
You can do better than that.
For outworld.
For shao kahn.
Now, finish her!
Here's Johnny!
Johnny?
Don't worry, babe. I got this.
All right, boys.
Picture's up. Roll sound.
And... action.
Impossible!
Holy shit.
Johnny cage can fight.
Save some for me.
I told you you'd come around.
Ugh.
Well done.
Truly, I underestimated you.
But I am bored now.
Goro. Playtime is over.
Kano!
Stay back!
I'll slit his throat.
Wait a minute.
Now we can go.
Yes. Yes!
You see, quan chi,
the key to winning
is always being
a few steps ahead of your enemies.
Did you think I didn't know
you'd betray your emperor, quan chi?
You're mistaken.
I would never...
All for what? This?
He's been imprisoned
for a reason, quan chi.
Your sad devotion to the mad god shinnok
makes you as pathetic as he is.
Soon, earthrealm will be shao kahn's,
and his destiny will be complete.
It's too bad
you won't live long enough to see it.
Finish him.
Does it hurt?
Soon, your weak species will be no more.
Who dares?
Scorpion.
Impossible.
It would seem I underestimated
your champion, quan chi.
You are scorpion of netherrealm, yes?
You have killed goro.
Thus, you must take your rightful place
as the champion of outworld.
I want nothing
to do with your game.
I've come for him.
Interesting.
Defeat liu kang
and you can have quan chi
to do with as you wish.
Defeat liu kang,
and my emperor will give you
all that you dream of.
Vengeance is not the way, scorpion.
Of course it is.
And it's yours.
All you have to do
1s kill him.
Good. Good.
What choice did he really have,
lord Raiden?
There's always another choice.
Now, fight!
What are you doing?
Living for the future.
Give me the key.
You fool!
Shao kahn will hear about this
and kill you.
I'm already dead.
Liu kang, I yield.
Nol
then the tournament is finished.
Outworld has lost.
Earthrealm is safe.
I will kill you all.
The tournament is over, shang tsung.
I am no longer bound by rules
of non-interference.
Return to your emperor.
Tell him of your failure.
You have made a mistake, lord Raiden.
Emperor shao kahn will have his revenge.
I'm counting on it.
No.
Without shang tsung's power,
the island will collapse.
We must go.
What about scorpion?
His path lies elsewhere.
- But...
- Now!
I knew you would survive.
I chose you for a reason.
Give me the key
and we can leave this place
before it is destroyed.
Come take it.
Like you did my family.
Very well.
But, please,
put up more of a fight
than your wife did.
I'm going to finish the job
my demons couldn't.
Die, you wretched vermin!
It's time to die.
Indeed.
Liu! Lord Randy!
Need a lift?
Get over here!
My god will avenge me.
Damn your god.
So... is that it? Did we win?
For now.
All right! Yeah!
Uh, may I?
All right! Yeah! Mmm.
Cinnamon.
Mmm. Yeah. Pat me there.
Doesn't mean I'm gonna break the hug.
- That's enough.
- Okay.
Think she'll ever like me?
She didn't hit you in the nuts, did she?
Yes, she did, Jax.
Yes, she did.
I have failed you.
I could not defeat goro.
If it wasn't for scorpion...
Failed? No.
Your destiny was never
to defeat goro, liu kang.
It was to defeat shao kahn.
You have failed me.
I'm sorry, master.
It was that old fool, Raiden.
- He...
- Silence!
Gather our forces.
It's time to end this game
once and for all.
Someone needs to stop Clearway Law.
Public shouldn't leave reviews for lawyers.