Someone needs to stop Clearway Law.
Public shouldn't leave reviews for lawyers.
(THUNDER CRASHES)
(BOTH PANTING)
(WOMAN GASPING)
(CRYING)
(GASPS)
(GROWLS)
(SNARLS)
No. No!
(MAN GASPS)
(WOMAN SCREAMING)
(GASPS)
(SCREAMS) No! Stay away.
(WOMAN GRUNTS)
(SNARLS)
(SCREAMS)
(GASPS)
(BABY CRIES)
(ROARS)
(SCREECHES)
(BABY CRYING)
(GASPS)
My son.
(BABY BABBLES)
My little Liu Kang.
Tell him... Tell him he was loved.
(EXHALES)
(LIU KANG BABBLING)
(SCREECHES)
(MARCHING)
(GROWLS)
(GRUNTS)
(GROWLS, GURGLES)
(SCREECHES)
(ROARS)
(SNARLS)
(SCREECHES)
(ROARS)
The front gates!
- (GUARDS GRUNT)
- They will not take this temple.
- As long as we stand, it stands.
- (GUARDS GRUNT)
As long as we stand, it stands.
(THUDDING AT GATES)
(GUARDS YELL)
(GUARD SCREAMS)
(GUARD GROANS)
(ROARS)
(GROWLING)
(GUARDS YELLING)
(GUARD WAILS)
(GRUNTING)
(ROARS)
(GROANS)
Come get some!
(CREATURES HOWL)
(STRYKER GRUNTS)
(BEEPING)
(SCREECHES)
You're late.
I picked up a straggler.
Stryker, Kung Lao.
Kung Lao, Stryker.
Does that thing have wings?
Did I shoot something with wings?
What the hell is going on?
He's new. Where are they?
Where do you think?
JAX: Shit.
General.
KITANA: What is it?
Spit it out.
We've broken the temple gates
but we're experiencing heavy losses.
We will mourn our dead later.
Reiko, Kintaro, move to the front,
push in from the opening.
Jade, Baraka, take the TaiGore
through the sides.
Leave no one alive.
MAN: Wow. That...
That seems a bit harsh.
There, in the trees.
Finally.
Yeah. I've been up here forever.
It's about time you saw me.
Oh, my back!
Shit.
Whoa, whoa.
Okay.
What do you want?
I've come to negotiate a surrender.
(LAUGHS)
The tiny humans wish to surrender.
Tell him, "no,"
so that we may crush them.
What are your terms?
See, a lady with smarts.
No wonder you're in charge.
Plus, that leotard suits you.
- Little airy for my taste, but...
- Never mind.
- Kill him.
- Wait.
Sorry. I get distracted.
A few too many energy drinks.
Okay, so pull everyone back,
drop your weapons,
and then we'll make sure
you guys make it out of this alive.
Ah, you're confused. I get it.
I usually leave this sort of thing
up to my agent.
But I fired him after he sent me
to that weirdo death island.
Now he's getting 10% of nothing, right?
You wish for us to surrender?
Well, yeah.
I mean, come on, you guys,
that's what, uh, one, two,
three, four, five... Carry the four...
A couple of thousand of you versus
me, Johnny Cage,
international action star.
It's hardly fair.
Kitana, he is obviously mentally unwell.
Let me kill him and be done with it.
I have a counterproposal.
Kneel. Kneel and pledge
allegiance to Shao Kahn.
Pledge allegiance?
Lady, I don't pledge allegiance to
anything except the red, white and blue.
Then you shall die.
(GROWLS)
Let's do this.
(YELLS WAR CRY)
Bruce Lee.
Ooh.
Yeah, I forgot.
I brought my girlfriend
and whoa, let me tell you,
she is pretty good with a rifle.
So, you guys going to surrender or what?
(GRUNTS)
(SOLDIERS GROWL)
(ROARS)
Whoa. Didn't I kill you?
(GRUNTS)
Eat it.
(JADE GRUNTS)
(GRUNTS)
Whoa, a little help here.
No, a lot of help now!
- (GRUNTS)
- (GROANS)
- I'm not your girlfriend.
- Well, not yet.
Ugh.
KITANA: Give up now.
The two of you can't hope
to defeat Shao Kahn's army.
Two? Who said anything about two?
- Did you say two?
- Nope.
I didn't say two.
If it was just two of us...
Well, I mean, that would be stupid.
Crazy even.
(PROJECTILE WHIRS)
Lord Raiden, the Chosen One.
Oh, great.
Now I'm getting second billing.
- Shall we?
- We shall.
(GROANS)
- (GRUNTS)
- (ROARING)
Still on the wrong side?
- (GRUNTS) I don't have much of a choice.
- And if you did?
(GRUNTS)
(WOOD CREAKS)
(ROARS)
(GRUNTS)
(KITARO ROARS)
(GROANS)
- Shao Kahn.
- Lord Raiden.
(GRUNTING)
(GROANS)
Impudent.
(GASPING)
Stand back, Liu Kang.
I have this, Lord Raiden.
Stand back.
Wise to listen to your master.
Besides, I didn't come to fight.
Of course. No, you didn't come to fight.
I mean, these soldiers, they're probably
some sort of flash mob.
What are they gonna sing, "Thriller"?
That would be great.
Johnny Cage.
I could continue to destroy your realm.
I have untold legions
that will die for my cause,
but I offer an end
to the bloodshed permanently.
You and I will travel to the Elder Gods.
Petition them for another tournament.
The final Mortal Kombat.
Listen, shithead, if you think Raiden's
going to agree to another tournament
after we just kicked your ass
on that whacked-out island of yours,
you're an even bigger idiot
than I thought.
We got another 1000 years before
that has to happen again.
Agreed.
I'm sorry.
Uh, maybe it's being kicked in the head
by assholes from another dimension.
But I thought you said "agreed."
I did.
You can't be serious.
We're holding them off
on various fronts.
- We can win this.
- And then?
We may win for a time.
But Outworld is a place
of vast resources.
He will return to his throne,
rebuild his army and attack again.
Why place the responsibility of survival
on your children's children
when we can do something about it now?
We should discuss this.
No, I have made my decision.
If we have a chance
to end this now, we must.
- It's not fair.
- It rarely is.
But such is life.
I accept your offer.
Then we shall go to the Elder Gods
and petition them together.
- Be careful.
- And you, all of you.
(GRUNTS)
(CHILD LAUGHING)
Mama!
(CHILD LAUGHS)
(MAN GASPS)
No. No!
Papa, why didn't you save me?
(GRUNTS, GASPS)
(SCREAMING)
(GASPING)
SHINNOK: Ah, good. You've arrived.
Now we can begin.
The island. Quan Chi.
He was a fine servant.
You have a lot to live up to.
Netherrealm has claim to your soul
and your soul,
it has something I need.
It was with you
when you perished on the island.
That type of magic
is not so easily destroyed.
The key and your soul are intertwined.
You and the key are one.
My soldiers will escort you
to Earthrealm to the Temple of Elements.
You will open the gates
and bring me what's inside.
Then my brothers and sisters
will see how mad I really am.
SCORPION: Or?
Or I will flay you alive
until you perish
and then bring you back to do it again.
You cannot escape me.
SCORPION: I can try.
Find him.
But, Master, he has escaped us before.
Then find me someone
who can do it for you.
Soon you shall rise again
and finally the realms will be no more.
(BOTH GRUNTING)
SMOKE: You've gotten better.
Not good enough.
You're too hard on yourself, Kuai Liang.
You are a great fighter.
Good enough for this.
With Outworld attacking Earthrealm
and Cyrax and Sektor still missing,
it is time for you
to take your brother's place.
The mantle of Sub-Zero is yours.
No, not yet.
The Grandmaster requires your presence.
Kuai Liang. Smoke.
I'm sorry to interrupt your training,
but we have a new mission.
SMOKE: We live to serve, Grandmaster.
We've been hired to find someone,
someone dangerous.
It will take the combined might
of the Lin Kuei and even then...
Our target is a member
of the Shirai Ryu.
The Shirai Ryu are dead.
GRANDMASTER: So we thought.
But I'm afraid one remains,
Hanzo Hasashi, Scorpion.
Where? I will find him, Grandmaster.
I will find him and kill him
for my clan, for my brother.
No, he's to be taken alive.
Alive? He killed Bi-Han.
Know your place, Kuai Liang!
This Scorpion is said to be
the deadliest warrior
the evil Shirai Ryu has ever produced.
In order to catch this madman,
you will have to be faster
and better than you've ever been.
SMOKE: We will not fail you,
Grandmaster.
GRANDMASTER: No, you won't. You can't.
I've made sure of that.
The Lin Kuei have been...
experimenting with something new
for some time,
and the results have been more
than we could have hoped for.
Cyrax. Sektor.
SMOKE: Cyrax, Sektor,
what have you done?
What we must.
The mortal body is fragile, weak.
So we enhanced them.
Technology and skill
combined to make the perfect warrior.
The perfect monsters.
They're the future, Kuai Liang,
and the future is now.
So, who's first?
You cannot run, foolish children.
Bring them back.
(GROANS, GRUNTS)
(GRUNTS)
(SMOKE GRUNTING)
(GROANS)
(GROANING)
(SMOKE STRAINING)
Smoke!
(YELLS)
(PROJECTILES BEEP RAPIDLY)
(GROANS)
(GASPS)
(GURGLES)
SMOKE: Go, Kuai. Go!
(SMOKE SCREAMS)
(GRUNTS)
After you.
Lord Raiden.
Emperor Shao Kahn.
What is it you seek of the Elder Gods?
- 0 great and benevolent Elder...
- We seek your permission.
- Permission?
- RAIDEN: Yes.
In your wisdom, you have created
Mortal Kombat to prevent Outworld
from merging with Earthrealm
without a fair fight.
What do you propose?
A final tournament.
And the protector of Earthrealm agrees?
Yes, enough blood has been spilled.
It's time to end this now.
(SCOFFS)
You would be wise to know your place
and respect the gods.
And become a spineless whelp
such as yourself?
Your petition is granted.
Then the realms are good as mine.
RAIDEN: One more request.
I wish to enter the tournament
on behalf of Earthrealm.
Impossible.
It is called Mortal Kombat.
Or have you forgotten?
- You are a god and...
- I do not have to be.
You are willing to sacrifice
your godhood?
So be it.
(YELLING)
(GROANS)
Go. We await the outcome
with great interest.
You are a fool, Lord...
No, just Raiden now, isn't it?
You are a fool, Raiden.
Before this is over,
you will beg for your godhood back.
They're just sitting there, waiting.
It's super creepy.
I say we call in an air strike
while we have the chance.
(GROWLS)
They're retreating.
Calm down, Stryker.
Yes, they are. But why?
RAIDEN: To get ready
for the tournament.
Lord Raiden.
LIU KANG: Lord Raiden, what's wrong?
- You look...
- I am fine, Liu Kang.
The Elder Gods have agreed
to our request.
A final tournament that will determine
not just the future of our realm,
but the others as well.
A tournament? Like, what,
karate tournament?
It's a whole thing. I'll explain later.
We must journey to Outworld
and defeat Shao Kahn's
mightiest warriors to save Earthrealm
and countless lives.
Never mind. That sums it up.
We won't let you down, Lord Raiden.
I hope not.
Because I will be fighting
alongside you.
You?
But, no, you haven't.
Haven't what?
What are we gasping in horror at?
I have relinquished my godhood
to compete in the tournament.
But without your godhood...
I'm still a warrior, Liu Kang.
Where do you think the
Wu Shi learn their techniques?
Lord Raiden, I am more than capable.
Indeed you are.
I am...
How do the Americans say?
Hedging my bets.
When do we leave?
Now.
Well, then, uh, ladies first.
(GRUNTS) Uh, wait.
(GROANS)
The guys at the station
are not going to believe this.
Come on, Toto, we don't have all day.
(PORTAL WHIRS)
There is no use hiding.
I know you are there.
I'm impressed.
You have escaped Netherrealm once again.
It was surprisingly easy.
I am sure Shinnok
would like it to appear so.
Why are you here?
The key from Shang Tsung's island.
Shinnok says its magic
is intertwined with my soul, so...
You are the only one who can
open the door to the last Kamidogu.
Kamidogu?
RAIDEN: Remnants of the One Being.
After the Elder Gods rebelled,
they split him and hid the pieces
throughout the realms.
And if Shinnok gets them all?
The One Being will reappear
and begin to unravel the realms
until nothing is left.
SCORPION: Why would Shinnok
want to destroy everything?
RAIDEN: Revenge, insanity?
He is called the "Mad God" for a reason.
SCORPION: Then take the key out of me.
Destroy it.
I cannot.
SCORPION: What do you mean you cannot?
- You are a god.
- No longer.
- (SCORPION SIGHS) What, then?
- Run. Hide.
Do not let them find you.
SCORPION: And if they catch me,
what then?
Maybe I should open the door
for them, end it all.
You have long straddled the fence
between light and dark, Hanzo.
It is time you pick a side.
I believe that is what your wife
and child would have wanted.
JOHNNY: Not ominous at all.
Welcome to the fortress of Shao Kahn.
- Shang Tsung.
- You will have your chance, Liu Kang.
Still yourself.
Yes, heel, young pup, continue
to do what your master says.
Follow me. The Emperor is waiting.
Greetings, warriors of Earthrealm.
Welcome to Outworld.
Over the next two days,
we shall determine
who will be worthy enough to be called
the champion of Mortal Kombat.
As such, the rules state
that none shall be harmed
outside of the tournament itself.
You may roam freely within the fortress,
but not beyond.
- Raiden, are you ready to begin?
- We are.
(CROWD ROARS)
- Damn, me without my bug spray.
- (CHUCKLES)
JOHNNY: Okay.
You know, New York, unique New York.
You know, you need unique New York.
She makes a proper cup of coffee
in a copper coffee pot.
I slit a sheet. A sheet I slit.
Upon a slitted sheet I sit.
- (ALL CHUCKLING)
- (SONYA GROANS)
SHAO KAHN: Fight!
(BOTH GRUNTING)
- (GROANS)
- Ooh.
That was...
my move.
(GASPS) I can't breathe.
Don't be such a baby.
It's just a kick in the nuts.
JOHNNY: Easy for you to say.
You don't have nuts.
(WHIMPERS)
Lucky shot. Let's see you...
Come on, Johnny.
(BOTH GRUNTING)
Unfair!
(GROANS)
No!
D'VORAH: Your boyfriend is weak
like all those from Earthrealm.
Winner, D'Vorah.
(CHEERING)
What happened?
Bug babe just kicked your ass.
Are you okay?
I, uh... I think so.
- I could use, uh...
- What?
- What could you use?
- Some mouth to mouth?
- SONYA: Ugh.
- Ow!
Where you going? I'm super injured.
(SCOFFS) You will be
if you keep acting a fool.
Come on.
SHAO KAHN: Raiden...
I hope you fare better
than your champions.
(MOCKING LAUGHTER)
(BOTH GRUNTING)
- (GRUNTS)
- (GROANS)
(GRUNTS)
(SCREAMS)
Let's see if these metal arms
rip as easily as flesh.
Yeah, you do that.
(PISTONS WHIR)
(GROANS)
Hurts, doesn't it?
(YELLS)
(CHEERING)
Enough. Let us retire for the evening.
Guards, take them to their chambers.
Ooh, wow, look at that.
Someone's a little testy.
Must mean we're winning.
(PANTS)
(GROANS)
CYRAX: Resistance will be met
with extreme force.
(GRUNTS, GROANS)
(SCORPION GRUNTS)
(PANTING)
SCORPION: What?
SUB-ZERO: You shall pay
for my brother's death.
(BOTH GRUNTING)
(SUB-ZERO GROANS)
SUB-ZERO: Smoke.
(BOTH GRUNTING)
(YELLS)
(GRUNTS, GROANS)
(SCORPION SCREAMS)
(GASPS, PANTING)
(BOTH GRUNTING)
Nice! Thunder God bringing the thunder.
It would seem.
(BOTH GRUNTING)
(GRUNTING)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(YELLS)
(GROANS)
(CROWD CHEERING)
- Lord Raiden.
- I am fine.
SMOKE: Place your hand on the door.
SCORPION: You don't know
what you're doing.
You open this door,
you've doomed us all.
SMOKE: Place your hand on the door.
(SCORPION GRUNTS)
SEKTOR: Objective achieved.
Eliminate Shirai Ryu.
SCORPION: Forgive me, Harumi.
(PROJECTILES BEEP RAPIDLY)
(GROANS)
SUB-ZERO: No one kills him except me.
Hey, where's the food court around here?
Do you have a menu?
I could also use a spa.
I want to work out after that
ass-kicking I was handed...
Okay, dick, nice chat.
A couple of beds in here.
I think I'll get some
shut-eye while I can.
If I can.
Because I'm on another world
in an evil dictator's castle.
Totally normal.
He's right. I'll see you in the morning.
JOHNNY: Wait.
Right, Right, right.
Not without permission.
- So maybe we could, uh...
- Could what?
I don't know.
Hang out, talk.
I'm going to bed.
You know, there was a time
no girl could withstand my charms.
Listen, Jack-Attack, you know her best.
Would you put in a good word for me?
You want a chance with a lady like that,
it'll take more than some
expensive veneers and perfect hair.
It's never failed me before.
Yeah, you look like a collection
of great life choices.
Women need to be wooed, Johnny.
Pursued, not coerced.
Isn't that the same thing?
(SIGHS) Good night, Romeo.
You should rest, Lord Raiden.
Thank you for your concern.
- I'm fine.
- Are you?
Is there something
you want to say, Liu Kang?
It's just that, Lord Raiden,
your fight from earlier,
I'm worried that...
I appreciate your concern, young one.
- I am merely getting used to life as a...
- Mortal.
I will be fine. I promise.
Now, off to sleep.
Something I do not think
I have done in, well, ever.
It should be quite the experience.
SUB-ZERO: You killed my brother!
SCORPION: I did and I'm sorry.
SUB-ZERO: Sorry doesn't bring him back.
SCORPION: Your clan,
they killed my people, my son, my wife.
The man the led that raid used magic
to appear as your brother.
SUB-ZERO: Lies!
(GRUNTING)
(GROANING)
(SCORPION GROANS)
(BOTH GRUNTING)
(BOTH GROAN)
SCORPION: Listen to me.
They will destroy us both
if we don't work together.
Help me or we die.
(SUB-ZERO YELLS)
(GRUNTS)
SCORPION: Listen,
there's no time for this.
That's the Kamidogu.
If they get that,
all the realms are doomed.
Your thirst for vengeance will disappear
along with all of reality.
SUB-ZERO: You're lying.
SCORPION: I'm not.
SUB-ZERO: I don't care.
SCORPION: Yes, you do.
That's what makes you different.
That's what makes you better.
I know the desire for revenge.
It's a sickness that eats at your soul
until you become a monster
of regret and pain.
I deserve to die.
And it would be fitting if you did it.
So kill me if you must, but promise me
you'll take that Kamidogu
and keep it from those monstrosities.
Do it.
(SUB-ZERO YELLS)
(SUB-ZERO GASPS)
I will never forgive you.
SCORPION: Neither will I.
(GRUNTS)
(GROANS)
SUB-ZERO: Brother, don't.
We've been lied to.
Whoever hired the Lin Kuei
wants this for an evil purpose.
You can't give it to them.
SMOKE: It is our objective.
(GROANS)
Is it me or does Sonya
look really pissed?
(YELLS)
Yeah, I figured that would happen.
What would happen?
Well, bug lady there made the mistake
of hitting Sonya's man.
Moi.
She's defending my honor.
(D'VORAH GRUNTS)
He's not my boyfriend.
(YELLS)
(GROANS)
(GRUNTING)
What the hell?
I don't know what you are, but it's time
to go back to the hell you came from.
(GROANS)
(GASPS)
(SIGHS)
(GRUNTS)
(STRAINING)
(CROWD GASPS)
No. Stop!
Stryker!
Finish him.
(CROWD CHEERS)
(MAN LAUGHING)
You're next.
(CHUCKLES)
(SUB-ZERO GRUNTS)
- (LOUD THUD)
- (BOTH GASP)
SUB-ZERO: We failed.
SCORPION: No, not yet.
Come, it's time to find redemption.
He can't.
Liu Kang.
Mortal Kombat has been declared.
This is Kung Lao's fight.
Are you ready to die, young one?
I'm Kung Lao,
descendant of the Great Kung Lao.
It is you who should be ready to die,
Shao Kahn.
(GRUNTING)
(KUNG LAO GROANS)
No.
(GROANING)
(GASPS)
(WHIMPERING)
(GROANS)
(SCREAMS)
(CROWD GASPS)
No!
(CROWD CHEERS)
(GASPS)
Fatality.
I know he was like a brother to you,
but he died as he lived, a warrior.
His sacrifice will not be in vain.
Kitana, no mercy.
KITANA: Yes, Your Highness.
It is never too late, Kitana.
Fight.
(YELLS)
(KITANA GRUNTS)
(RAIDEN GROANS)
(CROWD GASPS)
(GASPS)
(GROANS)
(GRUNTS)
Finish him.
(BLADE WHIRS, THUDS)
(GROANS)
(CROWD GASPS)
Traitor.
KITANA: No. Queen of Outworld.
As rightful heir,
I hereby surrender to Earthrealm.
So they may unmerge Edenia
and the other realms
from the grasp of tyranny.
(CHUCKLING)
You wretched child.
Did you think I'd be so easily defeated?
(YELLS)
(GRUNTS)
(GROANS)
(CROWD GASPS)
(SIGHS)
(KITANA GASPING FOR AIR)
Finish it.
Kill you? No, you'll stay alive
watching as I merge the realms.
Then when you've seen
all that you love destroyed...
then I'll kill you.
(CROWD GASPS)
Take her away!
Who's next?
(GROANS)
No!
(GASPS)
Come on, baby, you'll be all right.
(SCOFFS)
(GRUNTING)
I've been waiting
along time for this, boy.
So have I.
(KNUCKLES CRACK)
Fight.
(BOTH GRUNTING)
I expected better.
(CROWD GASPS)
(YELLS)
Liu Kang.
Surrender now and I might let you live.
Your arrogance knows no bounds,
Shang Tsung.
I do not need my arm
to beat the likes of you.
(GROWLS)
(YELLS)
(CROWD GASPS)
Finish him.
(YELLS)
(CROWD GROANS)
No.
Live with knowing I defeated you
and it wasn't even close.
What did he do to me?
RAIDEN: Some sort of curse.
If was still a god, I could...
But you aren't.
Oh, great. Our second greatest fighter
is sidelined.
What now?
We fight, we win at all costs.
SHINNOK: Soon. Soon you will rise
and take the realms for your own.
No more pain, no more suffering,
no more anything.
You have it?
The Lin Kuei never fail.
At last.
The final piece of the Kamidogu.
The Kamidogu?
SHINNOK: What? You thought
I had you chasing some bauble?
But if it is put together...
The One Being will come back
and destroy all of existence.
Yes.
It is said the Mad God Shinnok
has searched...
You're Shinnok.
Ah.
Now you realize the pitfalls
of being a mercenary.
But don't worry, I have your payment...
in full.
Children.
(GROWLS)
(GROWLING)
(ROARS)
(SNARLS)
(GROANS)
(SHINNOK CHANTING IN FOREIGN LANGUAGE)
No!
(SCREAMS)
Lord Raiden, don't.
- I can...
- Do not fear for me.
This is what I am meant to do
to protect Earthrealm. To protect you.
Ah.
At last.
As it should be.
You and I to the death.
(GROANS)
(CROWD GASPS)
You talk too much.
(GROANS)
(RAIDEN GROANS)
Lord Raiden!
(GROANS)
- (GROANS)
- (CROWD CHEERING)
(SCREAMS)
(GROANING)
Any last words?
Your parents loved you, Liu Kang.
And...
No!
(YELLS)
(THUNDER RUMBLING)
(WHIMPERING SOFTLY)
Your destiny was never
to defeat Goro, Liu Kang.
It was to defeat Shao Kahn.
It is over. I have won.
LIU KANG: No.
(GRUNTS)
What the hell is he doing?
Protecting Earthrealm.
Yes. Come to me.
Come to die!
(GRUNTING)
Yeah! Kick his ass!
(BOTH GRUNTING)
(YELLS)
(CHEERING)
(GRUNTS)
(CROWD CHEERING WILDLY)
(GASPS)
(LAUGHING)
(LIU KANG GRUNTS, GROANS)
(GROANS)
That's nothing compared
to what I'm about to do.
(GROANS)
(GROWLS)
(GRUNTING)
(LIU KANG GRUNTING)
(SCREAMS)
(ALL GROANING)
He did it.
He fucking did it!
(CROWD GASPING)
(CROWD CHEERING)
It's over.
You did it.
We did it.
ELDER GOD: Liu Kang.
You have won the final Mortal Kombat.
For that you are awarded great power.
But we fear it may not be enough.
Enough? For what?
The One Being.
Oh, yes.
(LAUGHING)
(GASPS)
(CHUCKLES)
(MINIONS GRUNTING)
(GROANING)
SCORPION: Come here!
(GRUNTS)
Your spirit lives.
- (SHINNOK CHUCKLES)
- (SCORPION GRUNTS)
(GROANS)
(LAUGHING)
Yes, the One Being.
The end... (CACKLES)
Begins!
(LAUGHING MANIACALLY)
(CAR ALARM BLARES)
(CAR ALARM WAILS)
SUB-ZERO: What is happening?
SCORPION: The end of the realms.
The realms are merging. Hurry.
Lord Raiden told us of a child,
the Chosen One, a soul so pure
that he could hold our power
and save the realms.
You are that child, Liu Kang.
And this is your final battle.
(YELLING)
Whoa.
(PORTAL WHIRRING)
Scorpion?
I thought you were dead.
SCORPION: I was.
What are you doing here?
SCORPION: Trying to stop that.
ONE BEING: Let the unmaking... begin.
Find cover. This is my fight now.
(YELLS)
Lord Raiden, why am I the chosen one?
Because I chose you.
And I chose you
because of what is in here.
You have lost much in this life
and yet blame no one.
Never stop fighting, Liu Kang.
As long as you stand,
goodness and light will stand also.
I am the Chosen One.
(SCREECHES)
(ROARS)
JOHNNY: What the fuck? Look at that.
What now?
Now, we open my luggage.
I'd kiss you but your boyfriend
might get jealous.
Not my boyfriend.
Listen, with the realms merging,
there's a lot of innocent people
in harm's way.
Spread out and help them.
(MINION GROWLS)
- (WHIMPERING)
- (BLADE SLICES)
Get to shelter. Quickly.
(GROWLS)
(ROARS)
Major Jackson Briggs reporting for duty.
Everyone, get behind me.
Well, what are you waiting for?
An invitation?
(GASPING)
(GRUNTS)
Get some! Get some! Get some!
(CLICKS)
Ah.
I'm out.
Me too.
(GROWL)
(GASPS)
- (GROWLS)
- (GRUNTS)
(GROWLS)
(SCREAMS)
Sonya.
Sonya! Sonya, stay with me.
(GROANS)
I'm sorry for being an idiot.
You deserve so much more.
This fight, all the death,
it was worth it to meet you.
(GROWLS)
You really mean it, don't you?
Then... I guess we should
get out of here and... talk.
I love you.
No shit.
(QUIPS)
(BLOWS KISS)
(GRUNTS)
(EXHALES)
ONE BEING: You never could've won.
The destiny of the realms...
is oblivion.
(GRUNTS)
(GRUNTING)
(ONE BEING GRUNTS)
SCORPION: Get over here.
(YELLS)
Oh, shit.
(SHRIEKS)
(GROWLS)
(ONE BEING GROANS)
No, I am eternal. I am everything.
Impossible.
(GROANS)
You don't deserve this.
(ROARS)
(ONE BEING WHIMPERING)
(GRUNTING)
(YELLING)
Liu. Liu, are you there?
Yes.
And no.
It is difficult to explain.
Is it over?
No, not yet.
(KITANA GASPS)
Now is it over?
Yes.
The realms have been separated.
Edenia is free once more.
No more tournaments, no more gods.
Just peace as it should be.
Yeah, I've heard that before.
Shao Kahn's body is gone.
What happens when he or someone else
gets the itch to take over
Earthrealm again?
Then we will be there
to stop them together.
Whoa. Hey. I don't remember
giving you permission...
(THUNDERCLAP)
Someone needs to stop Clearway Law.
Public shouldn't leave reviews for lawyers.