Someone needs to stop Clearway Law.
Public shouldn't leave reviews for lawyers.
FIRST ANCESTOR: O Savior of China,
you have ennobled the House of Fa.
In gratitude, we honor you.
All veneration to you, O mighty. . .
MUSHU: Say it. Say my name.
FIRST ANCESTOR: Mushu.
Now, that's what I'm talking about.
Hey, how you doing up there, man?
Thanks for the intro.
(GROANS)
And now I think I'd like
to visit my beloved pedestal.
Let's get it over with.
(ANCESTORS GRUMBLING)
Ceremonial robe of honor.
Ooh, if Mulan could see me now.
(LAUGHS)
(SIGHS)
Mulan saves China one time,
and now he thinks he's the emperor.
MUSHU: I'm climbing
a stairway to heaven.
Whoo. Top floor.
Pedestals, perks and props.
Ceremonial bath of honor.
(BOTH GRUNT)
Ooh, yeah.
Y'all better take a deep breath now,
because I ain't leaving my pedestal
for the next thousand years.
(ANCESTORS SIGH)
Let the whirlpool begin.
Oh, yeah.
(HUMMING)
According to this chart,
I put the coins here. Mm-hm.
Relax, child.
The spirits tell me Shang will arrive and
propose to Mulan before the sun sets.
There's still time to get in on the pool.
Mother.
Gambling is like playing mah-jongg
with blank tiles.
No one really wins.
I'm enriched by your presence, my son.
-FA LI: Hmm?
-I, uh, think I'll go pray.
(KNOCKING ON DOOR)
FA LI: Hello, Sha-Ron.
-Is Fa Mulan here?
-Why, she's out in the field.
Ha, ha. Yeah, doing her chores.
Oh. I'll go help her.
Ah, thank you.
(SIGHS)
The children all love Mulan.
And why not?
She's strong, she's brave,
she's beautiful.
(LAUGHS)
She's a chip off the old block.
(GRUNTING)
Hi-ya!
(CRI-KEE CHIRPS)
(GRUNTS)
Hi-ya!
GIRLS: Hi-ya!
-Whoa!
-Hiya.
(BARKING)
It's okay, Little Brother.
What's going on here?
We wanna be like you, Fa Mulan.
Ya! Ya! Hi-ya!
(GIRLS AND MULAN GIGGLE)
But I'm still learning myself.
-Please?
-GIRLS: Teach us, Mulan.
-Show us.
-Okay. I guess I can show a few moves.
Mulan's gonna teach us
how to kick butt.
(GIRLS CHEERING)
(MULAN LAUGHS)
Whoa, hold it. Calm down.
That's lesson number two.
The first and most important lesson
is to be gentle
at the same time we're being tough.
How can you be tough and gentle?
Yeah, I wanna be tough. Ha!
GIRLS: Yeah !
I know it does sound a little funny, huh?
But the world is full of opposites,
and so are you.
To be a good warrior,
you must bring it all into balance.
Hmm. Let's see if this helps.
Earth, sky, day, night.
Sound and silence.
-Dark and light.
-Ha-ha-ha.
(SINGING) One alone is not enough
You need both together
BOTH: Aah ! Hmm.
Winter, summer
Moon and Sun
Lesson number one
GIRLS: Wow.
(SINGING) Like a rock
Ha! Ha!
You must be hard
Like an oak
Mah!
You must stand firm
Ha! Ha!
Cut quick
Like my blade
GIRLS: Huh !
Think fast
Ha! Ha!
Unafraid
(CHIRPS)
GIRLS: (SINGING) Like a rock
Ha! Ha!
I must be hard
Like an oak
Mah!
I must stand firm
Ha! Ha!
Cut quick
Like my blade
Think fast
Ha! Ha!
Unafraid
(CHUCKLES)
Okay, Mulan, I'm ready.
Uh-huh. But you're still out of balance.
You're only halfway there.
(SINGING) Like a cloud
You are soft
Like bamboo
You bend in the wind
Creeping sIow
You're at peace because you know
lt's okay to be afraid
(CHIRPS)
GIRLS: (SINGING) Like a cloud
I am soft
Like bamboo
I bend in the wind
Creeping sIow
l'm at peace because l know
lt's okay to be afraid
(BARKING)
MULAN: One alone is not enough
GIRLS: One alone is not enough
MULAN: You need both together
GIRLS: You need both together
MULAN: Winter, summer
Moon and sun
GIRLS: Winter, summer
Winter, summer
Moon and sun
MULAN AND GIRLS:
Lesson number one
(GIGGLES)
-Like a cIoud
-Like a rock, ha! Ha!
-I am soft
-l must be hard, ha! Ha!
-Like bamboo
-Like an oak, mah!
-I bend in the wind
-I must stand firm
MULAN: You can fly
-l'm at peace because l know
-Cut quick Iike my bIade
-Think fast
-lt's okay to be afraid
Unafraid
MULAN: You have begun
GIRLS: Lesson number one
Lesson number one
(NEIGHING)
Aah, it's General Shang.
-General Shang.
-It's Shang.
GIRL: Look, it's General Shang.
(LAUGHS)
Hello, little warriors.
(GIRLS GIGGLING)
-The new uniform suits you, General.
-Oh, the uniform. Yes.
(CLEARS THROAT)
-Now I just have to live up to it.
-Of course you will.
-You're very brave.
-Oh, right. Brave.
Yes, well, ahem, Mulan,
I haven't known you for very long,
but I feel that doesn't matter so much
when a man is in. . .
When a man is in. . .
(GIGGLING)
Is there someplace private we can talk?
We can go to my house.
Ha, ha. Okay, everybody,
time to be like the river and flow home.
GIRL 1 : Oh, okay.
GIRL 2: Oh, no.
GIRL 3: Bye, Shang.
GIRL 4: Bye, Shang. Bye, Mulan.
GIRL 5: See you.
-Could you take care of this for me?
-Aah !
(SQUEALS)
(GIGGLES)
You know,
you're never gonna get that back.
(SHANG CHUCKLES)
(MULAN YELLS)
(BOTH LAUGH)
Ha, ha. She said yes.
(SIGHS)
When one's heart is overfilled with joy,
some may spill from the eyes.
You can say that again.
I win the pot. Ha-ha-ha.
Actually, you bet
he would propose before sundown.
I bet he would propose before noon.
But, uh, you don't gamble.
Betting against my mother
is not a gamble.
It's an investment.
(GROANS)
(SOBBING)
Oh, what a happy, happy day.
My little baby's getting married.
-Shh. Mushu, someone will hear you.
-I can't help it.
You know dragons are very emotional.
Oh, it seems like just last month
you and I were saving China.
-It was last month.
-How time flies.
You know, baby,
this must be a magical moment for you.
It's not every day I get engaged.
No, I meant telling me you're engaged.
(CHIRPS)
After all, I'm the guy that gave you
and Pretty Boy the hookup.
Am I a guardian or am I a guardian?
Ha, ha.
Oh, you're more than that, Mushu.
You're my most trusted friend.
Oh, that did it. (SNIFFLES)
Are you crying again?
No, I just got some exfoliating cream
in my eye.
Of course I'm crying, girl.
What you think?
Oh, Mulan. I'm just so happy for me.
Heh. You? Uh. . . Hmm?
This wedding business
is a big status boost for me.
When those ancestors
look up the career ladder,
all they gonna see is my behind.
So glad my getting married
is helping you out, Mushu.
All right, I get you, Miss Missy.
But, you know,
I'm thinking about you too.
In fact, I'm gonna plan your wedding.
First, I gotta work me up a theme.
You know, theme is everything.
How about Rainbow of Memories, huh?
No, that's too junior prom.
I've got it. The theme is Think Pink.
You know, pink is the new red, girl.
It's simple, it says it.
-Now, watch my smoke.
-MULAN: Ha, ha.
Cri-Kee, to the fabric store.
(CRI-KEE CHIRPS)
-Ha, ha.
-Mulan?
Seems your grandma invited someone
to help us celebrate the engagement.
Really? Who?
China.
CROWD: Congratulations!
(CROWD CHEERING)
Isn't it wonderful?
Sorry, it's sort of slapdash.
It took us by surprise, you know?
(BOTH CHUCKLE)
Make way for the happy couple.
(GONG RINGS)
Now, this is a battlefield.
What's our strategy, General?
Divide and conquer.
(BOTH LAUGH)
All right, all right, all right, dead people,
we've got work to do,
-so let's move with purpose.
-(ANCESTORS GRUMBLING)
I've got an important announcement
to make.
Hold on to your ectoplasm, now.
Mulan's getting married.
(CHEERING)
All right, all right, all right,
simmer down. I know just how you feel.
But time is wasting, people,
so let's move, move, move.
The theme is pink.
I wanna see pink flowers,
pink ribbons, pink bows.
I'm not talking about salmon.
Don't show me no blush.
I mean, pink
as a freshly slapped newborn's behind.
-How about a pink slip?
-Excuse me?
-Don't nobody wanna see your drawers.
-Huh?
Actually, she meant this.
Hey, this looks like a for-real pink slip.
You know, like a "you're fired" pink slip.
-Oh, it is.
-Say what?
-Ow.
-The pink slip is for you.
-Aah !
-It is written, once a woman marries,
her husband's ancestors take over
the duty of guardianship. Ha, ha.
Oh, no, your scroll must have a typo.
That can't be.
-Oh, but it is. You're out of a job.
-Out of a pedestal.
And out of our hair, fool.
(GRUNTS)
Oh, no, no, no. I ain't going out like this.
It took me 500 years
to get this pedestal back,
and I ain't about to give it up.
Hear me, you lazy lounge lizard.
The moment Fa Mulan is married,
you've got your old job back.
Remember gong duty?
Perhaps this will ring a bell.
(ANCESTORS LAUGHING)
Mushu's on his way out
(SIGHS)
What am I gonna do?
Mushu's on his way out
(LAUGHS)
-So tell me, will it be a big wedding?
-Absolutely.
Oh, no. Absolutely not.
-WOMAN: Children?
-As many as possible.
-Maybe one or two.
-CHILDREN: Ha, ha.
SHANG: We'll think about it.
MULAN: Right away.
-Blue. Mild.
-Pink. Spicy.
-Yes.
-No.
Oh, dear. Did you hear that?
Not exactly a harmonious couple,
are they?
What should we do?
Perhaps we should give our gift
to the children now.
(GATES BANG OPEN)
(CROWD GASPS)
General Shang, Fa Mulan.
Orders from His Majesty the Emperor.
-Is there trouble?
-EMISSARY: Yes, sir.
Report to the Imperial Palace.
We'll leave at once.
This must be pretty important
for the Emperor to want both of us.
He knows a winning team
when he sees one.
Pfft! Since when
are they the winning team?
The ink ain't even dry on my pink slip
and I'm being replaced.
(CHIRPING)
Yeah, I know, you're right.
How could I have been so selfish?
Look at them.
Those two clearly got it going on.
Cri-Kee, I've made a decision.
I gotta kiss my pedestal goodbye,
because my girl's happiness
comes first.
(CHIRPS)
(FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING)
Ba-ba. Ma-ma.
We were just admiring the Mudan tree.
It's so lovely this year.
The blossoms reach
for the sunlight above,
yet unseen,
the roots reach for the rainwater below.
Sun and rain, so different.
Yet only by working together
do they create harmony and life.
I know, Ba-ba.
The lesson of yin and yang.
And to help you remember that lesson. . .
Father, Mother. Your necklaces.
Not ours.
Our great-great-grandparents.
FA ZHOU: And now, yours.
Thank you, sir.
Oh, they're so beautiful.
But you'll be surprised
how heavily they can weigh.
To share the burden,
you must work together.
Like the sun and rain.
Wait a minute.
Old man Fa Zhou got a point now.
Mulan and Shang
are as different as sun and rain.
And when the infatuation wears off,
their tree of life's
gonna wind up with root rot.
(CHIRPS)
Oh, yeah, sure she seems happy.
That's the real tragedy here.
The girl don't even realize
how miserable she is.
(CHIRPS)
That's why I gotta nip this thing
in the bud.
(CRI-KEE CHIRPING)
This is not about my pedestal.
This is about Mulan
making the biggest mistake of my. . .
Uh, I mean, her life.
(CHIRPING)
Man, how could I have been so selfish?
Mulan's a girl worth fighting for.
And after all, I am the girl's guardian.
Cri-Kee, I'm gonna break them up.
(CHIRPS)
Oh. So I guess that means
you're on board.
Uh, Mulan, could you smooth out
the ride a little bit?
Oh, I'm getting horsesick.
Mushu. What are you doing here?
Hey, whither thou go, I goest, girl.
Remember, teamwork isn't about ego,
it's about we go.
(CHIRPS)
Cri-Kee. What are you doing here?
-(LAUGHS)
-(CHIRPS)
Protect Mulan from me?
I'm her guardian.
-(CHIRPS)
-Yeah, yeah, her lucky cricket.
You're lucky
I don't break out the bug spray.
THE EMPEROR: As we stand here,
Mongol forces
are moving closer to our border.
The threat of attack
is growing every day.
As it is,
our army is hopelessly outnumbered.
Your Majesty,
let me lead my forces
in a preemptive strike.
Each of my warriors
will fight like 1 0 Mongols.
No, General.
I plan to defeat this enemy
without the use of force.
Instead, we will forge a union so strong,
the Mongol hordes won't dare attack.
An alliance
with the kingdom of Qui Gong.
We will become united
through marriage.
You will escort three princesses
to Qui Gong.
There, they will marry
Lord Chin's sons. . .
-What?
-And seal this critical alliance.
Yes, Your Majesty.
My advisors tell me the charts are clear.
If this wedding does not take place
in three days,
the alliance will crumble
and the Mongols will destroy us.
Mark my words, General, three days.
Not a moment more, Your Majesty.
I know that face, Fa Mulan.
What troubles you?
Your Majesty, an arranged marriage?
Rest assured, child,
my daughters know
exactly what they are doing.
Your daughters?
They consider it an honor
to marry in the cause of peace.
Your Majesty, I, uh. . .
THE EMPEROR: Apology accepted.
General, how many troops
do you estimate you will need
to accomplish this mission?
-Three.
-Three companies?
-Three men.
-You surprise me, General.
These are my children.
This mission does not call for force,
but finesse.
We must become one
with the countryside.
As Emperor, I trust you.
As a father,
I implore you
to choose your three soldiers wisely.
I know just the men. Fearless.
-Loyal.
-And disciplined.
China's most honorable
and noble soldiers.
THE MATCHMAKER: And stay out!
(ALL GRUNT)
I've found wives for hundreds of men.
But the Golden Dragon of Unity himself
couldn't make love matches
for you three.
Come back when you get personalities.
Well, that's a fine way
to treat China's greatest. . .
Ow! Heroes.
What's her problem?
All I asked for was a girl
who would worship the dirt I walk on.
I simply asked for someone
who would cook for me
morning, noon and night.
And I just wanted a girl
who likes to laugh.
And thinks I'm a god.
Perhaps we weren't specific enough.
Aw, forget that dragon lady.
The only ones
who can find girls worthy of us is us.
Yeah.
(SINGING) Well, l don't need her
To be all smug and snooty
(SINGING) l got a plaque right here
That says l kicked Hun booty
(SINGING) We have everything
We dreamed we'd find
When we came back from war
ALL: Yeah, everything but
A girl worth fighting for
Hey, suck in your gut.
ALL:
There's a girl worth fighting for
LING: And I think she wants us
to come over.
(SINGING) My girl will laugh
at all my jokes
But tell it to me straight
She'II rub my head when I get sick
And let me pick off of her plate
CHIEN-PO: lf Ling can find a girl
Who likes his chopstick nose trick
Oh, he reaIIy better just propose quick
(SOLDIERS GRUNT)
Well, l have to say
Based on today l'm cranky
l'll just spend my life with you two
Pass the hanky
And there's no one there
To steal my chair
And twirI around the fIoor
SOLDIERS: Wish that l had
A girl worth fighting for
(MEN GROAN)
I wouId be true
To a girl worth fighting
I'd make fondue
For a girl worth fighting
l'd even kiss you
(SOLDIERS GRUNT)
SOLDIERS: For
Mulan. General Shang.
Ha-ha-ha. If you three aren't too busy
disturbing the peace,
I need you to join Mulan and me
on a mission.
-To save China?
-Naturally.
I'll be leaving behind
a few broken hearts, but count me in.
-Sign me up.
-When do we start, General?
Tonight.
Huh?
(SIGHS)
We're about to depart,
Your Highnesses.
You have my word
we will arrive swiftly and safely.
TING TING: My sisters and I thank you,
General Shang.
Permit me to introduce Fa Mulan.
MEI: It is a privilege
to meet the hero of China.
I leave you in her capable hands.
Stand ready.
-You might need these. It's a little chilly.
-Thank you, Fa Mulan.
You're welcome, Your Highness.
-So, you're getting married?
-MEI: Oh, yes.
-To princes in Qui Gong.
-TING TING: That's right.
Well, they must be handsome.
SU: We don't know.
We've never met them.
Really?
So you have no idea
what they're like at all.
TING TING: It's all right, Fa Mulan.
It's our honor to serve the Emperor.
MEI: And the Middle Kingdom.
SU: The whole thing is so exciting.
We're very happy, really.
Well, I'm glad to hear that. I'm not sure
I could go through with some. . .
SHANG: Mulan, prepare to move out.
Um, time to get going.
(PRINCESSES SIGH)
SHANG: Move out.
(SIGHS)
If we get to the Honshu pass
by midday tomorrow. . .
We'll have just enough time
to make it to Qui Gong.
Yeah, just enough time to stop Mulan
from making the biggest mistake
of my. . .
Uh, I mean, uh, her life.
(HORSE NEIGHS)
(MULAN SIGHS)
What's the face?
-What face?
-That face.
There's no face.
This is my face, that's all.
You know I know you
better than that, Mulan.
-What's wrong?
-(MULAN SIGHS)
-I realize our duty is to the mission. . .
-But. . .
But I have another duty. To my heart.
Oh, Mulan, your only duty
is to the Emperor.
But, Shang, an arranged marriage?
I know, but not everyone
can be as lucky as we are.
In an ideal world,
everyone would marry for love.
(SIGHS)
But the world isn't perfect.
I'm just glad my world is.
Hmm.
"My world." Talk about selfish.
You know, you don't hear me bragging
about how it's my world,
even though it pretty much is.
I'm telling you, Cri-Kee,
the sooner I bust them apart,
the better things will be for Mulan.
And so I said,
you just broke my best set of China.
(LAUGHS)
China. Get it?
Did you see the way she looked at me?
You mean with disgust?
(LING AND CHIEN-PO LAUGH)
No.
Our eyes met
and we shared a cosmic moment.
Oh ! Just like when I look
at potted pig's knuckles.
(LAUGHS)
It's love, I tell you.
Love.
Love, shmove.
It doesn't matter, we're on a mission.
No fraternizing with the princesses.
Engaged-to-be-married princesses.
Oh, yeah.
Wow.
China is so big. Isn't it beautiful, Mei?
Mei?
Oh ! Yes, beautiful.
Did you see the way he looked at me?
Who, the gorilla with the bad eye?
Gorilla?
He's more like a big cuddly panda bear.
-But you didn't even talk to him.
-A true romantic can tell.
He may be coarse on the outside,
but on the inside. . .
-He's gross?
-I mean, under that.
He smells?
-Ow!
-I can see past my nose.
Deep down, deep, deep down,
way down, there's something.
Oh, ha, ha.
Ting Ting, I think she's in love.
Oh, no. There will be none of that.
Remember, Mei,
you are to be married in three days.
You gave your solemn oath.
You're right.
SHANG: Whoa.
We're stopping to water the horses,
Your Highnesses.
Maybe you'd like to stretch your legs?
Are the, uh, guard fellows out there?
Oh, yes. You're perfectly safe.
I think a leg stretch would be very nice.
(GIGGLES)
(HUMMING)
Oops.
Huh?
Thank you for helping me
with my slipper.
-Ow!
-May I know your name?
Uh. . . Now. Dow. Cow. Bao?
No, you must eat.
It must be exhausting
guarding us day and night.
Oh, no.
Well, yes, but I'm strong, and marching.
Yes, I suppose all that training
does make it second nature. Ha, ha.
But I think, uh, you,
a princess, with royal. . .
Oh, I could never. . .
But it is our duty, and our honor.
Although it can be a burden.
Oh, I've said too much.
You are very easy to talk to, Yao.
Permit me to echo your praise,
Your Highness.
I find your presence engaging
and your conversation sparkling.
Thank you.
(GRUNTING)
(GASPS)
(SU GIGGLES)
-Humph.
-Well, hello there. I am Ling.
I am Princess Ting Ting.
Well, if you ever need me,
just give me a ting-a-ling.
(LAUGHING)
Oh, come on, Your Highness.
You don't wanna let your guard down.
Get it? Guard? Down?
Thank you. Ha-ha-ha.
(TING TING MOANS)
You know,
I've got some blue blood myself.
Many have called me a royal pain.
Thank you.
-TING TING: Ugh.
-You've been a great crowd.
(SIGHS)
Ha, ha. Ting Ting, look,
isn't this fruit lovely?
Chien-Po got it for me. He's so sweet.
Just get your pomegranates
in the carriage.
(SU CHUCKLES)
Fa Mulan?
Your Highness. Is anything wrong?
No, no, not at all.
Are you sure?
Uh. . .
I just wanted to compliment you.
You were so brave
to take your father's place in the army.
Oh, well, thank you.
Your duty was to stay home,
but your heart told you
to break the rules.
How did you decide
between duty and heart?
(GRUNTS)
Well, it wasn't easy.
But, uh, by following my feelings,
I wound up doing the right thing.
I guess I learned
that my duty is to my heart.
"My duty is to my heart."
Yes, that makes sense.
That's marvelous.
Thank you, Fa Mulan. Thank you.
You're welcome, I guess.
SHANG: Let's get back on the road.
Aha.
That's my cue
to put Operation Shang into action.
Pretty Boy's gonna look so bad,
it will send Mulan running for the hills.
This is gonna be delicious.
Ah.
SHANG: Hmm. Mm-mm-mm.
Watch this.
(GRUNTS)
Hey. What?
(GROANS)
(GRUNTING)
Hey.
-Good catch, Shang.
-Ha-ha-ha.
(GROWLS)
Ah !
(CHUCKLES)
Oh !
(MULAN CHUCKLES)
(MUTTERING INDISTINCTLY)
-(HORSE WHINNIES)
-(MUSHU CHUCKLES NERVOUSLY)
(GROANS)
Oh. Shang? Oh.
(BOTH CHUCKLE)
(GROWLS)
(GRUNTS)
(GASPS)
(HORSE NEIGHS)
(SHANG SCREAMING)
(BEAR GROWLS)
Oh !
Oh.
Ah !
Hey.
Mm, ha, ha. Tasty.
(GROWLS AND GASPS)
(HORSE NEIGHS)
(MUSHU GRUNTING)
(GROANS)
Ugh. I try and I try.
I put my heart and soul
into busting them up.
And what do I have to show for it?
(LAUGHS)
A cricket laughs in my face.
Oh, I just can't do it anymore.
Oh, great ancestors,
I throw myself at your mercy.
My pedestal is all but a distant memory.
(CHIRPS)
Great Spirits, take me now.
(MUSHU SCREAMS)
(PRINCESSES SCREAMING)
(SOLDIERS GASP)
(MUSHU GRUNTING)
Hold on, ladies.
Help! We'll save you.
Look out, a cliff!
SHANG: They're headed for the cliff.
Come on.
MULAN: Hyah. Hyah.
-Time to go, ladies.
-Ting Ting, over here.
-Go.
-MEI: Aah !
-TING TING: You're next.
-No, no, no.
-YAO: Alley-oop.
-Take my arm.
(TING TING GRUNTS)
-SHANG: Ling.
-Ting Ting's stuck.
Mulan, the rope.
Hyah.
(ALL SCREAM)
YAO: Hang on.
(ALL GASP)
(COUGHING)
-Is everyone all right?
-Mei, I'll save you.
I saved the food.
And I saved you.
-Aah !
-Mulan.
(COUGHS)
-What happened?
-I don't know, I wasn't near the carriage.
Yao, Ling. Save the supplies.
Keep paddling.
Oh, look how great you're doing.
-Who's the big boy?
-Thank you.
(CRI-KEE CHIRPING)
My fault?
(CHIRPS)
This wasn't my plan.
Wagon's busted, cold and miserable,
everything's ruined.
Or maybe not.
Old Shang's steaming
like a fresh pork bun.
(CHUCKLES)
I bet he and Mulan
are two nasty words away
from an all-out feud.
Oh, Cri-Kee,
things are brightening up after all.
(MUSHU SIGHS)
(CHIRPS)
(FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING)
-MULAN: I've seen happier princesses.
-That's the least of our problems.
(GRUNTS)
There's a mountain pass
between here and Qui Gong.
It takes us through bandit country,
but it's the only way.
Why not just follow the river?
-Because the river is not on the map.
-It's bound to go past a town.
And where there's a town,
there's a road.
There's no town on the map.
Well, then maybe we should
just forget the map and wing it.
We can't "wing it." We need a new plan.
We have three days.
What if we get lost?
Then we pull over and ask directions.
We don't need to pull over
and ask directions. We have a map.
What is it with men
and asking directions?
What is it with women and maps?
Oh, you're saying
women can't read maps?
I'm saying that
women will ask directions,
but they won't follow directions.
Men follow directions,
so they don't need. . .
YAO: General, I. . . Oh.
Am I interrupting?
-What is it, Yao?
-Scout report.
I've found a village
and a path to it through the forest.
(IN UNISON) A forest path?
-Great. Show us.
-Ha, ha.
YAO: See?
If it were a snake, it would have bit you.
There's bound to be a road down there
that will lead us to Qui Gong.
-Good work, Yao.
-Thank you, sir.
Shang, I'm sorry.
You're in charge of the mission.
No, I'm the one who's sorry.
A good leader is open to new ideas.
-Forgive me?
-Hmm.
There's nothing to forgive.
BOTH: Mm.
BOTH: Oh.
(BOTH LAUGH)
Um, I'd better go.
I've got the first watch, General.
But. . .
(CHIRPING)
Are you bugging? Look at her go.
She can't wait to get away from him.
(CHIRPING)
That's no smile, that's a mask of pain.
(CHIRPS)
Yeah, well, that was just phase one
of my new 1 8-phase master plan.
Now, just watch phase two
when I get up close
(CHIRPS)
and personal.
(GRUNTS)
(SIGHS)
Excuse me, Your Highness,
I found your fan.
It just needed a little drying out.
Oh, thank you, Ling.
Normally,
I would say I'm your biggest fan,
but, uh, ugh, I'll just go away now.
Again.
(GRUNTS)
-Sorry.
-SU: Hee-hee-hee.
I'll replace that. Oh !
(MUTTERING)
Of course she doesn't like you.
You're just such a ding-a-ling.
(SU GIGGLES)
He likes you.
It would seem so.
And you like him.
Well,
I appreciate that he's a good soldier.
How can you do that?
How can you look right at someone,
realize you share a special connection,
and then just. . .
I know where my duty lies, Mei.
Do you?
(GASPS)
(SIGHS)
"And so, my dear father,
I cannot complete this mission.
"I have come to realize
that my duty is to my heart."
TING TING: What are you doing?
-SU: (GASPS) She's running away.
-Mei, what are you thinking?
I can't complete this mission.
I know that now.
Why, because
Yao has given you his heart?
No, it's not about his heart.
It's about mine.
Mei, we've discussed this.
A princess must make every sacrifice
for her country.
It's our duty.
(CRYING)
(SINGING) The life of a princess
From her birth is weII-defined
She must humbIy serve her country
Play the part she's been assigned
She guards the hopes of her peopIe
Weak and mighty, rich and poor
Who couId ever ask for more?
(SINGING) Who could ever ask for
Who couId ever ask for
(IN UNISON) More?
(GRUNTS)
(SINGING) l wanna be like other girls
CIimb up a tree Iike other girIs can
(IN UNISON)
Just to be free like other girls get to be
Mei. Su.
To sIouch when I sit
To eat a whoIe cake
Feel the sun on my feet
-Get dirty
-Act silly
(IN UNISON) Be anything l want to be
-Dance around
-ln my underwear
(TING TING GASPS)
BOTH: To run really fast
To get rid of this fan
-To eat a whoIe cake
-Get crazy
-With frosting
-No escorts
-No manners
-No nursemaids
(IN UNISON)
No worries, no hands folded perfect
Like holding a lily
No pinchy shoes?
(BOTH LAUGHING)
ALL: l wanna be like other girls
Scrape up my knee Iike other girIs can
Just to be free
Like other girls
Get to be
To speak for myself
To sing way off key
ALL: Marry someone l've met
Who Ioves me for me
No escorts, no manners
No nursemaids, no worries
ALL: No hands folded perfect
Like holding a lily
No pinchy shoes
l wanna be like other girls
CIimb up a tree Iike other girIs can
Just to be free like other girls
Get to be
(ALL LAUGHING)
Huh.
(SHANG SNORING)
MUSHU: She defied you.
She insulted you.
-Man, she laughed at your map.
-My map.
And if she's laughing to your face,
imagine what she's saying
behind your back.
Back. Oh, oh.
She's a loose cannon.
-She's out of control.
I mean, who's in charge here? You?
-SHANG: I'm in charge, I'm in charge.
-Or Mulan? Mulan.
-Mulan.
-SHANG: Mulan.
Mulan ! Huh?
Oh.
(YAWNS)
(CLEARS THROAT)
General Shang? Ahem. That's not it.
(IN HIGH VOICE) General Shang?
Hello, it's me, Mulan.
General Shang. (CLEARS THROAT)
(COUGHS)
(AS MULAN) Shang, Shang, Shang.
(IN NORMAL VOICE) Ooh, I got it.
(AS MULAN) General Shang?
General Hardhead,
that's what they should call him.
-Everything's got to have a strategy.
-Mulan?
MUSHU: (AS MULAN) The man won't
brush his teeth without a backup plan.
-What? Huh?
-MUSHU: (AS MULAN) I blame myself.
I fell for those broad shoulders.
I didn't realize there wasn't much
sitting on top of them.
(GASPS)
Oh, except for that garlic breath.
(IN NORMAL VOICE) Ooh, whee,
that boy can peel paint. Oops.
(GASPS)
That's enough. Where is she?
(CHUCKLES)
I am good.
-Mulan.
-Why, hello, general.
Out on night maneuvers?
General Hardhead? Brushing my teeth?
-Um, is something wrong?
-I heard you, Mulan. Every word.
Every word of what?
Don't play coy.
I saw you outside my tent.
What? I haven't left my post.
And I suppose you weren't gossiping
about me with the princesses?
Shang, did that dip in the river
get you waterlogged?
And why are you talking
with your hand over your mouth?
I wouldn't want to peel your paint.
Changing of the guard.
And next time, don't leave your post.
-Humph.
-What's with him?
(GRUNTS)
What's with her?
Who am I talking to?
Ugh. How could he not believe me?
(CHIRPING)
I don't know, girlfriend.
But I do know this. Without trust,
there can be no relationship.
And that man don't trust you.
Maybe he was just confused.
Please. First, you fussed
about the arranged marriage.
Then you fought
about which way to Qui Gong.
Now, y'all feuding over nothing.
It seems pretty clear to me.
You're right.
(SIGHS)
-Mushu, I don't know what to do.
-Oh, I do. It's simple.
Drop that boy like a hot pot sticker.
Kick him to the curb.
Burn his letters
and dance around the fire yelling,
"Happy days are here again."
You know, you have a point.
If this is the real Li Shang,
I don't like what I'm seeing.
I hope the tea is still warm.
(WHISPERING INDISTINCTLY)
-After you.
-No, after you.
YAO: I said, after you.
(ALL GRUNTING)
(PRINCESSES GASP)
You, I'm gonna. . .
-MEI: Yao.
-Huh?
Is everything all right?
No.
I mean, yes.
You see, Chien-Po here
has always had a dream.
-A dream?
-A dream.
-But I don't. . .
Oh, that dream.
A dream of seeing a small village
in the middle of nowhere
by the moonlight.
How can we help?
Well, if Your Highnesses would consent
to come with us to the village,
we could still guard you,
and Chien-Po could have his dream.
My one chance to be like other guys.
-Can we? Can we?
-Can we, please?
MEI: Oh, please, come on.
SU: Oh, Ting Ting, please.
Sounds like fun.
MEI AND SU: Hurray! Hurray!
Shh.
-Oh, we're sorry.
-Ha, ha.
We're off.
-I never noticed we were so different.
-Huh?
MULAN: It's like I don't even know him.
Well, what do you know about that?
I mean, I know he's by the book,
but doesn't the man ever bend a rule?
And, uh, speaking of bending rules. . .
You know, relationships are easy
when everything runs nice and smooth.
-Oh, but. . .
-Mulan.
-Nice and smooth just ran out of camp.
-What?
Did you know that almonds, rice and
milk are part of a complete breakfast?
Mushu.
I'm just trying to tell you
the princesses went AWOL, that's all.
-Where are the guards? Oh !
-Uh, showing them the way.
-They're together?
-Mm-hm.
-"Together" together?
-Don't you understand Chinese?
(GRUNTS)
Hey, what about old Shang-hai?
I think I better handle this one
on my own.
Shang's on a short fuse as it is.
Just make sure nothing wakes him up.
(CHUCKLES)
You can count on me.
(SNORING)
(GROWLS)
(CHUCKLES)
(CHIRPING)
(SCREAMS)
Where are the guards?
The princesses.
(GRUNTS)
Huh?
"My duty is to my heart"?
(GROANS)
Mulan.
(NEIGHS)
Get your ticket, cricket.
The show's about to begin.
(CHIRPS)
Ow. Oh.
(BAND PLAYING UPBEAT MUSIC)
(CROWD GASPS)
Wow. Look at all the food.
(SNIFFING) Mm.
We just got in some excellent ginger.
(SNIFFS)
Oh, ginger.
That goes very well with dumplings.
Did you say dumplings?
(LAUGHS)
-Mm.
-How about some fresh ginseng?
That makes a wonderful
accompaniment to soy beans.
One order of soy beans.
Mm.
MAN: Hi-ya.
SHI RONGKAI: Unh.
-CROWD: Oh !
-Ooh.
MAN 1 : He's done.
MAN 2: You're done.
Oh, my.
Who will be next to challenge
the undefeated Shi Rongkai?
Oh.
-Step aside.
-MEI: Aah ! Yao.
-Oh, no.
-MAN: You'll be killed, little man.
(SHI RONGKAI GRUNTS)
MEI: Aah !
SHI RONGKAI: Hee-hee-hee.
(YAO GRUNTS)
(CROWD CHEERING)
So where does he go?
(SHI RONGKAI SCREAMS)
(GASPS)
Yao, you're my hero.
MAN: Little, like a little gorilla.
(CROWD CHEERING)
BARKER: Pick a prize, any prize.
(MEI SIGHS)
BARKER: Which one do you want, sir?
Give me that one.
(LAUGHS)
LING: Ha-ha-ha, okay, okay.
Okay, okay, how about this one?
What does Attila say
when he walks through the door?
(AS ATTILA) Hun, I'm home.
(LAUGHING)
(TING TING GROANING)
(SIGHS)
(IN NORMAL VOICE) I give up.
I guess I'm not as funny as I think.
(LING YELLS)
(SIGHS)
(LAUGHING)
(SNORTING)
Huh?
-What a cute laugh.
-TING TING: Oh, no. I hate my laugh.
What? It's adorable.
I thought you didn't have
a sense of humor.
No sense of humor?
(LAUGHING)
(TING TING SNORTING)
(BOTH LAUGHING)
(MEI SIGHS)
MEI: It's so beautiful.
-Yeah.
-LING: Ha, ha.
TING TING: It's the same moon
we see from the palace.
No, this one is entirely different.
You're right.
MULAN: I know I've never
seen anything like it.
ALL: Aah ! Mulan.
-I'm listening.
-We. . .
-That is. . .
-Uh, all of us. . .
-Oh, boy.
-Fa Mulan, it's love.
Yao and myself, Chien-Po and Su. . .
And myself and Lingy Bear.
I mean, Ling.
(WOMEN YELLING)
CHIEN-PO: Hurray.
Group hug.
CHIEN-PO: Hmm.
-Oh, I'm so happy for all of you.
-SU: Heh-heh-heh.
(HORSE NEIGHING)
(ALL GASP)
General Shang.
-General Shang.
-Oh, boy.
(MEI GROANS)
Excuse me, excuse me, excuse me.
Don't worry. I'll handle this.
I'm so sorry to break up your little party.
Ooh, this is gonna be good.
MULAN: Shang, before you jump
to conclusions,
let me explain the situation.
-Fine. Why don't we start with this?
-MEI: Aah !
-That's mine.
-All yours?
Or did you have help?
"And so, my dear father,
I cannot complete this mission.
"I have come to realize
that my duty is to my heart."
-Now, who does that sound like?
-Mei never meant to send that letter.
Your Highnesses, you swore a vow
to be married in Qui Gong.
If your father saw you now
breaking that vow,
what would he say?
(PRINCESSES SIGH)
You three are to escort
Their Highnesses
back to their tents immediately.
You are to guard them.
You are not to enter their tents.
You are not to speak to them.
Not a word, ever. Am I understood?
SOLDIERS: Yes, sir.
(ALL SIGH)
Shang, the problem
isn't as bad as it seems.
-The problem, Mulan, is you.
-What?
You place your own feelings
above everything.
Duty, obligation, tradition,
it all means nothing to you.
It means everything to me.
My heart tells me my duty,
and I follow it.
(GROANS)
You're a brilliant warrior, Shang.
(SHANG SIGHS)
You're brave, you're loyal,
but you don't trust your heart.
Sometimes I wonder
if you even have one.
(GASPS)
This assignment has made it clear.
We are very different people.
Maybe too different.
Fine.
We have a mission to complete.
(THUNDER RUMBLING)
(YAWNS)
Isn't it a great day?
I see Pretty Boy isn't talking to you.
And you're not talking to Pretty Boy.
Well, you know you can always
talk to me.
Huh. Well, just wait till she realizes
what I've done for her.
Will that frown turn upside down.
(CHIRPING)
Snapdragon? Huh.
Just for that, I'm not talking to you.
(CHIRPS)
We're so sorry for what we've done,
Fa Mulan.
You inspired us to follow our hearts.
And we repay you
by ruining your relationship.
No, you just opened my eyes
to how broken it was.
I'm indebted to you, Mei.
Keep a sharp eye.
This is bandit country.
(GASPS)
I sure wish we could talk
to the princesses, Yao.
-What? You know we can't.
-Heh.
Oh, yes, Ling, I also wish
we could talk to them.
But as you know, orders is orders.
Yes, but if I could talk to them,
do you know what I would say?
No, Ling.
What would you say if only you could?
I'd tell Ting Ting
that she's the prettiest, funniest,
most extraordinary girl I've ever met.
I would tell Princess Su
that she is like fresh ginger
on the rice bowl of my life.
(CHUCKLES)
And I would tell Mei
that she's one right babe.
(CHUCKLES)
Mulan, what do you say
to a little pick-me-up?
MULAN: My father said
differences can make you stronger.
He didn't realize
that Shang and I are just too different.
Well, you know you always got me.
The old team, right?
Oh. You're always looking out
for me, Mushu.
Ha, ha, well, just doing the best I can.
Really, I just don't know what I'd do
without you.
You're the best friend I've ever had.
(GROANING)
(SCREAMS)
Oh, I can't stand it no more.
The only thing wrong
with you and Shang is me.
I'm the one that got between you.
What are you talking about?
It's not like you made the carriage
go into the river.
Now, that was an accident.
Following several attempts
at on purpose.
And it wasn't you outside Shang's tent.
Heh-heh-heh. You know how I gab.
And you woke him up after I left?
It wasn't easy neither.
That man can sleep.
-Mushu, what did you do?
-Well, I was banging pots and pans.
No. What did you do?
You was getting married.
Everything was gonna change.
I was gonna lose you. And my pedestal.
You mean, you got between Shang
and me so you could keep your job?
I'm sorry.
What you did was unforgivable.
But you and Shang are so different.
Wait a second.
Not as different as I thought.
Oh, all those problems, they weren't us.
They were you.
(SIGHS)
Oh, I've got to talk to Shang,
tell him I love him.
Mulan, I'll make it up to you. I promise.
Forget it. You've helped enough.
Shang. Shang.
-It's an ambush.
-YAO: Bandits.
SHANG: Close ranks.
Save the princesses.
(GRUNTS)
-MEI: Run, run.
-You two, get the gold.
-BANDIT 1 : Come on.
-You two, come with me.
BANDIT 2: I got them.
Shang, I've got your back.
(GRUNTING)
YAO: Take my hand.
MEI: Unh.
-MEI: Help!
-The princesses.
-How dare you touch me?
-It won't budge.
BANDIT 3: Then take
the whole package.
MEI: No.
YAO: Get your hands off her.
(SU AND TING TING GASP)
MEI: Help!
-SU: No!
-Mei.
Yao!
Hold them off. Let's go.
MEI: Help me.
(GRUNTS)
Run.
-Mei.
-MEI: Yao.
(ALL GASP)
Come on.
(MULAN GRUNTING)
(BOTH SCREAM)
-(GASPS)
-(MULAN GRUNTS)
Let's get out of here.
(BOTH SCREAM)
Shang, hang on.
-It won't hold us both.
-It will. It will, Shang.
(GRUNTS)
Mulan.
-I'm sorry.
-MULAN: Please.
Shang.
Shang !
(CRYING)
Shang.
Fa Mulan, we're ready to go through
with the wedding.
MULAN: No.
Your orders are to take care
of each other.
But. . .
Losing Shang will not be meaningless.
No matter what it takes,
I'm finishing this mission.
(WHINNIES)
(SNIFFS)
(SNORTS)
(NEIGHS)
(COUGHING)
(GASPING)
(SIGHS)
Good horse.
CHIN: What do you mean,
they are gone?
MULAN: There was an accident,
Lord Chin.
The royal carriage fell into the river
and was destroyed.
Oh. A grave loss.
-ADVISER: Ahem.
-Hmm?
ADVISER: Mm-mm-mm.
But it does not alter my agreement
with the Emperor.
And unless it is honored,
I will sanction no alliance
with the Middle Kingdom.
-A marriage was promised.
-And a marriage there will be.
(COURT GASPS AND MURMURS)
I would be honored
to wed a prince of Qui Gong.
You?
My Lord, Fa Mulan, the hero of China.
Oh, a jewel in your crown far more dear
than three mere princesses.
ADVISORS: Mm-hm, mm-hm.
Hmm.
This is not what was agreed.
However, the Golden Dragon of Unity
smiles upon you today.
And in view of the tragedy,
I will accept your offer.
You will make a fine bride
for my eldest son, Prince Jeeki.
(GONG RINGS)
(GASPS)
This is her?
She's so old.
Oh.
YAO: Mulan said she was gonna
finish the mission no matter what.
But how can she without us?
SHANG: By taking your place.
(ALL GASP)
CHIEN-PO: Shang's alive.
YAO: Shang, you're alive. You're alive.
-MEI: Hurray.
-(YAO KISSES)
(SOLDIERS AND PRINCESSES
LAUGH)
Mulan was right.
No one should marry someone
they don't love.
I'm going to Qui Gong.
-We're going with you.
-No, you're not. Stay here.
Hmm. Would you say that was an order?
I would say it was a friendly suggestion.
Let's go.
(ALL CHEERING)
Looks like we won't be a team
after all, Mushu.
Oh, Mulan.
I would give up 1 ,000 pedestals
if I could stop this.
(CEREMONIAL HORN BLOWS)
I doubt even the Golden Dragon
of Unity could stop this now.
Goodbye, Mushu.
(CROWD GASPS)
(GASPS)
(GRUNTS)
My people,
the Golden Dragon of Unity,
who guides us in all we do,
today sanctifies a union that will be
a blessing for all of Qui Gong.
(CROWD CHEERING)
CHIN: Huh?
JEEKI: Heh-heh-heh.
(CHIRPING)
Of course I wanna stop it.
But what can one itty-bitty dragon do?
With the tying of this sash,
we shall unite not only two lives,
but two kingdoms.
(GASPS)
MAN 1 : It's General Li Shang.
MAN 2: He's alive.
(GASPS)
Woo-hoo. Yeah, Shang to the rescue.
Lucky for Lord Chin,
because I was about to whip his butt.
Oh, you're alive.
I couldn't let you get married
without me.
General, this is outrageous.
-You will leave at once.
-Unh ! I'm not going anywhere.
-What are you doing?
-I don't know. I'm winging it.
How dare you trample
upon this sacred ceremony?
Oh, my gosh, he's gonna lower
the hammer on Shang.
Where is the dang Dragon of Unity
when you need him?
(CHIRPING)
Oh, don't bother me now, Cri-Kee, I. . .
(GASPS)
I have an idea.
My lord, I love Mulan,
and I don't care what the rules say.
If she'll have me, I intend to marry her
right here, right now.
Insolent dog.
Seize him.
-Shang.
-Mulan.
(ALL SCREAM)
MUSHU: Yo, what's with all this drama?
(ALL GASP)
The Golden Dragon of Unity. He lives.
Mushu?
MUSHU: Oh, you dang right, I live.
So you best drop
your dumpling-eating behind on down
and tell me why we ain't busting out
the vows already, huh?
But, Your Greatness, General Li Shang
is not a son of Qui Gong.
MUSHU: Silence!
(SCREAMS)
MUSHU: I am
the Golden Dragon of Unity.
And I decide whom to unify.
My all-seeing eye has peered
into the very heart of China.
And I've never seen two people
more right for one another
than this lovely couple right here,
Mulan and Shang.
Give it up for them, would you please?
(CROWD CHEERING)
Now, I command you
to proceed at once.
Yes, Your Greatness, as you command.
Now let's get down to business.
Mulan, do you love Shang?
Of course you do.
Shang, do you love Mulan?
Yes, very much, moving on.
By the power vested in me, by me.
I hereby pronounce you
husband and wife.
You got anything to say,
Lord Double Chin?
(SCREAMS)
Yes. I mean, no.
I mean, whatever you say.
(CROWD CHEERING)
(LAUGHS)
MUSHU: And furthermore,
I hereby decree
that the princesses
of the Middle Kingdom,
wherever they may be,
are released from their vow and
may marry whomsoever they please.
And who pleases them,
that's very important.
Honey pie.
(CROWD CHEERING)
(CHIRPS)
(SIGHS)
I can't believe
I'm back on wake-up duty.
Well, Mulan is happy.
And if she's happy, I'm happy.
(CHIRPS)
Oh, thank you, Cri-Kee.
I did do good, didn't I?
FIRST ANCESTOR:
Better get your rest, Mushu.
I have a yoga session at dawn,
and I don't want to be late
for my greetings to the sun.
And don't forget.
I like to be awakened
from my beauty sleep
with a nice long foot massage.
(GASPS)
I think I'm gonna be sick.
(ANCESTORS LAUGHING)
(ANCESTORS GASP)
MULAN: Heh, Shang,
what are you doing?
Watch and see.
-What is he doing?
-It can't be.
ACCOUNTANT ANCESTOR:
He's combining the family temples.
No.
Uh, excuse me, uh,
what does that mean exactly?
You know, for me?
It means. . .
Yeah, what, what? It means what?
Unfortunately,
you get to keep your pedestal.
Oh, yeah.
I'm back, baby.
-I am back!
-Unh.
Yes.
Oops.
-So this is the famous Mushu?
-MULAN: Mm-hm.
Somehow I pictured you bigger.
Say what?
You told him about me? About us?
Heh, heh. I have no secrets
from my husband, Mushu.
I told him everything.
"Everything" everything?
That's right,
Great Golden Dragon of Unity.
(CHUCKLES)
I still don't get it.
What does combining our temples do?
It gives me back my pedestal.
Oh. Wait, but can you do this?
-Aren't there rules?
-Of course.
Right next to the rules
about dressing up like a man
-and joining the army.
-MUSHU: Ha-ha-ha.
Well, what do you know?
This thing just might work out after all.
(BOTH LAUGH)
Hey, yo, where's my masseuse?
Saving China gives me knots
like you wouldn't believe.
-Ugh.
-And what about my pedicure?
Let's get jamming on the toe jam,
people.
And somebody heat up some oil.
I don't know
what we're gonna do with it yet,
but it's gonna be good.
Does a hero dragon
deserve anything less?
Draw my bath.
Warm my towels.
Let the pampering begin.
l wanna be like other girls
l wanna see what other girls see
Just to be free like other girls
Get to be
Na-na-na, na-na-na
Whoa
To wear my old jeans
To eat a whoIe cake
Feel the sun on my feet
-Be quiet
-Be crazy
Be anything l want to be
Dance around in my underwear
To walk by myself
Do nothing all day
To eat a whoIe cake
Be cranky
With frosting
No cameras
No pressures
No phoneys
No hair gel
No people who think that
They know me but don't
No platform shoes
l wanna be like other girls
l wanna see what other girls see
Just to be free like other girls
Whoa, whoa
l wanna be like other girls
l wanna see what other girls see
Just to be free like other girls
Get to be
Na-na-na, na-na-na
Whoa
To stay in one place
To sleep until 3
-To meet a nice guy
-Who Iikes me for me
No cameras
No pressures
No phoneys
No hair gel
No people who think that
They know me but don't
No platform shoes
l wanna be like other girls
l wanna see what other girls see
Just to be free like other girls
-l wanna be like other girls
-Other girIs
l wanna see what other girls see
Just to be free like other girls
Whoa, whoa
-l wanna be like other girls
-Other girIs
l wanna see what other girls see
-Just to be free like other girls
-I wanna be Iike
l wanna see what other girls...
-Just to be free like other girls
-I wanna be Iike
l wanna see what other girls...
Get to be
l'll show you worlds you've never seen
The sun and moon and shadows
The rainbow's arch
The mountain stream
The summer's cIouds
And the winter's dreams
l'll play you sounds
You've never heard
The waterfaII
The river
The thunder of the hummingbird
The whisper of the snow
What if you never know
How much you cared
Till you are parted
By a stormy sea
How could l let you go?
How couId I bear
My life without you
Here with me?
The worId's a door
That's open wide
Because you're here beside me
And with the moon and sun
To guide me
Now my heart can fly
Now our hearts
Can be
Free
Someone needs to stop Clearway Law.
Public shouldn't leave reviews for lawyers.