That's Shuici Iguchi!
As I thought, the League of Villains!
Shit!
It's sturdy!
I'll go closer!
Deadbolt!
Sorry!
Dabi!
You're too persistent!
Bastards...
What are you up to-
Don't ask pointless questions.
Why are the heroes...
The information was leaked...
Leaked? From where...?
Who knows...
The pursuit team was overtaken.
Now...
You don't have to say it.
Leave it to me.
Endeavor!
The one who's moved up to
number one, huh.
At this late hour...
...you're working hard!
Jetburn!
Hey, hey, hey!
I'll run you over, Endeavor!
Mister, get back.
Prominence... Burn!
Damn, is this it?
Endeavor...
You were here?
Why didn't you gave us a hand, Hawks?
I just got here, Endeavor-san.
What about the League guys?
They were all doubles made
with Twice's quirk.
What's this?
Probably... a life-support system?
To transport a new type of Nomu or something?
What did you say?!
What in the world were Shigaraki and
the others transporting?
I was getting tired of waiting, Nine.
It was worth the wait.
The experiment was a success.
The world became a superhuman society,
and about 80% of the world's population
now has some kind of special trait.
Superhuman Society
I, Izuku Midoriya, was quirkless,
but then, I had a fateful meeting with the number one hero, All Might,
and he transfered his quirk,
One for All, to me.
U.A. HIGH SCHOOL
Afterwards, I enrolled to the hero
course at U.A. High School.
A prestigious school that has
produced many heroes...
...and where I continue to run toward my dream.
That's right,
this is the story of how I became
the greatest hero.
Hey, girls!
Come hang out with us!
--Yeah, yeah!
--No, thanks.
Don't say tha-
--What the heck?!
--It won't c-come off!
Are you ok?
Ladies.
--Thanks!
--You saved us!
No, that wasn't me just now...
Down! Look down!
Asui, 70 meters past the rocks!
There's a child drowning!
Mommy!
Momm-
A-Are you ok?
Why are you crying?!
Your face's scary...
Swimming forbidden!
Swimming forbidden past the rocks!
OFF LIMITS
It's dangerous to go past here,
so please don't enter.
--That's amazing!
--Not bad!
This it's not a show...
Shoto-kun, do you think you can make
some more ice please?
Sure.
Here you go.
That's too much!
There are so many heroes.
Hmm.
Oh?
Onee-chan?
U.A. Hero Agency!
Okay, I'll send someone right away.
Kaminari-kun, Matsuda-san in the west district said his battery's gone bad again!
Again?
That old man needs to get a new one...
Do your best, Chargezuma!
--Go, go!
Hi, this is U.A. Hero Agency.
We'll solve anything for you with a sparkle.
You found the lost dog?
Yeah, just now.
Don't worry, the dog's fine.
Good work.
Next you'll be looking for a parrot.
My little brother's lost!
I can't find him anywhere!
It's ok, calm down.
--First, what are your names?
--Don't worry. Yes!
Iida-kun, granny Sato hurt her back!
Got it!
I will rush over at once!
There's a lost child in the shopping arcade!
Any heroes who are free right now-
No way.
That was fast.
Don't say that, Bakugo.
Uraraka, I'll go with you-
NABU ISLAND GUIDEBOOK
You can't find a lost kid with your quirk!
If we're looking for a lost kids...
...then it's my turn.
Uraraka, I'll go too.
==========
Iogi Heights
====
U.A. High School
1-A
Agency
One for All: Full Cowling... 8%!
Hero Agency!
Class 1-A!
Heading out!
The twenty of us in U.A. High School's
hero course Class 1-A...
...have come to Nabu Island, an island far
from the main island of Japan.
Even though we've acquired our
provisional hero licenses,
why are us students even working as
heroes on this island?
LAST MONTH AT U.A. HIGH SCHOOL
Of course, there's a reason behind this...
PRINCIPAL'S OFFICE
Placing hero course students in areas with no pro heroes...
A practical hero work recommendation project?
Yes, the current superhuman
society is in chaos.
You, the number one hero and
Symbol of Peace,
are officially retired.
The villains are gaining power
because of that.
Are you saying that in order to
go up against them,
it's imperative that we train like this the next
generation of heroes?
The superiors at the Heroes Public
Safety Commission think so.
Well, I'm sure you have your
thoughts about this,
but I hope you will cooperate with us.
The hero work recommendation project.
You all will be stationed on Nabu Island,
an outlying island in southern Japan.
========
Their pro hero who lives there retired
due to old age.
You all will work as heroes there
until a successor arrives.
That's super hero-like!
I mean, we will be heroes!
Excited, yey!
I'm bursting with eagerness!
This isn't an internship or a work study.
It's real hero work...
I've wanted to be one since I was little...
Finally, I will...
Listen to what I have to say
until the end!
Good.
As a rule, you will not have backup from
any teachers or pro heroes.
Of course, if something happens, you will
bear the responsibility for it.
Bear that in mind, and behave
as a hero should.
Understand?
Yes!
Mahoro-chan, where are you?
Where are you, Maho-
Katsuma-kun?
You're Katsuma Shimano, right?
A hero...
You've been separated from your
big sister, right?
Now come with me-
You're late!
Way too late!
Onee-chan!
What's your name!
I'm D-Deku!
Um... and you are?
I'm Katsuma's older sister, Mahoro!
Eh, I guess you found him already...
I'm glad.
That's not to be glad at all!
Why did it take over an hour to find a lost kid?!
Explain yourself!
You're part of that famous U.A.'s hero course
but you are useless!
If this is what we get, then maybe that grandpa
hero we had before would do better.
I-I'm sorry...
Well, nothing you can do.
You are just a high school student after all.
I'm sorry.
I'm very sorry...
Deku-kun?
Next time, make sure you do your job
properly, okay, Deku?
G-Got it, I'll try harder...
Let's go, Katsuma!
Eh?
Ah... okay...
Um...
Thanks...
You don't have to thank him!
Deku-kun, what's going on?
What are you apologizing for?
I got scolded for taking too long
at finding a lost kid.
Huh? What the heck?
But, I'm glad...
About what?
That Katsuma-kun was able to get
back to his sister safely.
Deku-kun, you really feel like
Deku-kun, huh.
Eh? What do you mean?
That you're a hero to the bone!
=========
==========
NABU CORNER
STORE
RESTROOM
Those heroes were useless like I thought.
It's not like a small island like this has
any crimes in the first place.
I'm sure they're probably especially bad,
even among U.A. students.
They came to look for me though.
That boy was definely a hero.
Then I'll be the one to unmask
who he really is.
Onee-chan!
AT THE SAME TIME
I wonder if the Class A students are
being proper heroes...
The population of Nabu island is of 1000 people.
In the last 30 years, they've only
had trivial crimes.
Anyway, I'm sure they'll be fine.
Besides, being a hero doesn't mean facing
huge disasters by yourself.
or fighting evil villains like you did.
Interacting with those they protect will also be an important experience for them.
I'm exhausted...
We've gone Plus Ultra beyond what's allowed
by the Labor Standards Act.
Class Reps, don't you think we've taken
too many small jobs?
We shouldn't treat small and big
jobs differently.
Even if we're working as heroes,
we are still students.
We must do them faithfully and earn the trust
of the people on the island.
Excuse me! There's someone here who hasn't done
any hero work since we got here.
I've been staying in the office on purpose!
What're you gonna do if a villain comes out while you jerks are out, huh?!
There aren't any villains on this island.
Excuse us.
Mayor-san.
Thank you for carrying granny Sato to
the hospital earlier.
Thank you for fixing my bike.
And for my battery!
And for keeping the beach safe!
Here's some fresh fish!
It's not meant to replace our gratitude, but please eat these if you'd like.
Thanks for the food!
You people! Show some restraint!
I'm sorry for you going to all this trouble.
Oh no, it's really have been a big help
having you all here.
We're counting on you from now on, too.
Of course!
We will do our very best to carry out our duty.
Thanks for the food!
That was delicious.
I can feel the kindness of
people in my body.
It's moments like these that make me
glad I became a hero.
Yeah.
Kacchan of the Bakugos!
We're gonna take baths and go to sleep.
So we're counting on you for the night watch!
Why me?!
Because you haven't done anything all day.
1365, 1366...
--1367, 1368...
--I will tell you the truth...
My quirk, has the power to
transfer power.
One for All.
One person cultivates the power,
and passes it on to another person,
who also cultivates it.
It's the crystallization of power that unites
the voices of those who need help
in the hearts of the brave.
And next, it's your turn.
Now that you have inherited One for All,
you may one day have to fight against
this great evil...
Next, it's your turn.
Right now, I can only use 20% of
One for All at most.
I need to work harder, so I can make
this quirk my own.
Kacchan!
Oh, good work on patrol-
Looks like you've grown a bit, with
your One for All...
Not here, someone might
hear about this...
I'm impatient.
I know that better than anybody...
I've known you since we were kids.
So hurry up and make your quirk your own...
and fight me!
I'll prove it to you, that I'm the one who
will become the number one hero.
Yes, I will definitely make my quirk my
own and show you...
...in order to become the greatest hero!
And I'll be even better than the greatest.
Um...
You're from this morning...
A-A villain's...
came out!
A villain?!
Tell me more!
HEROES PUBLIC SAFETY COMMISSION
There have been continuous acts of violence
against heroes since last week.
All the victims were knocked unconscious,
and they all lost their quirks.
Shigaraki and his group have acquired a Quirk-Erasing needle manufactured by a disbanded villain group.
Do we have reports of them succeeding
in their mass production?
No, we don't.
Then investigate.
Continue your secret inves-
Have you thought about the possibility
that their quirks were stolen?
What?
The victims were heroes,
so the lost quirks were naturally
only useful ones.
If the suspect has a quirk that can steal
quirks like All for One...
That's...
Well, either way, it's related to Shigaraki.
I'll try investigating both possibilities.
So, where did the cargo end up?
The heroes didn't collect it, right?
Yeah, that's been confirmed.
What was in the cargo anyway?
According to the doctor, there's no
need for us to know.
What the hell?
He just makes us do the transporting,
but he won't tell us anything?!
Doesn't it make you even more curious?
Anyway, forget about it.
Okay?
Roger!
Don't want to!
Shigaraki Tomura.
Do not touch that.
Forget about it.
Doctor...
KYUSHU REGION
You said the next time you can come home
was in 10 days, right?
Daddy, do your best at work!
You don't have to worry about us.
I will take good care of Katsuma.
Thanks, Mahoro, Katsuma.
I will bring you as many souvenirs as--
I've finally found it...
F-Found what...?
Don't worry, I won't kill you.
But, I'll take your quirk.
We finally got it, huh?
With this, we can make it reality...
The new world... that we desire!
Nine?!
Wh-Why? Why...?
It doesn't work on type B blood.
What?!
After coming this far, we're back to
square one?! Damn it!
No there's still a way.
Daddy, do your best at work!
--You don't have to worry about us.
--I see...
Quirks are...
...inherited.
Why are you here too, shitty Deku?!
Why you say? Because if there
really is a villain...
I'll be fine by myself!
Hey, where did you saw that villain?
I-Inside those castle ruins!
Tell me that first!
Onee-chan...!
Over there!
Go hide.
Katsuma-kun!
Stun Grenade!
This guy's...
Kacchan!
Huh?
Ouch!
The villain's...
Ow, ow... Jeez!
At least get a little scared!
Th-That girl...
You're the one who made that
villain illusion?
Huh?! How did you know it
was an illusion?
It's obvious!
There's no shadow!
Hey, damn kid...
Are you having fun
taunting heroes, huh?!
I'm completly different from
your everyday heroes.
I'm the one who'll surpass All Might and
become the number one hero,
Bakugo Katsuki!
You picked the wrong person to taunt!
D-Don't scold my big sister.
Huh?!
Are you her accomplice?
You're going overboard, Kacchan!
Let me go, shitty Deku!
--We should be glad it were just fake villain!
--Don't touch me!
Kids these days have no respect!
Wait damnit!
--I told you to stop!
--Don't give me orders!
Wh-What's up with that Bakugo guy anyway?
What's with that
"I'll become the number one hero" thing?
Isn't he confusing it with the ranking
of heroes who look like villains?
But he... came to save us, right?
Katsuma, do you want to be
a hero that badly?
I'm against it.
It's dangerous.
Besides I know someone even
cooler than a hero.
Who?
Daddy.
He is always thinking of us, and protecting us.
I want you to be as cool as that.
Among the victims, there's another
one who lost his quirk.
But this time, he isn't a hero.
On top of that, everything that can be used
to indentify him has been stolen.
The suspect doesn't want anyone to
know what quirks he stole...?
Why does he need to hide this?
Hello! This is U.A.'s Hero Agency!
Your travel bag has gone missing?
Okay, we'll send someone right away!
At the shopping arcade, a tourist
said she lost her luggage--
Ok, ok! I'll go, I'll go!
Aoyama-kun, come with me!
Oui!
Another lost item...?
People should at least try to-
The client sounded really cute on the phone.
I can't just leave someone in trouble!
Shoji is asking for more support on the beach!
Then I'll go.
I'll go on a regular patrol.
I'll go out too, to help with the
fields at Nijima-san.
I'm off!
Katsuma...-kun?
Is something wrong?
U-Um...
S-Sorry about yesterday...
You are so well-mannered!
You came to apologize?
It's ok, I'm not mad.
Will you tell the other hero I'm sorry too?
Sure, I'll tell him.
But Katsuma-kun, why did you do that yesterday?
My big sister hates heroes.
Yesterday she said that when villains are around,
the heroes would be too scared, and
wouldn't come save me.
so that's why, I...
You believed in us.
Huh?
You believed that we will go and save you, right?
That's why you came to get us.
Yeah.
Oh, that pin--
It's the Ninja Hero: Edgeshot, right?
Yup!
Do you also want to be a hero, Katsuma-kun?
My quirk isn't good for being a hero.
Besides... onee-chan say's it's dangerous.
You're part of that famous U.A.'s
hero course, but you're useless!
I see, it's not like Mahoro-chan hates heroes, it's that
she's worried about Katsuma-kun.
Izuku, I can't take this anymore...
You keep getting hurt...
Your mom's heart can't take it anymore.
Hey, Katsuma-kun.
What kind of hero do you want to be?
A strong hero who can
beat up evil villains.
I see... I want to be a hero who can
save people in trouble.
Save people in trouble...?
Yeah.
Katsuma-kun, you want to be a hero who can defeat
the enemy to save people.
But I want to save the people in order
to defeat the enemy.
The order is different, but what we
are aiming for is the same.
I think we both want to be the greatest heroes.
That's why...
...let's both do our best.
Yeah.
Oh, but we should try not to worry
our families too much.
Yeah!
Little Katsuma really loves heroes, doesn't he?
Here, take this.
Thank you very much, Suzumura-san!
Please be kind to him.
They lost their mother when
they were very young.
Their father works away from home
almost the entire year,
so him and Mahoro-chan,
live on their own.
Of course, we in the neighborhood
look after them.
But it's lonely to not have parents
around at that age.
Onee-chan!
Where did you go, Katsuma?
To see Deku-niisan.
I went to say sorry for what
happened yesterday.
Why?
I love daddy.
I want to be someone as cool as daddy.
But...
But...!
Wh-What's this?!
The cruise is...
Why's the cruise coming this way...?
Hey, hey, hey, hey!
Run!
What... what's going on?
Chimera, Mummy, I don't want to be interrupted.
You two are in charge of diversions.
A preference of some kind?
As you see fit.
Roger.
--Slice...
--I know.
Villains...
Those are definely villains!
Onee-chan, let's call the heroes!
But they are still students--
Deku-niisan would definitely save us!
I'm sure of it!
I finished working the fields!
Welcome back, Midoriya-kun.
Good work!
What is it?
If it's some lame job-
Villains appeared at the fishing harbor!
That voice...
You're the damn kid from
yesterday, aren't you?
--Don't think that you can keep tricking us-
--I'm not lying! Bakugo it's true!
Hi, Deku here!
--Bastard-
--At the fishing harbor-
What did Mahoro-chan say?
========
NABU  ISLAND
BASE  TRANSCEIVER  STATION
Communications have been cut off.
Next is...
I hope it's still a joke...
Anyway, I'll go to the fishing port!
--Thank you very much.
Isn't it great, Maa-kun?
Yeah, Mii-chan.
What the heck? She has a boyfriend!
Damn that Ashido...
Hey, what was that?
Heroes! A v-villain...!
It's seriously a villain!
That's too sudden!
W-We need to do something!
Aoyama, use your laser!
It's called "Navel Laser"!
Oh? Three heroes in the middle
of nowhere.
He just made more!
Hagakure, did you contact the office?!
I can't reach them!
I don't have any signal!
No way!
If I keep shooting like this...
my tummy will...
Damn it!
What should we do?!
Froppy, Tentacole!
Evacuating everyone is our first priority!
I know!
Get away from here, quickly.
Twirling Tail Dance!
What are you after?
Why are you doing this?
You're quite young for a hero.
Tokoyami!
Sorry I'm late!
Dark Shadow!
Got it!
We can't use our phones!
Go back to the office and get help!
But-
I'll hold things as I can here!
Huh? My phone has no signal.
You're right.
Mine, too.
And mine.
What's going on?
Don't tell me...
This is bad!
Villains appeared!
Villains?!
They're attacking the shopping arcade!
Some heroes are fighting
with him but...!
Reporting in!
A villain has appeared at the beach!
What?!
Ojiro and the others are fighting
a defensive battle.
They're asking for help!
Iida-kun!
There's no time to hesitate.
Everyone here split up into two groups,
and deal with the villains!
Bakugo-kun, Kirishima-kun and Kaminari-kun,
you will intercept the villain
at the shopping arcade.
Yaoyorozu, Jiro and Ashido,
you will take care of the evacuation
at the shopping arcade!
Todoroki-kun, Sato-kun, Sero-kun
and Tokoyami-kun
will come with me to the beach!
Uraraka-san and Koda-kun,
you will take care of the evacuation
at the beach.
We're in a race against time.
We are the only heroes on this island.
And we are the only ones who can save
the people of this island!
U.A.'s High School hero course,
Class 1-A, heading out!
The fishing harbor!
I need to tell everyone!
No signal...!
Villains have came to this island.
Probably the others will go face them right after they will find out about this.
If that's so, then I must make sure that
Mahoro-chan is safe.
Their house is...
Of course, we in the neighborhood
look after them.
...close to Suzumura-san's house!
My tummy hurts...
My head also reached it's limit...
Mineta-kun! Aoyama-kun!
This place is full of useless people!
Just like these extras!
Bakugo-kun?!
Red Riot is here!
Chargebolt is also here!
Guys!
They are your friends?
Everyone!
Yaomomo! Girls!
Let's go help evacuating the
people out of here.
Got it!
AP Shot - Auto Cannon!
Damn!
Thanks!
Bakugo!
Shit!
What the hell's this-
Everything I catch with my bandages moves
according to my will!
It doesn't work with living things, but it does
work with what they are wearing.
Your suit, clothes and equipment
will act as I order!
Bakugo!
I'll crush your friends with your own hands!
Ojiro-kun!
Octoblow!
With this shape...
many people would make fun
of you, right?
Don't you hate your parents for this?!
Shoji-kun!
Leave it to me!
Ojiro, I'm counting on you!
Now!
Tokoyami-kun, Sato-kun!
Sugar... Rush!
This can't stop me!
Sato!
Hey, hey...
Although you are only kids, this
is going overboard.
Onee-chan, we have to notify the heroes
about villains!
Cell phones don't work so we
can't do anything.
Let's go home first, and tell
everyone after--
Our house...
Found it.
Type B cellular activation.
Young man...
I will take your quirk.
Don't worry, I won't kill you.
Stay away!
I said stay away!
I already know that's an illusion.
Onee-chan...
Deku-niisan!
A super-strength type quirk.
Everything's fine, can you run?
Yes.
Hurry, get away from here.
Stop!
Why are you after those children?
Back off.
I'm not moving from here!
If you stay in the way, I'll kill you.
Air wall?
So that's your power!
Did he shoot lightning bolts?
It seems like he
has two independent quirks.
It's almost like...
All For One.
Stop it, Bakugo!
He fully controls him.
What do we do, Kirishima?
What do we do, you say...
Damn!
S-Shit...!
Choose.
You can become one of my puppets...
or you can be defeated by your friend.
Shut up!
W-What?
Do not underestimate me!
Damn shitty mummy!
He sacrificed his own weapon...
I still have a lot of capacity left.
Maximum output!
Die!
You did it, Bakugo!
And with minimal damage to buildings.
Guys!
And the villain?
Huh? He's slightly injured.
And the people?
We evacuated them all towards
the west area.
Where are you going, Bakugo?
Take care of the evacuation!
I'll smash the remaining villains!
Shit...
He has us cornered with his power.
Iida, what can we do?
For now I just think we should keep this
on the sidelines.
At least until we finish moving the
people somewhere else.
Black Ankh!
Recipro... Burst!
You are so persistent, heroes!
If this continues...
Delaware Smash...
Air Force!
Air projectiles...
What an interesting way to use it.
I must keep attacking him if I don't want him to come
closer to Katsuma-kun and his sister!
He also has a quirk to launch
air projectiles!
How many more does he have?
If I can't know what your
quirks are, then I must hit first!
One For All, Full Cowling!
20%!
His power increased.
With this power I can...!
St. Louis... Smash!
20% wasn't enough!
This power...
This quirk...
It's worth stealing.
"Stealing"?
He said he can take it.
As I thought, you have the same quirk
as All for One...
He'll steal my One For All!
I couldn't steal it.
No, rather, it's essence won't
fit in my body.
This guy...
That quirk of yours has incredible potential.
I have to move...
Move! Move...!
It's existence is very intriguing.
But that's why, I have to destroy it.
Did he throw me with the air wall?
Deku-niisan?
Deku-niisan!
Run away!
But...!
Just hurry, run away.
That guy's objective is...
Deku-niisan!
Hurry... run away!
But...
No...
N-No!
What's that?
Deku...-kun?
Someone, please...
Protect Deku!
An explosive quirk.
I finally found you, damn villain.
Kacchan...
He's...
Bakugo!
Brats, look closely here!
I will become the number one hero...
...with my strength!
You are done!
Kacchan!
Shit... shit...!
Damn...
Kacchan...
That guy has multiple quirks.
And he can steal quirks!
Is All for One back?
In that case, it would be best
to finish him fast!
I already know that trick!
I'm way too strong for you!
Damn it...! From where did
this come from?
Move... Move!
Move!
You're just like a dog in pain.
That will...
be you!
Shitty Deku!
Detroit... Smash!
What's happening here?
What's going on?
The electricity is...
Now...
I won't let you...
go...
This fight it's still...
not ended...
Deku-niisan...
Bakugo...
Heroes really are...
He's in pain...?
Why?
Nine!
Hang in there, Nine!
The boy is...
Got it.
Stay still.
Don't worry.
We're on your side.
Over here!
Tsuyu-chan!
~Ribbit~!
Go after them...
No matter what, that child...
Nine...
They won't leave this island.
For now you need to rest.
So that's as far as we go...
You'll keep your lives for
today, little heroes!
Did he run away?
It's more appropriate to say
that he spared us.
--Shit-!
--Don't go!
It might be a trap.
We couldn't even win by
outnumbering him.
Trying alone is very dangerous.
But...
Now's more important to guarantee
everyone's safety.
That's also our job as heroes.
You two are using your quirks too much.
We... don't know when they will
attack us again.
If we don't do it now, there won't be...
You're already reaching your limit...
Here.
Thank you.
It's hot so be careful.
Take one per person!
There's enough for everyone!
What happened to the villains?
Don't worry.
We will take care of them and
will protect you all.
I'm glad this island han an abundance
of food on it.
What happened to the
villain they caught?
He's locked in the machine room.
But no matter how much you question him,
he doesn't want to tell us anything.
Todoroki-kun, how are Deku-kun
and the others doing?
They still didn't regained consciousness.
The doctors are treating them.
Thank you very much.
Sorry.
With our quirks we are hardly able
to close their wounds.
There is nothing we can do
about their fractures...
For that it's necessary to take
them to the hospital
I can help a bit.
Katsuma-kun?
Katsuma's quirk has the power
to activate cells.
We don't know if it could help with
the wounds, but...
They got hurt trying to save us!
That's why...
We would appreciate it, little one.
Got it!
I have to save them...
No...
I will save you!
How's Nine?
He will be fine.
In a few more hours he'll
be up again.
But Mummy?
He's not here?
It can't be, the heroes...
No way...
Either way, we must
continue with this as it was planned.
For sure.
No matter what.
Why... did you save me?
Come with me.
We will destroy this society that calls people
"villains" and "monsters".
We'll create a world that is dominated
only by power.
You'll join the League of Villains?
Strictly speaking...
I will participate in a League's experiment to
increase the power of quirks.
They just want to use you.
It's very dangerous!
For the objective we have, we
need more power...
We... choose you.
You can't abandon us.
I have managed to adapt the quirk
factor of All for One.
Steal 8 more quirks.
You became someone able to
use 9 quirks.
The experiment was a success.
We can finally carry out our plan.
However, the side effects also worsened.
If I use the quirks, the cells and the tissues
of my body will die.
But that's...
So that operation didn't make any sense!
I must steal a quirk capable of activating
cell tissues.
And so...
We can create the world we want.
Katsuma, at least get some sleep.
I don't want to.
I must go on.
But...
I must go on!
I can't give up.
Heroes never give up!
Deku-niisan!
Bakugo?!
I will first give a report of the
current situation.
The electricity and communications
were both destroyed.
We can't ask for backup.
A while ago I created a drone with a
distress message.
We sent it to search for help.
It will take at least 6 hours to arrive,
so help will take even longer.
I don't think the villains will wait
to act until then.
For now our highest priority is to
protect the inhabitants.
How will we do it?
That villain managed to seriously injure
Midoriya and Bakugo!
And the one we faced was really
skilled and powerful.
Yaomomo and Kaminari overused their
quirks, so they can't fight for now...
And as far as we know, there are still
three villains outside.
Not even by attacking them all at once
will assure us a victory.
If we could only know what's
their objective...
Yeah...
Then we could at least take some action.
I will steal your quirk.
Katsum-
I'm the target of those villains!
What do you mean?
He said he wanted to steal my quirk!
Steal your quirk?
Is he like All for One?
But now we know what his goal is!
--If we run away with the child then...
--It will not be that easy.
They are villains.
If we run away with the child they could threaten
with murdering the population.
So what can we do?
I will let myself be captured!
Huh?
I'm going to let him steal my quirk,
he said he wouldn't kill me.
If that's enough to save everyone...
We won't do that!
Deku-kun?
Midoriya-kun! Are you better?
Thanks to Katsuma's quirk.
My quirk isn't good for being a hero.
Cell activation.
A quirk that favors metabolism.
It's as if it were a stimulant
for healing.
Thanks to that I was able to recover this much.
It is an incredible quirk, Katsuma-kun!
Thank you!
Deku-niisan...
You don't have to be afraid anymore.
That's what we are here for.
All we have to do is crush those damn
villains good, right?
Bakugo!
Save to win.
Win to save.
If you can recognize these...
you will become...
one of the strongest heroes!
We will certainly protect you!
And I'll crush those villains!
We will save the inhabitants of the island!
I will definitely win!
Bakugo, Midoriya, I'm with you.
Me too!
I want to protect the people
of this island.
Let's fight!
Jeez, shut up already!
I still have to repair Matsuda-san's battery.
I also want Sato-san to be able to live
a much happier life!
I'm also with you!
Me too.
--I'll go!
--Me too!
--I also-!
--Yeah!
--I'll fight!
--~Ribbit~!
Alright, let's do it!
Yeah, let's do it
I guess we have to do it!
Because we are heroes!
We will show you that there's
no impossibilities
What do we always say...
Surpass your limits...
Plus Ultra!
Midoriya, what's the strategy?
We have confirmed three villains.
We will make our base in
the castle ruins.
So the villains will have only
one escape route.
Here we will separate them and from
there we will use the land.
I'm will beat them up.
We'll shelter the inhabitants in the caves
that are in those ruins.
We'll protect Katsuma and Mahoro-chan.
We will also secure our escape route.
How do we face the one who uses multiple quirks?
When Kacchan and I fought him,
he suddenly seemed to be suffering from something.
It's most likely that if he uses his quirks too much,
his body can no longer handle it.
That's why he tries to steal Katsuma-kun's
quirk, to heal himself.
I see...
Then will we make him use them?
We will attack him in waves to
make him use up his quirks.
To prevent him from stealing ours...
we will attack from distance
as much as possible.
If we can defeat him, that's fine,
but if we can't do it...
Just resist until help arrives!
We will protect everyone.
Wrong.
We will certainly win.
Nine!
Our goal is on top of Mount Shiroyama.
The heroes are there too.
A siege?
Let's head toward our goal.
The one who will become King doesn't need
to rely on cheap tricks.
They're here.
All three.
They're advancing along the
planned route.
We are counting on you,
Yaoyorozu-san, Aoyama-kun.
Twenty seconds until the villains
reach the spot...
Aoyama-kun, Naval Laser at
maximum output!
Charging energy...
5 ... 4 ... 3 ... 2 ... 1!
Can't stop twinkling... Supernova!
Plus... Ultra!
They separated!
I made these using the last lipids I had!
My final attack!
Where are you aiming-
First phase... accomplished.
I-I can't anymore...
We've successfully separated them!
Now...!
They're sending them to the
determined points.
So far it's going as planned.
We will certainly protect you all!
Tape Shot... Trident!
Release!
Uraraka!
Sero-kun!
--We'll make the villain's quirk...
--...use up!
Let's go!
They separated us.
Shit!
Damn it!
That was close!
Ashido, leave the rest to me.
This is my world.
Cheeky boy!
Shit...
They split us up, huh.
All right!
All according to plan.
No...
Hey, that was cold.
We meet again.
Heh.
Stop that...
Today... I'll be serious.
We are also not the same as before!
Now that all the inhabitants are safe,
we can give our best!
We will stop you.
Recipro... Burst!
Let's finish this in 10 minutes!
--Got it!
--Roger!
Bring it on!
Damn, we can't even slow him down!
Then what about...
It's almost time for our real attack!
Yeah.
Sero! Uraraka!
Mineta!
Everything's ready!
We're counting on you, Uraraka!
Plus...
...Ultra!
Go, Mineta!
Super Grape Rush!
Take that, and that, and that,
and that, and that!
And that, and that, and that,
This was our real attack!
All right!
W-We did it-
Hey, are you alright?
Serves you right...
We've sealed you.
He escaped the trap!
The villain's approaching Uraraka
and the others!
In that case...
--Aoyama-kun!
--Yaomomo!
Now while he's distracted...
The plan must-
It's no use.
Playtime's over.
So you were alive.
If you're gonna sleep-talk, then
sleep and die!
Bakugo's joined the fight!
Midoriya!
Take care of Katsuma-kun
and Mahoro-chan!
--Deku-niisan...
--Deku...
We'll defend this place until the end!
Die!
If I can't protect them here...
then there's no point in
trying to be a hero!
St. Louis Smash!
It doesn't have to be at full power.
Just think about how to make him use his quirks.
X-Catapult!
Not bad...
You won't go past us...
I'll kill you.
What's with "This is my world"?!
Say something like that again!
Is that all you've got?
She's moving a lot.
I just need an opening...
How pathetic!
Black Ankh: Sabbath!
Now!
Acid Shot!
We'll decide this now!
How dare you...
Ashido!
You little...!
Th... This is...
I won't let you get in Nine's way!
Tokoyami-kun!
Dark Shadow is...
Pay attention in what's in front of you!
Got it!
It's no use!
Red Gauntlet!
That itches.
I told you brats... that it's no use!
M-My body's...
There was a reason for why we were repeating
the same boring moves.
On my legs...
and on Kirishima-kun's hands...
we smeared a toxic mucus
made by Asui-chan.
You mean "Tsu-chan" right?
Resign yourself, old man.
You are acting so insolent...
I'll show you...
...why I'm called a monster!
He's gotten bigger!
That form make's him look
like Amajiki-senpai.
--Shit...
--Get shelter!
That's were... Iida and the others are!
They have problems?
I should go-
You can't! We must protect Katsuma-kun
and Mahoro-chan no matter what.
--Deku-niisan...
--Bakugo...
I won't let you!
Sero!
I'll make him float and...
Uraraka-san!
Not... yet...
Bastard...
How could you?!
We must make him back down.
At this rate... Katsuma-kun and
Mahoro-chan will...
Damn it...
This is...
This is it!
He reached his limit!
That's some crazy power.
We can't even get close to him.
My Recipro will be done soon.
Make an opening for me.
Get me close to him.
And then?
I have an idea.
All right.
This will be our last attack!
Iida, distract him with your Recipro Burst.
--Doesn't this reming you of Kamino?
--It does.
Whatever attack comes, I'll take it and get
you close to him for sure!
Got it!
Unbreakable!
Kirishima!
Go...
Increase the temperature in
your body to it's maximum limit!
If I can make this with fire...
...then I can also do it with ice...
Todoroki-kun!
Go down, over the limit!
Freeze!
Hibernate for a while...
D-Did we... do... our job...?
Midoriya... Bakugo...
Kacchan, let's attack in waves!
Don't give me orders!
I-If I could only get the cell
activation quirk...
Let's hit him good now!
Then I wouldn't... have to
restrain myself!
Deku-niisan...
Bakugo...
Deku-niisan!
Bakugo!
Cell activation?
Yes.
However, my quirk won't activate other
cells except those of type A.
It's a quite useful quirk for
helping people.
Shimano-san, do you have a family?
I'm from Nabu Island, and my daughter
and son live there...
That's pretty far...
...but Nabu Island is within the culprit's
range of progression.
Excuse me.
What is it?
A fishing boat sailing near Kyushu received
an S.O.S. message.
Villains have attacked Nabu Island, and
they request help immediately.
That's the suspect in Quirk-Loss crimes!
What?!
Send a rescue team to Nabu Island
immadiately!
Oh, and contact U.A. High School.
U.A.? Why?
For the practical hero recommendation project
sponsored by the commission,
the U.A.'s hero course students
from Class 1-A went there.
Shoji, take Katsuma-kun and Mahoro-chan
and get out of here.
We're counting on you.
Got it.
We'll definitely hold him back.
Yeah.
Found you.
Heartbeat Distortion!
Tornado Tail Dance!
Ojiro!
We have to evacuate...
Now get away...
Run!
Both of you, run!
Hurry!
Go!
Katsuma, run away.
O-Onee-chan...
I'll be ok, just run!
Stay away!
Don't lay a hand on my little brother!
I said stay away!
Onee-chan!
If you don't want her to die,
then come here.
No! Run!
Run!
Help me... turn my desire into reality...
Run... away...
Katsuma...!
Stop it!
I'll protect you!
I will protect you, onee-chan!
Smash!
Sorry being late.
Deku-niisan...
You really gave your best, Katsuma-kun.
You're amazing!
Bakugo... you're alive!
I told you.
I will surpass All Might, and become
the number one hero!
--Run away with Mahoro-chan!
--Got it!
Nee-chan!
How did you avoid my lighting...?
You used that on us already!
That's why...
We used that thunder idiot, as lighting rod.
I-Isn't that... too much?
Smash!
Die!
Over here!
This...
This can't end!
It can't be the end!
Like I'd let it end like this!
A tornado!
Damn it, he really can manipulate
the weather...
What should we do?
Katsuma-kun and Mahoro-chan
are still here.
On top of that, everyone who was
evacuated could be in danger!
Is he planning to destroy the whole island?
We definitely have to stop him!
One For All... 100%!
I'll blow that away... with everything I've got!
Detroit... Smash!
Howitzer... Impact!
Deku-niisan!
Onee-chan!
The entrance!
Sato-kun!
Leave this to me!
Get everyone further inside!
E-Even at 100%... it wasn't enough...
Damn... it...
Even thought I lowered myself
to fight with Deku...
It's no use.
You won't be able to live with
that level of power.
Not in the new world I will create.
New world...?
Those who have power.
The strongest will rule over the
weak in my utopia.
That can't...
It won't matter if someone's a
villain or a hero.
Everything's equal before power...
That's... what a true superhuman
society should be.
Such a selfish assumption...
You're crazy...!
Are you getting in the new world's way?
Then you should just disappear.
Think...
What would All Might do?
Like I'd let it end here!
Think!
I don't plan to lose!
Deku-niisan!
Bakugo!
Don't lose!
So there you were.
Kacchan.
There's still a way.
There's only one way to do this!
My quirk was passed on to me like a sacred torch.
The power to transfer power...
K-Kacchan...!
Heroes... really have a lot to protect.
That's why, I won't lose!
Deku!
A hero... can always break out of a tough spot!
A way to protect...
A way to win...
There's only one way!
What...
If you do this, will you still be
able to use it?
I don't know, but...
All Might still protected us with the embers after he transfered it to me.
What did you do?!
With two... One for All...
...we'll save everyone!
...we'll win!
You two... should already be dead!
This might be your last time you use it.
It's alright, there's no other way.
Also, All Might, would agree if it's you.
You never shared our secret, and we have
always admired the same person.
If it's you...
All Might it's so cool!
He's a super cool hero!
No matter how difficult it is, in the end,
good always...!
...wins!
No matter how hard it's to save
someone, you...
...have to save them!
Don't make me laugh!
Detroit...!
Smash!
What's this...?
What's this power?!
You won't stop me... from fulfilling
my dream!
Kacchan, let's go!
Don't give me orders!
You won't stop me!
This is... the last time...
My last...
My last...!
Smash!
Goodbye...
One for All...
Thank you.
Are you okay, Tokoyami-kun?
Hawks? Why are you...?
I am here to help, and I brought
some company...
All Might...
Young Midoriya, sorry for being late...
K-Kacchan...?
You always care about others first...
He's hurt badly, but he will be fine,
his life isn't in danger.
I'm glad...
We tried... too hard...
I understand...
All Might...
I... transferred the...
One for All to Kacchan...
One for All?!
If we wouldn't have used
two One for All...
We wouldn't have been able to
protect everyone...
We wouldn't have been able to beat the villain...
That's why, I don't regret it.
But... I'm sorry...
Even though you choose me as your successor...
Even though you told me I can become a hero...
I wanted to protect everyone with all I've got...
Young Midoriya...
I'm so sorry... All Might...
I'm sorry...
That's why...
I don't regret transferring One for All
to you either.
You used it as you knew it's best.
The crystallization of power that
unites the voices...
of those who ask for help in a
brave heart...
One for All is...
Did young Bakugo passed out before the
completion of the transfer?
No, it's something else.
It's a quirk for those who sacrifice their
lives to save others...
and the ones who sacrificed it...
Master... and those who preceded us...
Thank you... very much...!
What are you planning to do,
Tomura Shigaraki?
As I thought, you're still alive.
Shigaraki...
You had a great opportunity.
Just a little more, just a little...
Don't worry, I will fulfill your dream.
It takes... only one leader...
That's right, one is enough.
Sleep, Nine...
Good job.
Hurts!
What the hell's this?!
Undergoing
Treatment
Kacchan does not remember the transfer
of One for All.
One for All is still inside me.
Daddy!
Mahoro, Katsuma!
A bit later, Katsuma-kun and Mahoro-chan
meet their father again.
We were able to protect the people of this
island with very few wounded.
The program of the public security commission
was suspended, but...
we remained a while longer on the island...
to help as we can with the reconstruction.
And so, the final day came, and
we had to leave.
Are we going to leave without saying anything?
We can't help more in the
reconstruction work.
Now, let's just go quietly.
That's very typical of heroes.
Yeah.
We're already saying goodbye to this
island, huh.
Whatever.
It's really ok for you to leave without saying
goodbye to those brats?
There are some things I wanted
to tell them, but...
It's okay, I'm sure they will understand.
Hey! Hey!
Deku-niisan!
Bakugo!
Everyone!
Thank you for protecting us all!
Deku-niisan!
I will become strong!
At least enough to protect my
daddy and big sister!
I will become strong!
And then, I'll show you, how I will become a cool hero
like you and Bakugo!
Don't forget those words, shitty brat.
Katsuma-kun!
You... can become a hero!
I'll wait for you at U.A.!