"California, USA"
It's a villain!
Run away!
I'll take that ten million dollars!
This job's a piece of cake!
Bro!
Huh?
That's it, villains!
End it, Cow Lady!
Calm down...
Like I will!
Papa!
You're in the way! Move!
It's fine now. Why?
Because I am here!
Hey man, who the hell are you?
Just a hero from Japan who happened to pass by.
Then I'll send you back home!
In a coffin!
Who said he was going to send me back--
Huh?
You're so fast at running away!
You went too far ahead, Toshi!
He got away!
Follow him, Dave!
Your body moves before you think, as usual!
Bro, a car's following us!
Damn heroes!
What the hell?
Toshi, we're going to be late for the lecture.
Hurry up and finish this!
That's the plan, Dave!
You just keep coming, huh?
Detroit...
...Smash!
I'll end it with this move--
Dave, the move named after your home state...
Go!
California...
...Smash!
Who's that hero?
I've never seen him.
But he's amazing!
He's an exchange student from Japan!
His hero name is All Might.
All Might...
He's the man who will someday...
someday soon...
...become the Symbol of Peace.
Thanks, Dave!
Thanks to the suit you made,
we can make it in time.
Let's hurry! If we're late again,
we won't have enough credits--
SFO flight UA 857 has been hijacked.
--SFO flight UA 857 has--
--Dave!
It's too reckless.
You can't not help them, huh?
Let's go, Dave!
Yeah!
It's really tough being a hero, though!
I'll buy you lunch today!
All Might.
All Might, All Might!
What's the matter, Young Midoriya?
We can see it. Look!
The artificial moving city inhabited
by over 10,000 scientists, I-island.
It's like a dream come true to be able to go to
I-island right at the beginning of summer vacation!
I didn't think you'd be that excited.
I'm glad I invited you.
But is it really okay for me to come with you?
There's no need to hold back.
The invitation said I could bring a companion.
Isn't that usually meant for family--
We are connected by something
thicker than blood, aren't we?
The bond of One For All.
Yes!
This plane will soon
begin its descent to I-island.
Now, it's about to get pretty exhausting.
Because once I arrive, I...
...must maintain my muscle form constantly.
Now, Young Midoriya, you change, too.
You asked the school if you could
bring your hero costume, right?
Yes!
The world has become a superhuman society,
and about 80% of the world's population
now has some kind of special trait.
Fighting against villains
using their Quirks for evil
and saving people from distress,
professional heroes came into the limelight.
It's fine now. Why?
Because I am here.
He's so cool!
Once I get my Quirk, I wanna be like him, too!
You should probably give it up.
But I, lzuku Midoriya,
was born without any special trait,
and almost gave up
my dream of becoming a hero.
My life made an about-face on the fateful day
that I met the number one hero, All Might...
Even if I don't have a Quirk,
can I become a hero?
Can even someone without a Quirk be like you?
Top heroes have stories
about them from their school days.
Most of their stories have one thing in common:
Their bodies moved before
they had a chance to think.
Kacchan!
Why are you here?
You looked like you were asking for help...
You can become a hero.
Young man, I will tell you the truth.
My Quirk was passed
on to me like a sacred torch.
The power to transfer power...
That is the Quirk I inherited!
It was crowned with the name "One For All"!
One For All...
One person cultivates the power
and passes it on to another person,
who also cultivates it and passes it on.
It is the crystallization of power that spins
together the voices of those who need help
with a courageous heart.
That's right. And next, it is your turn.
After I received All Might's Quirk, One For All,
I enrolled in U.A. High School's hero course
and started running again toward my dream,
standing up to any difficulties
and saving people with a smile...
...in order to become the greatest hero!
"My Hero Academia: Two Heroes"
"I-island - Airport"
We will now begin the immigration inspection.
Here's a question for you, Young Midoriya.
Why was this artificial island created?
Let's see...
To create a place where the world's talents
could gather and research Quirks
and develop hero items!
This island was made mobile in order to protect
the scientists and their research from villains.
That security system is
the equivalent of Tartarus,
and no villain has committed
a crime here before.
"Mutter mutter mutter"
You really know a lot about this stuff, huh?
The immigration inspection is complete.
Currently, on I-island, we are
having the preopening of I-Expo,
an exposition showcasing the results
of various research and development.
If you received an invitation,
please come and take a look.
I can't believe so many people are here
even before they officially open to the public.
Seeing it in person,
you can really tell how amazing it is!
Unlike Japan, people are allowed
to use their Quirks as they wish on I-island.
Apparently, there are a lot of attractions
in the pavilions that use Quirks.
You should go visit them later.
Okay!
Now let's see... The hotel is...
Welcome to I-Expo!
Wait, All Might?!
All Might?!
The number one hero?!
It's really him!
Wow!
Thank you for such a warm welcome!
Line up for autographs!
I didn't think I'd be stopped for that long...
We were about to be late!
Late?
Yeah, I wanted to have a reunion with
an old friend that I haven't seen in a while.
Sorry, but would you mind coming with me?
All Might's friend...
Of course I'll go!
I haven't told him about One For All
or how I've passed the Quirk on to you,
so keep that in mind.
It's even a secret from your friend?
It's because danger follows around
those who know the secret of One For All.
I see.
That's true...
One For All is that important of a secret.
Young Midoriya, the one
who inherits One For All from me
bears the fate of one day
facing great evil and All For One.
That's right.
To be ready when that time comes,
I must learn to use One For All
properly as soon as I can.
Uncle!
Uncle Might!
Oh, Melissa!
Long time no see!
I'm so happy you came!
Thank you for inviting me!
But man, I almost didn't recognize you!
You're all grown up now!
I'm 17 now.
I'm heavier than I used to be, aren't I?
Not at all!
I'm glad you seem well, as usual, Uncle Might.
--She's All Might's old friend? --Sorry I'm late. I was
so focused on my experiment that I lost track of time...
--She doesn't seem to be the right age... --Sorry I'm late. I
was so focused on my experiment that I lost track of time...
"Could it be her Quirk?
--Don't worry about it.
Oh right, where's Dave?
He's in his lab.
It looks like he finished the first stage of some
research he'd been working on for many years,
so I invited you to this island
as a surprise to celebrate that.
Is that what it was?
By the way, what was
Dave researching this time?
He said it's confidential and won't tell even me.
Scientists have it hard, too, huh?
Oh, Young Midoriya,
she's my good friend's daughter...
I'm Melissa Shield.
Nice to meet you!
Is that how it is?
--Hm?
--Huh? What?
Oh, nothing!
N-Nice to meet you!
I'm lzuku Midoriya, a first year in
the hero course at U.A. High School.
U.A. High School? Then you're Uncle Might's...
Yes, I'm his student!
He's going to be a hero in the future!
Wow, I can't believe
you're Uncle Might's student!
You've got a promising future, huh?
No, I'm still in training, I mean, I'm...
What kind of Quirk do you have?
A p-power type!
It's cool, but it's a very orthodox design...
I don't see any support items, either...
S-So close!
Maybe you should refine your costume...
Melissa, it's about time.
Oh, I'm sorry! I got distracted...
We've gotta hurry up and make Papa happy!
This way, Uncle Might!
We were able to get into
the expo with no problem.
So when will the goods arrive?
Please come get it at 3 p.m. at gate 66.
I understand.
Professor.
Professor David.
I've finished cleaning up here, too.
Really? Thanks, Sam.
Why don't you go have lunch
with your daughter sometime?
She went to the Academy today, too.
I thought they had a break for I-Expo?
She's doing some independent research.
I mean, I'm Papa's daughter.
I can't help being like him.
Melissa.
Hello, Miss.
Hello, Sam.
Thanks for always taking care of Papa,
who does nothing but research all the time.
I can't say anything to that.
More importantly, what are you doing here?
To celebrate you completing
the first stage of your research,
I invited a certain person.
A certain person?
Someone you love, Papa.
I am here... shaking with
emotion from our reunion!
Toshi?!
All Might?!
Th-The real thing?
I came all this way just to see you, Dave!
Well? Were you surprised?
Y-Yeah...
Very surprised...
We both need to thank Melissa!
Man, how long has it been?
Oh, don't remind me about how old I am.
Neither one of us wants to think about that, do we?
Yeah, that's true!
I'm glad I could see you, Dave.
I'm glad to see you, too, All Might.
Young Midoriya, let me introduce you
to one of my best friends, David Shield--
I know who he is!
Professor David Shield!
A top scientist in Quirk research
who received a Nobel Quirk Prize!
He was All Might's partner
when he lived in America,
and for All Might's hero costumes--
“Young Age“!
"Bronze Age"!
"Silver Age"!
And "Golden Age"!
He was the genius inventor
who created all of those!
I never thought I'd be able
to meet him in person!
L-I'm so moved!
It looks like I don't need to introduce myself.
I'm sorry! It's just--
No, it's fine.
It's been a long time
since I last saw All Might.
Can you give us some time to talk alone?
Oh, sure.
Melissa, please show Midoriya around I-Expo.
Okay, Papa.
Really?
I'm honored to be able to go with a future hero!
Let's go!
Okay, I'm looking forward to it!
Sam.
You go rest, too.
What should I call you?
Midoriya? lzuku?
Please call me...
...Deku.
"Deku"?
That's a strange nickname.
You can call me Melissa.
Excuse me.
Hey, are you all right, Toshi?
Thanks...
The amount of time I can keep muscle
form has gotten even shorter...
You told me about your symptoms over email,
but I didn't realize it had gotten so bad...
Wow, this is amazing.
Looking at it like this, it's hard to
believe that this is a man-made island.
We have all the facilities of a large city.
Just about all we can't do is travel.
Really?
It's because all the scientists and their
families here have a duty to confidentiality
to keep information from leaking out.
Wow!
It's the Monster Hero: Godzillo!
It's my first time seeing the real thing!
His Quirk's amazing!
He must've been invited by a sponsor.
To show off their newest items
and sign autographs and stuff.
It looks like there are
a lot of different events.
I-Expo's amazing!
There's a party with all
the industry guests tonight, too.
But you'll be at that, too, right?
Since you came with Uncle Might.
Was that why All Might told me
to bring formal clothes?
Oh, Deku! You should
definitely check out that pavilion!
So many of the newest hero items in one place!
Deku, look at this!
This multipurpose Beagle can fly,
of course, but it can also move underwater.
Wow!
You can wear this diving suit up
to 7,000 meters in the deep sea.
SO deep!
These goggles are equipped
with 36 different sensors.
I can see too much!
Actually, almost everything here was
created based on things Papa's patented.
Wow, that's amazing!
Each and every item here helps heroes
around the world in their work.
You really respect your dad, don't you?
That's because it's my dream
to become a scientist like him.
Oh, speaking of which,
you go to the Academy here, right?
Yeah, I'm in my third year.
The I-Island Academy is where all those who
want to become scientists want to go, right?
I've still got a long way to go.
I need to study more.
I have to work harder
to become like All Might, too.
You really love Uncle Might, don't you?
You were so enthusiastic earlier.
It surprised me!
Oh, I'm sorry, I couldn't help it...
You look like you're having fun, Deku.
U-Uraraka?!
What're you doing here?
You look like you're having fun.
You said it again?!
Ahem.
Yaoyorozu?!
You looked like you were having a lot of fun.
Midoriya. I overheard.
Jim's Earphone Jack is something to be feared!
Are they your friends?
They're my classmates from school...
And it looks like there's
a bit of a misunderstanding...
U-Um, Melissa is just
showing me around the expo.
That's right! My papa and Uncle Might are--
Please, don't tell them
that I came here with All Might!
--Stare...
--Why not?
--There are reasons...
--Stare...
--All right.
Do you want to go have tea at a cafe?
Oh, you all have had experience
working with pro heroes?
Just training and going on patrol.
I got caught up in an incident,
but all I did was evacuate people.
That's still amazing.
For some reason, I ended up
being in a TV commercial...
You can't do that normally. That's wonderful!
Tomorrow, we're planning on going to
the pavilion where the Academy's exhibit is.
--I'm really looking forward to it! --Oh, good...
It looks like the misunderstanding's cleared up...
--Melissa, do you have something there, too? --Oh, good...
--Yes, of course. --Oh, good... It looks
like the misunderstanding's cleared up...
Thanks for waiting.
That voice...
K-Kaminari!
And Mineta?!
What're you two doing?
They needed some temporary staff
for the expo, so we applied.
Right?
We can go see the expo on our breaks,
and we get paid.
And maybe we can even have wonderful
meetings with the cute girls who are attending!
Hey Midoriya, where did you meet that hottie?
Introduce us! Introduce us!
Well, um...
Do they also go to U.A.?
That's right.
We're going to be heroes.
What are you standing around talking for?!
If you're going to take
the money, then work harder!
L-lida--
You're here, too?
I come from a family of heroes,
so we received an invitation from I-Expo.
But my family was busy,
so I'm the only one who came.
You too, lida?
I also received invitations because my father
holds shares of I-Expo's sponsors' stock.
And since Yao-momo had two extra invites...
No hard feelings, rock-paper-scissors!
Oh, no!
After an impartial game of chance,
we were chosen to go with her.
Yup. The other girls came to the island, too.
Really?
We're planning on all going around together
once it opens to the public tomorrow.
Would you like me to show you around?
Would you?
Sure!
Yay!
T-Take us with you, too!
Wh-What was that?
Clear time, 33 seconds!
Eighth place!
Kirishima?!
Deku, is he also...?
Yes, he's a classmate.
Now, the next challenger is...
Ka...
Kacchan?!
Now, Villain Attack! Ready... go!
Die!
Die?
This is amazing!
He cleared it in 15 seconds!
He's in first place!
Oh? Isn't that Midoriya over there?
Why are You here?!
S-Stop that, Kacchan.
--People are watching--
--So what?!
Stop that, Bakugo!
--Why is that boy angry?
--I don't have business with you.
--That's how he always is...
--Don't act like the class rep here, too!
--It's a fated battle between men! --A class
rep is a class rep no matter where you are!
Kirishima, did you both receive
invitations to the expo, too?
No, Bakugo was the only one invited
since he won the U.A. sports festival.
I just came with him.
What, are you all going to try that now?
It's no use!
Since I'll definitely be better than you!
Yeah, you're right. Yeah.
But you won't know until you try.
Yeah, you're right. Wait--
Then hurry up and go get
your pathetic results, damn nerd!
O-Okay...!
Now, we've got a challenger coming
in at the spur of the moment!
Just what kind of results will he get?
Since I decided to do it...
One For All...
...Full Cowling!
Villain Attack! Ready... go!
To keep from injuring my arm...
...I'll use 5% of my power!
This is amazing, too!
Sixteen seconds! Second place!
He has amazing explosive power.
And his destructive power...
It's like Uncle Might's...
But...
Ahhh, so close!
That was amazing, Midoriya.
I didn't think I'd be able to get
so close to Kacchan's time--
The hell?! Impossible!
I'll go again and blow you away!
Wow! Wow! Wow!
F-Fourteen seconds!
He's jumped to the top!
Todoroki!
He's in your class, too?
Yes!
You're all amazing!
As expected of future heroes.
Oh, you don't have to say that.
Half-and-Half Bastard!
Bakugo.
Appearing suddenly trying to make
everyone think you're amazing, you bastard?!
Midoriya and the others are here, too?
Don't ignore me!
Why the hell are you here, anyway?
I'm here to represent
my father, who was invited.
Um... the next person is waiting...
Shut up! I'm going next!
Everyone, stop them!
U.A.'s embarrassing secrets
will be exposed to the world!
--R-Rig ht!
--Y-Yeah!
Kacchan, calm down!
--Oh, I'm sorry.
--Don't embarrass us any further!
--Who're you calling embarrassing?!
--I was just thinking you guys
seem to have fun at U.A.
--Try to understand here, Bakugo!
--It's never boring, at least.
--What the hell's wrong with you guys? Let go!
--That's true...
--I'll burn you up!
I received the goods as planned.
What? All Might?
Don't panic. We'll deal with it.
All Might is on this island...
What's going on, Toshi?
Why are your Quirk numbers
going down so dramatically?!
Even if you were seriously injured
during your fight with All For One,
to suddenly get these numbers is too unusual.
What in the world happened to your body?!
If you're a hero for a long time,
your body's going to fall apart.
I can't tell him the secret of One For All.
If I do, then Dave and Melissa will get caught
up in the fight against All For One, too...
At this rate, the Symbol of Peace will be lost.
The only reason Japan is able to keep
its crime rate at 6% is because of you.
Other countries have crime rates
above 20% across the board...
There were so many times that
I wished you had just stayed in America...
There's no need to be so pessimistic.
There are many capable pro heroes,
and many people who
support the heroes, like you.
I can still be All Might a few hours every day--
But...
It's possible that another villain like
All For One will appear again somewhere...
Dave.
For the sake of when that happens, as well,
I have no intention of stepping down
from being the Symbol of Peace.
Besides, there is still hope...
For the will of One For All...
...and the Symbol of Peace...
...to connect to the next generation.
Today, we will be closing at 6 p.m.
Thank you for coming.
It's still the preopening
and we're already this busy...
What'll it be like tomorrow...?
Stop, I don't want to think about it!
Mineta, Kaminari!
Good work today!
You both worked hard today, huh?
What is this?
Invitations to the reception party.
Party...?
For us...?
Melissa prepared them for you.
She thought you should
at least have some fun today.
I had extra, so please use them if you'd like.
Kaminari...
Mineta...
Our hard work has been rewarded!
I heard that there will be quite
a few pro heroes at the party, as well.
In order to keep from
embarrassing the name of U.A.,
change into your formal clothes
and let us attend the party as a group!
We'll meet at 6:30 p.m.
in Lobby 7 of the central tower!
Make sure you're on time!
I will contact Todoroki and Bakugo.
Dismissed!
Lida's at full throttle!
See you later!
Yeah!
Deku.
Huh?
Will you go somewhere with me first?
Why would I go to a party?
I'm not gonna go listen to some guys I don't
know give speeches and then clap for them.
It's dumb.
I heard we can eat as much
fancy food as we want!
It's not like I brought formal clothes, anyway.
That's what I thought!
So I brought some for you, too!
You're way too prepared, Weird Hair!
Dave, I'll see you later...
...at the party!
Okay.
Toshi!
What's up?
Oh, uh, it's nothing...
See you at the party.
An accident during an experiment?!
There are still people
who didn't make it out yet!
Thanks.
I'm David Shield.
What's your name?
I'm All Might.
I'm a student trying to become a hero.
It's a costume made of the
newest materials just for you.
You should be able to
do a little more with this.
This is great.
The Symbol of Peace?
What I'm aiming for is a world
where everyone can live and laugh.
I want to become the Symbol of Peace
that shines a light on that world.
We've restrained them.
There were five guards.
Everything's going according to plan.
The security system is still working.
Keep them bound without killing them.
Yes, sir.
We will begin now.
It's going smoothly.
We're going to move, too.
This is the campus of the Academy,
where I go to school.
And this is the lab that I use.
Sorry it's so messy.
Wow, it looks so professional.
I can't believe you're doing
research in a place like this...
Melissa, you're really talented.
Actually, I wasn't getting very good grades.
That's why I studied really hard.
It's because I wanted
to become a hero no matter what.
A pro hero?
No, I gave that up early.
I'm Quirkless, after all.
Quirkless...?
I didn't have a Quirk even after I turned five,
so I was taken to a doctor.
I was told that I was the type
that would never get a Quirk.
The same as me...
Mom...
He saves everyone with a smile,
no matter what trouble they're in...
Can I... be a hero, too?
I'm sorry, lzuku!
I'm sorry. I'm sorry!
S-Sorry...
I'm... I'm sorry...
Hm? What's the matter?
Oh, nothing...
It's just, to be told that you didn't have
what everyone around you had naturally...
Of course, I was shocked.
But I had a goal that was close to me.
A goal?
MY Papa.
Papa didn't have a Quirk
that would let him be a hero,
but he supports Uncle Might and
other heroes with the power of science.
It's indirect, but he is fighting for peace.
Someone who helps heroes...
That's right.
That's the way I hope to become a hero.
I made this support item
before while watching Uncle Might.
Watching All Might?
Try pressing this panel.
This is...
If I had to give it a name,
I'd call it "Full Gauntlet," I think.
When I first met you and
saw the scars on your hands
and saw how you seemed to be limiting
your Quirk on purpose at the attraction,
I thought--
Maybe your Quirk is too strong,
and your body can't keep up.
She figured it out...!
This Full Gauntlet is strong enough to take the
full power of Uncle Might's punches three times.
If you wear these, I think
you'll be able to use your full power.
My... power...
Please use them.
Huh? But isn't it something important“?
That's why I want you to use them.
Become a wonderful hero
who can save people in trouble, okay?
Okay!
Hello?
What are you doing, Midoriya?!
"Lida"
Sorry I'm late!
Huh? Wait, where's everyone else?
They're not here yet. What do they think
"attending as a group" means?!
Sorry! I'm late...
I apologize, but Jiro...
Oh, Yes! Yes!
I'm... not used to clothes like this...
The clothes make the man, right?
She looks like a female assassin...
Shut up.
What? I complimented you!
No, you didn't.
It's my first time wearing formal clothes.
I borrowed this from Yaoyorozu...
I-It looks good on you.
Yeah, really good!
Oh, Deku! You don't have to flatter me...!
Uraraka?!
Oh, are you all still here?
The party's starting!
The headliner has appeared!
Crap, Mineta, I can't take this anymore.
What should I do?
Do whatever you want.
"Central Tower - 2nd Floor - Reception Hall"
Ladies and gentlemen,
welcome to I-Expo's reception party.
Let's have the number one hero,
All Might, who is visiting us today,
say a few words and lead us in a toast!
Everyone, please give him a round of applause!
Please, come to the stage.
Dave, I didn't know about this.
This was bound to happen once
they found out All Might would be here.
Jeez...
It's no good.
Neither Bakugo nor Kirishima are picking up.
Hey, are you absolutely
sure this is the right way?
I think it is...
You think?!
Well, actually, I left my phone in my room...
Thank you for inviting me. I am All Might.
I don't like formal talk, so--
This is an announcement
by the I-Island security system.
"I-Island - Business Area"
that an explosive device
was placed in the I-Expo area.
"A bomb?!
--Seriously?!
I-island will now be in high alert mode.
--Residents and tourists should
return to their homes or lodgings.
"I-Island - Hotel Room"
--No way...
--Residents and tourists should
return to their homes or lodgings.
--Will everything be okay...?
--Residents and tourists should
return to their homes or lodgings.
--We'll be safe as long as we follow directions.
--Those that have come a long way should
go and wait at the nearest evacuation center.
--You're right.
--Those that have come a long way should
go and wait at the nearest evacuation center.
Anyone still outside ten minutes
from now may be arrested without warning.
--Let's hurry to our rooms.
--Please refrain from going outdoors.
--Right.
In addition, most of the main buildings
will be sealed off by the security system.
I repeat--
It's just as you heard.
We have taken over the security system.
Don't think you're going to put up a fight.
If you do...
...then the security machines will bare their
fangs at all the good people on this island.
That's right.
All the people on this island are hostages.
Of course, you all are, as well.
Do it.
The restraining devices used for security...!
This isn't good!
Don't move!
If you take even one step,
then I'll kill everyone here in a second.
Shit!
Good boy.
You're all going to learn from All Might
and do what I say quietly, right?
Toshi, we have no choice
but to listen to them right now.
But, Dave...
I will definitely find a way to save everyone.
Just bear with it until then.
My phone has no signal.
It looks like all reports are being blocked.
Seriously...?
The elevator isn't responding, either.
Seriously?!
I can't believe the security system
would switch to high alert mode
just because they found something explosive.
Lida, let's go to where the party is being held.
Why?
Because All Might is at the party.
All Might is?
Oh, then we have nothing to worry about.
Melissa, can you get us to the party somehow?
If we use the emergency stairs,
I think we can get close to the party.
Please lead the way!
Our phones have no signal,
and we can't use the internet, either.
We can't watch TV anymore, either.
It can't be helped.
Why don't we play Uno until they find the bomb?
Don't worry.
If you stay quiet, you will not be hurt.
We are prepared to release
you once the time comes.
What are you all after?
Didn't you hear me?
I said, stay quiet.
Oh right, got it.
You're a researcher here, right?
Y-Yes.
Take him.
What in the world...?
Stop!
He is my assistant.
What do you plan to do with him?
If it isn't David Shield...
You come, too.
And if I refuse?
Then somewhere on this island,
someone's scream will ring out.
Fine. I will go.
Dave...
Will I be able to defeat the villains
and get the security system to work again?
Especially in this body...?
No, I must do it.
Because I am the Symbol of Peace!
Y-Young Midoriya!
All Might's noticed us.
Jiro, can you do it?
Yeah.
Please talk.
We're listening!
Can you hear me?
The villains have taken over the tower.
They have control of the security system,
and everyone on this island is a hostage.
All the heroes have been taken, as well.
It's dangerous.
Get away from here as soon as possible.
Th-This is bad, Midoriya.
We have received All Might's message.
I suggest that we follow the directions of
U.A. teacher All Might and escape from this place.
I agree with lida's opinion.
We are still students.
We cannot fight against villains
without our hero licenses.
Then what if we escape and tell heroes outside--
I think it'll be hard to escape.
This place is built with the
same level of security as Tartarus,
where criminal villains are kept.
Then, all we can do is wait until help comes...
Kaminari, are you okay with that?
What do you mean?
You don't feel like you should go help?
Hey, hey, the villains even caught All Might!
There's no way we can go save them ourselves!
We are trying to become heroes.
Yes, but we are still not
allowed to work as heroes--
Does that mean it's all right
for us to not do anything?
Th-That's...
I want to save them.
Deku?
I want to go save them.
You're planning on fighting the villains?!
Didn't you learn anything from USJ, Midoriya?!
It's not like that, Mineta.
I've thought about it.
We need a way we can save All Might
and the others without fighting the villains.
I understand how you feel,
but is there anything that convenient...?
Even if it's hard, I still want to try!
I want to look for the best way
possible and then go save everyone!
Deku.
I-island's security system is
on the top floor of this tower.
If the villains have taken
control of the system,
then the authentication locks and
passwords should have been disabled.
We should be able to restart the system.
We just need to get away from the eyes
of the villains and get to the top floor...
Then, maybe we can save everyone.
Melissa...
What do you mean by "get away
from the eyes of the villains"? How?
Currently, none of us have actually been harmed.
I think the villains aren't used
to working with the security system.
Avoid fighting and get the
system back to normal, huh?
I see.
We could do it, don't you think?
--Yeah!
--Definitely!
But the villains are waiting on the top floor...
There's no need to fight!
If we get the system back to normal,
then All Might and
the hostages will be released.
When that happens, the tables
will be turned in an instant!
Deku, let's do it!
Uraraka!
I don't want to sit around doing nothing
if there's something we can do.
I think that's something that's more
important than whether we're heroes or not.
Yeah, let's help the people who need help!
Let's do what our natural
instincts are telling us to do.
Yeah!
Midoriya.
I'll go, too.
Me, too.
Todoroki!
Kyoka!
I'll turn us back if I decide
we cannot do anymore.
If you're okay with that, then I will go, too!
Lida!
If that's the case, then I will go, too!
All right, me too!
Yaoyorozu!
Kaminari!
Oh, all right, I get it!
I just have to go, right?
Thanks, Mineta!
Let's take this on, Mineta!
Let's do our best, Mineta!
Melissa, please wait here.
I'll go, too.
But you don't have a Quirk...
Do you have anyone who can change
the settings of the security system?
I'm a student at the Academy.
I think I can be useful.
But...
I might just get in the way
until we get to the top floor...
...but let me help protect everyone, too.
Please!
All right.
Let's go and save everyone!
Right!
Young Midoriya?!
Those eyes... Don't tell me...
No, run away!
No, I won't run.
It's too dangerous.
I want to do what I can.
Young Midoriya...
I will definitely save everyone!
He's going, after all, huh?
I know that I must reproach him
as a teacher for his actions.
But, if you don't move now, you're not a hero.
In that case, I'll wait.
I'll believe that you all can
break us out of this situation.
We're counting on you, you zygotes!
Let's go!
--Yeah!
--Okay!
"Central Tower - Top Floor - Control Room"
I brought him.
Hurry up and unlock the vault.
Acting so high and mighty...
You heard him.
If you don't want to die,
then hurry up and do it.
R-Right.
Take him.
Get out.
"Central Tower - Emergency Stairs"
This is the 30th floor.
Melissa, what's the top floor?
The 200th floor.
Seriously?
We have to climb that much?!
It's better than running into villains.
Melissa, do you want me to use my Quirk on you?
Thanks, but I'm fine.
Save your power for when we really need it.
The shutter...!
What should we do? Break it?
If we do that, then the security system
will react, and the villains will notice us.
Then can't we just go from here?
--Mineta!
--No!
What?
Did a door on the 80th floor open?
Did you make a mistake scanning each floor?
Let down all the partitions on the 80th floor.
Don't let those kids get away!
Roger.
Be careful, everyone.
Villains are crafty.
Is there any other way to go up?
There's another emergency staircase
like this on the opposite side.
Hurry!
The shutters are...
The ones behind us are, too!
Todoroki!
Right!
Let's cross inside here!
"80th Floor - Plant Factory"
A plant factory.
They research how Quirks influence plants here.
Wait! Look at that!
The elevator's coming up.
Are the villains following us...?
Let's hide and let them pass us!
I wonder if we can use that
elevator to get to the top floor?
No, only authorized people
can operate the elevators.
And it's made as sturdy as
a bomb shelter, so we can't destroy it.
Come on, let us use the
conveniences of modern civilization!
Those clothes... They're the
villains who were at the party.
They said the kids were in here.
They came into an annoying place.
They're coming!
Quiet.
Don't come... Don't come...
Go away... away...!
Please, don't notice us!
I found you, you damn kids!
What should we do? What should we do?
Huh? What did you say, you bastard?
Kacchan? And Kirishima?
What are you two doing here?
--That's what I want to know--
--Leave this to me, okay?!
Um, we got lost...
Where should we go for the reception?
Why did you come all the way
to the 80th floor if you got lost?!
I can see through you! Don't lie to me!
His Quirk!
Kirishima...!
This Quirk is...
Todoroki?!
We'll stall for time here.
Look for a way to get to the top!
Todoroki!
What about you?
I'm fine, just go!
Todoroki!
I'll be right behind you after I clean this up.
Right!
You're all here, too?
What's going on, Todoroki?
You didn't hear the broadcast?
Huh?
Villains have taken over this tower.
"Huh?
--What?!
I'll explain more later.
For now, the villains...
What's with that Quirk?
Don't let your guard down.
Shut up! I know!
You kids...
Don't take advantage of us!
Die...!
BakLugo!
--Kirishima!
--Dodge!
You boys aren't normal kids, are you?
What are you?
Like we'd tell you, damn villains!
You're not worth telling my name to.
This is no good, either?
Hey, what should we do?
We're like mice caught in a bag!
Is this as far as we can go?
Melissa, do you see something
that looks like a door on the ceiling?
Over there!
The maintenance room for the sunlight system!
Wouldn't that have an emergency ladder?
It's true that there's a manual one,
but we can only access it from the inside.
Even though we got this far...
There's still a possibility.
If you go outside through the space in the vent,
you can use the outside wall
to get to the top floor.
That's right! As long as
there's something similar up top--
We can get inside!
Who can get into the cramped vent
and climb up the outer wall...?
Huh?
W-Wait, me?!
Please, Mineta!
You're the only one who can do it!
Stupid! Stupid! Just what
floor do you think we're on?!
If you save everyone and become distinguished,
then they'll interview you, and you'll
definitely be super popular with the girls!
Please!
Harem, harem!
All right! I just have to go, right?!
Harem, harem, harem!
Harem, harem!
"Maintenance Room"
I did it!
I made it!
Now, now, now, give me some love!
Just the ladies is fine. Just the ladies.
You were amazing, Mineta.
As expected of a student hero!
Come on, let's get fired up, everyone!
Yeah!
Hey, you still can't find them?
Damn it!
Hey, 80th floor! The kids are getting away!
What's going on?!
Be quiet! Shut up--
That guy's not opening up a hole in space.
He's hollowing it out!
Is that how it is?
Damn it, they just won't stop.
I can't keep playing with you forever!
Howitzer... Impact!
--I can't believe this!
--Bakugo!
Damn it... Hm?
What the hell?
It's the sweat from my palms.
It's like nitroglycerin.
Kirishima!
Are you all right?
I-I can't move...
Help me.
Are you dumb?
You just have to turn off your Quirk.
Oh... right.
But man, that surprised me.
I'm just glad you're uninjured.
Yeah, you too!
Thanks...
What the hell? That's not like you.
Don't worry about it!
I'm not worrying!
All right, let's go after
Midoriya and the others.
Don't tell me what to do!
Todoroki, give us the details.
Looks like they've gotten serious.
Boss, those are no ordinary kids!
They're students from
U.A. High School's hero course--
Hero reserves!
The brats are probably trying
to restore the security system.
You started the security machine
on the 80th floor, right?
Yes, sir!
Then raise all the partitions
on floors 100 to 130.
Huh?
Do what I say.
Doesn't it seem like we got lucky?
All the shutters have been raised
since we passed the 100th floor.
Could they have lost us?
That's probably not it.
They're leading us somewhere, aren't they?
Yeah.
Even so, to get just a little further up...
...we'll go where they want us to go.
"130th Floor - Laboratory"
It looks like the enemy has changed
from shutting us in to trying to capture us.
I'm sure they realized that we're U.A. students.
But in that case, we know what to expect, too!
Yeah. Let's go with Plan A, then.
Kaminari!
All right, I'll do my best, too!
I'm counting on you, lida!
Right!
Take this... indiscriminate
Shock 1.3 Million Volts!
They defended!
Damn it, then... 2 Million Volts!
Idiot! If you do that...
Yay...
...then you'll turn dumb.
But thanks to him, the security
machines have been stopped.
Kaminari!
They' re too sturdy...
We have no choice... Everyone!
Plan B!
Right!
We can jam their communications with this!
Take that!
And this!
Go!
Mineta!
Give Kaminari back!
He's got a harem waiting!
How's that?!
Man, they won't stop!
Let's go, Midoriya!
Yeah!
One For All... Full Cowling!
Full Gauntlet!
If you wear it, I think you'll
be able to use your full power.
First, 30% of my power...
Smash!
It doesn't hurt. My arm's fine, too.
I can do this!
Whee!
Jiro!
Where are the security machines?!
They're coming from the left!
Okay, let's keep going from the right!
--Right!
--Yeah!
Deku, what's with that arm? It's amazing!
Yeah!
Melissa, it worked perfectly!
You brought it, huh?
I didn't know how to take it off...
Boss, there's something interfering
with the sensors on the security machines.
We lost those kids!
Don't lose your presence of mind.
There's probably someone among
those brats with a hearing Quirk.
I hear a lot of security machine
wheels coming from the floor below.
Any sounds from above?
--No. It's fine.
--Let's go!
"138th Floor - Server Room"
A trap?!
Let's break through, lida!
Wait!
If the servers here are damaged,
then it could affect the security system, too.
Just how many are there?!
We'll stop the security machines here.
Midoriya, take Melissa
and find a different route!
Come with me, Melissa!
Ochaco, you come with us, too!
Huh? But--
Please, Uraraka!
Right!
Torque Over...
...Reciproburst!
I'll leave the gun to you.
I'll make ammo!
Roger!
I won't let you have my harem, okay?!
Yay...
Go!
Deku, you can't stop!
If we get caught here, then there was
no point in lida and the others staying behind!
R-Right!
Everyone, please be okay!
My engine stalled?
Lida!
Yao-momo, ammo!
Yo ormemme'?
I-I've reached my limit with Creation...
My scalp's reached its limit, too...
It's 'cause you kids were getting carried away!
What about the three who ran?
We're looking for them now.
Damn it, they're so annoying!
Th-This is...
The wind power generator system.
Why here?
If we go up through the tower, the security
machines are probably waiting to ambush us.
So we'll go up to the top all at once from here.
If we can just get to that emergency exit...
All the way up there?
If we have Ochaco's Quirk that lets
her make anything she touches weightless,
then we can do it.
Right. Leave it to me.
Melissa, hang on to Deku.
Okay!
Go...!
All right!
Oh, no...!
Uraraka!
Release your Quirk and run away!
I can't!
If I do that, then we can't save everyone!
Ochaco!
Hurry up! Hurry up!
Hurry up! Hurry up! Hurry up!
Kacchan!
Todoroki and Kirishima!
Are you okay, Uraraka?
Yeah, I'm fine.
Deku and Melissa are heading
to the top floor right now.
Yeah, I saw.
We're going to stop these guys right here!
Don't tell me...
...what to do!
But you guys are a good team!
As if!
Thanks, everyon--
Deku! Melissa!
Bakugo! Aim the propeller at Midoriya!
I said, don't tell me what to do!
A hot wind!
Wow!
Todoroki, you used your flames...
Thanks!
Deku!
You're going to hit the wall!
This Full Gauntlet is strong enough to take the
full power of Uncle Might's punches three times.
This is no time to hold back!
Hang on tight!
Okay!
One For All: Full Cowling!
Detroit...
...Smash!
They got into the tower!
Release!
Send Swordkil and the others!
Yes, sir!
Defend the control room until I get there!
Bear it...
Bear it, All Might!
I'm sure they can do it!
I'm sure!
Deku, are you all right?
I-I'm fine...
What about you, Melissa?
Yeah, I'm fine. Just some scratches.
You revolting kids...!
What are you all after?!
Don't pretend to be heroes!
Sum it!
Get out of the way!
--Smash!
--Little girl--
Melissa!
I'm fine.
It's not too bad.
Give me your arm.
Sorry I couldn't protect you...
You should be saying, "Thanks," right?
Yes!
Let's go and save everyone!
They're here!
"Tower - Top Floor"
Melissa, where's the control room?
In front of the central elevator.
Someone's here.
Papa?
Oh, it is!
Why is he on the top floor...?
Did the villains bring him here
to force him to do something?
We have to save him!
Yes.
"Storage Room"
I was able to unlock it. Go to block 1147.
O-Okay!
I'm opening it.
You did it, Professor!
Everything is here.
Yes, I have finally gotten it back.
This device and research data are
the only things I would never give to anyone.
I'll never give them up.
Everything's going according to plan, isn't it?
It looks like the villains are doing well, too.
Thank you. It was all because
you arranged everything for me, Sam.
Papa...
Mel... Melissa...
Miss, what are you doing here?
What do you mean "arranged"?
Papa, don't tell me you're
the one behind this incident?
In order to get that device...?
Is that true, Papa?
It is.
What...? Why...?
The professor is only trying
to get back what was stolen from him.
This groundbreaking invention
that mechanically amplifies Quirks...
It amplifies Quirks...?
Yes, it is still in testing,
but with this device, unlike with drugs,
Quirks can be amplified
without affecting the body.
However, the sponsors confiscated
this invention and research data.
The research itself was also frozen.
If this was made known to the world,
then the structure of superhuman
society would change drastically.
Fearing that, governments from
different nations put pressure on him.
That's why the professor...
I can get my research back?! How?
Instead of doing it ourselves,
we will have villains steal it.
Don't be ridiculous...
There's no need for them to be real villains.
We can hire people wearing the guise
of villains and have it be stolen by them.
Of course, they will not harm anyone.
After it's done, we can continue
our research in a different place.
But...
I want to get the research back no matter what.
Don't you feel the same way?
I have completed the preparations.
We will carry this out on the day of the
I-Expo preopening when the tower will be closed.
The plan will start at
the same time as the reception,
the only time when all the
people involved will be together.
We will pull the strings in the back
as the villains make it seem
like I-island has been taken over.
Professor...
No...
This is a lie, isn't it, Papa?
Tell me this is a lie!
It is not a lie.
This doesn't make sense...
The Papa I know would
never do anything like that!
So why...? Why?
It is for All Might.
You two probably don't know,
but his Quirk is disappearing.
However, if he uses my device,
then it can go back to normal.
It can even give him more
abilities than he started with.
The number one hero...
The Symbol of Peace...
...can get his light back again...
...and save many people once more!
Because All Might passed One For All on to me...
The professor was worried about
All Might losing his power, and--
Please. Please let me hand
this device over to All Might.
There's no time to remake it!
After he gets it, I don't care
what kind of punishment I receive.
--I've prepared myself--
--They risked their lives!
What do you think Deku and his classmates
went through to save the hostages?
What is the meaning of this?
The villains were fake...
It should've all been an act...
Of course it was an act.
An act pretending to be fake villains.
That guy's--!
Deku!
A Quirk that lets him manipulate metal, huh?
Stay there quietly for a bit.
Sam, where's the device?
H-Here.
Sam...?
Don't tell me you were planning on
giving the device to the villains all along.
Y-You're the one who tricked me.
I served you for so long, but you
let your research be frozen so easily,
and the honor and renown we were
supposed to get all went away...
If I didn't get at least some money,
then it was a waste of my time!
Here's the reward I promised you.
Sam!
Wh-Why...?
This isn't what you promised!
Promised?
I don't remember.
This is your reward.
Professor, why...?
R-Run away!
Papa!
Don't come here!
Melissa!
Feeling like playing hero after all this time?
It's no use.
No matter what reason you had,
you've dirtied your hands with evil deeds.
Whether we're fake or real,
the crime you committed will not disappear.
You're the same as us.
You can no longer remain
a scientist or continue your research.
You can only fall into the darkness of villains.
All you can do right now is
mass-produce that device for me.
Hey, take him away.
Give him back!
G-Give Papa back!
That's right, I have to get rid
of all the professor's attachments.
Stop it...!
Smash...!
Melissa!
I'll save the professor and Sam!
So, save everyone else...
Follow her!
Don't let her escape!
Yes, sir!
I won't let you past me!
Don't get carried away!
Everyone...
All Might...
Papa...
I will definitely...
...save you!
Damn it, did she get the
security system back to normal?
What the--
They stopped?
Did Midoriya and Melissa do it?
I-island's security system is
now operating in normal mode.
It's back.
My phone works again, too.
Wh-What happened all of a sudden?
What happened?
Damn it!
Did you do it, everyone?
Where's the helicopter?
It has landed.
We're getting out of here.
Y-Yes, sir.
M-Move, lzuku Midoriya!
What are you here for?
I will do what I can right now.
What's wrong, Melissa?
Uncle Might! Papa's been taken by
the villains, and Deku's gone after them!
It's fine! I will go!
Boss, what about everyone else?
We're leaving before the
security system gets reactivated.
Y-Yes, sir!
Kill...
me...
I'll add just a few more sins...
Then, I'll make your wish come true.
Wait!
Give the professor back!
I see.
Did you come to seize this man
who has committed wrongdoing?
No!
I've come to save the professor!
To save a criminal?
I'm going to save everyone!
I'm going to save the professor, too!
What are you saying?
Shut up!
That's what heroes do!
They save people who are in trouble!
How?
Don't worry about me... Get away.
Jeez, it's so inconvenient being a hero.
I didn't do much, and you already can't move.
No matter what, it's not a smart way to live.
Get us out!
Roger!
That guy shouldn't be able to activate
his Quirk without touching me with his hand.
You're...
Deku!
Professor!
Stop it.
Midoriya, get away.
Melissa is...
Melissa is waiting for you!
You certainly are a hero.
But you're an idiot.
Don't give up. Think!
What to do... What should I do...?!
Deku!
Have a nice nap!
--Crap... Damn it...!
--Deku!
Give him back!
Give the professor back!
Damn it...!
This is the time to smile, Young Midoriya!
It's fine now. Why?
Because I am here!
All Might!
I'll have you give my friend back, you villain!
Papa...
Papa!
Me... Melissa...
It's fine now.
I'm glad.
All Might...
I...
All Might!
Papa!
Professor!
That Sam...
He said that All Might's Quirk was declining
and that he didn't have the power he once had.
He's using... the professor's...
Shit! Time's...
You don't know when to give up, huh?
Texas...
...Smash!
What?!
All Might!
What do you call that?
As expected of something by David Shield.
I can tell that my Quirk is getting revitalized.
This is good. This thing is great!
Th-This is Dave's...
It's the power of the device Papa made...
Now, in order to raise the price of this device,
why don't we have a demonstration
of how it can blow All Might away?
All Might...
It's as I thought...
He's at his limit!
Uncle Might!
Hurry up and get crushed!
All Might!
Go to hell!
How can you get beat up
by such a damn lame last boss?
Huh, All Might?!
Young Bakugo!
While you can... the villains...
Todoroki! Everyone!
We'll take on the lumps of metal!
Yaoyorozu, take care of things here!
Right!
With my students so motivated,
I can't be held back by some stupid limit!
I need to go past my limit, and go beyond!
That's right, Plus Ultra!
Carolina...
...Smash!
Prepare yourself, villain!
Is this all you've got--?
Prepare myself?
You should take your own advice,
All Might.
What is this power...?
All Might!
Deku!
Damn it...!
This power enhances muscles...
There are multiple Quirks...
D-Don't tell me...
Yeah, when we were planning this extortion,
I received a call from that man.
He said that he wanted to work with me.
When I asked him why,
this is what he said:
If All Might's friend has said he wants
to have a hand in something evil,
then I definitely want to help.
It is unfortunate that I will not be
able to see All Might's face twist in pain
when he finds out, though.
All For One...!
You've finally stopped smiling, huh?
Noooo!
All Might!
Uncle...!
Farewell, All Might!
Uncle Might!
Detroit...
...Smash!
That brat!
Young Midoriya!
With that body... It's too reckless!
But a hero has to save those in trouble!
Thanks.
It's true that I am in some trouble right now.
Lend me a hand, Young Midoriya.
Yes, sir!
Let's go!
Worthless little brat!
You're nothing better than trash!
You don't know when to give up!
You're the one who doesn't!
I won't let you!
Out of my way!
Ow...
What... is that?
To overcome the crisis in front of you...
...with everything you've got...
...and save people...
...with everything you've got.
That is what makes...
...a hero!
I'll crush you and the tower!
Double Detroit...
...Smash!
Go...!
All Might!
Midoriya!
Get him!
Go...
...beyond!
Plus...
...Ultra!
Did they do it?
They did it...
They finished off the villain!
--Yes!
--All right!
--They did it! --It's over!
--All Might!
Deku!
Melissa.
I'm glad...
Dave, Dave!
All...
Might...
I came to save you, Dave.
Thanks...
Papa!
All Might!
If you want to thank someone,
you should thank Melissa and Young Midoriya.
I'm so glad... I really am...
Thank you. Thanks to you all,
we were able to save everyone.
It's thanks to you, too, Melissa.
I was saved so many times by your Full Gauntlet.
Thank you very much.
Deku...
Oh, but sorry! I broke it...
Don't worry about that.
Deku!
--Melissa!
--Hey! Hey!
--You did it, Midoriya!
Are you two okay?
We're fine!
All Might and the professor are fine, too!
Are you all okay?
We're fine!
I heard most of it from Melissa.
I...
I was scared to lose your light...
I was scared that the peace
you built would crumble...
But my ideas and that device were nothing
more than ways to keep the status quo.
Even though the future, and hope,
were right there in front of me,
I didn't notice them...
Like how Melissa is trying
to become my successor,
you have lzuku Midoriya...
He's your successor, isn't he?
He's still not ready.
But in him hides the possibility
of shining as a hero more than anyone.
I can see it, too, Toshi...
A light like yours...
The light of a hero.