Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org
Why were superhuman
powers, the meta abilities
known so casually as Quirks,
forced upon our kind?
Why was the first met a human...
The Shining Baby... born unto us?
These Quirks bring about
nothing but tragedy.
They are not a blessing
on our world,
but the beginning of its end.
It is foretold in the
Quirk Doomsday Theory.
As generations pass,
powers mix and evolve.
Eventually, none will be able
to control their abilities.
In this hour of need,
80 percent of humanity
is sick with Quirks.
How many of the
remaining pure humans
will have relations
with Quirk holders?
Spawning even more who are
cursed with this blight.
Our extinction is nigh at hand.
We, Humarise, must take action.
Even if it means dying
the earth red with blood,
that will simply be our
righteous burden to bear.
For humanity's salvation.
Now then.
Let us begin.
Ah, hello there.
It seems you don't have a Quirk.
Congratulations.
You are one of the chosen
who's been saved.
The group
claiming responsibility
for the recent attack
is known as Humarise.
This radical sect was founded
by Flect Turn and seeks
to save humanity from the
so-called Quirk Doomsday Theory.
The attack used a
Quirk-activating substance
known as Ideotrigger that was
spread through the streets
via devices we're
dubbing Trigger Bombs.
The mission
of the Hero team we've gathered
is to search the 25
known Humarise complexes
so that these bombs
can be destroyed.
Intelligence suggests there's
one device at each location.
Arrest any Humarise
members present
and neutralize the payload.
Be advised you should
expect heavy resistance.
They may detonate the bombs
once they realize we're moving.
As such, we're not asking local
law enforcement to assist.
This is the most urgent mission
many of you have ever faced.
All Might.
Heroes, the success
or failure of this task
rests on your shoulders.
Let's give smiles
back to citizens
who're frightened by terrorism!
This is it, heroes.
Start your missions!
Team A.
No matter what happens,
collect the Trigger Bomb
before it can be set off!
Roger that!
There. Humarise's
Otheon headquarters.
While they handle
the weapon, we're to take
the facility and capture
their leader, Flect.
Don't let your
guards down, Team B.
What, you think
we'd forget all that?
Shut up!
Stay back!
We won't let you past us!
This is what
resistance gets you.
Clair. Track down the device.
I'm on it.
Voyance!
They're violating our sanctuary!
Bakugo, most of
their members are Quirkless!
Don't be too rough.
Yeah. I know.
Stun Grenade!
Endeavor, there's
something wrong.
I can't find the bomb anywhere!
What's that? Where's Flect?
We're about to close in on him.
Once he's captured,
make him tell you
where the bomb is!
Roger!
Flect Turn is in that room.
Damn it! Their leader's gone!
Search the premises!
In the end, even though
we raided the Humarise buildings
around the world, we couldn't
find a single Trigger Bomb.
Yeah. We interrogated
the members we rounded up.
But it's no use.
They've got no clue where
the devices are being kept.
Doesn't seem like they even
knew the things existed.
It's the same for members from
the other branches, too.
My guess? It's likely
that the recent attack
was carried out by a
smaller internal group
directly under the
control of Flect Turn.
Director, there
might be another facility
that we don't know about.
They must have guessed
that we were coming
and moved the bombs
in anticipation.
All teams stand by in
your respective locations.
We're going to send
in more heroes
to find Humarise's secret base!
I have to deliver this.
If I don't, the world
will be destroyed!
Roro. Lala.
It's about time for me
to head off to work.
You know what to do.
We'll study bunches!
And if it turns out I'm not
gonna be home till late?
We'll make dinner for ourselves!
Mm. 'Kay, but...
What if a weirdo shows up
and tries to stalk ya, huh?
We'll pretend nobody's home!
Yeah?
Yeah!
Don't worry, though,
I doubt today's gig
is gonna take that long anyway.
Okay!
Pino!
All right, I'll catch
ya kiddos later.
Have a good day!
Old man, you got a lead for me?
Pickup's on East Third Street.
Be quick about it.
The package needs
to be delivered
to the Chinese restaurant
in South Grove.
How much cash are we talking?
Heh. Like you're in a position
to negotiate fees.
You'll take the regular rate
and do it with a smile.
Okay. I'm on it.
Done before you know it.
What are you... that's my bike!
You stole it from someone else.
I'll give it back to its
rightful owner later!
You can't just take
whatever you want, damn punk!
C'mon. Let's get this over with.
Whoa! The streets are so busy!
Yeah, well, I guess it is
the biggest city in Otheon.
Being told to wait
on standby is one thing.
But since when do I get
treated like an errand boy?
It's because we're the lowest
ranking members in our group.
Huh?!
The only reason we got called up
in the first place is because
we're doing our work studies
at Endeavor's Agency.
We're basically freebies
that were thrown in.
Still. We have a huge
responsibility here.
Our job is to protect
the world from Humarise.
And we will find them.
We'll make sure of it.
The stupid organization
is full of obsessed idiots.
Why do they believe the
Quirk Doomsday Theory?
They're taking a
totally hypothetical idea
and using it to
justify their crimes.
Those
thieves robbed my jewelry shop!
Somebody stop them!
Aw, hell. Heroes!
Catch up with you at the spot.
I'll leave the case to you!
You chase the other one!
Got it!
Move! Move!
Get outta my way now!
Black whip!
Todoroki! Stop him!
Leave it to me!
That'll teach ya.
What a pathetic blast!
I'll show you what
a real one looks like!
This is taking too long.
My contact better
not be a no-show.
Here!
Wait. What?
Not gonna work on me.
That took longer than expected.
Todoroki!
Midoriya. The case is gone.
Did he get rid of it?
There's a third!
Gotcha!
Stinks to be you.
He's already up on the roof?
I can't shake him.
Black whip!
Still got it.
Hey, knock knock!
Oh, thank you so much!
He couldn't have gotten
that far away yet, right?
Heh. I think it's pretty
obvious I'm too smooth for you.
You can't catch someone
with these moves.
Huh?
Whoa!
Yikes!
An accident?
Midoriya!
I'll take care of the car crash!
Thanks!
Hey. We're okay.
Dang. I'm gonna be late.
- ...- Wuh-oh!
- ...Wait!
Hold the door, will ya?
Man. Heck of a day, huh?
Aw, jeez.
This is my best set
of clothes, and now look,
they're all scuffed up.
That stupid hero.
I should send him
a dry-cleaning bill.
Wait, have we seen him before?
Is this town even
in his jurisdiction?
Oh, well.
Don't have to worry
about him now, huh?
Why exactly did you
chase me down?
Why were you running from me?
I have work to do,
so I was in a hurry.
What kind of work?
I move money. Know what I mean?
I may not look it, but I'm
a skilled negotiator.
So, will you please let me
get along with my business?
Okay, kid, thanks.
So show me what's in the case,
and then you're free to go.
How much are you offering me?
Huh?
Y'ask for somethin', it's only
natural you should pay for it.
I just wanna make sure
it's not stolen goods.
Say, you're not a hero
from this country, are you?
Is it really okay for you to do
hero work in a foreign land
if you don't have permission?
Well... The thing is...
You've got no authority
in this city,
so maybe rethink
your tone, my friend.
Or should I tell the police
that I was chased down
and harassed by
a power-hungry hero
who had no legal
right to detain me?
How do you think that's
gonna go over, buddy?
I'm so glad we could come
to this understanding.
If you wanna do pro work,
I suggest you stay in your
own country from now on.
Later.
Wait!
What's your problem?
I told you.
I wanna see what's in the case.
If you want to see,
then flash some cash.
Show me and maybe I will.
Show me 100,000 eurus.
You're out of your mind.
...A quick peek!
...Just let go 'a me!
Hands off!
Huh?
I'm... confused.
Good work.
Hey, come over here for a sec!
Take a look at these.
Where'd they come from?
Was this an attack?
Unfortunate. But so be it.
We'll take the
necessary precautions.
You shall continue
tracking it down.
Of course. Thank you, sir.
Don't forget, Beros.
There is only one way
for those possessed
by the demon of sickness
to atone, and that is
to give oneself to the cause
of saving humanity.
I understand.
I'm sorry!
Please forgive me, I beg of you!
Jeez! So much for
avoiding any kind of scene.
Well, I'm just glad
that you don't think
I'm a criminal anymore.
We're good here.
I guess even heroes
make mistakes
and chase after innocent
people on occasion.
Ah, crap, what's going on?
This isn't what I signed up for.
Wasn't this supposed
to be full of jewelry?
Oh, no.
Don't tell me...
I mixed up the cases?
Anyway, like I said, super busy.
You're really sweaty.
Do you feel okay?
Shoot, I need to
hurry up and backtrack.
But will the case
still be there?
If someone picked it up and
looked at what was inside,
there's no way
I'm getting it back.
I'm dealing with villains here.
I can't say, "Oopsy, I lost it."
This is bad.
What am I gonna do?
...'Scuse me.
Are you positive that
nothing's wrong with you?
Huh? Oh, I'm peachy thanks.
...Okay then.
The police? Already?
How'd they know to nab me?
Hands up and
kneel on the ground.
Um. Hey, guys!
Please just hold on!
It's not him.
Truth, didn't steal anything!
Stop there!
We have permission to shoot!
Fire!
Hang on and try not to flail.
Why would they be using
lethal force on you?
I thought that I was gonna die.
Someone's after us?
We can't put
bystanders in danger.
What's happening?!
No!
We have to get somewhere safe.
Idiots!
We're right in the middle
of an important mission.
You should leave
the petty criminals
for the local authorities
to take care of!
I thought heroes were supposed
to assist those in trouble.
You're the one who's
supposed to be teaching us.
Maybe you should a explained
how to ignore crimes.
That's not what I said!
And Deku? Where'd he run off to?
He's following someone who was
working with the jewel thieves.
But he's not picking up
his phone right now.
You slackers!
I shouldn't have
brought you with me
even if you are doing
your work studies!
It's him.
Midoriya, hey. Do you
have the suspect?
Police just attacked
us out of nowhere!
What?
Why, what did you do to them?
I don't know! They
barely said anything at all
before they started
firing at us!
And when we tried to run away,
we were attacked again
by someone who
looked like a villain.
Calm down!
Tell me everything
that happened.
Start from the beginning.
Okay, so, I chased the
guy who ran away with the case
and eventually caught him.
But there wasn't any jewelry
inside when I opened it up.
...Endeavor. Emergency.
It's about Deku.
Once again, according
to recent police reports,
the suspect, who is thought
to have killed 12 people,
is at large and
considered by authorities
to be highly dangerous.
He's a Japanese hero.
Uh, called Deku.
Real name, Izuku Midoriya.
The entire nation
is on the lookout.
There are also reports
that he has an accomplice...
Hello? Hello? Todoroki?
Midoriya. What did you
really do out there?
What do you mean? Nothing!
The news.
They're saying you're wanted as
a suspect for mass murder.
No.
That makes no sense.
What's going on?
We'll look into it on our end.
You stay off the grid for now.
They'll track you with GPS.
Once you turn off your phone,
don't forget to take
out the battery.
Ugh, don't do that!
So, you were able to get
in touch with your friends?
Wait, what are you
doing to your phone?
Did they say when
they're gonna pick us up?
Yeah. About that.
We're getting an emergency call
from the Otheon team!
Deku's been put on
the wanted list!
What did Young Midoriya do?
How could this have happened?
I don't know,
but according to this,
he killed 12
civilians in Otheon.
What kind of ridiculous
lie is that?!
But this intel comes from HQ.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait!
There's no way Midoriya
would ever hurt anybody!
Guys?
No, not a chance.
This must be some kinda mistake.
It's a false report!
I can't believe it.
No way that's true.
Deku fights to save people.
Something else must
be going on here!
Ribbit! I'm sure there's an
explanation behind all this.
I wouldn't worry, girls.
Endeavor and the
others are on it.
Tell me I'm still unconscious.
You're a stone-cold murderer,
and they think
I'm your accomplice?
I thought you were supposed
to be some kinda hero!
Explain yourself!
I don't know how
we ended up like this.
I can't wrap my head
around all of it.
Oh, great. It's all over.
Bye-bye life.
And here I thought I was
already living at rock-bottom.
What happens if I
fall even lower?
Is it even possible?
This is all your fault!
You dragged me into this mess!
So fix it!
That's what heroes do, right?
The police fired on us
without asking any questions,
and then we were
attacked by a villain.
That tells me that
whoever's behind this
doesn't care if
we're dead or alive.
I would suspect they're
not really after us.
Ah! They must want this!
I don't get it.
There's nothing in here that
looks incriminating, is there?
Wait, what are you doing?
You figure they're after
this dumb case, right?
That's perfect.
We'll hand it over and
this'll all be put to bed.
It's simple as that.
Life will just go
back to normal.
No way, it can't be that easy.
If what's in here is so
important, then they'd probably
wanna silence us even if
we did turn it in to them.
Hey, don't say that!
We're never gonna get anywhere
if you're only thinking
negative thoughts, buddy.
So new plan.
Let's destroy the case.
Then we can just say
"Whoops, it burned up."
That's not gonna
fix our problems.
Uh. New-new plan.
What if we contact the police?
Huh? And say what?
"If you want the case,
then give us 1,000,000
eurus, pronto!"
That would
make us real criminals!
We need to calm down.
Are you sure we
can't ditch it somewhere?
They won't really
kill us, right?
You're over thinking things.
If this case is related
to some sort of crime,
we can't give it
to the bad guys.
We might accidentally be
helping out real villains.
Don't get me involved with
your hero sense of justice!
I'm afraid we're
already in this together.
They wanted to kill us.
If we don't know the reason why,
then it's dangerous
to act rashly.
Otherwise we'll end up
full of arrows. Or worse.
Okay. Then what do
you suggest instead?
We run for it.
Huh?
No matter what
the situation may be,
we can't fight
against the police.
The people chasing us
are Otheon officers.
If we cross the border into the
neighboring country of Klayd,
then they shouldn't
be able to follow us.
Let's hurry and get out of here
before we end up trapped.
What about the arrow person?
A border's not gonna
stop a villain.
If that happens, then I promise
that I'll protect you from them.
Huh?
I think getting out of here
is our best course of action.
Okay, fine, I guess that plan
makes as much sense as anything.
I'll go to Klayd or
wherever you think is best.
Right.
That bus'll get us
to the border.
And it'll be free
if we hop on top.
Absolutely not! We have
to pay if we ride.
We're wanted bad guys, remember?
It'll be over if
somebody recognizes us.
Aw, man.
See? A freebie's not so bad.
The delinquent life grows
on you. You'll see, hero.
Delaware Smash. Air Force!
I just paid for two seats.
And yet I get the feeling
we're staying on the roof.
Well, yeah.
That's nonsense!
What evidence is there
to support that?
Explain everything you have
on Deku, Commissioner General.
The case against Izuku
Midoriya is still pending.
I'm afraid I can't discuss any
of the finer details with you.
Especially considering
you're his current boss
and fellow countryman.
Tch.
Endeavor.
Japan's number-one hero.
He's gravely afflicted
with Stage Five.
For humanity's salvation.
Shoto!
I just got this report back
from a detective friend of mine.
What does it say?
It appears the car you
saw was attacked by a Quirk.
The strange thing is,
the driver was a
member of Humarise.
Wait, Humarise?
Well, did he survive
the accident?
He's comatose,
in critical condition.
Police are standing watch
outside his room in the ICU.
So we can't interrogate him yet.
And there's one
other thing, too.
It looks like the stolen
jewelry was left scattered
nearby the scene.
Huh? But why?
It's a message from Midoriya.
What does he say?
"Keep eating
lunch with strawberries
and make sure you eat the
dinner in the fridge, too."
Why is he telling me
what to eat?
This is odd.
This must be some kind of code.
Clever.
K-L-A-Y-D.
What does this mean?
Did he flee to the neighboring
country of Klayd?
If not yet, he must
be heading there.
Which means I'm going, too.
All right, then.
I'll update Endeavor.
Bakugo, come with me.
Get your hands off me!
It's about Deku, huh?
I'll explain later.
First, let's lose the police.
Don't order me around!
I hope Todoroki and
the others figure out my code.
What secret is hidden
inside this case?
Looks deserted.
No police around.
Hey, uh...
Do you mind if I run and
make a call real quick?
Oh. Sure.
They didn't have anything
about you on TV,
so you should be okay
to show your face.
Try to make it short, though.
Got it.
Stanleyk here.
Yo. Old man.
Hm? Is that you, Rody?
Yeah, sorry to call
ya out of the blue,
but can you swing
by my house and tell
my little brother and sister
that I won't be
home for a while?
I'll pay you later. Promise.
You idiot!
I have no obligation
to do you favors!
And besides.
I got a complaint saying the
big delivery was never made!
Things went south.
No excuses!
It's not my fault!
If you don't want to die,
then hurry up and
deliver the goods! Got it?
I don't have the goods.
Damn it!
Hey, is everything okay?
Heh, oh, yeah,
life couldn't be any better.
Huh.
So, you think that the
cases got switched?
Yes. The jewelry
store was robbed by a villain.
But Midoriya thinks that
there was some kind of
mix-up on the street.
So the one he has now used
to belong to a Humarise member.
No jewelry.
And that's probably the reason
the police are chasing him.
Moron.
Possibly.
I'm guessing, whatever he's
carrying around is important.
Question is, why are
the police mobilizing
on such a large scale?
Humarise members have
infiltrated the police force.
Yeah.
And there's no telling
when they'll make their
allegiances known.
We have to be careful.
I'll do what I want!
That's not great.
Doesn't look like anything's
crossing the border from here.
We'll have to borrow a vehicle
of some sort tomorrow.
Otherwise, we'll
be stuck walking.
Walking? You're crazy.
Did you forget how
heavy this thing is?
If you get tired, I can
just carry you on my back.
After all, that's what
strength is for, right?
Helping people out
whenever they're in trouble.
Heh. Maybe fix our
current situation
rather than treating
me like a backpack.
Oh, I will. I promise.
Time for takeoff!
Let me, Big Brother!
Here you go.
You're so lucky!
Lift me up next!
Then me!
Wow, Rody!
Dad!
Welcome back!
Hey there, kiddos.
What's the deal? Why is the
puzzle you brought home so hard?
How am I supposed
to solve this thing?
I'll help, but I'm only
giving you one hint.
You should be able to
figure it out from here
if you keep trying.
Dad. This is yours.
It's a present.
Thanks for always
taking care of Roro and Lala.
You're a good brother, Rody.
I heard the
father abandoned them.
It's worse.
He became a member of Humarise.
That group who
thinks Quirks are a sickness?
Ugh, they're whack jobs.
They were behind
that incident the other day.
Wasn't the dad
a famous engineer, though?
I never would have
seen this coming.
Kids, I don't want
you to play with them anymore.
Who knows what they might
have picked up from him?
Okay.
Let's go to the park!
Yeah!
...Big Brother
...Brother
We'll be fine.
I'll always stay with you, okay?
You never have to worry
about me leaving.
If this case is related
to some sort of crime,
we can't give it
to the bad guys.
We might accidentally be
helping out real villains.
Hello?
What's happening?
No. He wouldn't.
Are you with the police?
Hand over the package.
So yeah.
This means I'm free
to bounce, right?
Where's your friend?
You both know, don't you?
You must've figured out by now
the reason we're
after the briefcase.
No, no I swear.
We haven't got a clue!
Please, my brother and
sister need me back.
They're only kids.
You have to let me go home!
Air Force first.
Then... Smash!
I... I'm so sorry!
Smash!
Why did you do that?
I need you to hold on
to me tightly.
Damn it!
Wait here, okay?
I'll find a doctor
or somebody quick.
No. It's not that deep.
I'll be fine, don't worry.
It destroyed my phone, though.
You mind?
I think there's a first aid kit
floating around in my backpack.
Oh. Yeah.
That archer is a
tough one for sure.
Once I'm patched up,
we're gonna need to find
another place to hide.
Why did you take
the arrow back there?
Huh? What are you asking?
I betrayed you.
You know that.
I stole the case
while you slept.
Instead of worrying about me,
you could have grabbed
it and run away.
Uh... Why would I do
something like that?
I was carrying the jewelry
the villains stole
this afternoon.
I'm one of those bad
guys you heroes hate
and wanna throw in jail!
Well, I can't ignore
when someone's in trouble.
It's kind of my life's
dream to help people.
But why would a criminal like me
be worth getting hurt over?
It's always worth it if
I'm able to help someone,
no matter who it is.
I do not get you.
That's why I admire heroes.
I want to be someone
who can save people,
with a smile on my face
the whole time.
I want to be like All Might.
You're talking about
the blond one, yeah?
He's pretty famous.
Uh-huh! He's my teacher.
Seriously?
So you wanted to become
just like All Might,
and you chased that dream until
it became a reality for you.
Heh. You an' me couldn't
be any more different.
Huh?
My future's pretty
set in stone already.
I don't have the luxury
of saying nonsense like
"I wanna be a pilot."
It's all I can do to provide
for my younger siblings.
- ...- Well, maybe...
- ...Don't say a word.
I don't want your pity!
Stupid heroes.
I've always thought they were
people looking for attention,
who wanted to make money under
the guise of helping others.
You see, pros never come
to the place where I live.
They wouldn't make
any cash there.
But... I guess there are
heroes like you around, too.
The more you help me
and I get to know you,
the more I wonder about what
I'm doing with my own life.
Truth is, I'm pretty lame.
I would say the
same about myself.
I've wanted be
a pro hero forever,
since I was just a little kid.
But I was too weak.
People kept telling me
my goals were impossible.
I couldn't use my Quirk
properly at first,
and I was at the
bottom of my class.
Even now, I'm always being
helped out by my classmates.
I'm still weak.
That's why I wanted
so badly to improve.
To become a hero
who saves people.
And always with a smile.
Oh. Yeah. That's Pino.
Hi, Pino.
Oh, and by the way.
The name's Rody Soul.
We sorta skipped intros.
And my name's Izuku Midoriya,
but call me my hero name, Deku.
"Deku." That's easy to remember.
Yeah. It's grown on me.
Let's get some sleep, Rody.
Yeah. Good idea, Deku.
I deeply apologize.
They escaped before
we could neutralize them.
The entirety of the police
force has been mobilized
to seek out their location.
Can't you get the army involved?
I'm sorry, sir.
I'm afraid that's
beyond my jurisdiction.
Then continue with the search.
Of course. For the
salvation of humanity.
A villain?
Rody?
Sorry, did I wake ya?
Where'd you get a truck?
I kinda borrowed it.
Just figured we
were done walking.
Even wrote an IOU in the name
of the World Hero Association.
They'll understand.
Wish they'd had a Cessna,
we could've flown
straight into Klayd
that way, no problem.
Like, an airplane?
You can really fly
something like that?
Only in my dreams, friend.
Get in.
Question.
Yeah?
Once we figure out
the case's secret,
I can go home, right?
That should be fine.
Oh. I bet your younger brother's
waiting for you at home, huh?
Yeah, with my sister.
What about your parents?
My mom died right after
she had my sister,
so it was up to my dad
to take care of the kids.
He did a pretty good job
there for a while,
raising us while juggling work,
then he suddenly up and
disappeared one day.
Disappeared?
Do you know about that
group called Humarise?
I do. They're a
terrorist organization.
Yeah. After people
in town found out
that Dad left to
become a member,
things got bad for my family.
Our friends started ignoring us,
we were kicked out of our
school and out of our house,
and I couldn't find anyone who
would hire me for honest work.
I'm sorry, that's awful.
I obviously resented
my dad at first.
But not so much anymore.
I don't have time to
think twice about him.
Now, my little
brother and sister
are the most important
things to me.
I just want to create a decent
future for those kiddos.
Aw! They're so cute.
My little brother's
stupid smart!
And my sister's
totally adorable.
First person to break
her heart gets KO-d!
Whoa! Keep
your eyes up, Rody!
Dang.
I can't get over how
useful your Quirk is.
What about you? I mean,
do you have a Quirk?
I've been wondering.
I don't wanna talk about it.
Oh. Sorry.
You won't laugh, will you?
I promise!
Really?
No! I swear it!
Okay. It's kinda weird.
The path is heavily guarded.
We're not gonna be able
to go this route
without fighting
our way through.
Our only choice
is to scale these ridges.
Get on my back. Hurry.
Deku. Take this.
What's the deal?
It'll be difficult
for you to carry me
with that injury from the arrow.
This is where I say goodbye.
Hold on. The truck's out of gas.
I can't leave you alone
in a place like this.
Come on. You know
how fast I can run in a pinch.
I'll scrounge up some food.
Then I'll wait for you.
You go figure out
what's up with this case.
That's what we're here for.
But, Rody.
I'm counting on you, hero!
It's them!
I will not fail again!
Use these.
Ah, damn it. They're
gonna flatten us!
Delaware Smash.
Air Force kick!
Rody! Are you okay?
Yeah. Maybe.
The case!
Watch out!
Rody!
Deku, catch it!
I'm coming!
For the salvation of humanity!
Wait, is this Todoroki?
You learned nothing from Hosu.
Your codes are still
hard to decipher.
Oh, don't even try it.
Wait. Free me, I'll do
whatever you want.
Tell me everything you know
and maybe I'll consider it.
Fine, yeah. You got it!
Die, you traitor!
Damn it.
Bakugo, take her down.
Don't give me orders!
We're out of control!
Stand down and come quietly.
For humanity's salvation.
All units get over there!
Rody, are you all right?
Yeah, but I'm not sure how.
Where is it?
Midoriya. I grabbed this.
Thanks, Todoroki.
But how did you find us?
All thanks to their
flashy attacks.
I spotted you from the train.
Is he the one you were
talking about on the phone?
Yeah, that's right.
He's been pegged as
a criminal, like me.
His name is Rody Soul.
Hey, thanks for the assist.
More importantly...
The damn case.
It's somehow connected
to Humarise.
What? Wait, are you
certain about that?
Yes. Our goal was to
save both it and you.
We thought it was possible
we'd be able to get some
useful intelligence.
What's the matter, Midoriya?
A compartment.
What is this? How does it work?
Try pressing it right here?
That'll just make it go
back to how it was.
Hm. This is hard.
Still not working.
Ugh. Hand it over!
I'll blow it up!
What? No.
You can't do that, Kacchan.
Deku, can I see
that for a second?
You know how to solve it?
I did a puzzle like this
before when I was a kid.
Let's see.
Like this.
And this.
Aw, yeah. I think I got it.
I'm not sure what this is.
We need to figure out
what's stored on this card.
Okay, there's a town at
the foot of the mountain.
Let's investigate there.
The target fled to the
neighboring country of Klayd.
I'm afraid I don't
have the authority
to search inside
their borders, sir.
No matter.
If he has fled the country,
then he won't be able
to interfere with the plan
while it's being
carried out, will he?
The time for revelation and
the great reckoning has come!
For humanity's salvation!
For the salvation of humanity!
Emergency alert, sir!
Humarise has started a broadcast
and it's streaming
across the planet.
Put it on the screen!
Humarise will now
fulfill its purpose.
To protect the pure humans
who are called "powerless,"
against those who have been
infected by the wicked disease
known as Quirks.
We have developed
humanity salvation devices
that will cleanse this world.
Soon, they will be activated
in 25 countries.
Seriously?
This deliverance from
evil shall be witnessed
by all in two hours.
That's hardly any time at all!
However, we are
not without mercy.
If you wish to prevent this
plan from going into effect,
we will generously
reveal the countries
where our devices
have been installed.
What is he playing at?
Even if you do not
understand our righteous cause,
you will have a
chance to live on.
Director.
These are the 25 zones
the bombs are placed in.
They match up with the locations
of known Humarise branches!
It's possible this
is a giant trap.
But we can't afford
to be that cautious.
Give marching orders
to the hero teams on standby!
Yes, sir!
There's widespread panic in
each of the 25 affected zones.
Surrounding areas
are in chaos as well.
Streets are gridlocked.
Transportation is a mess.
Oh, no!
Sun eater, you search
for anybody who's injured.
Red Riot and Real Steel, you
secure a solid evacuation route!
Roger that!
Chimera Kraken!
Let's do this!
Come on, Red Gauntlet!
There! This is your way out!
Don't stand there gawking... go!
Cementos!
Make it a loud one, Mic.
Listen up, everybody!
We've got a rockin' path for you
over here, so get to sliding!
Remain calm. Don't panic!
We're counting on
you, search team!
Find me that
Trigger Bomb immediately.
Hear me?
Understood, sir!
Ribbit!
We've got the
evacuations under control!
Then it's up to us to
find the enemy's device.
Right!
Tsukuyomi, leave the evacuations
to the American team.
It'll be easier for us
to find that death bomb
with a bird's-eye view.
Roger that!
Go. Fierce Wings!
Leave no corner unsearched.
Tokage! Take these sensors and
spread them around the city.
No sweat! We won't
let anyone die today.
Momo, Shall we
head to the next spot?
Yes, sir!
How are we supposed
to find a tiny bomb
hiding somewhere
in this huge city?
Hello! Hello! Hello!
Whoa, Salaam!
You must find what you seek,
not seek what you find!
Follow me young ones!
He's so fast!
Guess being paper
thin has its perks.
Clair, where's
the device, dammit?
There's no sign of it
in this area.
Moving to the next location.
Shoto. What are you doing?
Hurry up and get back here.
So many folders.
Where do we even start?
Move it!
Where's the most
recent time stamp?
It's this video file.
Hello. My name is Alan Kay.
Along with several
other scientists,
I was kidnapped by Humarise.
Kidnapped?
In order to enact their plans,
Humarise took our families
hostage and forced us
to manufacture Quirk
Factor Triggering Bombs
against our wills.
The first terrorist attack
using one of these devices
was merely a ploy, to gather
the world's top heroes
in places where Humarise
branches are located.
The group is planning to
use these horrible bombs
to eradicate those pros.
In an instant, the hero
population will be decimated.
After losing its top heroes,
society would collapse.
Using the vacuum
of chaos afterward,
Humarise will wipe out
anyone with powers
and build a world where only
the Quirkless are allowed.
That is the true goal of Flect
Turn, the leader of Humarise.
A madman.
I hope my voice will
reach the heroes in time.
Eddie Soul, another scientist
here, lost his life helping me.
He made the key I've included
that will disarm the bombs
at their base.
Please. Save the world.
I repeat,
Humarise, the organization
advocating for the
salvation of humanity,
has placed bombs
around the world.
The weapons are set to explode
in one hour and 52 minutes,
unless the heroes are able to
find and disarm them, worldwide.
As you might expect,
panic has gripped the areas
where the devices
are said to be located.
Heroes have been working
to evacuate people to safety
and subvert this attack.
Areas in danger of being
affected by the bombs
are as follows.
No, it can't be.
That circle's in Otheon!
My house is inside of it!
Oh, no.
Where are you?
We should send
this to HQ and have them
order the hero teams to
retreat before it's too late.
We can't do that.
The heroes are out there
looking for the Trigger Bombs.
Even if they're the actual
targets of the terrorist attack.
Even if they know
this is a trap.
As long as there are
people who need help,
the pros will never
leave them and run away.
That's what makes them heroes.
Humarise counted on this when
they came up with their plan.
Then we use that disarming key.
It's up to us to
stop those bombs.
But how do we do that?
On it!
The answer has to be
in here somewhere.
You're an idiot
if you make a key
without telling people
where the lock is!
We look for the
place that wasn't
part of their announcement.
This is where their base is!
Kacchan, Can you find
where the bomb controls are?
Let me work, ya damn nerd!
The furthest area underground.
So we know where it is, but it's
more than 400 kilometers away
from where we are.
We can make it.
I think I know how
to get us there.
Don't worry.
I know the basic controls.
This is no time to be chirping!
We'll definitely
stop the Trigger Bombs.
We'll crush those
crazy cult bastards!
We'll protect the heroes,
our friends, and the world!
We just received
a transmission from Shoto.
He's a hero who
was sent to Otheon.
He says that he's obtained
a master disarming key
for the Trigger Bombs!
Where is he now?
Heading to where
the villain's main system
is located, inside a
hidden Humarise facility.
Young Todoroki. Young Bakugo.
Young Midoriya.
Shoto's figured out a way
to disarm these damn devices?
Then let's go support him!
We can't. Our priority
is evacuation
in case he should fail.
Endeavor!
What is it?
I finally found the target.
Where?
It's in front of the
north gate of Otheon Tower.
Inside a semi-truck!
Heroes near the tower.
Get that bomb out of here!
Roger!
...Clair, come in!
What the hell is this?
Shoji! They're saying
Midoriya and the others
are heading to disarm the bombs!
Don't lose focus!
For now, we need to keep
concentrating on the mission
we were charged with.
Right. Yeah.
There! I've found it.
It's in the third container
of that freight train!
Quickly, shrimps! Go!
We're on it.
Oh, no! Villains!
Crap. Of course
there'd be guards.
Uravity, Froppy, hurry!
Get that bomb away
from everyone!
Yes, ma'am!
I believe Deku and the others
will stop the bombs for us!
But we'll do what we can
to back them up until then!
Get outta the way!
Our teams
have found the devices.
But they're meeting
resistance from Humarise.
They're not making this easy.
We have less than
30 minutes on the clock.
The pros across the
world are fighting desperately.
But we're counting on
you now, future heroes!
Almost there.
The afflicted must be purged.
That's it! The base!
Going in for a landing.
Brace yourselves.
No. Rody, you turn back.
What?
Extras like you
should stay out of the way.
He has a point.
This is a job for heroes!
I don't have time
for you idiots!
Some of their
members have Quirks, too!
I didn't expect there
to be so many of them!
A sound wave?
...Kacchan!
Yeah, yeah, I know!
I've got you!
Bakugo, we'll leave
these guys to you!
Stop them!
Don't tell me what to do!
Take them down!
It's a right at the
end of this hallway.
Hold on.
Huh. Couldn't be easier.
Why are you
morons helping Humarise?
You've got Quirks!
Because we were personally
chosen by Flect as the worthy.
We will work alongside Humarise
and live in their rebuilt world!
Tch. Oh, I get it,
you're just trying to
save your own butts.
Talk about selfish.
As expected of villains.
Die!
They're fast!
I won't just stay behind.
I have to help!
You're Rody Soul, aren't you?
Todoroki!
You go on ahead!
Fast as you can.
I'll stop you all at once.
Flash freeze... Heatwave!
My flames had no affect?
He's raging out of control.
Is he on Trigger?
Somehow he's rotating his Quirk
to control the flow of water.
Smash!
The crap?
How'd they cut through
my explosion?
You must not realize
you're facing the best!
Point blank range!
Too bad!
All that jumping
around's annoying!
Stop your laughing.
It's getting on my nerves!
Idiots never
saw that coming, huh?
I planted a few grenades
while we were fighting.
Hell, If you wanna get crazy,
I'm right there with you.
Hurry! Faster!
Get outta my way!
This is the deepest
room in the base.
Which means the
Trigger Bomb control system
should be on the other
side of those doors.
How dare you?
This is not a place where
someone so diseased
should set foot.
He must be their leader.
Flect Turn.
You have entered
a holy stronghold
that will bring about
the salvation of humanity.
You think this
is what the world needs?
The Quirk Doomsday Theory hasn't
been scientifically verified!
You're basing your crimes
on nothing but a rumor!
How can you accept
something so uncertain
and use it to justify
doing such terrible things?
Pure humans are being threatened
by the sickness of Quirks.
Of that there is no doubt.
As time passes these powers will
mix, evolve, and run rampant,
driving humanity to destruction.
You don't know that for certain!
Whether you have a Quirk
or not doesn't matter.
We're all alive.
We're all human beings!
The gravely afflicted
are beyond our help.
I suppose I shall have
to force you to atone.
I'll stop your Trigger Bomb
if it's the last thing I do!
Smash!
Did he counter my attack?
No, this shock and force.
It felt like I was
hit with a Smash.
That's right.
I was born with this
cursed plague myself.
A disease that can't be cured.
I automatically reflect
all I come in contact with.
I knew it.
His Quirk makes any attack
against him bounce back.
It's the kind of power
that's always activated.
So even though you have
an ability of your own,
you still think
they're somehow evil?
Long-distance attacks
don't work either.
You would question me?
Quirks are a tragedy.
Because of this ailment, I was
never once held by my parents,
never knew a caring touch.
Even my closest friends,
and those I gave my heart to
left me, their
feelings repelled.
I watched them all
leave me, one by one.
Since I reflect everything,
I couldn't even choose
death for myself.
A Quirk that
cannot be controlled
leads to a life of suffering.
But I can save others
from this misery.
These meta powers will
trample no more hearts.
I won't use One For All
until the moment of impact!
Even then...
...it didn't work!
The clock is ticking.
I'll try to avoid
him completely.
Right. Rely on speed,
and get to the controls.
I reject the corruption
within my veins.
I will eradicate
this global contamination
before it's too late.
By doing so,
I will save the worthy.
The pure humans will rise
to power once again.
You wretched soul.
In mere minutes,
the baptism will begin.
The blood of heroes will
cleanse this broken world.
And their deaths will bring
about a glorious new reality.
I won't let you.
Talk all you want.
I will stop the Trigger Bombs!
No.
You will be sacrificed
like your friends.
Uraraka.
Asui.
Kaminari.
Sero.
Mineta.
Kirishima.
Shoji.
Jiro.
Yaoyorozu.
You're all fighting
so desperately.
To stop these
weapons from going off.
To protect everyone's smiles.
Think.
How can I beat this guy?
Rody. Why?
It's fine now, Deku,
don't you worry.
No. You have to run.
I will.
Once I hand this over
to the blue guy.
The disarming key?
What?
Know that I am sorry.
But they said they'd stop
the Otheon explosion
if I helped them out.
Rody. Don't do this.
If we work together, we can
stop him and save everybody.
Please!
How are you gonna stop anything
when you're all messed up?
We're out of time.
The bombs are gonna explode.
It's game over.
No.
At least... I'm going
to protect my family.
I can do that much.
Look.
I'm a worthless
delinquent, Deku.
I can't take on the world,
much less save it.
I'm not a hero like you.
If I have to pick between
society or my family surviving,
the choice isn't that hard.
It was the same for my dad.
You forced his hand.
That's true.
Your father, Eddie Soul,
helped develop the
human salvation bomb.
He knew that if he didn't,
your lives would be forfeit.
It was him.
Eddie Soul,
another scientist here,
lost his life helping me.
Please. Save the world.
My dad didn't "help" you.
You threatened to murder
our whole family.
He only worked for you
because you made him.
Fortunately, he had the clarity
to make the correct decision.
And it appears you're a wise man
just like your father.
You're protecting
your loved ones.
An honorable choice.
I commend you.
We're quite alike.
I developed this plan
because I love humanity
and wish to save it.
Rody, please. You can't do this.
Rody!
We can stop him.
Sorry, hero, but this
is how it all ends.
That's life.
People get betrayed.
If it's any condolence,
it happened to me, too.
Nothing to cry about.
Rody.
What about you.
I mean, do you have a Quirk?
I've been wondering.
You won't laugh, will you?
I promise!
Really?
No! I swear it!
Okay. It's kinda weird.
Pino!
Nice job.
The plan's working, huh?
- ...- Deku!
- ...You foolish boy!
Don't stop!
No!
Rody!
You impertinent child!
Deku!
Don't you dare die.
You kick his ass!
I'll stop the bombs! And you.
You take 'im down, hero!
Let's go!
I'm the end of the line.
I don't care how strong you are.
You won't get past me!
What about you?
I mean, do you have a Quirk?
I've been wondering.
You may think I'm joking, but...
It's Pino.
Ya see,
her actions show
my true intentions.
Really?
No matter how good
I am at lying,
Pino always gives away
how I truly feel.
Almost.
Honestly, it's
not much of a Quirk.
Oh, I wouldn't say that.
Not being able to lie?
I think that's pretty amazing.
Damn it!
They're hammering my right side.
I think it's about time
that you two shut it for good.
No holding back.
You're not getting up!
Howitzer Impact!
Happy now? You idiots.
I'm... losing consciousness.
Is that...?
One last chance.
I won't let you
get in Midoriya's way!
Flash freeze Heatwave!
You can manipulate flames, too?
Fine.
This is the most powerful
move I've got!
My Flash fire Fist.
Jet Kindling!
Midoriya.
Make sure you stop them.
I'll be... like my dad.
And Deku.
He would never give up.
Rody?
For both father
and son to die in vain.
There's no hope
for such fetid scum.
Shut up.
Rody's not scum.
He's my friend, and more noble
than you could ever hope to be.
What a pity.
You still refuse to understand?
Look at how brave he is!
I believe in Rody!
Because I believe in heroes!
We need to lay down
cover for Endeavor!
Fight, Shoto.
But whatever happens,
I'll protect them.
Push it faster, Fierce Wings!
Get that weapon out of here.
Hawks, Quick!
We've just discovered
a new Trigger Bomb.
What? Well, is anyone on it?
This one
should be taken care of.
Any remaining devices?
We currently know of two.
Wait! I've found a new one.
So there's a total of three.
No way are the bad guys winning!
Right, Bakugo?
I'll get this in the
air and send if far away...
Ribbit!
Ochaco! We lost control!
I won't give up!
Because Deku would
never give up!
Midoriya and the
others will fight to the end.
So we won't stop!
It's my duty, as a hero.
That's right.
Heroes always
see things through!
And we use our
abilities for good!
Hm?
What? Has he gotten stronger?
Perhaps.
But something else
is different as well.
His resistance is decreasing!
Yes!
There must be a cap on what his
reflecting Quirk can take!
Good.
Simple, then.
I'll surpass that limit!
No, this can't be happening.
Have I reached my boundaries?
I didn't know such a thing
was even possible!
Because you gave up.
If you didn't lose hope...
If you kept trying...
You might have been able
to get along with people.
But instead, you decided
that powers are disease.
And chose to
wallow in self-pity.
You're a failure because
you stopped trying!
Be silent.
A hero knows what it means
to keep fighting until the end.
Shut your mouth.
That's why we always remind
ourselves what we have to do.
You filth.
Go beyond! Plus Ultra!
Shut up!
Detroit Smash!
A real hero
will always find a way
for justice to be served!
I know, All Might.
Young Midoriya!
A hero has so much
to protect in this world.
Which is why...
...I will defeat you!
United States of World Smash!
You're... too late.
The countdown is over. But...
There's no explosion.
The bomb's not detonating.
Did they disarm the bombs?
Yeah. That's a relief.
Well done. I'm so proud.
Thank you, Rody.
You hang in there, okay?
I'll get you to a hospital soon.
Deku. I did it, right?
I protected my family?
Just like my dad did.
And I stopped the bombs?
Yeah.
I didn't give up.
I saw it through
just like you would.
You did great.
You're amazing, Rody.
That's true. I am pretty cool.
The terrorist
attacks that shook the world
were successfully prevented
through the efforts
of multiple hero teams
working in tandem.
The members of Humarise,
the group behind the threat,
are being taken into custody.
Some from unexpected places.
The case was resolved
without a single new
Trigger Bomb exploding.
In the end, the heroes
protected this world.
But, it wasn't just
the pros and students.
The one who really
saved everybody...
The one who gave
his all, was him.
Rody!
...Ha, ha!
Didn't think you'd
be out so soon! Heh.
Ah, they said I was
good to head back home.
Well, I'm glad to hear it.
Although, if I had
died stopping those bombs,
I would've become
a total legend.
That's a morbid thing to say!
...Hah!
So, hey.
Come up with any big
plans for the future?
Just going back to
my normal life for now.
Though, I suppose,
with all I've been through,
who knows what's
in store for me?
Right.
We will now begin boarding
for flight NNY224.
I gotta run and catch my flight.
Do me a solid
and stick to Japan, 'kay?
Nothing good happens
when you're around.
Probably best for everyone
if you stay in your lane.
I'll come back
and visit for sure.
Yeah, like I care.
Got a job for me, old man?
Like a real gig.
Somethin' that's
more respectable.
One of my employees
did quit on me.
Guess you can help.
That is one possibility.
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today