Someone needs to stop Clearway Law.
Public shouldn't leave reviews for lawyers.
I must take the
stone to Paladin.
I want to stop until
I reach the monastery
The Paladin will
send to you that silver
my path is sure
I have no fear.
And the goddess says
you are to stay here for time being
Trust the goddess always.
- For adventure.
- To riches and gold.
This you're, Marek. And that nice
piece of magic in the Ogre cave.
- Gojun will be upset
- Sure he is get you?
friend.
Trust the goddess.
Something is no right.
The stone. He took the stone.
And I saw her for the Darkspore.
Be well my sister.
The Warrior Thane, I have
seen how you look at him.
Make your choices with a clear heart
and trust the goddess always.
He has had enough.
- Marek, enjoy your fun
- Teela has gone because of you.
- He is drinking full
- That is enough
Get off of me, you cripple punk.
Leave me alone.
Leave me.
- He is drinking full
- Go away.
Marek, no...
More
Hello dagen.
Necromancer your darkness is real thing.
- It draws you to me.
- Marek.
I've been waiting so hard time
Let me free from your pain
I can make you whore forever
Marek, I know you.
Arise.
Gojun.
Come with me.
you appear into the darkness
And he is appears back.
I am so foolish.
The forces drove us together...
... but we did not see it.
I'm not looking for one
so young or woman.
- I'm sorry.
- What do you see about , Gojun?
- You're a necromancer
- Necromancer ?
You so advance the barrier in a long time.
He searched and I wondered
With an agree warrior search in a certain
period into a sleep with my own
He has found you.
I had a dream, a figure.
He knew me.
Szorlok.
He is the darkest
as necromancers...
... 80 years ago he's trying on me
by Deira door star.
Over the Darkspore
Synthesize Century
Over the darkspore
You hold the Darkspore.
Synthesize Century
All you show when
I unify the heart of the Lich King.
Now you will fulfill the true
purpose of this ceremony
Lich king, for a thousand years
your power will rival the gods.
Szorlok, In the names of all the gods,
I command you to stop.
No.
Take the Darkspore,
we will hold him.
Gojun the betrayer.
The black heart beats again.
Darkspore is mine.
Parts in the wind.
For the four corners of the land
No trace of the passing
Man has not known a power,
that he does not crave.
Those are bounded by
the darkness do anything...
to keep their power.
The darkspore and they
all stand against Szorlok.
If the shards put together,
there is no way to stop him
they have the power
even beyond death.
What these have to do with me?
You are necromancer
your darkness is something he seeks.
Well, I won't be controled.
Yes, perhaps
But the lure of power draws in
the wisest men to their doom.
Szorlok was much like you once.
- I'm not like him. I am not evil.
you borrowed life for selfish gain
Is that not evil?
I'm not evil.
Evil runs in the blood of all men
You're untested and one day
You'll be forced to choose
You have the potential Marek.
For well good and for well evil.
But you need to learn to control your
power,or the choice will be made for you.
How can I control something
I don't understand?
I'm alone in this.
I will teach you.
But you must be wary.Marek
When you delve into the void,
there is others who can sense you.
Thus why Szorlok empoison your
dreams and Kishkumen is able to find you.
The man with the yellow eyes?
- I took Kishkumen to Caeryn.
- The darkness has come.
And the world has need of heroes.
For now you must stay here.
I will return in a few days.
Łapeta, well fetch me
something to write with.
A message from your friend. The Elf.
Kill Marek and come to my room.
Put those over there.
No, no. This one goes there.
And that one goes there. Right?
Hello, Marek.
I found you.
Dagen's looking for you.
Come on.
- I'm going to bed.
- Patience stay there
It takes some time to rebuild
the brush is broken
Right, of course.
Just a little attention here.
Yes, and it should open right up
- What is it?
- I am not sure.
But Kishkumen has one just like it
- Dagen, we're in trouble.
- Why?
Give me some ink.
Is it a cypher?
-or of a code maybe?
No, it's a map.
Mondiatha.
- What is Mondiatha?
- An ancient city of giants.
It's destroyed now, but it's only
It is the biggest treasure ever happening.
The Darkspore in Mondiatha.We have
to get there before Kishkumen does.
- The Darkspore.
Am I missing something?
It seeps city and heart of the Lich King.
Broken into four pieces.
Caeryn took the first piece from the
temple.And for Kishkumen was after.
- the second piece is in Mondiatha.
- What is it worth?
If it forced, an army can
become invincible
The limits of this power is
death and destruction.
I see why he is interested.
With any luck this
map shows the entrance.
Whatever it is,
we know where it is will be.
- We shall avenge the Caeryn death.
- I promised Gojun by to stay
Hello blue heart; If you see it is
where the risk of developments
Kishkumen has half a day on, Marek.
We owe this to Teela.
We owe this to Teela?
Last I checked Teela's
goddess owes us.
However
A hidden treasure of legendary
proportions, unguarded ...
and to have taken it I could be worry
I am free; but we all could be rich.
- Fight the treasure.
- Fight the treasure?
I don't have to share this with you, Ok!
It could very easily,
I have just taken this and...
Marek, you can get you
face of those posters
Then and Then
... You could save the world.
We leave today.
With Teela? Good luck with that.
She isn't speaking to anyone for 14 days.
But an assess, mourning rite.
- I'll find her
- Send this one
He need the work out, some of his anger
You and I can get my silver's
worth in the bed.
Paid before to noon.
What time is it?
Noon.
Tell Teela we are not with her
Eat fruit.
Noon?
your slave girl with the deformed foot
I like to purchase her from you
She ran
I put a bounty on her head.
yes the bounty is too high
Yes. Bounties are high.
She's worth what? 500?
600 on the open market?
what a pimp like you wants
for the trip of the girl anyway
let's just say she's left
an impression on me
Make an offer?
yeah 200 gold in your
pocket right now
And you let my girls, my
purse to track her down.
I will be grateful to be rid of
that conniving bitch
Okay. Leave.
Leave
I want her back alive and unharmed
Teela, Teela I know you are
still mourning, but ...
Teela, Kishkumen murdered Caeryn ...
Because he's going to unite the Darkspore
I need to stop him
Come with me.
Who are you, Marek?
Why do you seek
such dark magic?
You used the same dark power
which killed my sister.
- It is a power that I do not understand.
- Or control
You were marked
by evil for all to see.
Your foot is twisted
and cannot be healed
you seek danger
surrounded by evil
You say you wish to be good.
You have no power over
the darkness inside you.It calls you.
And in time it will claim you.
It is your fate.
- Sorry about Caeryn.
- I'll come with you.
And I will  report  you and I will deliver
the Darkspore to Paladin.
He will know how best hide it.
Declare yourself.
Beware of attack.
Go to Mineas and give them report it
Make haste.
Hold them off.
Teela I will tell you about
those  ten giants friendly loyal.
- Yes, several times. Yeah.
- Marek hasn't heard, have you?
- where you broke the Dragon?
- Ha, yes.
What's that sound?
It's elvish.
No, doesn't sound like
any elvish that I ever heard.
Someone' s in trouble.
Let's go have a look
- Get off me.
- Get off.
- Serious
- Nasty look figure.
- cock or cock Indian
- cock Indian
- We do not know who he is.
- Teela, we can find in this moment please
- Dagen and Thane,  with me?
- Now you're on your own on this one sweetheart.
All right here we go
Let's go on this pass
Go and fight; shit.
- Dagen.
- Dagen,  come here.
- Come now with me.
- Dagen, do you  petrified there?
If I get eaten by a pixie, just tell
Tell them it is a dragon or something.
Dagen.
What do you want from us, fairy ugly?
Come on, it won't be less
it won't  be long.
Let's get him out of
here before they wake up.
Have you seen a man with
yellow  eyes stark off?
- I'm o the Garun-Dan.
- Fuck you all.
What would you know, half-breed?
Dagen.
The Garun-Dan were destroyed
and didn't mark their faces...
... like savages from the north.
You're not Garun-Dan.
Are we standing
in rocks all day?
- We're turning to the road of Mondiatha.
- Don't fucking tell him the mission.
Make caution with yellow eyes
who commands a horde of Orks.
- What did I say?
- His name Kishkumen. Do you know him?
don't be stupid, so no need to ask your question.
He did not even answer that,
I am close to the gods
I must warn this world into life
Before the tests
replaces with them
How long have you wandered?
- Ten migrations of the Elch.
- Alone?
- Thane.
- Don't lie to us, long-ears .
- I speak the truth.
There is no honour in lying.
You saved my life.
I owe you a life of that.
I'm bound to you until
that debt is repaid.
Just one every girl once
He is lying by the way.
He's Dreucki they lay
Probably planning on slitting
our throats tonight ...
And painting pictures
of it all over his face.
You believe him?
I am telling you he is pure evil.
Good and evil are cross
every living being
Of course not.
what tribe
- Are you sure about this?
- We can use him
- What's your name?
- Qole.
Qole, You do not owe me anything
I've been a slave and I will
not accept to enslave anyone
But you're more than welcome to join us.
Free
ِAll right, but give him a shirt.
The Dark elf dies a bloody, bloody death
Right there in the middle,
that is where my pile of gold is.
Our pile of gold.
Something new?
- Shell of the cockatrice.
When use the right spell
you can turn flesh to stone.
I know a woman from Valencia
has the same power.
Right.
vary with us some on else barrier
Right. What do you suppose this is?
- It has a heeling potion
- I'm not asking you Qole
- I was hoping to offer it to you.
- From which you get that.
In Ogre cave.
Probably it is part from a temple
I might go and see where find Teela
If you excuse me.
Very well,
Right. Harm a hair on her
head and I will find you.Dreucki
The crow's plucked out
his bonny, bonny eyes.
Why you stare me that way?
It pleases me.
An amulet, the legend of my people.
The sun follows the moon
until she slows
He lies next to her in the sky.
Before they part .
He draws the stars from her
and cast them into the night .
Telling everyone of their love.
It means a lot to you.
It was a gift from a woman.
Oh.
My people no more slotted
I'm the last one
So are your faces marked?
In remembrance?
I was raised by a shaman.
So are your faces marked?
In remembrance?
Goodnight, Marek.
Thank you for keeping watch.
- This daily bathing is unsafe.
The goddess demands it.
- Keep talking.
- About what?
- Tell me of your childhood.
- There's nothing to tell there.
Please.
My father was a soldier.
I think I'd seen him twice in my life
before we got word he'd been killed.
We were put on the street.
I joined the army that
marched across the world
Ended up here,
long way from Mineas.
Are you from Mineas?
-  Is this capital very grand?
- I wouldn't say that.
Filth and shit, beggars.
However, there is a grand buildings, alright.
people grinding up against you ,
and they piss in the street
- Then how you imagine it?
- More beautiful
In fact  The Sun Goes Down
The city starts to glow
You can hear the music.
You hear people laugh and sing.
And love.
Thane.
Sorry.
- I am sorry, I am sorry.
It is so hard to find a woman
in privacy in this woods.
Put your sword away
You do not need it tonight.
Help!
Dagen wake up, come on.
Qole, my sword.
Can someone hand me my sword?
Oh ,oh. Good shot.
She's come with us.
The rest of you are free to leave
- You have to kill us first.
- Hey ; Hang on..
Oh .Gods. They are magnificent.
And she's good at the rope.
- Any of you bastards try to follow us.
I cut your throat and spine.
You understand?
Aphrodisiac.
- Damn
- Marek.
Marek. Marek.
Who are you and what
do you want with me?
Our new master wants to meet you
And with the trouble you've been,
I intend to collect in full.
Tuen and Samos scintilla's.
There're men in the woods
Not Deirans and they have horses.
Tuen and Samos scintilla's.
- I told you? Not Deirans.
- Why are Orks marching with men?
Hey, over here.
We will find you.
Marek.
You freed youselves?
Only thieves who can
break away from the rope.
Qole frees us using Teela dagger.
Where are the bounty hunters?
They fought with troops Kishkumens.
They headed north,
Mondiatha purposes.
You recognize them only
by the eyes or their mole.
We must move quickly to catch them.
It's  two-day march.
We've got six hours to find it.
No , No It's not enough time to find
treasure buried in a city.
- Now inform me
- Orks track the Darkspore.
There is another way,
through  the mountains.
- Passing Donkerbos.
- How far is it?
In 12 hours we reach the place.
Passing at night,
residence swamp creatures.
- Do I need ask?
- No.
The stories to scare children.
If we meet about Kishkumen
and his whore in a straight bottom
We lose.
Aniset will there
the pass is sure.
Now  we can take the chances
going into the long way road
All right. Who is in
favor of the shortest?
It was your idea.
Yes, but it's not a good idea.
I will go although
I did not raise my hand for.
This is a terrible,terrible idea.
This is more frightening than
story frightened children?
What it is frightening
We're being watched.
More than watched.
We're being followed.
- Aniset, hear my prayer.
- It's too late to call Aniset.
No.
I go and do what you want
You're mine.
Marek, release.
Release.
Teela, he needs your help.
I cannot do anything...
I could not feel my fingers anymore.
- Who knows what it does mean
- Who?
Kishkumen.
How ?
It's your doings. Now I do not
can shoot with my bow. It's your fault
Tell the truth to them, Marek.
He sensed me.
When you used the magic...
He can feel my presence
because he is a necromancer.
- So just like in the Ogre cave...
- I suck life force.
- Why did not you tell us.
- I could control it.
- Tell them the truth.
- I can control
I would use it again.
Then heal him.
your dark magic is too strong.
I should not join you.
I saved your life.
And take my hand has many benefits.
Remember that it's something
that you cannot control.
I saved your life.
Maybe you saved
to suck life.
- Hold, hold.
- Dagen. Dagen.
Dagen. Hold.
Hey...
Fuck you  Dreucki.
would like dark evil and damaged
Enough.
We do not have time for this.
We have to move.
Hey.
Come, Teela, we have to move.
- We need to rest.
- No time.
You saved them.
I will kill them.
They hate me.
They are afraid of you.
Some could feel the dark side...
because they are afraid
of being close to you today
What should I do?
Or we will die?
There's always another way.
Marek.
There is no destiny can be fixed.
The gods will help
You're strong.
You've been chosen.
This was once a great city.
They thought they could
lure their gods from heaven. by treasure
Instead earthquakes to dust
and he buried them all.
Their mistakes are stockpiled wealth...
And the treasure will spending then
The entrance is on side around this place
We proceed.
- Just like that?
- Maybe this entrance.
- Maybe only rock and sand.
- It look Sathuan.
I read a lot about it  when I was child
It Zwerfpad stone.
The others are in the four elements
of the worship in Mondiatha
This mark is on the map,
but there is no spell to open it.
He was so strong.
That symbol of the archway
there is also on the map.
But such symbols,
I can not recognize it
It's five points and five stones.
Marek, I need
to speak with you.
We are very close to the end Teela
We'll talk on the way home
after we have the stone.
- I need to say now.
- Then say .
you said  a hundred of that already
and said it repeatedly.
What?
- You blame me for Caeryn's death .
- That what I ask you to say
-And it's the truth.
- And you're right.
I am necromancer
and I could not control it.
When Darkspore being there and...
I touched it,
Kishkumen will see
Something in me pulled me into
and strength increases every day.
I'm not sure I can resist.
- We have come in this way .
- I did not go with you.
You must keep you away from me.
The Darkspore
can destroy us all
You know, I say this feel the priests.
What you see have the trace that
we can not imagine it  in other way.
Sorry buddy.
Stop.
- Qole, I need your help.
Well, It is that simple?
Qole.
- Qole.
- Let me go.
It's simple
It is simple
She started
She finally  lost her mind.
- Portal is open.
You will see anyway  necromancer.
He sense you here.
Well done, Marek.
Always stepping in front or behind,
never far from each other
My master have seen you in the dark
Marek the slave girl.
But you do not know
who you are, Do you?
Szorlok have a great purposes for you.
Drop your weapons.
In time he will show you
who he really is and you becoming.
Now you will save me from
the troubles to collect the stone
We will  not serve you  Szorlok.
Yes you will serve.
Whether the live or the death
Just like your sister's death.
Necromancer, you will  go retrieve
the stone and deliver it to me
-... or your friend will die.
- Do not, Marek.
There is no love for your
sister I see. Very well.
- I'll go.
- But Marek...
- I have no choice.
- Then we all go together.
Marek, you will be lost.
And show the dark will rise...
- No, no.
- Marek.
The poison united with her blood
with a sense terrible pain as a result.
Until  it reaches her heart
But I will heal
if you return the stone.
You have about two hours.
So.I suggest you make your decision quickly
We have to go now.
We will go.
Let's go.
Come on, dagen.
I will tie to you all
Marek, you'll be lost.
- black is pitch
- Briefly.
Tempus Alorus luminescent.
That way.
And the good fairy find
Sacs and sacs full of gold.
Silent, Dagen.
There is a door over head.
With a lot of gold in
behind it, I hope.
- What's that sound?
- Mouse.
let's go
Are you sure it was a rat?
The sound is amplified through the tunnel.
Do not worry, Dagen.
His voice was strong as many others.
Get away from me.
It's not a rat.
This is a dog monster.
You have a chance ; You know.
Once revoke straight sword lying here.
And this is only by
a rogue priest notice.
If I kill you,
I do with pleasure.
Kill me?
What you talking about?
Let's keep moving
Ogre, rats ,
hordes of orks.
Why is it always so complicated?
Hello?
He was still alive,
but he was not breathing.
- He's sleeping.
- Sleeping? What do you mean sleep?
Place is cursed.
You cannot trust your senses here.
We have to keep moving.
Mind should be clear
and just think our task.
ًWe can tie ourselves together.
If a person is asleep,
the other must be pulled.
I do not want to bind myself to anyone.
Silence.
This is the first intersection.
The door is this way
Good knot.
It is a magic wand, huh?
I know someone
needs it more than you.
I do not understand.
It is not in the map.
Oh, giants
They must have fled here
when the place is buried.
Place is cold, isolated place to die
.
Do you think they know it
will destroy their world?
Maybe they think , they can stop it.
He did not love you.
-Let's we report.
- Everyone is dead.
- Who's there?
- We must withdraw.
No one is here
They All are dead.
Tell me your name!
Come on, keep on the road.
Come on.
There should be a door here.
This is the end.
I can feel,
we are close.
I could feel the stone Darkspore.
This is one,
There must be more.
Hello, sunshine.
Treasure Mondiatha.
Why stir treasure?
This is really deceptive.
Oh, shit.
Dagen, we have no
time for their wealth
Run.
- Maybe he's not real.
- No, he was real.
This way.
Through this way.
We have to back ,
we have to find the stone
Finding the stone, we will die
Hold this.
I smell fresh air.
Help me up
Hurry up, Dagen.
This way.
Looks just like essay to escape
from the mother's womb
Run.
Dagen, I fight him quikly
Hurry up he is behind us,
dragon is also looking for me.
I think Darkspore keep the dragon alive.
- Perhaps this can help us?
- Schasaat.
- Save it for the dragon.
- What is that?
If this is successful.
We can distract him...
I would shoot him with this stick.
Go all surround him
Or you flick it safe
when would you talk
- It's a good plan, Marek.
- Without darkspore he will killed
Run, coward.
It is that a dragon or my sword.
You'll be a fucking hero,
Qole while doing all this.
Spread or all will die.
Hey, come get me.
If you can, ugly.
Schasaat.
Marek.
Dagen.
Qole.
Hey.
Come and get me.
- He came.
- Be careful, Marek.
Miamortile odillus rittik.
Bring Darkspore me.
Obey me.
You're still alive.
Fuck me ; Be careful next time.
you welcome
I'm good without
the kisses, thank you.
Take the Darkspore.
Run and do not look back.
Another way as Gojun pass
ِAll the treasures left behind there...
This is the one piece left
take it put it into the sun
- Just one more shot.
- To save Teela.
Nothing like selfless.
And there is no end for you.
Darkness will take this time.
The only absolute powers
in this world is death.
Goddess of light, hear my prayer.
Fill me with your presence and
Let me die, please.
You will surely die, but not
without friends as witnesses.
You have touched it. I can tell.
Its power lingers with you still.
Where is off?
He was buried with sand.
Your honor our agreement and heal her
You would trade what matters
most for what matters least.
It is too important to sacrifice.
Or cover your lies.
- Where Darkspore?
- We have never found it.
- Stop it, stop it.
- That is enough.
I date you to pay Shoman,
Release me from my badge
You've served me well, my child
You're free now.
You are fucking bastard, already
I told you.
Do not trust him.
They have already done so.
Let them free.
Where is our money?
- No.
- You gave your word
No.
Marek, I know you.
What should I do?
We will die.
There's always another way.
Schasaat.
Kill them.
You cannot escape.
I will be back.
I'm sorry, Marek.
Remember ; what  I said to you
The fate is not waiting
- What happened?
- Raw time that what happened
You can fix and save bodies?
I can save everyone obeys
- He escaped with the Darkspore.
- We failed.
You're not wrong to believe and hope.
your suffering is nothing
If we are not fighting this darkness,...
we will be part of it
Caeryn said so.
And you do not stop
against darkness, Marek.
I was wrong.
There is goodness in you.
And you're so strong.
And your struggle has just begun.
where we go ?
Aniset instead of Caeryn
would I save this party
And I need you Marek
I'll follow up
goddess told me the other way.
I'm sorry that I was
not able to heal farther
I am  grateful of this
nice on watch
When i am there at the gate of Mondiatha .
I wish tope death.
But I'm hold into alive...
Because I want  to see you alive once more
Do you know what I want to do next ?
We get the biggest tank of ale.
The time has come to spend a week on my back
How are you going to pay for that?
Scaly Panthers
has a toothy grain
One hundred of gold a piece .
was it go?
And it is yours.
Six hundred gold.
I'm here to purchase my freedom
Very well show me your mark
- Do I know you?
- I doubt for.
holds
This girl has runaway
she's my property
you buster
Dagen, dagen.
Her life is for my taken
My get
He is lying
600 Gold is in danger some
in this bag 600 Gold
Give me the contract with my freedom
600 pieces of gold in the given
by a runaway slave?
Majesty , please.
This girl is my property
I believe gold is mine.
Fine
Please this is no right
He is your master under the law
I think he is all right.
Ah No, Is not that
Marek, I will come for you.
Oh, if you of course have a lot
of time for me my dear
But I'm in the light  finding
the ways to make it up to me
Get out
My friends would come to me.
Silence. These people want to sleep.
Listen very carefully you worthless piece of shit
You're going to sign on the freedom
contract of  Marek
Or I'll cut your head off
Do it myself
What? What did he say?
- Say that again.
- What?
I think he's right.
Sign you back here.
Beautiful.
Here we are you paid for it
Nice and we go
wow. wow, we do not really must pay to him
If you ever follow her
again, we will be back
But this time we'll break your bones.
You would not be survive.
Understand?
Hey Hello,
little marmot.
They are waiting for us.
- It is good  to see you.
- You too.
- Ready for another adventure?
- What now?
Maybe we should do
something in a warmer place.
Someone needs to stop Clearway Law.
Public shouldn't leave reviews for lawyers.