Someone needs to stop Clearway Law.
Public shouldn't leave reviews for lawyers.
ANNOUNCER: We're halfway through
round one of our second preliminary battle
here in Beaumont Fight Night!
Hometown boy Ronnie Shelton is getting
a little more than he bargained for
from this journeyman fighter who seems to
have the former champion's number tonight.
(CROWD CHEERING)
(YELLS)
(CHEERING CONTINUES)
(BELL DINGING)
ANNOUNCER: Oh! And Shelton
is down again for the second time.
TRAINER: Looking good, Case.
Why are we going for a decision again?
If you keep stomping everybody,
no one is gonna want to fight us. Come on.
- Two more rounds.
- (BELL RINGING)
Come on, come on, come on.
Give me two more rounds.
...Beaumont Rough Riders in round two!
(CROWD CHEERING)
(MAN GROANING)
Winner by tap out, Case Walker!
(CHEERING CONTINUES)
Hey, you got great kicks.
You need to set 'em up
with your punches, okay?
You hang in there.
- (ANNOUNCER TALKING INDISTINCTLY)
- (MUSIC PLAYING)
How do you expect me to do my job
when you won't play ball?
Exactly. You play ball,
you don't play fight.
Look, you want to do things
only your way, fine.
I'm out. I'm out, man.
I can't do it no more.
...number one car dealership,
Buck Taylor Auto Show.
Located at 17th and Oak Street.
Next on the undercard
at Beaumont Fight Night,
in the welterweight division
fighting out of California
with a record of six and two, Tony Richards.
Flip that just like a gymnast
Hit him up, right upper-cut, left hand jab
Freshest, fl yest
Please don't test this
Lethal weapon
Bigger than Mel Gibson's
They got you carrying buckets now, Case?
Brody?
Oh, no, man, I was just, uh...
I was fucking with you.
I saw your fight on the monitor in the back.
You looked good out there.
Man, Brody James, man, how you doin'?
BRODY: Come here.
It's good to see you.
Man, you, too. How you been?
I've got four Minotaur
and Strikeforce belts
and all the money a kid
outta the trailer park could ever need.
That's all good for your fan club,
but how are you?
Oh, man, I'm all good.
Still happily married,
and you should see the size of the kids now.
Man, that's great.
Wait a minute, what are you doing
in Beaumont, Texas?
I was gonna ask you the same thing.
It's good to see you in the ring,
but it's kind of hard to see you slummin'.
I've seen what you can do.
What's the story, Case?
Maybe another time.
Better get your man in the ring
before he cools off.
Ain't no time like the present.
Come to the after-party, ask for my table.
We're gonna catch up.
See you there.
(CROWD CHEERING)
(ROCK MUSIC PLAYING)
I was born
On the seventh day alone
Rampage Jackson,
how come you ain't called?
Said you can run, you can run
But you won't find
Because I was born the seventh son
Whoa...
Whoa
I'm the seventh born son
Whoa...
Nothing quite like it, right?
Excuse me?
Pure, unadulterated fame.
More addictive than heroin.
I wouldn't know.
Case.
My man.
Hey, bro.
- I'm glad you decided to swing by tonight.
- Oh.
It's going to be a great night.
I see you've met the lovely Myca Cruz.
Come here, sexy.
Now, I ask you, who's got a sexier publicist
than Brody James?
Mmm. Down, tiger.
I do corporate marketing
and publicity for PFC.
Brody. Hey, Brody, man, chill, man.
MYCA: Excuse me.
Me and Myca, we're just playing.
CASE: Yeah, I know.
'Cause you're the happily married guy
with two kids, right?
Oh, right. What you drinkin'?
Come on, let's catch up.
Cheers me, man, come on.
(GLASSES CLINKING)
You know, not many people know this yet,
but I just signed with Primortal Combat.
PFC? Seriously?
Taking it to the next level, man.
(SCOFFS) Yeah, next level down maybe.
Primortal pays way better than anyplace else
out there, Case, look, I'm tellin' ya.
They're the fastest growing group around.
'Cause they're a freak show.
A bunch of 'roided up fighters
with damn near no rules.
Getting $2 million for my next fight.
Guaranteed.
Wow. Seriously? When?
Six weeks from now, Thailand.
Brody James vs. Caesar Braga
for the vacant PFC title.
Man, what the fuck are you doing?
Relax, come on, man.
No, no, no.
You're fighting "Psycho" Caesar Braga?
Come on, man,
$2 million is not gonna buy you
a new brain if you're in no shape
to defend yourself.
Come on, man.
You know, I need someone like you.
Somebody to keep me honest.
Hey, why don't you come out
and train with me sometime?
Uh, no, no, Brody. I'm good.
Well, if you're so good, what are you doing
fighting for scraps in Beaumont then, huh?
This is the place where you begin a career,
not where you end it.
Catch you later.
Looks like he could use some help.
He sure can.
I meant with the ladies.
Is that what you call them?
Huh. Leaving so soon?
Yeah, this is not my thing.
Really?
What is your thing?
Not this.
You know, you have this ninja-like way
of just popping up out of nowhere.
- Miss... What's your name again?
- (CHUCKLES)
- Myca.
Spelled M-Y-C-A.
Well, nice to meet you, Myca,
spelled M-Y-C-A.
Am I wrong for having
that Village People song in my head?
You know...
Okay, Okay.
You know, I could have sworn
you said you were leaving.
- Good night.
Getting there, babe, make it look good.
We're on our way.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
What the fuck?
MAN: That's my fuckin' wife!
BRODY: Fuck you, man!
Fuck it, let's go, motherfucker!
Come on! You want a...
No, no, no, Brody, Brody.
- It's a setup, it's a setup!
- BRODY: You're dead meat, Porky Pig!
- (GROANING)
- (CROWD EXCLAIMS)
- BRODY: How does that taste?
- (MAN WHEEZING)
- (PEOPLE EXCLAIMING)
- (MAN COUGHS)
Sue me.
(INDISTINCT MURMURS)
BRODY: Bitch set me up.
(MAN COUGHS)
One punch, are you kidding me?
(DRAPES SLIDING)
BRODY: You gotta come with me, Case.
Hey.
I'm serious about it.
Oh. Somebody seriously needs
a breath mint.
I want you to come over there.
Help me train for this fight,
help me get ready for this thing.
What, in Thailand?
It's paradise, man, you'll love it.
(SIGHS)
I don't know, the stuff you got
going on in your life, man,
that's not for me.
Okay.
Well, what is it that you want then?
Why'd you walk away from the game?
Um...
Man, my head was really messed up
after I lost both my parents.
I went on a bad spiral.
I guess I just didn't want it anymore.
Time's running out, Case.
Every day you're scuttling around here
in the boonies
is another day that you're not on top.
There'll be people over there
that could make a difference in your life.
I'll pay you to train with me.
Maybe even be a spot on the undercard
if somebody drops out.
You fighting for Hugo Vega?
Man, I don't know about that.
I'm not asking you
to compromise on anything.
I'm just tellin' you
to put yourself into play.
- By helping you.
- No.
You're helping me because
I'm supposed to be your friend, remember?
You'll be helping yourself.
Look, you gotta show people your skills.
Mmm-hmm. I looked pretty good last night.
In Beaumont.
BRITTANY: I just don't understand
why you have to leave so soon.
You just got home.
If I play my cards right
over the next few years,
we're not going to have to worry
about money ever again.
It's not money that I worry about, Brody.
I mean, Thailand of all places?
(GRUNTS)
What's up, tough guys?
- You take care of Mom while I'm gone?
- Yes.
- Can you handle that? Come here.
- Yeah.
I'll miss you.
Come here.
One more, one more.
(WOMAN TALKING INDISTINCTLY ON PA)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
(WOMAN SPEAKING THAI)
"Paradise."
(REPORTERS CHEERING)
(CLEARS THROAT) Thank you!
Good morning. Welcome to the...
Primortal Fighting Championship
welcomes you.
The PFC would like to announce
and is pleased and proud to announce
to our world and our fans,
a title fight between these two
gigantic titans of MMA.
The many times decorated,
three-time world champion, Brody James,
and the undefeated force of nature,
"Psycho" Caesar Braga.
- (CHUCKLES)
- Let's hear it for them, folks.
(APPLAUSE)
We're going to be right here
in Bangkok to ensure
that this will be a fight for the ages.
Let me tell you,
it's going to be a hell of a fight!
(APPLAUSE)
Yes, sir. Yes, sir.
Hi, good morning.
Uh, Joe Kanarot from Now On.
I have just two questions.
The first is,
does the PFC still stand by its policy
of drug tolerance
with absolutely zero drug testing
required by your league?
I'm glad you asked me that
because I feel like it's high time
for all of organized sports
to recognize the inevitable,
and fling open the doors
to unfettered competition.
If there are no regulations,
except those governed
by the laws of common sense,
then there's no cheats.
It's a level playing field.
This is what the fans want
and this is what my organization
plans to give them, thank you.
Even if this means a clear
and present danger to your fighters?
(CHUCKLES) Well, you know what,
I invite you to take a good look
at these two fine specimens
and tell me if either of them look like
they're in any sort of medical duress to you.
Uh, my next question
- is for you, Mr. Caesar.
- Hmm.
Can you give us an update
on the assault and battery charges filed
on behalf of your ex-wife?
(REPORTERS MURMURING)
You want to ask the question again?
Sure.
Can you give us an update
on the assault and battery charges
filed on behalf of your ex-wife?
- (HUFFS)
- Wait, wait, wait!
Argh!
(CURSING IN PORTUGUESE)
As you can see, folks,
it's gonna be a hell of a fight.
(SCATTERED CLAPPING)
(CAESAR CURSING IN PORTUGUESE)
(YELLING)
Not right now.
(REPORTERS CLAMORING)
(GROWLING)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
(SPEAKING THAI)
Okay, that's good,
that's good, Jazzo, yeah.
Yeah, good, good, good.
Okay.
Looking for somebody?
Yeah, yeah. Brody James.
All this come with him?
That's right. 7:00 a.m. to 3:00 p.m.
Fighters only.
We're not open to the public.
Sorry.
T-shirt's some sort of punishment?
Who the hell are you?
I'm the guy Brody asked
to fly halfway around the world
to help him train for this fight.
- Funny, I thought that was my job.
- Hmm.
After you're done with your phone call,
maybe you can tell me where I could set up.
I'll be back after I do some shopping.
(HIP-HOP MUSIC PLAYING)
I've been having this vision
Uh, I've been having this vision
Breaking out of these walls
Bustin' out of this prison
Either rise or you fall
I'm on a mission
Bringing my dreams to fruition
I ain't playing at all
Bring out the bodybags
I'm about to kill them
Deliver them to the mortician
I got to do what I've got to do
That's what I'm facing, back in my phase
I pray to God, He doesn't care
I'mma do me, I'mma do me
That's in my blood
I'll never change
This is a toast to the underdogs
Now we doing it our way
I got to do what I've got to do
That's what I'm facing, back in my phase
I pray to God, He doesn't care
I'mma do me, I'mma do me
That's in my blood
I'll never change
This is a toast to the underdogs
Now we doing it our way
Light 'em up, light 'em up
Light 'em up, fight 'em up, fight 'em up
I got to do what I've got to do
That's what I'm facing, back in my phase
I pray to God, He doesn't care
I'mma do me, I'mma do me
That's in my blood
I'll never change
What the hell is this Bruce Lee shit?
(ALL LAUGHING)
(IN FAKE CHINESE ACCENT)
"Boards don't hit back."
(ALL SNICKERING)
Man, forget this clown.
(CROWD CHEERING ON VIDEO)
Are you okay?
- Yeah, fine.
- (LAPTOP CLICKS)
- (GRUNTS)
- Okay, stick and move, stick and move!
Don't go after this guy! Step...
Take a step back!
Don't... Whoa!
- Step back!
- (GRUNTING)
Don't... What are you doing?
Don't move up!
(GRUNTS)
You gotta go easier, Cobra!
At this rate, nobody wants to spar with you
and you got three more rounds!
What about him?
No.
Hey, I said no.
What the fuck?
What's up, Mr. Miyagi?
Practicing your wax-on, wax-off?
What do you even call that?
Tae Bro?
You know, it's rude to ignore people.
Didn't your mama teach you better?
BRODY: So, who ordered pizza?
(ALL EXCLAIMING)
Now, it ain't New York pizza,
but it ain't LA neither,
so I don't want to hear
too many complaints.
Hey.
You guys working hard. Hey, Taj.
I would say, "Looking good,"
but we know that is a lie.
Some of you guys are ugly as hell.
- What's up, Brody?
- Hey, Coach.
- Good to see you.
- Taking care of business, as always.
Case Walker in the house.
Hell yeah, man.
Good to see ya.
Man, welcome to the Land of Smiles.
I see you already made yourself at home.
Yeah, yeah, getting there.
I checked in and somehow
I don't think we're in the same hotel.
Yeah, look, mine was already all booked up.
Since you're a late addition,
you're on my dime.
Man, I'm sorry. Nothin' personal.
I'd do you better if I could.
Got to meet all the guys, right?
Yeah, everybody's real friendly.
Hey, Brody, you know Blacky Chan here?
Shut the fuck up.
He's here for me.
You got a problem with that?
You bringin' this guy in here
to help you train, champ?
Sure. Why not?
I'm going up against that monster Braga,
I could use all the help I could get.
You're gonna dismantle
that bitch-ass Brazilian, Brody.
Bang!
Smartest thing you ever said, you know?
Hey, Brody.
Oh, come on.
I'm going to be working it right off.
Ah, I hate that look. Fine.
My man, Case, always keeping me honest.
Thought that was my job.
All right, so I go get changed,
do some road work.
What do you want me to do?
I say we do a hard 10k.
We only got five-and-a-half weeks
till you fight Braga,
and we got a lot of ground to make up.
What do you think, Case?
Well, I would say do a moderate 5K.
No sense in being too sore
to train tomorrow, right?
Looks like it's settled.
I'll go get changed.
Yo, Matty, what about sparring partners?
I still got three more rounds.
You got plenty of people to spar with.
What about Old School here? I want him.
Nah, nah, nah,
it's Case's first day in the gym.
It's okay. I'll spar with ya.
See? We're all good.
Look, Case, this kid is pretty tough.
It's okay, Brody.
You go get changed.
Yeah, like hell.
I'm gonna watch this from right over here.
This is gonna be hell of a show.
Ooh!
What's going on?
New school versus the old school.
You know, Case could have been huge.
Just didn't know how to play the game.
Lots of different ways
to play the game, Brody.
Yeah, but in the end,
it all comes down to winning or losing.
And I think my old pal, Case,
is about to lose the hard way today.
Well, maybe you should tell your new pal,
Cobra, to go about 80% on Case.
BRODY: What, you got
a sweet spot for Case now?
Come on, he's not even in your class.
You know, speaking of which,
when are you and me gonna go a few rounds?
(CHUCKLES) Brody, I tolerate you.
First, because I grew up with brothers
and I kind of look at you
as one of their idiot friends.
Second, you're married.
Third, even if you weren't...
And fourth, just... Ew!
You gonna get in the ring Jet Leroy?
(EXHALES) Just let me know
when you're ready.
Come on, Old School, let's do this!
(ALL CHEERING AND WHOOPING)
Dude, I can't wait for Cobra
to wreck this dude!
CREECH: Speed dial fucking EMT, man.
The old school is about to get schooled!
Turn the fucking phones off!
People wanna see me, they gotta pay!
(CHEERING CONTINUES)
You gonna listen to me, okay?
Take it easy in there, all right?
The more rounds you get in, the better,
you understand?
I'm gonna fucking waste him.
Don't pretend like
you don't want him outta here, too.
CREECH:
All right, let's go, Cobra! Let's go, man!
(CHEERING)
(ALL EXCLAIMING)
MATTY: Hang back, hang back!
Hang back!
(FIGHTERS EXCLAIMING)
Okay, Okay.
Hang back, Cobra, hang back!
Oh!
Okay, get him, get him!
(ALL EXCLAIMING)
(ALL CLAMORING)
Cobra, Cobra! Are you all right?
Cobra.
Somebody call an ambulance.
I don't need this, Matty, I'm okay.
It's regulation, kid.
You get knocked out, you get checked out.
So, what do you think?
It doesn't look good.
Vega's not going to be happy about this.
So, you ready to get this run in?
You know, why don't you go run by yourself?
What's wrong?
"What's wrong"?
About a minute in, you already knew
you had that kid's number.
And you want to know
the really fucked up part?
Is that you knew that he knew it, too,
and you still went out there
and just completely
kicked the living shit out of him.
What about all that karate code of honor shit
you're always talking about?
Thought you were
a better man than that, Case.
I expected more out of you.
Come on, Brody,
you don't think he had it coming?
Course I did.
I'm just fuckin' with you.
Quit being such a pussy.
Says here that Case
was undefeated in 42 fights.
Come on, man, that can't be true.
You saw what Old School did to Cobra.
Yeah, guy's a freak.
Let's go.
(SOFT MUSIC PLAYING)
Yo, Brody!
Brody!
(MUSIC PLAYING)
(GROANS)
Oh, hell no, Brody, man,
we're supposed to be liftin'.
Oh. (GIGGLES)
Spot me, bro.
Man, I'm outta here.
Call me when you wanna win a fight.
I always knew you were gay.
(WOMEN GIGGLING)
Me? The brunette's a man.
Dude, I was kidding.
TAJ: Guess who's two hours late.
Yo, Brody, man, what the fuck?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, I got it, I know.
But, look, just the first couple days.
Still getting into the swing of things.
- I'm not gonna be late all the time.
- It's okay, champ, it's okay.
We'll get you back in shape.
But this guy you brought with you...
This guy's a disruptive
presence to the camp.
But it is my camp, right?
Looks like the old school is
showing Brody James how it's done.
Round before you fire.
Holy shit.
Hugo Vega?
MATTY: Mr. Vega, welcome.
Where's Brody?
Too early?
BRODY: What the hell
are you doing here, Vega?
Came to see the guy who beat my guy.
Which one of you is called Old School,
gave Cobra a concussion
and broke three of his ribs?
Jesus Christ, Case Walker.
Casey "The Headcase" Walker.
It's been years.
What you been up to, brother?
- "Brother"?
- Come on.
It was a lousy contract and your team
should've been on top of it.
You got nerve, I'll give you that.
Well, let's make it right.
Got room on the undercard now,
thanks to you.
So, I came down to see what you can do.
Thanks, but I'm done for today.
Hey. Hold on, be right back.
Hey, what the...
Hey, hey, hey.
What the hell are you doin', man?
What's your problem?
Do you know who that guy is?
Do you?
Don't be an asshole.
I don't understand why shit's always
gotta be so goddamn difficult for you.
You want a shot,
go show the man what you can do.
Everything doesn't have to be
so goddamn difficult, all right?
Look, we really need him.
We need a fighter.
Excuse me, Mr. Vega. Excuse me.
Uh, let me try out.
I mean, if you've got room on your card,
let me show you my stuff.
Sorry, kid, I got things to do.
Hey, I'll spar him.
Taj, come on.
It's okay, Taj.
Come on, just show him what you got.
Take it to Old School.
CREECH: All right, let's go, Taj.
You got it!
Let's go!
(FIGHTERS EXCLAIMING)
Taj, get 'em! Get 'em, get 'em!
Come on, kid, you're losing him.
Come on, Taj. Come on, come on.
(GRUNTS)
HUGO: Like I said, nothing to see here.
Let's get out of here.
(INDISTINCT MURMURING)
It's okay...
MYCA: I don't understand.
He wasn't even trying.
Yesterday, he was unstoppable.
All right, you handle publicity,
I'll recruit the talent.
Do you honestly think
that the guy you saw today
is the same guy that beat Cobra yesterday?
You don't understand, okay?
It's like this guy looks at the world through
the wrong end of the telescope, all right?
He's not all there.
He wants it his way or no way.
I can't do business
with somebody like that.
Well, sounds like you two
have some history.
Care to elaborate?
Yeah, I want you to focus all your energy
on generating interest
for the Braga-James fight.
- Understood?
- Understood.
- Understood, I'm on it, Hugo.
Well, "I'm on it" is not good enough, okay?
I've got everything riding on this.
Hugo, I'm calling in
every favor for this fight.
By the time I'm finished
with everything I need to do,
from the Internet ties
to the media buy-ins,
believe me,
they will know about this fight on Mars.
Why stop at Mars?
Hey, what the fuck was that out there?
Hey, man, if you want to fight for Hugo Vega,
that's your business.
I'm just here to help you out, right?
- Yeah, but...
- Am I right?
So let's go do some mitts, come on.
Dude, you lit his ass up.
Dude, don't be a dumb-ass.
- He wasn't even freakin' trying.
- (THUDS)
Need somethin'?
Yeah, what do you call all that?
I've never seen anything like that before.
Hey, man, why did you let me
pound on you like that?
"Pound"?
Yeah, Why'd you agree to spar with me
if you weren't gonna fight back?
Well, it looked like it was important to you,
I was just trying to make you look good.
I've got nothing to prove to the man.
Hugo Vega is one of the top
promoters in the sport
and you just shined him on.
Can you teach us?
Been there, done that.
TAJ: We're all in the same camp, bro.
We should all help each other out, right?
Oh, yeah? How you going to help me out?
CREECH: Come on, dude,
this guy's not gonna teach us anything.
Wait a second.
Look, I'll show you a few things
after I'm done with my workout, okay?
That's only after
I'm finished working out.
After you're done?
- Yeah.
- Okay. Got it.
Yeah, no hurry, man.
Just, whenever you got some free time.
Okay, it's going to be awhile.
(CRICKETS CHIRPING)
(INDISTINCT CONVERSATION)
You done?
(SIGHS)
Okay, stop.
Gloves off.
Okay, question.
Why do you wrap your hands
in boxing and in MMA?
So you don't sprain your wrist?
Or break your hands.
Exactly.
That's because
you don't know how to punch.
You don't know how to punch
without hurting yourself.
Not your opponent, hurting your damn self.
News flash, guys.
In martial arts, your hands, your feet,
your elbows, your knees
even your head were used as weapons
and were trained as such.
You understand?
See, striking is not just about
putting on gloves and hitting a heavy bag
and letting a heavy bag stop your fist.
Striking is about perfecting the technique.
Maximum result, minimal effort. Okay?
Just like the precision of a golf swing.
You transfer all the power
into one specific point.
See?
Stop that shit.
Okay, now look.
If I were an inch closer or further away,
they wouldn't have broken.
See, you have to find your sweet spot.
So distance.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Distance along with proper technique
is where you're the most powerful.
Now you try.
I want you to punch through the board.
Okay? Use these two knuckles.
Wrist straight, not like this, like this.
Go.
See?
Now, hitting a heavy bag would give you
nearly a 100% success rate.
Not so with this.
Yeah, and it doesn't hurt your hand.
Five hundred hand strikes.
Knuckles and shuto.
Five hundred kicks,
ball of the foot, shin and instep.
Rub this on your bruises tonight.
I can't believe I'm doing this shit again.
I must be some kind of fool.
ANNOUNCER: (ON TV)
...James will have his hands full
up against the seven-foot
"Psycho" Caesar Braga.
Braga is undefeated and has decimated
his last three opponents.
Tickets are now on sale
at the Bangkok Sporting...
I don't want to get hit
with any of his power shots.
I think I'll have Case work
with me on that.
...Bangkok heavyweight championship!
It's gonna be a hell of a fight.
BRODY: Hello, everybody,
hello, hello, hello.
Hey, everybody, nice to see you.
Brody, Brody, Brody.
Sawadee, Mr. Kanarot.
(GREETING IN THAI)
Good morning to you, too.
So, how is Thailand
treating you, Mr. James?
Like a king, so far.
I have a few questions for you.
- You bring security this time or what?
- (CHUCKLES)
No need, I assure you.
Okay, are you nervous
about the fight with Braga?
I'm a bit nervous.
Nervous that I might end his career
and his family would have to go graze
- in less favorable pastures.
- (REPORTERS LAUGHING)
Elaborating a little bit
on the Beaumont, Texas nightclub fight
where Quinton "Rampage" Jackson
pulled you out of?
I don't think
you have the right information.
But Jackson was arrested yesterday
on assault charge
in connection with this,
and he's on a $10,000 bail.
No comment.
Hey, champ, who's that?
(REPORTERS MURMURING)
(REPORTERS CLAMORING)
I know who that is.
That's Case Walker.
JOE: I thought he died in prison.
Dead guys don't move like that.
JOE: Not many live ones either.
All right, everyone,
Brody has a few more minutes
before I have to sit him down
with Inside MMA.
- Any last questions?
- REPORTER: Yes, uh...
What's his plan after the fight?
(INDISTINCT CLAMORING)
You do know
you're allowed to talk to me, right?
(CHUCKLES)
I mean, you haven't said so much
as "hello" since the night we met in Texas.
Hello.
Okay, okay. That's better.
I guess asking for some eye contact
would be pushing it.
What with your hectic social life and all.
I bet your life is pretty hectic
working for Hugo Vega.
But I bet it comes with its benefits, huh?
Well, you know,
not that I need to qualify myself,
but my job with PFC and my boss
is purely professional.
Not that you would be
insinuating something more,
which I know your ass wasn't.
No.
So, I see you made a lot of new fans today.
Press was eating you up.
What were those little things
you were doing?
- Uh, muscle ups. Yeah.
- Muscle ups, right. Yeah.
I don't know, I was just doing what I do.
Doing what you do?
Well, you know,
you might want to think about
toning back on some of
that awesomeness of yours.
Just a little bit.
At least, while your old pal,
Brody, is around.
What do you mean?
Come on, Case.
You're not stupid, I know that.
Shoot, Brody shouldn't be worried
about what I'm doing.
He should be worried about
his fight with Braga.
I'm just here to help him out.
And if you just so happen to
get written up by some of the best
fight journalists in this country,
well that would be pretty nice, too,
now wouldn't it?
Isn't there something you want to ask me?
(CHUCKLES)
Boy. Well, if you're not
actually gonna ask me out on a date,
I really do hope
you're at least thinking about it.
(CLEARS THROAT) Uh...
Okay, look.
Lunch, Louie Thai, Saturday at 2:00.
Sound good?
- Yeah, good. Mmm.
- Yeah? Yeah? Okay.
Well, I will see you then.
Don't stand me up.
(EXHALES)
Let's see.
(GROANS)
How long is this going to take?
- You want to look good, right?
- (KNOCKING ON DOOR)
TAJ: Hey, man, what took you so long?
Do you know how hard it is
to find his size in Thailand?
Dude's a freaking Sasquatch
with a girly waist.
You know I can hear you, right?
Don't worry about it, I got just the thing.
Check this out right here.
Ba-bam!
Kinda colorful, isn't it?
Nah, man, this is what's up.
Besides, Myca's like a dime piece,
so you're gonna wanna look your best.
Yeah, don't forget to bring flowers either.
Where am I going to get flowers?
GIRL: Those are pretty.
Oh, you think so?
Yup, they're called calla lilies.
Calla lilies? Wow.
Try to say that three times fast.
- Calla lily, calla lily, calla lily.
- Calla lily, calla lily...
- You win.
- (CHUCKLES)
Well, listen, I'll get these calla lilies
as soon as we find your mom or dad, okay?
How's that sound?
My daddy's in heaven and my mom is...
Morgan, there you are.
Baby, how many times have I told you
to stay where I can see you?
But I was helping Mr...
Mr. Case.
I was helping Mr. Case buy flowers.
Flowers, huh?
I wonder who for.
MYCA: Now, you be good for Boonkie, okay?
I'll be back in a few hours.
MORGAN: Bye, Mr. Case.
Where we're going is right over there.
So, this is our neighborhood
while we're here.
It's one of our favorite spots.
CASE: It's nice.
So, Morgan's adorable.
Thank you.
I didn't mean to spring her
on you like that.
I was going to tell you at lunch.
It's all good.
I was just surprised...
How does motherhood
work with your schedule?
Oh, Boonkie is the best nanny.
She gets her to her tutor,
gymnastics, karate.
Karate?
Yeah, karate. She loves it.
Hmm.
BRODY: I told those t-shirt guys,
"Forget it."
There's no way I'm going to do anything
for that cheap.
Not this day.
Ah, here he is.
All right, I don't have time
to beat around the bush.
Word on the street is you're not exactly
setting the world on fire in training camp.
BRODY: "Word on the street"?
You've been watching
Starsky & Hutch reruns?
Maybe Huggy Bear will come join us later?
What are you, a fuckin' moron?
You think this is some kind of joke, huh?
You're one loss away
from anonymity at the UFC.
I'm giving you a second life.
I'm laying the groundwork for you
to become a fuckin' superstar
and all you can do is
make some fuck-tasticjokes.
You believe this guy?
Brody meant no disrespect, Mr. Vega.
Okay, I didn't ask for your input.
Understand?
You're supposed to be
getting this guy in fighting shape,
not making bullshit excuses for him.
CASE: So, what happened?
He claimed to be a stockbroker
and died robbing a jewelry store.
Wow, I'm sorry to hear it.
Yeah, don't be.
We met, got married two months later.
Kinda swept me off my feet
before I ever really got to know him.
Guess we live and learn, huh?
Yeah, we do.
So, what else can you tell me
about yourself?
Other than having some
really bad-ass moves in the cage.
Well, uh, I'm from New Orleans.
I happen to be the only person I know
without a cell phone.
I don't know how interesting that is.
But I guess I'm just like everybody else,
just trying to make it day by day, you know?
Well, there was one more thing
I was a bit curious about.
You want to tell me a little bit
about your time in prison?
Why you went in?
Who told you about that?
No one told me, I just looked into it.
"Looked into it"?
You mean, like, you investigated me?
No.
The Internet. Maybe you've heard of it?
Welcome to this wacky world
of dating in the 21st century.
Look, Case, I'm sorry if I offended you.
But I've been through a lot.
And I have to be extremely careful
about who I bring into my life.
Into Morgan's life.
Hey, look, I think we made a mistake.
I need to go.
So, what's your plan
for improving the situation?
Because you got less than four weeks
to turn things around.
No worries, Hugo.
Kickin' it into high gear.
This fight's in the bag.
What gear are you taking?
BRODY: I'm not taking anything.
I thought I'd give my body a rest.
That's a problem.
What do you got? You bring anything?
- Well, I got some Deca and some Winnie tabs.
- That's bullshit.
I want you to call my guy.
All right, go see my doc, okay?
He'll get you on a course
of Test Cypionate, Winstrol.
We'll throw in some Anadrol.
(SCOFFS) Should have you in beast mode
by the time of the fight.
If you don't think
Braga is doing the same thing,
you're a lot dumber than I thought.
Come on, champ, balls to the wall.
Give our customers and your fans
a fight they'll never forget.
Do that and we'll all be making more money
than you know what to do with.
All right, I'm outta here.
Lay off the nuts.
Keep this between us, all right?
I don't want to hear any of Case's
holier-than-thou bullshit.
Well, I can keep a secret.
And, apparently, so can he.
Okay, what?
When I stepped out to have a smoke,
I saw your boy, Case, with Myca
and the nanny and her kid.
Just outside the restaurant.
All nice and cozy.
She introduced him to the kid?
TAJ: Dude, I don't even know
why you bother.
The freak over there
probably drinks from a toilet anyway.
CREECH: Hey, chill, she's a human being.
TAJ: If you say so.
What's going on?
Uh, Brody wants to spar with you.
I think he's pissed about something.
Hey, Case, come over here.
Let's get a little work in today.
(ALL EXCLAIMING)
Don't let him get set!
(GRUNTS)
Hey, man, what's your problem?
(YELLS)
Go for the chicken wing.
Stay on him, champ!
(BOTH GRUNTING)
Feet first, Brody!
(GROANING)
MATTY: Okay, that's enough!
Brody, sorry, man.
Go fuck yourself.
(GRUNTS)
- Fuck.
- Dude, you smoked him.
Shut up.
Yo, Case, what is it, man? What's wrong?
If you can't control yourself,
you sure as hell can't control the outcome.
Damn it!
That's the second one of my fuckin' fighters
that mock has beat up on.
- Wait...
- No! Just give me a second here.
Okay.
You're going to find out everything
there is to know about Case Walker.
- Okay?
- Yeah.
Complete bio, fight history,
criminal record,
whatever exists about him, I want to know.
- Get back to me ASAP.
- Okay.
Now.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
(WHIRRING)
(WHIRRING STOPS)
Stop your bitchin' and go.
(BOTH GROANING)
Faster.
Come on back up.
Two at a time!
- TAJ: Two a time?
- Yes!
Okay, that's one.
CREECH:
Hell, man, what'd I ever do to you?
You want a babysitter or a trainer?
TAJ: Dude, you might be
the worse sensei ever.
Not like I haven't heard that before.
Down.
What's up?
I wanted to apologize.
It was completely inappropriate for me
to pry the way I did.
I realize now that privacy is
underappreciated in this day and age.
It's no big deal.
Look, I had a really great time
hanging out with you the other day.
And Morgan just adored you.
Case, I don't want anything from you,
other than...
Just you being who you are
and your good company.
That is if you're still open to sharing it.
Sometimes, I think we forget
how important it is just to...
Just show up and take care
of the good friendships that we have,
or might like to have.
Good friendships are hard to come by.
Ain't that the truth.
Hey, Myca.
Thank you.
(UNZIPS)
Hey, Brody.
What you got there, man?
How is that any business of yours?
You hungry?
Come on, man.
Let's go get some street meat.
(WOMEN LAUGHING)
(SPEAKING THAI)
(GIGGLING)
They got this hot sauce,
they only have in every now and again,
it's fucking great.
- Your order?
- Uh...
Two orders of the chicken satay,
stir fry vegetables.
No peanut sauce.
- Name?
- Isaac Cox.
Okay.
What?
You know, this place could grow on me.
Yeah, me too.
For a city this crowded,
it sure is peaceful.
I don't think I need to tell you,
but with this Braga fight
you're gonna have to get focused
and cut out all this bullshit in your life.
At least until after the fight.
You need to pick apart his flaws
and plan a strategy
that he can't help but fall into.
Brody?
Brody.
Come on, man.
Do you not want this anymore?
If you don't, it's okay, man.
Just be honest with yourself.
I want this fight, Case. I do.
But it's not just about
what I want anymore.
There's a lot of moving pieces
in this whole operation now.
There's people with families
depending on me.
I get hurt, there's no insurance
that's going to cover me.
And you got the media bullshit.
Not to mention the political bullshit.
It never ends.
One thing I envy about you is,
your life is simple.
Come and go as you please.
Got no wife, no kids.
Basically nobody to own up to.
Just you.
What you trying to say,
my grass is greener?
Man, I don't even have grass.
I basically live in a van
down by the river.
Yeah, that's true.
(SIGHS) Your life really does suck.
You know, we need to schedule some time
for you to go fuck yourself, okay.
Done.
I'm all in, Case.
I'm 100% committed to this fight.
That's good to hear.
Now, show me.
Better yet, show yourself.
All right.
I gotta say something though.
I gotta apologize for...
Well, how I acted the other day.
Hmm?
I deserved that ass whooping, man.
My ego's just so used to me
getting whatever I want,
however I wanted it...
When I heard about the you and Myca thing,
I lost it.
I started acting like a spoiled brat.
Man, that's behind us, man.
Okay?
You were ragin'.
That's why you were making
so many mistakes.
You know what I say...
- "An angry mind is a narrow mind."
- That's right.
And for your information,
there is no "me and Myca thing."
If you had half a brain, there would be.
That's a good woman, right there.
Man, she saw through all my bullshit
from day one.
That's why she keeps rejecting me.
Besides, I'm married.
Oh, you remember that?
Oh, that's good!
Yeah, you are, brother.
Yeah.
I'm gonna make that right, too.
Just watch.
You're looking at the new, improved
and totally serious Brody James.
Isaac Cox.
Isaac Cox!
There it is.
What do you think?
Not bad.
Hey, Matty!
Get over here.
Come on.
This shit has gone on long enough
between you two.
All right, I realize you both come from
different backgrounds and all that
and I know you both got your own ideas
about how this gym should be ran,
but fact of the matter is, you're both
here for the same reason.
That's to make better fighters.
Am I right?
- Yeah.
I think this gym is big enough
for all of our egos.
So, let's put this shit to bed.
I ain't got no problem with that.
Come on, Matty, take the man's
goddamn hand, all right?
Don't make me have to fire your ass.
See, that's not so bad, right?
Now, maybe we can get
some real work done, huh?
(HIP-HOP MUSIC PLAYING)
Yeah
I tried telling you ain't ready
(INDISTINCT)
Have you ever seen
a man not afraid to die?
Gave his life for a dream
Born hustler, so the game conceived
A caged beast, but now I'm free
How can you blame me?
I was born for this
The game chose me
Now I've been training
for this my whole life
Carpe diem, huh, seize the moment right
We're gonna turn up
And rock in the ice
This is our time
Yeah, I'm about that life
I'm a street dude
Teach dudes to think quicker
Would take over the world
but I train bigger
Never satisfied I'm trying to be richer
And pour a little bit
for those who ain't with us
Ready, ready
I don't get ready, I stay ready
'Cause the consequences is heavy
My man "D" said it, we never quit
Even though the thing's heavy
We push like a seven-seven Chevy
Ready, ready
My whole clique is so sick
Was on the bottom now we running this
Trying hard when the load gets heavy
The money was sloping, now it's steady
An angry mind.
You need to take advantage of that.
(STRAINING)
(FIGHTERS EXCLAIMING)
Ready, ready
My whole clique is so sick
Was on the bottom now we running this
Trying hard when the load gets heavy
The money we sloping now it's steady
You boys is not ready
BRODY:
How much is this insurance costing me?
Believe me, Brody, it's worth it.
Besides, you're making
enough money to afford it.
Yeah, man. Plus, you got kids.
What if something happens to you?
You could lose everything
off one major injury.
What if I don't pass the physical?
Don't be ridiculous,
you're healthy as a horse.
All right.
What if something I'd taken in the past
shows up in my blood work?
They disqualify me?
Whatever you might have taken
before you came to Thailand
won't still be in your system.
Don't worry about it.
Hey, I'd really like to thank you.
For what?
Well, you said some things
I really needed to hear.
And I'd like to show my appreciation
if you'd let me.
Well, I appreciate your appreciation,
Mr. Walker.
So what do you have in mind?
A Louie Thai do-over.
I'd like that. Done.
TAJ: Come on, Creech!
Whoa.
(FIGHTERS EXCLAIMING)
(FIGHTERS GROANING)
TAJ: Come on, Creech!
(GRUNTING)
That's all right, bro.
You just didn't have it today, that's all.
His fucking style, man,
it's just throwing me off.
I can tell.
Dude. If it's styles that win fights,
I just gotta learn how...
Mmm!
(YELLS)
No flinch. Block only what comes close.
MYCA: You know, Brady's really lucky
to have you as a friend.
Loyalty is rare these days.
CASE: Well, I consider my friends family.
Where is your family, Case?
I mean, if you don't mind me asking.
I know now you are about your privacy.
Okay, stop.
First, let me apologize
about the other evening.
I'm way out of practice
with this whole dating thing.
But I'd really like
to get to know you better,
so listen, you can ask me anything
from now on, okay?
- Okay.
So, is there a Mrs. Case?
Any little Cases running around?
- (CHUCKLES) No mini-Cases.
- (CHUCKLES)
I thought there'd be a Mrs. Case one time.
- But turned out she was already married.
- Oh, wow.
- Yeah.
- That must've hurt.
What was up with that?
Well, there are these women
who fixate on romancing inmates.
There's a name for them, but I forget.
But once the inmate gets released,
then the fantasy's over.
How long ago was that?
Seven years ago.
Well, I believe seven's
a very lucky number.
- You do, do you?
- Yeah, I do.
Case, I think things are really gonna
start turning around for you.
Think so?
I think so.
- So here's my place.
- Oh.
(CHUCKLES)
Thank you.
So, I hope I didn't have you out too late.
It must be just about the time
to tuck little Morgan into bed, huh?
Oh, Morgan spending the night
with Boonkie tonight,
so, I don't have a curfew.
So, I guess you have to get up
pretty early to train, huh?
Yeah, yeah. I got to get up
pretty early to train Brody.
And, uh, you know, work out.
Well, I had a really great time tonight.
- Yeah, me, too. Me, too.
- Thank you.
- Yeah.
- (BOTH CHUCKLE)
Good night.
Bye.
You froze again, didn't you? (CHUCKLES)
"No, Myca, I don't have to wake up early.
I don't have to train."
"All I have to look forward to is going back
to my room and talking to my-goddamn-self."
You are an idiot.
All you had to do was say,
"Well, Myca, since you don't have a curfew,
I would like to spend more time with you.
"Since we happen to be
in front of your condo..."
You'd think I'd get it.
You'd think my dumb ass would get it.
- But no...
- (WHIRRING)
Fucking stupid...
(KNOCKING ON DOOR)
(WHIRRING STOPS)
(KNOCKING CONTINUES)
Who is it?
What?
Mr. Vega has been hearing
a lot of good things about you lately.
Some very, very good things.
And I care, why?
This.
What's that?
It's a contract.
It's your contract to fight for the PFC.
And where's Vega?
Don't flatter yourself.
Mr. Vega is a very busy man.
(SCOFFS)
You must be out of your mind.
(SIGHS)
You know what, those work fine.
But these are too basic. It's too clean.
If you haven't noticed, it's Caesar Braga.
B-R-A-G-A. It says here, "Barga."
"Barga," not the name. Not the name.
These... I'm gonna have to re-do
all of these, guys.
- No, it's Braga, like that. Not Barga like...
- Mr. Vega?
Excuse me, Mr. Vega.
Yeah, who the hell are you?
Well, I'm Eddie,
but everyone just calls me Creech.
All right, how can I help you?
Oh. Mr. Walker wanted me
to deliver this to you.
- Oh. Mr. Walker.
- Yes, sir.
All right, um...
Yeah? Can I help you?
Well, I was just kind of wondering here...
No. No. No.
Whatever you're thinking, no. Okay?
Please, we're kind of busy here.
Okay, but you know it says "Barga"?
Okay, no, please,
just get out of here! Please!
This is what I'm talking about here.
Okay, even a fucking...
You gotta look at it. Look at it.
Excuse me a second.
What the fuck?
The balls on this guy.
Who the fuck does he think he is? Hmm?
Did you find out? Did you dig up anything?
- I'm working on it. I'm working on it.
- Well, work a little harder. Okay?
I don't care if you have to dig up
the whole fucking Internet.
Find something. Bring it back.
Don't come back until you do.
Go. Go. Go. Go.
BRODY:
What is it with you and Vega anyways?
CASE: What he's done to the sport
is a travesty, man.
It's what he represents.
What? And you're so pure?
What's wrong with doing it clean?
That's the way it started, right?
Everybody's got their price, Case.
Tell me, there's not some number out there
to convince you
to bend the rules, just a little.
What does it benefit a man
if he gains the world,
but loses his soul, right?
- You get that shit off a fortune cookie?
- (CHUCKLES)
Come on, let's pick this shit up.
(ALL EXCLAIMING)
Hey!
(EXCLAIMING)
What are you guys watching?
Case, this is some wicked shit.
(GRUNTING)
CASE: Where the hell did you find that?
Showed up yesterday on Worldstar.
Then it just exploded.
Now it's everywhere.
That happened years ago, I was framed.
How the hell did you not end up
under the jail for this shit?
Long story.
Felon in possession of a firearm.
That's five years mandatory.
You planted that gun.
What'd you say, you piece of shit?
I ain't gotta plant no gun
to get rid of your black ass.
You done lost your manners, boy.
Hold his ass.
(GRUNTS)
Fuck!
I said hold his ass still!
(GROANS)
CASE: Like I said, long story.
One that's better forgotten.
(ALL GROANING)
HUGO: Are you fucking kidding me?
Our pay-per-view numbers
should be twice this by now.
- We don't turn this around, I'm fucked.
- Wanna get Myca on the line?
No, she's been flogging
this bout everywhere she can.
I've thrown more money into this thing
than in my last five fights
and still I can't move the fucking needle.
Fans just don't wanna see this fight,
simple as that.
Fans don't wanna see Brody James fight,
that's the problem.
He's done.
He's over, he's yesterday's news.
I hear he's looking a lot better, boss.
It's too little. Too late.
Now, Case Walker...
It's different story
with that Internet cop thing.
- What if...
- What are you thinking?
- Mr. Case?
- Mr. Case!
(SPEAKING THAI)
What?
Mr. Walker, your video has exploded.
Do you think its popularity
is a symbolic response
to police brutality in your country?
No comment.
Now could you people move back, please.
Just answer that, please.
You have seen the video, right?
REPORTER: Okay, back up...
Back up. Back up.
All right, everyone,
I'm Myca Cruz, Mr. Walker's publicist.
He will not be answering any questions
or conducting interviews at this time.
Any media requests can
go through my office, and my office only.
- REPORTER 1: Come on!
- REPORTER 2: Please. Please.
(ALL CLAMORING)
Come in.
So, what do you think?
Wow. This is really nice. But whose is it?
No strings attached, Case.
It's Vega's way of showing his appreciation
for everything you've done for Brody.
Twenty-four-hour security guards.
No one's getting in here
without your permission.
Or Vega's.
He's trying to help.
Look, I'm just around the corner
if you need me.
I'm sure your services don't come cheap.
Case, I'm trying to help as a friend,
if that's okay with you.
Well, okay. I'll go get my stuff.
Thank you.
(BRODY GRUNTING)
(KNOCKING)
Hey, Matty, who's this guy?
Sambo guy, supposed to help Brody
with his leg locks.
Used to fight in Pride.
Did you send for him?
No, he's local.
What's the matter?
He just pops up outta nowhere
and he's working
with a number one contender?
Now you know how I felt
when you walked in.
Come on, man,
what's a Russian Sambo specialist
doing in Bangkok?
And he just happens to come to this gym?
Come on, man, something doesn't fit.
Yeah, not like a 250-pound
black karate guy.
CASE: Hey, guys, take it down a notch,
come on you got one week
before the fight, Brody.
I'm only 230.
- You look 260...
- (BRODY GROANING LOUDLY)
CASE: Shit!
MATTY: What the hell happened?
I had him in a heel-hook
and he spun the wrong way.
What?
Fuck, it was an accident, Brody moved.
MATTY: Shit! Somebody get some ice!
MYCA: Hey, how's it going?
We're waiting for the nurse to come back
with his release papers.
He won't need surgery,
but he's gonna be out
for the next eight to 12 weeks at least.
Oh, God.
I gotta call Hugo.
Oh, champ, I'm so sorry.
You'll bounce back.
We'll reschedule your fight.
(CHUCKLES)
Vega needs this fight more than I do.
He's not going to reschedule it.
Now, I gotta fuckin' pay for re-hab.
I'm gonna lose my house.
No, Brody, you forgot.
You have insurance now.
The hell I do.
I'm not gonna qualify, Case.
Well, why not?
Because I've been taking steroids, all right?
The whole time.
I've been on them
since the beginning of the camp.
How do you think I got in shape so quick?
You mean these steroids?
Well, see these...
These are just crushed up baby aspirin.
And these, saline solution
with a little food coloring.
You know, Matty,
you need to change those locks
'cause they're a little too easy to break.
Yeah, he switched them out
a long time ago.
You knew about this?
Yeah, he told me a couple weeks ago.
But, it was actually kind of funny
watching you get stronger,
thinking all the while
it was some kind of drug.
You believed it, so you achieved it.
All the while it was just you.
Motherfucker.
(LAUGHS)
Thanks, man, I owe you one.
(KNOCKING ON DOOR)
- Case. You mind if we come in?
- Hey, it's your place.
All right, look at you.
What's this?
Getting my stuff together.
Wait a minute,
somebody told him he had to move out?
No, nobody said anything.
But with Brody out of commission,
and the fight off...
Yeah, Brody may be done,
but this fight's going to happen.
Really? Who's fighting Braga?
You are.
(SNAPS FINGERS)
- What's this?
- Go on, open it.
You're getting a million dollars.
How does that feel?
Are you serious?
Dead serious.
Half now and half after the fight.
Just like you stipulated in your contract.
See, I'm a businessman
and you, my friend, are in business.
What do you say, my brother?
You wanted a shot.
That's your shot.
This is a whole lot of money.
Yes, it is.
Breaking news in
the Brody James-Caesar Braga
PFC 14 Battle in Bangkok.
James is out after suffering
a knee injury in training.
Replacing him will be veteran fighter
Case Walker who shot back into the spotlight
with a video of him destroying four cops
while handcuffed went viral weeks ago.
With less than a week to prepare,
Walker's unlikely victory
against four armed policemen
might not be as tough
as going up against the seven-foot,
350 pound, undefeated
"Psycho" Caesar Braga,
who's said to be
the most dangerous man in all of MMA.
(FIGHTERS CHEERING)
(WHOOPING)
BRODY: That's a lot of adulation
for my stand-in.
Why don't you come say hi?
Hey, hey, Brittany. Hey, BJ. Oh, Davy.
Man, you guys got big.
Hey, Case. Congrats on the fight.
I'm actually relieved that
Brady's not fighting that animal.
Well, I'm just relieved
that I have his consent.
You have my consent
if you go out there and whip his ass.
Now, go get in the ring before I do
something nasty with these crutches.
Well, you heard him, all right.
Bye, James gang.
ALL: Bye.
See ya.
Two. Two-kick.
Nice. Now move out on a '45, now.
Three.
Still feels strange.
Yeah, I know, but don't worry about it,
this shit happens all the time.
Plus, it's giving me
a nice chance to scout you out
before you go
and get that belt off of Braga.
I'm coming for that belt, you know.
Two.
Two. Two-kick. Time.
Nah, he just got done hitting mitts.
All right, I'll get him over here.
Hey, Case, come here real quick.
(BUTTON CLICKS)
Yo, Case, let me holla at you man!
Why in the fuck are you running around
pretending to be me?
Man, you got me lit up! Arrested.
I go to the motherfuckin' jail' house!
And both my chicks are there,
my baby mama and my side chick!
- (BRODY SNIGGERS)
- You done got me arrested
and fucked up my sex life!
I'm gonna fuck you up, man!
I'm gonna kick you dead
in the motherfuckin'...
- (LAUGHING)
- Ha-ha-ha.
Yeah, real funny.
The man seems mad.
I'll get you back. You know what's up.
Hey, Taj.
So, what's been wrong with you today?
- Yeah, you don't want to know.
- Try me.
You said you didn't want to fight for Vega.
Then Brody gets hurt and you take his place.
Yeah, what about it?
You said you didn't want to fight for Vega.
(SCOFFS) Hey, man, I understand.
For a mill, I'd change my principals, too.
What does he know, he's just a kid, right?
A kid who really looks up to you.
Besides, you're the one who said
you wouldn't fight for Vega.
(SCOFFS) Yeah, but, I mean,
these are my terms.
Yeah, your terms.
But I will promise you this.
Hugo Vega pulls strings
at many different levels.
He needs big numbers on this fight
or he loses everything.
What's that got to do with me?
Case, don't you realize
you're the reason for the big numbers.
I mean last week alone your police video
got 20 million hits on the Internet.
You can't buy publicity like that.
Brody getting hurt was the best thing
that could have ever happened to Hugo Vega.
Why would you want to practice leg locks
with that guy after what happened to Brody?
There's something I want to learn.
Hey, do me a favor, keep him busy.
(INDISTINCT WHISPERING)
- So, Case, are you ready to warm up?
- How much did he pay you?
What? Who?
Vega. How much he pay you
to take out Brady's leg?
Get the fuck outta here.
It was an accident.
I had Brody in a heel-lock
and he spun the wrong way.
You're a fuckin' liar.
What the fuck you doing' with my phone?
You sent a two-word text,
10 minutes after your session with Brody.
"It's done."
You fuckin' serious? Put your hands down.
I'm definitely not going
to the cops with this.
Vega's the one that needs to suffer.
Way I see it,
the way we beat Vega
is by Case beating his man.
That's how we hurt him.
Exactly. And after you defeat Braga,
sign with a different promoter.
You'd be the champ then,
you call the shots.
But then Vega still makes
a shitload of money
and gets away with what he did to Brody.
(SIGHS)
I could just walk away and not fight.
Yeah, that would screw him royally.
But then you'd be out of the other
half-million you get after the fight.
Plus, he'd sue you.
Come on, Case, beat Braga.
What? Win the battle, not the war?
Look, sometimes
you gotta just take half a victory.
- Compromise a little, huh.
- (SCOFFS)
Not real good at that.
But learning.
What he did to Brody, use it as incentive.
Fuel to the fire.
What do you want to do, Case?
(HIP-HOP MUSIC PLAYING)
I got to do what I've got to do
That's what I'm facing, back in my phase
Well, looks like he finally
made his decision.
It's the right way to go.
Assuming, that is,
he can actually beat Braga.
Now we doing it our way
Light 'em up, light 'em up
Molotov music, let's all lose it
Burn 'em up, burn 'em up
Set a fire to my amusement
I got to do what I've got to do
That's what I'm facing, back in my phase
I pray to God, He doesn't care
I'mma do me, I'mma do me
That's in my blood
I'll never change
All right, that big ol' monster
starts moving forward.
I'm on my bicycle.
There you go, there you go.
He plants his feet, he's looking to throw.
Kick the legs.
Nice.
All right. Takes you down. Takes 'em out.
I'm screwed.
(CHUCKLES) That's true.
- (CHUCKLES)
- All right, look, we get there. TK Scissors...
He takes them out,
TK Scissors, slip out the back.
Got it, Coach.
That's fantastic, great. All right.
We're almost at 400,000 buy-ins U.S.
Okay? Fully expect to hit it
before the fight starts.
At $69 per, that is almost $30 million.
Yes! See, that's what I'm talking about.
You see, by sidelining
the has-been Brody James,
and replacing him
with the Internet Ram-Bro...
I mean, come on,
that puts us back in the black, Jack.
(CHUCKLES)
Let's go make some money.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
Hugo. I quit.
You quit? Now?
Oh, my God, it's you.
The name's JeeJa.
But at the gym...
I mean, why do you look so...
- Well, you know.
- (CHUCKLES)
If I came to the gym looking like this,
do you think the guys would let me workout?
Yeah, I guess you're right.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
Oh, my God.
REPORTER 1: Tony Jaa!
REPORTER 2: Tony, this way.
Look here! Look here!
REPORTER 3: Tony, over here.
(CLAMORING)
(CHEERING)
Look at that!
(HOWLING)
Come on.
I'm big fan. I'm big fan.
Let me take picture. Okay? Like this.
He thinks I'm Rampage Jackson, doesn't he?
No. He thinks you're Cuba Gooding Jr.
He really likes Snow Dogs.
(EXCLAIMS)
(HOWLS)
(CHUCKLES) Big fan, man.
Strong.
I have just one question.
Care to share?
They're going to be coming to get us
in about 20 minutes to take us to the ring.
You need to start warming up.
Come on, let the man wrap your hands.
I don't need it, Brody.
This is more of your karate shit?
Look, it's for your protection,
let him wrap 'em.
You're as stubborn as my wife. Jesus.
What?
What's wrong?
Where you going?
Hey, Psycho!
"Psycho" Caesar Braga!
Braga, get your ass out here!
Hey! Got one question for you!
One question!
There you are. Hey, hey, hey!
- I got one question. One question...
- Fuck you! I answer in the ring!
Come on. Come on. One question.
Hold on here, what's going on here?
Save this for the paying customers, all right?
- Get Caesar out of here.
- It's just one question.
- Stop it!
- What? What?
CASE: No, no. One question, Braga.
Hey. Listen.
Don't try anything stupid, Walker.
Or I'll toss you into the gutter
you crawled out of.
We know what you did to Brody.
You're getting payback tonight.
- Hey, Psycho! Hey!
- (CROWD CHEERING)
Braga! Hey, Braga, just one question.
Just one question.
What's your problem?
Hey, man, if you're so tough,
Why'd it take you two punches
to knock your wife out?
- (GRUNTS)
- Stop it! Stop it!
(GRUNTS)
(SPEAKING PORTUGUESE)
(GROANS)
(YELLING)
(CROWD CLAMORING)
(GRUNTING)
(INDISTINCT CHEERING)
(GROANS)
(YELLING)
Come on, get up! Come on, get up!
MYCA: Yes! Yes!
No!
Yes! Yes!
- Go! Yes!
- (GRUNTS)
(CROWD CHEERING)
MYCA: No!
(GROANS)
(GRUNTS)
No! No!
Come on! Get up!
Get up!
(CROWD CHEERING)
(GRUNTS)
Go, baby! Go, baby!
Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes!
(GROANS)
(CROWD CHEERING)
(HOWLS)
(GROANS)
(EXCLAIMS)
(CROWD CHEERING AND APPLAUDING)
- Hey. Are you okay?
- Yeah.
Nice.
Breach of fucking contract. That's right!
You are so sued, okay?
I'm going to bury you when this is done.
- Are you finished?
- No, I'm just starting.
Good luck fighting your criminal charges
for getting Boris to take out Brady's leg.
Yeah, we got your payment transaction
as well as your phone records. Don't we?
Yes, we do.
No. What are you talking about?
Yeah, I'm thinking an extra million
would be good for Brody and his family.
That's unless you want him to sue you
for punitive damages,
which will cost you more like
$5 million when he's done.
No, no, no. Wait, wait, wait. Just wait.
Let's just talk about this because... What?
- Every dollar boss.
- What?
We have to refund every fucking dollar!
- Everything!
- Excuse us.
Looks like I'm out of a job.
Well, I could always use a good corner man.
- No place I'd rather be.
- (BOTH CHUCKLE)
- Pupils!
- You did it!
Respect to the sensei.
Very impressive.
Long way from Beaumont, huh?
Paradise, man.
You did it your way,
just like you said. Clean.
It's a game-changer.
Believe it...
You can achieve it.
There it is.
- (CHUCKLES)
- Let's get the hell out of here, all right?
(CROWD CHEERING AND APPLAUDING)
Do you back down?
I don't back down
I never back down
Tell me, do you back down?
I don't back down
Do you back down?
I never back down
Tell me, do you back down?
I don't back down
Do you back down?
I never back down
Tell me, do you back down?
I don't back down
Do you back down?
I never back down
You better have some backup
'Cause I never back down
Nigga, if you act up,
I've gotta put the smack down
Beef's gonna be bad, bro
I give a nigga mad cow
Snap you like...
Before you even get to tap out
And I'll tell you what I'mma do,
Right before I bash out
Choke you till you turn blue
Make you fucking pass out
Put that money up
Pull that fucking cash out
You'll be bloodied up
This is gonna be your last bout
Got knuckle game
Put hands and feet on you
I'm a producer
'Cause all I'mma do is beat on you
I'mma kick you in your fucking chest
Like this is chess
In three moves or less
My guns are working
but they about to get fired
I'm looking for a job,
I'm a hitman for hire
Who wanna come get murdered
in this ring of fire?
Hope you believe in God
'Cause I'mma send you higher
Do you back down?
I don't back down
I never back down
Tell me, do you back down?
I don't back down
Do you back down?
I never back down
Tell me, do you back down?
I don't back down
Do you back down?
I never back down
Tell me, do you back down?
I don't back down
Do you back down?
I never back down
I don't back down,
I fight back
Don't go nowhere, I'll be right back
I came right back
Hit 'em with the right jab
Yeah, we fight back,
Nigga, we don't back down
We tap their jaws and wrap in gauze
Bloody fists
Yo, let me crack his jaw
We tap their jaws and wrap in gauze
Bloody fists
Yo, let me crack his jaw
Overhand rights, a couple uppercuts
Left to the mid-section
His leg buckles up
Put on the black gloves,
It's time to knuckle up
Put 'em in the ring
and watch me fuck 'em up
Fucking with me
That's a huge mistake
Heavyweights get knocked out
by cruiserweights
Got 'em scared to death,
Got 'em losin' weight
Death is the prize that the loser takes
Do you back down?
I don't back down
I never back down
Tell me, do you back down?
I don't back down
Do you back down?
I never back down
Tell me, do you back down?
I don't back down
Do you back down?
I never back down
Tell me, do you back down?
I don't back down
Back down, back down
Someone needs to stop Clearway Law.
Public shouldn't leave reviews for lawyers.