Someone needs to stop Clearway Law.
Public shouldn't leave reviews for lawyers.
What's he doing?
No!
Stop!
Fire!
She's a-sinking already!
Board! Before she takes
her booty with her!
It's an 'eavy one, Captain.
Oddio.
It's a war chest, I imagine,
filled with Spanish doubloons.
Eh?
What the hell is it?
It's the holy grail.
Don't be ridiculous, Smee.
idiota. There's no such thing.
All right,
it's Aladdin's lamp, then.
There's something inside it.
Aaah!
What's the matter?
It's possessed!
The damn thing's got
a ghost inside it!
Or a genie!
Maybe it'll grant us
a wish or two.
It's not of this world.
Help!
Let me at him!
- I'm gonna kill him!
- Come on, you little runt!
Aah! Help!
Come on, you mutt!
- Help!
- Little runt!
-
- Let me at him!
That's us.
Get him! Get him!
Grab him!
Oi! He's got my watch!
They're thieves!
Thieves!
A gold watch.
Blimey, Tootles.
- Ohh.
-  You're an artist.
What now?
What's up, Twins?
Slightly's gone
and got himself nicked.
Any instructions from Peter?
No, he's--he's gone quiet.
That's Beer Barrel Bertie.
We don't have no plans
for Beer Barrel Bertie... do we?
Wait. Look over there.
Excuse me.
Officer, you, er, dropped this.
What? Impossible.
Must have a buckle loose.
- And, er, you dropped this.
- That's my whistle! Well, how did you--
It was down there, with your keys.
My keys!
Go. Go!
He's got the blighter loose!
- You there!
- Come here!
Whoa!
Yes!
Don't watch his sword, Stevens,
watch his eyes!
Remember, a man's intent
is in his eyes!
Sometimes smaller is smarter.
Jimmy's gonna love this.
Well done, Peter.
I've got a nice job for you boys.
- How nice?
- Harbottle's Antiques.
- Are you mad?
- You're ready.
- That place is tighter than the tower.
- We'll get nicked for sure.
Sorry, Jimmy,
too dangerous.
I think it's a brilliant idea.
Harbottle's has two doors,
as I remember--
one at the front and one at the back
leading to an alley.
There is a night guard,
of course,
and the windows
are sealed shut, but...
there are other ways in
if you're small and cunning.
If we get nicked, it won't be
the orphanage they throw us in,
it'll be the clink.
We wouldn't last a week.
Weren't you at the bottom of Hackney Canal
when Jimmy found you?
Tied in a sack, with stones
around your wrist and ankles.
Jimmy's rescued every one of you.
He's pulled you from
the workhouses and asylums.
He's given you a home.
Food in your belly
and shoes on your feet.
Isn't it time we paid him back?
Harbottle's Antiques.
All who's with me,
raise your right hand.
A word in your ear, Peter.
Curly's right.
This one's too dangerous.
- But it's worth it.
- How do you know?
You wouldn't risk it otherwise.
You're growing up quickly, Peter,
but you still have a lot to learn.
Do you want to do this job or not?
Oh, I want to do it, all right--
it's what I've been waiting for.
Might get me back where I belong.
But I've changed my mind.
I'm going it alone on this one.
You don't trust me.
I don't want you to get nicked.
- I'll get us in and out safe.
- No. This one's mine.
Things will be different
when you're older.
Licorice?
What do you think of accounting?
What?
Bookkeeping.
I had an uncle in Pinner
who made bucketloads
from just adding things up.
Sounds a bit dull, Fox.
He had a good life.
Married a draper's daughter
from Bexleyheath.
Cooh. Brenda Fitzwilliam.
Nice smile.
Fox, what are you talking about?
The future.
Something to look forward to.
What about you, Peter?
You ever think of the future?
I'm stickin' with Jimmy.
If you're not careful,
you'll grow up to be just like him.
And what's wrong with that?
- It's a dangerous life.
- Adventurous, you mean.
You want to spend the rest of your days
in a shoebox, fine.
But I want more.
Now, Jimmy's going places,
and so am I.
One day we'll be partners.
Believe me, that day can't...
...can't come soon enough.
- Come on, we got a job to do.
- What? Job?
Yeah, Harbottle's Antiques.
You remember?
Tonight? Whoa, Jimmy didn't say
anything about doing it tonight.
Jimmy doesn't have to know.
We'll surprise him.
Make it look like an ordinary break-in,
take whatever else you want.
Of course.
And should you be lucky enough
to find the artifact there,
handle it with the utmost care.
Have you considered my terms?
Money's not a problem,
but the other business is more difficult.
I'm afraid it's not negotiable.
My client is using
what influence he has, but--
But what?
Reestablishing your position
in London society
is proving more
troublesome than he thought.
The Granville Club
won't take you back,
and most of the new businessmen
he spoke to want concrete references--
introduction's no longer enough.
Well, if anyone can do it,
Fludd can.
As I said, he's doing his best.
If there's a slip-up,
I don't know you. Understand?
Perfectly.
Penny for the guy, mister?
It's September!
Now get lost!
Ruddy pests!
Penny for the guy!
Where did you spring from?
Come here.
Come on.
Gotcha!
Not bad.
Wow!
Whoa!
Oh...
Oh!
What the hell do you think
you're doing?
- Isn't this what you wanted?
- You know it isn't.
I changed my mind.
I told you I was doing this one alone.
Yeah, but look.
We're in!
Why didn't you tell us, Peter?
- Because you wouldn't have done it.
- So you lied to us.
I wanted to show Jimmy
what we were made of.
- He thought we were too young.
- I am too young.
Fill your bags and wait by the door.
Curly, keep an eye out the back.
Nibs, watch the front.
Sorry, Jimmy.
I just wanted to show you
that I could do it.
If you're going to be
my partner one day,
you must never
go behind my back.
One day? But I'm ready now.
Believe me, you've got
a lot of growing up to do first.
Are you looking for
something in particular, Jimmy?
I'll go and find something
to force it open.
Whoa!
Wha-What is it?
Not bad.
Unh!
It's all your fault, Peter.
If you'd done as Jimmy said
and just--just left it alone...
...then they'd still be here.
You were looking for this,
weren't you, Jimmy?
Who were you working for?
- Where's Jimmy?
- He's out.
When will he be back?
What do you want him for?
What do you want with Jimmy?
Oi, come back!
Why do you follow Jeffries, boy?
- Jimmy didn't send you, did he?
- What do you want with Jimmy?
That's my business.
Where is he?
Just...gone.
What do you mean, gone?
A bomb in Harbottle's.
- He found the orb, didn't he?
- You know what that thing is?
So it was in Harbottle's after all.
- Jimmy was working for you?
- Where is it now
Tell me!
It blew him up and all my crew.
Let him go, Jeffries.
They weren't blown up.
Where are they, then?
Another world, more beautiful
than you can imagine.
But I can get them back
if you tell me where the orb is.
- How?
- It's a portal.
A kind of door.
And the slightest knock
will activate it.
But we must hurry. Heavens, Jeffries, if I'd
have known it was at Harbottle's for sure,
I'd have engaged
someone more diligent--
- Hey!
- After him!
Hurry, Jeffries!
A door...
to another world.
The slightest knock, eh?
Wha--What a weird-looking place.
But you're in there somewhere.
Ain't ya, Jimmy?
Open up, Peter!
We can help you!
Help me?
When has a toff ever helped
the likes of me?
I got him into this...
I'm gonna get him out.
Hello?
Where am I?
Come on, where are you?
There you are.
Lots of smoke...
but no flames.
- Give me that.
- No!
We've landed in hell, I tell you.
Soon, Lucifer's demons will rise up
to record our sins
and throw us down there
into the everlasting fire of damnation,
where we will burn in agony
for all eternity.
Jimmy!
Fox!
Hear that?
They're headed this way.
Kill the smoke.
Hide! Quickly!
Buongiorno, amico.
Got any goodies?
-  Leave us alone!
Let me go!
- Go.
-  Just get off!
Found another five little ones!
Get off me!
- Get off!
- Let me go!
Jimmy?
Tootles.
Pirates!
We're coming aboard!
Going aboard!
- Aaah!
- Aahh!
Fox!
Where did you spring from?
You have no idea
how glad I am to see you.
- Where the hell have we landed?
- I have no idea. All I know is...
we're not in Shoreditch anymore.
It was that thing...
in Harbottle's, wasn't it?
I'm sorry, Fox.
It's all my fault.
We should never have broken
into Harbottle's in the first place.
If Curly was here,
he'd string you up.
I'll make good.
I'll get them off that ship
and home safe.
Ship?
A pirate ship.
It's a bloody nightmare.
Weird crocs, spooky woods--
now pirates!
What's next?
Swarms of flying beasties?
What's that?
Ohh, what now?
Run!
Get 'em off!
On your feet!
We've gotta stay ahead of the swarm,
otherwise we're dead!
Injuns!
What year do ya come from?
1906.
Ooh, that'll make me...
163 next October.
263, you mean.
Ooh, maybe I can start thinking
about settling down.
Nice cottage on Venus.
From the 1700s.
Ho0s that possible?
Cod liver oil, stewed prunes,
and regular trips up the rigging.
Good for ya.
And what are you good for,
I wonder?
It still works.
Tick-tock.
Tick-tock, tick-tock.
Tick-tock,
tick-tock.
Tick-tock, tick-tock!
Did you bring anything else
with you, did ya?
Oh, sugared almonds, perhaps?
- Just what you see.
- Pity!
How sweet.
He carries a picture
of his true love.
What is this place?
Can't you tell?
It's heaven.
Or hell!
Depending on your point of view.
See? Lucifer's demons.
What shall we do with them?
Hmm?
Well, I want the English lads.
- What for?
- They look so tender.
I bet they'd taste good
in a stew.
My boys stay with me.
He's a bold one, no?
Well, he's not
a bad-looking wag.
- Eh?
- Hmm.
Maybe I could find a use for him
in my cabin.
Good idea!
Maybe I need a rest.
Just playing with you,
Starkey.
I'm just playing with ya.
- Throw him to the crocs!
-
Smee, you can keep the boys.
Oh, thank you, ma'am.
You won't be sorry.
I've got some coriander seeds
and some ginger saved.
Aaah!
Right. Now,
you'd better come with me.
- You're not gonna like this next bit.
- Jimmy!
Come on.
Aaaah!
My boys...
stay with me.
Wait.
I want to watch.
You asked what I was good for. Well,
as you can see, I'm handy with a blade.
Who are ya?
My friends call me Jimmy.
"Jimmy."
But the name's Hook.
James Hook.
I'm sorry for this, but...
entrance to our village is secret.
What are you gonna do with us?
Dinner.
You're gonna eat us?!
Why? Do you taste good?
Come. You must be hungry.
What's this meat?
Xaw.
Are we in America?
Not anymore.
But you're Indians.
We are the Kaw,
people of the raven.
We have become part
of this world now.
Do you know the way
back to London?
The chief.
Chasing tree spirits is hungry work.
He asks if you want to join our tribe.
Thank you, but, um, once we've
finished dinner we'll be on our way.
We saved you before--
we may not be there
to save you again.
We're very grateful, but we have to
rescue our friends from pirates.
Where are we?
We call this Geih Gwaay.
Neverland.
Why?
Because we never age here.
You might not believe this,
but I am 130 years old.
Innu's son is 81.
The chief's daughter.
She is called Aaya K'aang.
"Tiger Lily" in your language.
She is named this because she is
as wild as she is beautiful.
Don't get any ideas
because she is almost 100 years old.
You've left me
with a bit of a problem.
Three of my best men dead.
One was my personal bodyguard.
- It was self-defense.
- That's not the point.
I can't get replacements here.
No?
You're not in London now,
Hook.
Do you notice anything
unusual out there?
I don't follow.
Orion.
Polaris.
- Maybe you can point to the pole star.
- Astronomy's not my best suit.
Well, if it was, you'd notice
that there isn't a pole star.
And Orion is over there--
in the wrong place.
Ho0s that possible?
Planet earth is in a different galaxy...
far, far away.
There's no way back.
Are you sure?
I've had almost 200 years
to work it out.
We've gotta fatten you up,
and no mistake.
Any bread and jam?
Hmm. I've got cream cakes,
s¤eetmeats, pickled herring,
and crystallized dates.
But sadly, no bread and jam,
your highness.
We're stuck here,
but it needn't be all bad.
This planet has something...
special to offer.
It's mined by creatures of this world.
The Indians call them tree spirits.
This...is the stuff
that makes them fly.
Indians?
We're not the only ones
from our world, Hook.
A year ago I captured one of them.
He was carrying this mineral,
and under torture,
he told me of its power.
It'll make you feel more alive,
more complete,
than you've ever felt--
it'll light you up from inside.
Literally turn you into...
a god.
And give you the power...
to fly.
Incredible.
As you can see, it's unstable.
But that's only because
I don't know how to use it yet.
Besides, I only have enough
for this magic trick.
We need more, lots more.
The only problem is,
we can't get near the tree spirits.
They're protected
by the Kaw mountains on one side
and the savages on the other.
Join me, Hook.
I badly need fresh blood,
and you bring knowledge
from a modern world.
You help me defeat the savages,
and together we can rule
Neverland like gods...
and turn this endless purgatory
into an eternal paradise.
Gods?
Yes...
gods.
What are you doing up here,
Starkey?
Don't the captain need you tonight?
Leave me alone!
Oh, dear.
There must be a way down.
We will build you
and your friend a hut.
Thank you.
Why live up here?
To be near the tree spirits.
That is their city.
We protect them from the pirates.
How do you get down to the sea
from here?
The same way you were brought in,
through a secret passage
through those mountains.
Will you show me?
If you try to rescue your friends,
the pirates will capture and torture you
until you show them
the mountain passage.
But I can't just sit on my hands.
I'm the one that got them into this mess,
I've got to find a way
to get them home and safe.
There is no way home.
What?
No.
There is a way back.
There must be.
Fox!
Fox, I have a plan.
- For what?
- To get us out of here
and onto that ship.
Come on.
See what they're carrying?
Fishing nets.
So?
Have you seen any fishing
waters around here?
No.
Exactly.
I don't understand.
That's how we're gonna find
the secret passage through the mountains.
Come on.
My God!
Look at the size of it!
Grab on to that.
Quick, grab on to it.
Shh! Quiet.
Do you see Jimmy?
No. How are we gonna
get 'em out, Peter?
They're surrounded by pirates.
Yeah, but sleeping pirates.
Drunk, sleeping pirates.
Peter, you're here!
Peter!
Shh. Shh.
Come on.
I'm not going anywhere with you.
- Shut it, Curly. He's here to help.
- Yeah, well, we don't need his help.
Yeah, he's the one who got us
into this mess in the first place.
Well, I'm the one
that's getting you out.
You want to stay, fine.
You want to live,
follow us.
Did I ever tell you
my recipe for turtle soup?
Please, Smee.
Shh!
Hey...
Something, she is not right.
What?
I'm going to go look around.
I wouldn't do that if I was you,
not up there in Bonny's cabin.
Thank you.
Where's Jimmy?
The captain's quarters.
- Are you sure?
- She's got a shine for him.
"She"?
- Where you goin', Peter?
- To get Jimmy.
But we're all here. We can
make a clean getaway if we go now.
I'm not going without Jimmy.
Where's Jimmy?
Peter! How did you get here?
Get your clothes on.
I've got a canoe waiting below.
Put the pistol down, Peter.
Bonny's a friend.
- Bonny?
- How many more in your litter, Hook?
Let me speak to him.
I didn't know he was here.
- Give me the gun, Peter.
-
-  Wait, Starkey.
- Peter, give me the gun!
Tell him to put his away first!
Listen to me, Peter.
Captain Bonny and her men are on our side.
She's assured me that
the boys will be well looked after.
The Indians say they're crazy.
- Indians?
- He's with the savages.
Trust me, Peter,
they're anything but crazy.
These are our people. It's a dangerous
place, they can help us survive.
- Do you want to stay here? With her?
- We've nowhere else to go.
We can stay with the Indians
until we find a way home.
- They'll scalp and skin the lot of ya.
- No, they won't! They're good people!
- How do you know?
- They're kind!
Listen to me, Peter.
I'm staying here.
If you want to stick with me,
give me the gun.
I don't trust them, Jimmy.
So trust me.
Give me the gun.
Come on!
Leave him be.
Hook!
Leave it.
You little rat!
You... piccolo ratto!
Your boys are gone, Smee.
But I captured this one.
He's not one of my boys!
Hook - he had him working
behind our backs.
What did you do with my boys?!
Leave him be! He's just a boy!
He doesn't know what he's doing.
I'm gonna keelhaul him if he don't tell me
what he's done with my boys!
Where are the others, Peter? Hm?
We must all stick together.
Not here.
Not with these crazies.
Shh shh shh.
You're safe with me.
Now let's go inside, get something to eat
and forget this foolishness.
Hmm?
Peter!
Get back here!
Come back here!
Aaaah!
Unhand me!
Where is he?
Where are you?
Aha!
Fox!
Run! Run, Fox!
There!
Quick! Quick, hurry!
Come on, come on!
Quick!
Row faster!
Quickly! Quickly! Faster!
Quickly!
Peter!
- Over here, Peter!
- Come on!
- Come on! Let's go!
- But Fox is up there!
He came back for you.
-  Jump!
Jump! If you jump now,
you'll make the canoe.
Jump, Fox!
Unhh!
Fox.
Fox!
Peter!
Peter...
We trusted you,
gave you the freedom of our village.
And you abused that trust.
Stole two canoes
and used the mountain passage
without our consent.
I should punish you,
but in light of your loss,
I will be lenient this time.
I want to find them.
Things have come a long way
since I terrorized the Spanish Main.
What else is new?
Flying machines?
Where is this Indian settlement?
You would choose the boys over me?
I'm responsible for them,
I brought them here.
- They look up to me.
- What will you do when you find them?
They're clever.
Trained in the streets, pickpockets.
They could be useful to us,
help us find the mineral dust.
"Us"?
I've never met anyone like you.
And what about her?
You forgotten already?
She passed away many years ago.
But you still carry her portrait.
She had hold of me once.
Now I have you.
I'll give you what you want,
Hook,
but only if you give me what I want.
There is no "us."
Understand?
I'll let you live because
I want to know what you know--
all 200 years of it.
You lied to us.
We never should have
broken into Harbottle's.
- You were just showing off to Jimmy.
- And now we're stuck here.
- Wherever "here" is.
- And you got Fox killed.
- Curly!
- We were all in that canoe.
All right? We could have all got away,
but he had to go back for Jimmy.
What's the point of rubbing it in?
Curly's right.
I got Fox killed.
No, no, no, no.
It should go...
At the end, up, not down.
You know this tune?
Come.
Where did you see this?
In here.
A dream.
The same dream every night.
You have the dream too,
don't you?
Uh-huh.
That music, it's the sound
of tree spirit wings.
He's holding the orb,
isn't he?
That isn't quite right.
The peaks were different in my dream.
Draw it.
It's something like--
No.
Can I try?
Something like this?
Do you have the dream too?
No. But I hunt and fish.
We call that Bull Mountain.
We've never been there.
It's too far away.
But we can see it on a clear day
when we pass the outer islands.
So the hooded man was in Neverland.
- Why do we have the same dream?
- How did you get to Neverland?
- I hit the orb with my dagger.
- Me too, with the staff.
I hit it so hard I brought
the whole tribe with me.
Perhaps part of its great power
enters those who strike it.
Do you think the hooded man
is still there?
How do I get to this island?
- I'm coming with you.
- No, Toots. It's too dangerous.
I don't care.
But I do.
I've done enough damage.
Look, it's just a dream. It'll probably turn out
to be a wild-goose chase,
but if I do find a way home,
I'll be back for you and the others, okay?
What do I tell them?
To sit tight and wait for me.
And that I promise I'll do everything I can
to get them home safe.
We'll find
the mineral dust here,
in the tree spirit colony.
But the problem is,
it's within the Kaw territory.
The mountains from the north
to the east are impregnable,
and tall cliffs line the Kaw.
So there's no way through.
- How do the Indians get in and out?
- We don't know.
We can watch them cook on their campfires
from across a narrow ravine,
but if we try to rope across
they will pick us off
like gulls on a gaff rig.
They hunt on this part of the island,
going back and forth
as if these mountains
weren't even there.
Any ideas?
Perhaps we should watch them
a little more closely.
The chief's daughter
is a prize indeed.
She'll tell us how to get into
the tree spirit colony.
I'll send some men to cut them off.
No. Sometimes smaller is smarter.
They're up to something.
L¤t's find out what first.
He was standing on a hill
in front of the mountain.
There must be
a hundred hills here.
Let's try that one.
I find it!
The prints go this way.
Right, then. Let's go.
Aaya) Your family back home
must be very worried about you.
I don't have a family.
My mother died when I was three
and I never knew my father.
So I was brought up in a workhouse.
Is that where you met your friends?
Nah.
No, I was the only kid there.
"Punchbag", they called me.
Jimmy fished me out.
He was visiting one day
and saw me getting a kicking.
He was a good man once.
The best.
He saved my life, but...
that pirate turned his head.
Recognize anything?
It wasn't as overgrown
in my dream.
Let's find a place to rest.
It'll be dark soon.
Wait!
It's the tree spirit from my dream!
Come on! She might lead us
to the hooded man!
See her?
- No.
- She's too fast.
I've never seen
a tree spirit glow like that.
She's really beautiful.
Oh, no.
What?
The sun's coming up.
Now we're never gonna find her.
I've never seen anything like this.
We've got to find a way in.
He must be in there.
How are you at climbing?
It's a mile high.
Then we better get started.
It's incredible.
Do you see anyone
down there?
No.
Come on. Down is sometimes
harder than up.
Where is everyone?
They'll come to us.
How do you know?
Anyone clever enough
to make all this
already knows we're here.
That's right.
You. You're the hooded man!
Hello, Peter.
Can you get us home?
Of course.
Now that I'm here,
everything shall find its proper place.
You have the orb?
In a manner of speaking.
Hmm?
Finally, after almost 350 years,
it's back where it belongs.
Now we can start to bring
the elite of our world here to my utopia.
So how will you get us back?
Patience, young friend.
- You made all this?
- Mm-hm.
It's easier than it looks.
A simple growth solution
which compels the forest to grow...
in the way that I want it to grow.
- Who are you?
- My apologies.
My name is Dr. Richard Fludd.
Alchemist to Her Majesty
Queen Elizabeth the First.
What?
Hard to believe, I know,
but I am almost 400 years old.
Come, I'll show you my life's work.
It's only a few hours old.
I was engaged in the search
for the philosopher's stone,
the elixir believed to grant
everlasting life.
There were others like me,
of course,
but they were all trying
to make a tangible substance
which could be
consumed in some way.
What I discovered was that
the philosopher's stone
cannot be made--
it has to be trapped.
You see, it's a form of cosmic energy
which lives at the very
center of the universe...
where its four corners meet.
This is the shape
of the universe.
And here...
at its center...
is this tiny planet.
- Neverland.
- Mmm.
And because it lives at the farthest
reaches of the universe,
as well as at its center,
time stands still
for all those who come here.
So how do we get back?
Ah.
When I first arrived on this planet,
I was stuck here,
because, of course, the orb
that I'd made in London remained there.
But as you know,
the harder you strike the orb,
the more it...
So thankfully, most of
the contents of my laboratory
traveled with me, and in time,
I was able to build a twin.
I activated it here in Neverland
with the power from two meteors.
It's just like the other one.
I call her Tinker Bell...
because of the beautiful sound
her wings make through the air.
When she saw me harnessing
the astral energy of two meteors,
she thought I was in trouble
and tried to save me.
That's my dream.
All who activate the orb
are imprinted with that memory.
Why does she glow so bright?
Well, much of that astral energy
is trapped inside her.
Hmm.
Come.
We'll take the orb below.
There's an open area
where I can send you both back.
No. Not yet.
I've got to find my friends.
Seems I have more guests.
Incredible.
What's it all for?
Mi sento il diavolo.
Attenzione.
There could be demons lurking
behind these walls.
No. Only me.
That's the man in my dream.
Fludd.
You know him?
Dr. Fludd.
Where's Peter?
Please lay down your weapons.
This is a sanctuary.
You're in no danger here.
Why such a big city
forjust one man?
It will soon be filled
with the elite of our world--
artists, statesmen, philosophers.
What the hell for?
Think what great minds can achieve
if they have the rest of eternity to study.
- Can you help us get back to London?
- Yes.
Did you send Peter back already?
Not yet.
Then where is he?
As I said, this is a sanctuary.
All who enter here
are granted my protection.
If you lay down your weapons,
I can start to prepare your return.
I don't want to go back.
No?
Who wants to return
to the Caribbean?
Do you think we'd still strike terror
into men's hearts?
Tell them, Hook.
Tell them how it's changed.
We wouldn't last a week.
And if we did, we'd grow old,
Quickly, in a world that
we no longer understand.
Is that what you want?
- No, of course not.
-  No!
But we don't want legions
of pompous braggarts coming here either
with their fancy new weapons,
telling us how to live our lives, no.
Now, you tell me how it's done.
Is there a door?
Or another sphere like the one
that brought us here?
If you don't want to use it,
why do you care?
Because, Dr. Fludd...
I want to police it.
I won't allow that to happen.
I won't tolerate violence.
Lay down your weapons.
Gunpowder and lead
have no place here.
Leave now,
and your lives will be spared!
Shoot them!
Shoot them all!
You are dealing with forces
beyond your understanding.
Run! Run for your lives!
Peter!
Peter, wait!
I need to talk to you!
Peter! Over here.
Make your way
for the door, men!
This way!
Dr. Fludd?
It took me almost a century
to grow my city.
Look how quickly it disappears.
Where's Aaya?
I don't know.
Try and save the orb. I'll face them here.
Go, go, go. Go! Go!
Aaaah!
I don't want to hurt you, Fludd,
I just want to see Peter safe.
Engaging you, Hook,
was a terrible mistake.
The glass sphere, Fludd.
Where is it?
I'd rather burn in hell.
You're responsible for this!
No!
Peter!
Move!
Aaya! Where are you, Aaya?!
Going back?
- You can't have it.
- What makes you think I want it?
I heard your girlfriend.
You don't want people going back.
That doesn't mean you, Peter.
I'll make sure you get back safely.
Then let me take it back to my crew.
I have a better idea.
Why don't they come to us?
Us? Who's "us"?
The pirates?!
Because they will kill them!
Just like they--
Just like they killed Fox.
That was a terrible mistake.
I tried to stop it.
You let it happen!
You've become one of them!
Listen to me, Peter.
There's something in this world
that will completely change
our lives in London,
make us more powerful
than you can ever imagine.
And Bonny and her men
can help us find it.
She's turned your head,
Jimmy.
Give me that knife.
I taught you too well.
I swear, Peter,
I will run you through
if you don't calm down
and let me explain what I found here!
You don't care about me.
You just want that woman!
You couldn't be more wrong.
I didn't pull you out of that workhouse
because I took pity on you, Peter--
I did it because of the debt I owed...
to your mother.
You--You knew my mother?
Very well.
This is my mother?
I vowed to bring you up
and rear you as my own.
And I won't give up on you now.
This is her watch?
It was your father's.
I hate to break up such a touching reunion,
but we have to get out of here.
Give me another minute
with him, Liz.
There is no time.
The place is a tinderbox.
It's even more beautiful
than I remember.
No! No!
Peter!
Hey, you! Hey, you! Wait!
Ha! Come on!
Leave him be!
- Where is the squaw?!
- Tell them, Peter.
I wouldn't tell your girlfriend
the time of day!
I will give you one last chance
to redeem yourself.
Stop!
Let him live...
and I will tell you
what you want to know.
And what is that?
How to get into
the tree spirit colony...
and the secret of the mineral dust.
No, Aaya! Run!
Agghh!
And you'll do this...
just to keep him alive?
Only if you set him free.
Aaya, run!
Tie her up.
Come on, Aaya! Run!
-  Peter!
- No!
No! No! No!
There.
I set him free.
Now let's get out of here.
Dear God.
Now I see why you were
so protective of the boy.
But you mustn't brood, Hook.
The stars have finally shifted
in our favor.
When Starkey's finished
with the chief's daughter...
oh, she'll tell us whatever
we need to know.
No, she won't talk. Not now.
Well, Starkey's never let me down.
This is the tree spirit
colony here, right?
Surrounded by
impregnable mountains.
What about this narrow ravine
by the Kaw settlement?
Fifty feet wide.
We can rope across.
Nope.
We'd be sitting ducks.
Not if we bring
that princess hostage.
That's a big risk.
A risk worth taking.
We set off at first light.
Ready ten of your best men.
I am captain.
I will decide what's best.
You listen to me!
Now that I have the orb,
I intend to return to London,
but not before I have the power
of the mineral dust
coursing through my veins.
I will be a god amongst men,
and rule over the same
London society
that banished me to the fringes
of the East End.
Countless scores will be settled.
You have a choice, Liz.
Stand with me and have all the thrills
of the modern world at your fingertips,
or remain here and rule over
the living dead for the rest of eternity.
Now you are like us.
- Where am I?
- My kingdom.
- You speak English?
- No. I'm using my mind, Peter.
Thoughts have no language.
But the mineral dust gives you
the power to hear our people.
- What happened to Aaya?
- The pirates have her.
Easy, Peter.
The elders have closed your wound,
but it's not yet healed.
- That will take many days.
- I'm so cold.
Your clothes are ready,
repaired with silk from our farms.
Come. You must go before
the three elders
who rule our kingdom.
Your kind pose
a great threat to our world.
So we ask for your help.
Find the magic orb
and bring it to us.
We will use it
to send home your kind.
Your new powers will help
in this endeavor.
Powers?
Close your eyes, Peter.
Breathe softly.
Clear your mind.
Imagine you're floating
in a warm sea,
drifting safely,
and you're blissfully happy...
so happy you don't even feel
the water under you,
just a warm breeze
holding you up...
up...
Aaah! Aaaah!
Oh, my--aaaah!
No, Peter!
You must stay relaxed!
Close your eyes again.
Peter, breathe normally.
Trust in yourself.
Good! Clear your mind.
Picture the clouds around you,
feel the wind on your face.
The wind is your friend, Peter,
the wind carries you.
Now open your eyes.
How is it happening?
You are doing it, Peter.
The mineral dust gives you the power,
but you must control it.
- How
- With your heart.
It responds to the way you feel,
but if you doubt yourself,
it will falter.
Look down, Peter.
Our world suffers.
Help us.
Get us the magic orb
so we can stop this brutality.
- Why me?
- You still have an innocent heart, Peter.
It's a quality we share,
and trust.
Crossing that ravine
is a foolish waste of time.
It's likely to get us all killed!
Your courage has always impressed,
Starkey.
The ravine is a death trap.
So stay here!
Darn your socks!
What has happened to you, Liz?
Hmm?
Ahem!
You're wearing
my best suit of clothes.
Not anymore.
I should have dropped you
when I had the chance.
Then drop me now.
Hmm.
That's a coward's weapon.
I'd prefer it if you killed me
with a sword.
Here.
You can use mine.
Look at your men!
Do you see any of them
run to your defense?
Hmm?
Two hundred years
on the same boat,
and no one cares
if you live or die.
You're mine now.
You understand?
This is amazing!
Ha ha ha! Whoa!
Steady, Peter!
Let the wind guide you.
Peter! Lean into the breeze!
-
- You're going too fast!
Remember,
short, fast breaths.
Aaah! Aaaah!
Aah aaah!
Look out!
Aaah...whoa!
Ohh!
Peter, are you all right?
Peter.
Boo!
Got ya.
I can't teach you
if you act like a child.
Yeah, but I thought that's what
you liked about me.
You need to rest.
Your wound will take
many days to heal.
I've got to go now, Tink.
Rescue Aaya and get back to my crew.
Your crew?
My friends. They're the ones
I'll get home first once I've found the orb.
You're not ready, Peter.
The sun's going down.
We can't rope across in the dark.
We'd better stop for the night.
If I do find a way home,
I'll be back for you and the others.
So how do we get back?
Tie her up!
- Now we're stuck here!
- Wherever "here" is.
Aaya, run!
Bloody hell.
Ooh, my God! Sweet mother of--
- What do you want here, specter?
- The alchemist's glass orb.
Fetch it--
I will spare your life.
I don't know where it is.
None of us do.
The captain hid it
somewhere on shore.
If you don't own up, pirate,
you'll be wearing your tonsils
for earrings!
Now, listen, they wouldn't
bring it onboard,
it's too sensitive, so they buried it
somewhere on Bull Island.
"They"?
Yeah. Captain Bonny
and Master Hook.
Well, you must have some idea
where it is.
They took it out
in the middle of the night.
I swear to you, specter,
they are the only ones
that know where it is.
Very well.
Fetch the chief's daughter,
and I will leave you in peace.
Oh, God.
Keep moving, men!
This is the ravine here!
Yes, but the Indian village
is further along.
Well, this looks unguarded.
If we cross here,
we can go around them.
It's unguarded because the web
was made by man-eating spiders.
Then we should cross with care!
I'd rather face a few spiders
than a hundred angry braves.
Aaah!
Pull her up!
I'm trying.
Aah!
Come over and help me!
Aaah!
Aaaah!
How did you do that?
What's wrong?
I'm fine. I'm fine.
- I'm fine.
- The mineral dust.
It's in your skin.
Wait here.
I'll come back for you
and we'll climb up together.
Is it really you?
Back from the dead.
How did you survive?
I have friends in high places.
Santa Madonna!
The mineral dust--
he's covered in it!
You were saved
by the tree spirits?
And I see you've become
one of them.
Fludd's orb, Jimmy--
where did you hide it?
I can't tell you here.
Hurting me won't help, Peter.
You're right.
But hurting your girlfriend might.
- You're not a murderer, Peter!
- Aaaah!
Perhaps I've changed!
Aaaah! Aah!
All I have to do is cut the rope,
and down you go.
Now, I know it's on Bull Island...
but where?
I said where?!
Wait! Don't pull her up yet.
He'll cut the rope.
Stop!
Aah!
Well? What's it to be, Jimmy?
Pull her up now!
We have to take him with us.
He knows the secret of the mineral dust.
See, I knew it was possible
to take their power.
Oh...
Wake up, boy.
Wake up.
There's more than the flying,
isn't there?
Hmm?
The power lives inside you,
doesn't it?
It nourishes you from inside.
Now, you tell me what that's like.
Wake up.
Wake up. How did you do it?
What did you do?
What did you do?!
He's getting weaker.
His wound has opened up.
I've tried to dress it, but...
I want it. I want it!
We're finished, Hook.
I have lost eleven men
since you arrived.
And for what?
A wild-goose chase to nowhere!
- Peter will help us now.
- He probably won't even survive the night.
You have worked your charm on me
for the last time, Hook!
No!
Starkey!
Keep him alive...
till I've decided my next move.
Jimmy took him back
to the pirate ship?
I think so.
I'm sorry.
He's back with the pirates.
They saved him from the spider,
so they must have wanted him alive.
A gift.
I'm not wearing that.
Me neither.
Why not? They're tougher
than our old clothes.
We have to get Peter out--
like he got us out.
Don't be daft.
Have you forgotten what he did to Fox?
And you want the same
to happen to Peter?
Let's show a little bottle.
They're two peas in a pod,
if you ask me.
Peter always wanted to stand
shoulder to shoulder with Jimmy.
Now he's got his wish.
It's not the same
without him.
No. It's a lot safer.
Who's gonna take his place?
You?
- We'd be better off.
- You don't have it in ya.
Oh, we'll see.
Tomorrow I'll lead the croc hunt,
and when I bring one of them beasties in,
the Indians will make me a blood brother,
and then, perhaps,
you'll show me some respect.
You signed up for the croc hunt?
Come on, Curly,
you said you'd do it.
-  Run, Curly!
Boys.
Where's Curly?
¤hal has something to give you.
The first time he faced Xaw,
he was so scared
he ran and didn't return to the village
for many days.
When he did, I told him,
"Fear is good.
Fear is part of us."
But he was too ashamed to listen.
Today you helped Xyhal prove to us
that he has great courage after all.
For this,
he is very grateful.
He wants you to have
his father's bear tooth.
-
- Ohh!
Peter.
Peter, are you okay?
Jimmy?
Shh. Drink.
I'm so sorry, Peter,
I've been a complete fool.
Come on.
Put your arm around me.
I'm taking you home.
Feeling better?
How did we get here?
Berry water.
Not as sweet as it sounds.
I challenged the lads
to a drinking game.
There'll be a few sore heads
this morning.
What happened?
Well, after that, it was easy
to steal a rowing boat and--
No, um...
I mean, what happened to you?
I woke up.
And your lady friend?
She'll have to find someone else
to wrap around her little finger.
I thought I'd lost you, Peter.
And although I hated Bonny
for what she did,
I had nowhere else to go.
I can't deny she had a hold
on me, she's a...
very...
hypnotic woman.
But when I saw you...
alive...
I woke up.
Now all I want to do is
get us home safely...
go back to things as they were.
Hmm?
Ohh.
Here.
It's a bit chewy, but it tastes good
when you're hungry.
Hmm.
What now?
We gather up the lads
and hurry to the caves on Bull Island
before Bonny figures out
where we've gone.
The caves?
A weird place.
A labyrinth.
But the perfect place
to hide the orb.
Are you ready to go home, Peter?
Yeah.
Can you walk?
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah, no, I think so.
Unh! Ow!
- Which way?
- You tell me.
Where are the lads?
This way.
Jenny was the most beautiful woman
I'd ever met.
- How did you meet?
- At the Granville Club.
I was in the arms trade--
respectable, well-off.
She was treading the boards.
Only the best West End theaters,
mind you.
- And my dad?
- He came later.
Stole her away from me.
No hard feelings.
I always knew she was
too good for me.
What was he like?
- Look in the mirror.
- I look like him?
I always thought
you looked like your mother.
Now I see him.
That's because
I'm finally growing up.
What happened to him?
All I know is he died
before you were born.
When I heard, I went looking for Jenny,
tracked her down to the workhouse.
Got there five years too late.
And you wound up
with me instead.
The consolation prize.
When we get back...
it'll be like old times,
won't it, Jimmy?
Working the East End,
you know?
Apart from I won't have to
climb up no rooftops no more--
I can just fly up.
Yes, that'll come in
very handy.
Shh.
There's a scout 50 yards away,
halfway up a tree.
How do you know?
I can feel it.
I can feel a lot of things now.
What else can you do?
Shh.
We'll go this way.
Don't look like much from out here,
but inside it's huge.
And it goes all the way
through the mountains?
It's not as far as you'd think,
but it's dark.
We'll need torches.
No. I'll light the way.
There's a lookout on each end.
- Just one?
- Yeah.
But one can turn into twenty
in a heartbeat,
so I better go talk to him,
tell him why I'm here with a pirate.
Hello.
Peter?
Yeah, yeah, that's right.
I'm Peter.
What are you doing?
No, get off me!
Are you crazy? Stop!
Is this the only scout?
- There's another at the end of the passage.
- No! You can't tell them that!
I'm sorry, Peter.
This way no one gets hurt.
It was all a trick?
It was the only way I could
get you to cooperate.
Like it or not, you're still a child. There are
some things you'll never understand.
- Yeah, like betraying your friends?!
- I just want what you've got!
You've redeemed yourself
in spades, Hook.
Perhaps I was too quick to doubt.
We should hurry.
It'll be clinical, we'll be in and out
before anyone notices.
- I trusted you.
- You've done the right thing, Peter.
Believe me, it'll all turn out for the best,
I promise. Now come on.
It's even more beautiful
than I imagined.
Where are they?
Over there.
Ready, men?
Ready.
- What are they doing?
- It's just something to ward them off.
No.
Now, Starkey!
You're killing them!
They shouldn't come so close!
Then they wouldn't get hurt!
You murderers!
- Get off me! Get off me!
- Keep still!
Where do we find
the mineral dust?
Shh.
Look, we can't undo what we've done,
but once we have what we came for,
we'll disappear back to London.
Don't you see?
The best way to get rid of us
is by telling us what we want to know.
You promise to leave forever?
The mineral.
It's in the rock.
How do we get it out?
You swim through it.
Give me some room.
Where will she come out?
There.
Take him.
Hurry, Hook.
It'll transform you.
It's everything I dreamed of.
What went wrong?
What happened?
I don't know.
She did everything
exactly as I did.
- Except...
- Except what?!
The tree spirits were here then,
singing a strange song.
You're just like your father!
Self-righteous, smug!
And I see through your innocence
just as I saw through his!
What are you talking about?
You think I'd let him
get away with humiliating me?!
Stealing my girl?!
Oh, there were no hard feelings
once I cut him open
like a Christmas goose!
You killed my father!
He had his chance!
It was a fair duel!
So why did you take me?
I loved your mother.
And I saw her in you.
Stupidly thought
I could ease the guilt
by rearing you as my own!
But all I raised was
another one just like him!
Head for the woods!
4,000 years lost
in one night.
I'm sorry. They tricked me.
You wanted to give them
what we gave you--
please the one called Hook,
allowed his greed and ambition
to corrupt your innocent heart.
- I made a mistake.
- A mistake which has cost us dear.
For that, you must pay.
You shall walk for the rest
of eternity without any memory
of who you are, where you came from,
or those you loved.
Your innocence, the innocence
we recognized and trusted,
will be your only guide,
raw and heartless.
Listen carefully.
You will feel great loss,
grief, torture, distress,
heartache, suffering...
Stop!
He can still help us!
This won't accomplish anything!
Let him be!
Peter.
Peter, are you all right?
The alchemist
has given you a great power,
and you use it on your own kind.
I'm sorry.
When I get angry,
I can't control it.
You have broken a sacred covenant,
and are no longer welcome
amongst us.
Peter. Was I too late?
Peter!
Tinker Bell.
Oh...
Ha ha ha! Gibberish,
gibberish, gibberish!
I can speak gibberish too,
you know?
- Peter, are you all right?
- Never better.
Who are your friends?
Why are you in fancy dress?
Is there a party?
-
- Hey!
Let go of me!
How many?
Another two dead
and three wounded.
This is your doing, Hook.
We have been on a slippery slope
ever since you have appeared.
And I have watched you
while you have dragged us
in every direction...
except the right one.
Sent some of our best men
to their deaths.
What is that thing you say?
"Smaller is sometimes
smarter," yes?
I think it's time
we tested this theory.
You see, without you,
we are a smaller group.
But much, much smarter.
I have two shots...
and there are five of you.
Who will it be?
How about you, Starkey?
You could take me...
if you had the guts.
Just because it didn't
turn out how we wanted
doesn't mean we have to give up.
I could get more men here in days,
heavily armed with Gatling guns
and grenades
and fire in their hearts!
Fifty, a hundred,
perhaps a thousand!
We can overrun the Indians
and force the tree spirits
to give up the secret of the mineral dust.
And where will you get
these men from?
I'll go back to London.
Recruit them from the streets.
Believe me, there are many
who would give their right arm
to be shot of
the London gutter forever.
No, no, no, no, you're not
listening to this, are you, men?
You don't fall for this again?
This is just more of his...ehh...lies!
If we let him out of our sight,
you will never see him again.
So come with me.
Eh?
He's the only one who knows
where the alchemist's orb is.
And how to get us back from London.
Join me, Starkey.
Come see what pleasures
the modern world has to offer.
Believe me, you won't
be disappointed.
We can't just leave him down there.
Say we do get him out.
What then?
Run for the hills?
Live in the wild?
- We'd starve.
- Peter wouldn't let that happen.
Peter's ga-ga. He-He lost his marbles
so they threw him in the pit.
And he's a traitor.
He led the pirates
through the mountain passage.
The Indians know
what they're doing, Toots.
Three months back,
Tom McKenna and his gang had me
trapped down a blind alley.
There was four of them
and only one of me.
And they had knives.
"Let's make him suffer,"
said Tom.
I knew I was dead.
I started whistling
our S.O.S. song.
You know, the Marseillaise.
I didn't think any of you
would hear me, but...then...
out of nowhere,
Peter appeared.
"We're in luck, lads," says Tom.
"Two for the price of one."
And...
I looked at Peter,
and he smiled back.
No fear, nothing--
just that cocky smile.
"Go ahead," he says. "Try it.
"And tomorrow fifty snipes
just like us will come
"looking for you."
I didn't know about that.
Peter kept it quiet.
Didn't want to show me up.
Look, we survived the streets
because we stuck together,
and we looked out for each other
even when the odds
were stacked against us.
I thought the rules might work
different here...
but they don't.
Peter.
Get off!
Get off me!
Peter, it's us.
Who are you ugly mugs?
Hold on,
I'll throw you a rope.
You can fly?
What do you want with me,
Indians?
Come on, Peter,
we've got to get out of here.
I'm not going anywhere
until you tell me who you are.
Hey! Get off me!
- Oi!
- Hold him down!
Let's try this one more time.
Your name's Peter.
You grew up in the East End,
and you're the best set-up man
on the street.
If you don't let me go,
my people will come looking for you.
He thinks he's a flipping tree spirit.
Do tree spirits speak English?
Untie me!
I knew this was a bad idea.
Hello, Peter.
I see you've all gone native.
Peter!
Welcome back!
Hurry, lads!
We've got work to do.
We thought it'd be safer higher up.
Where's Aaya?
Home. In the village.
Don't you remember?
She tried to stand up for you,
but they were too angry.
What do we do now, Peter?
You can't get over these mountains,
there's nothing but ice and rock up there.
And you can't go back down
into the forest, so...
you're gonna have to sit tight.
And you?
You know that glass orb
Jimmy found in Harbottle's?
There's one just like it here,
and it can get us all home.
Where is it?
That's the bad news.
Jimmy hid it in some caves
in Bull Island.
But I'm gonna find it
and bring it here.
How?
- What are you doing here?
- I was going to ask you the same question.
Who, Hook?
I don't have to. I'll be shadowing him
the whole way.
What if he can't press-gang
an army off the streets like he says he can?
Then we come home without him.
Once we've passed
this peninsula,
Bull Island should be straight ahead.
Sì.
They're going to the orb,
Peter.
If we sit tight,
they'll take us right to it.
Then what? Snatch it
from under their noses?
No! We wait for them to use it.
Once they're gone,
the orb will be ours.
But then they'll come back to Neverland
with an army and wipe out the Indians.
If we can deliver the orb to the grand elders,
they might forgive us.
But what about the Indians?
The elders will use the orb
to get rid of the pirates.
And imagine,
if he can do what he says he can,
and we show up
with a thousand men and them guns,
and bombs and all----
the Indians won't know what hit 'em.
I have to warn them.
Peter!
- Aaya.
-
Hook and the pirates
are planning to use Fludd's orb
to bring an army to Neverland
and... wipe you out.
So...was it all an act?
You playing a fool?
Of course not.
And what about leading the pirates
to the mountain pass?
Was that you?
They tricked me.
Really?
How?
Listen, we don't have much time.
They're on their way to Bull Island now.
You've got to get everyone together
and stop them before they get there.
I'll try and stall them
somehow, but...
I can't fight them on my own.
Fight them? Why would you
want to fight them?
I thought you were with them.
Did you really think that
we'd get in our boats
and go out into the ocean
so you and your friends could have
a little target practice?
You really think
I'd do that to you?
- What happened?
- We're on our own.
We'll do it your way.
No, no, no,
only as much as they can carry.
I thought it was just
you and me, Starkey.
Then you tell them yourself.
There's not a man here
who doesn't want to visit home.
What if the Indians take the ship
while we're gone?
We'll have nothing to come back to.
Look, once we have control
of Fludd's London orb,
we can come back and forth
as we please.
Everyone will have their turn.
Including you, Mr. Smee.
- I'm not staying!
- And I'm not leaving anyone else in charge.
- Oh, leave--
- Look. I'll bring you back a little treat, okay?
Some--A nice bottle
of rumbullion, perhaps.
And an Eccles cake.
A whole sack.
You're on.
But I'm not going alone, Hook.
Pensi che sia stupido?
You might know what we will
find there--I do not.
Half a dozen men only,
you understand?
I don't care how
you choose them, Starkey,
but any more,
we'll be too conspicuous.
Va bene.
Hear that?
- Hear what?
- That.
Aaaaah!
Get off me! Get off!
What is Peter doing?
We won't hurt you.
You are our friends.
But I need to know
what Peter is planning.
Not a word, Toots.
He came to me a short time ago,
told me that the pirates are planning
to bring an army from your world.
Listen, if Peter is telling the truth,
we are all in terrible danger.
He went to find the orb.
All right? To get us all home.
That's all I know.
Where?
The caves on Bull Island.
Jimmy used to work in the arms trade.
He's got a mate in the Woolwich arsenal
who can get anything for a price.
Grenades...
even poison gas.
- What is this?
- It's spread by the wind.
Won't even see it coming.
It'll choke you to death
before you know it's there.
We don't take children.
We can look after ourselves.
You'll get in the way.
Then I don't need this.
Very well.
Bloody hell.
All hands on deck!
Man the cannon!
Watch your step.
Fire!
Oh, mio dio.
I don't like the look of this.
Twins!
Come on!
All we have to do
is wait until they've gone
and the orb will be ours.
Are you ready?
I'm sorry, Tink.
I can't let this happen.
What?
Oh--oh--aaah!
You've interfered
one time too many.
Help! Help me!
Pull!
Give me that.
Hold still.
Ohh! Unhh!
Where's Hook?!
They're long gone.
You're too late, Indian.
And when they get back,
you're all dead.
Hook's not on the ship.
They're already in the caves!
Look for tracks!
Where are you, you little rat?
We're wasting time.
Let them fight on
in the streets of London.
No!
Where has he gone?
Over there.
Hold your fire!
The cave's not safe!
Come on, Hook.
Let's leave him and go.
Not until we've dealt with Peter.
Otherwise we leave the orb in his hands.
The tracks lead this way.
Hurry!
It looks like they went this way!
Hold your fire! He's mine.
Hold him still!
No, Tink! Get out of there!
-
- Vermin.
Here he comes.
In here! Hide! Hide!
Hey!
Over there! On the ledge!
Tink?
We shouldn't fight, Peter.
This is silly.
Call off the Indians and the lads
so we can join forces.
We were...a team once.
We can join forces again,
only this time it'll be different,
this time we'll be partners.
Isn't that what you always wanted?
Stand with me, Peter--
as my equal, my friend,
and together we'll rule over London.
Peter.
Take my hand, Peter.
You killed my father.
And you lied to me
my whole life!
Be careful!
You might hit Peter!
- Come back down to earth.
- Down to your level!
I'm gonna beat you
without any help!
Be careful!
Quick!
Curly, look out!
Aaaaah!
Arrghhhh!
Ohhh! Ohhh!
Finish me off.
No. I'm not like you.
Come on!
Be a man!
Never.
My father's watch.
Oh, Peter!
Peter!
Enough of this.
Out of my way!
- No!
- Unhh!
Ahhh!
Run! It's coming down!
-  Go!
Peter!
You've got to get out!
Tink?
Run!
Run! Get out of here!
Come on, Peter.
Where's Peter?
It landed in the water...
...I think.
We have to jump.
It's our only chance.
Hmmm.
Hmm.
So, my friend...
...if we get out of this alive,
what will you use for a hand,
Hook?
What?
Is this our home
for the rest of eternity?
What will we do with ourselves?
A gift for your bravery.
Paddles! Thanks.
I've always wanted one of these.
Not just a paddle,
Twins.
There's a canoe to go with them.
Now that the last of the pirates
have been banished
to the Outer Islands,
the sea is safe.
Thank you, Aaya.
What's that noise?
S-Sounds like--
Peter!
Oh!
Hello, lads!
- How did you get out the cave?
- The orb took a bit of a knock.
- You went back to London?
- Yep. And I got you all something.
One of them newfangled
pen knives for you, Slightly.
The Arabian Nights for Mr. Toots.
A Greenwich mountain compass
for you, Nibs.
Curly...
harmonica.
And Foxton's Pocket Encyclopedia
for you, Twins.
Two copies.
And new shoes for everyone.
And the orb?
Buried under a thousand tons
of earth, I expect.
How did you get back, then?
I paid a visit to Fludd's friends.
When they weren't looking,
I borrowed their orb,
and, er, hid it in a part of London
no one would ever think to look.
Why, Peter?
Because I promised a friend
I'd keep the aliens away.
But why did you come back?
Now you're stuck here.
I wasn't gonna leave you snipes
to have all the fun without me.
What fun?
Are you mad?
Neverland is filled with adventures.
We haven't even scratched the surface.
There's a million islands, with a different
adventure on each and every one.
And d'you know what the best part is?
We never have to grow up.
We can do whatever we like,
live by our rules,
with no adults here to cheat us.
This is our world,
pure and fair.
Now, I'm going off
to look for a secret camp.
All who's with me,
raise your right hand
and shout, "Neverland!"
Neverland!
Peter...
look.
Where's your shadow?
Someone needs to stop Clearway Law.
Public shouldn't leave reviews for lawyers.