Someone needs to stop Clearway Law.
Public shouldn't leave reviews for lawyers.
This is madness.
There's only one man I know who's capable of doing this.
The survivor of the Pirate King Gol D. Roger's generation...
Where have you been hiding for the last 20 years?
You lost to Roger and then got apprehended by the marines...
The man who cut off his feet, shook off his shackles, and escaped from prison.
The Golden Lion, Shiki.
This is a warning.
Fire! Fire!
I wish you would've remained just a legend...
Yet, you've resurfaced to take your revenge on this world?
I have to find the guys.
Gomu Gomu No
Rubber Rubber
Fuusen
Balloon
A praying mantis?!
One after another. Seriously, what's wrong with this island?
Bastard, you wanna go?
Gomu Gomu No
Rubber Rubber
PISTOL
That's right, I can't underestimate the animals on this island.
Gear Third
Hone Fuusen
Bone Balloon
Gomu Gomu No
Rubber Rubber
GIGANTO PISTOL
Giant Pistol
That was dangerous.
Shrinking after using this technique is such a pain...
This octopus looks yummy.
I wonder what that sound was...
Who knows... We don't have time for that.
NO!!!
What's wrong?
Now it's ants?!
You're coming for us?
Franky, didn't you run out of fuel?
That's right!
It's coming back.
Just like me.
Are you guys okay?
Now I know why they didn't go for you.
'Cause to them you don't have any substance.
Ah...
Isn't that a bit rude?!
Hanauta Sancho
Three-Verse Humming
Yahaza Giri
Arrow-Notch Cut
Yes, I'm only bones, but that's because I have an interest...
In dieting.
Anyway, what's wrong with this island?
Animals and bugs have evolved to a stage I've never seen before.
They exert far greater strength and intelligence than humans, and rely on that to live.
An island befitting the survival of the fittest.
INP-Fansubs Presents
Swordsman: Roronoa Zoro. Bounty: 120,000,000.
Doctor: Tony Tony Chopper. Bounty: 50.
Archaeologist: Nico Robin. Bounty: 80,000,000.
Shipwright: Franky. Bounty: 44,000,000.
Musician: Brook. Bounty: 33,000,000.
Cook: Sanji. Bounty: 77,000,000.
Sharpshooter: Usopp. Bounty: 30,000,000.
Captain: Monkey D. Luffy. Bounty: 300,000,000.
Navigator: Nami. Bounty: 16,000,000.
Have you reached a decision, Baby-chan?
Hurry up and let me out of here.
What a strong-willed girl.
I have to say I don't dislike that kind of woman.
Can't you do a damn thing about the sound of your footsteps, Dr. Indigo?
What the hell are you trying to say?!
Come to think of it, I have something to show you.
You can talk?!
M-Mom?
It's a freaking gorilla!
Don't look at me.
You're as cold as ice, Baby-chan.
What were we thinking?
One week ago
What about East Blue?
The mysterious disappearance of villages due to menacing attacks.
It appears that many villages in East Blue have disappeared overnight.
Currently, the islands we're from are fine, but I don't know how long it's gonna stay that way.
Luffy, Zoro, Nami, and Usopp were born in East Blue.
I see.
Oh, was Sanji too?
Well, I was born in North Blue, but I was raised in East Blue.
What's that? A relic?
What's that?!
An island...!
Why is that island floating?!
They have a flag.
Is that a vessel?
They have a skull flag! Is it a pirate ship?
A floating island-ship?
This wind...
This course is dangerous, Luffy.
A cyclone is approaching soon!
Really?
I see. Let's inform them as well.
Hey, there's a cyclone coming!
You sure about this?
It seems like he's shouting something.
Are they pirates?
They appear to be.
Hey!
W-What's wrong, Luffy?
Nami!
Isn't that a Tone-dial?!
So that means they've been to a sky-island as well?
It seems like they aren't ordinary folks.
Doesn't matter who they are.
Nami.
They know how to use it.
A cyclone is approaching. Navigate your ship to 9 o'clock.
Navigation team...
No, sir. There's no indication of such a thing.
The reading on the barometer appears to be normal as well.
They are heading in the 9 o'clock direction.
It's coming fast!
Perm?
It's a freaking rain cloud!
Are you kidding me?
Shiki-sama, please direct our course to 9 o'clock!
It's a huge cyclone!
Shiki-sama! Please open the door, Shiki-sama!
Don't ever give me a false forecast again!
Yes, sir!
Nevertheless...
Who is this woman who posses the knowledge to outsmart my best and brightest navigators?
Just now, how did he come down here?
B-Beats me.
I'm Golden Lion Shiki, a pirate.
Anyway, whose voice was it in the tone-dial?
It was me.
So it's you, baby-chan. You have my gratitude.
No problem.
Um, old man, how's that thing floating?
Oh that? It's the result of Fuwa-Fuwa fruit.
Fluffy-Fluffy
I can negate the gravitational pull of things I touch and have full control over them.
Here goes.
Just watch.
What the?
Amazing!
Old man, make me float!
Me too!
I'm afraid not.
I can't levitate any other humans beside myself, nor animals, or any living beings.
What? That's lame.
Boo~ Boo~
Anyway, I'd like to thank you on my own turf.
It's gratitude for saving my life. You'll come, won't you?
Forget it.
We have to go to East Blue.
Luffy!
Hey you, what about adventure?
We have time to do that as much as we want later.
Can you sit still while the folks in our home-towns are in a pinch?
Well... That's...
It's decided.
Are you sure?
I-I see... You're right...
That's good.
That's how it is, so forget about it.
I'm starting to like you guys!
I see... East Blue is your home, eh?
You must be very worried.
Fine, I get it. I'll take you there with my ability.
Are you sure?
Thank you. Old man, you're a good guy!
But of course!
Can you actually do that?
Alright guys, prepare for battle!
You're too hasty!
We're up high!
It feels so good!
Are you guys even mentally prepared to fight?
Good grief, I wish they'd act a little more nervous.
You're one to talk!
I can see something!
This is amazing!
Are they also up here because of your ability?
That's right.
Once I levitate something, it stays levitated in the air.
That island is huge!
We're finally here.
Well then...
This is Merveille!
An island befitting adventure-lovers like you guys!
Play to your heart's content!
DOKUJA
Poisonous Snake
I've got your navigator!
Nami!
Luffy!
Guys!
Shiki-sama!
We have ourselves a newly evolved species.
Take a look.
A guitar?
It's a freaking bird!
You piece of shit!
Hey!
That's the evolution you mentioned?
Yes, it's the type with fortified electricity conduction.
What evolution?
I see...
I'm asking you to join us anyway, so I'll let you in on this.
Originally, this island was crawling with never-before-seen evolved animals.
And it's all thanks to a plant called "IQ."
It stimulates their brain and prompts them to evolve accordingly with their environment.
Knowing that, I collected every single IQ on this island.
We've been living on this island for 20 years, and finally, we've discovered a new kind of drug extracted from IQ!
We call it "SIQ."
Once we inject this into the animals, we can evolve their battle instinct.
If we continue to shoot them with this, we can invoke their atrocious nature.
That's why this island is swarming with these animals!
What a terrible thing to do. What is your goal?
You will know what my goal is...
If you become my nakama.
Like I said, I will never—
You will!
You will one day beg me to allow you to join.
Then, I will allow you to ask me anything you want once you've calmed down.
Because there's always something you'd want to request of your nakama, no?
"Give me this woman!" you said.
She's out of your league, you perverted gorilla!
What a surprise. For a moment, I thought you were my aunt.
Just how many branches of your family tree were made up of gorillas?!
They probably haven't gotten here yet because of the animals.
Nami-swan!
Quiet down.
A bug!
Robin-swan!
I said quiet dow—
A bird!
Nami-swan!
Why the hell are you wasting your energy?
Robin—
SHUT THE HELL UP, WILL YA!!!
I'm gonna fall! I'm gonna die!
That was close!
Up! Up! Up!
Huh?
Sanji-kun!
Concasse
Crush
Damn cat.
Good job. Well done following my instruction!
What now?
Huh?
What the hell are these animals?
Give it a rest!
Thank God we made it.
Chopper, lend her your fur-coat.
You're right... It's pretty cold...
Like hell I could!
You're awake?
Huh?
What were you doing in such a place?
Um... Well...
That's...
Whatever, let's get out of here.
I've been in this place for a few days now, and I'm getting tired of it.
You should be able to get out of the snow in half a day.
What?!
Over there.
See?
Have we been travelling according to your instructions, Zoro?
It's just a coincidence.
My village is just across the river.
Thanks for saving me. My name is Xiao.
Zoro's the name.
My name is Tony Tony Chopper.
The gorilla just talked.
Don't faint!
This island is inhabited?
Have you noticed, Usopp?
Yeah...
This village, has no maidens.
That's what you've noticed?!
Are you awake?
I was surprised. You suddenly fell down from the sky.
I'm glad you're doing well.
Thank you.
Thank you, madam.
Come on, don't call me madam.
And those feathers on your arms?
You mean this?
For some reason, people from the village have these.
Heh...
Is this village short on food?
Everybody is skinny.
That's because all men and maidens are summoned to the royal palace.
The remainder are unable to work, so we just live to manage the day.
Why is that? It sounds horrible.
Well, if we oppose Shiki, it'd spell doom for us.
Shiki?!
That's right. He has complete control over us.
Furthermore...
Hide, you two!
Ouch!
What the hell are you doing?
It's huge! What is that?
It's the so-called self-propelled image-transmission den-den-mushi.
Any image captured is sent directly back to the royal palace.
We're constantly being watched.
If someone shows any signs of opposition, he or she will be killed immediately as a warning to the rest.
What's with it all of a sudden?
It's the smell.
The inside of my nose feels like it's getting shocked.
Can't you feel it?
It's the "Daft Green."
Our village is surrounded by a kind of plant called Daft Green. It protects us from the animals.
Animals hate their smell after all.
You bet.
Then cork your nose with something.
Let's go.
This is the plant?
I can still smell it with my nose corked.
Now that you mention, it sure stinks.
You're too slow!
Don't try to inhale too much; it's poisonous.
Say that earlier!
Didn't I tell you not to go out the border of Daft Green?!
But... All I wanted to do was to save Grandma...
Xiao...
Don't risk your life for me.
But... If you stay as you are... Grandma will...
Thank you very much... Guys...
I would like to repay you...
We just happened to bump into her.
That's right. She ended up helping us too.
More importantly, what's her illness?
It's an illness called Daft.
Any part of the body with the green lump gets stiffened up, and eventually the person will be unable to move.
It's the result of inhaling too much pollen from Daft Green.
The only cure can be made from a plant called IQ, but... We need more than just one.
That's why she ventured into that place alone.
I'm sorry.
It's not your fault.
The bad guy is Shiki who monopolized the IQ.
Shiki? Did you say Shiki?
20 years ago, humans, plants, and animals coexisted peacefully.
But that man ruined everything.
I wish they'd just leave... To the Sea of Stratagems...
Can't you do anything about that?
I've never seen this kind of illness before.
I don't want to make it worse.
Anyway, we won't get attacked by those animals as long as we stay here, right?
Yeah. I can still smell a little bit of Daft Green here, but at the very least, I can stand it.
But I wonder if everybody's alright.
Yeah, me too.
We'll start looking for them again after a quick rest.
I'm all worn out.
I feel weird... I can't move my body...
You're telling me.
We haven't had the slightest bit of good rest for a whole week!
What? It's just you...
Sanji! Usopp!
It looks like all captains have gathered at the port.
Okay, we'll make our move after the meeting.
Finally, tonight is the night?
Return all those men back to their village.
You sure about that?
I promised them after all.
But return just one of them...
It's only natural to give them hope before despair.
The expression of someone falling from a high place is exceptional, no?
Boss Shiki.
You could talk!
Bad news. That little girl has escaped.
What?
It seems like she's realized that the royal palace's pool is connected directly to the sea.
She got us, but we can't allow such a rare talent to escape.
Inform all networks. We must find her!
Yes, sir!
That hurts!
Geez...
Stop!
But you saved me... Thanks.
Anyway, where are we?
Sunny-go!
Oh, Sunny-go!
Luffy!
Nami!
I'm glad you're alright.
Good job running away from that guy.
Don't come over here!
Where's everybody?
This place is so big, I haven't been able to meet any of them yet.
But I didn't think I'd meet you first...
Anyway, let's eat, this scorpion is good.
Isn't that right, Biri?
No thank you.
Biri? Who?
shock
This bird, it's producing biri.
Right?
I see. You're a rubber-man, so electricity doesn't affect you.
Anyway, we found Sunny-go.
Should we wait for everyone? Or should we look for them?
We'll look for them!
crayfish
This Zarigani-san is amazing!
It's my custom design. Call it Zari Davidson.
Yes!
Zari Davidson! Zari Davidson!
I can see something.
A town?
I think so.
I bit my tongue... Though I have no tongue.
I told you not to jump backwards!
It's shaking.
It's no use. It won't listen to us.
Let's walk.
What's wrong?
It's a village.
I saw those kinds of trees around Shiki's royal palace too.
Do you dislike that smell?
Is that right?
I think the area surrounded by the trees is safe from those animals.
Then, the guys could be there...
I'm glad you're okay, Nami-san!
I was so worried about you that I haven't been able to sleep well.
He wasn't kidding about not being able to sleep.
We haven't found Robin-chwan yet!
You're noisy as hell!
Huh?!
Anyway, I'm just glad you're all okay.
There's even more people now.
Looks like you've gathered a crowd.
You can rest inside if you'd like.
Nami, go rest inside.
Eh? Okay...
Wake up, Xiao. Bring them some tea.
Yes.
We've found her, Shiki-sama.
Ah.
Then why don't I head off to welcome back our navigator.
They're not here.
On the other hand, why are there so many pirates gathered around here? Are they preparing for war?
From the Eternal-poses they are bearing, it looks like they were summoned here by someone.
Excuse me, would you show me your panties?
Like hell I would!
You arms...
Oh this? I think it's because we want to become birds.
Become birds? Do you think you can become one just because you want to?
Yes.
Um... Panties...
You guys are the Straw-Hat's mates, right?
Huh?
Are you guys here to seek alliance with Boss Shiki as well?
Yeah, that's what we intend to do.
Why has Boss Shiki gathered so many pirates for?
Why you ask?
Don't play dumb. Didn't you read the newspaper?
Here!
Huh?
That's...!
Eh?
Grandma, Mom, I have big news!
What did you say?
It's true! Shuu-chan's dad has returned home!
He said everybody will be able to return soon!
We'll be able to see Dad and Sister soon!
Are you sure? I'm not dreaming, am I?
In other words...
That's right. Shiki is leaving this place.
He's going to take all of the animals with him to the Sea of Stratagems.
To East Blue!
I see...
East Blue is your home-town, eh?
You will know what my goal is.
You will one day beg me to allow you to join.
Become my navigator, Baby-chan.
Because there's always something you'd want to request your nakama, no?
It feels like I'm dreaming when there's a hope for living after being here for so long.
You're right.
I wish they'd leave for East Blue even if it was a minute or a second earlier.
Luffy...
That's right.
That was a warning for the World Government.
In other words, Boss Shiki's intention is...
Annihilate East Blue and then overturn the world!
I heard that after tonight's meeting, he will send all those animals to East Blue.
If he did that, a lot of lives would be lost.
Don't mind all that. He's doing it in order to get the World Government to surrender.
We're following a great man.
You bet!
Come on, let's cheer!
Cheers!
Hey guys, don't think you can attend the meeting with your current outfits.
Wear something formal!
Follow the dress code, right? Got it.
I heard there's a demonstration for us tonight.
Demonstration?
I heard he's going to destroy the only village on this island.
Actually, I can't wait to see it!
There's an inhabited village on this island?
Luffy?
Stay back, Nami!
I've found you, Baby-chan.
Shiki!
You're cold, Baby-chan.
You left without a word. That hurts me deep.
Shut up, you shitty bastard.
You fooled us and took Nami-san away.
It's hard not to snatch such an elegant woman away.
If you don't want me to take her away from you, then protect her properly!
Although, I don't think she's able to leave my side now.
Am I right, Baby-chan?
Bastard!
Hey, Steering-wheel!
Don't think you can leave this place unscathed after hurting my nakama.
What are you going to do?
Beat the crap out of you!
Luffy!
If you could, I'd like to see you try!
Huh?
Gomu Gomu No Kama
Rubber Rubber Sickle
Hissatsu Hi No Tori Boshi
Sure-kill Phoenix Star
Nanajuuni Pound Hou
72 Pound Cannon
Arm Point
Kokutei Rozeo Michieeri
Kokutei Roseo Metel
Poitrine Shoot
Breast Shoot
You make quite a good team.
I've gotta say you're pretty good for making me use my hand.
But now that I've used my hand, don't expect me to hold back.
Sanji!
Let's start with you.
Rocket
Did I interrupt your conversation?
Not really...
To think you're able to fight on equal ground with me...
It's such a pain. I'll get rid of you all at once.
He's going to do something.
Shishi Odoshi
Menacing Lion
Chimaki
Winding Earth
Gomu Gomu No
Rubber Rubber
CANNON
Wow!
Cook!
Huh? Damn...
Armee de L'Air Power Shoot
Air Force Power Shoot
Hissatsu Atlas Suisei
Sure-kill Atlas Comet
Good aim, but it's useless.
Santouryuu Gyuuki Yuzume
Demon Bull's Brave Hoof
You don't even deserve to be killed.
Zoro!
Damn!
Gear
Luffy!
Guys!
I'll have them sleep in the earth for a while.
It's annoying when I have to deal with these ignorant fools.
Especially when you were about to comprehend the situation and return to me.
Am I right?
Was East Blue also your doing?
That's right.
Don't...
Don't do my nakama or my home-town any more harm than you already have!
You've got the order wrong.
I told you before.
There's always something you'd want to request from your nakama.
The only threatening thing to me is that cyclone.
You should know fully well that what I need is a talented navigator.
Is that a mirror?
Stop bullshitting.
This is the ring my sister from my home-town gave me when we parted.
If I join you, you'll spare East Blue, right?
Of course, I'm a man who values his nakama more than anything else.
I won't lay a single hand on my nakama's home-town.
Don't do anything stupid, Nami!
Usopp!
You're still conscious?
You're not gonna sell yourself out just because of our home-towns, are you?
Luffy won't forgive you if you do that!
What do you mean by won't forgive, brat?
Looks like you still haven't fully understood the situation you're in.
Wait, I understand the situation!
Don't harm my nakama!
Then let me hear you answer, Baby-chan.
Usopp, we have no other choice.
I will protect East Blue.
So put your mind at ease and just go.
No, Nami...
I'm gonna be okay.
Stop it!
I'll live no matter anywhere I go.
Shut up!
Who'd agree if you—
Usopp!
What an annoying brat, geez...
Well, Baby-chan, let me hear your answer.
I'll become your nakama.
Become, huh?
Please make me your nakama.
I see.
Welcome, my excellent navigator.
Understanding that there are opponents you can't beat is also part of the learning process.
I'm not a kidnapper.
Moral code is valued even in the pirate world.
Leave your nakama who have been through hard and happy times a final farewell.
Good farewell.
I hope this won't bring me any future trouble.
Your nakama should be able to accept it...
If they are able to crawl out of there alive, that is.
Alright, get ready, everyone.
We shall commence as planned.
Welcome back.
Ah.
Hey, what're you doing? Come in here.
The more I look at you, the prettier you become.
Look...
You made a good decision.
You should be grateful that your home-town won't be part of this turmoil.
Hurry, to the underground trench!
Awesome, those animals are devouring the village!
As expected from Boss Shiki. He sure knows how to roll.
It's just a little side-show to see what happens if we remove Daft Green from the village.
I'm not interested...
I'm going back to my room.
Geez, I thought she would go into a frenzy.
Damn it... We're late.
It's identical to the photo in the newspaper.
They sure did terrible things...
It won't be long before East Blue ends up like this.
Mugiwara, let me know if you're here!
Luffy-san, are you here?!
Mugiwara!
Luffy-san!
What in the world happened?
Quick, get them out!
Shiki was the one behind all the incidents in East Blue?
Yes.
So he intends to use those beasts to turn our home-towns upside-down...
Shitty bastard, treating others like fools...
In order to protect our home-towns, she left with Shiki.
We were saved by Nami.
Xiao, are you alright?
We were hiding in the underground trench.
Anyway, what you guys were talking about... Is it true that East Blue is your home?
Is it also that girl's home?
Yeah, that's right.
What have I done?!
I said I wished Shiki would just leave for East Blue in front of her!
How could I say such a terrible thing?!
I was happy, too...
Xiao, what's that?
This? I picked it up from here...
Let me see.
Sure.
You're amazing, Xiao.
You have time to worry about Nami when your own village is in such a mess.
I've never seen people as kind as you guys are.
You don't have to blame yourself...
The one at fault is that bastard Shiki.
I'll beat the hell out of him.
Cheer up, 'kay?
What's that? A tone-dial?
Yeah, it's the one Shiki was using.
Please forgive me for being unable to say farewell to you all directly.
It's Nami's voice.
I've decided to join Shiki's crew as their navigator.
Shiki is a legendary pirate whom Luffy and you guys can't oppose.
You will only be wasting your life if you come after me.
That's why I'll say this...
WHAT THE HELL IS THIS?!!
What's wrong with her?! Why is she leaving this kind of message?!
C-Calm down...
She said we can't beat him?!
What the hell was she thinking when she said all that?!
But in reality you all were beaten by him, weren't you?
What did you say? I was just... Doesn't really mean...
Calm down... Stop...
Damn...
Usopp, let me hear it again.
Please forgive me for being unable to say farewell to you all directly.
I've decided to join Shiki's crew as their navigator.
Shiki is a legendary pirate whom Luffy and you guys can't oppose.
You will only be wasting your life if you come after me.
That's why I'll say this...
Our elites are gathering one after another...
It's finally time, World-Government...
It's been 20 years since my legs last ached...
I see...
I got it.
I'll go now.
HE UNDERSTOOD?!!
I see...
You plan on letting the animals attack this place by destroying these trees...
You've planned this since the beginning, haven't you, Baby-chan?
Despite all my effort complying with your conditions...
There's no way you'd listen to me...
I don't want to see my home-town in ruin nor my nakama depressed from hearing this bad news!
Don't be so hasty...
The powerful poison from these trees wasn't a part of your calculation, was it?
Pirates should not be concerned about their family nor their home-town.
You'll only be misplacing your life if you cling onto those things.
If you are unlucky enough to survive until the end of the meeting...
I'll use you as my navigator for the rest of your life.
I don't dislike cheeky women...
Well done gathering here.
We shall now commence the Shiki alliance ceremony.
First of all, I don't appreciate traitors. Keep that in mind.
Well then, let's depart to the Sea of Stratagems.
To the tragic sea of East Blue!
Let's go, Franky.
Got it.
Hold on tight.
Coup de Burst
Burst Blow
For real?!
How dare you dock your ship on the royal palace?!
Who the hell are you?!
As you know, East Blue is the weakest among the five seas.
No one will mourn its demise.
Do as you wish with it.
The Golden Lion Pirates are complete!
Shiki-sama!
What do you want at a time like this?!
My deepest apologies, but I have an emergency.
8 people? They are rushing in?
Well...
What?
That's lame, man.
This is how you do it.
W-Wait a second!
It's you guys... What a surprise.
I heard you're going to attack East Blue?
Well yeah.
Is Nami alright?
She's lively.
You look tough, but don't think you can make a difference with just 8 people.
A stupid woman who believed that if she sacrificed herself, she would be able to protect her home-town...
Together with a reckless suicide squad.
Are you stupid?
Nami didn't sacrifice herself.
She came here as the vanguard!
Brace yourself, Golden Lion...
We're the main force!
We're out of ammo...
There's a bunch of them left...
We were just saying hi... That's about right...
Usopp! Chopper! Find Nami!
Got it!
Shoot these impudent fools! Kill them all!
Boss Shiki, please go inside.
Yeah.
Kill their boss!
Nemuri Uta Flanc
Lulluby Parry
Did you do something...
To my nakama?!
Boss!
Don't get in my captain's way!
Didn't he tell you to clear the way?!
Biri...
Did you do this?
I have a favor to ask... Listen to me...
Please stay here and listen to what I have to say...
Renpatsu Kaen Boshi
Continuous Flame Star
Chopper, can you trace her smell?
It's no good.
I can't smell well when the air is filled with Daft Green.
Damn it...
There she is! She's over there!
Nami...
Won't you take it with you?
Have fun...
Don't worry... It's going to be okay...
I won't allow our home-town to meet its end...
Just a little longer, Nami...
We're okay somehow...
Where's Nami?
Nami!
Nami! Hang in there!
Are you alright? I'll get you out of there.
This lump... It's just like Xiao's grandma...
We have to get her treated.
This... This is...
Could it be...?
We've got a lot on our hands already...
Hurry and get Nami out of there...
NO!!!
What the...?
Hanauta sancho Yahaza Giri
Three-Verse Humming: Arrow-Notch Cut
How is she, Chopper?
It was a close call. She's finally able to breathe again.
We have to do something...
Biri...
The only thing that can cure this disease is IQ, but I heard Shiki is the only one who has it...
What did you say?
Where exactly...?
Is Nami—
She's okay...
Shiki!
You've done it now, little girl...
It seems like you really want to die.
I don't need you any more!
I'll make sure East Blue is destroyed no matter how hard you struggle.
We're done for!
Shishi Odoshi Gosho Chimaki
Imperial Palace of Winding Earth
Die in despair!
Damn it!
Luffy!
You still want to fight?
Nami, I'll beat that guy and we'll go back together.
Luffy...
Leave this place to me. Take Nami to safety.
Got it.
Fight hard, Luffy.
It's death for you anywhere you go.
You have no right to decide our fate!
JET PISTOL
Biri, give me a hand.
I won't let you go to East Blue!
You stupid brat...
Don't expect me to go easy on any man from East Blue!
What is this place?
They're all IQ.
They are using moonlight to plant them...
It's the smell of medicine...
This is where the IQ research is carried out...
Which one should I let her take?
An enemy!
He smells of medicine...
Are you a scientist?
Yeah, an excellent one at that.
Hand over the cure for Daft!
Why should I give it to you, idiot?
This is what you want, right? I've always been carrying it with me for an emergency.
Well, that makes it simple.
All I need to do is take it from that guy.
Back off, I'll chop him to pieces.
Zoro!
Looks like you've chased me to this place as well.
Take care of him... We need the cure from him.
You're going to chop me? A pawn from East Blue?
Furthermore, no one would give a damn about that sea even if we were to destroy it!
Chemical Juggling
Ignite!
I can't dodge...
Zoro!
Are you alright?
Feel the power of Chemical Juggling?
I don't have time to juggle with you.
Mass Juggling
Eat this!
Zoro!
He ate the whole thing!
Kiki Kyuutouryuu
Demon spirit nine sword style
Ashura
Asura
If you were to be...
Chemical
Defeated by a pawn who was born in East Blue like me...
Juggling
Ugui
Menacing Drill
Then, what kind of pawn would you be?
Zoro is super cool.
Is he invincible?
Chopper!
It's the cure...
I'm heading back now... Take care of Nami.
Yeah!
That way, man!
As expected...
There's no end to them.
Over there?
That's...
Robin-chan!
What?!
You said you want to make Robin-chan your wife?
YOU PERVERTED GORILLA!
He understands the gorilla's language?!
Just you wait, you shitty gorilla!
How dare you harass a lady in front of me?!
Outta the way!
Robin-chan!
You're biting off more than you can chew, man...
You want to conquer the sea?
Do have any idea... how many ladies there are in East Blue?!
Diable Jambe
Devil's Leg
Flanchet Shoot
Belly Shot
That's the taste of East Blue's love.
Shit! Robin-chan!
Are you okay, mademoiselle?
Yeah, thanks!
Why the hell are you taking the best part?!
I'll grate you whole, you shitty-
I don't have any flesh for you to grate...
Nami's safety is our priority...
Usopp...
You're right...
I can hear Chopper's voice, too...
Where are we?
Nami.
Thank god... You're awake.
The cure worked...
Did you come to save me...
Of course... And we're not the only ones...
Zoro, Sanji, Robin, Brook, Franky, and Luffy... We're all here.
Thank you.
This isn't the time to cry.
I know.
If we don't beat Shiki, East Blue will...
This is...
Stop.
What's wrong, Nami?
A storm is coming...
The pressure is dropping... There must be a big cloud nearby.
We're going back to the royal palace.
Eh?
Biri, are you alright?
About time we put an end to this.
Zanpa
Guillotine wave
It's settled, kid...
Navigation team to Shiki-sama...
What?
Please move the islands east... There's a storm coming!
A storm?
Was that good enough?
Nami, was that good?
Yeah, that's enough.
But, are you sure we're going to be okay heading into a storm like that?
No way we're gonna be.
Eh?
But, we have no other choice.
I guess that's good enough.
Well then...
This must be painful for a devil-fruit user.
Though you can't take back what you did to me... Nor can that young girl...
Watch as she perishes in despair!
Shishi
Lion
Senjindani
Valley of a Thousand Cuts
What's that?
Perm?!
What?!
The beasts are running away.
The storm! This island is heading into the storm!
What did you say?!
Guys, to the sea!
I've got a strange feeling about this weather.
Those animals are victims as well.
I won't forgive you for using this drug to turn them into monsters.
Good grief, this is such a bone-breaking job.
If they really broke, it would really spell doom for me.
Biri, can you still fly?
Let's go beat him up!
Take me... to the sky!
Huh?
Imbecile...
Shiki!
Huh?
Nami, don't be reckless!
It's Nami!
It's over... Everything...
I've finished planting the bombs!
Bombs, you said?
That's right.
Your factory, your palace, and this island.
Not a thing will remain.
Your plan has failed!
DON'T SCREW WITH ME!
Nami-san!
As if brats like you are able to destroy my carefully thought out 20 year plan!
Eat this!
Hissatsu Tenryuu Boshi
Sure-kill Heavenly Dragon Star
Die!
You're all bark!
Biri, save Nami!
Nami-san!
How about me?
Biri!
Curse you!
Your opponent is me, Shiki!
Huh?
Gear Third
Hone Fuusen
Bone Balloon
Everybody, hurry to Lion-chan!
What's that?
Sucker, get struck by lightning and fall!
You're the one who's gonna fall, Shiki!
Huh?
I won't let you go to East Blue!
What an idiot!
Ouch...
That's...
Here it comes!
Do it, Luffy!
I'm the man who controls the seas from the sky!
You won't get your wish with...
My nakama...
Or the seas...
'Cause I won't let you!
Giganto Thor
Giant Thor
AXE
Am I going to be stopped by another man from East Blue?
ROGER?!
We're blasting off! Hold on tight!
Coup de Burst
Burst Blow
Luffy!
Luffy-san!
Luffy...
Biri?
Biri!
Luffy...
It's Luffy?
Where is he?
Yeah!
I'm glad he's okay.
Me too.
He did it! Now East Blue is safe!
But that figure is pretty lame.
Yeah.
Sure is.
Those are...
Shiki's ability has dispersed...
What about Xiao and the others?
Check that out!
Thank God.
Nami?
Nami-san...
Hey!
Nami.
Hey, Nami.
The islands are falling!
Run! Get away from here!
Hurry!
I spotted Shiki.
It's the Golden Lion Shiki!
Capture him!
Don't tell me... They did all that?
The target is the Straw-Hat's crew!
Prepare the cannons!
Yes, sir!
Yes, it was the Straw-Hat's crew.
Mugiwara...
We're still investigating. We'll provide you the full details later.
I see. Okay.
So we didn't do anything, huh?
Well, it's good that you're recovering faster than I expected.
But don't push yourself too hard.
Don't worry. I just want to take a breather outside.
I see.
Then go. I'm sure everybody will be happy.
Guys, Nami's up.
What?
Huh?
Nami-swan.
Yo, are you all good?
Yeah, I'm all good.
That's good.
Now that you're up...
Excuse me, Nami-san, would you mind—
Knock it off!
That was harsh.
Shut up!
Hey Nami!
Huh?
How do you explain this?
Wait, that's...
You said I couldn't beat Shiki and everybody's going to die... What a bunch of bullshit.
It's true that he buried me, but that's only because I was hungry.
That's because I thought...
I'm speechless.
I didn't think you couldn't trust me despite knowing each other for so long.
I'm disappointed.
Luffy, what are you talking about?
What do you mean?
Maybe you didn't hear it?
Nami was in a tough spot, you know.
That's what I thought too, but after I heard that...
Heard what?
Geez, you're hopeless.
Though all I could hear was a love message...
That message was intended for the dumbest guy like you, too...
Why don't we hear it again?
Wait!
I see.
Knock it off! It's embarrassing!
Please forgive me for being unable to say farewell to you all directly.
Quiet down.
It's over, so throw it away!
I've decided to join Shiki's crew as their—
Ah!
Hey!
Huh?
Don't throw it away. It's a precious dial.
We can still use it.
Give it back.
Nami, don't throw it away!
Please forgive me for being unable to say farewell to you all directly.
Wait!
I've decided to join Shiki's crew as their navigator.
Shiki is a legendary pirate whom Luffy and you guys can't oppose.
You will only be wasting your life if you come after me.
That's why I'll say this...
Definitely... Come to save me.
Kuyandatte ato no matsuri
悔やんだって後の祭り
It's too late to mourn now...
Mou kinou ni te wo furou
もう昨日に手を振ろう
Wave goodbye to yesterday.
Saa tabitachi no toki wa ima
さあ旅立ちの時は今
Now it's time to embark.
Omotaku shizunda ikari wo age
重たく沈んだ碇を上げ
Raise the deep-sunken anchor.
CONGRATULATIONS! Ima mune ni takanaru FANFARE!
Congratulations!今胸に高鳴るFANFARE!
Congratulations! Our hearts beat fast to the fanfare!
Mou Gradation wa mugen de nou ni kamifubuki yo mae
もう Gradation は無限で脳に紙吹雪よ舞え
The confetti dances in the boundless gradation of our memory.
kakugo nakimono wa sare atedonai rurou no tabi
覚悟亡き者はされ当て所ない流浪のたび
Wandering in an aimless journey, we lose our resolution.
Nobody knows koukai no matsuro
Nobody knows 航海の末路
The end of a voyage that nobody knows.
Chotto matte to iwaretatte docchi ikunda to towaretatte
ちょっと待ってと言われたってどっち行くんだと問われたって
You ask me to wait and ask for my destination.
Kotae wa itsumo kaze no naka ni arundesutte
答えはいつも風の中にあるんですって
But the answer is always in the wind.
Itsu no manika otona ni natte ukkarishite matomo ni natte
いつの間にか大人になってうっかりして真面になって
One day we'll grow up through our carelessness and our seriousness.
Ushinatta takaramono sagashi ni ikou
失った宝物探しに行こう
Let's search for the lost treasure.
Kuyandatte ato no matsuri
悔やんだって後の祭り
It's too late to mourn now...
Mou kinou ni te wo furou
もう昨日に手を振ろう
Wave goodbye to yesterday.
Saa tabitachi no toki wa ima
さあ旅立ちの時は今
Now is the time to embark...
Kaze wo yonde dekai ho wo hare
風を呼んでデカイ帆をはれ
Call forth the wind and raise a huge flag!
Chotto matte to iwaretatte docchi ikunda to towaretatte
ちょっと待ってと言われたってどっち行くんだと問われたって
You ask me to wait and ask for my destination.
Kotae wa itsumo kaze no naka ni arundeshitakke
答えはいつも風の中にあるんでしたっけ
Has the answer always been in the wind?
Kitto kyou mo anata no hitomi de
きっと今日も貴方の瞳で
Surely, today, in your eyes,
boku mo shiranai atarashii boku wa guruguru tabi wo shiteru
僕も知らない新しい僕はぐるぐる旅をしてる
A new me is embarking on an endless journey.
Itsuka dare mo ga otona ni natte chakkari shita otona ni natte
いつか誰もが大人になってちゃっかりした大人になって
One day we'll grow up...to be shrewd adults...
Ushinatta takaramono sagashi ni ikou
失った宝物探しに行こう
Let's search for the lost treasure!
Presented by INP-Fansubs.
Someone needs to stop Clearway Law.
Public shouldn't leave reviews for lawyers.