The sea is watching...
The beginning of the world...
The sea knows...
Of the end of the world...
So it shows...
The path to be followed...
So he guides us...
Towards a correct world...
Pain, suffering, he collects it all...
Big and gentle, he cuddles them all...
I will destroy
all pirates!
I'll just follow master Z.
Catch this!
I'll also follow master Z.
Smash Buster!
Retreat! Fall back!
Master Z...
How long has it been?
Master.
What brings you here?
Borsalino!
I've warned you not to depend too much on you're Pika Pika no Mi power.
You're still hard as rock,
like always.
Master Zephyr.
I abandoned that name.
I am Z!
Don't you think you're feeling
too sure of yourself
by becoming "Admiral Kizaru" of the Navy?!
I didn't come here to remember the past.
You won't be able to match my speed with that heavy weapon.
What will you use the
Dyna Rocks for?
Since ancient times,
I never got along with you!
Come, return the Dyna Rocks.
They say that the Dyna Rocks
rival the Ancient Weapons.
How about we use them
to celebrate our reunion?
Dyna Rocks cause a massive explosion
when exposed to oxygen.
Let's Go!
Master Z!
Damm!
What in the hell is the Navy doing?
Come on!
Come on, baby!
I'm always a
lively skeleton.
Come on!
It's good drinking while watching
the cherry blossoms.
Right, Chopper?
Yes! I love drinking milk
while watching the leaves as well!
Cherry... No, It's me!
Meat!
It stinks!
I smell poison!
It's a deadly poison!
What is it, Chopper?
He was poisoned?
Chopper!
He took poison...
I remembered!
Do you have any idea of what it is?
Listen to this song..."The poison I took".
It's a song?!
Now that I think about it,
the taste of the drink is...
Wait, or was it
always like this?
They are always so lively.
Plant care,
taking care of plants.
Come on, my children!
I want you to give birth to a lot of Pop Greens!
The worms exterminator,
the great Usopp, shall protect them!
Usopp!
So it's your fault!
Look! Usopp was
caught by the poisonous milk!
It's your fault
for being there!
The poison is
for killing worms!
If you die, it means you are worms!
Well, then we can relax.
After all, we are not insects.
So, are you ok?
The taste is a bit different,
but it's also pretty good.
It's a little bitter...
is it because I'm becoming an adult?
Let me try it.
That's horrible!
Agricultural chemicals
also affect the human body.
I am the cherry tree...
I'm slowly spreading...
Luffy, the cherry tree!
The autumn will end.
Wait a bit more, cherry!
Lets go!
It's south... I'm going south!
Change of course!
Damn you, why
did you spilled my drink?
Frankly, they make so much noise...
Why can't you rest quietly?
Hey, be quiet! Damn it.
Nami!
Delivery of the special orange juice!
Thank you, Sanji.
I'd also love some dessert!
Nami! Yes,
with pleasure!
Hey, Sanji!
I also want dessert! And meat!
I want some candies!
Me too!
I want cola!
My drink is ending!
I want dessert too!
Shut up, bastards!
When you ask something to someone,
it has to be politely, you idiots!
I was born only
for the ladies!
It taste bad!
Hey, Usopp, your poison is here again.
I'm not using it anymore!
What is this?
It's snow!
No, its not freezing to be snow.
What is it?
This is... volcanic ashes!
Volcanic ashes?!
That's disgusting!
The ashes entered
your fur, did it not?
Let's take a bath together after.
-Bath?
-Together?!
Today
is not my bath day...
But I'll take it,
this is very disgusting.
Me... Can I take a bath
with you as well?
Can I?
Look, my face
is also disgusting!
Don't hurt your
feelings by what you said.
No...
Brooke, you can
take a bath with me!
I love you, Chopper!
Hey, Nami!
Do you have any idea?
The needle that pointed to the direction that came the volcanic ashes
began rotating randomly.
It is a strange movement.
It looks like a lost child
who lost their parents.
Lost?
How so?
For example, the volcanic eruption that released those ashes,
could've exploded the entire island.
And because of that
the needle stopped pointing?
That's impossible!
This is the New World!?
That's right, you bastard.
Don't be surprised.
Disappear before the beauty of Nami.
You cherry shit.
Nami, some tea.
Thank you.
Anyway, we have to avoid at all cost, the island the needle was pointing at.
In that case, Nami...
There is someone we can't
show that pointer by any means.
That's true.
Choosing the safest route
and guarantee the
crew life is my job.
Hey, that needle is
moving very interestingly!
Luffy!?
Let's go there!
Crap!
He saw it!
I smell adventure!
Wait, Luffy! You didn't listed correctly!
According to Nami, those ashes were...
Hey, guys!
Our route has been decided!
Get ready!
Luffy!...
But...
If the pointer is crazy,
how will we know where the island is...
Be quiet.
I'm a navigator.
If we decide to go,
I can take you anywhere.
Luffy, keep an eye out.
Leave it to me!
Hey, is it really alright
choosing it like this?
In the New World, the path you
choose can cost us our lives.
Franky,
Turn 20 degrees to port.
Turning 20 degrees
to port.
Hey, do you hear me?
We don't know what might happen,
so prepare yourselves!
We can't do anything.
After all, he is the captain.
But we don't want to get
involved with volcanoes
or anything that can
threaten our lives!
Castaway located.
Prepare to rescue him immediately!
He's being dragged!
Leave it to me!
Luffy, whats wrong?
I'm running out of strength...
Pull, pull!
Luffy, don't let go yet!
Luffy, are you ok?
So? Is he alive?
His heart rate and breathing are weak, but he's only passed out, he's not in danger.
Really?
I hope we didn't get someone
problematic again.
A big guy all bruised!
And this business in his left arm...
Just by looking, anyone
can tell its not just something.
Thats really made of Kairouseki.
I get it! Thats why Luffy lost his
strength when he touched it.
A powerful weapon
made of Kairouseki...
Awesome!
Thats not it!
Kairouseki has the same
energy as the ocean.
A weapon made from that material...
means that it was made
to end Devil Fruit users.
He might be an enemy.
and we can't lower our
guard in the New World.
If you're worried, throw him overboard.
Idiot!
We can't do that.
I don't want to!
He might kill you as
soon as you heal him.
Even so, I'm a doctor!
I can't abandon him.
Whats the problem?
Heal him, Chopper.
If he's the
enemy, I'll finish him off.
Is that alright?
Yes! Thank you, Luffy!
Well, as a see warrior,
of course it's alright.
Damn, they are so carefree.
I really have a bad
feeling about this...
It's exciting, right?
There is no need for
that kind of excitement.
Luffy, it looks like he woke up!
Yes, it seems so.
Hey, crappy cooker.
Shut your mouth.
I know, you shit marimo.
Got that?
We caught a big fish.
Are you ok?
You don't need to force yourself.
You were floating in the see,
do you remember it?
Yes, I remember.
Thank you for the great treatment.
It looks like I came back
to life, doctor...?
Chopper!
Doctor Chopper.
You are a great medic.
Praising me doesn't
get me happy, you idiot!
You are the captain of this ship?
Can you tell?
Yes I can.
I've seen a lot of
young man like you.
I'm a specialist when it comes to
understanding your powers.
Really?
What will you do? Stay with us until we arrive to the next island?
I got a Vivre Card, my friends should be using that to get here.
Old man...
thats a cool weapon!
Where do they sell those?
When I lost my arm to a damn pirate, a crazy scientist from the Navy made this one for me.
Battle Smasher.
It's made of Kairouseki,
the weakness of the Devil Fruit users
this way I destroy their power and crush them with this powerful squeeze.
Dr. Chopper, I don't
recommend something heavy like this.
Awesome!
I can't get it off without a special key, so something terrible can happen
if I fall with it
on the ocean.
Old man, are you a Marine?
No. I got too old for that, so I left them.
I'm doing something different now.
What are you doing?
I'm fighting for the
mission I gave myself.
What are you fighting against?
It looks like I'm being questioned.
I'm sorry about that.
It's just that it would be
bad for us if you were a Marine.
Would there be a
problem if I were a Marine?
Yes. After all, we are pirates.
Really?
You are pirates.
Luffy!
Nami, go outside!
Take care of it, please.
How painful... a punch from a
Kairouseki weapon really works.
Straw Hat...
Why are you a pirate?
To become the Pirate King!
Pirate King...
Pirate King?!
He's strong!
Damn!
Brooke! Let's fight too!
Ok!
They're here?
I am a Vice-Admiral of the New Navy, Ain!
We are confiscating
this pirate ship.
Do not resist.
You will only shorten your lives.
There is no pirate that doesn't
resist when he's asked not to!
Even we started to attack!
Mosa Mosa!
What the hell is this?
-Thats is...
-A Devil Fruit user!
Mosa Mosa no Mi ability...
Mosa Mosa Dance can control
every plant there is!
Things look dangerous out there as well.
Let's end this now!
Dos Fleur!
What...
Mosa Mosa!
He's so fast that I
can't establish a target!
Mosa Mosa!
Mosa Mosa Mosa!
Can't breathe...
Mosa Mosa!
Be careful!
Don't come down!
Mosa Mosa!
What is this?...
-Stop it!!
Mosa Mosa Mosa!
No!  No!  No!
Gust Sword!
Modo Modo!
Nami!
How dare you do that with Nami?!
Heavy Point!
Modo Modo!
Chopper!
No! Stop...
Don't come close...
No!
No! No!
Brooke!
Stop!!
Seis Fleur!
You are also a
Devil Fruit user, right?
What have you done with
Nami and Chopper?
Robin! Stop using
your ability!
Modo Modo!
I ate the Mono Mono no Mi.
I am a regressive person.
My ability can transform
anything 12 years in time.
Now you should be about 18 years old.
I'm so tiny!
If I touch you two more times, you will regress 12 years two times, in other words, 24 years,
Making your
existence disappear.
Smash Buster!
Mosa Mosa!
You'll become the
Pirate King with that power alone?
Don't make me laugh.
Should I crush you like this?
What do you think, Pirate King?
What's you're name?
Monkey D. Luffy.
I get it.
You're Garp grandson.
Master Z,
I'm happy you're alright.
We're destroying this pirate ship
with a simultaneous attack from out fleet.
Luffy!
Are you ok, Luffy?
I am the Commander
of the New Navy, Z!
I will obliterate every
single pirate!
Try to survive while you still can.
Pirates!
Damn!
Wait!...
Our fight...
Our fight isn't over yet!
Sunny!...
Damn!
Chopper, take that off!
We're really in danger!
Luffy!
Luffy, let's run!
Franky, let's retreat!
Come on! Damn!
I'm free! Super!...
Come on, Sunny! I believe in you!
Emergency escape system!
Coup D'Burst!
They really did that.
Originally, they are our trump card to protect the Final Points of the pirates.
Using the Dyna Rocks to
destroy the Final Points...
The first Final Point sank
with the base that protected them.
Z objective is to destroy
the three Final Points...
...and destroy the
sea of the New World.
Even that man would get injured if he was caught in the Dyna Rocks explosion.
He's alive.
Everyone here must know this.
He doesn't know when to fall.
Z....
Or rather, former
Admiral of the Navy, Black Fist Zephyr
He is alive.
Either way, we have to recover the Dyna Rocks, no matter the cost.
He may have taken
care of us in the past...
...but now he is our enemy,
enemy of justice.
And everyone who's
part of the New Navy...
...even if Z is alive.
They all should be disposed of...
...in the name of justice.
Hunt Z and his New Navy
with all the power of the Navy!
Let's recover the Dyna Rocks
and execute absolute justice!
If the Final Points were destroyed, the world would be as well.
Is that really a lie?
You think that if it was a lie we
would take this so seriously?
I understand what Z is planing.
He wants to end with all the
pirates of the New World.
If he uses the Final Points,
that becomes possible.
But of course, he won't destroy only the pirates, he'll kill all the innocent citizens as well.
Vice-Admiral Garp...
Who is this Z?
A man who was our comrade once.
We were friends.
We should have been comrades.
Zephyr... your anger is
so strong to destroy the world?
Do you hate
us that much?
Luffy!
I'm going to
completely fix Sunny!
It will take some time, but while
I fix it you'll go after Z, right?
Yes, I'm leaving Sunny with you!
This is for the doctor.
This if for the load...
I'm so sorry...
All of this because I
wanted to save that Z.
Don't apologize.
A pirate shouldn't regret
doing what he believed in.
It's not your fault.
We all know that.
Thank you.
New Navy...
Who could that Z be?
When he found out we were pirated, e attacked out of nowhere!
The ability of that
Binz is problematic.
Next time we are going
to settle things straight.
Besides, we need to avenge Sunny, that showed so much bravery.
If it wasn't for Sunny strength,
we would all be swimming at sea because of the Navy attack.
We need to find that New Navy
and pay them back.
Are you serious?!
I don't want to mess with
those dangerous people again.
Let's just stay in this island
until Sunny is repaired!
What are you talking about?
If we don't find them,
my body won't return to normal!
Me neither!
I don't want to stay like this!
With this body of a child,
I can't do anything!
The navigation in the New World
will be a lot harder!
As navigator, I need to get back to normal, so I can guide Sunny Go!
That's right!
I didn't said for you to
continue like this.
It would be a problem if
I didn't return to normal as well.
I bet you're happy to be 18 again and having everything in the right place again.
I'm sorry!
Honestly. Don't joke around
when our ladies are in trouble.
But, wait a second...
That means I'll be able to closely follow Nami's precious days while her body matures?
I'll be able to see the moment when the larva turns into a beautiful butterfly?!
That's incredibly awesome!
Disgusting.
Hu? I'm going to kill you,
you marimo!
If you went back into a kid,
I'd give you a lesson.
Idiot!...
I'd defeat you even as a kid!
What did you say?
Then I would defeat you even
younger, with 3 year old!
Idiot!...
And I would have defeated
you when I was a baby!
-Hu?!
-What did you say?!
This is no time to fight!
You know...
Actually, my
age was also decreased...
It looks like...
It didn't change...
Anything...
I was also touched by
that Ain from the New Navy.
Speaking about it, it's true.
But it didn't change anything...
No! Brooke,
dead and only bones.
I've been a
corpse for more than 50 years...
But something changed
that had never happened before.
My age went back 12 years.
Look, my hair has the
softness of 12 years ago!
No it hasn't!
You painted your hair!
Then were you
happy to rejuvenate?
You don't need to
go back?
Yes, that's right.
No, No! I also want...
to return to normal?
How do I know?!
For us to go back to normal, we have to gather information about Z and the New Navy.
Do you need
something, old man?
If it's the price of consulting
the doctor, talk to our navigator.
Did Z showed up again?
Old man,
do you know Z?
Many pirate ships have been attacked around here and comes to these docks.
All the injured pirates
say they were attacked by Z.
Grandpa told me that when when costumers come to the docks,
they are all pirates
saying they were attacked by Z.
They come to fix their ships
and they use the docks,
We receive the ships that
were totally destroyed by the navy.
My grandpa was a sailor, so he takes care of the pirates or anyone that comes with a problem.
I only like people that risks their lives here in the New World, searching for their dreams.
Many were totally defeated by Z, lost their way and abandoned the New World.
Z is stealing the men
freedom on the sea.
Even if staying by their side
is wrong, I won't accept that.
If you were defeated by Z and
even so you want to face him,
I'd like to give you my
strongest equipment I have stored.
Strongest equipment?
Amazing! A powerful equipment!
Wait a second!
What, Nami? He said the
strongest! The strongest!
Before that,
we have to pursue Z!
And with Z attacks, our
clothes were all burned,
So we have to take care of that first.
If we stay the whole
time with these cherry fantasies,
we're going to raise suspicion when we are looking for information about him.
First we have to gather
information and clothes!
The strongest equipment
to defeat Z comes after that!
Got it.
Nami is small, but she's
the boss of it all, right?
Excuse me, do you have any big city on this island where we can get some information and clothes?
This island has nothing
besides our docks.
How about you go to
the neighboring island?
They are very popular
for the hot springs and volcanoes.
And now there is the sea train passing there, it has a lot of people visiting!
Sea train? Are you talking
about that sea train?
Yes.
That's right.
Luffy, Marino, Bones.
You guys are very strange. Leave it to us that we'll gather the information.
Isn't that right, Nami-swan,
Robin-chwan?
You're strange too, Sanji.
A lover face also won't do.
We will gather
the information!
No... But I wanted to go with you...
Let's enjoy the hot springs.
How about we rest before the battle?
Leave the new clothes to
me, I'll take care of them.
Looks like there is some
great brands on this island.
Okay, we're here!
Guys, don't get yourselves
caught by the Navy!
Spread out!
Honestly... Devil Fruit users
are full of weak points!
They lose their
strength even with that?
If we don't get the
upper part wet, we will still survive.
That's nice.
Can we really stay
here wasting our time?
Thats right! I want to beat him up, that Z!
You Idiot!
If a delinquent like you starts walking though out this island full of Marines,
it will cause us trouble again.
Nami told us already, right?
That we're letting them and Chopper gather information about Z?
Good, right?
A beautiful dancer!....
Everyone is so excited!
I'm happy you
liked it, sir.
Are you going on a date now, sir?
Yes. Leave it shining, please!
I can feel it...
I can feel it in my bones...
Everything goes away
along with the exhaustion.
Z....
I got distracted with the weapon in his arm and I let my guard down.
Since you're a Devil Fruit user, and you attack him without thinking...
and get caught by that Kairouseki arm again, you'll lose all your strength.
Let me and
Marimo take care of Z.
I don't want you to do anything.
I will finish him off.
Next time, I'll dodge that arm of his and attack him with everything I got!
You're lively as always.
I got tired of waiting
for you guys here.
Aokiji!
What's wrong, guys?
Who is this person?
A Marine! Admiral Aokiji of the Navy!
Admiral?!
Hi there. How long has it been?
We've finished
positioning the Dyna Rocks.
Understood.
When this volcano erupts,
those Navy brats...
Will know of my rage and
the scale of my hatred.
-Zoro, Sanji!
-Yes!
What does an Admiral
want with me?
Calm down, don't get too excited.
What do you want with us?
Don't tell me...
It's nothing like that.
I don't want to
capture you now.
I left the Navy, you should've known that.
I'm not a Navy Admiral anymore.
Then what are you?
What? I don't like a skeleton asking me that...
But since I'm not an Admiral anymore...
Am I an ally of justice?
No, that's not it...
What am I?
How should I know?
How will we know?! Well, that's it. I have no intention of fighting with you now.
Think about it. If I wished to fight, I wouldn't be in a hot spring where I can't use my powers.
You were waiting for us?
That's right.
I don't want
to stay here anymore...
So, let's talk
about the rest outside.
Ah, this?...
Well, how can I say,
I got carried away too much.
Chopper, have you found anything?
I heard some rumors that a few Marines came to this island after Z.
But I couldn't get
anything more.
Only rumors, hu?
In the store I'm at,
really has more Marines arriving...
...but I don't know
if it's because of Z...
...or due to Robin's popularity.
Robin is that
much popular?
Just look at how much I got for being her manager!
Awesome!
We can't do
anything with rumors alone.
So, what will we do?
I know! Leave it to me.
What happened to you leg?
Have you ever heard that in the world, there are things that it's best not to ask?
Then I won't ask...
Bu the way, why did
you fought against Akainu?
Aren't you both friends?
Well, well. You're really a
brat without any consideration..
No comments about that too.
Then, why are you here?
You really don't learn anything.
Well, that I can answer you.
Enjoying the hot springs.
That's what I'd like to say...
But actually,
I can't stay relaxing too much.
I'm chasing after a certain man.
You guys fought
against a strong guy, right?
Z...
That old man was strong, wasn't he?
After all, he is a former
Navy Admiral.
Sorry for the wait.
Thank you.
Young lady, you are
very small, but you strive a lot.
Mr. Marine, don't you
have any cool story to tell me?
You know Z?
Young lady,
how do you know Z?
Everyone knows him!
The adults are talking...
That you've come here to capture Z!
Ah, the rumors are
already saying that?
Ah, hey!
What's the problem?
So, Z is really
in this island?
That's right. We've come here
to take the bad guy Z.
We are heroes of justice!
So, what is Z objective?
What is he doing
here on this island?
That's enough.
To destroy the End Point.
End Point?...
Is that a lie just to scare me?
It so happens
that it's not a lie...
That's enough!
You guys drank too much already.
You're talking too much.
We're truly sorry, sir!
And you've got a lot
of interest in Z, young lady.
Is there any objective behind that?
No! That man
asked me to ask about Z!
Crap!
It really is a strange man.
Nami threw
the blame on us!
Should we run for it?
It's really a shame, but it's enough disguising myself as a manager.
I have got to work.
Would you come with
me, young lady?
Let me go!
Seis Fleur!
-Let's run away!
-Yes.
-Captain!
-Are you alright?
That's the power of
the Hana Hana no Mi!
That woman is Nico Robin
of the Straw Hat pirates!
Don't let her escape!
Yes, sir!
The world is in the
Great Era of the pirates.
At sea, arise and vanish pirates
that go after the One Piece.
When some disappear, other are born.
Does pirates appear because the One Piece is on the other side of the sea of the New World?
Or does One Piece exists
because Pirates also exist?
Do dreams come first?
Or is it the people?
In some moments,...
when pirates choose their dreams, they loose their happiness and the loved ones cry for them.
What must be done?
Is there an answer?
The former Navy Admiral,
Z, found an answer by force.
If the One Piece
disappears, so will the pirates.
It's a very simple way of thinking, is it not?
I left the Navy, but I want to see where does the bath that Z has chosen will take him.
But I don't
know what to do next.
Straw Hat Luffy.
You'll follow your conviction
and face Z again, right?
Show me your
answer.
See you later.
Z is on this island.
Even so well disguised, in the end, we ended up creating a huge conflict!
But we got the information we needed!
Z is on this island!
Despite not knowing what he plans.
There they are!
Go on ahead!
Hissatsu! Midori Bosshi, Devil!
That's it!
Let's regroup with Luffy and the others?
Yes!
What do you think about
the clothes I got you?
It combines a lot, doesn't it?
With me, I mean.
-With you?!
I have a great taste.
Shut up...
Try to survive while you
still can, Pirates!
Luffy, Luffy!
Usopp and the other arrived.
And they brought a lot of friends along.
In the end, they caused a mess.
If so, we should have ...
Hey, Luffy! Let's ask them where Z is,
leave a few unharmed!
Luffy, take care of them...
Please.
That's...
Haoushoku no Haki...
Hey! Where is Z?
On the other side of the island.
My squad should be
chasing him now.
Tekkai!
Your justice is useless.
Justice, freedom...
You'll have to start
everything all over again.
It looks like the
Dyna Rocks worked on this island.
With that, the destruction of the
second End Point was a success.
Grande Imbuto.
We'll achieve that goal when
the third End Point is destroyed.
The pirates will vanish from the sea,
and the world will see
once more, a beautiful dawn.
Gomu Gomu no...
Rifle!
What are you doing here?
You pirate brats......!
Who are you calling a brat?
If you keep talking,
I'll kill you, old geezer!
Old man! Return
my friends back to normal!
Ain, Binz!
Yes!
Understood.
I'll take care of the swordsman.
Damn Marimo!
Going ahead like that...
Right! I don't even need
to fight! Go on, guys!
Mosa!
Mosa, Mosa, Mosa!
When a pirate wants something,
they take it by force, right?
If you want to return your friends to normal, come and get it the pirate way!
Damn! We've got not choice.
Usopp!
I'm going to
fight Z one on one.
Luffy!
Z...!
Help me!
We won't be able to run away!
Someone help us!
Stop right there.
Ladies, go to
the sea train and be careful.
Thank you very much!
Doesn't he care
about anyone?
Isn't this too much craziness?
This time you wont
catch me with that weapon!
You accelerated the flow of your blood.
To increase the skills
of your body over the limit?
Gear Second!
You said you'd become the Pirate King, Right?
Yes! I'll find the One Piece
and become the Pirate King!
I get it now...
But do you have determination?
Are you determined
to risk your own life?
I am!
But what about your
friends?!
Are you prepared to sacrifice your friends in order to fulfill your objective
and walk on top of
their corpses to continue?
Hurry up! Their not here yet?
If we wait too long, we'll
also be caught by the volcano!
Are they...
...alright?
Modo, Modo!
That's enough!
If we find each other
again, I'll kill you next time.
Time's up!
Look at this!
She ran away?
What a crazy ninja...
If you stay always afraid of this Smasher, you won't hit me with any attack!
Who said I was afraid?!...
Fear and pain weaken
your determination.
Smash Tornado!
I'm a rubber man, bullets wont work!
Really?
I'm loosing my strength...
Your body won't move anymore.
This ammo is
made of Kairouseki.
You didn't expected this, did you?
After all, it's not an easy
task getting Kairouseki.
This thing wouldn't hit the most powerful who live here in the New World,
but works wonders on those who are too convinced in their own power and let their guard down.
You too
are a sinful man.
This straw hat
also got old...
I'm going to bury it with my own hands, together with this Great Pirate Age.
Give it back!
I got that hat from
Shanks, to take care of it!
I promised I would find
him and give him that hat back!
Give it back!
The one who dragged you into this pirate business was Shanks, the redhead?!
His sins are also deep...
Give it back.
Don't you worry.
When my plan, the Grande
Imbuto get's completed,
He will have
the same fate as you.
Those convinced fools who call them selves the Four Emperors...
Will all die without being able to do anything... Without even knowing of my plan.
Don't mock...
...on Shanks!
That's not good!
It seems that the
pyroclastic flow began.
Usopp!
Where is Luffy?...
Luffy!
Luffy! Luffy!
We can't do anything against that.
Lets go, guys!
How fast is that, really?
They say its more than 100 KM/h!
I get it!
I know! If this is a descent,
Hissatsu Midori Bosshi!
Boaty Banana!
Jump!
We need more speed!
It has no engine! It's just a boat!
Look out!
We're gonna hit!
It also has no helm!
It's just a boat!...
To the right!
Now it's divided in two!
We won't make it!
Damn it!
They're here!
Those are some nice fireworks, huh!
It blew up the entire island...
Master... What
about that straw hat guy?
The fire mountain
will decide his fate.
One Piece?
Everything in this world?
What a ridiculous dream.
How many sacrifices do they think it took? How much suffering and hatred?
They can call that will, freedom... If that's what they call the new age, then I'll squash it all!
I'll use my own hands to get rid of all the pirates in this world, to the very last.
Your dreams will
end in deep hatred.
I, Z, will close the
curtains on the Great Pirate Age!
What happened to him
in the past was really terrible.
But causing a tragedy like this, involving innocent civilians as a motive...
It is not right...
Dry as always...
Not everyone can easily
separate things like you do.
Am I right, Sengoku?
Vice-Admiral Garp!
What is it?
Z... No, the former Marine, Admiral Zephyr...
What kind of person was he?
He, more than anyone,
believed in the Navy justice.
Then why is he
doing this?
A certain accident happened.
An accident?
Zephyr was a serious man.
Even on the dangerous battlefields, he was always in front of his subordinates,
and he risked his life fighting
against the rivals of that era.
He became an Admiral of
the Navy when he was still young.
And when he was living an happy life, his wife and son were killed by a pirate that hated Zephyr.
By fully understanding the burden of
having a position as a Navy Admiral...
Zephyr kept that hatred and
sadness in the bottom of his heart
and continued his mission.
The years passed and Zephyr pledged himself on training the young Marines. The man who created all Marines...
Every soldier that raised their
patents lately, are his apprentices.
I want to
create a hero.
However, a bigger
tragedy fell upon him.
The training ship of the new
recruits commanded by Zephyr
was attacked by a pirate
with Devil Fruit powers.
And only Zephyr and two more survived, everyone else were killed. Zephyr lost his arm.
Took an arm from a Navy Admiral?
And then, Zephyr got a weapon to defeat Devil Fruit users, from the Navy scientists.
And together with his disciples,
he created an attack unit.
And he hunted down
Devil Fruit users.
He was still in the Navy,
but that was when they
weren't disappointed with the Navy.
And then, the only thing that was keeping him in the Navy was destroyed.
That year, the pirate that had killed his disciples,
was chosen to be a War Lord by the government.
And so, Zephyr left the navy.
And now he showed
up in the New World.
Hating pirates...
Disappointed with the Navy...
Leading the organization
he created, the New navy.
The unacceptable reality...
has changed that man.
You suck, Navy!
Why does Black Fist
Zephyr is called Z now?
Z..........
Who knows?
I can't say that. Enemies
without hesitation are strong.
The sea is watching...
The beginning of the world...
The sea knows...
Of the end of the world...
Even if I...
...disappear...
He knows everything...
You shouldn't be afraid...
...the orientations of the sea.
As you are here...
...you should not fear it.
Because your friend are waiting for you.
I hated that song,
master.
A song for the Marines who
travel north does not excite me.
You liked that, didn't you?
Yes. This is the best drink.
I also used to drink that
a lot, imitating you.
I wanted to be a cool man like you.
You came to give a lecture
to a stubborn old man?
Sorry,
but I won't stop.
Do you intend to die?
If that happens, there is no problem.
It's to get rid of
the evil called pirates.
The Navy can't execute
the true justice.
I'm sorry, but step aside.
Next time we meet,
let's drink together.
Go now, I don't want to kill you.
Neither do I.
Master Zephyr...
This is a Kairouseki bullet?
It was on Luffy's shoulder.
How long will
you stay here?
A-Aokiji!
You!...
What is Aokiji doing here?
It's alright.
We met a few moments ago.
Z is a former Navy Admiral?
He stole the Dyna
Rocks from the Navy.
Dyna Rocks?!
What is that?
Those are rocks they say it has a power comparable to the Ancient Weapons.
If they receive an impact and are exposed to oxygen, they create a massive explosion.
But due to its massive power, it's use is forbidden in civil zones.
The Navy has control of them all.
And now Z stole them?
He wants to use them to destroy the three End Point's of the New World.
Stop right there!
What are these End Points?
At the New World sea there are three magma concentrations,
and they call it End Point.
When I heard that from
a Marine, I doubted it...
Does that really exist?
I can't believe that breasted
lady turned into this dull little girl...
Are you listening to me?!
Does the End Point
really exist? Or not?
They do.
First, second...
Even when they hear the news about those two islands, all the pirates must be laughing thinking thinking it's nonsense.
Many know the legend of the End Points, but no ones believes it.
But the government investigated and declared the legend was false!
It's because the investigation results were different from what was announced.
The government used every possible means to make the world believe it was a lie.
Don't you think it would be terrible if pirates showed up wanting to use that?
Only the Government and the Navy superiors know about that.
But no one never thought
a former Admiral would use that.
That's true.
If it was a lie, the Navy
wouldn't be so desperate.
We got involved with a very dangerous man.
Z already destroyed two
End Points with the Dyna Rocks.
If he destroys the last one...
There will be a chain reaction that connects all three End Points.
Reaction?
There will be a major catastrophic eruption, that will burn the entire New World sea!
Every single pirate in the
New World will get burned to death.
But if he does that, he'll also
involve the innocent people!
Wait a second! He will involve
civilians... That's just wrong!
Don't you think you're
thinking too much about yourselves?
How much fear and victims do you think pirates cause in the world? Don't tell me you don't know.
Z hates all of that...
He hates it so much that
he doesn't care if he dies along.
It doesn't matter!
I'm going there to get my hat back!
I'm going to settle things with him!
Are you crazy, Luffy?
The New World will be destroyed!
I promised Shanks.
That I would become a great
pirate and return him that hat.
If I let that guy take my hat, I won't be able to become the Pirate King.
But you know...
The New World will...
That won't work with the
stubbornness of our captain.
Nami, which way?
Ah, yes. Let's see...
I've already offered my life
to captain Luffy, so I'll follow him.
Then let's go.
Do we really
need to do that?
Isn't the fate of the New
World too much for us?
You two want to stay?
What are you saying, you idiot?
When did I said that?
Of course I'm going!
I'm the brave sea warrior!
Isn't that right, Chopper?
Yes! Let's go!
War with that darned man!
Franky, how much longer?
It's ready!...
The repair is finished!
We can go at any time!
Super!
Guys, thank you!
What are you saying?
It seems they've decided.
The island where the last End Point is, where Z is... It's this way.
An Eternal Pose?!
Why are you giving this to us?
What do you mean, why?
Without it, you can't go
to the island where Z is.
Well, that's true, but...
The Navy is moving,
they also went to the last island.
The Navy too?
As two End Points were already destroyed, the Navy is taking it seriously now.
If you loose to Z, you'll be
destroyed along with the New World.
Even if you win, you'll be surrounded by the Navy and you'll also be destroyed.
Anyway, I want to
see it until the end.
Our initial objective was returning Nami and the others to normal,
and now it turned into a battle with the future of the New World at stake.
Guys, do you remember
the strongest equipment?
They brought the ships
Z sunk to these docks.
The old with pity to throw away the things and dreams that others have left behind... And he saved it all.
So, it's
great, isn't it?
Let's bring along the feelings of the pirates
defeated by Z, and attack him with everything!
I'm counting on you!
Defeat Z, that's trying to
take the sailors freedom!
Guys!
When I grow up,
I want to be a hero!
Which one should I be,
a Navy Admiral or a Pirate?
Pirates aren't Heroes.
Really?
They're both
the same to you?
Yes...
You guys are cool!
Gari! The best is
to do what you like!
Keep going in this direction!
Prepare the frontal cannon!
Target: Enemy fleet!
Ready...
Frontal cannon, fire!
I see it! It's the last island!
They're here!
Don't let them
reach Master Z!
Where the hell is Z?
Let us pass!
You go on ahead!
Take that!
Usopp 100 Tons Hammer!
I'll leave the
rest with you!
Leave the rest to me, Usopp!
Guard Point!
Shooting with full power!
Z...!
They got separated...
But it's an awesome sight...
Modo, Modo!
I won't let you reach the master!
I'm going to stop you!
I'm glad...
I have nothing against you, mas this is to return my friends to normal.
I'm fighting with everything I got.
Indeed, if we fight normally,
I'm not going to win.
But I'll win him some time.
I don't mind dieing for
Master Z ideals.
Your master ideals, uh...
So you're ready to throw
your lives away for that?
However, I felt hesitation
in you sword.
Don't be so sure of
your self, you pirate!
You lowly pirate!
You have no right to live!
Die before Master Z!
Master... Master... always that,
are you kids, by any chance?
I'm getting tired.
It started...
So that the old man doesn't get sad, we're going to kill the Straw Hat's without leaving any of them alive.
Gomu Gomu no Pistol!
-Don't let him get away!
-Shoot him!
Take that!
Modo, Modo!
Listen do the requiem
of the other world.
Soul Solid!
Mil Fleur!
Gigantesco Mano! Stomp!
Take that!
Hissatsu Midori Bosshi!
Take Javelin!
I'm going to show you the
power of my Magical Clima-Tact!
Heat Ball!
Cool Ball!
Thunderbolt Tempo!
Damn you Nami!
You got us too!
That was
quite a shock!
-It was good, wasn't it?
-What was good?
You guys defeated
a lot of them.
What about Luffy?
He went on ahead...
Then let's go right after him...
Guys, look!
Those are the Pacifists!
But those are different
from the ones we saw before...
You came, boy.
The explosion that's going to destroy the last End Point already began.
I didn't come
here for that.
I'm only here to
get my straw hat back!
This hat?...
What does it mean to you?
It's what shows me the path.
The path to become the Pirate King.
I wont allow pirates to have dreams!
And I'll destroy the sea you keep sailing!
Remember this...
The name of whom will
destroy evil... my name is Z!
That's useless!
Did you stopped thinking
and came here just to attack me?
Not good!
Sorry it took so long, guys!
Let's go, partner!
It's here!
Iron Pirate!
General Franky!
Awesome!
Franky Radical Beam!
That's so cool!
Mosa, Mosa!
Sky Walk!
Diable Jumble!
Take this!
Santoryu!
Seiryuuin!
Ryuusui!
If you're not sure,
cut them your self.
I prefer the sexy Nami!
Sexy fire!
Burn
Meteor attack of love!
Take this!
You can fall in love, Nami.
I'm back!
I also came back to normal!
-Really?
It's really great! The 90 years!
Zoro and the other did it!
Now there is only Z left!
Let's join Luffy!
It's useless!
You can't destroy my justice!
Gomu Gomu no Pistol!
Gatling!
Even being a
pirate, you have courage.
Much better than that wimpy Navy!
But...!
Gear Third!
Gigant Pistol!
I am... Z!
Z!...
Smash Buster!
Luffy.
Boy...
Why do you want to
face me so much?
Even if you defeat me,
in the end, you're still a pirate.
Nobody from the
society will thank you.
And so what?
I'll do what I want!
If I'm not able to defeat you, I also won't be able to become the Pirate King.
Is that so?
You sound like a kid.
You'll do what you want?
If that's the case,
I'll do the same.
I'll dedicate my entire life
to end with your ambition!
Come at me! This is the final battle!
Black Fist Zephyr... has returned!
I will do it!
I will become the Pirate King!
My name is... Z!
You bastard!
I got old...
With only that and my body
doesn't want to move anymore...
What a shame...
That fun moment
ended so quickly...
Frankly, that battle ended
right on time, what a close call.
Luffy!
Those who follow their dreams, destroy everything and move on.
Take your straw
hat and my life.
I don't want your life.
I'm already satisfied.
If you want to
continue, I don't mind.
No.
I'm also satisfied.
Luffy!
Are you okey, Luffy?
Guys!...
"Guys", nothing!
You went on ahead again!
Master Z!
Ain... Binz...
Forgive me... for giving
you so much work...
Me... Me...
I'm happy to
see that you're alright.
It seems everyone is gathered here.
Kizaru...!
It's a shame that the Straw Hat and Master Zephyr are almost dead.
But seeing you're all going
to die anyway, it's the same.
Damn it,
just at time like this...
You brought them all...
At the end, I did what I wanted.
Now I have to pay
the price for doing what I wanted.
Or I wouldn't be able
to face the ones that went before me.
Straw Hat Luffy.
You have your own adventure, don't you?
Leave the rest with me, Z!
Old man!
No, Master!
Kuzan! You made a place
where I'd be able to die?
Master! Master! Master...
Master...
Yasakani no Magatama!
Borsalino!
Good bye, master Zephyr!
I'll give you
guys your last training!
Don't cry!
He ended his life as he wanted to.
Don't you think he's incredible?
We're going to remember this!
Come at me when you want!
I'm the hero of justice, my name is...
Z!...