Someone needs to stop Clearway Law.
Public shouldn't leave reviews for lawyers.
EDITED BY ACAPCOOL999
PLEASE DO NOT REMOVE CREDIT ORIGIN RESYNC
Show time!
What's that?
GREAT!
Nami, is this ship is the right place?
Yes, the world's largest entertainment city.
and the only one in the whole world.
Gran Tesoro!
Eh, it's not an island huh?
All of it ...
Let's go to the casino!
Yeah!
Ah, what is that shining thing?
This....
Gold powder?
I-It's real gold.
Guys, quickly grab as much as possible!
Everything becomes golden colour! Gold!
Super!
Even the water is become gold.
Interesting too, yes.
Faster! Franky!
Leave it to me!
Coup de Burst!
Advanced!
GREAT!
Meroline!
What is this?
Great!
Who are they?
What the hell?
We are the long-long pirate! Hand over your valuable things!
We have never lost in seizing the money!
Hah? What's that?
Take this!
We're been fire!
What?
Tesoro-sama!
There are pirates who outrage us!
No problem.
Might as well be used as entertainment only.
That...?
Yes. It seems they are the Straw Hat Pirates.
Straw Hat Pirates?
Well, well.
It will be interesting.
What? What?
Submit, your valuables!
Geez, how dare you interrupt my sleep.
I do not know who you are ...
but if I had pulled my sword, be prepared!
Of course!
Santoryuu
Onigiri!
Hoi, Hoi ...
This drink could be spilled.
What?
Annoying!
Robin-cwaan!
Sorry!
Thank you, Sanji.
Stop!
Girl, where's your money ?!
Let me tell you the good news.
We do not have any money.
Your meat and bone
was cut!
Although I had not had meat, anyway.
Keep shooting!
Radical Beam
It's still not okay!
Forward, if you dare!
Got you!
Usopp!
Are you alright? Hold on!
Shit!
I remember. They are ...
Hey ...
Long head!
What are ...
... You doing ...
... to Sunny ?!
Long head?
I would...
make you shut up!
Pirate captain long-long!
Alexander Alex Kent Paul Harris
Hendrix Howard Rudolph Eccentrix
Not effective!
What?
Because I'm made from rubber!
Gomu-Gomu no
Jet
Wait, not yet --
Pistol!
The captain had been defeated!
Run!
What's wrong?
What is that?
Great!
Gold Sprash!
The entertainment city in the world!
Welcome to the Gran Tesoro!
Extraordinary!
The place is interesting!
Masterful!
This city is great!
Wow. Amazing!
You Straw Hat Pirates, right?
Greetings.
Hello, pretty lady.
I was the chef at our ship, Sanji.
It was very lucky to be met by a woman as beautiful as you.
Well, you philandering yes, I got goosebumps lo.
I serve VIP guests, my name Baccarat.
Do you know us?
Of course.
All the pirates were chased by the Navy and the Government.
Everything is recorded in this VIP's book.
Isn't it?
Looks like we're famous, yes.
Yes. If you need anything, just tell me.
Please.
Tortoise!
Great. What is this?
Transportation?
Yes. This is a car turtles. One of transportation here.
Great. Turtles as the engine huh?
Yes. This car is running on eight golden turtles.
Tortoise.
Come on, please get into the car.
So soft.
There are also drink in here.
Please enjoy this drink
Sake is also there.
Is there any cola?
Yosh, let's go!
Good. Let's go to the town of Gran Tesoro.
Depart!
Tortoise!
This car is a comfortable one, huh.
Yes. This car is made with emphasis on passenger's comfort.
OK. The first is the business area.
Like the dream state, yes.
No, no ...
This is just half of it.
The overall length of the ship is 10 kilometers.
10 kilometer?
Ya.
There are hotels, shopping malls, and of course there is the amusement park and swimming pool.
Even theater and a golf course was also there.
The big ship is the same as one country.
This place even has been officially recognized by the Government and the world.
This ship is powered by a giant turtle,
so as to surround the entire world.
Next is the first-class area.
Masterful.
The town is made of gold, huh.
Yes. King in Gran Tesoro, Tesoro-sama,
very fond of gold.
Gold in worldwide.
The city also included the city of his dreams.
Great. His money is certainly a great deal huh?
Yes. Tesoro-together has been recognized as the richest man in the world.
He is well-known performers, and highly respected.
In addition, he also served as King.
So fantastic! (Remarkable)
Hey. All the goods here is very valuable, right?
I think so, I wish I could steal it from the beginning.
Unfortunately, it can not.
Look over there!
Denden Mushi CCTV ...
Correct. In every corner of the city is already installed CCTV.
If there is a thief or a group of rebels ...
according to city regulations, they have been indicted.
Detained underground.
Hey. Hurry to the Casino, Casino!
Of course, but ...
Before that...
You all deserve to wear that attire.
Hey, can we really wear this?
Yes of course, because you are a VIP guest.
Here is a gambling town. You are free as long that you pay.
Hm hm, that's right yeah.
Wait, you do not know anything, right?
What if we lose?
Anyway it's good!
Hear me talk!
This casino, huh?
Correct. Gran Tesoro's pride.
The largest hotel in the world.
The Reoro!
Great. All are from gold!
Everything is made of pure gold.
Weeh. What the hell are you doing?
Buy yourself flowers.
Please.
These guys VIP's guests, right?
What?
Please, buy this flower ...
Come on, buy, have mercy on us is ...
Yes, Yes ...
How much it costs?
5000 berry.
That's expensive!
If you do not have money, we will not be able to be free!
Hey, I'm begging you, do you?
What does it mean?
Well, well. Children...
Why are you disturbing my guests?
Here is not the place for a child like you.
Quick, go home.
Sister.
Sorry. Let's go!
Wait.
Huh? Hey...
Sorry for the interruption.
Then, let's continue the journey.
Tonight, your voice is very beautiful, huh, Carina.
Good work.
Tesoro-sama were still far superior.
Tesoro-sama.
Baccarat has managed to convince the Straw Hat Pirates.
Oh, I see?
The man who beat Doflamingo is very troublesome.
Then we'll see what they can bring something for me?
Ohh, that name ...
I've heard about it.
"I will be the Pirate King" is a silly word.
Right?
You're drunk.
Yes, yes.
Hey.
Can I ask one thing?
Why are you laughing in front of me?
I do not...
Who decide that you can laugh in this town ...
Who is he?
I-It was ... of course you, Tesoro-sama.
No!
Tesoro-sama, please forgive me.
I will never laugh again.
So? You already understand, yes.
Then that's good.
Please!
Look! She squirms!
That's an entertainment!
What will we do with them, Straw Hat Pirates?
I wonder how? Complete with money alone.
OK.
It will definitely be a very interesting show.
So this is a casino, huh?
It's really big, huh?
Yes. There are many types of games here.
If anyone you do not understand, please ask me alone.
I'll show you the way.
Forgive me.
Anyway, we lend 200 million berry chips first.
200 million?
Can we really wear this?
Certainly. Do not hesitate.
Thanks. I play first!
Luffy!
We also!
Wait!
Come on!
Ya!
Wait a minute!
Geez, their own wishes!
What is this game?
Yes. Here is a turtle car racing game.
Racing?
Correct. 100 million berries for this game registration's fee.
100 million berry?
OK. I will explain the rules of the race of turtle cars!
Hotshell!
You guys, watch it if you lose!
Leave it to us!
We must win!
There are 6 participants' cars.
You can invade and disrupt the opponent.
Anyway, whoever got here first is the winner!
The race lasts for 10 rounds.
Well, we start.
Ready to go!
The race begins!
Well, who first led the ...
Oh, that lead is Jimmy Myers!
Hey, move over!
What the hell?
Ah, Jimmy has been eliminated ...
And the lead now is ...
Advanced!
He continues to go forward without giving up.
Straight warrior!
Sir!
Dead end, we must turn to the other directions!
Do not inconsequential!
In my dictionary, there is no term revolving direction!
Nice, Sir!
Ah! Off the track!
The remaining 4 cars!
Oh, now that is pursuing is
Straw Hat, Luffy!
The first position is occupied by Whitejack!
I will not let you race!
Kiruko-chan!
OK!
Look out!
Oh no!
Ah, they are slipping!
And here they go!
Hurry, Usopp!
I know!
The first position is occupied by Whitejack.
And 3 other cars continue to pursue.
Whitejack has been off the track!
The great strength of Kent Beef Jr.
Uh oh!
Team Count successful in racing!
This is bad!
Damn!
What?!
Come on!
Kill them, Pork!
There is sharp lap in front of them!
Will they pass through it?
Ah! Off the track!
Oh, nice shot!
Gomu-Gomu no
Rocket!
Come on!
Marry me!
It's them!
Ah, what happened?
Luffy!
Straw Hat's team back again!
Impossible!
That sounds good.
Come on!
The last round!
They were racing each other!
Who will be the winner?
Come on!
The winner is the team of the Straw Hats!
Yosh, we gain great money!
Yosha!
Great!
A lot!
Huh?
Win again ?!
Yosh, very good!
Cool!
Great.
We immediately got a 30 million berry.
You guys are great.
Then, we must immediately go to the VIP room.
What's that?
Only the winners can enter.
If you win a special gambling there, you can become a billionaire.
Want to try it?
How?
Of course. We're going to win.
That's great! (That is good)
I can't wait.
Are we there yet?
Wait a minute.
What is that creature?
He set up all game here, Tanaka-san.
Welcome.
He Nuke Nuke devil fruit eaters.
He can penetrate any object.
Guests, please sign in.
Great, right in!
Is this the VIP?
What the hell is this place?
Eh, gambling specifically placed here huh.
Yes.
Hey, Hey.
Navy is also here?
Really! Bad!
Take it easy.
Gran Tesoro is the place that has been officially recognized by the government and the world.
Navy is forbidden to touch a pirate.
That's our rule.
Apparently so.
Ready.
Then let us begin.
Who is he?
He is Dice.
Unbeaten fighters in the underworld.
He is the underworld champion.
Because there was no one dared to fight him,
now he works here.
Yess!
Great strength!
That axe was nice as well, huh.
Be prepared!
He flew!
Wadaw!
Yeash!
What is he doing with his axe?!!
The joy!
2 and 6 odd!
How? Interesting right?
I do not know what he is doing.
Alright guys, the present coins of the game is $ 300 million berry.
300 million!
It's a chance we become billionaire.
Just do it!
This place that really makes me shocked!
Good! Bet it all!
Wait, woi!
Yeah!
The joy!
1 odd!
Yosh!
Masterful!
Steady, steady!
Luffy-sama is great.
You're so lucky.
We certainly can! We could really rich ...
Truly...
Just normal!
Tesoro-sama!
It Tesoro-sama!
Well, well.
Welcome to the Gran Tesoro.
You guys having fun?
Who are you?
Yes, yes. Nice to meet you.
I am the King of this vessel.
My name Gild Tesoro.
So you're being called the King of entertainment, huh?
I am a person who will become the Pirate King!
Why did you even show off ?!
Able to meet the future Pirate King,
really gives me the creeps.
Oh yes...
Why don't you play against me?
Play?
It's a great opportunity.
These are the rules.
If you win against me,
I would pay 10 times as much.
10 times?
Of course if you lose, you don't have to pay 10 times.
I have a lot of money and they are not inexhaustible.
I think such regulations very exciting.
Well, how?
Alright, I will not lose!
Hey, was this okay ?!
Now this is a great opportunity.
I believe with Luffy's luck!
Yosh, I have decided!
Bet it all!
Luffy-sama is great.
Risking it all are really great.
Luffy, wait!
I will support you.
Let's play!
Hey, how?
Yeesh!
I lose.
Impossible.
Luffy lost?
Well. Good work.
It's really great shows, Baccarat.
Shows? What does it mean?
You devil fruit eaters, right?
Eh?
Yes. Correct.
I'm Raki Raki devil fruit eater.
I could change the fortunes of man into misfortune.
Misfortune?
So, Luffy ...
So I'm being unlucky now?
Ya.
But I do not feel anything.
What is this?
My stomach hurts!
Impossible!
Luffy could had abdominal pain ?!
Banana peel?!
Raki Raki fruit is creepy!
Is this not cheating?
Cheating?
Let me tell you one thing.
This is a city ordinance
people who have been deceived here
just a loser.
We have been deceived!
Then, money lending totaling 3 x 20 million berry that ...
Will you give it back?
Can you afford that much?
You should work to restore the money, really.
Work?
People who work in this town
are the people who owe me because they lost in games.
If you refuse, we have no other choice but to act harshly!
Interesting too.
Try it if you dare!
Ouch.
My leg sprain.
You okay, Baccarat-cwaan ?!
Gotcha!
Bad!
Hot, hot ...
Banana...?!
Intelligent enemies, yes.
You're a fool, huh ?!
He disappeares!
Again!
Damn, what the hell is he ?!
Strong Right!
The joy!
Nice punch.
Again, again, please!
What the hell is he ?!
Let me fight!
The fight will be over faster if the boss is defeated.
Interesting too. So you want to beat me
in my own town?
Of course.
This...
Zoro!
Don't move, guys!
Selfish, too, huh?
If you move, your whole body will be gold.
The strength of what?
Gold.
I'm Goru Goru fruit eaters.
With my gold, I'm free to cheat anyone.
What have you done to Zoro ?!
When entering this town,
You saw the gold powder, isn't it?
At that time, I put my gold strength
into your body.
The entire city is ...
is under my control.
As well as all human beings.
If so, return all the money you are borrowing.
Total it all worth 3 x 20 million berry!
So from the beginning you were ...
No one can defeat me!
Do not be too happy, yet...
Do not move!
Who?
Shut up!
You...
I understand!
We will prepare the money!
Give us time!
Hey, Nami!
Deal.
The deadline until tomorrow at 12 am.
If the money is not there ...
I will execute this person in front all of you!
What?
I know. I'll promise.
Huuooii!
Ah, of course.
This is the most exciting game!
Can you prepare the money until tomorrow?
or you will perish together ?!
Let me see the interesting shows.
I'm hungry!
Most importantly, we must think the ways to save Zoro!
Of course, but eat first!
Well, why?
But, we have to fill the stomach first.
Well, that's right.
Yosh, Let's eat!
There was a meat's smell!
Meat!
Ah, Luffy-san!
Geez.
Better cool off first.
Oh, sorry.
Wait!
Why?
Oh, looks like there is progress in you, huh.
Cat burglar.
You are also increasingly inattentive huh, Wolf burglar.
Duh!
Apparently it you, Carina.
Long time no see, Nami.
You're a friend of Tesoro?
You guys know each other?
Yes, right.
Nami and I are fellow thieves long time ago.
Yes, right?
It is not like that.
When I was a thief in East Blue,
me and her just often fought for treasure.
Do you often lose you?
The way you use is really tacky!
What do you said, cat burglar!
Wolf burglar!
Do not fight!
Eat first!
Forgive my attitude.
But, I was there as Tesoro's men.
So I had no other choice.
Relax, do not sweat it.
Don't say that you want to find Tesoro's treasure?
Tesoro's treasure?
According to legend, some wealth in this city
is 20% berry of the property around the world.
People call it Tesoro's treasure.
It is an honor for the thieves who managed to steal it.
All the thieves of the world trying to steal it,
But, until now no one else managed to steal it.
I've been stealing the key from Tesoro.
Key?
On the top floor alone, there are vault full gold.
So, you're ...
Yes, I'm after the vault!
And get the money worth 500 billion berry!
500 billion?
Was that great ?!
The vault's gold could buy a small country.
State?
Tesoro give part of his property in Tenryuubito.
Tenjou King, ya?
He uses the power of money to control Tenryuubito.
That's why the Navy and the World Government,
dare not complicate Tesoro, huh.
It turned out that way.
But, not only for the control of pirates,
He also uses money to control the dark world.
That the goal he really is.
So, if my advice ...
if we could get the money, your friend could return safely.
Rather than bother as it was, what about we just directly attack it?
You've seen it, right?
In our bodies there is strength Tesoro gold.
It makes us hard to beat.
Therefore, we have to play crafty.
And using the city's regulations for the win.
What can I do, huh?
Hey Nami, what she really can be trusted?
Now it's just the only way, right?
You sure this will work ?!
As long as there is a chance.
Yosh, let's do it!
That's it.
Geez, what can we do.
Our goal was 500 billion berry.
We're going to steal Tesoro's money!
It is betting that risked lives.
But, I'll give you 30% of its course.
No kidding! I gave the key!
There's a lot of us!
Without me, you can't do anything!
What did you said?
What are you doing?
You're okay, Tempo?
Hey, hey.
What do you guys do on Tesoro-sama's men like us?
Sorry, forgive us.
Shit!
Your debt has increase 20 thousand berry!
Impossible!
They are ... children earlier.
They were small and had to pay the debt for the sake of the family.
Forced labour and slave of Tesoro.
What?
Do you mind?
Wait a minute.
What are the children have done?
The store manager!
Don't you know how to educate children?
Please forgive them.
Taught by Tesoro-sama together,
have you forgotten?
You have to smile at customers!
Come on, smile at me!
Do you want your whole family dead?
More sincere, again!
Sorry, forgive them.
Fake smile!
They jerk!
Teach your people with the right, you know ?!
Come on, why?
Uncle!
Manager!
I'm fine, Rikka.
Go back to work.
Hoi!
Why did not you fight back?
It's no use!
Why?
If there is no money, there is no freedom at all!
Brother!
Right on time, too.
Chiper Pol .... or is called what?
This time is for gold packaging to Tenryuubito's ship.
Leave it to Spandam of CP-0's!
Well, I'm counting on you.
This is not how.
Woah, what?
Please accept.
That person!
What is wrong? You do not want?
This, this.
Anyway, I received this first.
By the way, now this Straw Hat Pirates was on this ship, lo.
What?
Don't make any trouble.
Will this run smoothly?
We leave it to people like that?
Send someone more useful again here.
More useful in Chiper Pol.
And also, tell him to send 10 Navy ships here.
Ready to execute.
I knew it.
So, where is Max?
If it is, I still do not get.
That man, surely he was scared there.
Oh yes, they are also there, lo.
Who?
Straw Hat Pirates.
10 warships, you say?
Do not make me laugh!
Plus, for pirates like Tesoro?
Why the Navy must help the enemy?
Since when CP-0 become Tesoro's men?
This is not for Tesoro!
This is for the success of the mission.
Just do your job.
Shut up and prepare 10 ships!
Who do you think you're talking to?
Do not be proud of you!
Rob Lucci!
EDITED BY ACAPCOOL999
PLEASE DO NOT REMOVE CREDIT ORIGIN RESYNC
Geez.
Until made posters of all.
Hoi, Luffy!
Enough for today!
Tomorrow, we should be ready.
Carina.
We're ready.
Oh?
Where have you been?
There is little affairs.
I thought you were going to run away again.
I run away? When?
Do not pretend to forget.
When we steal the treasure of the pirate,
and we both caught.
Oh.
At that time, we both caught
and was severely tortured.
So, who wants to die first?
We will restore everything.
The money we get for this, we will give everything.
So, forgive us both.
Carina!
It's OK.
Come back before sunset.
If you do not come back, he'll kill.
Trust me!
I will definitely be back!
But, you never go back!
Time has run out.
Your friend is sneaky as well, right.
He is not my friend.
Hey, let's make a deal.
I would give my treasure there somewhere.
And a calling into a shameful my life with it.
I'm sorry, Carina. I've took all of it.
Impossible!
That's unfortunate, yes.
Money for the harvest has been stolen.
Don't raised again, it is.
I almost died, you know!
When I returned the money to him,
both of us would be killed.
At that time, I had no other choice.
You are!
If this time you fool me again, I will not forgive you!
Wolf burglar.
Yes.
Cat burglar.
Let's do the plan.
Yosh!
But, what's the plan ?!
Duh! I just explained it ?!
Here's where the gold's vault located.
High class area.
That's where the gold's vault is.
In it, there is money worth 500 billion berry.
Floors, walls, and roof are made of gold.
So it's rather hard to crack.
Doesn't it indestructible?
Don't. Tesoro is an intelligent power user.
The whole system in this city is connected to him.
If there is the slightest attack,
he will find out soon.
Hoi hoi, then how do we get in?
Through this way. Here is a spiral staircase.
This way is not guarded.
But this place is full of Denden Mushi CCTV.
If not being careful, we will be caught.
But there is an exit.
So, I need your help.
First, Team A.
You will climb the hotel to the top floor!
Sneak into the watch tower.
And go to the Control Room.
Exactly upper part of the room is where the Denden Mushi's Host.
If you take over that, CCTV at the spiral staircase will be dead.
Next, Team B.
The first step is to take the elevator.
Straight to the VIP's area.
We must not be caught from Tanaka-san.
Go inside the high class area.
and from there, we should take the door.
If we pass the guards,
we just have to take the big road at the back door.
and follow the spiral staircase.
While the Denden Mushi CCTV has been dead,
we should go up through the staircase faster.
While in front of gold's vault. By using these keys,
I'll open it.
Just take the money by camouflaged
and go out through the main door.
By doing so, mission accomplished!
Yosh!
Still half, huh.
How do I get up there?
Leave it to me.
I've got a spy tool given Usopp.
Spy tool?
Well, just watch.
Franky
Sponge Rocket!
Great! Spy tools!
Isn't it?
Eh?
Oh yeah, Sanji-san can fly, right?
How can I fly with carrying this heavy load?
Besides, if I had to protect the women, I'm ready to do it.
Ssh. They come.
EDITED BY ACAPCOOL999  RESYNC ORIGIN PLEASE DO NOT REMOVE CREDIT
Eh.
Hello guards.
Carina-san.
Hey, where it would be escorted to?
Anoo, this would be escorted to the VIP room.
There are customers who were waiting for him.
Let me see.
Great.
Huge.
Yes, it's huge.
Very beautiful.
Yes, beautiful.
Thank you. The spirit drove him, huh.
Good!
In this way, smoothly.
Three boxes of metal dice.
Who is this?
Carisan-sama, please sign in.
It's beautiful scenery!
Be careful!
Stay out of sight!
Good!
Yosh!
Our destination is where the guards are.
I understand!
Luffy!
You're okay?
I also want to fall!
Hold me!
Coup de Boo!
Come on!
Finally!
Defrauding success!
Let's go!
That the place where the guards are!
From here, turn right to spiral staircase!
The road is maintained.
Leave it to me.
Onee-sama really great.
Come in.
I've never been here before, so I do not know what happened here.
This...
Red-eyed owl.
What's that?
If you were exposed to the red eye,
they will respond and issue a trap.
They...
I knew it.
What is wrong?
I know the direction in which they point.
"Up, down, up."
Masterful. You know the language of animals.
That does not make me happy at all.
Come on!
Now!
Stop!
Now run!
Come on!
Bad!
Run fast!
Brook! Quick!
Yes! Wait, I had trouble running!
Ah, bad!
Brook!
E-Eh?
It seems that you were not living beings, they do not respond.
Really cruel!
We've arrived at the spiral staircase, huh.
Franky. What's the situation?
Almost done.
Yosh.
That's it. The Denden Mushi's Host.
It is Denden Mushi that sends the entire signal.
By connecting with the cable number 3.
It will be connected to CCTV in a spiral staircase.
That one, huh.
If we put a white Denden Mushi there,
it's CCTV will die.
Yosh. Understood.
If you completed, return immediately!
Now!
Almost!
Be careful!
Yosh!
Yosh. Now stay put Denden Mushi.
This...
Infiltration!
Brother!
H-He!
Hey, caught you?
Bad!
Shoot!
They are there!
We retreat, Luffy!
Yes.
EDITED BY ACAPCOOL999  RESYNC ORIGIN PLEASE DO NOT REMOVE CREDIT
Franky!
I can't believe you dare to go into a place like this.
Location!
Geez.
Don't you care about the lives of your friends that you to dare to do this?
Zoro!
How? It's beautiful, isn't it?
Do you not feel that it was a suitable place to execute it?
This is an entertainment.
How, Straw Hat?
Laugh.
I will not laugh!
I'll punch you!
Gold Bumper
There's no point!
I'm unbeaten in this city!
Can not be separated!
Remember this well!
Without the money in the world, the world will not do!
Being a slave is the only option!
Shut up!
This thing will not be able to make me lose!
This thing?!
If you want to do,
just try it!
Hopefully we can meet again in the future!
Are you entertained? This is the name of entertainment.
Please wait for the next release of Gran Tesoro.
What the hell.
Indeed ... against it will be pointless.
Can I take them all?
Its up to you.
Importantly, first check all places!
Ready to execute!
Oh no, they're here!
If this continues, we will be in danger!
Importantly, we have to get out of here first.
They are there!
Sanji-kun!
Leave it to me!
Concasse!
Diable Jamble
(New Kick :))
Wait, you're safe here!
After them!
Through this way!
What place is this?
It is among the top Tenryuubito area.
Tenryuubito?
They...
Hey, if this keeps up ...
Escape is not an option.
This place determines the winner.
Brook!
Stupid ... it was not him!
Franky.
What happened?
Where am I?
The place is filled with gold!
Everything is made of gold, huh.
Great.
Give us water.
Water.
Give us a drink.
What?
We beg, we will give all our money.
We do not even have water.
Shit.
Damn!
You have loads of money, huh?
There's no point!
Even gold is not useful.
In the city's golden prison, gold is the most valuable.
Gold is the most valuable?
Yes.
Yes. All the gold that is stored by Tesoro here ...
Formed into a golden city of gold ...
Many people are already controlled by gold.
There is only gold and no food.
Tesoro greatly enjoyed our suffering.
Uncle who?
Me?
I'm just a loser.
I remember him!
You're Raise Max ,isn't it?
Who is that?
You do not know, huh?
Raise Max, not just the person who is unbeatable ...
He is a legendary casino players.
Since I was a child, I was admired the great man.
If I'm not wrong, you joined the Revolutionary Army.
It's true I was Raise Max.
People who are unbeaten in the casino.
But there are two reasons.
He has lost the bet of his life?
But I'm not wearing that name.
And had no connection with the Revolutionary Army.
I could have lost the whole town.
When I lose in the casino,
Raise Max is dead.
Shit. We must hasten to help Zoro.
Hey, was there is an exit here?
There is no exit.
There was no other choice but to die.
Shit.
Yosh. Let me crush it!
Gomu-Gomu no
Wait wait, if the gold was destroyed Tesoro will know.
Anyway what you can with your hands like that?
If my hand couldn't do it, I could still use my head!
Gomu-Gomu no
Stop!
That's enough, Straw Hats boy!
Just give up.
As long as there is still gold in your body,
you can't beat Tesoro!
Then, we just get the gold out from the body!
Is there a way to get it out?
That...
Not possible if there is no way at all.
Tesoro gold strength is the same as devil fruit powers.
By using sea water, the gold that is in our bodies will disappear.
Yosh. So I just need to find the sea.
Useless. If someone is doing it on this ship,
Tesoro would not allow such a thing!
The only way to get to the sea water was through a pipe.
This place is entirely made of gold.
Until to the bottom was also made of gold.
At the bottom of this place,
There is a pipe that is connected with the sea water.
But, the only way is this hole.
Many people who try it for this, but they all failed.
Bat?
This is a small chance. Give it up!
No!
I will not give up!
I'm going!
Franky, quickly went down!
Yoo!
Luffy surely soon be able to go through this,
and could even beat the Tesoro that!
He is a person who believes that nothing is impossible!
It's like gambling, right?
It's worth risking my life.
"Nothing is impossible", huh.
Easy to be said.
Interesting.
Thank you, Roronoa Zoro.
Blessings, our ticket sales set a new record.
How? Did you have fun?
Not so bad, huh.
They will not be able to get the money.
Do you still believe in your friends?
As if there could still be trusted?
Actually, in hopes it would be despair.
I've heard it ~
What actually happens ~?
Is it true there are thieves who steal our money ~?
What's going on?
You are not polite at all.
F-Forgive us!
The gold's vault has been tightened, so please do not worry about it.
No.
I could not believe you guys talk!
Now, order all the people to go to the vault!
Impossible!
How dare you fight me!
You probably also associates of with the thieves!
So do you mean to blame us?
N-Not like that.
We did not dare.
Do you want to fight Tenryuubito ?!
You know the consequences, right?
You understand?
G-Good. Immediately implemented.
Hurry up, otherwise we are toast.
Correct.
But there was nothing more to be done.
We already do not have time anymore to execute Zoro!
How much are they ?!
Bad!
You're okay ?!
Yes.
Come on!
Zoro!
Straw Hats boy!
This sound ?!
What?!
The fans were huge!
The road should go down from here.
But this is impossible if you can pass.
It is a trap created Tesoro.
Because it is made of sea stone,
Haki, weapons, or the devil fruit powers will not succeed.
Just give up!
Don't want! Let me!
Do not!
You idiot!
Luffy!
It was impossible, surrender!
Not impossible! I will never give up!
Shit!
Once again!
Straw Hats boy!
He had crossed the limits!
We should go from here.
Still not yet!
I ... I will not give up!
I...
I understand.
Let me destroy the fan.
Uncle.
What would you do?
It was tantamount to gambling.
Focus is required.
Now!
EDITED BY ACAPCOOL999  RESYNC ORIGIN PLEASE DO NOT REMOVE CREDIT
Max!
Uncle!
Don't want! I will not give up!
I will never give up!
I will not give up!
Success!
Nice!
Stop!
It is impossible if only on his own!
You!
I do not want to return in empty hand!
We want freedom!
Great!
Stalled!
Straw Hats boy!
You must beat Tesoro!
Well!
I know!
Success!
It's the pipe!
Finally got around to.
So this is the main entrance gold's vault.
Just to enter this key, then ...
This is...
our victory.
Showtime!
What does this mean?
You're shocked, right?
It is the theater.
Theater ...
Correct.
Don't you think here is the good place to execute Roronoa Zoro ?!
Look!
Zoro!
The scenery is nice, is not it?
Neither here is not gold warehouse, nor the 5,000 billion berry.
All gold is already packed in the Tenryuubito's.
You all have been deceived!
By the great of me, and Carina.
Carina! You...?
I have said from the beginning, right?
This is Gran Tesoro.
The fooled one will lose.
Impossible!
Damn!
Looking good!
Good!
We are always watching you.
You become a tool of our gambling.
How stupid you think there gold's vault.
We've worked hard to set up this game for you.
Good work.
For the sake of earning money with his life but in the end even cheated.
This what we called a great show!
Very beautiful.
Because you have given an interesting game.
Instead, I show interesting performances.
And that this was really great.
Luffy!
Done!
Well, Luffy! Destroy it!
And remove the seawater!
I know!
Gomu-Gomu no
Kane
Dangerous! I can't hit the sea!
My body felt the difference, the gold is gone!
Success! We did it!
In this way, we are free!
We are free!
What happened?
Bad!
We are caught ?!
Luffy!
Franky!
Damn!
Hope that turns into despair.
This is the main entertainment!
Money is power. Money is everything.
People who have no money, can't get anything.
Couldn't get the love, or dream,
Can't have the strength, or even freedom.
Even...
Hope was also not able to.
Though already come this far!
Luffy!
Noisy!
Asshole bastard!
Sanji-kun!
Then ... the stage at last!
The scenes are very good!
Tesoro!
Then you just enjoy it.
Roronoa Zoro ...
will be executed!
All...
Let's give applause to them!
Gold Sprash!
Goodbye, Straw Hat Pirates!
With this, I'm the one who wins.
This is an entertainment!
What is this?
What happened?
What does this mean?
What are you laughing at?
Who actually been fooled?
What?
I-It ... The sea.
What did you say?
Tesoro-sama!
Through this way!
Great!
This sea!
Rain sea water!
With this, Tesoro will not be in power again!
We are free!
Finally...
we are free!
Suupeerrr
Franky!
Looks like we make it in time.
What are you doing?
Actually we already know your intention to shows the gold powder from the beginning.
Thanks to the children of your loyalty, Carina.
Forgive me...
Parties that I chose was ...
Straw Hat Pirates.
Carina.
All that you have seen, we were set.
For us, gold's vault or gold, not a problem!
What is important is removing sea water.
It was also one of the plan.
Our goal from the beginning was open seawater pipes.
Of course. Luffy didn't know anything.
We don't need to follow your rules again.
We will also fight!
Now, you must follow our rules!
We are pirates.
We were able to act independently.
Then, return our friend!
TESORO!
Luffy!
Good Luffy! The plan went well!
Plan?
Yes. Now, beat that guy!
Dammit!
Eh, didn't you said it yourself?
This is Gran Tesoro.
Who have been deceived is a loser!
This is new...
The main entertainment!
I would...
beat you!
How is your mood today?
When your hope turned into despair.
What's so hopeless.
How is it desperation.
I will be a star!
Do not sing something that is meaningful!
Useless!
Noisy, Tesoro!
If only we had the money.
In this way, we are partners.
Stupid brat! You don't want to pay?
The song was nice, yes.
Someday I will change.
Damn ...
But my heart will not change.
Just change, I will definitely buy you.
If you have money, you can give anything.
Noisy!
Thank you!
With this feeling, I've been pleased.
... I'm very happy!
In front of me...
Tesoro-sama ...
Don't laugh at me!
What?
So what if you managed to open it?
I just close it again!
Bad! My handle!
Coup de Burst!
All the power in this town is in my hands!
Anything that can be laughed at ...
I define it!
Impossible!
I've had enough!
He was horrifying!
What is this?
Then let's begin to its greatest show!
What do you know, the Straw Hats?
I'm the one who controls this world!
You are nothing but scum!
I have the power of a god!
Noisy!
I already told you, I will not give up
Gear Third
Gomu-Gomu no
Elephant Gun
Do not be too confident!
You...
Sister.
Luffy...
You can too.
Shucks!
Passable.
Soon ... launch
The joy!
Show your abilities again!
Do you really want to start
This is not an ordinary steel, eh.
This is the power of granting of the Tesoro-sama, Gold Armor!
Gold Armor?!
In other words, our strength
increased dramatically.
Then, you want money, isn't?
I'll give you a special gold prize!
Well, make it more interesting!
You are mine.
Ouch.
What is this? Power ...
You're careless.
It was a chain is made from sea rocks.
Straw Hats!
What a coincidence!
I will eliminate you now!
You...
who?
Damn, if you forget ...
I'll help you remember!
Satan where are you ?!
You...
I've decided ...
I will not give it up again.
I have to fight.
I am indeed...
want freedom!
Huh?
That's it!
What's freedom? Stupid!
Look!
Do you think you can win?
Hear! In this world the one that has the power will win!
It's not necessarily ...
What?
Uncle?
Hoi, boy!
I would also join. Calm down, we will win!
We definitely win this fight!
Trust me!
I was the legendary casino players, Raise Max.
Well!
Let us seize the freedom!
They!
You...
just annoying!
Yesh...
Ui-Tora Gari
The joy of ...
Senhachiju Pound Ho
Shut up!
Again, taste this!
You...
Did you know?
How to avoid losing the gamble?
Take back the coin, then use it to play again!
Interesting too.
Let's start!
Well, can you arrest me?
Shit!
Let me torture you first ...
Then kill!
Noisy!
Do not move, yes.
Damn!
What did he do?!
He even took his ally's luck ?!
Anyway, this is an opportunity.
Midori Boshi - Dokuro Bakahatsu
What?!
Eh, once lucky.
Strength of Raki Raki fruit,
Not just take other people's luck,
but also could use the luck of others.
In other words, now I'm invincible.
If I fight you anyway.
By this alone is enough.
I will beat you just with this coin.
What...?
We will not be defeated so easily!
Well, we'll see.
I'll blast you!
NO!
Eh, once lucky.
How should we fight it?
We just kept attacking.
He might not be lucky continues.
What you can survive until then?
What to do!
What?
Oii!
Impossible!
Eh, that's only?
This is just a warm up.
Damn, how about this ?!
I have an idea.
Hissatsu
Usopp da!
Well, well. He escaped?
Friends are cowards, huh.
Tesoro!
Luffy!
It is over yet?
Not yet!
Grizzly Magnum
Not too bad.
Shot of the 500 million are great!
Shoot!
What?
Wait a minute!
Aren't we not commanded to help Tesoro and get the Tenjou gold?
And follow the plan.
But why do we even shot at it?
We can hurt people!
Continue?
Hey, Navy!
Why are you shooting at Tesoro?
Hei!
What are you doing?
Say something!
Quick help us!
Hello hello ...
Keep shooting!
This is for the success of the mission.
Destroy Tesoro!
Navigate the entire cannon!
Ready!
Target : Tesoro!
Shoot!
Hiken
What was your purpose is actually here, Revolutionary Army?
Instead of business as usual?
I will not let you go with your own wishes, CP-0!
Additionally, this is the fight my brother.
I will not let you bother him.
Tch. Navy just only intervened!
I'll show you the consequences
the power of the gods!
Is this your justice?
No, but freedom!
I do not care!
Fear ...
This is the power of a god!
Tesoro!
Gomu-Gomu no
Jet Hawk!
Full strength!
Gold Emperor!
Straw Hats brat!
How can you?
Nice expression, Carina!
I'm very disappointed in you!
Carina!
Nami...
Why did you help me?
I'm just returning the favor.
Eh?
At that time, in fact you want to help me, right?
You've been fooled, huh?
You!
Your treasures ...
I'll get it ...
Stupid!
At that time, I understand completely!
Get him!
In order to save both of us, are you willing to risk your life.
Nami.
Carina...
You are our friends, right?
If so, trust me ...
They definitely will not lose.
We...
are a team, right?
Well!
Nami!
Team?
What is the point of trust like that ?!
Give it up!
With this, the game over!
Even so...
I believe in them!
Tesoro!
Remove your hand!
Laugh, Straw Hat!
He still believe you!
You've lost a bet with me!
Your lives are mine!
Everything on this ship is my slave!
Everything is mine!
You're the ... the kind of person I hate most!
Remove your hand!
I told you smile!
I am free to do anything on my body!
Nami!
Right, Calina ?!
NAMI!
ROBIN!
Spider Net!
My friend is not yours!
Gear Four!
Gomu-Gomu no
Kong Gun
Great!
Damn you!
I could not give up.
You can't beat us.
Robin-chan, are you hurt?
No.
Oh, I see.
Forgive me.
Diable Jamble
Don't you dare to strike women!
Fucking animals!
With this, it already end!
Sorry to keep you waiting!
Eh, what for you get back here?
Usopp!
Of course. I will help my friend!
You sure can fight me?
Success!
Why...
I can be defeated ...
Probably ...
You're great. The lucky lady!
It's a miracle!
Jackpot?!
Only then, I will not lose!
Kokujo O Tatsumaki
Do not tell me!
Kokuton
Shi Shi Sonson
What's up with that joy?
What voice is exhausted?
Impossible!
The executives have been defeated!
F-Flee! '
Gran Tesoro is over!
All the money was gone!
My children ...
Where did you want to run?
What is this?
What?
Nami!
Franky!
Look!
How beautiful this gold!
I will conquer it all
We're going to drown!
I will make all witnessed it.
My dream is to create joy,
freedom and fortune ... into despair!
Tesoro!
Nice!
Angry, Straw Hat!
Something that you protect,
something that is valuable to you,
will be under my control!
Such is the world.
Everything is made of gold.
In that case...
I'll beat you!
Gomu-Gomu no
Leo Rex Bazooka
How? I am a god!
Gold Sprash!
What's so being god!
You're the only animals!
Warghh!
I am a person who will become the Pirate King!
I am very happy.
It is time
vicious
Great.
Straw Hats brat!
Successfully ...
Tesoro defeated!
This...
Tesoro!
So shocked, huh.
I thought he was a god descending from the sky.
This man is . . .
a beast!
Bring Tesoro!
Luffy!
What sound is that?
What's that!
Everything, quickly leave this place!
Tesoro intends to drown his ship!
Everything, quickly went to the ship!
There's no way out!
Go, hurry!
Robot!
Quick!
Carina too!
You go ahead!
I will stay on this ship.
If we all run together, the explosion will be faster.
If I stay on this ship, I can be a little far to the explosion.
What are you talking?
They are good friends, yes.
Struggling with you until the end makes me happy.
Carina.
Franky?!
I'm counting on.
I understand.
Carina!
Hey, where is he ?!
Its about to explode!
What does it mean?
Why there are fireworks ?!
There!
Captain Carina go first!
He ... Teases us!
He steals his ship!
The main objective he want is gold, huh.
We've used him.
Oh, so we're being lied to, huh?
Navy's shooting at us!
Yosh, All of it!
Let's go!
What is this?!
Wolf Burglar!
EDITED BY ACAPCOOL999  resynch ORIGIN PLEASE DO NOT REMOVE CREDIT
Someone needs to stop Clearway Law.
Public shouldn't leave reviews for lawyers.