Someone needs to stop Clearway Law.
Public shouldn't leave reviews for lawyers.
Script by Vegapunk Fansubs
www.vegapunk.com
Translation from Japanese:
Cornman from Vegapunk
Timing:
Hedi and Chopperrules from Vegapunk
Editing:
Tahz and SakuraDestiny from Vegapunk
Kohza!
Toto-ojisan!
Vivi!
Oi!
Pell!
Hey, Pell.
Yes?
Why do you practice fencing everyday?
Because I'm a guardian.
In order to protect this country,
I need to become stronger.
Who are you going to fight?
Well...
It's more about protecting than fighting.
Is it different?
The intention is different.
That's strange.
Papa.
Soon I will reach the country.
Don't be deceived.
That man is not the country's hero.
He's trying to steal Arabasta.
Please don't do anything rash!
What?
What is it?
Okama (gay) way
We caught an Okama!
What're you doing to Carue?!
There's no bait left...
You just ate a while ago, didn't you?!!
But...
Really, swan, swan...
To think, I was rescued by a pirate crew that I don't even know.
This favor, I shall never forget it.
We didn't catch you on purpose.
What're you doing in a place like this?
It's a long story.
Then, never mind.
Huh?
You're so cute!
I really like you.
Weird man.
Even so, at the moment I fell into the sea,
I thought I was done for.
You can't swim?
That's right, I'm a hammer.
Are you a Devil's Fruit user?
That's correct.
I'm a rarity in this world.
I ate the Devil's Fruit!
What's that, not very surprised...
You're nothing unusual.
You're so full of yourself.
There are abilities which you might not know.
Bastard! What you want is to provoke Nami-san, right?!
Since I've already seen so many, there's nothing that can surprise me now.
Fine, then.
I'll show you my amusing way of thanking.
Alright! Alright! Show… us…
Oi!
What're you...
No way.
Hey you! What're you doing?!
Wait.
I told you it was amusing.
It's no joke.
It's me!
Do I look like you?
Surprised?
This is the ability of the mane mane fruit I ate.
mane: mimicry
Amazing!
But if I touch myself with my left hand…
Look! I'm back to normal.
The voice too...
Even the complexion...
To be honest.
The truth is...
It isn't really necessary to hit...
Don't touch me.
Well, it's okay.
But if I...
With my right hand...
Touch the face of my partner...
Like this, I can...
Imitate anyone.
My body too.
Stop it!
Ouch!
You're amazing!
Amazing!
Furthermore, I can use my memory ability.
The faces...
I touched...
Before...
I definitely...
Won't...
Forget.
How is it?
My hidden talent.
So cool!
It's no joke!
Do whatever you want...
Hey, isn't that your ship?
Oh? Time to part already?
Don't be sad!
Farewells are natural things.
But, just don't forget this...
In friendship...
The time we've known each other doesn't matter!
Let's meet again!
Well, let's go guys!
Yes! Bon Kurei-sama!
Bon: Festival of the Dead; Kure: Year End
Eh?!
Bon Kurei?
Vivi?
Crocodile's subordinate!
Didn't you recognize his face?
I've never met him until now.
When he looked back into his memory,
My father's face was there.
Why my father's face...
For example, if you disguise yourself as a king…
You can do some bad things…
Dance powder… that guy…
What is that?
A powder that can make artificial rainfall.
The World Government prohibited its production.
That's a useful powder…
Why not use it?
Dance powder, right?
It makes clouds that aren't ready for rainfall…
Artificially grow into maturity in order to make it rain.
It steals the rain from neighboring countries.
And because of the frequent disputes between them…
The World Government had to prohibit it, huh?
2 years ago,
A large quantity of dance powder arrived to the port city of Arabasta, Nanohana.
At that time, except for Alubarna where the king lives,
Abnormal incidents of rain not falling occurred.
So they got suspicious of the king.
As if he used that powder to posses the rain.
Vivi!
Then, your father is a bad guy!
Idiot! He was framed!
Vivi's father wouldn't do such a thing.
He wouldn't.
It's as Sanji-san says.
My father isn't an egoistical person, so something must have happened.
At the port, the appearance of the person receiving the cargo was witnessed,
And judging by the hat he was wearing...
The identity of the man who was transporting the dance powder to the palace is now very clear.
I see, that guy was disguised as the king.
We let such a troublesome guy get away.
Everything was the plan of Crocodile, his organization's boss.
As he expected, it caused rebellion.
I see.
Make the royal army and the rebel army clash,
So when both are weakened, he'll steal the throne.
He disguises himself as the country's hero.
He stole the royal family's trust, the rain,
Even people's lives, and created disorder in Arabasta!
That's Crocodile!
Amazing!
Crocodile! Crocodile!
Sir Crocodile!
The Protector God of Arabasta!
The King of the Desert!
Crocodile! Crocodile!
Shut up, you ignorant fools!
Even if you say that, you always come and rescue us.
He's fantastic!
Well, call it whatever you want.
Your Majesty, Crocodile-sama has arrived.
It's a present, Mr. Cobra.
We always receive your help.
It's fine.
The royal army takes care of the rebel army. I take care of pirates.
Well, I'll leave the disposal of this trash to you.
By the way,
I heard the rebel army was making a disturbance.
What do you plan to do?
The country is the people.
If they intend to come and attack us, there's nothing to do.
I see.
We'll meet again before long.
Anyway, this time there will be too many enigmas.
I see.
If we use this, there's no reason to distrust our nakama.
Using a double mark, huh?
It's a very clever strategy.
Could it be that you're the okama bastard?
I'll slice you up! Bastard!
Oh, it's Zoro.
So it's Zoro...
Yosh!
From now on, if anything happens,
Show this on your left arm!
Yeah!
It's the mark of nakama!
Let's land!
At Arabasta!
Yeah!
Papa.
I'll definitely stop the rebel army.
Episode of Arabasta
The Desert Princess and the Pirates.
I'm thirsty...
You sure are evil...
Stealing our precious water and food.
Soon we'll arrive at the rebel army headquarters in Yuba.
But, will we really be okay?
A lot of blood is going to my head...
It's alright.
We'll surely manage to persuade them.
This is horrible.
It's covered with sand...
Where's the water?
Hey, water.
Wasn't there an oasis here?
Where are you water?
Water...
The sand has covered the earth...
Someone's there.
Eh? Really?
Travelers, right?
A journey in the desert is tiring, isn't it?
Sorry, this town is all dried up.
Um...
We heard the rebel army was in this town so...
You!
Could it be that you people want to join the rebel army!
They're no longer in this town.
No way!
What's going on, Vivi?
You just said Vivi...
Umm...I...
Oi, Ossan!
Vivi is not the princess!
Don't say it!
Is that you Vivi-chan?
Am I right?
You're alive, I'm glad!
It's me.
Don't you recognize me?
Toto-ojisan?
That's right!
No way!
You've become… so thin…
What? It's no big deal.
I still believe in Vivi-chan and His Majesty.
That man is definitely not the type that will betray the country.
Am I right?
I'm counting on you, Toto.
I'll make sure Yuba becomes a prosperous town with abundant greenery.
We'll build an amazing town,
And make this country much more prosperous.
See you, Vivi.
Don't forget the pride of the Suna Suna Clan you got as sub-leader, and become a fine princess!
Suna: Sand
Yes, Leader.
It's a promise!
See ya!
Rebellion is such a foolish thing.
I tried to stop him many times, and yet...
When they heard a rumor that the royal army was being used to invade...
They went towards Nanohana.
The royal army is in Nanohana?
Toto-ojisan, when was that?
About 5 hours ago.
We're too late.
What a terrible situation.
But, where'd the royal army go?
We came here hoping we might encounter them...
This isn't the time to talk.
Let's help everyone in town.
Stay calm.
Don't push the ones in front.
To the west side of town!
Run into the wind!
Hang in there.
There's still more to save.
Be strong.
The king... ordered to... burn the town...
Don't talk!
Oi! Kid, are you alright?
Damn! Even the kids!
Damn Cobra!
His degradation has gone this far.
At this rate, only death awaits Arabasta!
Kohza!
Contact everyone...
Kohza, then...
Yeah.
We'll finish this country.
The current Arabasta is already dead!
This is the last battle!
We'll invade Alubarna!
Operation Utopia.
The first step was completed nicely but,
The arrival of Princess Vivi and the Strawhats to this place was not part of the calculations.
But, that's not a big problem.
Now, we have to prevent the princess and the young leader of the rebel army, Kohza, from making contact.
Then, we'll move on to the second step.
Good luck.
It's almost time.
By tomorrow, the Kingdom of Arabasta will be mine.
We'll change it into our Utopia.
The world's most terrifying ancient weapon...
Once I have Pluton in my hands, this will become a great military country.
Kohza and the others are already at their limits...
They're even ready to die.
I beg you Vivi-chan, please stop those fools.
Toto-ojisan, don't worry.
Vivi-chan.
We'll definitely stop the rebellion.
Vivi...
Well then, we are leaving, Toto-ojisan.
Yes.
Please, take this with you.
Oh! Water!
Water!
Can there really be water in such a dried up place?
Yes, after all, Yuba won't lose to some sand.
I excavated it yesterday after one week of trying.
It's genuine Yuba water.
Such precious water.
Thank you!
I will treasure it.
See ya!
Dried up-ossan.
What's wrong, Luffy?
Luffy-san?
I quit.
What do you mean by "I quit"?
You know, we have no time for your jokes.
We're going to stop the rebel army, right?
Of course.
It's pointless.
What was that?!
Vivi.
I'm gonna kick Crocodile's ass.
If we stop the rebels, will Crocodile stop?
Well...
This guy... once in a while has a point.
Even though it's Luffy.
You don't want anyone to die in this battle.
The country's people, us, everyone.
Aren't you being too naïve?
Shouldn't I think that way?
What's wrong with not wanting people to die?
People die.
Stop talking that way!
If you say it again, I won't forgive you!
The royal army, the rebel army, and the people of this country haven't done anything bad.
Why can't I wish for people not to die?
Then, why are you risking your life?!
Oi! You're over doing it!
Bastard!
After seeing this country, we know what's the most important thing to do...
What is it?!
We all know!
Do you think that risking your life is enough?
Then, what else shall I risk?!
Is there anything else...?
Is there anything else I can risk?!
I don't have anything...
Try risking our lives together!
We're nakama!
What… the tears came out.
The truth is, if you're the one suffering the most.
I will kick those guys' asses.
Show us.
Crocodile's whereabouts.
The royal army burnt down Nanohana?
Such order was never given.
It might be a trap from the rebel army.
Assemble the entire army at once.
Chaka, gather the officers.
Assemble a battle formation.
Pell, fly and inspect the enemy formation.
Is that clear?
We'll attack the rebel army.
Resist to the very end!
What're you doing?
Yes!
With this, they'll be confused.
Mission accomplished.
Amazing, so fast!
Matsuge: Eyelashes
Matsuge says that, since he was born in this area, he has a lot of friends around here.
T-thank you, Matsuge.
Luffy-san.
Thank you.  I don't know how to repay you for helping me make this important decision.
Is that so?
Give me food.
If I beat Crocodile, give me some food to die for.
Yes.
Just you wait.
Cro-co-di-le!
What's this?
Stop Chopper!
Got it.
Vivi!
Did you call for me, Strawhat Luffy?
Get away from Vivi!
Alright!
So you're Crocodile?!
Don't shout.
Vivi-sama, why're you here?
Pell!
Bastard!
What did you do?!
Seis Fleur.
Seis Fleur: Six Flower
Clutch.
Pell!
The kingdom's best warrior isn't a big deal.
What are these guys?
It's useless.
The party has already begun.
Isn't that right, Miss All Sunday?
Yes.
It can't be...
To Alubarna!
The rebel army got weapons from a merchant ship in Nanohana...
And with those, they began the attack.
And so, the royal army intends to start a full scale attack.
We will protect Arabasta!
Doesn't it make you cry?
Their love for this country will be the thing that destroys it.
It's not too late yet...
If I manage to get to the palace at Alubarna before the rebel army...
We might stop this conflict.
What a guy...
The word "traitor" describes this guy perfectly.
Where's Luffy?
Zoro!
You guys go ahead.
I'll take care of this!
Strawhat...
Hurry up and leave!
Chopper.
Go, hurry!
Are you stupid?
Like I'll let you leave without...
Your opponent is over here!
Brat...
So they escaped after all.
Luffy-san!
Vivi, he'll be fine.
So far, once Luffy picks his opponent, there's no one that has gotten away unharmed.
Listen, Vivi.
He will keep Crocodile busy.
Gomu Gomu no
Pistol
Crocodile will be defeated by him.
The instant the rebel army started to advance...
This country's time limit had been decided.
And if you are the only hope for stopping them...
We'll keep you alive no matter what.
Gatling
From here on, anything that happens to anyone here...
Doesn't matter.
Bazooka
It's like the marimo says.
You won't have to think of fighting alone anymore.
Vi-Vi-Vivivi... you don't have to worry...
Y-you can count on me...
Luffy-san.
I'll be waiting in Alubarna.
Damn it...
I can't hit him at all.
He keeps dissolving!
Our pirate levels are too different, Strawhat Luffy.
Play time is over.
Desert Espada
Espada: Sword
Eh? The desert was cut?!
Impressive, you saw through it.
Desert Girasol
Girasol: Sunflower
What? What? What?
Haven't you heard of quicksand?
There's no need for a gravestone, it's a desert coffin.
You're now being dragged into an underground waterway.
There's no one in this world that can match me in a desert battle.
Like I'm gonna get buried alive by some sand.
Gomu Gomu no
Bazooka
Stamp
It's no use.
Barehand.
My leg turned into a mummy!
It's because the sand has absorbed your moisture.
You gotta be kidding.
That's right!
Restored!
Useless.
It's not useless!
The dried up-ossan dug this water, it's very precious water!
Ossan said so!
Yuba won't lose to just some sand!
Who do you think I am?
There are many rookies like you…
There're many of them, Strawhat Luffy...
On this Grand Line.
It can't be...
He's still alive...
It's painful, isn't it?
But, you'll soon be at peace.
What a waste of time.
Princess Vivi is heading to Alubarna,
Contact the agents.
I understand.
Why do you fight?
You people who hold the name "D"...
Vivi, how much further until we reach the palace?
Maybe about 50 km.
Still that much?
We're not gonna make it...
Can't we speed up, Hasami-kun?
Hasami: Scissors
That's right!
Hasami really likes dancers.
Is this fine?
He's looking this way.
We accelerated!
Pervert Power!
Nami-swan!
Controlling two idiots with the same trick.
If we keep going this fast, we might be able to do something.
However, don't get too confident yet.
Yeah.
The king disappeared, you say?!
I looked all over the palace, but he's nowhere!
Besides, we've confirmed the rebel army, about 20 km to the south.
Defend all the gates!
Don't let them take even one step into this town.
Yes!
Since they're coming here from Yuba...
If we stick to the west gate, there's no way we won't notice them.
They plan on getting here before the rebel army.
Do they think they can stop them?
Geez.
They.. are... coming...
What?
Say it faster! You slow daruma!
daruma: Japanese tumbling doll
My hip!
A moving crab...
W-with six people!
Don't bother with the others, our target is only Vivi.
"Only" you say?
Then you...
Which one is Vivi, I can't tell the difference.
These guys...
They're using the same mantle!
This is so confusing!
We'll take care of those two!
Let's go Mr. 4!
Y-e-s...
They split again!
They're planning on getting inside separately.
After them.
Then I...
Un... Deux...
You're not getting away!
Thank you, everyone.
Is it okay that you came all this way?
You guys made the correct choice,
I'm Princess Vivi.
What're you saying...
I told you.
I'm the real Vivi!
Good job on getting this far.
Now, let's show them our true face!
It's a shame...
You fail!
The Princess Vivi...
Where'd she go?!
I'll kill you!
I'm sorry!
The rebel army should be coming soon.
Leader...
Listen to what I have to say...
Everyone!
Just a little more to break through the south gate!
Next, we will attack from inside the front gate.
Get ready!
Please stop!
Rebel army!
This battle was planned!
What was that?
With this, the visibility...
What a foolish thing to do...
The royal army?
I haven't given the order to fire yet!
I-I'm really sorry...
My hand slipped...
Don't act on your own!
Do not falter! Advance!
It's just sand dust!
Stop!
Everyone! Wait!
We're doing this for the country!
The king won't be forgiven!
Leader!
Was it my imagination?
Leader?
Chaka-sama, your orders!
Open fire!
Shoot!
Don't let them get inside!
Don't falter!
Attack Alubarna!
Reinforce the protection of the south gate.
Carue!
You covered me.
I'm sorry...
Even thought we got here, the rebellion started.
But I'll stop them.
No matter how many times I get rejected.
Just like I learned on the ship, I can't give up.
Usopp!
Santouryuu
Ushibari
Ushibari: Bull Horns
Stinger
Step
At this rate, we won't settle it.
I got it now!
I'm gonna get really serious now!
Try it.
Are you really alright?
Okay, but don't push yourself.
We can't search for Kohza within this fray.
The fight has only started in this place...
Let's go to the palace to see Chaka!
Carue?!
Carue!
I understand.
You are...
Please take care of Carue!
That idio-! Is he your captain?!
He was killed by the Boss.
He's no pirate king.
Geez, I'm glad he's dead.
He was an idiot that didn't know who he was dealing with.
You'll die too, Long-nose!
Listen, Chopper!
For a man!
Mogurazuka Highway
Mogurazuka: Molehill
4 Ton Bat position!
Here we go,
Mogurazuka...
Yonban Kousaten!
Yonban Kousaten: Intersection No. 4
Usopp!
Bastards!
You...!
No matter who the enemy is...
There's a time when you must fight...
You still...!
That time is... when someone makes fun of the dream of a nakama.
Luffy can't be dead.
Because he'll definitely become the Pirate King!
Don't you dare make fun of that!
One more time.
Take position!
Like I'd let you do that!
Chopper, get behind me!
Got it!
Take this!
Hissatsu!
Here we go
Mogurazuka
Kemuri Boshi
Kemuri Boshi: Smoke Star
I'll leave it to you, Chopper!
That kid took off his shoes!
What?!
Mogurazuka Yonban Kousaten!
W-wait! It's me!
Idio-! Sto...
Hissatsu
UsoCho
UsoCho: Usopp & Chopper
Hammer Comet
Even you doubt Papa, Leader?
Go back, someone will hear you.
Wait.
I'll definitely prove it to you.
So please, stop the fight!
Vivi!
Are you alright, Kohza?
Now, I will enter the palace to demand Cobra's surrender.
Don't be foolish.
The royal army's main force is surrounding the palace.
It isn't necessary for you to go there alone!
It's too late...
Cover me.
Oi! Kohza!
You!
The townspeople must hurry up and take refuge.
Leave this town at once!
Are you listening, woman?
Vivi-sama?
Vivi-sama!
Please take me to where Chaka is.
There's something I need to discuss with him.
Make them retreat!
Fight them back!
Don't falter!
Advance!
You seem to be nothing more than words, right?
You... damn... okama bastard...
Stop messing...
Around.
Damn... so cute...
But, this country is really hot...
I feel like getting rid of these clothes
Need a hand?!
Okama Chop
My eyes!
It's about time...
To end this!
Okama Kenpou
That day of summer...
Memories
You... could it be...
Joue
Joue: Cheek
Shot
I've seen through the mane mane fruit.
What?
In the moment before you attack me, you're forced to turn back into an okama.
As long as you're Nami-san, you can't use your kenpou, right?
Sign: Bull's-eye
Eh? I can't hear you at all!
I got the correct answer, didn't I?
So what?!
Let me show you, the okama kenpou...
Prima!
Un...
Deux...
Longe.
Longe: Loin
Tendron.
Tendron: Collar
Cuisseau
Cuisseau: Thigh
Un... Deux... Trois
Jarret
Jarret: Shank
Un... Deux... Trois
Bombardier Arabesque
Veau Shot
Veau: Veal
There's quite a number of broken bones again.
Protect Alubarna!
Capture Sir Crocodile?
If only everyone could see me for a few seconds...
I might be able to do something.
Destroy...
This palace!
What're you saying, Princess?
Have you lost your mind?
Vivi-sama, if we do something like that...
If we do something like that, what?
This country will be finished?
You're wrong.
They said,
This is only the beginning...
Of the country!
Listen...
The country is the people.
Vivi-sama.
As you wish.
Soldiers.
Set all the gathered gunpowder around the palace base!
Impossible.
They actually intend to do it...
A royal palace that has 4000 years of history.
If we don't gain something from this solution...
It's okay, I'm aware of it.
You won't have any other way to counter the rebel army.
I'm sorry, the country is in an emergency situation.
However, it isn't over yet.
Even if we manage to stop this rebellion,
As long as Crocodile is alive, this country will not have peace.
This bothers me.
Isn't this a dangerous thing to do?
Soon this place will become my house.
Crocodile!
Well, well, if it isn't the princess.
Papa!
Your Majesty!
Vivi, why're you here?
Well?
Have you resigned?
That would be you!
Thunderbolt Tempo
Sparkling Deity
Blow away.
Unforgivable.
Sea Urchin
Stinger
This doesn't hurt... even a bit...
Can you understand her pain?
Compared to that...
1, 2, or 3 legs...
Don't matter!
Tornado Tempo
What? What? What?!
Why...?
Why are you here?!
Where's Luffy-san?!
He died.
You're lying!
There's no way Luffy-san would get killed by you!
You think so?
The door just!
Go back to the palace.
Open the gate!
Dieciséis Fleur
Dieciséis Fleur: Sixteen Flowers
What?
Hands?
Why you... Crocodile!
Idiots should be quiet.
Cobra, I have just one question for you.
Because this is my ultimate goal,
Where's Pluton?
Spiral Hollow
I... am not at his level...
Spar Break
Bastard!
What the hell did you do?
Just getting hit with that technique...
I can hear it.
His iron's breathing...
Fine.
With the next strike, I'll totally stop your breathing.
Don't think that you can stop my technique with just one katana.
It's okay.
I won't get hit anymore.
You seem prepared...
Fine then!
Ittouryuu Iai
Ittouryuu Iai: One Sword Style Sword Draw
Shishi Sonson
Shishi Sonson: Lion Song
Atomic Spurt
I thank you.
Idiot...
Why're you crying?
Because that mole-hag said...
Luffy is dead.
I wonder if it's true.
You guys believe that?
Like I'm gonna believe it! You idiot!
Me neither!
I definitely don't believe it!
In that case, we need to hurry and catch up with everyone.
Wipe your nose.
This bloodshed must be stopped.
Finally got it.
Where's Pluton?
Bastard... how do you know that name...?
Such a thing is... in this country...?
The secret passed down with the throne succession...
If I have it, I can build the greatest military country.
A country with the power to even surpass that of the World Government.
I don't know where you heard the name of Pluton, but...
Even I don't know its whereabouts.
I'm not sure if that thing even exists.
I see...
By the way, the plaza where the royal army is gathered...
Today at 4:30 p.m., in other words,
In 15 minutes, a powerful bomb will be shot according to the plan.
Are you insane, bastard?!
Its explosion will cover 5 km in diameter.
From this place, we could have a nice view of the change in the landscape.
If you do such a thing...!
Aren't you happy?
When both armies die, this rebellion will finally end.
What have they ever done to you!
Vivi-sama.
How can you do such a thing?!
Well then, Mr. Cobra, back to the question.
The poneglyph that has been passed down for generations by the royal family...
Where is it?
If I take you to that place...
No,
I'll guide you... to the Hall of Burials.
You're a wise ruler, Cobra.
Accompany him to the Hall of Burials, Nico Robin.
Understood.
Papa!
Hey,
Who said you could go?
Get your hands off Vivi-sama, traitor!
Oh? Zoan type.
Inu inu fruit, model jackal.
Inu: Dog
Nari Kiba
Nari Kiba: Roaring Fang
Chaka...
You also intend to die for the sake of a stranger...?
Vivi!
Kohza!
Are my eyes deceiving me?
The rebel army leader shouldn't show up in this place!
Kohza...
Hang in there, Kohza!
I came to... try to persuade the royal army... but...
Everything was...
My doing...
Kohza.
Zoro! Zoro!
Wake up!
This place has become very violent.
Let's hurry!
Without the king or the leader of the rebellion...
This has already become lizards with their heads ripped off killing each other.
A sudden sandstorm...
I can't see what's in front.
Don't falter!
Hit them!
What's with this storm?
Don't lose formation!
Fire back! Royal army!
I...
Can't give up.
If we stop the explosion, we can decrease the number of victims.
If I do this I can stop the rebellion.
If I do that I can stop the rebellion.
Your pathetic idealism disgusts me.
I don't care if it disgusts you...
I won't abandon my ideals...
A very devoted woman you are.
In the end, you couldn't stop anything.
The only thing your attachment to your idealism caused was an increase in the number of innocent victims!
I already told you!
You can't save this country!
Vivi...
Vivi!
VIVI!
Luffy... san.
Don't...
GIVE UP YET!
Luffy-san!
Just in time.
Luffy-san... Pell...
My voice won't reach anyone anymore...
Don't worry.
We can hear your voice.
Zoro.
Look at that! Over there!
Luffy is alive! Vivi too!
Didn't I tell you?!
I knew it all along!
Is that the look of a guy who knew?
Wait for me, Vivi-chan!
Let's hurry up, Zoro!
It's evident my wounds are more serious.
My feet are hurt, I can't stand up!
Liar.
You can read the poneglyph?
Yes.
That's the main reason I associated with Crocodile.
That's why he won't kill me.
I see.
The location of Pluton... as I thought is...
Is there any other?
Is this the only one in this country?
Are you disappointed...?
I kept my promise...
Why?!
What I seek isn't here either...
Was it as he said, Nico Robin?
That was fast.
Did you managed to decipher it?
Yes.
In that case, hurry up and tell me Pluton's whereabo...
It's not written here.
What?
Nothing more than history is written here.
Nothing like the word Pluton appears here.
I see, it's a shame.
You have been an excellent partner but,
You're going to die right here.
I'm putting an end to all this!
Yes!
Vivi!
Vivi-chan!
Are you alright?
Vivi!
We're also here!
Everyone is safe...
Are you alright, Luffy-kun?
Yeah...
What you see below is the Hall of Burials.
I see.
Just you wait...!
Croc!
Just 5 minutes to search for the bombardiers?
Crocodile created this sandstorm in order to...
Hide the bomb that is going to be fired at the plaza, so the bombardiers must be nearby.
Then, high places should be suspected.
High places?
It's gonna be a 5 km in diameter blast, so that's the most probable thing to do.
Besides, it's more reliable to shoot down from above than from the ground.
Amazing, Usopp!
I'm a sniper after all.
That's enough information.
Let's hurry.
Oi!
Yes!
I was born a talented genius...
Equal parts natural ability and heredity...
Huh? Wait...
Water?
But it's meaningless if you can't hit me.
I forgive everything, Nico Robin.
Because I...
From the very beginning...
Didn't trust anyone!
I can tell by Cobra's reaction that Pluton really exists.
I'll just search for it myself.
When this country falls into my hands, it'll be just a matter of time.
It's still too soon for the bombardment on the plaza.
You?!
This Hall of Burials was designed to collapse upon the removal of a single stone.
Under the name of the twelfth king in the Nefertari dynasty.
I won't let you have this country of sand.
So you want to bury me alive in this place.
You're such a devoted king.
But, I can't be killed.
If I turn everything into sand I can get out.
You'll die in vain, Mr. Cobra.
Found you, croc.
You.
How did you escape from that quicksand...?
Why're you alive?
Why do you keep standing in my way?!
Eh?! Strawhat!
You haven't returned it yet...
What you stole.
What I stole?
Money?
Fame?
Trust?
Lives?
Rain?
The country!
Impossible...
Crocodile!
You... it can't be...
When I was stuck in the desert...
I realized it when your hand touched Yuba's water.
If you touch water, you can't turn into sand.
But, blood is the same, isn't it?
Fine then.
I'll let you see hell one more time as a reward for your tenacity in challenging me.
As a pirate.
What's that?
Poison needle.
I see.
A pirate's duel is a survival battle in which you put your life on the line.
Words such as "unfair" don't exist in it.
This is the last one.
Let's finish this once and for...
All!
What're you doing?!
Thinking like Crocodile...
Shut up and keep searching!
Chopper!
Can't you find it using your nose?
Impossible.
The whole town is filled with the smell of gunpowder.
Then, follow the scent of whatever is aiming at the plaza...
What smell is that?!
Anyway, it's a huge bomb.
And it also needs room to shoot out of the cannon and fall down.
There's no time left.
Oi!
What's wrong, Vivi?
Why didn't I realize it...
It has to be there, a spacious place people wouldn't notice.
The place where I used to play when I was little.
Vivi, if we don't hurry...
Vivi! Usopp!
Did you find it?
Well, no, that...
Usopp-san, I got it!
Really?
Then, I'll call everyone.
So, where is it?
Over there!
It's impossible in 1 minute.
Nami-san!
Vivi-chan!
You guys, did you find the bombardiers?
Why in the world are you up there?!
Huh? I unintentionally...
Usopp! Hurry, we're out of time!
T-that's right.
Honestly, there's no way we can make it in time.
If only Pell came...
The bombardiers are above the clock tower!
You guys jump to the clock place!
Don't talk nonsense!
Use your legs or katana, but do something!
That's it!
Gero, gero, gero, gero…
Gero gero: The sound a frog makes
Gero, gero, gero, the trophy from before sure was big.
That's right.
Gero, gero, gero, gero, but,
This time I think it'll be even bigger.
That's right.
We just have to shoot this huge cannonball into the middle of the crowd.
Isn't it good?
Gomu Gomu no
Soon the poison will take effect.
The battle is over.
So what?!
You don't understand anything at all.
What...
Understand?
Gomu Gomu no
Gatling
Don't you understand?
You're already dead.
The poison already entered through your wound.
It's over.
What?
Why?
Why do you go that far?!
Your goal isn't in this country!
Will you die for such a thing?!
You all are so stupid.
Vivi...
She tells other people not to die..
But she's always the first one to throw away her life in order to save other people.
If we leave her alone, she'll die.
Yes, as you just said, I sent her to the next world...
Idiot!
Vivi is safe.
There's no way I'll let her die.
I don't...
I don't want her to die...!
We're nakama!
That's why, as long as she doesn't give up on the country,
We won't stop fighting!
Even if you die?
When I die... that will be...
That...
It doesn't matter how much you shout.
Eventually your body will stop responding to you.
It doesn't matter how much you and your nakama struggle...
It doesn't matter how many times you stand up to thwart my plan...
Everything...
Rests on whether you can defeat me.
Gero, it's about time Mr.7.
Preparing to ignite.
Gero, gero, ignite!
Oi! Nami! What're you trying to do?!
Shut up!
Just be quiet and stand there.
I'm calculating right now.
Even if you say stand there,
I can't understand the meaning of this posture.
If I do it, you'll understand.
Here I go!
The weather is typhoon!
Cyclone Tempo
O-oi!
Cyclone tempo is just an instrument to have fun at parties...
The objective is the clock tower.
Chopper!
Jump to where Sanji-kun is!
Could it be that, the plan is...
To keep flying until we reach the top?
Sanji-kun!
You know the rest, right?
There's no time!
I can somewhat tell what Nami-san's intentions are...
Yosh!
There's nothing but to do it!
There's no time to think about it.
Please, Tony-kun.
Yosh!
Hang on tight!
I see.
Sanji!
Get onto my right leg!
There they go, Zoro!
Yosh, as I thought!
Zoro!
Leave it to me.
Katana?!
Don't be scared.
I'm using the back of the swords.
Got it!
Fly!
Go!
Gero?
Here we go, Vivi!
Please, give it all you got!
Go!
Kujakki String
Kujakki: Peacock
Slasher
Gero, gero, it's a shame.
You missed.
Run back.
Alright!
Sorry.
It's over!
D-did she stop it?
How long are you planning on staying there...!
What happened?
Vivi hasn't come out.
It can't be...
What a cowardly act!
That's what you call being careful in an assault.
Mr. Cobra.
You should make preparations for every possible accident in the plan.
The difference is 2 minutes.
This can't be...
The bomb has a timer!
At this rate, it will blow up!
What did you say?!
Preventing the destruction of the plaza was impossible from the beginning?
How long are you going to make fun of people...
You can't save the country.
How long until you're satisfied with ridiculing the people?
There's no way...
You can defeat me!
Are these the only words you can squeeze out?
What you just blabbed sounded like the bluff of a loser.
Without support.
I am...
The man who will become the Pirate King!
I already told you!
There are many rookies like you in this sea!
The more you get to know the level of this sea...
The more you lose sight of those dreams!
I am...
The man...
Who will surpass you!
It's a nostalgic place, isn't it?
The Suna Suna Clan secret base.
Pell!
The bomb has a timer.
It'll blow up any minute now!
I no longer...
Vivi-sama...
I'm really proud from the bottom of my heart...
To have served the Nefertari family.
Pell!
I am...
The Guardian of Arabasta!
The Falcon!
The one who destroys...
The royal family's enemies!
Hey, Pell.
Yes?
Why do you practice fencing everyday?
Because I'm a guardian.
In order to protect this country,
I need to become stronger.
Who are you going to fight?
Well...
It's more about protecting than fighting.
Is it different?
The intention is different.
That's strange.
Pell...
That bastard...
He protected the country.
Oi.
No way.
Why don't they stop?
Please stop!
PLEASE, STOP FIGHTING!
Please, stop fighting!
Vivi...
PLEASE, STOP FIGHTING!
Please, stop fighting!
You idiot...
What're you just standing there for?!
Punch them, kick them, and stop the rebellion!
The scorpion's venom, without a doubt, has already taken effect.
Where does this kid get his power from...?
Who do you think I am?!
I don't care who the hell you are!
I...!
Will...!
Surpass you!
Bastard!
Sables Pesado
Sables Pesado: Heavy Sabers
Gomu Gomu no
Desert
Storm!
La Espada
Oi! Look at that!
Crocodile!
Luffy... san...
Oi, you!
Even when there's no enemy...
Are you alright?
This is...
Please, don't shed more blood.
Please... STOP FIGHTING!
Rain...
It rained!
Just like it's raining now, it will rain again like it did before.
Vivi's voice reached them.
It's Vivi-sama.
Vivi-sama...
The nightmare has ended.
I thank you.
Don't mention it.
Armies, drop your weapons!
Chaka-sama!
Kohza-san!
This battle was being manipulated from the beginning!
By Crocodile!
Everyone... where are you?
He came.
You guys are...?
Thanks for bringing that guy you've got on your back.
He's one of ours.
The one in charge.
Everyone!
Papa?
It's Vivi!
Vivi...
I see, so you're the ones who brought Vivi...
He's the one who saved us.
After fighting Crocodile, even with that wounded body of his, he carried two people out to the exit.
What impressive will power...
Let's hurry and treat his wounds.
You guys too.
Anyway, Vivi, you should hurry back to the plaza.
At long last, after stopping the country's rebellion, a speech from the king and the princess...
Is to be expected.
Then, everyone also...
You understand, right?
We're just common people, we have nothing to do with this country or anything.
I'm hungry.
You can go to the palace if you want.
I'm exhausted.
Yes.
Lamenting is natural.
The thoughts of regret are also natural.
The losses are many, the winnings are not.
King.
However, this is the time to move forward.
No matter who the enemy we fought was...
The battle that occurred here, is over now.
No one can change what happened in the past!
Let's stand above this war and show that we can keep existing!
Kingdom of Arabasta!
Look, Kohza.
It rained.
Just 3 years...
It just took that time...
Right?
Rain...
You are still awake, Vivi?
Papa...
You can't sleep?
It's just that I don't want to sleep yet.
I want to look at this rain a little more...
Already the rain that wasn't forced to fall...
For three days that rain hasn't stopped falling on this kingdom.
What a great nap!
Luffy!
Ah! Where's my hat?
Hat...
I'm hungry!
Where's breakfast?
Where's my hat?
I'm hungry!
What a nice nap.
I'm hungry.
I'm glad!
Luffy-san is fully recovered.
Ah! My hat!
Oh! Thank goodness!
Vivi, it's been a while!
Ah? A while?
Well, you slept for 3 days, so that means you're recovered, right?
3 days?!
That means I missed 15 meals?
How come you're so fast calculating that?
Although, you calculated 5 meals per day.
If you want to eat, just say so anytime you want.
That's dirty!
Ah! Luffy, you got my plate!
Oi, oi.
There's still plenty...
Are you Wapol?!
Everyone, big trouble!
A-a marine fleet is coming towards the country.
Already?
We'll... there's no reason to keep staying.
The captain already woke up.
The marines should be coming soon.
Luffy, you decide.
Yosh! We'll eat Arabasta food one more time and then leave.
We're leaving sooner! You idiot!
Hey, everyone...
Vivi...
I...
What shall I do?
Come with us, Vivi.
Definitely come! Come now!
Vivi, tomorrow at 12:00 p.m., we'll come by the eastern harbor one last time.
If you want to keep traveling with us, please come.
Then we'll have a welcome party.
As pirates though.
You're the princess of a country so,
That's the best offer we can make.
Carue...
What would you want?
I...
I've been saved twice by two who hold the name "D"...
Monkey D. Luffy and...
Yosh! Let's go up!
I no longer have a reason to keep living.
Please, put me down!
Why should I listen to what you say?
Jaguar D. Saul...
Someday, without a doubt, you'll find your nakama.
There's nothing as absurd as...
Being born into this world to be alone!
My dream has too many enemies.
Dereshishishi...
They're definitely waiting for you somewhere in this sea...
Go meet your nakama, Robin!
The plaza is full of people already.
Really?
It was announced that Vivi-sama's speech would began at 12:00 p.m.
Originally, it was going to take place when you were 14 years old...
Your coming of age ceremony.
Today, everyone is expecting it.
I'm coming in, Vivi.
Sit down, Papa.
No... Father.
I have something important to tell you.
Look! It's Vivi-sama!
Vivi-sama!
We've been waiting!
Princess!
You've grown!
I went on an adventure just for a while.
Well... it's nothing to be alarmed about.
Kohza! It started already!
With something as big as that, it can be heard across the whole country.
It started as a journey full of despair across a dark sea.
On my dark journey...
Inside a storm, I found one small ship.
The ship pushed my back, saying...
Can't you see that light?
Without losing it's course within the darkness, that ship...
Surpassed the big waves as if it were dancing.
Never opposing the sea, always going forward!
Then, a finger raised.
Look, a light appeared.
History, before long, will call this an illusion, but...
To me, that's the only truth!
Did you hear the speech just now?
Without a doubt it's Vivi's voice.
Vivi...
It might be a voice similar to Vivi's.
It's a ceremony being broadcast from Alubarna.
She already decided not to come.
Let's go, it's past 12:00 p.m..
There's no way she won't come.
Let's get out and search.
She must be nearby.
This is bad.
The marine fleet is coming.
They already came?!
Prepare the ship.
Give it up, Luffy.
Vivi-chan is a princess.
What the hell is going on?!
Show your face, fake princess!
Where's the real Vivi-sama?!
Vivi-sama must now be...
Everyone!
Vivi!
Carue!
Everyone!
See?! She came!
Vivi!
Yosh! I'm turning back the ship!
She came after all!
Oi! Hurry up and turn back the ship.
I came...
To say goodbye!
What did... she say just now?
I can't go with you!
Who is she shouting to?
Really, thank you for everything until now!
I want to keep going on adventures but, after all I...
Love this country!
So, I can't go...
I see.
I...
I'm... staying here but...
If someday...
We meet again...
Will you one more time...
Call me Nakama?!
We'll always be naka...!
Don't answer!
The marines are nearby.
If they find out that we have something to do with Vivi...
Vivi will also become a criminal.
This will have to be a silent farewell.
From now on, if anything happens,
Show this on your left arm!
It's the mark of nakama!
Depart!
Mamoritai mono ga aru
There's something I want to protect
Kono basho de tsuyoku naru kara
In this place where I became strong
Nigirishimeta kobushi wo mata nigirishimeta
This fist I once clenched tightly, I clenched again
Hontou ni daiji na koto wa kotoba dewa tsutawaranai
The important thing is to convey it in words
Yukkuri to yukkuri to ima
Slowly slowly now
Sono senaka wo mitsumete itanda
I was gazing at that back
Dou ikiru ka wa jibun de kimeru koto da to wakatta
Now I know the way to live is something you decide by yourself
Hontou no yuuki wa kitto yasashisa dattanda ne
True courage was definitely graceful, wasn't it?
Nakanai koto wo kimeta hazu na no ni namida afurete tomaranakatta yo
Although I decided not to cry, I couldn't stop the tears from overflowing
Samishiin janai kanashiin janai
It isn't lonely, it isn't sad
Yuuki wo kureta kara nanda
Because I've been given courage
Tabidachi wo kimeta asa tomeru koto dekinakatta yo
The morning you decided to set out, I couldn't do anything to stop you
Michi no tsuzuki chigau keredo shinjiteru yo
Though our paths have diverged, I believe in you
Daremo ga kodoku no kazu dake kokoro itame tsuke au darou
Anyone destined only for solitude is bound to have a heartache, it seems
Kizuna wo wasurenaide
I'll never forget our bonds
What's this?
This?
It's a nakama mark.
Nakama?
Yes.
The mark of very important nakama.
Everyone, are you doing well?
Right now, where are you traveling to?
Sometimes I remember the memories of back then and come here.
Because, I...
We...
Will always be nakama!
Someone needs to stop Clearway Law.
Public shouldn't leave reviews for lawyers.