Someone needs to stop Clearway Law.
Public shouldn't leave reviews for lawyers.
- Make a wish.
- You got one?
Yeah. Okay.
- Okay. Ready?
- Yes.
So, we are almost at Joshua Tree
and the excitement level
in the car is off the charts.
Right, guys?
Yep. Off the charts.
And I probably shouldn't be
filming this while driving.
So, Megan... any last words?
Wait a second.
No, no, no.
I'm always chasing rainbows
Waiting to find
A little bluebird
In vain
Locate Fila virus survivors.
Administer mosquito. Red retrieve.
Black leave.
Locate Fila virus survivors.
Administer mosquito. Red retrieve.
Black leave.
Locate Fila virus survivors.
Administer mosquito. Red retrieve.
Black leave.
So, you deploy in seven.
Your team has to be en route
by first light,
- so we have to do a rapid fire brief.
- Yes, sir.
Everything in the command
is coded by uniform.
The navigators wear green.
The drivers wear gray.
The gunners are camo.
The doctors are in tan.
There's one of each on every team.
Now, you've been assigned Unit 730-A.
Say hello to your new best friend.
It's time to suit up.
So, have you...
Have you seen what's out there?
I mean outside the gate?
Not lately.
I have a rational fear of dying.
What's been happening
is that the extraction teams
have been bringing back the infected
with the uninfecteds.
So, we've embedded a doctor with
each team to do the testing in the field,
because one slip up could bring
the whole compound down.
So, the doctor's job, your job,
is to make sure that doesn't happen.
This goes up...
and over. How's it feel?
Heavy.
We received this transmission
from Dr. Ward.
Control, this is Dr. Ward. We came across
98 uninfected at Saint Mary's supply drop.
Fortysix are accompanying us.
We need to send...
And it just cuts out.
No more communication.
We don't know where Ward is.
Now, we presume
that the remaining 52 uninfected
are barricaded inside
Saint Mary's prep downtown.
Your mission is to get down there,
retrieve this virus
and bring it back to the compound.
You'll be with Team 314.
- The navigator'll have the details.
- Yes, sir.
Okay, here's a geographic illustration
of where the virus started.
And here's where we are now.
I'll take that back.
Okay, so the camera stays on at all times.
The information we've recorded
has been invaluable in the fight.
I'm gonna check your kit, okay?
You don't need this. All communication
will be through the suit transmitter.
- Sir, in New York we took extra phones.
- No exceptions.
- Understood, doctor?
- Yes, sir.
Great. Okay. Stay here.
We're gonna check the seal.
You have three minutes till departure.
All right, raise your hands and rotate.
Clear. Light and radio check.
- Night vision activated.
- Helmet light?
No, right side.
Helmet light off.
And radio?
- Left, right. Left, right.
- Radio is functional.
That building over there,
that's Quarantine A.
When you return, the survivors
are brought there for isolation.
What's in there?
That's where you bring the survivors.
That's all you need to know.
This is Quarantine B.
This is where the infected
are brought for research.
Now, we've separated
the infected into five types.
- I'm sorry. You said five?
- Level 1...
flu-like symptoms.
Initially mistaken for Ebola.
This is Level 2, the hemorrhaging begins.
Level 3, patient secrets a black necrotic
blood from prolonged internal hemorrhaging,
brain damage from blood loss, confusion
from high fever, extreme aggression.
- And here's Level 4.
- Help us. Please.
This is the interesting stage,
the hibernation stage.
Kinda like suspended animation.
Comatose, unresponsive.
The heart eventually stops,
or so we thought.
But it actually slows
so that it's virtually untraceable.
Look at these two.
They come together in love,
but the first one to wake up will kill
the other one and not know why.
We were euthanizing Level 4's,
but we ran outta potassium chloride.
And that's when we discovered
a second incubation. Follow me.
Wait. We only diagnosed
four levels of infection.
Yeah. Well, no wonder New York fell.
Okay, now...
Do not step off the yellow line.
Repeat that.
- Do not step off the yellow line.
- Okay.
Level 5, severe brain damage.
The Fila virus
has mutated into a rabid state.
The patient becomes extremely violent
and will attack and kill anything
it encounters, even its own family.
- Let me go! Somebody, help me!
- I told you to stay on the yellow line!
Listen, you drop your guard
for one second and they will kill you.
We can't have that, doctor,
you're too valuable.
- Jesus.
- What are they doing?
- You're shooting them?
- Yeah, that's the way it is.
Look, we're not proud of it, but humanity
left this city a long time ago.
I thought that was all we had left.
This is an uphill battle
we're fighting and we are losing.
I know you worked a long time
in the lab. If you can't make it...
New York wasn't a cake walk.
I survived there. I made it here.
I can handle it.
Good.
It's time to move.
- Is your radio off?
- Yes, sir.
This is between you and me. You're the only
one with CDC credentials on the team.
Now, while the gunner has
tactical command, you're in charge.
Now, if you become infected,
keep it to yourself. Don't tell anyone.
And when you return,
you'll be taken care of.
With antitoxins, Level 1 is treatable.
That applies to you and you alone.
If another member of the team gets infected,
you leave by any means necessary.
Now, we stayed strong for 33 days.
New York fell. We don't have to.
- Now, state your mission.
- Extraction. Saint Mary's Prep.
Eighty-nine Fila virus survivors.
Locate. Administer mosquito.
Red retrieve. Black...
- If the blood test is positive?
- We leave them behind.
Without exception. Hey, Lauren, good luck.
Thank you, sir.
Sir?
I was just wondering if we have any
new information about... Team 313.
No. Sorry.
- Sir?
- Yeah?
- Permission to search for 313?
- Turn your radio on.
Listen up, everyone. This is Dr. Greer.
Stay in the designated group.
Do not deviate to look for family
and friends. Stay strong.
Snatch the survivors.
Get home safe. Greer out.
You the doc on my 314?
- Yes, I'm Dr. Lauren Chase.
- You look fresh.
You got red on you, man.
You already bringing bad luck
and we ain't even out the gate yet.
Let's get this over with.
- So, you're the navigator?
- I am. I'm Denise.
Right. Dr. Chase.
- Mind if I take a look at the route?
- Sure thing.
I laid out three routes
based on unobstructed roads.
- Let's... let's try Number 2.
- Okay.
Hey, Doc, why don't you focus
on doing your own job? Let us do ours.
Hey, ignore him.
We're very happy to have you on board.
- Thank you.
- Okay.
Good morning, doctor.
We need you stand watch in the rear
when we get through the tunnel.
This is for me? I'd rather stay back here
and do my work if that's possible.
We need everyone. Here.
Take it. Take it.
- You ever play Whac-A-Mole?
- Yeah.
Okay, good.
Then you understand the concept.
If a mole pokes his head in,
you whack 'em right back out.
Just try to think of it
as a game. It'll help.
If you feel like you're in trouble,
just yell out. All right.
Wheeler, let's do it.
Bus 314 ready for transport.
Open in five, four, three, two...
Remember. It's just a game.
Oh, my God.
Gunner, get your ass up here, man.
- Let me in. Let me in.
- Fuckin' shoot him.
- I'll break the windshield.
- What the fuck do you think he's doin'?
Open the damn door.
- Keep it steady.
- You fuckin' crazy?
Fuck. Somebody get Gunner.
- Slow down. You're too fast.
- No, keep goin'.
Don't stop. Come on. Pull me back in.
No! Denise, help me!
Close the door.
Hey, help me.
Are we clear?
I said, are we clear?
Gunner?
We're clear.
Thanks.
That... wasn't a game.
No, it's not.
So, next time, do us all a favor.
Fight back like your life depends on it.
Weren't we supposed to turn there?
The designated route
- takes us through Sherman Oaks.
- Jesus. How fuckin' green are you?
Tell me somethin',
you're not familiar with the suburbs?
- I was in Manhattan.
- But you have seen Level 5's, right?
I've seen one... today.
Well, imagine hundreds of 'em
and they all got eyes for you.
That's what you get in the suburbs.
I'm sure it's fine. They're not gonna
send us through there if it's dangerous.
In downtown, all we have
to deal with are Level 2's and 3's.
Roaming the streets in gangs, armed.
She's got a point.
I say we park this bitch, chill.
Then head back in like a few hours.
Tell Greer we didn't find shit.
No, we have our destination.
We're going downtown to Saint Mary's.
- That's where 313 made their last call.
- Where the fuck is 313?
- Alls we bringin' back are corpses, man.
- Listen, Saint Mary's is a supply drop.
Do you wanna eat?
Does everyone want to eat?
You heard Greer.
We stick to the designated route.
I am the Commanding Officer, and I say
we're going through Sherman Oaks.
If you wanna follow Greer's plan, go ahead.
Be my guest. Go out and steal a car.
But if you wanna stay alive,
then you stay with us.
And we're not goin'
through any suburbs. That's final.
Hey.
We're just changing the route.
We're not changing the plan. I promise.
What's 313?
Another team. They went to Saint Mary's
on a supply run, came across the survivors.
But 313 never made it back.
- His wife was their gunner.
- Greer played me the tape from your doctor.
Okay, you're gonna try to get
on this freeway here on the onramp.
Just be careful.
No. Pick up.
Pick up, pick up, pick up.
It's about time you called.
Too bad I'm not here. So leave a message.
There's no use for it.
We use our suit transmitters for com.
Get back in your seat.
Where is everybody?
There aren't many left alive,
but most of them stick around churches.
And parking garages,
they treat those things like roach motels.
They're not roaches.
They're starving and scared.
Fuck this.
Don't worry. I'll put it back on.
You said you were in Manhattan.
Is that where you're from?
No, I'm from here. I was moved to New York
to be part of a team working on the vaccine.
Can you tell us how it's going,
finding a cure and all?
We've made some promising
breakthroughs with antitoxins. We...
We've extracted the contaminant from the
defective cells. We feel very confident...
Ain't nobody even figured out
what caused this shit-fest, man.
And we countin' on these same
fuckin' idiots to save us.
- I heard it was in the water.
- There were lice and Ebola mutations,
brain parasites, the rapture.
I've heard 'em all.
What about you guys? You from LA?
- I lived in the valley with my son.
- Is he back at the compound?
This is Josh.
He passed before the virus hit,
of leukemia.
I'm sorry.
It doesn't what we did before.
It only matters what we do now.
Bullshit. Look at you
tryin' to act all tough.
- He was a traffic cop.
- Go head. Keep talkin'.
That piece might make you feel safe,
but you need it.
Anybody can pull a trigger.
You're just Greer's bitch.
- Wheeler?
- No, let this jerkoff say what he wants.
- Put that down. I'll say a lot more.
- Yeah.
Y'all didn't ask me shit,
but I'll tell you anyway.
Forty-two, 92, seven off.
I call this work release.
- You're a felon.
- That scare you?
No. We all do
whatever it takes to survive.
For some of us,
this may be one last opportunity.
Yeah. For what?
A second chance.
Please stop! Please...
Help me. Please stop.
What the fuck is this?
- She doesn't look sick.
- Please...
All right, get what you need.
- I'm not sick. Please!
- Oh, man.
What are you doin'?
Get your tools. Your tools.
Shit.
Get me out of here, please!
Let's go, doctor!
Open the door.
Please get me out of here. I'm not...
Please get me out of here.
All right. Just take it easy.
We're gonna take care of you.
- Just relax. Just relax.
- Get me out of here.
Please. We have to get
out of here. I'm not sick.
Doc, what the hell are you doin'? Come on.
Check and see if she's infected. Let's go.
We have to get out of here now.
We have to get out of here now!
We will, ma'am. You have to calm down now.
I'm not sick. I'm not... I'm not sick.
- Come on. What are you doin'?
- Making sure this... this test...
Doctor, what are you doin'? Give it to me.
Give it to me. Give it to me.
- Here.
- I'm not sick, please.
All right, listen, just...
just turn around. Turn around.
Come on, Doctor.
Talk to me, Doctor. How she doin'?
She's not infected. She's not infected.
We can take her with us.
Let's get her on the bus. Let's go!
- Gunner, she's... she's stuck.
- She's what? What?
She's stuck. Gunner, she's stuck.
She's taped to the grate. I...
- Please, don't let me die. Please!
- Doctor, get back on the bus.
Get back on the bus!
It's a trap. It's a trap.
- Get on the bus!
- All right, let's go. Let's go.
Open the door.
Come on, come on, you can make it.
Grab my hand.
- Wheeler, slow down.
- I can't!
You're gonna shoot Gunner!
Shoot, damn it, shoot.
Shit!
Slow down! Slow down!
Run, you motherfucker, run!
He's in! He's in! He's in!
Never again, you hear me. You learn
your ass to run like the rest of us.
Is it over?
- What are you doing?
- Listen to me.
You better start fightin' back
or you gonna get us all killed,
and I'm not lettin' that happen.
You understand me?
Now, you go to Denise and then
you fix my goddamn shoulder.
Now do your damn job!
How could they do that?
Everybody has their limit.
Think of it like being underwater.
Holding your breath, you're fine,
but once you reach a certain point...
you'll do anything to get back on top.
Did they train you for the field?
- Yes, extensive.
- Where'd you practice before this?
What?
You are a doctor.
- So, where did you practice?
- Lab technician, 11 years with the CDC.
I was chosen to lead this team
because I am qualified to do so.
I got it. Thank you, doctor.
We're less than two miles to the school.
Let's hope we're not too late.
It's hard to believe, isn't it?
Those people that attacked us...
what do they want?
Get various supplies, a way back in, food.
Are you the suburbs are as bad?
The suburbs still look nice.
Don't let that fool you.
- Did you have family here?
- My husband and my daughter.
Did they make it out?
I haven't heard from them
since all of this started.
If the outbreak had happened...
a couple of days different
on either end, I would've...
I should've been there.
Two point five billion dead
and he still believes in God.
There's one theory you can cross off.
The rapture would've sucked
his dumb ass right up.
Shouldn't you ask him to stop
and check for uninfected?
- We're not stopping.
- They're trying to preserve the population.
Please. Greer could give
two shits about these people.
We're pickin' up guinea pigs.
You really think it's conspiracy shit?
Once the docs run outta people
to try their new vaccines on,
they'll turn to us. Am I wrong?
What am I asking you for?
You don't know shit.
If we get back,
ask Greer about Quarantine A,
about what he plans to do with these
survivors. He'll tell you I'm right.
The only thing I'm stoppin' for is Denny's.
I am fuckin' starvin'.
- Isn't there food at the compound?
- No, not for us. We have to earn our keep.
I've hardly eaten in days,
but it could be worse.
Most of them die of starvation.
Not all of us live in
the first-class camp, Dr. Chase.
- Oh, shit. Stop the bus!
- Dude, you see somethin'?
Yeah. Stop the bus.
I'm gonna take a lap around the block.
Make sure this ain't no trap.
Either this bus stops moving
or you stop moving.
Stop the bus.
Oh, my God.
Sorry.
Help me! Help... help me.
Get off.
- Grab her.
- Oh, my God.
Thanks.
Nice shot.
- Thanks.
- Where the hell were you?
I'm the only one who knows how
to drive this bitch. I ain't riskin' shit.
Did you find anything inside?
Hey...
the school's like three blocks
from here, so...
I'm gonna keep us movin'. Cool?
Yeah.
I'm sorry about your wife.
Have...
Have you ever...
heard of infecteds...
eating people?
No.
Why?
Did you see something?
We're here.
Shall we?
Let's do it.
Open the door.
Fuckin' sauna in here. I can't see shit.
Well, it looks like nobody's home.
Maybe they all left.
Yes. Yes.
Yeah, somebody help me push this.
Yeah, baby. Jackpot.
- Oh, my God.
- Wheeler, you can't take your helmet off.
What's it matter?
It's not like it's airborne.
We have to keep going.
We have to keep looking for survivors.
Fuck that. Don't you wanna eat?
I'll help you look.
- Yeah.
- Don't go far.
Yo!
They got raspberry.
Shit. They got steak. What?
Yo, can I ask you somethin'?
What you think of the doc?
Please...
Shit.
I'm gonna check out a few more of
these rooms. You go ahead. I'll catch up.
Okay.
Please, pick up.
Megan? Megan, sweetheart, is that you?
- Mom?
- Hi. Hi, baby. How are you?
- Mom, is that you?
- Yes. Yes, it's me. I'm here.
Are you okay? Where are you?
Are you at the house?
- Yeah.
- Why haven't you been answering?
Dad said to only turn it on once a day.
Where is your father? Is he there?
He left to find help.
- I'm scared. Please.
- I know, baby. I know you are.
But you're doing great. Okay?
I want you to listen to me.
I'm coming to get you.
I'm gonna be there very soon,
and I love you more than anything.
So, you stay put
and I'm gonna be there soon, okay.
Megan?
- Shit.
- You all right?
Yeah.
You call for us?
I found something.
Let's go.
- What?
- Here.
All right.
It's barricaded from the inside.
Hello?
It's okay. I won't hurt you.
Where are the others?
Is... is that your child?
Please. Take it.
- Please take it.
- Stand back, ma'am.
- Step back.
- Put your gun down. Put it down.
It's okay. It's okay.
We're not gonna hurt you.
Are there other people here with you?
- Just take him, please. He's not infected.
- That's great.
I'm gonna have to give him
a blood test to make sure, okay.
But he's not infected. Take him.
I know. Just... just put him down
right in front of you.
His name's Jeffrey.
He cries a lot, but it'll pass.
I'm sorry. I can't take him.
But... you have to. He can't stay here.
You have children? He's all I have left.
- I'm so sorry. I can't take him.
- But you said you'd take him.
It's okay. We can can come back for him.
Are there other people here with you?
- But you're here now. Take him now.
- Lower your fuckin' voice.
- Fuck her, let's go.
- Let's go. Come on. Let's go.
- Take him.
- We have to go now.
Please. Take him! Take him.
Take him! Take him!
How many you kill today?
This ain't no different.
Let's go. Come on.
We're leaving. Let's go.
Now.
Denise!
- What the fuck are you doing?
- We have to finish this.
- Help me, Gunner. Please. Please.
- All right, all right, all right.
Move to the side. Move.
Holy shit.
We're too late.
What a fuckin' waste.
You wanna check 'em, doc?
No. You heard Denise.
Mission's over. We should go.
Fuck is that?
Run. Run.
Get those doors closed!
Denise, get somethin'
to keep these doors closed.
- Come on, goddamn it. Feel it.
- Gunner... I really do.
All right, come on. Let's move, move, move.
We need to get to the bus now.
Fuck this.
We can't jump from here.
We'll break our legs.
I don't care. Open the window.
- You can't open it?
- Wheeler they're nailed shut.
Move damn it. Move.
Take this. You got it?
Okay.
- Gunner!
- Go. I'll be right behind you. Go.
Oh, my God.
- Give me the gun.
- What? No.
- Give it to me!
- Why? So you can leave us?
- Fine. Fucking die with it.
- Wheeler? Shit.
You okay?
Let's go.
- Where do we go?
- I don't know.
Come on. You'll catch your breath later.
- You have a cellphone?
- No. Call the control center.
How do I do that?
Hello? Control, this is Dr. Chase, 314.
Is anybody there?
Hello? This is Team 314. Is anybody there?
We must be outta range.
How we gonna get back to the compound?
It's too far to walk back.
We need to find a place to hide
until Dr. Greer sends out the next team.
How long will that take? I can't wait.
We don't have a choice. It's almost dark.
They'll be ten times as many of them.
Pull it together. Let's go.
Why can't we just take one of these?
Because the X's mean
the gas is sucked out.
- How many bullets do you have left?
- Two.
You might wanna save them.
For us.
Shit. I think someone's coming.
- The van over there.
- Okay.
Fucking starving.
- We're moving to the next block.
- Almost gone.
His feet...
I think they're gone.
Are you all right?
Yeah. Let's go.
What was his name again?
Josh. He would've been eight.
I told you maybe he was lucky
not to see all this.
That's the lie I tell myself.
I want his clothes. I want his smell.
I want his room. I...
I want him, not this fucking picture.
Denise,
I spoke with my daughter. She's alive.
Oh, my God, Lauren.
I don't know what to say.
How long do you think it will take
for them to send another team?
Maybe a day or a week, but they will.
- We just have to wait here together.
- What do you mean?
They're not gonna let me back into
the compound without you or the bus.
- Yes, they will.
- No, Wheeler was right.
They don't care about us. I need you.
But I can't wait. Dr. Greer said they
were gonna stop sending teams out,
that they were gonna lock
the doors and wait it out.
No, you're a doctor.
They will come for you.
No.
Not if they...
What?
Dr. Chase?
If you could get Josh back...
wouldn't you do whatever it takes
no matter the consequences?
I can save my daughter.
I thought she was dead, but she's alive.
And they won't... they won't be
coming for me, not if they know...
If they know what? What?
- Lauren?
- I'm not...
I'm not Lauren Chase.
- What do you mean?
- I came to the compound on an extraction.
I'm not a doctor.
No, I saw you.
You were with Greer. I saw...
I stole this...
from a doctor I found
in the street in New York.
Dr. Chase.
- My name's Rebecca Thomas.
- Why are you telling me this?
Because I thought you should know.
I was on a business trip
when the outbreak hit
and I should've come right back, but they
told me everything was gonna be okay.
And I believed them.
And then they told me I couldn't leave.
- They told me my family was gone.
- You put all of our lives in danger.
Gunner is dead because of you.
How could you do this?
How could you be so selfish?
I did everything I could
to get back into the city.
The only way was to pretend
I was somebody else.
I lost my family once,
because I didn't do anything,
because I trusted that someone else
would bring them back to me.
Now, I'm sorry that I lied to you...
but I need to go my family
and I need to go now.
You can't go. We don't have Gunner.
We don't have a bus.
If Josh were alive...
and you knew that he didn't have a week,
you would go to him, you would...
you would try no matter what.
Before when you wanted to change
the route to Sherman Oaks,
- that's where your family is, right?
- It's close.
- All right. I'm gonna go with you.
- You don't have to.
No, you're right. If Josh was still alive,
I would've done the same thing.
Besides if they haven't realized
you're lying, you're my only way back.
Okay. Let's see if this place
has water and weapons.
I can't see it. Can't... Denise?
Where did it go? Did you see it?
Help me. Help me.
- I can't see it.
- Hit it! Hit it!
I can't. Denise?
You came back.
I ain't dyin' a virgin.
What took you so long?
Come here.
Thank God.
First time I seen a Level 5 downtown.
If you ain't gonna trust no one else to touch
that, how bout you keep it with next time?
- Where the hell did you go?
- I hid in a bank. Retirement plan.
I saw y'all run up in here.
But did you talk to the doc?
- No response from the compound.
- I'm talking about the doc here.
- Another team?
- No, he's locked up in some hospital.
I told him I'd find you and call him.
He didn't even believe
I was with the team. Turn it on.
This is Dr. Chase.
Is there a doctor out there
who spoke with my driver?
Hello? Dr. Chase?
Yes, Dr. Lauren Chase,
extraction team 314.
- Thank God.
- Told you I wasn't lyin', motherfucker.
My name is Dr. Ward.
I have eight survivors with me.
- Can you rescue us?
- Ward...
- Are you the doctor from 313?
- That's right.
It was his voice on the call
that Greer played me.
We were on an extraction to Saint Mary's.
We lost our vehicle in the process.
We have one. Does your driver know
how to hotwire an ambulance?
- Fuck yeah.
- Good. We're in the Presbyterian Hospital.
We'll be waiting for you
in the back entrance.
That's like three
or four blocks from here.
You really know
how to hotwire an ambulance?
Not so bad having a felon now?
Yeah.
Three blocks. We can run.
What?
Oh, shit.
- I was gonna say.
- What happened?
In the bank, I saw a dude like that.
I killed him, but...
Open it.
- Oh, my God.
- It's not bad. I can move, but...
- It can't be that bad yet. Stitch me up.
- She can't.
- We lost our first-aid supplies.
- Shit.
- Then we gotta get back to the compound.
- Wheeler, they won't let you back in.
- Those are Greer's orders.
- We are not leaving him.
- You came back for us. Yes?
- I'm here.
You chose to go to the compound and work.
You could've joined one of those gangs,
but you didn't because you wanted to help.
You wanted to help.
You want a second chance, right?
Yeah. I do.
Good.
We aren't going back
to the compound, not just yet.
We're gonna go the hospital.
You're gonna get us a car.
You're gonna drive to my house
- and we're gonna save my family.
- What the fuck are you talkin' about?
My husband and my daughter,
we're gonna go get them.
- You know about this?
- I'm going with her.
We get my family and I will get you
back into the compound
and have you treated for the virus, but
only if you do exactly what I tell you to.
- Yes or no?
- You ain't give me a fuckin' choice.
- If I do, you're gonna fix this.
- Yes.
- Can you?
- Level 1 infections can be treated.
Then, yeah. Fuck yeah.
You save me, I'll save your family.
Wait. What are you doing?
You wanna make it to the hospital...
I go ahead of you,
let you know if it's clear.
I'm already infected, so...
- fuck it, right?
- Are you sure about this.
What have I got to lose?
Shit.
- They're gonna kill him.
- Get ready to run.
Wheeler?
What's happening?
- Are you okay?
- I think I just shit my pants.
What happened?
They wanted what I had,
which ain't nothin'.
So I said I seen a bus
a couple miles back.
- I think they bought it.
- Okay.
- Are we close?
- Yeah.
- It's just around this corner.
- All right, let's go.
- Where is Josh?
- What?
- I can't find Josh.
- Oh, shit. Oh, shit.
Over there.
- Come on, Denise.
- Josh...
- Denise, come on!
- Josh.
Come on, Denise.
Doc, she's gone. Come on. She's gone.
Denise!
Denise! Denise!
No. Please. Please. Please. I'm hurt.
Don't hurt me.
You're a doctor, right? Right?
Please. Please. Please, no. No.
It's me. It's just me.
You're all right.
I'm so sorry. I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
We gotta go, all right? Come on.
I can't hear you!
- Are you Dr. Chase?
- Yes, I am.
- Who's he?
- This is my driver. Now let us in.
- No, he's not. He's one of them.
- Fuck you, man. I'm the fuckin' driver.
- He's my driver. You have my word.
- Why isn't he wearing his suit?
- We don't have time for this right now.
- Prove to me he isn't infected, both of you.
- Otherwise, no one's coming in.
- Let us in.
Okay. Wheeler, can you open my pack.
See. I'm not infected.
Now him.
Okay.
He's not infected. Now let us in.
Meet us down in the garage.
- You can take one of those.
- This one got gas?
Yeah. And most civilians don't even know
where the tank is on one of those things.
- Are you all from Saint Mary's?
- Yeah.
Right after I contacted the compound,
our bus was ambushed.
My whole team perished along with the rest
of the survivors. We're all that's left.
All right, clear out the entire cabin.
We need to fit everyone inside.
- Where's the rest of your team?
- Where the fuck do you think?
My apologies.
Did you hear that?
All right. Come on. Let's go.
Everybody inside. Let's go. Let's go.
After you.
- What the fuck?
- Wheeler?
- You lied to me!
- Look, Doc.
- Who are you?
- Dr. Ward, what...
Answer me. Who are you?
I already told you.
I'm Dr. Lauren Chase from 314.
I worked with Dr. Chase.
What have you done with her?
- I...
- We were sent to bring you all back, doc.
- Answer the question!
- Lower your gun.
We are all going back
to the compound together.
Get back. Back!
At least leave us the gun.
If I see you in that compound,
I will fuckin' kill you!
You're infected. You never will.
Motherfucker!
I'ma kill you, you motherfucker!
Go, go, go.
Just one more second.
Yes! Come on!
You all right? All your fingers and toes?
- Yeah, I think so.
- Good.
Now, where we goin'?
So, what's your real name?
- Wheeler, I can explain.
- It's cool. Takes a con to know a con.
I was onto you way before
the doc blew your cover.
You didn't know how to use the mosquito.
You didn't know how to wrap
Gunner's shoulder.
But you did fake
that blood test pretty quick.
I met some grifters in my day,
but you're good.
- You gonna leave me out here?
- No. Your secret's safe.
Just tell me one thing. Where'd you
learn how to speak like a doctor?
Thesaurus.
Wheeler, I will get you into the compound.
I know.
So you just a mama
tryin' to get to her cubs?
I'm Frederick. Freddie.
Rebecca.
Let's just stick with doc.
Up there, the one with the garden.
All right. I'll keep the engine runnin'.
If you don't find what you're lookin' for,
say your goodbyes.
It's more than most got.
Thank you.
Megan?
Baby, are you here?
Please, please. Please. Please. Megan?
Megan, it's Mom.
Megan? Oh, my God.
Oh, my God.
Megan? Megan?
- Stay...
- No, baby.
Baby, it's me. It's me.
Mom?
Come here.
Come here. Come here, sweet...
Mommy, you came.
- You're okay.
- You came.
Of course, I came for you. I told you
I was gonna come for you, didn't I?
Of course, I came.
I love you so much.
- Megan, where's Dad?
- He's still not back.
It's just me.
It's us now, okay.
- Are we leaving?
- Yes. We have a ride out front.
I have something for you. Eat this slowly.
I'm gonna be right back, okay. Stay here.
Baby? Megan?
Tilt your head back a little bit.
It's just a little bit of water.
What's that?
It's nothing to be nervous about.
I just need to check your blood.
Hold my hand.
Am I sick?
No.
No, you're not infected.
You're gonna be fine.
- I am?
- Yes. Everything is gonna be fine.
No... I thought for sure that...
Baby, you haven't eaten in so long.
Of course you feel sick.
I'm gonna go to the garage,
I need to grab a few things.
And when I come back,
we're gonna go the safe zone, okay?
No.
Oh, God, David.
My name is David Thomas.
I've locked myself in here
to protect my daughter.
Whoever you are, please save her.
My wife is Rebecca Thomas.
If you find her...
tell her I love her.
And that I'm sorry.
Goodbye.
David.
I'm so sorry.
Megan's alive.
And if she's only Level 1, I can...
I will save...
our daughter.
Fuck me.
Megan, I've gotta check something
by the window, okay?
Level 5's.
What's that sound?
- What are you doing?
- You need to put this on.
- What about you?
- Megan, trust me.
Here, let me help you.
Get down. Put your feet in first.
- We're gonna have to run, okay.
- Mom... I love you.
Megan, I love you more than anything.
We're gonna be fine. Let's go.
We're almost there. We're almost there.
- Mom? Mom?
- Run, Megan! Run!
Mom? Mom?
Go. Go, Megan. Up the stairs. Go upstairs.
- Go, Wheeler, go.
- Go, go.
Mom!
Megan, run! Run!
Wheeler! Go, Megan.
- Fuck. There's too many.
- Okay. Okay. Open the door.
- What?
- Just do it. Trust me.
Go to the window. Megan, open the window!
Go!
- You have to come with us!
- I know. Fuckin' jump!
Come on, Megan. Come on.
He's hurt.
Help me. We gotta get him
to the front yard.
Come on... Get up.
- I can't.
- Get up.
No, I'm good.
No more hero shit. Just get your girl.
I'm so sorry, Freddie.
- Run! Run!
- Go. Come on.
No. Run. Run.
It's okay. It's okay. Go.
It's okay.
Get in, Megan. Get in. Get in.
Lock the door. Lock the door.
Baby, it's okay. They're gone.
It's behind us. They're gone.
Megan? Megan, look at me.
Keep your eyes open, baby.
Open your eyes. We're almost there.
Megan? Megan, stay with me.
Megan? Megan, please.
Lord.
It's okay.
There it is.
Megan, come on, baby.
We have to get out. Okay? Hold on to me.
Talk to me.
Megan? Get up. Get up. Get up.
Megan.
Don't shoot. Please. Please. Don't shoot.
I'm Dr. Lauren Chase. Please.
It's okay. Please.
Get up here now!
I love you.
We have an unconscious...
in the rear of the compound.
- What's the code on the suit?
- 730-A.
- Goddamn it. Are you sure?
- 10-4.
Okay, that's Dr. Chase. I need an evac at
the back entrance now! Is she still alive?
She's unconscious, sir.
I think she's infected.
Bring her to Quarantine A,
prep her for treatment.
Orders are to keep all infected
outside of the compound.
I give the orders.
She's the last of the CDC.
Bring her to Quarantine A!
Yes, sir. Bringing her in.
Come on.
Let's move. Let's go.
Someone needs to stop Clearway Law.
Public shouldn't leave reviews for lawyers.