Watch Movies, TV Series and Live Sports
Signup Here -> WWW.ADMITME.APP
I wrote it all down:
4,222 square feet, four floors. Perfect.
Courtyard in back,
south-facing garden. Perfect.
-Shouldn't we wait for the car service?
-No, we'll sit in traffic forever.
-ls that the listing sheet?
-There isn't one.
I heard about it this morning.
lt'll be gone soon.
-How many more?
-None. You know the market is tight.
-Sarah, do you have to ride that here?
-Mom, we're in the street.
Evan!
One day you will learn
to respect people's time, Lydia.
You'll realize that the world does not stop
and start at your convenience.
l'm so sorry.
l'm meeting Arthur Digby Laurence
in 26 minutes...
...and if you think he's the kind of man
who tolerates tardiness...
...you are sadly mistaken.
You're a saint to wait for us.
-Thank you.
-Hello.
lt's kind of between a townhouse
and a brownstone.
We call it a "townstone."
Built in 1879, this is the middle
of the house, the parlor floor.
Here is the living room.
Formal dining is in the back.
Casual dining below on the kitchen floor...
...which was renovated in '94
with all the expected amenities.
Sarah.
There are two bedroom floors above.
My God, it's amazing.
Hey, kid. No scooter.
l don't have to tell you this amount
of living space is uncommon in Manhattan.
lt's got a yard. Sort of.
lt is in a bit of disarray, but then again,
21-foot lot, 53 deep.
lt allows for an expansive garden.
Working elevator.
The previous owner was disabled
the last years of his life.
Highly unusual, the elevator.
You will not find this
in 90 percent of brownstones.
Perhaps it's something of a fixer-upper,
but we anticipate enormous interest.
lt's a very emotional property.
Shall we have a look at the rest?
You should make an offer immediately.
Can l see it first?
There is nothing like this
on the market right now.
You can't move from Greenwich
to the Upper West Side...
...and expect to still have a house, a yard
and a dog and cat, but here it is.
lt's got everything
you told me you wanted and more.
You'll have another family.
You could have two.
lt's a fortune.
Mom, it's not Barneys.
You don't have to pay the price on the tag.
He can afford it.
lt would be so lovely
if l could show the property before l leave.
Hardwood floors throughout,
as many as six working fireplaces.
This is the top floor. Two bedrooms.
One at either end.
They share one small bath.
Originally, this would have been
the servants' quarters.
The previous owner
kept a small nursing staff.
l don't know if you have live-in help.
No, it's just the two of us.
Third floor, spare bedroom, den,
or what have you.
Mr. Pearlstine used this as an office.
He's talking about Sidney Pearlstine,
the financier.
May l ask what you do, Mrs....
Altman.
Actually, l'm going back to school.
Columbia.
Her husband's in pharmaceuticals.
l didn't realize
you were Stephan Altman's wife.
Yes, until recently.
Master bath.
Pearlstine's been in all the papers
since he died.
His kids are suing each other
over the estate.
He was a recluse. Rich, paranoid.
Now they can't find half his money.
l hardly see how gossip
is germane to showing the property.
Stop calling it "the property."
lt sounds ridiculous.
Walk-in closet.
Could the little one please stop that?
Kid, no elevator!
And we emerge in the master suite.
That's strange.
What?
ls this room smaller than it should be?
You're the first person to notice.
On caravan, no one from our office
had the slightest idea.
lt's called a panic room.
-What?
-A safe room.
-A castle keep in medieval times.
-l've read about these.
They're in vogue in high-end construction.
One can't be too careful
about home invasion.
This is perfect.
The alarm goes off
in the middle of the night.
What will you do?
Call the police and wait till Tuesday?
Traipse downstairs in your underthings
to check it out? l think not.
Concrete walls. Buried phone line,
not connected to the house's main line.
Call the police, nobody can cut you off.
You have your own ventilation system.
A bank of surveillance monitors that covers
nearly every corner of the house.
This whole thing makes me nervous.
Why?
Ever read any Poe?
No, but l loved her last album.
What's to keep somebody
from prying open the door?
Steel.
Thick steel. Very thick steel.
Full battery backup,
so even if the power's out...
...it's still functional.
Oh, my god.
Old Sidney didn't miss a trick, did he?
Open it, please.
And with kids like he's apparently got,
no wonder he wanted a place to hide.
Please open the door.
That is highly inappropriate.
Open the door, please.
My room. Definitely my room.
This is really dangerous.
-That door is a hazard.
-Not at all.
Motion detector, like an elevator.
The door won't close if it's blocked.
There's another one at your ankles.
lt couldn't be safer.
l know they'll take asking price.
lt's working. l hooked up the phone!
Good for you, Mom. Hooked up a phone.
579 what?
3000.
patsy's pizza. pIease hoId.
Hey. Enough.
Mind the pizza?
What do you mean?
Our first night.
l should've thought of something special.
l like pizza.
Fuck him.
Don't.
Fuck her, too.
l agree.
But don't.
Don't you think this place
has way too many stairs?
You didn't carry anything up them.
You never asked
what l thought of this house.
l didn't want you to tell me you hated it.
-l liked our old house.
-Well, so did l.
You know what l was thinking?
l was thinking we could
stencil the whole bookcase.
We could cut the stencils, do it ourselves.
Go ahead.
Oh, damn.
l forgot to set up that tour
of your new school.
Dad already did it.
l'm going with him on Sunday.
Oh, yeah?
So l'll take a cab and meet him there.
ls that what he said?
lsn't that what's so great
about Manhattan?
You don't have to drive me everywhere?
l'll ride with you.
Why'd you bring me here
if l can't go anywhere on my own?
That's it. l quit.
l'm not fighting with you till tomorrow.
Come here.
lt's disgusting how much l love you.
Tell me about it.
-Mom?
-Yeah.
lt's too dark.
Better?
That's better.
"Bypass non-ready zone."
"Shunt. Enter."
"Shunt."
"Enter zone number."
"Shunt again."
ln the morning l got to figure out
how to turn this thing off.
Go, go back.
Do it.
Come on. Come on. Jesus fucking Christ.
Amateur.
We got a problem! We need to talk!
lt's about time. l'm freezing
my tits off out there.
-Who is that?
-This is Raoul.
Who the fuck is Raoul?
Raoul is okay. Raoul has experience.
-Where'd you get him?
-Through some people.
Open the fucking door.
No shit.
What is this?
There's a girl on the top floor,
a woman on the third. They're asleep.
They're not supposed to be here.
-This is your department, Junior!
-They are not supposed to be here!
Videotape. We're on videotape.
We've been on videotape since we got here
and the tapes are upstairs.
-14-day escrow.
-You fucked me!
14-day escrow! That's almost 3 weeks!
They should not be in for another week!
Exactly how is 14 days three weeks?
Business days.
Escrow is always business days.
Five-day weeks always!
Right?
l'm out of here.
Just wait a minute. Wait a minute!
We can handle this.
Can we still handle this?
lt's just a woman and a kid?
-Unless Daddy comes home.
-He's not.
They're divorcing. Daddy's banging some
B model on the Upper East Side.
lt's just her and the kid!
Now, can we do this?
Yeah, we can do it.
Not with people here. And not with me.
-Wait! Twenty minutes!
-She'll call the police.
They'll be here before l unpack my bags.
So, we keep an eye on her.
Raoul can totally administrate that part.
l don't want Raoul to administrate that!
He's not even supposed to be here!
Nobody gets hurt.
What about us? What if she has a gun?
Who are you?
l'm Raoul.
You know we can't do this without you!
This is still a good plan.
Fuck that! This is a great plan.
lt's just got a slight twist.
Yeah.
Felony kidnapping. Thirty years.
You make a lot of promises, don't you?
You promise me, you promise your kids.
No family.
You're right. lt's all fucked up.
l fucked it up!
lt's not how it's supposed to be.
But the fact of the matter is
there's still $3,000,000 in this house...
...and no one but you and l
even knows it's here.
Hey, l want that money. l want it!
But you...
...you need that money.
Or have you forgotten why you're here?
So let's quit dicking around, okay,
and get this over with.
Kill the phones.
Top floor, little girl. l've got the mother.
Give me that!
You stay here! Nobody gets past!
Wake up! Sarah!
Get up!
What did you do that for?
Where are you going?
-What's going on?
-People. ln the house.
They're in the elevator, heading down.
Fuck! They're coming down to you!
l told you. l don't hurt people.
They're going downstairs.
-That room.
-What?
The panic room.
No, press emergency stop.
Fuck!
Coming back up!
That's you.
Shit.
Go!
Fuck!
Fuck! Fuck! Fuck! Fuck!
Damn it! Mother--
Shit!
That's seven years bad luck.
Shit.
Tell me they're not in there.
Oh, damn.
-lt doesn't work?
-lt's a different phone line.
l never hooked it up.
Now what?
l can't hear a thing.
What do you think they want?
l don't know. Rob us....
l don't know.
What do we do?
We wait.
-What if they get in here?
-Well, they can't.
They can't get in. lt's not possible.
Mom. l heard you.
-Do you feel okay?
-Yeah.
-You shaky?
-No.
-Chills?
Please. Don't worry about me.
He's got kids. What do you think he'll do?
Hang out while the cops waltz in?
Use your head.
Here he comes.
l locked the roof access.
She's not getting down from there.
-Good.
-She could be in there calling the cops.
Could she have hooked it up today?
No. You don't just call up Bell Atlantic.
She would've had to do it through
Manhattan Security, my company.
l checked the paperwork
and the phone is not connected.
You see? She couldn't have.
-l thought she wouldn't be here.
-He said she wouldn't.
Fuck you! And fuck you!
She is not supposed--
Do it.
Excuse me.
The poIice are on their way.
-She's lying.
-You're full of--
lt's not an intercom. lt's a PA system.
l know. l'm just scaring her.
I suggest you Ieave before they get here.
-What?
-He's saying that we don't have a phone.
How could he know that?
Take what you want and get outI
lf only it were that easy.
Some paper. l need some paper.
Give me some paper.
Hey, Zorro! You going to help us out?
You got a piece of paper?
-What is he doing?
-l don't know.
"What we want is in that room"?
They're coming in here, aren't they?
No, no. l told you. They can't get in here.
What do you know about this room?
What do we know about that room?
-Let's not tell her anything.
-Just a few details.
We're not coming out,
and we're not letting you in!
Get out of my houseI
-Say "fuck."
-You fuck.
-Mom.
-What?
"Get the fuck out of my house."
Get the fuck out of my houseI
Okay, l have an idea.
She's a woman. Women need security.
She won't believe you.
She needs to know she's dealing
with decent people and she can trust us.
Conversation's overI
What? She's not coming down?
Shut up.
Will you please shut up and let me think?
Like that'll help you think.
You know what? Fine! You think!
-What if she did call the cops?
-She didn't.
She said it again, that she called the cops.
lf cops were coming,
do you think l'd still be here?
Okay, fine. Good, excellent.
We all believe you.
How do we get into that room?
What is funny about this?
ls this shit funny to you?
l spent the last 12 years
building these rooms...
...to keep out people like us.
lt's all so ironic and amusing, okay?
Now, how do we get in?
We can't.
You can't get in the panic room.
That's the whole point.
We have to get her to come out.
And why would she do that?
l don't know.
But when she does,
she can't get out of this house.
We keep her here,
we keep her quiet for 20 minutes...
...and l don't want any help
from Joe Pesci over here.
They want to hole up in this house? Fine.
We make it impossible for them to leave.
And why would they come out
in the first place?
l'm working on that.
-Are you okay?
-Yeah.
Small space?
l'm okay.
-You can't wig out.
-l know.
-l mean it.
-l won't.
You know,
people never get buried alive anymore.
l guess it used to happen all the time.
Really?
Yeah, l read that.
And when did this happen all the time?
Twenty, thirty years ago.
What are they doing now?
l don't know.
They're locking us in.
This is not happening.
Sarah, calm down.
You know what could happen
if you let yourself get worked up.
Sarah!
-What the hell are you doing?
-We're coming in from below.
No, you're not. Even if you got through
the concrete, there's steel.
You won't even make a dent.
We'll see.
Hey. This is what l do.
lf some idiot with a sledgehammer
could break in...
...do you really think
that l would still have a job?
Don't get that in your eye.
Neighbor.
Help!
Please help us!
-Call the police!
-Do you hear us?
Help us!
Help!
-Help us, please!
-Call the police!
Shit!
You guys just going to stand there?
Why? What do you got, MacGyver?
He can't get in here with a hammer,
can he?
Could you be any louder?
Give me a hand with those boxes.
Listen, goddamn it!
l'm in charge here.
Now, what the hell is going on?
-They're going to get in here.
-No, they can't get in here.
We're going to be fine. We'll be just fine.
Oh, this is good.
This could work.
l was just thinking
that we should do something like this.
-Open it.
-l just did.
Open it some more.
We're just sending them a message.
They'll get the point.
Honey, get down on the ground.
Quit dicking around
and open this fucking thing up.
-Don't be stupid.
-Quiet!
We're trying to scare them, not kill them.
What is it?
lt's bad.
They're coughing.
lf they're coughing, they're going to die!
Nobody is going to die, man!
Will you please have the balls
to follow through with something?
Mom.
The worst that'll happen is they'll pass out.
They'll have a hangover.
How are we going to get in there
if they pass out, Junior?
Cut it back a little.
They won't pass out, numb-nuts.
They'll throw up first.
We can't get in if they're dead!
Stay on the ground and breathe.
Turn it down.
Turn it down! lt's too much!
-Don't you start up with this shit.
-Keep it down!
l'm turning it down.
-Keep his ass off of me.
-We're not killing anybody.
-Tell him to turn it down!
-Turn the shit off.
-No.
-Turn it down.
-Mom?
-Just a second.
Get under this.
Oh, my god.
-Fucking amateurs, man!
-lt's my fucking idea.
Shut the fuck up!
There are people trying to sleep over there.
What is that?
Turn the gas off.
Turn the gas off right now.
Get back!
Shit!
God!
Get it off me!
lt's okay.
You fucking bitch! You fucking bitch!
l'm coming in there!
Calm the fuck down.
-Are you okay?
-Yeah.
Promise me you'll never do
anything like that.
l won't.
They're moving.
At least they're still moving in there.
What?
Talk to him.
Please, man, give it a rest.
-That Morse code?
-SOS.
Where'd you learn that?
Titanic.
We got to talk. Downstairs.
No, no, no. Not you.
Come on, come on, come on.
Get up.
Come on.
Wake up.
The first thing l'm going to do this morning
is call my plastic surgeon.
There's been a change here.
$100,000 is not enough. Not for this shit.
l want a third
of whatever's in that room up there.
Fine!
Okay? Full share, one-third.
Congratulations.
You bought a ski mask, made $1,000,000.
Your parents will be proud.
Got him.
Let me straighten out something else.
Get control of your goddamn expert.
l'm not losing
my half of the money because--
Slow down. Half?
Did you sleep through grade school?
Five seconds ago, it was a third....
Come on.
l'm letting you know he's a problem.
But this wasn't my idea,
so he's your problem.
You're right. lt wasn't your idea!
None of this was your idea!
lt was my idea!
Come on, look over here.
Yes.
Yes, yes, yes.
Let's hope this guy's an ex-Boy Scout.
-We're here!
-Help us!
We're over here!
Help!
Open your window!
We're never going to get out of here.
l'm the loving grandson who put in
the time with the old man...
...every goddamn weekend for two years...
...talking to him, dressing him,
walking him, feeding him.
Are you done?
No. l'm the one the old man
finally told about the safe.
l'm the one who found the guy who built it,
and l convinced him to break into it!
Wait a minute.
-What?
-The bedroom's empty. Where are they?
Two of them, on the stairs.
Where's the third guy?
l left my cell phone by the bed.
l earned that money.
l will not let you jeopardize
my fucking plan...
...because you have a problem
relating to others!
Got it?
lf l don't come back, close this door.
Just do what l say.
He touches me again, l'll shoot him.
Christ!
Wait!
Any other schoolyard bullshit to settle,
or can we get back to work?
Don't take no tone with me, jerk-wad.
l'll shove it up your ass and snap it off.
You're a bus driver, Raoul.
You live in Flatbush.
Don't spout some Elmore Leonard
bullshit you just heard...
...because l saw that movie, too.
What is this?
l got some news for you.
Go.
Go!
Fuck!
She got something. What did she get?
No.
Charger!
She has a cell phone.
No!
All right, signal.
Come on. Signal.
l don't think they'll be talking
on no cell phone from in there.
-Why not?
-You can't call out from in there.
No signal.
l didn't hook up this line,
but l hooked up the main line.
lf we can find it, we can cut into it.
l can't go to prison, man.
l'm not built for that shit.
Be careful.
Get the phone.
-lt doesn't come off.
-Rip it off!
Screwdriver. Phillips.
Junior, when l asked you to cut
the phone lines, did you cut the main line?
Or did you just cut the cord on the phone
in the kitchen?
Shit!
Strip this and expose the wires.
-What are we doing?
-l have no idea.
-Okay, got it?
-Yeah. Here.
Okay.
Yellow, yellow.
Dial tone.
911 emergency.
Yes, this is 38 West 94th Street--
-pIease hoId.
-No, no. God.
Call Dad.
How do you live in New York
and not have a single Percocet?
-HeIIo?
-Stephan. Put Stephan on the line.
-Who is this?
-lt's Meg.
Do you know what time it is?
-Put him on the phone, bitch.
-It's your fucking wife.
Move.
-HeIIo?
-You've got to help us.
Move!
There are three men upstairs.
They broke in--
What--
-He'll do something.
-No, he won't.
He'll call the police.
You don't know her. She won't let him.
No. He knows that there's trouble.
He heard me.
He's across the park. That's why
we got houses close to each other.
Just in case we needed each other.
He'll help us.
-He won't.
-Yes, he will!
l'm sorry.
No, l'm sorry.
Why?
l was trying not to tell you.
What?
l'm dizzy and hungry.
All she's got is NyQuil and fucking Midol.
Looks like that gas idea
didn't work so well.
Whose fault was that?
This is impossible.
What's the plan now, hot rod?
This is worse than impossible.
This is unpleasant.
Here, drink this.
All right, drink lots of water.
You dropped to the low 40s.
We have to get your blood-sugar up.
Can you hear me okay?
l'm just dizzy, not deaf.
Great. Smart ass. That's excellent.
Did you see anything in here?
Any candy bars or something sweet?
Let's check it again.
Mom, l did it.
We got to stay calm, okay?
lf we stay calm, everything will be fine.
All right? Stay calm.
You're making me nervous.
l'm sorry.
What if l keep dropping?
You won't. l'll figure something out.
You know, he's right.
There's no way
we're getting into that room.
What are you talking about?
l just got to be honest with myself here.
l don't need to be involved...
...with anything so harrowing
or perilous at this point in my life.
-You're giving up?
-Hell, yes.
l don't need the fucking aggravation.
l'll make an anonymous phone call.
They'll find the floor safe. l'll inherit.
Stephen, Jeffrey, Catherine, David.
Five grandkids, 60 percent inheritance tax.
Fuck, l'll still put away 8 or 900 grand
and keep my goddamn hair.
Take it. Go out and get loaded.
Wait a minute.
Say what you just said again.
Say that shit about the money
again, babycakes.
When? Before?
Yeah, before.
Splitting the money in your head,
you said you'd put away 800 or 900 grand.
What are you doing?
That was after tax, which makes it more
than a million and a half gross.
So now you're a tax attorney.
-l'm out of here.
-Wait a minute.
There's sugar in everything.
Places you'd never expect. Like ketchup.
Where else?
Travel kit.
Plus, you named eight people
you got to split it with...
...so that's 10 or 12 million bucks
in the safe.
A fuck-up like you has got to get less
than everybody else...
...so now l don't know what to think.
You're adding up money
you'll never touch, buddy.
How much is in there?
Mouthwash.
Saccharin.
Hey, l'm talking to you. Answer me.
Fine. There's more.
And when were you going to tell us
this minor economic detail?
lt doesn't matter now.
lt's totally fucking moot!
-Why are we having this conversation?
-What were you thinking?
How did you expect to get away with this?
Did you think that l'd open that safe...
...and then me and Raoul would wait
while you picked out your share?
What's the matter with you?
You got us into this mess,
and you were going to fuck us?
You got yourself into this.
You got the custody lawyers up your ass.
Your eyes were huge
when l told you about the gig...
...so don't play innocent.
Things didn't work out.
Play past it.
Mints? Sugar-free.
l'm opening that safe.
You leave, you get nothing.
lt's looking doubtful there, big guy.
l will split the money with Raoul.
But l don't ever want to see you again.
Cops show up on my doorstep,
we will know who sent them...
...and we will fucking find you.
l'll see you, Burnham.
Later, Raoul.
Mom!
Ride in a Town Car to 125th Street
a couple of times...
...think you know all about it.
You don't know nothing about me.
Sarah, listen to me:
Go to the corner. Shut your eyes
and don't turn around.
Okay.
You should see the look on your face.
What's happening?
-Don't move. Don't you fucking move.
-No, don't.
Come here.
-Don't shoot, please.
-Come on.
Shut it, lock it
and get the fuck away from it.
-Stop it, you fucking--
-Fucking what?
Clown? ldiot? Fucking asshole?
Who's the clown now?
Me.
That's right.
lt's burning me.
Who's got the gun?
You.
Remember that.
Find out who the fuck that is.
Give me your wallet.
Stephan Altman.
Did your wife give you a call, Stephan?
What did she say?
Don't know. Cut off.
-Phones are dead.
-Did you call anybody else?
Did you call the fucking cops, Stephan?
No.
He's telling the truth.
Yeah.
Yeah, he probably is.
Because when l do this, people don't lie.
What?
-What do you want?
-Get us into that room.
-l can't.
-Yeah, you can.
You're full of ideas.
You just got to squeeze one out.
You want me to just make something up?
You've got till the count of three.
Then you end up like Junior over there.
-One, squeeze.
-This is ridiculous.
Two, squeeze.
l don't know what to tell you.
-Three.
-Wait!
Okay.
l got an idea.
Maybe.
HeIpI Rubber SouI...
...Yesterday and Today,
MagicaI Mystery Tour, The White AIbum....
Stay warm, baby. Stay warm, all right?
Let It Be, RevoIver, Sgt. pepper....
Oh, god!
Dad?
No, no.
Take it easy.
Open the door! Open the door!
No.
Don't open the door!
-Just make it look good.
-Don't you tell me what--
Open the door!
Don't open--
Knock it off!
You kill him, they'll never open that door.
Oh, god.
All right. Lie down. Lie down.
Lie down.
All right.
You'll be fine. Come on.
He's fucking crazy.
Get your hands off him,
you frightening hillbilly motherfucker!
You're a strong girl.
You be strong. Be strong, sweetheart.
Get the fuck off him, now!
Just get off him!
lt's almost over.
Yeah, that's it. That's it.
All right, turn around.
l'll be right back.
lt's got blood on it.
You might want to wear it inside out.
Get your tapes.
Who's this?
lt's her kid.
What happened to her?
Who gives a fuck?
Hurry up. Get your stuff.
Hey, lady.
Mom?
What are you doing?
We've got your kid.
Come down here.
Let's get this over with.
Get her, get her!
Shit!
What happened?
No! Let her out!
-Where's your gun?
-Open the door.
No!
-Where's your gun?
-l don't know.
Open up!
Open it.
Shut up! Listen to me.
She's got your gun.
She's got your gun!
Stop screaming. Stop it.
l know you've got the gun.
put the gun down
and step away from the door.
You got to open the door.
My daughter is very sick.
She needs an injection.
Do you hear me?
Open the door so l can give her a shot.
Or l swear to God, l'll kill you both.
lf l open the door, you'll shoot us.
So give her the shot yourself.
Give her the shotI
Do you need this?
Can you do this yourself?
What happens if you don't get it?
Coma.
Die.
Fuck! Open it.
put the gun on the fIoor.
And go aII the way downstairs.
And I'II give her the shot, aII right?
I toId you to Ieave the gunI
Shit.
You fucking bitchI
If you puII any shit Iike that again,
I wiII fucking kiII her.
Do you hear me?
lf you step outside, l'll kill her!
If I see a uniform inside this house,
I'II cut her fucking throatI
Do you understand?
Yes.
But please, just give her the shot.
Please.
pIease.
Don't fucking do it.
While we're in here, she'll call the cops.
Are you going to open the safe?
Don't you look at me.
All l know about this is what l see on TV.
You got to talk me through this.
This right here?
lt's this?
Yeah, okay.
Nice house you guys got.
Your mom's rich.
Dad's rich. Mom's just mad.
Tap it.
l wish l could have put my kid in
a place like this.
lt's not that l didn't try.
Sometimes things, they don't work out
the way you want them to.
Done.
Wasn't supposed to be like this.
He had it all worked out.
Nobody was supposed to even be here.
Thanks...
...Burnham.
Wasn't supposed to be like this.
She's going to be okay.
I gave her the shot. She's aII right.
It'II be over soon.
Stephan.
Oh, my god.
Can you move?
Not much. l think my arm is broken.
Raise your arm.
Come on, raise your arm.
Try again.
Come on. Try again.
Meg, please don't do anything stupid.
They're going to kill us.
Just do everything they ask.
lt'll be okay that way.
Stephan, they'll kill her.
Holy shit. She called the goddamn cops.
The police.
You called the police?
Of course, l called them.
You scared the shit out of me.
She killed the kid.
She just killed her own kid.
All right, take this.
Don't say a word.
No, her husband must have called them.
Foreign son of a bitch. l told you!
Where is she?
There.
What the fuck's she doing?
She's going to handle it.
l'm just trying to unlock....
-ls everything okay?
-You all right, ma'am?
What are you.... What time is it?
lt's a little after 4:00 a.m.
We got a call, ma'am.
Somebody called you?
Can we come in?
What do you want?
-We'd like to come in.
-No, you can't come in.
Ma'am, you sure you're all right?
l'm fine.
Ma'am, you don't look so good.
Well, you don't look so hot yourself,
Officer Keeney.
Come on, l'm freezing out here.
"There are three."
What?
Your husband said you called for help.
That you said, "There are three"
right before you got cut off.
Oh, that phone call.
And your neighbors...
...called in about some loud shouts
or a loudspeaker of some kind?
That was the TV. lt's off now.
Can l just ask you one question?
What was the end of that sentence?
When you said, "There are three"...
...what was the rest?
Look....
My husband and l just split up...
...and it's my first night in a new house...
...and l admit l was a little drunk.
And the sentence,
if you insist on knowing...
...was going to be:
"There are three things that l'll do for you
if you come jump into bed with me."
Thank God l came to my senses
before l said all that, and l hung up...
...so nobody would ever have to know
what l was thinking.
Unless, of course...
...two policemen came in the middle
of the night and interrogated me.
So, Rick, you want to go?
Or do you want her to tell you
which three things?
All right.
Ma'am...
...if there's something you want
to say to us...
...but maybe you can't say it right now...
...you might want to make some kind
of a signal...
...by blinking your eyes a few times.
Something like that.
That's something you could do safely.
Man...
...you guys are good.
You mean, like if there was somebody
in the house or something?
They really train you guys.
No, l'm fine. l'm fine. Cross my heart.
Sorry to disturb you, ma'am.
'Night, ma'am.
This kid has seen my face.
Yeah, well, that's not my problem.
Yeah, it is. You're here with me.
You're on the hook, too.
Do one. Same price for the rest.
Stay the fuck away from me.
You know how this is going to end.
Goddamn!
What's up?
Why the hell didn't we do that?
What's she doing?
What the fuck does she think she's doing?
She's got your gun.
Who told you to bring a gun?
Just let me drill, man.
Empty?
Come on, man.
Bank bonds.
One second.
Two, three, four, five....
Why are we doing this?
Because it's going to come to that.
There are 22.
22 million dollars.
That lying little shit!
Let's get out of here.
Lift.
Leave that. Christ, l'll buy you new tools.
You'll be okay.
lt's glass. l got you. Come on.
Hurry up.
Watch the glass.
Get down here.
Wait.
Wait. You don't want to do that.
Dad, don't shoot him!
Let my daughter go.
We're finished. Your daughter's fine.
We'll go out the back door.
You'll never see us again.
Let her go.
Okay.
lt's okay.
Let's go.
Just let her go. Let her go.
Let go of her!
Put that gun down.
-Sarah, come here.
-Put that gun down!
-Do as l say.
-Don't be crazy, man.
-Just let her go.
-Let her go!
Are you okay?
-Did they hurt you?
-No.
-Did they touch you?
Stephan, shoot him. Shoot him!
Get off her!
You'll be okay now.
-Police!
-Don't move!
-Nobody move!
-Everybody on the ground!
Team two, upstairs. Team three, down.
Are you okay?
Are you all right?
Freeze! Don't move, motherfucker!
Don't move! l will kill you!
Move away from the wall!
Get off the fence! Move!
Put your hands in the air!
lt'll be okay. lt's fine, Dad.
ls there anybody else in the house?
No.
Central, l need a bus at 38 West 94th.
lt's okay. l'm all right.
l want to see the palms of your hands!
Do you hear me? Open your hands!
Dad, it's okay. You're going to be fine.
Everything is going to be fine.
This sounds interesting.
"Two-bedroom with den or third bedroom...
"...new kitchen, original bath, 70s East."
l thought you liked the West Side.
"61st and Central Park West.
"Bank foreclosure, must sell,
luxury doorman building, health club...
-"...conserg--"
-Concierge.
-What's that?
-lt's French for "superintendent."
What's W.E.A. mean?
That's West End Avenue.
"81st and West End Avenue.
"Three bedrooms plus den
or fourth bedroom, spacious living room...
"...cathedral windows--"
Do we need all that space?
How about this?
"West 83rd, two-bedroom,
doorman building...
"...park block, partial views, bright and cheery,
high ceilings and wood floors."
Yeah, that one. I like the sound
of that one.
Someone needs to stop Clearway Law.
Public shouldn't leave reviews for lawyers.