Someone needs to stop Clearway Law.
Public shouldn't leave reviews for lawyers.
If the number of humans could be reduced by half...
If the number of forests is burnt by half...
If the number of human beings is reduced to a hundred...
Could existing waste...
become one in a hundred as well?
Someone in the world definitely thinks so...
if you want to save the lives of others.
What's wrong?
Oww!
What are you doing?
A-A snake entered my hand!
Huh?
A snake got into it...!
Really...
what are you thinking?
Hey, wait--! Don't!
Are you really alright?
Huh?
It's because you're listening to something like this,
that's why you got this strange dream?
Good night.
Good morning.
Morning.
Oh, no...
This turned out bad...
I'm going to leave first, okay?
Eat your breakfast properly.
And don't forget your lunch.
Hey...
Keep yourself together...
Somehow...
my right hand feels weird.
Isn't it because of last night?
Strangling your own right hand
with your earphones and all.
I'm heading out.
What are you doing?
I'm going shopping at the next shop.
Huh...?
What's with that surprised expression?
Stop doing that.
What are you gonna do if my heart stopped?
Oh, c'mon. You're okay, right?
Don't mess around.
I'm not a kid anymore.
Ho-ho, you're blushing!
You're really cute when you do that.
Argh, get off me!
W-What is it?
Now, wait a second!
What the hell are you doing!?
Eh, huh?
I-I can't believe this!
In 1952, ECSC ...
The European Coal and Steel Community
is established.
This was 1950
when the French Foreign Minister, Robert Schuman
In order to prevent war
from breaking out between Germany and France
proposed a bill...
Run!
Pass it over!
Izumi, pass it!
That was great, Izumi.
Nice shot!
Carry on with the game.
Hey...
"Hand moves involuntarily"
I failed... I failed...
I didn't eat...
I failed, I failed.
What the hell are you?
What... are you?
My right hand...
I ate it.
You ate it!?
Teach me... to talk...
Shinichi.
Huh!?
Currently, the IAEA is carrying out
an investigation into a case.
IAEA.
Research.
Mom, I'm home.
Is the dinner ready yet?
I'm hungry.
Welcome back.
Hey, mom!
Where's the food!?
I'm really hungry.
Although I'm awake...
the dream is still continuing.
Hey, c'mon.
Gimme my right hand back.
I can't right now!
I'm gathering information.
You, since when did you
learn to talk so well...?
Studying the Japanese language,
one day is enough.
Shinichi...
Shinichi, you'll be late.
I'm up, mom!
Everything's fine!
What's okay, anyway?
Mom/Mother...
the body associated with Shinichi,
from the relationship with the father who lived in this house.
You know what a hospital is?
A place where the wounded and sick are treated.
I'll go there and let them cut you out!
I refuse!
I live on the cells that exists inside Shinichi.
If you do that, I would immediately die.
That's why I'm going to let them cut you out.
It will cause Shinichi to lose his right hand.
No point in doing that.
So what the heck?
No use asking questions.
Where did you come from?
Coming from nowhere,
and going nowhere?
What was I actually?
What answer can you give?
Shut up!
I do not have any memories.
My first memory starts with
failing to take over your brain.
And thinking that it's too bad.
Brain?
You're planning on taking my brain?
Because I've become a hand...
continuing my main mission is now impossible.
My feeling is wrapped up in despair.
That's my line.
Can you read faster?
It'd be bad if you got seen.
I do the same thing as you to learn.
No way?
To know the world that you live in,
I need a lot of information.
It doesn't seem like a thing a right hand should say.
Don't think like that.
Don't you want to be somebody?
You're annoying, monster.
I do not agree with you calling me that.
So what do I call you?
If I really need a name...
call me Migi.
Migi?
As in a right hand?
Right.
So you can also think of
simple things like that, huh?
This kind of movements are very intriguing.
Stop talking out loud here.
I want to know more.
Take me somewhere else.
I see. Compared to the melee combat a while ago,
this focuses on a longer range?
Like I said, don't talk out loud!
What kind of training do you have, Shinichi?
I...
don't do training.
You're late, Satomi...
Sorry, it took me a while.
Oh, you came.
If you do something like that again,
I'll kill you. Got it?
It's just--
What?
Sorry.
Oh...
It's turning out pretty good.
Why did you pick that?
Because I don't have talent like you.
That's how it is.
Eh...
But you're doing great over there.
Hey...
Your model...
could it be Satomi?
Huh!?
Don't say random things...
Hey, it's a woman, right?
You're not being honest.
Shinichi...
What the hell, you guys?
I'll just restart it!
Wah!?
Heh?!
Sorry for interrupting...
Shinichi, do you want to
mate with that female?
Hah?
Murano Satomi.
What do you know of it?
I know about the sword...
down here.
Can I investigate?
Don't joke around!
I'm not joking.
I'm interested in this!
Ah, wait--!
Stop, stop. Stop!
Welcome...
The price is 268 yen, and 980 yen for this,
Total 1248 yen for all.
Where are we going?
Where would you like to go to?
[Motive unknown,
Method unknown]
[Multiple killings discovered!]
[Terrifying acts of murder?]
For safety reasons,
please store your luggage.
Do not leave anything behind,
and check again before you alight.
To stop at the next stop,
please press the buzzer.
What are you doing!?
We have to get off!
Stop doing that with everyone around!
There, it's there!
What is?
I felt the real brain eaters.
Even though it's my first time.
This...
But why?
Your same kind?
Others just like you?
The distance is about 200 meters.
Come on.
I don't wanna!
Hah?
I-It's not what you think.
I need to know what it was
I'm supposed to have become.
Ok fine, I'll go.
Just calm down.
Here?
Yes, the distance out is only 5 meters.
Idiot!
Stop it!
Fellow kind?
You've come to a good place.
This place is nice...
By waiting alone,
I can get my next meal.
This is the original host.
Hmm?
What is this?
Is the brain still intact?
Now, that's bad...
Very bad...
Shinichi, run!
I sense killing intent!
You're a human.
You can't win!
Shinichi!
Wait!
If you lay a hand on this human,
I'll kill you!
I understand where you're coming from.
If the host dies,
you too won't be able to live.
So, you just have to move over here.
Move?
To do that...
it's impossible.
Seems you haven't done your homework at all.
It is impossible for one head with two brains.
But...
if it is from hand to hand,
then it's possible.
Look, I've cut it off.
Move over here.
Move over from that body.
My body should be better, right?
Migi?
You not going to listen to him, are you?
C'mon, say something!
Ah, whatever.
I'll cut off that whiny boy's head!
Are you serious!?
My body...
Is he dead?
Good thing we watched those sword fights.
You...
You've killed one of your comrades.
There was no other option.
If you die, I die.
His proposal was risky.
You saved me!
This is not for you.
I just saved myself.
And also perhaps,
someday maybe I'll leave.
Hey...
Remember not drink too much.
Tell your wife to come over, okay?
Ok, I'll remember to tell her.
Get well soon.
Thank you very much.
I'll finish up soon,
so wait there a bit.
I'll go shopping first, okay?
Welcome.
Two mincemeat, please.
All right.
Why mince?
Huh? You like it, don't you?
Don't have any appetite?
Is there a problem?
Eh?
You've been acting weird lately...
I'll be a 3rd year soon, right?
It's just school work stressing me out,
that's why I'm like this.
Oh, I see.
A body was discovered in a car,
in a car park in Kanagawa.
Sakagami Kohei was identified as the victim,
aged 41 years and died on the spot.
Apparently, I can't tell mom.
It's better that way.
But if this continues,
the victims will continue to grow.
Actually I want to tell her all about you.
Why?
Only I know what's going on.
I can't just keep quiet, right?
You will be arrested as one of the suspects.
Is there no way?
If you don't do something about your friends soon...
Shinichi, I don't understand your logic.
My kind are just eating.
I'm digesting the nutrients in your blood as food
but the others had to rely on themselves to find food.
But they don't have to eat people...
Shinichi, why are you against eating other humans?
Hah?
Don't you understand?
Human lives are precious.
The most precious thing is one's own life.
For me, that is the most important thing.
That's because you're all just monsters!
For you humans, you eat cows, pigs,
birds, fish and many others.
Whatever plants and animal,
you've eaten them all.
By comparison, isn't eating human beings,
not as awful as you all?
You can't compare it that way...
In short, Shinichi.
If you continue to give me the nutrients to live,
I will fully protect you from anything.
If you're going to harm me,
making you unable to talk will be easy.
Even if I cannot take the rest of the body...
Eh?
Very nice expression.
Demon!
Demon?
Thank you very much.
What's the result?
We saw body parts...
however, it doesn't look like a human being.
Hah?
The owner?
You mean he ate people?
Man-eater...
He was found dead in a position like this.
Detective, what exactly is this?
It makes no sense.
Shinichi, after being called a demon,
turns out humans are what's closest to it.
At the start of this new semester...
many of you will find yourselves
at different points of your goal.
Do not give up, but push yourselves as hard as you can.
That goal can be reached with every little step.
Therefore, for all of you who have come here,
please continue to strive for the best.
Shinichi.
I felt a presence.
One of my kind is near.
You've got to be kidding...
Don't look for it.
It's also searching for us.
There's no way it would take the fight
to a crowd as big as this.
And that's the end of my speech.
So, to substitute Mr. Machiyama due to an accident,
I will be introducing you our new teacher.
Please.
There she is!
For real...?
Don't look!
We'll be spotted!
Tamiya Ryouko.
Nice to meet you all.
Don't be afraid.
Come closer to me.
I can hear your heartbeat pounding from here.
Don't worry.
If a fight takes place here,
we will both be harmed.
Besides,
if there's killing intent in the air,
your right hand would have sensed it.
It's Migi.
Surviving on one of the host's body parts...
it's unimaginable...
I didn't reside here on purpose.
You...
what are you planning to do in this school?
Planning something?
I just want to live normally.
I want to talk more,
but it seems impossible here.
Your girlfriend...
Come look for me after school.
I want to talk directly to you.
Fine.
You don't get to decide.
I don't want to talk with you!
Izumi,
mind your manners when talking to your teacher.
See you later.
Acting like a real teacher...
We have to go.
If she's planning something,
what're we gonna do?
I was surprised to see it,
but although it ate her brain,
she's living like a human.
Maybe it could solve our existing problem.
In addition, she teaches manners to a human.
That really surprised me.
I want to know more!
Taking me to a place like this...
Just what do you want to talk about?
There are two more,
the distance is 10 metres away.
Two!?
What is the meaning of this, Tamiya?
Distance from them, 1 metre.
I can totally see it.
I will introduce them to you.
Shimada Hideo.
Yo.
He's the same as you, a high school kid.
I thought it would be convenient
if you two talked to each other.
The other is an officer...
You don't need to know my name.
In that case,
call him Mr. A.
There's even a police officer...
disturbing.
This is Izumi Shinichi,
and also Migi.
You really took his right hand, huh?
That's interesting.
This is real.
What made you want to take these people
into our Network,
Tamiya Ryouko?
For collecting data.
What's a Network?
I told you to shut it!
To survive,
we need each other's help.
Such as,
finding hidden places to eat everyday.
In order not to look like a homicide.
But lately,
don't you think everything has been reported?
News of the amputee and the man-eating?
So what?
It's because you can't hide what you're doing.
What we are looking for,
are people who will not be missed.
We were all sharing information
in order to learn from each other.
It's very important,
the Network.
Don't tell me...
you want us to join your Network?
But I'm not entirely the same as you.
We are monsters.
I agree.
So I conducted an experiment.
Mr. A and I had sex.
As a result, I'm now pregnant.
So in other words,
what is this something that exists inside me?
Both of you used humans bodies,
therefore a human being was created.
That's right.
What I have inside me is a human child.
So the question arises,
what are we, actually?
We do not have an original body
and just took over someone else's.
How can it be possible?
Just for what purpose
do we exist in this world?
Like I know...
Leaving that aside,
we just want to protect ourselves.
I'm thinking of our future cooperation.
I refuse, ok?
I'm asking Migi.
At least don't disturb us,
or do something like oppose us.
I can kill a whole class within 3 seconds.
Remember, the school is my hostage.
Including your girlfriend.
See you next time.
Shinichi,
beware of A.
I can sense killing intent from him.
It turns out that a menstruating woman tastes awful.
Make sure you finish up the rest!
And keep the place clean for us to eat.
Don't you want to a have a bite?
I'm doing an experiment.
Disgusting. Eating something like that...
it's not good for your body.
Tamiya Ryouko.
Do you really plan on taking that human in as our colleague?
If we can think like how humans think,
Izumi Shinichi and Migi
will make the ideal subjects of research.
You guys,
should be able to also understand this.
Especially you, A.
In order to survive in this human world.
Like me, right?
The newly opened restaurant has really good food.
Should we go there sometime?
Sure.
Don't be shy,
we can think about it occasionally.
I think it's better
if you don't leave the house that often.
Eh?
Because there are many incidents happening outside.
Lately, I haven't been able to talk to you.
No need to worry about little things like that.
See you later.
Wait a minute, Shinichi.
Something must have happened?
Tell me.
Nothing happened!
Don't hide things from your parents.
I know something's happening with you.
I'm not a kid anymore.
Hiding something... it's only natural, right?
Just remember...
that I'm always here to give you a hand.
Stop doing that!
I'm not a kid anymore!
I can take care of myself,
so don't worry.
Hot water or hot oil
causing local tissue damage on skin called a "burn".
Whenever you see your mother's scars,
your blood pressure rises.
I want to know why would a mother do that.
That's got nothing to do with you.
Yes, it has.
Because the nutrients I got was good.
Pan fried tempura.
When I was 4 years old,
I almost got splashed by hot oil on the head.
I turned out fine because mom caught the pot immediately.
Even now,
whenever it rains her scars will itch.
Sacrificing yourself to protect others.
It is something I cannot understand about humans.
As for your painting... it's not someone else.
It's your mom, right?
The distance is 20 meters.
Shinichi, he's here.
It's Mr. A from yesterday.
We should wait for him to pass by.
This killing intent...
he's serious this time.
What do we do now?
He also seems to have good fighting skills.
We best avoid him.
There is a choice of Plan A and Plan B,
which one do you want?
If so,
Plan A then.
So first, we avoid him.
I'll do the talking.
What do you think you're doing?
I'm not the same as Tamiya Ryouko.
What's the point of our kind
fighting each other?
Our kind?
Your kind with whom?
Why don't you let us pass?
During the recent murder case,
I saw his body at police headquarters.
At that time,
we had to find out the cause of that incident.
There is only one thing I know who can kill that way...
and it's parasites alone.
You are dangerous.
Leave the attacks to me.
But our victory will depend on you, Shinichi.
Shinichi!
Hurry!
What is this?
The blood won't stop.
Your body is slowly failing
because of massive hemorrhage.
You will completely bleed out.
Disregarding an attack from a human
was your biggest mistake.
It can't be...
that--
A human...
What's wrong with you?
You haven't taken any damage.
That was a human body.
I've killed a man!
When his brain was taken over,
he was no longer a human.
What's with you!?
Human nature
really is hard to comprehend.
That Plan B... what's that?
There is no such thing.
It was only the option to make it easy.
Huh!?
Welcome.
2 packs of minced meat.
All right.
My son loves eating it.
Oh, I see...
This body can no longer survive.
If there is a new body,
cut...
separate...
merge...
replace...
Cut...
Are you alright?
separate...
merge...
Replace...!
Shinichi, this is bad!
Shinichi!
What the heck?
150 meters.
140 meters.
It's getting closer.
Another one!?
I can't take this anymore!
30 meters.
20 meters.
I can beat it, I can beat it, I can beat it...
10 meters.
What's wrong?
He stopped in front of the house.
Give me a break...!
It can't be...
He's coming in...
How does he have our house key?
This feeling...
Mom?
Shinichi, you're wrong.
It's you, right, mom?
It's A!
What're you talking about?
A is dead, right?
Mom.
Welcome home.
That's A!
You have to realize that, Shinichi!
Stop it, Migi!
He separated from his old body,
and moved to your mother's body!
Don't go saying things like that!
It's the truth, Shinichi!
Too bad...
It turns out that the body I took was your...
Mom, I'm sorry...
C'mon, mom...
stop joking around like that...
Don't, Shinichi!
Your mother is not human anymore!
I told you to shut up, right!?
You're the monster!
Mom...
I'm sorry for hiding it from you.
T-This is just...
I'm just afraid that mom will worry about it,
so I didn't tell you.
I was looking for the right time to talk about it.
It's because I'm weak and afraid,
that's why I didn't want to make you worry.
I always wanted to thank you.
From the beginning,
I really wanted you to know...
That's why...!
Please tell me it's all a joke, mom!
Mom...
Shinichi!
I pierced his heart, so it's over.
You will also die with him.
Because you didn't take the brain of that boy.
You're awake? It's a miracle.
I used a piece of myself to cover up
the hole left in your body.
Then I left a part of me in your heart
that had been destroyed.
Afterwards, I slowly returned back into your right hand.
It was like a risky experiment.
But luckily it turned out well.
You should've just left me to die...
Mom...
Forget it! She's been taken over by A!
You haven't been to school these past few days.
Why, I wonder?
Shinichi?
Are you alright?
Where are you going?
Shinichi!
Stop following me.
Near your house, a policeman's body was found.
It was on the news.
Was that your doing?
Do you know where A is?
You killed him already, right?
That's what we thought at first,
but he had taken over Shinichi's mother.
Shinichi and me were almost killed.
So for those few days,
you were repairing his cells.
Where's A?
I don't know.
Don't lie to me!
He's in your Network, isn't he!?
Even if I do know,
I won't tell you.
So you're hiding your friend?
We all have a personality of our own.
A has a strong personality,
so he's considered dangerous.
If you already knew about that,
then why introduce us to A?
An experiment.
Just an experiment.
Just an experiment?
You did it just for that!?
Brave, aren't we?
If you insist,
then it seems I have no choice.
For a while, I saw...
a change in you.
Interesting...
You two really are interesting.
Wait!
Looks like we'll meet again, Izumi.
I swear I'll find you.
No matter what, I'll find you.
I'll kill you.
Detective.
Huh?
About the fish market police killing,
a residual fingerprint has been found consistent...
...with the iron pipe weapon
and the back door of the restaurant murder.
So the suspect is the same...
About the victim at the scene,
they found human flesh in his stomach.
How can it be possible?
Can't you see?
I'm eating right now.
But you're still looking at these photos, right?
Then, the rumors are true...
that there are unknown
parasitic organisms infecting the body.
Don't rush in with conclusions,
or the top will put the brakes on this investigation.
This station is one we haven't visited yet...
Where are we going?
I don't know.
I just want to walk somewhere today.
What if we accidentally crossed paths with A?
You've got a radar.
That's not an effective way.
If you were to meet A in this state...
What's up?
Someone's within 200 meters.
Is it A?
I have no idea.
But, Shinichi...
It isn't just one or two...
The reason is simple.
Is it in this crowd?
I can't sense it clearly.
I only know they're around here...
Really!?
Shinichi.
What?
In this crowd...
among this crowd...
Reduce the seats of parliamentary members!
Cut off the excess and redundant!
Not just the parliament
In each area we have to separate the wheat from the chaff!
Cut off the excess!
Not A, but...
It's the one on the stand, huh?
This is surprising.
I was shocked by Tamiya Ryouko being a teacher,
and now they have someone in politics.
So they want to create a place where people can be eaten?
To control the town and have a place for them to gather.
There's no mistake.
After a few months,
they will become a highly evolved group.
You're too enthusiatic about all this...
Maybe someday,
the parasites will have full control over the entire world!
Don't talk about it so casually.
As if you monsters can do something like that.
You're underestimating us humans.
Izumi Shinichi, right?
Um, yes.
So... you live alone now?
That's right.
You cook for yourself?
Once in a while, yeah.
What about your future?
My mom still left me a decent amount of savings, so... umm...
Don't worry about it.
Sometime ago,
there was a case where a policeman was killed?
Do you know anything about it?
Not really.
Is that so?
Pardon our intrusion.
Well, thanks for everything.
Migi!
Good morning.
It's been difficult, huh?
I hope you find your mom soon.
What about your meals?
No problem.
If you want,
I can make you some.
It's him...
Good morning.
This is Shimada, our new transfer student.
I'm Shimada Hideo. Nice to meet you.
You can't shake with your right hand?
Why the hell are you here?
C'mon, what are you saying?
There, hope you two become friends.
What's wrong...?
Well then...
What was that?
I'm only testing out his power.
Good morning!
Got into another fight?
No, no, no. It's nothing like that.
Hey, that guy just now.
That was the new transfer student, right?
You do remember, right?
Murano Satomi and the rest of the school are her hostage.
Damn her...
It seems his physical strength has been greatly increased.
Migi's presence must have had
an effect on his body.
Basically, he was not supposed to be like this.
But as I thought...
he is changing...
He really is interesting, huh.
I now understand why you want to study him.
To obtain such an information...
they both play a very important piece.
I'm going out again to find A.
I already told you that when your heart was destroyed,
I used my cells to repair it.
Those parts of me are still alive, it seems.
And they're flowing through your blood.
So can't you take it out?
As my cells are tiny particles,
they're now fused inside your body.
I cannot recall them anymore.
So what you're saying is...?
That my body is starting to become more like you?
I don't want to look like you.
Where are we going anyway?
Today we'll do a little sightseeing.
You're gonna look for A again, right?
It seems not only your body is changing, but so is your personality.
I want you to stop.
You know I can't.
If you do see her,
there's nothing you can do.
The dead won't come back,
so think about your own life.
Moreover...
don't be concerned about my problem.
Your problem?
After saving you,
I now have to sleep for 4 hours each day.
I also sleep for 8 hours.
Unlike you, I can't be woken up when asleep.
It's as if I'm dead during that time.
I also don't know when it'll happen.
That means...
if an enemy appears and you fall asleep...
Good luck on your running away.
What!?
Here it comes!
Eh?
I'm sleepy.
Hey!
Sorry, but I'm going to bed.
Hey, wait a minute! Hey! Hey!
How to identify parasites?
"Once you pull out their hair,
the hair will react by curling."
...that's what it says here.
Oww!
So you're not one of them, huh?
What is the meaning of this?
I told you not to arouse more suspicion.
Looks like they found a way to detect us,
just by pulling out our hair.
That is a problem.
Isn't it because you're often playing
with things that interest you?
You better stop it--
I'm grateful for your concern.
But it's not because of them.
In fact,
those are my precious samples.
If you're going to continue with your experiments,
just be careful with them.
I...
I'm also thinking about the future of our kind.
When I get elected,
I will make you all my subordinates,
and reorganize the system.
Don't you worry.
Tamiya.
How's your baby?
It can already move.
It's body is developing
just like an ordinary human.
Hey, how about I cook you dinner tonight?
I don't mind. Do it then.
It can't be helped then.
I'll make something healthy!
She has a point. Balanced food is
good for your health. Obviously for me, too.
Sorry about the food I ate lately.
And this is also an opportunity to approach her.
You're always talking about it.
Who are you whispering to?
No, it's nothing.
Shinichi, you've been a little scary lately.
Eh?
I can understand it a bit
because of what happened.
I think you really have changed,
not like before when you were a bit shy and wishy-washy.
Because that's what makes you so cute.
What the heck is that...
But now I'm relieved.
Relieved to know that you're still you.
So any comments?
No, no...
Just it seems a bit much...
What is it?
I thought I heard something.
Poor dog...
Watch out!
It's too late.
He's dead.
What are you doing!?
What do you think you're doing?
I'm just throwing away garbage.
That's not garbage!
Don't you pity it?
But it's already dead.
Since it's dead,
it's not a dog anymore.
Now it's just flesh and bones.
You...
you're Shinichi, right?
What's wrong?
Sorry.
Looks like I got the wrong person.
Hey, Migi...
Did I say something wrong?
You said that body is
just made up of flesh and bones.
That's something I would be saying.
I see...
She really hates me now, huh...
Umm, Ms. Tamiya...
Yes? What can I do for you?
I was just wondering...
You're pregnant, right?
Is there a problem with it?
Well...
we can't talk here in public, so...
Can you come to the principal's office?
Ah. So you're home.
Sorry for barging in.
Welcome home.
It surprised us
when you suddenly quit teaching.
So it's true...
We got the news from school.
Father.
Hmm?
It's not her.
She's not Ryouko.
She's not Ryouko!
What are you saying?
Father, call the police.
Call the police immediately!
Hey, are you okay?
Father!
It's me.
There're two bodies for you to eat.
Leaving school already?
I knew this would happen sooner or later.
What about Shimada Hideo?
He will continue to watch over you.
And besides,
he's going to be fine in this environment.
What do you mean?
Like me, he rarely eats human meat.
Even Shimada?
Right now, there seems to be a problem.
If we learn not to eat humans,
the problem will be solved, right?
It is possible.
So even Shimada, too...
Like you said, if you can adapt to this world,
then there won't be a problem anymore.
Wait a minute.
Didn't he also take over the body of someone else?
And even so,
I still can't believe anything you'll say.
Yo.
I asked him to be our model.
Satomi, want to join us?
Ah, no, I'm fine.
Hey.
Hmm?
Is your relationship with Shinichi doing okay?
Huh?
I-I don't know what you're trying to say.
So, on to the next pose.
In that case...
Put your hand over here.
Now then,
face over here...
Perfect.
Honestly, your style is something...
Like you're not human.
Just kidding.
Why did you have to do that?
I was even kind to you.
1, 2, 3...
4, 5, 6...
7...
8 people.
Did you hear that?
I can sense Shimada Hideo's killing intent!
Even here in school!?
Where is Shimada!?
We shouldn't approach him!
As if I would listen to that!
I promise you.
I will make it painless.
So please remain silent.
Everybody, run!
C'mon! Make it quick!
Where did that scream came from!?
It definitely came from the Art Room.
I can also sense Shimada's killing intent.
Don't go near him. Don't go near him!
Shinichi!
Move! Out of the way!
Calm down, Shinichi!
I-I can't-- I can't--
You've got to calm down!
M-My...
my classmates...
It's alright, Shinichi.
Your heart won't get destroyed again.
Everything's alright.
You will be... alright.
He's lost control of himself.
Let's take him down.
One more incoming...!
Tamiya...
Shimada Hideo.
You look horrible.
I-I-I can't return to my original form anymore.
Help me...
I hate comrades who drag me down.
Shinichi, run!
We're going!
Everything's alright, Satomi!
Did he go west?
We've just past the stairs.
Surveillance is continuing.
Be careful. Roger.
Hey...
Hey!
You!
Shinichi, this may surprise you.
But I can still sense Shimada's killing intent!
He's heading to the roof.
It looks impossible... for an ordinary human.
See yah...
Shimada.
Shinichi, someone's here.
I'll disappear for a while.
Why come just to say that?
I've killed 13 people.
I should've killed you and Shimada from the start.
If you kill me,
you'll also kill the child inside me.
Can you kill a human child?
Tamiya Ryouko.
What are you going to do
with that human child?
I'll also
be using him for my experiments.
Don't you dare...!
Izumi Shinichi.
Mothers are
quite a strange breed of human beings?
To become a mother...
I have to see it through for myself.
Where does their strength come from?
I want to know.
This...
is where you'll find A.
Is it here?
Yeah.
Don't be reckless.
I know!
Don't slice up her body.
It's still my mom's body, after all.
We'll aim for the head.
Got it, Migi?
Shinichi.
Something serious is about to happen.
We have to retreat.
Huh? What are you saying?
I feel sleepy.
What!?
I can't bear this sleepy feeling.
Why now of all times!?
I don't have a say in this.
Let's retreat.
C'mon! It's right in front of us!
Then good luck.
Hey, Migi!
The only thing I could do, at least...
is this...
You can't be serious...!
How did you survive?
Doesn't matter...
Humans can't move that fast.
What happened?
Mom, I'm coming for you now.
Please stop, Shinichi.
Why are you doing this?
It's me, your mom...
Mom...
Looks like you've succeeded.
In the end...
mom saved me again.
I see.
Even so, Migi...
It seems I...
may really be just like you.
When mom was taken away...
even now...
I can't...
even cry.
Hooray! Hooray! Hooray!
(Hirokawa Takeshi, elected)
Even though the road to victory
may have seem long
We thank everyone
for working hard to support us.
Thank you very much!
Why have we been called to HQ?
I have no idea...
Chief!
May we be of some assistance?
I'm Detective Hirama...
And I'm Detective Tsuji .
Please provide all the information
that has been gathered.
Sign here.
This is a letter of confidentiality.
The title for this operation is,
"Human Life Protection".
You are...?
I apologize. I'm one of the special forces.
I'm Yamagishi.
Special forces?
The SAT, sir?
If the number of humans could be reduced by half...
If the number of forests is burnt by half...
If the number of human beings is reduced to a hundred...
Could existing waste...
become one in a hundred as well?
Watching it again, I see.
You really love that, don't you?
Someone in the world definitely thinks so...
if you want to save the lives of others.
That may be true.
Isn't that right... Gotou?
We didn't know how to talk before,
but now we do.
We didn't know how to move before,
All living things
follow some kind of command.
Command?
When I took this brain,
I got a command.
What is it?
To kill...
mankind.
Migi.
What?
I know now.
The one thing I should be doing.
The thing that you should do?
I don't care who or what they are.
I just need to find all these parasites,
then kill them one by one.
That's what I should do.
If we are born to destroy mankind,
then you are their only hope.
I'm going to kill their leader's child!
I'm really grateful for failing to take your brain.
Deceitful humans, look at this world.
Aren't you all the ones destroying everything!?
Everyone in this world forgets...
If the lives of people are protected...
Shinichi is human.
I have to find them!
So, run!
Migi!
Someone needs to stop Clearway Law.
Public shouldn't leave reviews for lawyers.