Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org
The situation on the
ground is ongoing
while the entire disputed area remains
closed to news organizations.
As last night's report of a
series of large explosions
awaits official confirmation, widespread
fear of a biological weapons launch
continues to spread
throughout the region.
Justine, what are you
seeing in the capital?
The Foreign Ministry remains
shuttered for a second day
as evidence mounts that the
insurgents may have used
at least some part of their long-rumored
biological weapons stockpile
in the course of last
night's incursion.
Have you been able to get any
word yet on the government's response?
Well, it's hard to find any officials
here at all in the capital, Mark.
But those who are willing
to speak off the record
confirm the regime's plan for a massive
retaliation in the next five to seven days.
Well, while we are trying
to restore that image,
ITL News has just obtained amateur
video footage purporting to show
casualties from last night's
exchange of missile fire.
A warning... this footage contains images
that may be disturbing to some viewers.
Obtained from a junior military officer
fleeing the site of last night's clashes,
it seems to belie assurances
from both sides of the conflict
- that no chemical or biological weapons...
- Damn it.
Have been deployed.
Such images are horrifying enough, but
there's an even more horrific scenario
if the contagion spreads beyond the
region, potentially infecting tens...
if not hundreds of thousands.
- They're saying...
- Look, I'm...
if you want, I'm just gonna
go to the guitar shop.
The pickup fried out, so...
They can't just keep
fighting, right?
We are now going
live to a press conference
at the Centers for Disease Control.
As of 8:00 a.m. Eastern Standard
Time, the CDC has not measured
any airborne contaminants
beyond a 100-mile radius
of last night's advance
in the Middle East.
What this... what this means is the
continental United States has not
and will not be affected by the
reported use of these pathogens.
Steven, the
situation in the larger cities
near the epicenter of the conflict remains
tense as persistent rumors of mass deaths
in scores of towns and
villages gain credibility.
At least three regional governments
have begun issuing gas masks...
Rumors abound in the capital
as the prime minister and his
cabinet depart the city...
This is simply a precaution
in order for us to maintain
government function...
Meanwhile,
a veritable exodus of refugees
continues to stream
across regional borders,
desperately seeking safety from a threat that
remains, perhaps intentionally, undefined.
In Washington, the
president has issued a statement
urging calm and affirming that no
known pathogen poses any threat...
The trade winds
are spreading the pathogen
well beyond the conflict's borders,
confirming officials' worst
fears about the airborne virus.
Reports of mass casualties as far north as
Italy and Portugal are pending confirmation.
What we're
apparently seeing here is a virus,
or a complex of viruses, killing
some almost immediately,
while leaving others fully mobile.
However, within hours, nobody in
the affected area remains alive.
Stay tuned, please, for further
developments on this breaking news story.
That pickup's all right.
But when I move around...
it doesn't have that punch
and it's just fading out a lot.
- Don't worry...
- All right, so...
Okay, cool. Thanks, man.
He says it's gonna
be, like, an hour.
There's something...
- I am so hungry.
- Oh.
I don't even know why
we're fighting this thing.
- It was the fucking dishes.
- Yes!
You guys have maids, you know?
So it's not like you see a
dirty dish and you're like,
"Hey, here's a dirty dish. I've
got to do something about it.
I'm gonna wash this dirty dish."
- You're...
- What are you... I mean...
You're totally fixated on this.
It's not the dish. I'm not even
talking about the dish anymore.
It's a metaphor.
- Yeah, it's a metaphor...
- I know what you're gonna say.
- No, you don't.
- The dish is a metaphor
for my anxiety about
how different we are.
What?
- You did know.
- Well, of course I knew.
- So, fuck it.
- Just wash the dish.
Just metaphor the metaphor.
Just address my anxieties
with dishwashing liquid.
We'd miss this if we ever lost it.
We'd be like, "I wish
we could go back
to when the worst thing we had
to worry about was the dishes."
Hey.
Oh, my God. You guys,
congratulations!
Let me see. Oh, my God.
That is so adorable.
So what's going on with
this shit in the news?
- Honestly, I'm not watching it.
- Don't know, right?
- Nothing's changed.
- I am going to go to the bathroom.
Oh.
Ahem.
Although state
and county authorities
have been almost unanimous in
urging residents to remain calm,
a spreading, seemingly spontaneous
exodus along the Eastern Seaboard
has caused state highway
patrol officials
to shut down six major northbound
arteries, piecing together...
Traffic's insane out there.
Did you guys eat my food?
I got you this.
Anna, why have you been
so freaked out lately?
So, what, I'm not allowed to talk
to any girl I've ever slept with?
Are you gonna go crazy? Is that it?
No, it's the exact opposite.
I think you should talk to
all the people you want to...
any girl you've ever met,
whenever they call,
whenever they stop by,
whenever you bump into them.
Yeah, I think you should take as many
opportunities as possible to talk to them.
Jesus, Anna.
Because, God, there is so
much time, isn't there?
There is so much time between
all the dishes lying around,
the fucked-up amps,
the fried-out pickups,
your rich grandparents...
and your boring,
stupid ex-girlfriends
coming to the "Gates
of fucking India"?
You know?
Because between all that,
there's so much time for...
laying in the bathtub...
and reading the soap bottle...
and looking out together,
up at the leaves...
and holding each other,
because we're both so happy
that we're actually scared.
Because if it really is all over...
Erik, if it was just us,
and there really was
nothing left on Earth...
What are you doing?
No, Anna, Anna,
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
That's the song.
That... that is the song.
Those are the lyrics to our song.
That's it.
It's gonna be beautiful.
No one is willing to
confirm or deny what we're seeing here.
It clearly isn't benign.
Even at this distance, David,
I've got to admit, I'm scared.
We're getting
unconfirmed reports of rioting
at dozens of airports as all domestic and
international flights remain grounded.
Hundreds of
thousands of people are now running
through the streets here
seeking any kind of shelter.
The president and
his cabinet have been evacuated
to an undisclosed location while
assuring local authorities...
as yet
another American city reports
an almost unbelievable
casualty rate...
I, the Lord, have held
My peace a long time...
Just in the last
several minutes, it's really...
Oh, my God! Oh, my God!
We are no longer receiving reports
from the following cities
and municipalities...
Boston and the Boston
metropolitan area,
- Bridgeport and the...
- Philadelphia...
- Baltimore...
- "Then the fifth angel
poured out his bowel
on the throne of the beast,
and His kingdom became
full of darkness
and they gnawed their tongues
because of the pain..."
- Jesus Christ!
- Oh, my God.
- "They shall become refuse on the ground."
The following is a bulletin from
the Emergency Management Agency.
If concentrations in your area have
exceeded 80 parts per billion,
you must take immediate shelter and remain
where you are for a minimum of eight days.
State authorities will continue
to broadcast hourly updates
as long as emergency networks
remain operational.
What does that even mean,
"parts per billion"?
Per billion what?
Per billion of whatever else
was out there, I guess.
It's a beautiful day.
Not a cloud in the sky.
We could read something.
Sure.
Remember this?
Oh, that.
That was a moment of weakness.
Well, at least we're not
going to get divorced now.
It's so clear out, baby.
The birds up there, they're
just flying around.
It's too bad we aren't birds.
I wonder what they're feeling.
Like their favorite
TV show got canceled.
I could talk to you
for another 20 years.
Aw, shut up.
I mean it. I was just
thinking it the other day.
I just realized that...
that you're my wife.
It took me practically till
just now to really believe it.
We're going to have
to go to Children's.
What?
There are no more canisters here.
We're going to have to go
to Children's Hospital.
Okay.
- Oh, my God.
- Don't look.
Oh, God. That looks like...
that sweet nurse in Cardiology.
Sarah. Her name was Sarah.
Sarah.
Sarah? Sarah. Sarah.
- Mr. Sachs, I...
- Wait a minute.
Look, I know you're busy, but
I need a favor from you.
It's for my wife. She's in there
waiting to see Dr. Henderson.
They took her off life support.
They took her out of ICU.
We're just waiting, Sarah.
Well, we have an emergency...
Well, this is an emergency!
You understand?!
This is an emergency,
Sarah! She's dying!
And the doctor's just taken
a three-hour coffee break.
- Mr. Sachs...
- I'm sorry.
I know you're a good person.
Esther and I really think of you
as someone close to us,
like you're really family.
Please, I'm begging you.
Just come with me.
Help me. Help me get her
to ICU. Come on.
I'm not sure I'm going to be able to do
that. We have an emergency... Mr. Sachs?
Mr. Sachs!
Jacob! Get me an oxygen unit.
- Jacob, get me an oxygen unit, now.
- Yes, right.
Mr. Sachs? Lift your
head up for me.
Try to breathe normally.
- Okay?
- Yeah.
- I've gotta go.
- Wait, wait.
Listen to me.
It's a biological attack.
- Isn't it?
- They don't know.
People can't breathe...
old people...
kids...
animals are okay.
We only have about three hours...
It has to do with how much
material is in the air.
And winds and...
if it gets up to more than
35 parts per billion,
you're going to need one of
these to survive, Sarah.
Now listen to me. Listen.
You got to get one.
Not a charcoal filter. Pure oxygen.
You'll be able to last
eight days. Okay?
Thank you. Thank you very much.
Good luck.
Nurse!
I have to go!
"Connect me to something.
Give me something,"
I said. You know?
"Give me something, Counsel.
Give me something that connects
my client eating baba ghanoush
at some streetside cafe
somewhere in...
do we even know where
this was taken, Tracy?"
And then Tracy said...
And then I said, "No, the prosecution
just gave us Exhibit 345,
defendants Hightower,
Esselen, and Sachs
and 'unidentified man.' 1979."
"So, please. Help me out here,"
I said, looking sort of baffled.
"Give me whatever it is you're hanging your
case on so that I can defend my client.
But don't keep giving me
exhibit after exhibit,
so-called 'fact' after
so-called 'fact'
that doesn't add up
to A... trade secrets,
B... any of your employees actually
compromising your trade secrets, or C...
any material damages done to your
company's overseas interests,
because if opposing
counsel doesn't or can't,
or for whatever
reason, they won't...
Your Honor, I respectfully request
that you dismiss the
case against my client."
And the judge dismissed it.
You guys? We're...
we're evacuating the building.
The news, then a proliferation
of rumors and hearsay, and then
almost street by street...
Hey, man. Leave a message
and I'll get back to you.
Hey, man. I'm leaving
a message, dude.
Did you... if you're watching TV,
there's a...
anyway, turn on the TV.
It has something to
do with the war.
We're supposed to...
conflicting reports
of trade winds...
So, um...
meet me back at the house.
And...
please change your outgoing
message, though, baby.
Seriously.
But efforts to keep citizens calm
and encourage them to
maintain their normal...
I'm gonna take you
left, then right...
- Ah!
- Busted!
Surprise myself!
Ah! Take it back right here.
And then I'm gonna score again.
Perfect defense.
Oh, yeah! That's game, baby!
- No, no, no.
- That's game.
No.
Okay, so here's the deal.
If I sink this, right here,
you let me pay you back.
You don't owe me anything, man.
You see, that's exactly the kind of talk
that won't be allowed if I make this shot.
What happens if you miss?
Uh...
You know, this is really gonna
determine my inner morality.
If I miss, then you never
have to hear about it again.
How's that? Okay?
Borrowed your Jeep, fucked up
the transmission, we're square.
But if I make it, you
accept the cash.
All right, I'll trust
your subconscious.
You hear that, Rick's subconscious?
You don't really want him
to make this shot, do ya?
Make him miss.
You're just... you're
gonna stand right there?
You never said anything
about where I could stand.
- Okay. Okay.
- Oh, I'm sorry.
It doesn't really matter.
That doesn't bother me.
- 'Cause you know why?
- Why?
'Cause I got it like that.
I give up.
Nice work on the Sachs case.
Thanks.
Where are you going?
Home.
That's it?
That's it.
Whatever.
Let's not end this on a bad note.
You're a wonderful guy,
and who knows what
would have happened
if we had met before.
But it was never a question.
There was in my mind.
I'm sorry.
It's the end of the world.
If it really is the end of the
world, how funny, you know?
For once, it really would
be when it feels that way.
How romantic.
Anyway, turn on the TV.
It has something to do
with the war.
Meet me back at the house
and please change your outgoing
message, though, baby.
- Come on, come on. Let's go.
- Seriously.
I'm starting to tighten
up a little bit.
Let's go.
What?
She told me to turn on the TV.
- She wants me
to meet her at home. - Now?
Yeah.
- So you're...?
- Sorry, man.
You know what, man?
You are so fuckin' whipped.
Hey, I canceled a lot of shit for
this so we can just hang out.
Yeah? Like what?
Coffee at Saga?
Tarot card reading?
- Yeah.
- I'll see you on Thursday.
- You gotta be kiddin' me.
- I'll see you Thursday, man.
Yeah, fuck you, motherfucker.
- Thursday.
- If you're lucky.
God damn it.
Hey.
I finished the song.
I have an idea.
Why don't we take a nap, just
forget about everything?
Listen to this.
"The souls of all my dears
have flown to the stars.
Thank God there's no one
left for me to lose."
Hm.
You know what your
grandmother said to me?
Mm.
She said...
that "the only important language
spoken in the world
is spoken between
a man and a woman.
In bed."
I don't know. Maybe you
want to watch the news?
- Nuh-uh.
- Or write some more poetry?
No.
You know what? We should probably
get up and do the dishes.
No, I don't think so.
And so, finally...
eight years later or whatever...
at some New Year's Eve party,
Grandpa finally got up the
courage and he kissed her.
At least, that's how my
mom used to tell it.
They're gonna love you. Seriously.
Don't worry about it.
I'm not worried, baby.
- Hello!
- Hi!
I'm so glad to meet you.
I'm so happy to meet you, too.
Yes! Goodness! Ooh!
Someone did very well.
This is a beautiful ring.
- That's right.
- He did very great.
How are you, sweetheart?
Men are so much like
kids, it's silly.
I mean, there's the guitar
and there's the garden
and there's basketball
and football...
it's a wonder they have any time
at all to devote themselves
to other responsibilities
for family.
But they do. They do.
- Yeah.
- Bless 'em.
You know.
I'm gonna have to
sit down, I think.
- I just got a little pooped.
- Yeah, sure.
What you've gotta watch, of course,
is when you breed something
more and more specialized,
it can only survive
under very narrow
and specific conditions.
Here.
Thank you.
- Got something for you.
- No, Grandpa, I'm fine.
- No, no, no.
- I'm fine.
No, no, you can't refuse me.
You just can't. I'm not gonna
take no for an answer,
- so you might as well just stop.
- Okay.
And I wanna tell you something...
man to man, okay?
No matter how much
a woman may tell you
that she's happy to support you,
that she's not interested
in material things,
she wants you to be free...
sooner or later, they all
want the good things in life.
- I know, I know. But Anna isn't like that.
- Well, I'm sure she's not.
I'm not telling you
that she's shallow.
Probably is the most natural,
basic instinct in a woman...
actually, any human being...
make a home,
make a nest.
You know, I'm playing
a show at this thing.
It's called "South by Southwest."
And you know there's a lot of...
record company people,
and managers go.
That's wonderful.
- I can make a living playing music.
- I'm sure you can.
And I'm sure you'll figure it out.
Don't let anybody
pressure you, huh?
Just take your time.
If there's anything ever
I can do to help you,
you know I'm here.
So funny... I was just
thinking this morning
that, God, I have turned
into such a typical "girl."
I never thought
it would happen to me,
but I... oh, God...
I am completely obsessed with him.
Beyond obsessed with him.
I mean, even when
I'm angry or jealous
or, I don't know...
maybe that's the same thing...
but he leaves for an hour
and I can't stand it.
I don't know
what to do with myself.
I feel kind of crazy and...
that can't be healthy.
Well, I'm not sure it's healthy,
but it is the way it is.
- Yeah.
- Yeah?
And I'll tell you something else.
You'd be someplace at a party
or a friend's house or something...
and he'll be over there
talking to somebody.
And you see his face.
And you think,
"He and I are going to make
some beautiful babies."
- Cheers.
You know what? I don't
think I can take this.
No, no. I told you I'm not
taking no for an answer.
- No, Grandpa, I can't.
- Oh, Erik, come on. I got it, you need it.
- What's the difference?
- I always appreciate...
I am not taking it back.
That's final.
- I'm sorry.
- Idiot.
You're too good for my dirty money?
You think there wouldn't be such a
thing as war if it wasn't for me?
I got news for you, kid. There
are worse sinners on this earth
- than your grandfather.
- No, no, no. I don't...
Wait till you have a child!
Wait till you have a sick child!
Then you'll lecture me.
And if you have any trouble
at all remembering
or if you aren't sure
of your answer,
just say, "I don't remember,"
or, "I don't have
any specific recollection."
Now, that last one actually
covers quite a lot.
If, for instance, you "sort of"
think you might remember something,
but it's possible that you
aren't remembering it clearly,
it's never perjury to say, "I don't
have any specific recollection."
They were developing a pathogen.
I know, Mr. Sachs.
But the prosecution won't be
asking about that tonight.
It wasn't even my division.
I offered advice to my clients
on pharmaceutical lines.
Okay.
We have about 15 minutes
until opening statements.
They just offered me so much money.
So much. Millions.
Okay. Mr. Sachs, look at me.
This trial is not about
how certain governments
got a hold of certain weapons
or formulas for weapons
over 30 years ago.
This trial deals with
the very narrow issue
of whether or not
you violated your contract
with Sichel Systems
by revealing trade secrets,
and you didn't do that.
You didn't break the
terms of your contract.
You're innocent.
Have you had a child?
- No.
- You can't watch them die.
She lived another 15 years
and she gave us our grandson, Erik.
But the prosecution doesn't
need to know that, do they?
I took it.
I took the money.
I knew it was wrong, but I took it.
My wife is living in denial,
but I know it's my fault.
I deserve to be punished.
We really need to leave, Mr. Sachs.
Oh, my God.
Oh... it's too far.
We'll get there, we'll get there.
Hold on. If we can find some
more canisters up there,
it's gonna get us
eight days of air,
and the poison will be gone.
To think I was so scared
about having that operation.
And Dr. Henderson died...
Esther, if you're
going to go through
all the ironies of the situation,
we're going to be talking another
20 years. You know that?
I won't say a word. I don't
ever want to say anything.
What? What did you say?
Excuse me?
You don't want to say anything?
Huh? You don't wanna
say anything...
about my pants?
Something about my pants?
They're too high.
Okay, here we go.
Have you been looking for a job?
Yeah, I've been looking for a job.
I print out another
175,000 resumes,
I change my profile on
another million job sites.
- I mean, the thing is...
- I even call Human Resources.
I swear to God, I feel like
"Willy Loman." I said...
"If anything comes
up, do me a favor.
Keep my number. Give me a call."
I mean, you were
getting plenty of work
when you were putting
her through law school.
Yeah. People used to hire writers.
You can get any job you want.
Yeah. One more job.
Pay some bills.
Buy some stuff, get another job,
pay some more bills,
buy some more stuff...
Yeah, but it's that or what?
Play basketball
with your buddies all day
and let Mia buy your shirts?
You know what's interesting
to me, is that why...
instead of printing
a bunch of resumes,
why we all don't just stop
in the middle of
the street and say...
"What the hell is going on here?
What is this all about?"
I mean, why am I here on
this earth, you know?
- Oh, Len...
- No, I mean it. I mean it.
Why does the universe
expand for eternity?
Wh-why...
how much longer am I gonna live?
Why am I the only animal
that knows it's gonna die?
We all asked ourselves
those questions
when we were, like, eight.
Yeah, but why did we
stop asking, you know?
'Cause I never got any answers.
Is this about the war?
This is about what I'm supposed
to be doing with my life.
I just don't know what I'm
supposed to tell Dad.
Oh, God, Sarah. Tell him I'm happy.
I mean, you tell me...
X-ray vision...
am I horribly depressed?
You know what I just
realized the other day?
We're at some party at Mia's office
and we'd just gotten
in some stupid fight
and we're outside
in the parking lot.
And I just realized that...
she's my wife.
And I love her.
I mean, I really love her.
She married me...
so I can't really be
that depressed, can I?
God.
I hope I meet someone
like you someday.
- Except with a job.
Come on.
Come on!
Fuck.
Shit.
Mia? Sarah, what the
fuck is going on?
Listen... they're not telling
the whole story on the news.
Well, I haven't seen the news.
What's going on?
Just ignore what
everybody's saying.
You have to get back to the house.
Get out your dehumidifiers
and ionizers...
anything you have that filters air...
and seal yourself into the basement.
What... what is it?
Is this the war?
Just listen. Remember how we put
Mom's oxygen tanks up in the attic?
Yeah. I got rid of those
months ago, Sarah.
Damn.
Well, just stay down there
as long as you can.
I'm starting to freak
out here, Sarah.
What's going on?
How do you know all this?
Because I... I met someone
who knows about this,
- and I...
- Hey, Sarah?
Sarah, listen to me, okay?
What the fuck? Hold on a second.
I gotta give you a call back,
okay? I'm gonna call you back.
Stay safe.
Attention, please.
There has been an emergency
reported in the building.
Leave the building immediately
using marked stairways and exits.
Do not use elevators.
Hey, buddy.
Do you know where your
mommy and daddy are?
You okay?
Using marked stairways and exits.
Do not use elevators.
Attention, please.
There has been an emergency
reported in the building.
Leave the building immediately
using marked stairways...
It hurts.
What hurts?
My tummy.
Where does it hurt? Hmm?
It...
Okay, okay, buddy. Okay.
Uh...
we're gonna...
What the fuck are you doing?
- Hey...
- Get the fuck away from my boy!
Hey, man, it's okay.
Your kid is not doing...
hey, whoa!
Hey, hey... hey, listen!
Jesus Christ! Hey, listen, man!
- Listen!
- Fuck you...
- Daddy!
- Damn it! Listen!
Listen!
Jesus Christ, man! Stop!
Listen to me.
Take care of your son!
Hey, do you have any Goldfish?
- Um...
- Yes, Goldfish.
Maybe up there.
Thanks.
Uh...?
Wow.
Do you think that they
stuffed everything up
like that for the party?
No, I think that is just how
they keep their things.
- You know what's weird about that?
- What?
Oh, shh... Oreos.
- Look at this.
- Mmm.
- Mmm, mmm.
Yummy, yummy.
What's...
- What's weird?
- Huh?
- What's weird about it?
- What's weird, what's weird.
- You said...
- It was...
I don't know. It's just weird...
ever since we got engaged,
there's suddenly like all these...
I don't know, these
waves that we...
No. I know exactly what you mean.
There's, like, a right way and a wrong way
of doing everything, and we're, like...
You know why? It's 'cause we're, like,
we are like, the Anna and Erik tribe.
You know? And I mean there's
something terribly wrong
about putting the... look, the
cat food next to the tea.
Yeah, but probably the
way we stack things
and put things together really neatly
seems completely insane and constricting.
- Right?
- Yeah, yeah.
I mean it already feels so wrong to do
it any other way than the way we do it.
Right, but that is how
it begins, you know?
That is why countries
invade each other...
'cause of that.
"You don't put the tea
in the right place."
Yeah? Fuck you! Fuck you,
you're the bad guys.
You have no idea how to
do it, and we're better.
"You know what? The green
tea goes on the top shelf
next to the cocoa, fuckwad,
or I'm gonna kill you."
The beginning of civilization.
I'm sorry. I have got to move this.
- No, I mean, it so doesn't belong there.
- There is something immoral about it.
- We'd be hypocrites if we fail that.
- Future generations will thank us.
The products of this apartment
will cry out for liberation.
It will be a beacon of proper shelf
arrangement for the entire region.
Oh, my God. So good.
I can't find the Goldfish.
He was up there. God.
I hear you.
Hi.
- Was I talking to myself?
- No.
I've been feeling so weird
these past few days.
You know...
I see stuff.
Out of the corner
of my eye sometimes.
I don't even tell my boyfriend...
my fiancé.
And these past few days, I...
I mean literally,
last night, for a second,
it was like there was
nobody left anywhere...
except animals.
Running down the middle
of the street.
God, and Erik was like,
"What?
What are you staring at?"
You didn't say?
They say schizophrenia starts
when you're, like,
19 to 25.
You hear voices?
Well, I just heard a bunch of crows
screaming "War! War!"
Well, they aren't telling you
to jump off any
high buildings, right?
No.
Good.
My name is Rick.
I'm Anna.
I've considered
the high building option.
But life is so absurdly
short, anyway.
Yeah, I've been thinking that.
Makes you only want to do
the important things.
But what are the important things?
I'm pregnant.
First time I've told anybody.
- Greyhound.
- You got it.
Vodka and grapefruit.
Here you go.
Thank you.
You don't know what a Greyhound is?
Hey, who got us this job?
So, anyway, all I'm saying
is marriage is just
all of these artificial
restrictions.
It's like going on
some radical diet
when you're not even fat.
All I'm saying is, yes,
agreed, congratulations
Anna is hot. She's incredibly hot.
And, granted, you're probably
not going to meet anybody
who's that hot and whatever cool
and interesting and wonderful.
I don't know
what you're talking about.
You're making a scene.
Well, what is he looking at, then?
Right now he's looking at you.
Having dragged me across
the room and yelling at me
- in front of all my coworkers...
- I'm not yelling at you.
Can I get a vodka and tonic?
Brilliant, that's exactly right.
- Yeah.
- Fucking more alcohol
because that's really
going to help.
Thank you.
See? He probably
thought he was marrying
the most magical,
beautiful girl on earth.
It's up to you, man.
I'm just saying
you could be dealing
with that kind of shit
for the rest of your life.
Or I could spend the rest
of my life saying,
"I met the one true love of my life
when I was 22 years old
and I was too scared
- to ask her to marry me."
- If she is the one true love of your life.
I mean, there are
billions of people.
No, she's...
she's the one true love of my life.
Okay.
So you have the rest of your
life to ask her to marry you.
Fuck.
It happens every time.
I get dressed up to come to a thing
like this, and it's a fucking disaster.
Len,
none of these people matter to me.
None of these people mean
anything to me except you.
Let's get out of here.
Ah, fuck.
Oh, God I need water.
Water.
Done.
What's this?
I got it at the museum.
It's a trilobite.
It's probably like
300 million years old.
And now they just give them
away with a $50 membership.
There used to be billions of 'em.
They must have had a lot of sex.
They couldn't help themselves.
They were in love.
Or it was just instinct.
Same thing, I guess.
I'd have babies with you.
I mean, not right away, but...
we should, you know?
What?
I never said never.
I said, "Don't marry me if
you want to have children."
But you would?
I could.
Yeah, I would.
We should.
- Right?
- Right.
Think of how beautiful it would be.
"It"? She. She.
Okay. We will.
You promise?
Not right away.
But someday.
Promise.
Mia?!
There you go.
It's okay.
Come here.
So we need to...
I need you to get everything
out of the kitchen
that you can, okay? I need you to
just get everything that you can.
Okay? I'm going to go upstairs
and get some blankets. Okay?
Gonna bring it down
to the basement.
Okay? Yeah?
Sure.
Okay.
The following message is transmitted at the
request of the United States government.
This is not a test. All
residents of the United States
are strongly encouraged
to establish...
Gonna need some more tape.
We've gotta seal all the windows up
here, we've gotta seal the door.
Does creme soda count as water?
What?
- Come on, sweetheart.
- I'll just get that, okay?
Let's get everything downstairs.
It's all diet food.
It's all fucking...
low carb crap.
All of it.
It's okay, sweetheart.
Hey, look...
I have a chocolate bar
in my pocket, okay?
With almonds, okay?
Go back downstairs.
Okay?
- Come on, sweetie.
- Okay, okay, okay.
I got it.
Do you need this tape?
- Nope.
- Okay.
Did you call Sarah?
Mm-hmm.
You okay down there, sweetheart?
Ooh.
Andy, it's...
it's time to stop.
I thought you didn't
want to talk anymore.
I just don't want to sit here
watching you kill yourself.
We'll get there.
You see? If we can
just make it up there,
we're gonna find some more
canisters, I know it.
Stop that, Esther.
Stop it, come on.
Take your hand...
Take your hand off the wheel.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, but look.
I've gotta...
we can't afford the energy it takes
to fight like this.
I wish... I wish you would put
more energy into finding solutions.
There are no solutions, honey.
The news broadcasts
have stopped, and...
everybody that we love is dead.
Listen to me.
Everyone I love is not dead.
The only person
on earth that I love
is still alive.
Oh, you're such a charmer.
You could charm the
knickers off of any girl.
Well, there's no girls
left but my girl.
Okay.
Here we go.
I can't stand how much
I miss you when I'm gone.
I know.
Oh... so, I got a new book
that I really want to read to you.
Okay.
Wait, I don't know
which one to read to you.
Wow, that song is really good.
Yeah, you know, I...
Let me just read you one.
What... you don't have to stop.
I know, I know.
I mean, I just, I just...
I just wanted to
show you something.
In the park. I want your opinion
on something that they're
building across the river.
Uh, what, before we go home?
Yeah, yeah.
It's just been bugging me.
I pass it every day on my run,
you know.
Right.
So do you want to look at it?
Uh, sure.
You don't want to hear this?
No, no. Read it to
me, read it to me.
Ahem.
"At the red towers of
your native Sodom,
the square where once you sang,
the spinning shed, at the empty
windows set into the house,
where sons and daughters
blessed your marriage bed.
A single glance, a
sudden dart of pain
stitching her eyes
before she made a sound.
Her body flaked into
transparent salt.
Her swift legs rooted
to the ground."
Right?
That's... that's incredible.
- You're so distracted.
- No, I'm not. I liked it.
No, you have no idea
what I just read to you.
Not no idea. Come on.
Hey. "Dilute."
"Dilute. Dilute!"
Dilute. Okay.
Come on. Let's go see
your weird-ass building.
Okay. Uh...
this looks right.
See that...
that big red building with
the arches? It's that.
- Oh.
- Right next to it with the...
The water tower, just
right under that,
there's like this cluster
of red buildings.
That red garage-looking thing?
- Yeah.
- I can't really see it.
- Is it next to the...
- Yeah.
What am I looking at?
Hey!
I have to give this to you now.
Oh, my God.
What does that mean?
What does that...
is that a "yes"?
You have to say yes
if you're gonna...
You still need to say "yes."
I love you.
I love you so much.
Say yes. You need to say yes.
Please.
Look at you.
You love me...
Well, what do you
think of our news?
- What news?
- Our news.
Erik and Anna.
Oh, that's fine.
Oh, honey. You don't
dislike Anna, do you?
I think she's wonderful
and I just love her.
I'm just so happy about this.
I like her fine.
You know I offered him some
money and he wouldn't take it?
Oh, well, he's getting married.
You know, he's going to
be the big macho man now.
Head of the family. He'll probably
never take money from us again.
Well, I bet if I made it in real estate
or cattle ranching, he'd take it.
What are you laughing at?
Nothing... well, yes, I am.
I'm thinking of you standing in
the middle of a herd of cows.
Very funny.
Honey, don't do that.
Oh! Oh, shit.
God damn it.
- Did you cut yourself?
- No.
Just leave it. I'll get it later.
Come on over here, my darling
man, and talk to me.
What's the matter?
Tell me what's really
troubling you.
I took their money.
They wouldn't have paid me so much if
they weren't gonna use my knowledge.
Oh, no. You weren't
working for them.
You were just working
at their laboratory.
They wanted great scientists
to work at their laboratory.
It gives them prestige.
I knew they were
working on pathogens.
They were just picking my brain.
All I could think about was Liza.
Listen.
That money...
gave Liza 15 more years of life.
It gave her Erik.
What if they use it, Esther?
What if they use it
and everybody dies?
Well, I think you're
going completely crazy.
I really do, you know.
You are not to blame for
everything in this world,
no matter how smart you are.
And I'll tell you something else.
I'm taking a little
offense at this.
I didn't marry a murderer.
I married the kindest,
gentlest,
most loving man
in the world.
I don't think you ever knew
just how much I love you.
I swear, it...
- Esther?
- Ow...!
- What is it, honey?
- Ow!
- Come on, Esther. Come on. Come.
- Oh. No.
- Come on, come with me.
- I'm fine. I just got excited.
Come on, come on. Let me take you.
I'll take you upstairs.
Okay, come on.
One, two, three.
- Here we go.
- Oh...!
Come on.
I'm okay, really.
Well, whatever it is,
seven or eight days.
When we're done with the water...
and there's tangerine juice, too.
When we're done with
everything, then we go up.
Even though the radio
said eight days.
Maybe we ought to make it seven. But
what the fuck do they know, you know?
Air could be clear at six. Clear
enough, anyway, for me to go up
and get supplies and
come back down here.
- What?
- The last thing they said was...
"200 million dead in Europe."
So that's not everybody.
Nothing's gonna be left, Len.
We don't know that until we see.
Len, nothing's left.
The radio stopped.
There's no more planes
or helicopters.
When's the last time you heard
anything other than birds?
We'll stay down here
three more days.
And then...
- We'll drive to the marina.
- No.
We'll get a boat.
We'll go out on the lake.
And we'll keep going
until we find someone.
- I don't...
- What?
I don't wanna...
wade through a bunch of corpses
to go steal a boat
to go look at more corpses
lying on a bunch of docks.
Even...
even if we did make it, Len,
what are we supposed to do?
Do you really want
to play "Adam and Eve"?
Build it all back up so it all
just gets destroyed again?
Maybe people will learn.
It's like that guy who hit you for
trying to take care of his kid.
It's like that guy
I defended... great guy,
good father, always showing me
pictures of his grandson...
who helped invent the shit
that killed everyone.
People aren't going to learn.
It's something in us.
It's something in the
way that we're made.
Then at least...
we'll have more time.
At least we'll go out
on the water together.
We'll find a boat with
a nice, big cabin.
Come on.
Len?
That guy, Jay, from the law firm?
He fell in love with me.
I never did anything.
I never let him touch me.
But I...
you know, I...
I made him think, I guess...
that he had a shot at it.
- Why?
- It was just a way to...
Just a way to pass the time?
To feel better
about myself, I guess.
Why do you need to feel
better about yourself?
It wasn't about you.
It was just my curse.
Len.
Why are they gonna stay down
here like caged animals?
Or we're gonna go
upstairs tomorrow...
and lie down on the grass.
Breathe in...
and die...
when and where we choose.
We'll eat the chocolate bar
before we do it, okay?
Okay?
- Oh, my God.
- What? What?
Did you buy this weird soap?
What?
I seriously think
I've found my new religion.
Oh, yeah, that stuff.
Wait, have you read this?
No. I mean, the
writing's so tiny...
Wait a minute. Listen to this.
"Einstein, 1939.
After Nazis and Commies united,
proposes 'space bombs'
that destroys all unless we
finally teach the moral ABCs
the real Rabbi Hillel taught Jesus
to unite all in,
all one, God faith."
Did you find a pay phone?
I got some noodles.
Just gotta add water.
And some drinks.
And there's these things...
energy bars.
And napkins.
I couldn't find a pay phone. I don't
think they make them anymore.
What is this doing on a soap bottle?
And where did you get this?
I mean, it was at
the health food store.
- It was cheap.
- "We're all one or none.
There is no god but God.
Teach 'Love thy enemy.'
One Israel-Moses-
Buddha-Jesus-Mohammed.
- One! All one!"
- All one!
"Dilute! Dilute! Okay!"
How about the switchboard?
The hospital switchboard.
Or all of these houses and
apartments around here.
They've all got to have phones.
Esther...
he's gone.
Erik's gone.
Oh, look at this. Read this.
"For on God's spaceship, Earth"...
"With bomb and gun,
we're all one or none.
All one, all one, all one!
Exceptions eternally?
Absolutely none!"
"Absolutely none."
Oh, my God.
Why is the most inspiring
thing that I've ever read
sitting on a soap bottle?
"Dilute."
"Dilute! Dilute!"
"Dilute! Okay."
- You don't know that.
- It's just the way it is.
Because he could be
with any of his friends.
That's just it, honey.
You don't know it
for sure. You don't...
No! No!
Oh, oop!
No...
Oh, God, no.
Shh...
Okay, people. We're closing
down shop in two minutes.
You've got two minutes to get
your purchases up to the counter.
Okay?
That's it, man.
We gotta go. Come on.
250. Let's go.
- Come on.
- Yeah.
Um... fuck.
- Hey. We're done, man.
- Let's go.
I-I gave all my money to...
here, just run this.
Yeah, okay, buddy.
That's it. We're outta here.
You're closing up shop.
Just... just...
you're not selling any more
of these anyway, right?
Don't be stupid, man. We ain't
giving them away, either.
I understand that. Just take this.
Here. That's all I got. It's all I got.
Get the fuck out of here.
Get the fuck out now.
- Hey.
- Hey! Put down the kit!
It's the end of the world, okay? Just
let me walk out of here with a chance.
Put down the kit.
What? The last thing you wanna
do on earth is shoot me?
This is how this shit
started, anyway.
Right? That's how it
started in the first...
- You ready?
- I'm fine.
Good. If you're fine,
the tests are gonna show it.
Anyway...
we haven't seen Dr.
Henderson for a long time.
- Come here.
- That's right.
And here I was,
trying to cheer you up.
Oh, yeah.
You remember when
we lived in Washington,
the Georgetown apartment?
Yes, I do.
We both got the flu
at the same time.
Yeah. And I took care of you first.
I ran out in the freezing cold,
went and got you a nice,
big bowl of hot soup.
- It was so cold.
- Yeah.
And I wrapped you up all
nice and cozy in a blanket.
Remember?
Then I turned the thermostat
up as high as it would go.
Then it was my turn to baby you.
Tucked you in real tight,
And I made you some of those
awful poached eggs you like.
Mm-hmm.
It's been a good life.
Yeah, I think so.
A good life.
Oh, I forgot to tell you.
What?
The best thing in the world.
I have something to tell you.
What...?
The best thing in the world.
We're going to have a baby.
We don't have to do this.
Whatever we said last night,
we don't have to do it.
Not today, anyway.
Mmm, mmm.
I regret every fucking
diet I ever went on.
Mmm.
Come on.
Let's get out of here.
Ahem.
If you have to, if that's
what you have to do...
go, but I won't.
I...
I don't think we're gonna run out of food.
I don't think we're gonna run out of water.
I think that if we just stay down
here another couple of days...
- No.
- If we go up then, we're gonna be fine.
- Mm-mm.
- Okay?
- No.
- Yeah.
Yes!
Yes.
Mia! Don't leave me!
Don't leave me. Stay with me.
I love you, baby,
I love you. I need you.
I need you, I need you.
I need you, I need you... stay!
Please stay!
Please, I need you. Please?
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org