Zeus.
Poseidon.
It's been many years.
What do you see?
Thunderclouds.
But no lightning.
Stolen.
What?
You think I took it?
Omnipotence has
blinded you, brother.
We are forbidden from
stealing each other's powers.
But our children aren't.
You're accusing my son?
I haven't seen him since he
was a baby. He doesn't know me
or even know who he is
because of you.
If your son
is the thief,
I will send him to
the depths of Tartarus.
If you touch him, you will
have the fight of your life.
He must return the
bolt to me in 14 days,
by midnight on the summer solstice,
or there will be war.
And he's alive!
Percy Jackson is a beast! You're
a beast, man! Give me some.
How long was that?
Seven minutes.
Seven minutes?
Mmm-hmm.
Oh.
That's crazy, man. That's
ridiculous. How do you do it?
I just like
being in water.
It's the one place
I can think.
Mmm-hmm.
I wish I could spend all day
underwater instead of this place.
Right. It's like high
school without the musical.
Every day it's the same
thing. Look at this.
Good morning.
I'm Mrs. Dodds, your
substitute English teacher.
Would someone
please explain
what Shakespeare was trying to
convey in this line from Othello?
Percy Jackson?
Well?
I'm sorry, I don't know.
Anybody else?
Hey, Mom,
I'm home!
I'm up here, honey!
Hi.
Hey, Mom.
How was school today?
The usual.
I think this dyslexia
thing is getting worse.
Oh! Why do you
think that?
I don't know.
Maybe it's the ADHD.
You know,
I thought this school
was supposed to
make things better.
Percy, I know how hard this is for you.
But someday
it'll all make sense.
Really?
When? Hmm?
Tonight? Tomorrow? When?
Woman!
Hi, Gabe.
Where's my beer?
It's in the fridge.
So, what,
it's supposed to
magically float
from the icebox
and into my hand?
Hustle.
Come on, man. You have
to do that right here?
It's disgusting.
We're in a kitchen.
Yeah, real charmer
you got there. Really.
Show some respect,
all right?
That's my mom
right there.
This is my house.
You show some respect.
Oh, come on.
Why do you stay with that
pig? He smells like a sewer.
He sleeps till noon every day
and he can't even hold a job.
Why do you
stay with him?
He's been good to us, Percy,
in ways you don't understand.
You're right. I don't
understand. I don't get it.
POSEIDON: Be prepared. Everything
is about to change, Percy.
Everything is
about to change.
There are 12
Olympian gods.
The big three are the brothers
Zeus, Poseidon and Hades.
They attained power by
overthrowing their father, Kronos,
chopping him
into little pieces.
The three gods have
been rivals ever since,
always arguing,
always threatening war.
On several occasions, they would
come down to Earth and, um...
How shall I put this?
Hook up?
They would hook up
with mortals.
The children of these unions
were half god, half human.
Can anyone tell me
what they were called?
Percy.
Oh, I'm sorry. What?
What, Mr. Brunner?
What is the proper name of the
offspring of a human and a god?
Demigod.
Exactly.
And many became
great heroes,
like Hercules
and Achilles.
Can you name another?
I'll give you a hint.
You have something
in common.
Percy...
Perseus?
Correct.
Now, over here,
we have a depiction
of Hercules defeating
the Nemean lion.
Hercules killed the beast
with his bare hands
and took the skin
as a trophy.
Percy?
Yes, Mrs. Dodds?
We need to talk.
Okay.
The next 11 labors
would become
increasingly difficult.
It would take Hercules
three months...
So, did I do
something wrong?
Mrs. Dodds?
Hello?
Where is it?
Oh, whoa! Hey! Hey.
How did you get up there?
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
You stole
the lightning bolt!
I don't know what
you're talking about!
Give it to me!
Give it to me! Now!
Or I will bite
your heart out!
Percy!
Release him!
You!
Release him or I swear
I'll tear you to pieces!
I'm going crazy! Oh! I
should be on medication.
Percy, calm down, okay?
Everything's gonna be okay!
Oh, God, wait! Did
that really just happen?
She just turned
into that thing?
A Fury concealed in our
school. I should have known.
Wait, a Fury?
What's a Fury?
And why did you say you
could tear her to pieces?
What did she
want from you?
She said something
about me stealing
a lightning bolt.
They found him.
He's in danger.
Who found me?
He's no longer secure here.
Where should we move him?
We have no choice.
The Camp.
Huh? What camp? Look,
I'm standing right here.
If they think
he's the thief,
there's nowhere safe on
heaven and Earth for him now.
Percy, take this
to defend yourself.
It's a powerful weapon.
Guard it well.
Only use it in times
of severe distress.
This is a pen.
This is a pen!
Take him to his mother, and
don't let him out of your sight.
Okay. Percy, come on.
Come on, man. Come on!
Are you guys crazy?
Let's go!
This is a pen, man.
What do you want me
to do with this?
Come on!
Look, man,
what's going on?
Look,
don't trust anyone, okay? Don't
look at anybody, just keep walking!
Why did Mr. Brunner
ask you to watch me?
Because I'm your protector.
Wait, wait, wait. Hold on.
My protector?
Are you kidding?
What, you think because I'm like this,
I'm not capable of
keeping you safe?
Maybe you're not seeing what
I'm seeing. You have crutches!
Look, I would give my life
to secure your well-being.
What are you talking
about? What's going on?
We got to warn your mom. Come on, Perce.
Come on!
Sally! More beer!
Mom!
Hey, Mom. Mom! Mom!
Look, we gotta talk, okay?
Hey!
Can't you see she's
servicing me and my friends?
Hey. Hey! Don't talk
about my mom like that,
you bald-headed freak.
No, Gabe! Gabe!
Calm down!
GABE'S FRIEND: Whoa!
Hey, nice one.
Like I said,
I'm your protector.
Yeah.
Sally, Percy has to leave
now. Like, right now.
Okay.
Look, what is happening? Okay,
I swear, I didn't steal anything!
Honey, I believe you.
I believe you.
Where are you taking me?
What is this camp?
It's a camp for really
special people,
like you.
"Special people"?
What, am I crazy
or something?
No, honey, no.
Percy, this is
about your father.
I was just
out of school
and working at
the Jersey shore
when we first met.
Your father was unlike
any guy I'd ever seen.
He was just dazzling.
Mmm. They're always dazzling.
We were really
in love, Percy.
And then you came along,
and then it was just perfect.
But he had to leave.
So he did abandon us.
No, honey, he was
forced to. He loved you.
Leaving you, it was probably the
most difficult thing he ever did.
Why did he have to go?
Because he's...
Sally, watch out!
Whoa!
Mom! Go straight!
Percy?
Mom, you all right?
Yeah, yeah.
Grover, you all right?
Is it me or is it
raining cows?
What is that?
Get out!
Come on! Come on!
Why are you taking your
pants off? What are you doing?
My job!
Whoa! Whoa!
You're half donkey?
I'm half goat.
Go, Grover!
Guys, watch out,
there's glass!
Come on, get out of the car!
That thing's getting closer!
You don't even
need these.
Look, man, those are just for show.
Follow me!
Whoa!
This way, guys! This way! Come
on! Come on! Come on, run! Run!
Come on! Come on!
We're here!
Mom! What are you doing?
This is as far
as I can go.
Come on! I can't go
through! I'm not like you!
Look, I'm not leaving
without you.
You have to!
You're meant to!
Put my mother down!
Percy, go! You're safe inside the gate!
What can I do?
Listen, use the pen!
What? Use Brunner's pen and click it!
Whoa!
Perce, are you okay?
Percy,
behind you!
Perce, you okay?
I'm not feeling...
Percy!
Perce, I'm sure glad you're alive.
Ow!
Where am I?
What is this place?
The infirmary.
You've been unconscious
for three days.
Three days?
So, Perce,
what do you remember?
Some crazy dream.
I don't know.
There was a monster.
My mom was there.
You were there, too, but you
were some weird hybrid man-goat
thing! Whoa!
Yeah. The politically
correct term is Satyr.
No.
No, no, no, no!
All of it was real?
My mom's gone?
I'm sorry, Percy.
I try, man, I really do.
But, frankly, I'm just a junior
protector. I don't have my horns yet.
It was my fault. It was
my job to protect you.
Both of you.
So this is
Camp Half Blood.
"Half" meaning what?
I think you know.
"Half" meaning "half mortal, half god. "
Fire! Whoa! Guys! Watch the arrows!
Newcomer! Hello! Gosh!
Look, man,
remember all the myths
about Greek gods
and goddesses?
Well, they're not myths. Look,
remember what Mr. Brunner said?
Sometimes they
come down to Earth
and they fall in love
with mortals?
And then
they have kids?
No way.
Yes way.
Yep, you're a demigod!
Two points for Percy Jackson!
Look, don't worry.
But you're not alone.
There's hundreds
in the world.
Some lead normal lives,
and some, I'm not allowed to
divulge their names, are very famous.
I'm talking about, like,
White House famous.
See, man,
this place right here,
this is the place where you'll
learn to harness your powers.
You'll train to become
leaders, warriors and heroes.
I think you have the wrong
guy, all right? I'm not a hero.
I'm a loser. I have dyslexia, ADHD.
And those are
your greatest gifts.
When you try to read, the
words float off the page, right?
That's because your
brain is hardwired
for Ancient Greek,
not English.
Like at the museum,
I could read.
Yeah. And your ADHD?
You're impulsive, Percy.
You can't be still!
Those are your natural
battle reflexes, man.
They kept you alive
in your fight.
Look, no pitiful loser
can defeat a Minotaur.
Your blood is special.
It's the blood of a god.
This is a lot to process.
Yeah, a lot. A lot.
This is where you'll do
most of your battle training.
What's her name?
She will squash you
like a bug.
Her name.
Annabeth. Daughter of
Athena, the goddess of wisdom.
Hey, no staring.
Keep it moving.
Come on.
Uh-huh.
There's someone I want
you to see. Check this out.
Oh, wow!
What are those things?
They're Centaurs.
Wait a minute.
Is that Mr. Brunner?
Come on.
Whoa, whoa, whoa,
whoa, whoa.
Mr. Brunner?
In my world,
I'm known as Chiron.
Are you recovered?
Am I recovered?
You, you're not in
a wheelchair. You have...
A real horse's ass.
I apologize for
hiding my true form,
but I needed to keep an eye on
you. I hope you'll forgive me.
Come.
GIRLS: Hey, Grover!
Ooh. The daughters
of Aphrodite.
Okay. All right, guys. You guys
got a lot of catching up to do.
Their mother is the goddess of
love, so you know where that leads.
Hey, baby! Whoo!
Satyrs.
What is this place?
Welcome home.
Your father
built this for you.
Wow.
This whole place
is mine?
This thing's got
some weight to it.
My father is Poseidon!
God of the seas.
Why didn't anybody
tell me?
It was for
your own safety.
It's exceedingly rare
for a child to be born
to one of
the big three.
You're very powerful.
A threat.
A threat?
Who am I threatening?
Poseidon's brothers,
Zeus and Hades.
That's why your mother
married your stepfather.
His pungent odor masked
the smell of your blood
and hid you from anything or anyone
the gods would send to kill you.
My mother put up with
that creep to protect me?
Mmm-hmm.
I wish I'd known.
She sacrificed
so much for me.
Now she's gone.
Why am I even here?
CHIRON: You're here
because you're in jeopardy.
Everyone thinks you're
the lightning thief.
Look, I didn't steal it.
Zeus' bolt is the most
powerful weapon ever created.
And if it's not returned by
the summer solstice, in 10 days,
there will be a war.
This is your problem,
all right? Not mine.
This is about
your world, not mine.
all worlds!
Olympians would be forced
to choose sides.
Earth would become
a battleground.
Mountains erupted,
earthquakes, raging fires!
The end of life
as you know it.
What can we do?
I want to take you
to Olympus,
convince Zeus of
your innocence.
Someone's using you
to start a war.
What are we doing here?
Let's go now.
Your boldness is commendable,
but outside those gates
you would be in danger
at all times.
The Fury and the Minotaur
were only the beginning.
First, we must train.
This is always
a fun game to watch.
Ow! God, how do you guys wear
this stuff? It weighs more than me.
Look, trust me. Wear
it or you'll get killed.
Wait. What?
What? Wait...
CHIRON:
Heroes! Warriors!
Fall in!
Hustle, hustle!
Dylan, Paris,
stop lollygagging!
Percy. Step forward.
This is Percy Jackson!
And he's going
to need a team.
We'll take him.
I'm Luke. Son of Hermes and camp leader.
Not necessarily
in that order.
Where's your helmet?
No one gave me one.
Chiron, you still got your
wheelchair? Kid's gonna need it.
You're a goner, man.
I'm messing with you. Smile a
little bit. It's good for you, kid.
Anybody got an extra
helmet? Please pass it up.
Try it on.
That'll protect you.
So will all of us.
Welcome to the Blue Soldiers, my friend.
CHIRON: All right! Everyone in
position for Capture the Flag!
First team to capture
the enemy's banner wins.
Dismissed!
RED SOLDIER LEADER:
Steady, steady!
Now!
Percy, I know where
the flag's at. Come on!
Keep your eyes open.
Don't get killed.
Whoa! Whoa,
whoa, whoa!
I'm coming, buddy, I'm coming!
Sons of Ares. Watch out!
Whoa, that's a sword!
That's a sword!
Oh, you guys take camp
way too seriously.
Go!
Percy, get out of here!
Go look for the flag!
How did I just do that?
No.
I won.
Whoa! Whoa! Whoa!
Did you really think
it would be that easy?
My mother is goddess of
wisdom and battle strategy.
Do you know
what that means?
I always win.
I always lose.
Maybe we're both wrong.
Ow!
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
Whoa! Whoa, whoa, whoa!
Okay, Chiron, shouldn't we
get in there and stop them?
She's killing him, man.
You've got
to be kidding.
This is the best part!
Stand up and fight,
hero.
Come on, Perce.
POSEIDON: Go to the water.
The water will
give you power.
Yeah, Perce!
Get up there.
GIRL: All right! Yeah!
Excuse me!
Ladies and gentlemen, the son
of Poseidon is coming through.
A hero is coming through! Move it!
Hey, no dirty looks.
Stop that.
Sorry, I'm trying...
Hey, Percy?
We're having a party
at our place later.
And we would really love it if you came.
I'd love to come.
That'd be great.
That would be amazing!
Awesome.
I would love to come,
too, to the party.
You know? Thanks for
inviting me, ladies.
Beat it, nymphs.
Wait, don't leave.
Ladies... I'm available.
Wait, come on, don't leave. I'm
available! What time's the party?
Feeling like a hero?
More like a mutant.
I'm not gonna grow a fish tail or
gills or anything like that, am I?
Not likely.
Although a huge ego
isn't out of the question.
You know you could have
killed me out there?
I could have died,
if I was normal.
But you aren't.
I get the sense that you
don't like me very much.
It's possible. I mean, our
parents hate each other.
Wait. They do?
Mmm-hmm.
I definitely have
strong feelings for you.
I just haven't decided if
they're positive or negative yet.
Well, you let me know
when you figure it out.
You'll be the first.
Percy Jackson,
show yourself!
Hades! Stay back!
Percy Jackson,
bring me the bolt!
Be a good boy.
Hand it to me and I will
exchange it for your mother.
Percy!
Don't listen, Percy!
My mother's gone!
No, your mother
is still alive.
I sent the Minotaur
to abduct her.
She is here with me
in the Underworld.
Mom?
Percy?
What have you done
with my mother?
If you ever want to see your mother
again, you will bring me the bolt!
Chiron, I have
to go get her.
Percy, you don't
have the bolt.
Look, I'll tell
him the truth!
When he realizes I'm not
the thief, he'll release her.
No. You cannot
negotiate with Hades.
When he finds out
you don't have the bolt,
he'll kill you
and your mother.
This is her only chance.
No.
Stick to our plan.
Travel to Olympus,
bargain with Zeus.
Once you convince him
of your innocence,
we will do everything in our
power to bring back your mother.
Okay.
Going somewhere?
Yeah. Yeah,
I'm going for a walk.
Oh, for a walk?
I'm coming with you.
No, no,
I'm going alone.
No, I'm coming
with you.
No!
You're being followed.
You're stressing me out.
Leave me alone.
We got a 1:00 demigod curfew, okay?
Leave me alone. Go
to sleep or something.
No.
Come on.
One small victory
and you're ready
to fight Hades?
Ooh, double team.
Really? You, too?
Look, I just found out
my mother is still alive.
I'm gonna get her back.
From the Underworld?
Whatever it takes.
Huh. Yeah, well, maybe
you'll outsmart Hades.
Maybe I will.
Look, man,
I can't let you
do this, okay?
Look, I'm not asking
for your permission.
Okay. Well, according
to regulations,
if I can't stop you,
I must accompany you,
'cause I'm your best friend
and your protector.
Junior protector.
Is that
really necessary?
I don't need
your help. Okay?
This is something I
have to do on my own.
Yeah, well, we weren't
asking for your permission.
Come on, all right? Today
you tried to kill me.
Now you want
to defend me?
That wasn't real.
That was just training.
Yeah.
Percy, that's all
I've ever done,
is train and train
and train.
I've grown up here. I've only been in
the outside world a couple of times.
And I've never had the chance
to go on an actual quest.
Besides, you've won one
battle and I've won hundreds.
You're gonna need
my experience.
Good point.
You two really
want to come?
Yes!
Yeah!
Okay. I guess
we're all going.
So who knows how to
get to the Underworld?
I did not think
of that one.
I think I know
someone who might.
MAN'S VOICE:
Friendly Harriers inbound!
Luke?
Hmm?
Hey, guys.
Percy. I figured you'd
stop by sooner or later.
Everybody does, just to
get away from all that
Renaissance fair stuff
out there, you know?
But welcome to
the modern world.
Cool. New stuff.
What are you
guys up to?
We're going to
get my mom back.
Oh!
Your dad is
the messenger of the gods,
one of the only ones who's gotten
in and out of the Underworld.
Do you have any idea how?
Mmm. My dad's a jerk.
I've never met him.
You, too?
Guess we all got
Daddy issues, huh?
That's because all gods
are the same. Selfish.
They only care
about themselves.
But I once broke into my dad's
house. Got some cool stuff.
For you.
Whoa!
Flying shoes?
Mmm-hmm.
They're my dad's.
He has hundreds of
these little guys.
He won't even miss them.
Look underneath
the other one.
You see, people have gone
to the Underworld before
without having to be dead.
Hercules did it.
Orpheus did it.
My dad does it
all the time.
Getting in's the easy part.
Getting out,
now that's tricky.
This is a map to
Persephone's pearls.
Persephone?
You mean Hades' wife?
Yeah, he forced her to marry
him. Keeps her prisoner.
Needless to say, she hates it
there. It's hot, he's a weirdo.
So she has, um,
secret visitors.
Hmm!
Mmm!
She keeps pearls hidden
for them all over the world,
and these pearls,
they provide a quick escape
from the Underworld.
You could use them
to get out.
So, how do
the pearls work?
Easy.
You take a pearl, you
step on it, you crush it,
visualize where you
want to be taken.
Right now, there's three
pearls in the United States.
This map will
guide you there.
Right here is
your first location.
"Auntie Em's
Garden Emporium. "
Once you find
the first pearl,
the map will show
you the next one,
and the next one, and
then you're off to Hades.
Which reminds me.
You guys
might need some
extra protection, so...
My favorite shield. You might
want to take a step back.
Mmm.
Hey. Thanks, Luke.
Ah, don't mention it.
But you're gonna have to
promise me one thing.
If you see my dad on
the highway to hell...
Yeah?
Kick his ass for me.
I'm on the highway to hell
Highway to hell
Don't stop me
This place definitely
needs an extreme makeover.
Hello!
Hello? Anybody home in Auntieville?
Check this out.
They got free sodas.
Okay. That's nasty.
The Health Department needs
to give this place an F.
Hey, guys,
check this out.
Look at this.
Nice.
Gold drachmas.
That means we're on
the right track.
Here.
How are we gonna find
the pearl in this place?
That's a good question.
Okay, let's split up.
Check everything.
Good idea.
Yeah.
I'm gonna go this way.
Hello?
Get out!
She's coming!
What? Who?
We stopped... Directions...
My poor husband! Help me!
Please, help me!
Check this out. He looks
just like my Uncle Ferdinand.
That's crazy.
He got the mole
in the same place.
No. It's not
my Uncle Ferdinand,
because Uncle Ferdinand
was killed by
Medusa.
Percy! Annabeth!
We're in trouble!
Grover?
Please! We have to leave
before she finds us!
Who?
She's turned
my husband to stone!
Grover! Where are you?
Percy! Annabeth!
Annabeth, where are you?
Grover!
Come on, man,
watch where you're going!
Perce! Listen.
Where are we?
We're in Medusa's lair.
Annabeth!
Annie!
We're lost!
We'll never leave!
Don't move.
Well, this is
a fabulous surprise.
It's so heartening to
have such young visitors.
We get so lonely here.
Don't we?
That's why I create
my statues.
They're my only company,
daughter of Athena.
How do you know me?
You have such
beautiful hair.
I once had hair
like that.
I was courted,
desired by
many suitors.
But that all changed
because of your mother,
the woman who cursed me.
Who turned me...
Don't look!
...into this!
They say the eyes
are windows to the soul.
I hope you find my eyes
attractive.
So rude, not looking
people in the eyes.
Come on.
Sneak a peek.
How are we supposed to fight
something we can't look at?
We can look
at a reflection.
Okay, wait.
Check this out.
All right. Good idea.
I'm gonna go get Annabeth.
Okay, I'm gonna
take care of Medusa.
Okay.
You'll make a wonderful
addition to my collection.
We'll be
friends forever.
Do you mind?
Oh, no, no.
Sooner or later you
will open those eyes.
The temptation to look at
me is too hard to resist.
Don't look, Annabeth!
Don't open your eyes!
Who's that?
Another demigod?
Mmm.
I can sense you.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Whoa!
Mmm.
Son of Poseidon.
I used to date
your daddy.
Need a hand?
Grover. Help.
Thanks. Okay.
Come on. Let's go.
I hear you have
the lightning bolt.
May I see it?
I don't have it!
Let me see your eyes.
I hear they're bluer
than the Circassian Sea.
Open them,
or my hungry babies will
have to open them for you.
But it would be
such a pity
to destroy such a
young and handsome face.
Stay with me, Percy.
All you have
to do is look.
Are you okay?
Yeah, I'm okay.
Son of Poseidon!
Heads up.
Hey, guys! It's cool
to open up your eyes!
Annabeth, that was great,
great demigod driving.
Thanks.
We should
take it with us.
The head?
Oh, no. That's sick.
If you open the eyes, they
still work, dead or alive.
You never know when something
like that might come in handy.
Yeah, you're right.
But I'm not touching it.
Come on, man, just take off your jacket.
We'll wrap it up
until we get some ice.
Why do I got to
take off my jacket?
Because you're
the protector.
Yeah, you're right.
I am the protector.
So I'm gonna give you my
hoodie, not my jacket. Okay?
Come on, you baby.
Disgusting.
Yeah, just toss it up.
Come on, don't...
Hey. Hey. Guys, wait.
The pearl.
One down, two to go.
Would have been nice if Luke
had warned us about Medusa.
Maybe he just
didn't know.
GPS from the gods.
Where to next?
Let's see.
The Parthenon
in Nashville.
Nashville? Oh, great. Home
of my least favorite music.
Yee-haw!
I make believe
that the sight of her
in my head's seldom seen
Let's stop for the night! Yeah.
Good idea.
Oh, my God.
Percy.
Hey.
Nice work today.
Thanks.
What happened to you?
Oh, that poor lady who
turned to stone, she...
She had a tight grip.
Check this out.
Cool. Very cool.
So,
why do our parents
hate each other?
They both wanted to be
patron god of Athens.
And the people
chose Athena.
And our parents have hated
each other ever since.
What's your mom like?
I don't know.
I never met her.
What? Is it like
this for everybody?
Don't any gods
see their kids?
It's forbidden.
Right after we were born, Zeus decreed
that the gods couldn't have physical
contact with their mortal offspring.
Oh, that's a stupid law.
I agree.
Although, between us,
I think my mother
speaks to me sometimes.
In times of trouble,
I hear her voice
giving me advice.
That's happened to me!
Yeah. That's your father talking to you.
Yo, Percy! Get in
here, man! This is ugly!
Right.
Hey, hurry up!
Perce, check this out, man.
You're on TV.
...surrounding the
missing boy, Percy Jackson,
and his mother,
Sally Ugliano.
But their relatives have
some interesting theories.
So, Mr. Ugliano, talk to me
about your son, Percy Jackson.
No, he's not my son.
He's a stepson.
He did not come
from these loins.
Ever since he started with
the drugs and the alcohol,
he's never been the same. Oh, no.
Five nights ago,
he tried to kill me
and he threw his mother
on the ground.
And his cripple friend
then attacked me
from behind
and knocked me out.
When I woke up, Sally was gone.
She was kidnapped by Percy.
She would never
leave with that...
Oh, shut up, Gabe.
Great.
Now I'm a fugitive.
See? That's what
I'm talking about, man.
Gabe's always
running his mouth.
He's just mad because I
busted him up with my crutches.
Guys,
I can't pee
with her watching me.
Sorry, guys.
I messed up.
I should have
closed the curtains.
Come on, guys.
Let's hit the road before
Homeland Security shows up.
Wow, that's amazing.
A complete replica of the
Parthenon in Nashville.
All right, guys.
Let's go get the pearl.
Wow.
Hey. That's your mom.
I wonder if she really looks like that.
We'll find out.
Guys, check this out.
Oh, man.
It's the pearl.
That was easy.
Easy?
It's 30 feet in the air and this
place is filled with tourists.
I got an idea.
We'll come back after the place
closes. Come on, follow me.
Or I can just throw
my crutch up there.
I'm saying, the pearl
would fall out... Grover!
Perce, I'm saying...
It's not a bad idea!
The park's been closed
for an hour. Let's move.
Yes, sir!
All right, this will be easy. Okay.
I'm gonna fly up. I'm gonna
use Luke's flying shoes.
I'm gonna grab the pearl, and... Cool.
Oh!
Okay, so what are
we going to do?
All right, guys.
I got this.
You got what?
Hey, yo, hey, listen!
You're going to
kill the janitors?
Chill.
Those are working-class Americans!
Oh, man.
Oh. Why did
you do that?
They're not dead,
they're unconscious.
Now, we have 30 minutes.
Come on!
Cool.
Y'all, what's cracking?
Hey.
Luke!
Annabeth!
How do you
turn on the shoes?
Tell Percy he's got to
break into a run, okay?
He's got to build up speed,
kind of like a jet on a runway.
It's gonna take
some practice.
Okay.
I got this.
Whoa... Whoa!
It's gonna take
some practice!
Whoa!
Oh! Whoa. Whoa.
I got it!
Yes!
Yeah, Percy!
There we go!
There it is.
Yeah!
That's what
I'm talking about.
Way to go.
All right,
let's grab everything...
Uh-oh. Uh-oh.
Oh, man.
Look, I got this, okay?
Hey, guys, I'm with
Park Recreational Services.
You guys have been caught sleeping
on the job. You better be happy
I'm not writing you guys up,
okay? This is the last time.
We've been expecting you,
Mr. Jackson.
Not again.
Just give us the lightning
bolt and we'll let you go.
Look, I don't have
the lightning bolt.
Okay. This is bad.
Hydra!
Guys, watch out! The
middle one spews fire!
Whoa!
Oh, you got a sweet tooth?
All right! Try that!
Whoa!
Percy, stop! No!
How flipping
awesome was that?
I just killed
that thing!
Killed it?
You only made it worse.
What are you
talking about?
Percy, when you cut
off one Hydra head,
two more grow back.
Get back!
Distract that thing!
I'll get the pearl!
Whoa, whoa,
whoa, whoa!
Let's go!
Let's go! Come on!
Go!
Open the door!
The door won't open!
Grover!
That's nasty.
We interrupt our regularly
scheduled programming
for this special report.
Scientists are baffled
by what now appears to be
a single storm cloud that is
expanding over much of Europe and Asia,
moving towards
the United States.
Savage winds,
rain and mammoth waves
are being reported
along the coastlines
of several continents.
So far, no casualties, but countries
everywhere are preparing for the worst.
The gods are angry.
We need to get
the last pearl.
Where's the next location?
Yeah.
Well, let's see.
Well, guys, we got ourselves a good one.
We're going to Vegas!
Yo!
Oh. There it is.
Lotus Casino.
I've been
looking forward to this!
Look, guys, remember, always split
the eights, never the tens, okay?
We're not here to
gamble, remember?
We got poker,
we got blackjack...
Grover, we're not here to have fun.
We just need to grab
the pearl and go, okay?
All right.
This is nice!
A little less conversation,
a little more action, please
All this aggravation
ain't satisfactioning me
Okay, this place
is officially dope.
Here's your complimentary
Lotus Fun Book.
Thanks,
but we're not staying.
Please, I insist. It's good for
everything in the hotel and casino.
Don't comp us.
We're not checking in.
Okay, that guy
was persistent.
Yeah!
Yeah, we're here for one
thing and one thing only.
Wow.
That is really
awesome.
Where would we find a
green pearl in this place?
Maybe on a cocktail
waitress or a showgirl.
We should start there.
Can I get you something? Try a
lotus flower. They're so good.
It's our signature dish.
Oh. Really?
Signature?
Is it good?
Thank you.
Yo, do we have to
pay for this?
I guess we don't.
It's free.
Mmm. That's really good.
Mmm. Wow. This is the most
delicious thing I've ever consumed!
I wanna hold 'em
like they do in Texas, please
Wow.
Fold 'em let 'em hit me,
raise it, baby, stay with me
I love it
Love, game, intuition,
play the cards
Guys, why don't we
stay here for a while?
Yeah!
That sounds like
an amazing idea.
But we're on a time-sensitive
mission right now.
Aren't we...
I can't remember.
I totally forgot
what I was gonna say.
I think I figured it out. I
think I know why we're here.
Why are we here?
To have fun.
Okay. Let's never leave!
Yeah!
Let's stay here!
Can't read my
No, he can't read
my poker face
She's got to love nobody
Can't read my
No, he can't read
my poker face
Whoa!
Yeah!
Poker face, poker face
I'll get him hot,
show him what I got
You're awesome!
Can't read my
No, he can't read
my poker face
She's got to love nobody
Can't read my
No, he can't read
my poker face
Ooh! Ooh!
Ooh!
Thanks.
Thank you! Thanks.
POSEIDON: No, Percy.
Don't eat the flower.
It dulls the senses,
keeps you prisoner here.
Hey, I think I'm gonna go get
some air. I'll be right back.
Okay.
WAITRESS:
Another lotus flower?
No, I'm good.
Thank you.
POSEIDON: Look around you. Focus. Focus!
Another lotus flower?
No, thank you.
Would you like another one? I'm fine.
The French Connection, huh?
Yeah.
You seen it yet?
Yeah, yeah,
I think so, on DVD.
What's DVD?
Seriously?
Whatever. I think it's
the best movie of the year.
What? Wait.
This year?
Yeah, this year. 1971.
POSEIDON: Percy, wake up.
You need to escape.
Wake up!
You could really use
a lotus flower.
I really
don't want one.
Thank you.
Just one.
No!
Another lotus flower?
No.
We insist.
I really don't want another lotus
flower, so please, leave me alone.
Is there a problem,
Mr. Jackson?
No. Thank you.
Percy Jackson's awake.
Excuse me.
Annabeth. Annabeth!
Whoa, whoa, whoa! What're you
doing with that? Don't eat that.
What?
We have to go. Now.
What do you mean?
We're having so much fun!
No, no, no, we're not having
fun. Grover! Grover! Wake up!
Grover! Come on,
we got to go!
What? Look, Perce, your
timing is terrible, okay?
Dude, we're heading to the
chapel. We're getting married!
How romantic!
No, no, no, no, no.
Hey, which of y'all
did I propose to?
Wake up!
Yo, man, you're such a buzz kill.
Percy, what's wrong with
you? Why are you doing this?
Both of you need
to wake up, now!
Look at me. Look at me. You're
in a trance, okay? We're trapped!
Listen to me.
If you eat the flowers,
you're never gonna
want to leave. Okay?
We're gonna be
stuck here forever!
Oh.
Oh, no.
We got to go.
Okay, I see
your point! Okay.
Let's get
the green pearl!
Hold it right there!
Stop right where you are.
Move, James Dean! Out of the
way! Let's go, guys! Car! Car!
Come on, guys! Car!
Get in!
Come on, come on! In the
car, in the car! Let's go!
Keys! Got the keys.
Come on! Go!
Drive! Drive!
They're coming!
Come on, start driving!
I got this.
Go!
Now, that's how you get out of
a casino! That's how you drive!
Of course.
Now that all makes sense.
What?
That was the lair
of the lotus eaters.
They've been luring people into
their trap since ancient times.
Guys, look.
Tomorrow is June 21 st.
No. No, no. It can't
be. Today's the 15th.
No, tomorrow is the 21 st. We
were in there for five days.
It felt like hours.
Then tomorrow's
the solstice.
Our deadline is
tomorrow at midnight.
Okay, look, we've got to
move it. Where's Hades?
It's in Hollywood.
All right. I can get
us there in four hours.
Maybe three.
MAN ON RADIO: And now, the
latest breaking news from KZLY.
An unprecedented storm cloud has
grown to cover most of North America.
Authorities in several states
are ordering evacuations,
reporting severe
weather conditions.
Don't slip.
Watch your step.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Wait, wait. Hold it.
"Woe to all
depraved souls. "
Well, I guess there
ain't no turning back now.
Yep. Looks like
we're stuck in here.
Yeah.
Hey, Perce, who's that
creepy guy with the hoodie?
I don't know.
Let's find out.
Who are you?
We need to see Hades.
The living are
not permitted here.
Die and come back.
Okay, we won't die
and come back, but...
You know what?
I think I know what he wants.
What?
You got to pay
the ferryman.
Watch this.
Yo, my friend!
What up?
Okay, guess not. Look, you
like dead people, right?
I got a few dead people
you might recognize.
Check this out.
Jackson, Grant.
And look who's joining the
party. Benjamin Franklin.
Yeah, you like that,
don't you?
Look, you give us a boat
ride, you take the money
and you get
an interior decorator,
'cause it is too
depressing in here.
All right?
Here you go.
That was $170!
Wait, wait. Wait, wait, wait, wait,
wait. The drachma. The drachma!
Climb aboard.
Thanks for telling me, man, you're
burning money. We're in a recession.
That's treason. Just shut
up. Shut up, man. Go on.
Welcome to
the Underworld.
What is all this?
The scrapheap
of human misery.
Lost hopes and dreams.
Wishes that never
came true.
All lives end in suffering and tragedy.
This is as
far as I go.
Guys, do you
hear that?
Yeah, what is that?
I don't know.
Annie, stab that thing!
What are we gonna do?
Back!
What were those things?
Hellhounds.
Yeah, well, maybe you should feed them.
They sensed the presence
of another animal.
Great, they smell goat.
Hmm. A Satyr.
I haven't had a Satyr
visit before.
Persephone!
What could possibly
be taking so long?
Don't ignore me!
Or what?
What will you do?
I'm already in Hell.
We have visitors.
Nephew.
Welcome.
You have your
father's looks.
Always the lucky
side of the family.
Wait. Wait a minute,
wait a minute.
You're Hades?
Yes.
Sorry. I just didn't expect
you to look like this, man.
Kind of stylish.
I like it.
Would you prefer
that I looked like this?
No! No! Look, stick to the Mick
Jagger thing! It works for you!
You're very
brave coming here.
Come closer.
Hey. Perce.
I can see the look of
disgust in your eyes,
but this existence
was not of my choosing.
I was banished here by Zeus
and your father. I am damned.
My only chance of
getting out of this place
is to defeat my brothers and take
control of Olympus. But, of course,
I'll need the bolt.
And I need my mother.
Then we have
an understanding.
You give me the bolt and
I'll give you your mother.
I need to tell
you the truth.
I'm not the lightning
thief. I don't have the bolt.
I never did.
Why did you
come here, then?
Well, I was hoping
that when you saw that I wasn't
the thief, you'd let my mother go.
Yes. Yes, but do you think I'm an idiot?
I'm Hades!
Now, give me the bolt,
or say goodbye to your mother!
Percy!
I thought
I'd lost you forever.
No.
Zeus' master bolt.
Liar.
I swear, I don't know
how that got there.
That's not even
my shield!
No!
Luke rigged it!
He put the bolt in
his shield and used us.
Luke stole
the lightning bolt.
I think we're done here.
Feed them to the souls.
Whoa! Whoa!
We had a deal, all right? You
have the bolt! Just let us go!
Summon the hounds.
Ella tho!
No. No ella tho.
Lassie, sit! Sit!
No! No!
I am going to be
king of the gods.
Stay back! Stay!
Stay!
All right, come on.
Go on, give it back.
Bad dog!
He won't
remember a thing!
Why did you do that?
Because he's cruel
and abusive!
The only thing
I look forward to
is my allotted time
away from this hellhole.
A war of the gods
would put an end to that.
And I'd be alone,
with only him,
forever.
Go. Take the bolt,
and your mother.
Only three?
Oh, no.
There are four of you.
Each pearl transports
only a single person.
One of you
will have to stay.
All right, I'll stay.
You three go. What? No.
No, no, no.
I've achieved
my quest. I'm staying here. No. No!
I've trained for
situations like this.
Guys! Guys.
Knock it off.
I'm staying, because
I'm the protector.
Grover, come on.
Look, man, I don't want
to hear it. Just go.
It's my duty.
It's what I'm meant for.
We'll come back
for you.
I'll take very
good care of him.
All right.
Now move it, guys!
Each of you, step on a pearl and
concentrate on where you want to go.
Take this.
To Olympus.
Ooh!
Hey. Look.
Zeus and Poseidon
preparing for battle.
Oh, no, no.
This isn't the right place.
This isn't Olympus.
This is...
This is the
Empire State Building!
Percy! The entrance
to Olympus is there!
Well, there's 10 minutes
till midnight. Let's move.
Percy Jackson!
Well, you weren't supposed
to make it out alive.
I can't let you take
that bolt to Olympus.
I'm the lightning thief.
You hid the bolt
in my shield. Why?
Well, when you said you were
going to the Underworld, it hit me.
"That is the perfect opportunity
to get the bolt to Hades. "
Why would you do that?
To bring Olympus
crumbling down.
Percy, let's go.
Let's go!
Well, it's too late, 'cause I'm
returning the bolt to Zeus right now.
Not before midnight.
You all right?
Yeah.
Luke! Why do you want
a war of the gods?
Control.
They've been in power
for too long.
I say it's time for our
generation to take over.
Remold the world
in our image.
A world of new heroes.
You're no hero.
Huh!
Mom, are you all right? Yeah.
Stay here.
Luke!
Maybe they were wrong.
Maybe you're
no son of Poseidon.
Yeah. I think I am
the son of Poseidon.
He's got the bolt! Come on!
Let's move! We've got two minutes!
Olympus.
Percy, I can't get
through. You've got to go!
Silence!
It is almost midnight.
This was predestined!
You wanted this battle!
You have only
yourself to blame!
Please! Let's be rational.
War is not the answer!
Time has run out.
Wait!
Wait! Wait!
Wow.
My name is Percy Jackson, and I
think you might be looking for this.
Give me the bolt,
lightning thief.
You're wise to
betray your father.
I didn't steal it. And I have
no connection to Poseidon.
But tell me, if you didn't
steal it, then who did?
Luke, son of Hermes.
You see,
he was angry at you.
All of you.
He wanted you to
destroy yourselves.
You have done well.
Let there be peace.
Hi, Mom.
Annabeth,
I am so proud of you.
Zeus, I have
a good friend.
He's a Satyr
named Grover.
He's my protector,
and the only reason why
we escaped the Underworld
is because
he stayed behind.
And now you expect me
to bring him back.
Very well.
I believe this assembly's
business here is finished.
Brother, please. I
need to speak with him.
Just this once.
I'll meet you outside.
I'm not expecting you
to forgive me.
But I want you to know
that I'm grateful.
I didn't do it for you.
I did it to save Mom.
Please. We don't have much time.
How old was I
when you left?
Seven months.
Look, I didn't need you
there all the time, but...
I would have liked to
have seen you just once.
Why didn't you
ever come back?
I wanted to.
When I was with you
and your mother,
I became less concerned
with my responsibilities.
I was becoming human.
And that's a bad thing?
For a god?
Zeus thought so.
That's why
he passed the law
preventing gods from ever having
contact with their children.
That was because of you?
But I was always
watching over you.
Just because
you didn't see me
doesn't mean that
I wasn't there.
When you were troubled,
I tried to help.
I heard you.
I know I'm not the father
you always wanted,
but if you ever need me,
I'll be there for you,
in your thoughts
and in your dreams.
I'll stand by you, Percy.
Always.
You can come
visit me anytime.
Just promise me that I don't have
to see that loser Gabe ever again.
I kicked him out.
Yeah, he's gone. He's
out of our lives forever.
Finally.
Oh!
I'm going to
miss you.
Me, too.
Percy?
This is where you belong.
Good job, man.
Thanks, Perce.
Ready! Aim!
Hey, whoa, Perce... Watch it! Hey!
You guys gonna kill the
man who saved the world?
Great job. All you guys,
take a lunch break. Thank you!
So, the conquering hero
returns, triumphant.
Grover.
Hey!
You notice anything
different about me?
No.
You sure? Anything
that's improved about me?
No. What,
you've been working out?
What, you get a new
cologne? You smell good.
Look, man.
I got my horns!
Oh! I was seeing them
the whole time.
I mean, look at that thing. You
got little horns in your head.
Right?
Crazy.
Zeus came through,
and now I'm Senior
Protector, First Class, baby.
Congratulations.
Definitely earned them.
Thank you, man.
CHIRON: Keep moving, keep
moving! Don't lose interest!
One foot in front
of the other,
and the next thing you
know, you're running!
Percy.
You left the camp. You
disobeyed my orders.
Yeah, about that.
Which is why
you're my
favorite student.
You can receive all the training
in the world, but ultimately,
you have to follow
your instincts.
Grace under pressure.
All right. Time to train. Go suit up.
You might be
a big shot on Olympus,
but down here, you're still
just one of my students.
Move it.
Nice horns, Grover.
I'm serious, man. We
talked, we wooed, we dined,
we had a great time!
Well, I'm happy
for you, you know?
Persephone might really
like me. I'm serious.
I think you can handle
this one on your own.
Uh-huh.
All right, Perce.
Hey, Perce, awesome
job, man. Hey, thanks.
Good job.
Thanks.
Who's next?
I think I'd like
to give it a shot.
Welcome home.
Whoa! Whoa! Wait!
First rule of
battle strategy.
Don't ever let your
opponent distract you.
Sally, open the door!
Open up!
You changed the locks?
Yes.
So, here's your junk.
You can
let yourself out.
Well...
How am I supposed to move
all this stuff by myself?
Deal with it.
I need a beer.
What? "Do not open..."
That little brat.
Well, I may not
live here anymore,
but I'm still the king
of this castle.
English - US - PSDH