Watch Movies, TV Series and Live Sports
Signup Here -> WWW.ADMITME.APP
(TICKING)
(MOANING)
MAN: The story always ends the same.
Peter Pan shouts...
PETER: Goodbye, Wendy!
And then Wendy shouts back to him...
I'll always believe in you, Peter Pan!
And Wendy did believe always,
even as she left childhood behind
and came to have children of her own.
There it is, Jane.
Second star to the right
and straight on to morning.
Never Land!
The second star to the right
Shines in the night for you
To tell you that the dream you plan
Really can come true
The second star to the right
Shines with a light that's rare
And if it's Never Land you need
Its light will lead you there
(BELLS RINGING)
MAN: Our story begins in difficult times.
England is threatened with war
and many men have been asked
to leave their families
to protect their country.
I'll be home before you know it.
I promise.
Now, now. What's all this?
I want to go with you.
I need you here
to take care of your mom and Danny.
Can you do that for me?
(SNIFFLES) Mmm-hmm.
That's my big girl.
- Be safe, Edward.
- Look after each other, now.
Goodbye, Daddy! I love you!
I love you all.
MAN: Drive off!
But the war lasted much longer
than anyone could have imagined.
(BOMB WHISTLING)
Bombs fell from the sky
and tore at the very heart of London.
- Don't cry, son.
- (TRAIN WHISTLE)
All aboard!
In an effort to protect its children,
the government decreed
that they all be sent
to the countryside for safekeeping.
- Goodbye!
- Bye-bye!
- I love you!
- Good luck, sweetie!
In times such as these
it is no wonder
some discard childish things,
like Peter Pan and Never Land.
(BARKING)
What is it, Nanatwo?
(CHUCKLES)
We don't have time, you silly dog.
- We have to get this home to Danny.
- (ALARM SIREN)
Oh, no! Quick, Nanatwo!
(BARKING)
(SIREN CONTINUES)
Mommy, where's Jane?
Don't you worry, Danny.
She'll be along.
All right, now. Here we go.
Into the bomb shelter.
MAN: Bring the lights up!
(GROWLING)
- What is it, girl?
- (SNIFFING)
- Oh, my gosh!
- (BOMB WHISTLING)
(HOWLING)
(CRASHING)
Nanatwo,
we're not out of the woods yet.
We have to get back out there.
Look, who's in charge here?
(BARKS)
Don't be silly. I am!
Now, come on!
(HONKING)
(MEN SHOUTING)
- (EXPLOSION)
- (GASPING)
Mommy, I'm scared!
I don't like planes and bombs.
Is that what it is?
For a moment, it sounded like cannons
on a pirate ship.
(GASPS) You're right!
It's Captain Hook!
I hear him! He's coming!
WENDY: Jane!
DANNY: Jane!
Oh, Jane! Where have you been?
Why didn't you...
- Mother, I'm fine!
- Jane, you made it past the pirates!
- Daniel, careful!
- What's that? What's that?
Whoa!
Hey! It's for me, isn't it?
Let me see! Let me see!
All right!
- Happy birthday, Daniel.
- Yippee!
Socks. Two of 'em.
Jane, dear, how very practical.
Got them a size large
so he can grow into them.
Look, Danny. Pan and Hook, see?
- Curse you, Peter Pan!
- Oh, Mother.
I want to hear a Peter Pan story!
(BARKING)
Shh! Nanatwo!
WENDY: All right, then.
How about the time
Peter and the Lost Boys
captured Hook's ship
right from under his nose?
DANNY: Ooh! That's a good one!
WENDY: It was late one misty evening
and Hook was sure once again
that he'd found Peter's hideout.
Hook and his bloodthirsty crew
went ashore
leaving the Jolly Roger unguarded.
That's when Peter Pan arrived!
He and the boys slipped aboard
and there they found it.
Hook's remarkable treasure!
DANNY: Wow!
WENDY: Peter told the Lost Boys
they'd hide it
and Hook would have to
hunt them down to get it back.
It was all a great game for Peter.
And then, from out of the mist,
he was there,
the evil Captain Hook!
A fierce and ferocious sword fight
was fast underway.
Ah-ha!
(WHIMPERS)
- Give up, boy!
- Never!
WENDY: And at that moment,
a shimmering magic covered the ship.
DANNY: Tinker Bell!
WENDY: Yes! And the Jolly Roger
lifted into the sky
as Peter and the boys
escaped with the treasure.
(GRUNTING)
You've not seen the end of me,
Peter Pan!
I'll get you for this
if it's the last thing I do!
So you see, Danny,
Hook will never win
as long as there's faith,
trust and pixie dust.
Poppycock!
Slow down, you old codfish!
Oh, my notebook! Ow!
- Daniel!
- Come on, Jane!
We'll beat old Captain Hook together!
Daniel, please!
I've no time for fun and games.
You used to. You got to be
the very first Lost Girl ever.
That was a long time ago.
Yeah. Back when you were fun.
JANE: Honestly, Mother.
I don't know why you fill his head
with those silly stories.
- But they're not silly. They're...
- (KNOCKING)
- Take care of Danny, will you?
Go on. I'll be right there.
- Yes?
- Evacuation, ma'am.
Your children are scheduled
on the morning train.
So soon?
But I haven't even told them.
The sooner the better, if you ask me.
Good night, ma'am.
Yes.
Uh, Good night.
(WHIMPERING)
Jane, dear.
Will you promise me something?
Promise you'll watch over Danny,
- whatever might happen.
- What?
(SIGHS) You and your brother
are going away for a while.
Away? But where?
All the children are being evacuated
to the country.
It's so dangerous here.
But you'll be safe there, both of you.
- I'm not going! I'm staying here!
- But, dear, an order has been issued.
Every child must go.
But Daddy said that I'm supposed to...
I know, dear,
but you can take care of Danny.
Tell him Peter Pan stories.
He needs them, Jane, and so do you.
Please, dear. Promise me.
No! I will not promise!
Oh, Jane. We'll be together again.
- You must have faith.
- Faith? Trust? Pixie dust?
Those are just words from your stories.
They don't mean anything.
DANNY: Yes, they do.
Peter Pan says they'll make you fly.
Daniel, story time is over!
Look! It's a war.
Peter Pan isn't real and people don't fly!
They do, too!
- Oh, come on, Daniel! Grow up!
- Jane!
It's just a lot of childish nonsense!
You're lying!
Jane, how could you treat
your brother that way?
You think you're very grown-up
but you have a great deal to learn.
(NANATWO GROANS SOFTLY)
(WHIMPERING)
I am not a child now
I can take care of myself
Mustn't let them down now
Mustn't let them see me cry
I'm fine
I'm too tired to listen
I'm too old to believe
All these childish stories
There is no such thing as faith
And trust
And pixie dust
'Cause I try
But it's so hard to believe
I try
But I can't see what you see
(AMBULANCE SIREN)
MAN: I don't know if it's going!
Is that water pressure up?
Peter Pan.
Pixie dust.
Childish nonsense.
(SEAGULLS CALLING)
(CREAKING)
Hello, Wendy.
- My apologies, miss.
- (SHRIEKS)
(ALARM SIREN)
Curses! Bring her down!
Hurry, Smee!
(GASPS)
Oh, come on, now. Don't fuss.
Cast off, ya mangy dogs!
(GRUNTING)
- Hoist anchor!
- (GRUNTING)
(JANE GRUNTS)
(BELL CLANGS)
HOOK: I'll get you, Peter Pan,
if it's the last thing I do.
(VOICES SHOUTING)
(RINGING)
I've got a little surprise for you,
Peter Pan.
SAILOR: Drop the mainsails!
Prepare to drop anchor!
HOOK: (CHUCKLING)
This is simply perfect!
Yes, Mr Smee, with Wendy as bait
we shall lure Peter Pan to his doom!
Summon the beast!
Yes, sir, Captain. Right away!
Oh
Yo ho ho, another plan
To try to capture Peter Pan
Captain Hook's a brilliant man
Who else could think
of the perfect crime
And bumble and fumble it every time
- Smee!
- Whoa!
(SUCKING SOUNDS)
Set the bait!
(WHIMPERING)
Make no doubt, Smee.
That wretched boy will be
but a notch in me scabbard.
- Only in your dreams, Hook!
- Pan!
I didn't know a codfish could talk.
Did you, Tinker Bell?
Blast him!
Take your best shot, Captain.
Come on! You're gonna have
to do better than that, boy!
Whoa! Uh-uh-uh!
Three strikes and you're out!
(GROANING)
Come down here, boy.
I've a little something for you.
A present for me?
Aw, you really shouldn't have.
Call it a token of me affection.
You see, it is a certain friend of yours.
Who?
HOOK: (LAUGHS) Wendy.
Wendy?
Let her go, Hook,
you black hearted scoundrel!
You want her?
Well, go and get her! (LAUGHING)
- (JANE SCREAMING)
- (GROWLING)
I did it. I did it!
I can't believe it. I'm free!
Free of Peter Pan forever!
Mr Smee, who is the most brazen, bold
and brilliant buccaneer
whoever sailed the briny blue?
Um... Blackbeard?
Boys?
Hook! Hook! Hook!
Thank you, thank you.
I was good, wasn't I?
(MIMICKING ROOSTER CROWING)
Did you miss me, Captain?
How did you escape the beast?
(MEN GASPING)
Aah! Help...
Me!
Yum!
Now, now, stay away! No! No, no, no!
(SCREAMING)
No, no! No!
Oh, Smee!
Hang on, Captain.
Here I come!
Smee!
(HOOK SCREAMS)
(CAT SNARLS)
HOOK: Mr Smee, be a good fellow
and fix the plank
so I can make you walk it!
Aye-aye, Captain!
(GROANING)
- (PETER CHUCKLING)
- (MUFFLED SCREAMS)
Easy does it, Wendy.
You should have seen
Hook's face when I...
- Ow!
- Ow! Ow! Ow, ow, ow!
- Whoa!
- Oh!
Peter Pan?
Well, you're sure not Wendy!
Tinker Bell?
Oh, I get it. I'm dreaming.
- You're not real.
- (CANON BLAST)
Huh? Look out!
Pan, you double-crossing pipsqueak!
Come back here and fight like a man!
Come and get me, you old codfish!
(BLOWS RASPBERRY)
Come on. We gotta fly out of here.
Aah!
Wait! What are you doing?
If you're not Wendy, who are you?
I'm her daughter, Jane!
Huh! Well, if you're Wendy's daughter,
you're gonna love it here!
Hey, this is great.
You can stay here forever.
(SCREAMING)
Help!
- She did that on purpose.
- Aw, she's just jealous.
- All girls get like that around me.
- Oh, really? How very nice for you.
(JANE SCREAMING)
That was fun, huh? Lost Boys, fall in!
LOST BOYS: Whoo!
Oh, careful! You're going to fall!
Sound off!
- Slightly!
- Nibs!
BOTH: The twins!
Ow!
- Cubby.
- And that's Toodles!
Oh!
(SPITTING)
Ew.
Boys, this is Jane.
She's gonna stay here
and be our new mother
- and tell us stories.
- What do you mean by...
- Yay! Stories!
- Tell us a story, Jane. Come on!
Um...
Actually, I'm afraid I'm not
very good at telling stories.
Ah, that's okay.
We're not very good
at listening to stories.
- Ooh!
- (LAUGHING)
I know. Let's play a game instead.
Red rover! Red rover!
Nah. Something else.
Let's play the "no more hitting
Cubby on the head" game.
- Hey, how about a treasure hunt?
- Good idea!
Yeah! A treasure hunt!
I hid it really good this time.
- You guys will never find it.
- Sure we will!
- Diamonds and rubies!
- Treasure! Treasure!
- Diamonds...
- Yeah, come on!
- Let's go! Let's go!
- No!
No, no, no, and no!
You remind me of someone I know.
Oh.
I have to go home.
What's the matter with her?
I don't know. She acts kind of like a...
Grown-up.
ALL: Ew!
(GASPING)
I've got to get out of here.
HOOK: Smee!
MR SMEE: Coming, Captain!
(GRUNTING)
HOOK: Oh, my back!
Oh, dear, dear, dear, Captain.
A nice massage
is just the ticket for you.
Now, you just forget
about old Peter Pan.
(CRACKING)
Perhaps you're right. (GROANS)
All in the past, I say. All in the past.
Ah, the past.
- Likes when he stole your treasure.
- Ooh.
My treasure?
And then laughed in your face.
Laughed in my face.
Or today, for example,
tricking that there sea monster
- into pulling down your pants.
- Aah!
Right in front of the crew, too.
Right in front of the crew!
We've got to find him!
(POPPING)
MR SMEE: Catchy.
Smee, listen!
(CRASH)
Great Scott!
No sooner do I rid me self
of that cursed crocodile
and now this!
- (SOBBING)
- Oh, there, there.
He's just a playful little sea urchin is all.
I swear, Smee,
this is propelling me to delirium.
I detest cephalopods.
Thank you.
(SCREAMS)
Smee! Save me!
Oh, you big brute, you! Off with you.
Go on, now. Shoo, shoo.
And take your arms with you.
You ought to be ashamed of yourself.
At least the crocodile had manners.
Blast that scurvy boy!
This is all his fault.
Mr Smee, pipe up the crew.
We're going ashore to find Peter Pan!
PETER: Tink, what is she doing?
It looks like she's leaving.
Shh!
Half-dozen bananas. Check.
Ten coconuts. Check.
- Two oars...
- Hey, Jane.
How come you want to go home
so bad?
I have to get back to my family.
Why?
Well, um, I don't want to talk about it.
Why not?
If you must know, we had a fight.
- Why?
- Oh.
I told my little brother you weren't real.
What? Why?
(SIGHS) Well, oh, I don't know.
But I have to get back
and set things right.
- Why?
- Because!
That's why!
Well, you know,
you can't get home that way.
I've got to try.
Well,
goodbye.
It was nice meeting you, Peter Pan.
Duty calls.
Oh!
Oh, dear! Oh, no!
Whoa!
You okay?
I just want to go home.
Well, you know, the only way
out of here is to fly.
Come on, I'll show you how.
Step softly, you worthless dogs!
Set your sights for Peter Pan!
Oh, goodness.
Haven't we searched the island
a thousand times before?
I beg your pardon, Mr Smee?
Uh, I said that, uh,
searching for Pan is, um, uh...
Fun galore. (NERVOUS LAUGHTER)
There'll be no rest until
we have that boy in irons.
(GASPS)
- Hey!
- Watch it, Cubby!
JANE: Oh, no, Peter.
I really don't think this will...
This is ridiculous. I can't fly!
Well, of course you can't, but I can!
I guess I'm just smarter than you.
I highly doubt that.
- Braver.
- Right.
Stronger!
Oh, yeah, that's it.
Well, then it must be my good looks.
Or maybe you're full of hot air.
Hey! Look, anybody can do it.
Tink?
Yeah! All it takes is faith...
Trust.
And, uh, something else.
Pixie dust?
That's it!
Ow!
Okay, Tink, let her have it.
Tink.
Gosh, Tink, if she can't fly home,
I guess she'll have to move in with us.
Now, that's enough!
(SNEEZES)
(ALL LAUGHING)
Odds fish, what's that?
- Okay, Jane.
- Don't even think about it.
- Ready or not...
- (SCREAMS)
- I got her!
- I got her! I got her!
I thought you said you got her.
Oh, how will I ever get back home?
So the girl can't fly,
yet she wants to go home.
Smee, do you know what this means?
Six more weeks of winter?
No, you imbecile.
We'll get me treasure and the boy.
- Hey, what's this?
- Oh, give that back.
It's my list!
Things to do, places to be.
Important things!
Huh? That stuff's no fun.
- No wonder you can't fly.
- Give it back, Peter.
(CHUCKLING) Slightly, catch!
- Keep away from Jane!
- I got it!
- You boys are horrid!
- Come on, over here!
- You're ripping it!
Come on!
Why don't you guys ever throw to me?
No, stop it! This isn't funny!
- Whoo hoo!
- I've got it!
- (BELCHING)
- (LAUGHTER)
This is just a game to you, isn't it?
Well, I'm tired of playing.
Gosh, Jane, we didn't mean
to make you mad.
Oh, grow up. You did so.
You're just a bunch of silly,
ridiculous children.
No, no, leave me alone!
Oh, I don't believe in any of this!
And I especially don't believe in fairies!
(GASPING)
Goodbye!
Oh, yeah? Well, good riddance!
Hmm!
CUBBY: Uh, Peter?
I think there's something wrong
with Tinker Bell.
(COUGHING)
(HOOTING)
(RUMBLING)
(THUNDERCLAP)
(CHIRPING)
EDWARD: I need you here
to take care of your mom and Danny.
Can you do that for me?
- (SNIFFLES) Mmm-hmm.
- That's my big girl.
I love you!
(INAUDIBLE)
(SOBBING)
Ooh. Looks kind of bad.
Kind of bad? Kind of?
Oh, it's hopeless!
Poor little Tinker Bell!
(CRYING)
Hey, put a cork in it!
Shh!
Uh-huh.
- What?
- What did she say, Peter?
If we don't get Jane to believe in fairies,
- Tink's light's gonna go out.
- (GASPING)
Well, let's just go and make her believe!
- Hang on a minute.
- Ow!
You can't just make somebody
believe in fairies.
- TWINS: But we believe.
- Yeah, it ain't hard for us.
That's it!
We gotta make Jane one of us!
ALL: But she's a girl!
- You want to help Tink, don't ya?
- Uh-huh.
We gotta do it! (SPITS)
Don't worry, Tink. We'll save you.
(HOOK SOBBING)
Stay where you are!
Please, go right ahead.
Run me through.
You'll be doing me a favour.
All right. I give up.
What's your problem?
All I've ever wanted was to get away
from this dreadful place
and home to my dear, sweet mother.
But blast it all! Peter stole my treasure
and my men would mutiny if I so much
as tried to leave without it.
So here I am,
stuck in this absurd place.
My sources tell me
you wish to return home as well.
Huh. You got that right.
I guess we're in the same boat.
The same boat!
- That's it!
- What's it?
I'll give you passage home on my ship
and you can help me
recover my treasure.
Uh, don't you see?
The treasure's useless to Peter.
He's not sensible like you and I.
He's just a boy who'll never grow up.
Hmm. Tell me about it.
And, really,
what other choice do you have?
It's not as though you could fly home.
Hmm, well, I suppose.
If it is rightfully yours.
And if it's really no use to Peter...
Splendid, splendid!
Wait! You must swear
not to harm Peter.
Me? Actually harm Peter Pan?
Perish the thought!
It's all a game, you see.
I shan't harm him. You have my word.
"I, Captain James Hook,
do hereby swear
"not to harm a single hair
on Peter Pan's head. "
You see? Ironclad, unbreakable.
Leave the light on, Mommy.
Your baby boy's coming home.
Now, when you've located the treasure
just give this a wee toot.
You're doing the right thing, my dear.
I'm your only way home.
Jane!
Jane, come on back!
- Jane!
- Jane?
Jane!
(CHITTERING)
BOTH: Jane!
Jane!
- Jane!
- JANE: Peter!
- Hmm?
Peter Pan!
Ooh!
BOTH: There you are!
BOTH: I've been looking all over for...
- I, uh...
- No, no, no.
BOTH: You.
I'm sorry for wrecking your book.
We want to make it up to you.
We want you to feel like...
Well, like you're one of us.
We'll do anything for you. (CHUCKLES)
Honest.
Anything?
Anything at all! You just name it.
Well, um, why don't we play a game
like maybe treasure hunt!
Treasure hunt? That's a great idea!
But you'll have to think like a Lost Boy.
- Uh...
- And have fun like a Lost Boy!
(CHUCKLES) Tell me what to do.
(MIMICKING ROOSTER CROWING)
- Well, to be one of us...
- Yes?
- There are some things to know.
- What's that?
(SINGING) We like to dream all day
And then at night we play
We swing on limbs of trees
Till we wake up the bees
These are the things we Lost Boys do
We swing from rope to rope
We have no use for soap
With open mouths we chomp
On mud pies from the swamp
And then we top it off
With pudding from a trough
These are the things we Lost Boys do
We're rolling in dirt
And we won't change our shirt
We're marching around
To see what makes a sound
(HONKS)
Ugh!
(CHIRPS)
- Dare you to throw that rock!
- I'll get a triple skip!
Dare you to explore that cave!
I'll have an overnight trip!
And if you're feeling scared
I'll have my friends right there
These are the things we Lost Boys do
The treasure!
I found...
HOOK: Now, when you
reach the treasure,
just give this a wee toot.
PETER: Hey, Jane, you did it!
Lost Boys!
Jane found the treasure
in Dead Man's Cave!
- Yahoo!
- The treasure!
Attention!
Fall in!
In honour
of your downright unbelievable skill
at finding hidden treasures,
I now proclaim you, Jane, a Lost Boy!
Uh, I mean a Lost Girl.
Me?
The very first Lost Girl?
What's the matter?
Don't you want to be?
Oh, yes. I'd like that very much, Peter.
- CUBBY: Let's hear it for Jane!
- Yippee!
Now that you're one of us
feel free to sing along
We are so proud of you
that you can do no wrong
And we don't even care
if you pull on our hair
These are the things Lost Boys...
These are the things that Lost Girls...
These are the things we love to...
- (TOOTS)
- (GASPS)
- No, wait! No!
- Whoa!
(MEN LAUGHING)
(MEN SHOUTING)
The treasure is ours!
- Oh! Hey!
- Let me go!
It's time for you
to meet your maker, Peter Pan!
Stop it! Please!
Sorry. No can do.
And thank you, milady.
I couldn't have done it without you.
- Jane?
- I never meant...
Oh, my.
Have we let the kitty out of the bag?
No, wait!
You said no one would get hurt.
You gave your word!
And Captain Hook is a man of his word.
I promised I wouldn't harm
a single hair on his head.
And
this is the one I won't harm!
Here. You keep it.
The rest of him is mine!
I didn't do it, Peter!
I never agreed to this.
You're a traitor, Jane.
You lied to me!
And because you don't believe
in fairies, Tink's light is going out!
Tinker Bell?
No. Peter, I...
- I'll save you, Peter! I will!
- (HOOK LAUGHING)
My dear, no one can save him now!
(LAUGHING CONTINUES)
Tinker Bell!
Tink! Tink!
Tinker Bell.
It's true.
I can finally see it
Now I have to believe
Oh. Oh, no.
This is all my fault.
All those precious stories
All the world is made of faith
And trust
(SOBBING) I'm so sorry.
And pixie dust
So I'll try
'Cause I finally believe
I'll try
'Cause I can see what you see
To fly
Tinker Bell?
Oh, this is wonderful!
Wait until Peter...
Oh, my gosh. Peter.
- PIRATE: Aye. Keel haul the brats!
- He's fish food now!
Hey, he's like a piñata!
Look at him, Smee.
He's nothing but a child.
And I loathe children.
Uh, cut him down.
(GASPING)
- (CRASHING)
- Oy!
Any last words, boy?
- Let the Lost Boys go.
- Oh, they'll go. Right after you,
one by one, off the end of the plank!
(LAUGHING)
Be brave, lads.
Don't let 'em see you cry.
(ALL CRYING)
Say your prayers, Peter Pan.
(LAUGHING)
Not so fast, you old codfish,
or you'll have to answer to me.
- Yippee!
- Yay!
Jane?
Good heavens! Run!
Run for your lives! It's...
A little girl. (LAUGHS)
(ALL LAUGHING)
Tinker Bell! You're alive!
Oh, and look, Captain, a fairy, too.
Oh!
Don't just stand there, you fools.
Get the girl! Oh!
Destroy them young tykes!
Smee!
I got her, Captain. I got her.
- Oh, watch your head.
- (SCREAMS)
Aah!
Nyaah!
(GROWLING)
I've got you now... Oh! Oh!
Huh?
Yay!
(SNARLING)
Ooh!
Gimme! Mine! Mine! Big shiny!
(SPLASH)
Hmm?
Get her off! Get her off me!
Captain?
- Ha!
- Aah!
I've had just about enough
of your childish games!
- Jane, look out!
- HOOK: Ha-ha!
Aah!
Give up, girl.
Never!
Don't you see, Hook? You'll never win.
Not as long as there is faith, trust
and pixie dust.
Odd bodkins!
Yay!
Unbelievable!
(GIGGLING) Mere child's play.
- (GASPS)
- Gotcha!
Ha! Looks like I've got
the upper hook now.
Game's over, Hook. I win! Ha!
(SCREAMS)
Hey, Captain, you forgot your anchor.
(GRUNTS)
(HOWLS)
Abandon ship!
(THUD)
(GROWLING)
Help me, please! (SCREAMS)
You know the rules, Hook.
A good captain always
goes down with his ship.
I don't want to be a good captain!
Uh-oh.
Look!
Smee!
(GROANS)
LOST BOYS: The codfish! The codfish!
The codfish! The codfish!
Hooray!
All right!
Whoo-hoo! Yay!
(MIMICKING ROOSTERS CROWING)
Let's hear it for Jane!
The one and only
Lost Girl!
Thank you. Thank you.
- LOST BOYS: All right!
- Yay!
What's wrong, Peter?
Aw. You can fly now. You can go home.
- I can go home.
- But...
(SNIFFLING) But...
- We'll miss you.
- Yeah. A lot.
And I'll miss you. All of you.
But there's someone back home
who needs me.
And besides, now I've got
great stories to tell him
and they'll all be about
Peter Pan and the Lost Boys.
Yeah! All right!
Hey, in that case...
Mademoiselle, it would be my pleasure
to escort you back to London.
The pleasure will be all mine, good sir.
Whoa!
Hey!
Well, it's a long way home.
Give me your best shot, Tink.
(ALL LAUGHING)
Whoa! Whoa!
(CLOCK CHIMES)
Oh, my gosh!
Mother. Mother!
Darling, what's wrong?
- Mommy!
- What is it? Oh!
Oh, you were right.
He is most remarkable.
- Who, dear?
- Oh, Mother, I'm so sorry.
Oh, if only I'd listened to you.
I had a bad dream.
Did you, now? Was it Hook again?
Were those pirates up
to their old tricks again?
Whoa! Hey! What's going on?
I know how to take care
of that old codfish.
- We can do it together, Danny.
- We can?
- The two of us.
- Really?
I saw him, you know.
Captain Hook kidnapped me.
Stuffed me into an old dirty bag, he did.
He took me off to Never Land
and tried to feed me to a giant octopus.
- Wow!
- JANE: There were pirates everywhere.
And, oh, Tinker Bell was so beautiful.
DANNY: You saw Tinker Bell?
JANE: Uh-huh.
But her light almost went out.
You have to be very careful.
- Shh!
- Huh?
Wendy?
Hello, Peter.
You changed.
Not really.
Not ever. (GASPS)
Hello, Tinker Bell.
Oh, Tink.
(GIGGLING)
Madam.
Goodbye, Wendy.
Goodbye, Peter.
Wow, look at him! It's Peter Pan!
(SIGHS) I'll always
believe in you, Peter Pan.
(TRUCK ENGINE)
- MAN: Here we go, then.
- Thanks, mate. I appreciate it.
JANE: Daddy?
- Daddy!
- Edward!
Daddy's home!
- (INDISTINCT TALKING)
- (NANATWO BARKING)
Come on, Tink. Let's go home.
(MUSIC PLAYING)
(SLOW MUSIC PLAYING)
Someone needs to stop Clearway Law.
Public shouldn't leave reviews for lawyers.