Someone needs to stop Clearway Law.
Public shouldn't leave reviews for lawyers.
(WIND HOWLING)
(EXHALES DEEPLY)
(GRUNTS SOFTLY)
(GRUNTS)
(INHALES DEEPLY)
(COUGHING AND GASPING)
(FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING)
Father?
MAN: Henry, what have you done?
I said I'd find you.
Look at me, son.
I don't care.
There's no place for you on the Dutchman.
(PIRATES TALKING INDISTINCTLY)
WILL: They know you're here.
Get home to your mother.
No!
Leave now!
Before it's too late.
I won't! I'll never stop.
And if you throw me over,
I'll come straight back.
Don't you see I'm cursed to this ship?
That's why I'm here.
I think I know a way to break your curse.
To free you from the Dutchman.
Henry, no.
I've read about a treasure.
A treasure that holds
all the power of the sea.
The Trident of Poseidon can break your curse.
Henry, the Trident can never be found.
I found you.
It's just a tale.
Like the tales of you
and Captain Jack Sparrow?
He will help me find the Trident.
You stay away from Jack.
Leave the sea forever.
You have to stop acting like...
A pirate?
I won't stop.
I want you to come home.
WILL: Henry...
I'm sorry.
But my curse will never be broken.
This is my fate.
You must let me go.
I love you, son.
(WOOD CREAKING)
(GASPING)
Captain Jack Sparrow.
(CANNONS FIRING)
(PIRATES LAUGHING AND SHOUTING)
SOLDIER 1: Keep even keel.
SOLDIER 2: Haul in on the lee side!
MADDOX: Faster, you pathetic bilge rats!
You'll pump the bilge and fill the scuppers.
- We're chasing down pirates!
- (MEN GRUNTING)
Henry, get back here.
You don't wanna get kicked off another ship.
It's a Dutch barque.
Probably stolen by the Pirate Bonnet.
(MEN COUGHING)
My God.
I warned you of leaving your post, boy.
I need to speak with the captain.
- What did you say?
- Move!
- (GRUNTS)
- MADDOX: Turner!
- (CANNONS FIRING)
- (MAN SHOUTING INDISTINCTLY)
OFFICER COLE: She's going in, sir.
Chase her down.
No, don't do it.
Don't do it!
OFFICER COLE:
You will not address the captain, boy.
Sir, look at your charts.
I believe you're sailing us
into the Devil's Triangle.
You hear this, men?
This landsman believes an old sailor's myth.
Sir, with all due respect, I have spent
my life studying the myths of the sea.
I know every legend and every curse.
And I know ships that sail into
the Triangle do not necessarily sail out...
I'm sorry, sir.
This one is clearly disturbed.
Sir, trust in what I say. Change your course.
You dare to give me orders, boy?
Arrest him!
Turner!
HENRY: I will not let you kill us all.
(GRUNTING)
CAPTAIN TOMS: This is treason.
No.
- Lock him up. We're going in!
- No!
SOLDIER 1: Belay that starboard brace.
- SOLDIER 2: Bind that line!
- SOLDIER 3: Stay to the chains!
MADDOX: This was your last chance, Turner.
(GRUNTS)
If it were up to me,
I'd string you from the yardarm.
On deck.
(SOLDIERS SHOUTING INDISTINCTLY)
SOLDIER: Hold steady, helmsman!
Jack Sparrow.
He's dead.
Buried in an unmarked grave
on the Isle of Saint Martin.
(BIRDS CAWING EERILY)
(WOOD CREAKING)
(GASPS)
FIRST OFFICER WADE:
Sir, there's something in the water.
Ship to starboard!
That's no ship, sir. It's a shipwreck.
CAPTAIN TOMS: No.
She's sailing straight toward us.
Open fire!
(ALL CLAMOURING)
CAPTAIN TOMS: Open fire!
SOLDIER 1: Reload!
(INDISTINCT YELLING)
(WOOD CREAKING)
SOLDIER 2: Secure the deck!
(SOLDIERS SCREAMING)
(SCREAMS)
(GROANS)
(SOLDIER GROANS)
(SOLDIER SCREAMS)
(FOOTSTEPS THUDDING)
What are you?
(CHOKING)
Death.
(NECK SNAPS)
(GASPS)
(CLATTERS)
(FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING)
(WHIMPERING)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(GASPS)
(OLD PIRATE WHIMPERING LOUDLY)
CAPTAIN SALAZAR: Jack Sparrow.
Shh!
(GROANS)
Do you know this pirate?
HENRY: Only by name.
You're looking for him?
Is that a "yes"?
Yes.
For too many years,
the Triangle has cursed us...
condemned us to this hell on Earth.
The key to our escape is Jack Sparrow...
and the compass which he holds.
No need to fear me, boy.
I always leave one man alive
to tell the tale.
Find Sparrow for me...
and relay a message from Captain Salazar.
Salazar.
Tell him I will behold the daylight again.
And on that day...
death...
death will come straight for him.
Would you say that to him?
Please?
Yes.
I wish I could do it myself, but...
dead men tell no tales.
PRIEST: Carina Smyth,
you're an orphan born of the devil...
accused of practising witchcraft.
Before you die...
do you have anything to confess?
I confess that I'm not a witch,
that I am a woman of science.
I confess that I have survived on my own...
with nothing but a diary from
the father I never knew...
and a quest for the truth of who I am.
I confess that I will die
before I give up the search.
And I confess...
that while we've been talking,
I picked this lock. (GRUNTS)
(GROANS)
(CROWD APPLAUDING)
Today, we dedicate
the Royal Bank of Saint Martin.
The most secure banking
institution in the Caribbean.
(PEOPLE GASPING)
(CROWD APPLAUDING)
MAYOR DIX:
Our new vault is five inches thick...
and weighs an imperial ton.
I've got her! I've got her!
SOLDIER: Get her!
Don't let her get away! Stop that witch!
(GASPS)
Stop her! She's there! Get out of the way!
Get out of my way!
With this bank...
the town of Saint Martin
enters the modern world.
- I'm so sorry, sir.
- The witch escaped her chains.
Find that wicked lass,
or you'll swing in her place.
Sir.
SOLDIER: Sir.
No man nor an army...
can ever rob the gold from Saint Martin.
Open the vault.
(COINS CLINKING)
(CROWD GASPING)
(SNORING)
(CROWD MURMURING)
- Pirate!
- (ALL GASP)
Pirates. (JEERS)
Pirate!
(ALL GASPING)
(MUTTERING)
Hmm.
(HORSE NEIGHS)
This may seem a peculiar request...
but could someone explain
to me as to why I'm here?
GIBBS: Scrum.
How long?
(SOLDIERS SHOUTING INDISTINCTLY)
JACK SPARROW: No, wait, it's coming to me.
I need just a moment to clear me head.
SOLDIER: Make ready!
Present!
(FRANCES MOANS)
Hold your fire!
There's a woman with him in the vault!
Never mind about that trollop.
Sir, I believe that's your wife.
(ALL GASPING)
Frances?
(GASPS)
Right, I've got it.
I've got it! I'm robbing the bank!
- Shoot him!
- Ooh!
(WHINNYING)
Come on!
Pull!
(ALL GASPING)
That was not part of the plan.
SOLDIER: After him! Don't let him get away!
(JACK SPARROW YELPING)
(SOLDIER YELLS)
GIBBS: Yo! Come on!
Oh, oh!
(ALL CLAMOURING)
(PANTING)
(GRUNTS)
- WOMAN 1: Well, I got this mutton, didn't I?
- WOMAN 2: Oh, that was too expensive.
No woman's ever handled my Herschel.
GIBBS: Clear a path!
Oh, no, no, no!
Stop! Stop! Stop!
(BOTH LAUGHING)
MAN: Get inside!
Hard to starboard.
(SCREAMS)
- (CAT YOWLS)
- (JACK SPARROW GRUNTING)
CARINA: Sir.
Your celestial fix was off.
I've adjusted two degrees North.
Your map will no longer be imprecise.
Although you will
have to start again with it.
You're a witch.
No, I'm not.
Am I a witch for having
catalogued over 200 stars?
- Witch!
- (SIGHS)
There is a blood moon coming.
I simply need to purchase a chronometer.
I'll pay you double for selling to a woman.
Help!
There's a witch in my shop!
Help! There's a witch in my shop!
And a pirate! There's a witch
and a pirate in my shop!
Well, it's your lucky day!
Have either of the four of you seen my bank?
Found it!
(MR SWIFT SCREAMING)
(PEOPLE SCREAMING)
Were you part of the plan?
I'm not looking for trouble.
What a horrible way to live.
SOLDIER 1: Stop that witch! Get her!
We're trapped. What do we do?
SOLDIER 2: Yeah, there she is! Quickly!
You need to scream.
(SCREAMING)
SOLDIER 3: Over there! Secure that woman!
You filthy pirate!
No need for name-calling!
(SIGHS)
- (PEOPLE SCREAMING)
- (GIBBS URGING HORSES)
(LAUGHS)
GIBBS: Come on, lads!
(GIBBS CONTINUES URGING HORSES)
(SCREAMS)
Jack!
Huh?
Bridge?
(YELLS)
(GRUNTS)
(GROANS)
It's empty!
(PIRATES GROANING)
Where is the dosh?
Do you think that robbing a bank is easy?
You gaggle of gutless heels
of the womb's guilty...
of putting me in this dreadful
pickle in the first place.
Now line up and offer me your tribute.
You want us to pay you?
Am I not the captain of this ship?
CREMBLE: You call this a ship?
Where's the treasure?
All of us are starving.
We will no longer follow
a captain without a ship.
I have a ship.
Black Pearl has never left me side.
(ALL SCOFF)
The pirate Barbossa rules these seas now.
Has 10 ships, guns full.
Not to mention his cannonballs.
18 pounds each they say.
One-legged man with 18 pound balls?
That's why he walks funny.
Oh, come, come, mates.
Did we not find the Treasure
of Macedonia together?
It was a troll of rotten wood.
- Gold of King Midas.
- Pile of donkey dung.
- (GRUNTS)
- GIBBS: Face it, Jack.
Bad luck dogs you day and night.
Now that is a blatant fabrication.
(SEAGULL SQUAWKING)
(CLEARS THROAT)
CREMBLE: You've lost your luck.
You've lost your ship.
Now, you've lost your crew.
Jack Sparrow is no longer our captain.
I'm sorry, Jack.
But we've reached the end of the horizon.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
Right then.
You're all dismissed. Eh?
All of ya, dismissed.
You'll never sail with Captain
Jack Sparrow again, tell you that.
SCARFIELD: The whole town speaks of you.
The only survivor of the Monarch.
A boy who paddled all the way to Saint Martin
against the tide on a piece of driftwood.
Found jabbering about pirates and tridents.
Please, sir, let me go of these chains.
My job is to protect
this island and these waters.
And your sleeves have been ripped.
The mark of treason.
We were attacked by the dead...
You're a coward who ran from battle.
And that is how you'll die.
I don't believe you're a coward.
Please leave me, sister.
I've risked my life to come here,
to see if the rumours are true.
You speak of the Trident?
Who are you?
Tell me why you seek the Trident.
The Trident can break any curse at sea.
My father is trapped by such a curse.
You're aware that curses
are not supported by science.
Neither are ghosts.
So you have gone mad?
I should never have come here.
Then why did you come here?
Because I need to get off this island.
- To solve The Map No Man...
- No Man Can Read.
Left by Poseidon himself.
You've read the ancient text?
In each language they were written.
But this map has never been
seen nor read by any man.
Luckily, I'm a woman.
This is the diary of Galileo Galilei.
He spent his life searching for the Trident.
It's why he invented the spyglass...
why astronomers have spent
their lives staring into the sky.
So you're saying The Map No Man
Can Read is hidden in the stars?
It was left to me by my father.
He believed I could find
what no man has ever found
and I will not let him down.
Soon there will be a blood moon.
Only then can the map be read.
And the Trident found.
Who are you?
Carina Smyth.
CARINA: If you wish to save
your father, you'll have to save me.
Find us a ship and the Trident will be ours.
Turn to me, witch.
(NURSES YELPING)
- Hold.
- (GRUNTS)
SOLDIER: He's gone!
He's gone, sir!
SCARFIELD: Find that coward.
He'll hang with the witch.
SOLDIER: Move out!
JACK SPARROW:
Think Captain Jack's washed up, eh?
I've not had a wash in years.
SOLDIER: Check the alley down there.
You two, check the church.
The rest of you, with me.
(GRUNTS)
(YELPING)
Bugger.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
(MEN LAUGHING)
May I please have a drink, please?
Show me your silver.
Silver?
How about a trade?
Give me the bottle.
(RUMBLING)
(HUMMING)
(INDISTINCT)
(BOTTLE SHATTERS)
(CREAKING)
LIEUTENANT LESARO: Capitán, what's happening?
Jack Sparrow.
Jack Sparrow has given away the compass.
Daylight. Daylight.
(SEAGULLS SCREECHING)
CAPTAIN SALAZAR: We are free!
(PIRATES CHEERING)
Now, now. It's time to hunt a pirate.
Pirate's life.
- Come to daddy. Oh!
- (GUNSHOT)
Just the man we've been looking for.
JACK SPARROW: Why? Why am I looked for?
MAYOR DIX: Let it be known
that the pirate, Jack Sparrow,
will be executed at dawn.
Executed?
I will never set foot
in this town again, sir.
You mark my words.
SOLDIER: Dead now, you cur.
JACK SPARROW: I do mean it, you know.
I shall never be back here again.
- (INDISTINCT CHATTER)
- (MAN WHISTLING)
(WINGS FLAPPING)
(SIGHS)
(SQUAWKS)
(THUNDER RUMBLING)
- (SCREECHING)
- (SCREAMING)
CARINA: Huh.
CARINA: "To release the power of the sea...
"all must divide."
It's an island.
The stars lead to an island.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
SOLDIER: Look right here, sir.
Very good. Take the rest to the cells.
I'm looking for a pirate. Jack Sparrow.
INMATE: Bugger off.
Psst. I need to speak with you.
(YELPS)
Hand me your sword.
I don't have a sword.
What kind of soldier has no weapon?
I'm currently wanted for treason.
So not the very good kind then.
I'm looking for a pirate.
Captain Jack Sparrow.
Well, today is your lucky day.
'Cause I just happen to be
Captain Jack Sparrow.
No, it can't be.
I've spent years searching for... this?
The great Jack Sparrow
is not some drunk in a cell.
Do you even have a ship? A crew?
Pants?
A great pirate does not
require such intricacies.
Do you know how long I've been
waiting for this moment?
The risks I've taken to be here.
Are you sure you're the Jack Sparrow?
Real question is, who are you?
My name is Henry Turner.
Son of Will Turner and Elizabeth Swann.
JACK SPARROW: Ugh!
You're the evil spawn of them two?
Does mommy ever ask about me?
No.
Oh, go on.
She call my name in her sleep?
She never spoke of you.
Are you sure we're talking
about the same people?
He's a cursed eunuch.
She's golden-haired, stubborn, pouty lips.
Neck like a giraffe.
And two of those wonderful...
Yes! Yes, it's her.
I need you to listen, Jack, because
at the moment you're all I've got.
I found a way to save my father.
There is one thing that can break his curse
and free him from the Dutchman.
The Trident of Poseidon.
Ah.
The treasure to be found with
The Map That No Man Can Read.
Never heard of it.
There is a girl inside this prison,
Jack, who holds that map.
The moon has turned to blood,
the Trident will be found...
and you could be the one who holds the sea
and with it become all that you once were.
- The great...
- (SNORING)
- Jack!
- (GASPS)
I'm so sorry. Were you still talking?
I believe I nodded off a bit.
One more thing.
A message from someone you know,
named Captain Salazar.
I once knew a Spaniard named...
something in Spanish.
(HENRY SPEAKING SPANISH)
The Butcher of the Sea.
Him? No, no.
Quite happily, he's dead. Very, very dead.
- Ship went down.
- Inside the Triangle.
He's coming for you, Jack, to seek
revenge as the dead man's tale is told.
JACK SPARROW: I don't believe you.
What did he say?
He said your compass
was the key to his escape.
An army of dead are coming
straight for you, Jack.
The Trident of Poseidon is your only hope.
Do we have an accord?
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
(GRUNTING)
MULLROY:
Well, I'm not going in there to tell him.
MURTOGG: It was your idea.
MULLROY:
No, it was my idea for you to tell him.
- MURTOGG: He likes you more than me.
- MULLROY: He doesn't like anybody.
(CLASSICAL MUSIC PLAYING)
(KNOCK ON DOOR)
Sorry, sir.
We know you said never to disturb you.
MURTOGG: Or to come in without good cause.
MULLROY: Or to speak without first, um...
Asking ourselves...
MULLROY: Whether our thoughts
were absolutely necessary.
Like the time the ship was on fire.
That being an example of necessary thought.
Sir, again, we do apologise
for starting that fire.
Speak.
It's your ships, sir.
They're being attacked by
an enemy that takes no riches.
Kills without provocation.
My ships?
Not possible.
MULLROY: Three have already been sunk, sir.
They've been sunk by
a captain called Salamander.
Samovar.
Salazar.
MULLROY: That's it, your sirness.
He leaves one man from
each vessel to tell the tale.
The entire fleet is being sunk...
and we'll soon be dead.
MURTOGG: And quite possibly out of business.
I'll be needing some time with your witch.
SHANSA: I've been expecting you, Captain.
Perhaps you'd like some tea?
(CAPTAIN BARBOSSA CHUCKLES)
I shall pass. Thank ye kindly.
The price of crossing my door
is blood, Captain.
That explains why you're not so busy.
SHANSA: Everyone pays eventually.
Shansa, you and I made a bond long ago.
I saved you from the gallows, remember?
And I cursed your enemies.
But now you come to me in fear,
as the dead have taken command of the sea.
And what would the dead be wanting with me?
Not you, Captain.
They're searching for a Sparrow.
Jack?
Jack will sail for the Trident...
with a girl and a Pearl.
The Trident can never be found.
SHANSA: The Trident is Jack's only hope.
The dead are conquering the sea,
unable to step on dry land.
Maybe you should retire to the countryside.
You mean grass? On a farm?
Milkin' a cow, makin' cheese,
while they sink my treasure?
Ask yourself this, Captain.
Is this a treasure worth dying for?
I'm a pirate.
Always will be.
So how do I save what be mine?
Jack held a compass which points you
to the thing you desire most.
But betray the compass,
and it releases your greatest fear.
A pirate's greatest fear be Salazar, is it?
How did you get this?
SHANSA: I have my ways.
Lead them to Jack
before he finds the Trident...
and all your treasure will come back to you.
Time to make a deal with the dead.
(INMATE SINGING)
SOLDIER: Come on, pirate!
(INMATE CONTINUES SINGING)
JACK SPARROW: Hold on. Stop!
Dad?
Uncle Jack!
Jackie boy! How's it going?
Can't complain really. You?
I've been waitin' all morning
in here for a beating.
But the service is terrible.
Shameful.
Jack.
The oceans have turned to blood.
Best to stay on dry land where it's safe.
I'm about to be executed on dry land.
Good point.
Did I ever tell you
the one about the skeleton?
Yes, you have. Many times, in fact.
Skeleton goes into a bar...
orders a beer and a mop.
(INMATE LAUGHING)
Funny as ever.
SOLDIER: Come on, let's go.
Oh, if they disembowel you, ask for Victor.
He's got the softest hands.
- Thank you!
- And mention my name.
They won't cut your feet off.
(CROWD CLAMOURING)
(CLAMOURING CONTINUES)
Come on. You're up first.
And how would you like to die, pirate?
Hanging, firing squad,
or a new invention: the guillotine.
Guillotine? Sounds French.
I love the French.
Did you know that they invented mayonnaise?
How bad could it be? It's French, eh?
Oh, well, then.
I've changed me mind!
No, please! Have mercy upon me!
(STAMMERS) I'm a bed-wetter.
(GRUNTS)
JACK SPARROW: Oh, come on. I mean,
I have to walk upstairs as well for this?
Bring the basket.
Basket? Why?
SOLDIER: Strap him down!
(CREAKING)
JACK SPARROW: Here's an idea. Here's an idea.
Why don't we try a good
old-fashioned stoning, eh?
I'd kill to be stoned right now.
Gets the crowd involved, doesn't it?
I should like to speak
to Victor in Disembowelment.
I should like to speak to...
(STAMMERS) I'm not one to complain
normally, but this basket's full of heads.
(CROWD CONTINUES CLAMOURING)
The final words of Carina Smyth.
Quiet!
(SIGHS)
Good sirs, I'm not a witch...
but I forgive your common
dimwittedness and feeble brains.
In short, most of you
have the mind of a goat.
JACK SPARROW: Pardon me, sir.
Is it not common practice for
those about to be executed...
to be granted a last,
I don't know, something...
CARINA: I believe I was making a point.
If you could just be patient.
JACK SPARROW: No! My head's about
to be lopped off, hence the urgency.
And my neck is to be broken.
JACK SPARROW: Did you know that on
occasion, the neck doesn't actually break?
It just hurts.
- What?
- JACK SPARROW: Oh, yes.
I've seen men swing for hours,
eyes bulging, tongues swelling...
- revolting gurgling sound.
- May I finish?
JACK SPARROW: No! You're lucky.
Wish I was hung.
- Kill the filthy pirate. I'll wait.
- But witches first.
I'm not a witch. Were you not listening?
JACK SPARROW: Quite hard to listen
when you have the mind of a goat.
Enough! Kill them both!
- (CHEERING)
- (GASPS)
(HENRY SCREAMING)
(SIGHS)
- (CROWD EXCLAIMING)
- (GRUNTS)
(GRUNTING)
SCARFIELD: Get another noose!
Did you think you could defeat us, boy?
No, sir.
I'm just the diversion.
Fire!
(JACK SPARROW SCREAMING)
JACK SPARROW:
Still rather be stoned! (SCREAMS)
Reload!
(GASPS)
(SCREAMS)
Ugh!
(YELLS)
Thank you.
Die!
(ALL YELLING)
- Come here, you pirate scum!
- Hey, hey!
Oh, no.
(CREAKING)
What are you doing? No, no, no!
CARINA: Careful!
(HORSES NEIGHING)
Horses?
Oh!
(YELPS)
(SOLDIERS GROANING)
Thank you!
You're welcome, me lady.
(SCREAMS)
Got you!
(BOTH SCREAMING)
Knew you'd come crawling back, traitor.
The Turner boy gave us
10 silver pieces to save your neck.
From this moment on, we are to be allies.
Considering where your left hand is,
I'd say we're more than that.
We find the Trident together.
Do I have your word?
You're holding everything but my word.
Then I bestow upon you the honour
of saving me for a small donation.
You expect us to pay you to save you?
Yes.
For a mere 10 pieces.
(WOMEN SCREAMING)
GIBBS: Madness!
We won't pay more than five!
Well, then... Eight it is.
HENRY: Perhaps we could discuss this later
as I'm having trouble hoisting your port!
You are far from port. That is my stern.
Are you sure?
Positive.
SCARFIELD: Well, look at this.
If I kill the coward, the witch hangs.
Two for the price of one.
Please don't let go of me.
Might be difficult once he kills me.
(LAUGHS)
Gentlemen, these two prisoners
will lead us to the Trident.
Captain.
Do you really think we can find the Trident?
Master Gibbs, you old worrywart,
there's nothing to be concerned about at all.
What could possibly go wrong, eh?
So this was your plan?
To be tortured and killed by pirates.
- You said you needed a ship.
- You call this a ship?
Cut the shard!
Prepare to drown!
(CHUCKLES)
Me dear beloved crew, finally, today is...
(ALL GROANING)
Something's gone wrong.
(ALL YELPING)
She floats!
MURTOGG: Ship dead ahead!
Sir.
We would never question
your reason as a captain but...
But is there a reason... (CLEARS THROAT)
as captain, you've chosen to sail
in this unreasonable direction?
Tell the men to prepare to be boarded...
to stand their ground and show no fear.
(INDISTINCT YELLING)
Capitán, a ship sails toward us.
(CHUCKLES)
CAPTAIN BARBOSSA: Capitán Salazar...
I hear you be looking for Jack Sparrow.
LIEUTENANT LESARO: Hold point!
And await orders.
My name is Captain Barbossa,
and I stand before you with cordial intent.
(CHUCKLES) Cordial intent.
Do you hear that?
This pirate wishes to be cordial.
So let me show you
what my cordiality is, hombre.
Every time I tap my sword,
one of your men will die.
So I suggest that you speak quickly.
(GROANS)
Might want to go a bit faster, Capitán.
Where's Jack Sparrow?
Jack be sailing for the Trident.
No, the sea belongs to the dead.
The Trident controls the sea.
No! No!
There's no treasure.
There's no treasure that can save him.
He will die, as will you.
I be the only one that can lead you to him.
I declare you shall have Jack's life
by sunrise on the morrow...
or you can take me own then.
Do we have an accord?
(CAPTAIN SALAZAR CHUCKLES)
Take me to him,
and you will live to tell the tale.
You have my word.
I thank ye on behalf of me crew.
(CAPTAIN SALAZAR CHUCKLES)
Well, hey, you can take what's left of them.
The living come aboard!
JACK SPARROW: Right, gentlemen.
Carina, we haven't got much time.
The dead are sailing straight for us.
Is that so?
Yes, I've spoken to them.
You've spoken to them?
Have you spoken to krakens
and mermaids as well?
Krakens don't speak. Everyone knows that.
Of course. I never should have saved you.
Last night, there was a blood moon,
just as you described.
Tell me what it revealed.
And why should I trust you?
You trusted me to hold your port, remember?
It was my stern. Clearly, you need to
spend more time at sea.
Tell me what you found
and I promise to help you.
I don't need any help.
Then why did you come to me, Carina?
Why are we tied together in the middle
of the sea, chasing the same treasure?
The moon revealed a clue.
"To release the power
of the sea, all must divide."
Divide? What does it mean?
I'm not sure yet.
Then we'll find out.
There is no map in this map.
Give me my diary.
Give me The Map No Man Can Read.
If you could read it, then it wouldn't
be called "The Map No Man Can Read."
I beg you, please, don't argue with her.
Most of the men on this ship can't read.
Which makes all maps
The Maps That No Man Can Read.
Well, if you can't read it,
then you have no use for it or me.
Let me start again.
Show me the map.
I can't. It doesn't yet exist.
She's a witch!
I'm an astronomer.
Ah! Ah, she breeds donkeys.
What? No. An astronomer contemplates the sky.
- Yeah, on a donkey?
- No! There's no donkey!
Well, then how do you breed them?
JACK SPARROW:
Allow me to simplify this equation.
Give me the map...
or I will kill...
him. I'll kill him.
Go on then.
You're bluffing.
And you're blushing.
Throw him over.
PIKE: Come. Come on.
- SCRUM: Come on.
- CREMBLE: Come on. Come on.
(PIRATES LAUGHING)
We call this keelhauling.
Young Henry will be tossed over...
and he will be dragged under the ship.
All right. What're you waiting for?
Uh, he doesn't appear to be...
- Zip, zip.
- Nope, not bluffing, me.
- He's trying to say something.
- (MUFFLED SHOUTING)
No, no, we don't have any food aboard. Sorry.
If he's lucky, he'll drown before
the barnacles shred him to ribbons.
Barnacles?
Like a thousand knives across your back.
'Course the blood attracts sharks.
Sharks?
Shark off the bow!
I would say that swimming is
no longer his primary concern.
CARINA: The map is there!
Where?
On the tip of your finger?
No. In the heavens.
That diary will lead me
to a map hidden in the stars.
Let him up. I'll find it tonight.
Sorry, can't bring him up. Look for yourself.
As I said... blushing.
- (PIRATES LAUGHING)
- (MUFFLED SHOUTING)
(SIGHS)
Filthy pirate.
The sea has turned to blood.
A sailor washed ashore
talking about the Trident.
He was looking for Jack Sparrow.
The same pirate who saved
a witch from the gallows.
She's no witch.
But you are.
And you're going to help us.
You're afraid, Lieutenant.
As ships burn in the night, you want
to know if you can save your own.
If the Trident is real.
You're going to read that wall
for me or you will die.
The British Empire will have
the Trident and rule the sea.
I want to know where that pirate
is going with that witch.
SHANSA: Your destiny is in these stars.
I will set your course.
(JACK SPARROW SNORING)
(GASPS) Spaghetti wolf!
HENRY: Why did I bother coming to you?
The dead are hunting us down
and you do nothing.
Nothing! You call this nothing?
You're drunk! And you're sleeping.
My point exactly!
I am doing two things at once.
You can't save the unsaveable, mate.
Like it or not, Jack,
you're going to help me.
I will break my father's curse.
(GUN COCKS)
Next time you raise a sword,
boy, be the last to die.
Oh.
Might I suggest you entice her
with a bit of flattery?
I'm here for my father, nothing more.
(CHUCKLES) I knew it.
Absolutely smitten with her.
Now, a bit of discretion
when courting a brunette...
never pursue her sister.
But if you cannot avoid
the charm of her sister...
kill the brother.
Savvy?
No, I do not savvy.
Who hurt you?
By the way, that little sliver
of knowledge will cost you five pieces.
I'm not paying you for that.
Never say that to a woman.
Just because you can't see something,
doesn't mean it's not there.
Like the map?
I have to find it.
It's the only link to who I am.
Who my father was.
So we've both spent our lives
searching for our fathers.
Perhaps you and I are closer than you think.
The sun is up, and so is your time.
Not to disagree, but the precision
of our accord ends at sunrise.
This be but first light,
far from a fully risin' sun.
And I know you to be a man of honour.
Honour? You know nothing of me.
I know what it's like to be
bested by Jack Sparrow.
He's an enemy to us...
You don't know who I am.
I've heard stories
of a mighty Spanish captain,
El Matador Del Mar.
A man who scourged the sea,
hunted and killed thousands of men.
No, no, no. Men, no. No, no, no.
Pirates, eh?
Pirates.
(MEN SCREAMING)
Pirates had infected the seas
for generations.
Taking the life of my father
and his father before.
So I vowed to end this plague
once and for all.
And that is what I did.
I destroyed dozens of ships.
(SCREAMING)
The last ones joined together
to try and defeat me!
But they soon realised it was hopeless.
(INDISTINCT SHOUTING)
(MEN SCREAMING)
Nothing could stop the Silent Mary.
Hit them below the water line.
Vamos! Vamos!
Hang on, boys!
(ALL SCREAMING)
The sea was finally pure.
Their wretched flags
would no longer stain the sea.
(PIRATES SCREAMING)
They are begging for mercy.
CAPTAIN SALAZAR: Mercy? Mercy?
There's no mercy.
(HUMMING)
LIEUTENANT LESARO: Make ready!
- (RIFLES COCKING)
- PIRATE: Please, help us!
(SIGHS)
CAPTAIN SALAZAR: Adiós!
Fire!
It's up to you now, Jack.
This compass points towards
what you want most.
Never betray it.
The Devil's Triangle.
CAPTAIN SALAZAR: The last of their ships
were burning before my eyes.
(MEN CHEERING)
And in that moment of victory...
it's when I heard it.
JACK SPARROW: Hey! Hold on, Capitán.
CAPTAIN SALAZAR: One ship was
trying to escape through the smoke.
JACK SPARROW:
It's a lovely day for a sail, innit?
And there, in the crow's nest...
there was this young pirate boy.
JACK SPARROW: The way I see it,
there's just the two of us left.
You surrender to me now
and I'll let you live. Simple.
He stood there looking like
a little bird, eh?
And from that day...
he earned himself a name that would
haunt me for the rest of my days...
Jack the Sparrow.
Right then. You surrender
to me now and I let you live.
I shall let you live.
(JACK SPARROW LAUGHS)
This boy was mocking my power,
so I chased him...
knowing that I would
run my knife along his neck...
and when he was dead,
I would finish finally
with the pirate's life.
Follow him in.
JACK SPARROW:
To the gallows. Grab some lines.
Prepare the bootleg. Portside.
Throw it now.
Bootleg turn.
(ALL GRUNTING)
(EXPLOSION)
(CLEARS THROAT)
What's all this?
Tribute, sir.
(CHUCKLES)
Ooh!
CAPTAIN SALAZAR:
He took everything from me...
and filled me with rage.
And pain.
And here is where the tale ends.
(SWORD SWISHES)
Not yet, Capitán. There!
Found as promised.
So she's saying she's got the map,
but she's the only one who can follow it?
So we should shoot her?
Leave her be. She will
take us to the Trident.
You've been saying that for hours.
Two things we know are true, eh?
- Yeah.
- Stars don't shine by day.
And she forgot the donkey.
How can we go to a spot where
no land exists on any map?
This chronometer keeps
the exact time in London.
I'm using it to make an altitude
measurement to determine longitude.
Only then will we find our exact spot at sea.
So you expect to find
the Trident with a timepiece?
Yes.
My calculations are precise and true.
I'm not only an astronomer,
I'm also a horologist.
- (GASPS)
- BOLLARD: Mmm.
No shame in that, dear.
I mean, we all have to earn a living, eh?
Oh, yeah.
No. No, I'm a horologist.
So was my mum.
But she didn't crow about it as loud as you.
Are you saying your mother
was academically inclined?
More like, horizontally reclined.
Horology is the study of time.
And she was always looking at her watch.
I can vouch for that.
So no one can find the "X" but you, right?
- CARINA: No.
- SCRUM: And the donkey?
Ship to the aft!
Salazar.
Jack, the dead will not rest
until they get their revenge.
Dead?
No, no. The dead were never
part of this deal.
We should have never followed
a luckless pirate and a witch to sea.
Right, that's it. Kill 'em all.
Kill me and I'll be dead.
And then the other dead won't be
able to have their revenge...
against me.
Being dead.
What?
Which will anger them even more. He's right.
That's right.
Are all pirates this stupid?
Yes.
- Yeah.
What are we going to do?
As Captain, might I suggest...
CARINA: Mutiny? You had to suggest a mutiny?
HENRY: Carina, the dead are coming.
Well, I choose not to believe
in supernatural nonsense.
Do you not see what's behind us?
(SEAGULLS CAWING)
Drop them. Drop them.
(FLIES BUZZING)
HENRY: What are you doing?
CARINA: The men on that ship are looking
for Jack and Jack is on this boat.
So I'm going to swim for it.
How dare you do exactly
what I would do if I were you.
- Carina, stop that.
- No, no, no. Don't stop that.
This has gone far enough.
No, it has not.
Listen not to him. Carry on. Carry on.
Why? She was almost finished.
I saw her ankles.
You'd have seen a lot more if you'd
have kept your cake hole shut.
Kill the Sparrow.
Oh, that's not good, is it?
Keep rowing, man. Faster. Faster.
No. That's it.
I'm going with her.
You would leave me for
some horologist in her knickers?
Yes.
You men are all alike.
(HENRY SCREAMS)
(BOTH GRUNT)
Shark.
(GRUNTING)
(YELPS)
Henry!
Doesn't seem to be working!
No, we'll be fine. We'll be fine.
(MEN YELLING)
Vamos!
How do they do that?
We have to swim for it. I'll distract them.
(HENRY GRUNTS)
Now!
(GRUNTS)
(SCREAMS)
Oh, shoo!
Go away!
Henry!
(GRUNTING)
(LAUGHS)
(GRUNTS)
(BOTH SCREAMING)
(MEN YELLING)
(PANTING)
(GASPING)
JACK SPARROW: Oh!
Hi, Jack Sparrow.
(CHUCKLES)
Jack the Sparrow.
You're Spanish?
(SCREAMING)
(STAMMERS) You're ghosts!
Oh.
They're unable to step on land.
(LAUGHS) I knew that, though.
Ghosts!
(CARINA SCREAMING)
Carina!
You will soon pay for what you did to me.
No, no, no.
There's no need to bother, really.
- Carina!
- I have no time to chat...
because me map's just run away.
I will be waiting for you!
Why would you be waiting for me?
Why would he be waiting for me?
(CARINA SCREAMS)
Pirates!
(GASPS)
Scrum.
Captain.
Jack always told me that if anything
should ever happen to him...
he wanted you to be captain.
Yeah, but the men voted for you.
That's why you got a captain's hat.
Be that as it may...
them were his wishes, so be
a good lad and take the wheel.
And, uh, you...
take the captain's hat.
Oh. (CHUCKLES)
This is the proudest moment of my...
(GROANING)
We will beat your captain to death
until he reveals where they're heading.
HENRY: Carina!
JACK SPARROW: I know what's ailing you, boy.
You've got the unscratchable itch.
HENRY: Carina is the only one
who can help us find the Trident...
and I'm not in love with her.
Love?
Who said anything about love?
What are you talking about?
The unscratchable itch?
Scabies. I'm talking about scabies.
Small mites that burrow under the skin.
It's certainly ailing me, has been for years.
Oh, no.
CARINA: Help!
Help me!
- Carina!
- Help!
- Henry, help me!
- Help her!
CAPTAIN SALAZAR: By rule of the King,
I sentence you all to death!
(MAN GROANS)
I think we should tell each other
where our treasures are buried...
just in case one of us survives.
Oh, good idea.
You go first.
My treasure is buried between
two crossed palm trees...
in an unmarked grave in Aruba.
What about yours?
I haven't got any.
CAPTAIN SALAZAR:
You promised me Jack's blood!
CAPTAIN BARBOSSA: But Jack be trapped!
He can never escape that island.
He's on land!
(HENRY GRUNTING)
Hello.
(YELLS)
I upheld our deal. Me men
and meself will go ashore.
The scurvy traitor will be yours...
on me honour.
Honour? What honour, hombre? What honour?
You don't know what honour is.
Spare me my life,
and I'll fetch you the Sparrow.
(SPEAKING SPANISH)
(IN ENGLISH) An accord?
(SCREAMS)
MAN: (ECHOES) Wake up, Sparrow.
(ECHOES) Wake up, Sparrow.
Wake up, Sparrow. It's time to pay your debt.
Pig... Pig Kelly?
(CHUCKLES NERVOUSLY) Me old mate.
Mate? (SNORTS) You hear that, boys?
This lyin' pirate owes me
a plunder of silver...
and luck has brought him to Hangman's Bay...
where he can settle his debt here and now.
Oh, and I will. I will, Pig.
Name your price.
Her name is Beatrice...
and she's my poor, widowed sister.
(WHIMPERS)
(STAMMERING)
What is that?
She's been looking for a respectable man.
But you'll have to do.
Louis, let's get on with this.
No! Why? Why would we do that?
PIG KELLY:
To make an honest woman of her, Jack.
Congratulations. It's your wedding day.
Let us begin.
We'll honeymoon in the barn.
(YELLS AND CHUCKLES)
(GROANS)
(FIDDLE PLAYING WEDDING SONG)
No, no, no.
Now, Pig, how could I...
honestly make an honest woman out of it?
That... Her. I mean, her.
(WHIMPERS) What are those things?
Our children.
Best not look them in the eye.
Bring the best man and the bridesmaid.
(CHUCKLES)
I looked it in the eye.
Place your hand on the Bible.
I've got scabies.
- So do I.
- JACK SPARROW: Ugh!
Place your hand on the Bible.
I'm a bed-wetter.
PIG KELLY: Say "I do..."
or I'll put a bullet in your skull.
Jack, they're going to kill us!
- I don't care!
- Just say "I do."
- Last chance, Jack.
- Wait!
Surely, this is not legal.
This is not legal.
He's right.
Does any man here object to these nuptials?
- I do.
- PRIEST: Congratulations!
- You may kiss the bride!
- (JACK SPARROW GASPS)
(CROWD APPLAUDING)
(YELPING)
(SPITS AND SNIFFS)
No.
(STAMMERING)
You like seafood, do you?
- Come on!
- (YELLS)
(GUNSHOT)
Jack, we meet again.
JACK SPARROW: Hector!
This is me bestest mate in the whole world.
I always knew you'd settle down eventually.
Did you bring me a gift?
(PEOPLE SCREAMING)
That'll do.
You look marvellous.
Got quite the spring in your step.
Has your leg grown back?
Uh, Captain, shouldn't we
be getting back to Salazar...
trade Mr Sparrow's life in for our own?
CAPTAIN BARBOSSA: Aye, that we could
but I've come for the Trident of Poseidon.
You're gonna double-cross the dead?
You did promise.
And with it, I'll gut the dead
that stole my command of the sea.
As much as I love this plan...
no vessel can outrun
that wretched hull of a ship.
But there be one, Jack.
The fastest ship I know, the Pearl...
trapped in that bottle by
Blackbeard five winters ago.
By the power of that
blackguard's sovereign blade...
I hereby release the Black Pearl
to her former and rightful glory.
(SCREAMS)
Get ready!
Get ready for it!
It's coming!
It's coming! It's coming, it's coming!
Stand aside! Stand aside!
It's coming!
It's shrunken.
Why doesn't it unshrink?
Maybe it's cold, huh?
She needs the sea.
(SIGHS) She was a fine ship.
(WATER BUBBLING)
(LAUGHING)
- (GUN COCKS)
- Let...
There be room for only one captain.
JACK SPARROW: Ooh!
Filthy beast.
Time to race the dead.
JACK SPARROW:
The only safe place is the land.
Why are we going away from the land? Anyone?
CARINA: Captain, your map is incomplete.
I can take us to the Trident
if you'd only trust me.
JACK SPARROW: Anyone?
Did you not hear anything I just said?
So you be saying that that star
is pretendin' to be a map?
MURTOGG: Sir, there is no island on any
map to support what the woman says.
Captain, you don't have to understand her.
Just believe her.
JACK SPARROW: Anyone?
(THUNDER RUMBLING)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
- (GRUNTS)
- (COW MOOS)
If we had something sharp,
I could pick that lock.
You're not gonna find anything sharp in here.
- (SCRUM SCREAMING)
- Keep still, you bilge rat.
SCRUM: Captain!
No, please! I don't wanna
be captain any more!
Release 'em!
Sir, you wouldn't allow...
a woman to steer your ship?
She will follow her star,
or we'll all die together.
(MULLROY SIGHS)
The Black Pearl! She sails again!
- (ALL CHEERING)
- Come on, lads!
This ship, those ghosts...
There can be no logical explanation.
The myths of the sea are real, Carina.
I'm glad you can finally see you were wrong.
Wrong?
Perhaps I had some doubts.
This is the worst apology I've ever heard.
Apology? Why would I apologise?
Because we've been chased by the dead,
sailing on a ship raised from a bottle.
- Where is your science in that?
- Fine, then I will apologise.
Go on, then.
Although one could argue
that you owe me an apology...
as my life has been threatened
by pirates and dead men.
Which you now believe in, sorry to say.
Apology accepted.
I'm going to the lookout.
I'm glad you see it my way.
Twelve degrees to port!
- Ready the guns.
- Aye!
OFFICER: Ready the guns!
Those pirates are going for the Trident.
Where did you get that from, missy?
I know this book.
Stolen from an Italian ship many years ago.
Stolen? No, you're mistaken.
There was a ruby on the cover
I would not soon forget.
This was given to me by my father...
who was clearly a man of science.
(JACK CHITTERING)
He was clearly a common thief.
The memory of my father will not be
defiled by the tongue of a pirate.
This diary is my birthright.
Left to me on the steps of a children's home.
Along with a name and nothing else.
Oh, so you're an orphan.
What be you called?
Brightest star in the North gave me my name.
That would be Carina.
Carina Smyth.
So you do know your stars.
I'm a captain.
I know which stars to follow home.
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
JACK SPARROW: Smyth.
Smyth is quite an unusual name.
Did we not once...
know someone called Smyth?
Shut your trap.
What was her name?
It's right on the tip of me tongue. Oh!
Do you wanna lose that tongue?
Margaret Smyth. (CHUCKLES)
Aye.
Should we make an accord then?
Or shall I tell you-know-who
what we both know to be true?
We both take this secret to our graves.
You mean, it is true? I was bluffing.
I'm not.
You kill me, you got nothing
to bargain the dead with.
So you need me.
I'll have to be frank, Hector.
You are very, very ugly.
So how could you produce
a fetching creature such as that?
Margaret died.
I summoned as much honour
as a worthless blaggard ever could.
I placed the infant in an orphanage...
never to see her again.
I thought the ruby might afford her
some ease in life...
but I never imagined
she'd take those scribblings...
and make a life of her own.
A life that's led her back to me.
I'd say this puts me
in a rather favourable position, Daddy.
You tell me what you want.
I want me compass.
216 barrels of rum.
- And the monkey.
- (SQUEALS)
You want Jack?
Dinner. I want to eat him,
I want to eat that monkey...
No deal, Jack.
A clever young woman such
as that would never believe...
that a swine like me could ever be her blood.
(MUFFLED SPEECH)
And the Trident will be mine.
(WIND HOWLING)
HENRY: Redcoats!
Redcoats!
Prepare to fire!
OFFICER: Prepare to fire!
Man that gun!
(MEN SHOUTING)
CAPTAIN BARBOSSA: She comes starboard.
We shall fight to the last.
The Pearl will not be taken from me again.
(ALL CLAMOURING)
OFFICER: Sir.
SCARFIELD: Only the British Empire
will hold to the power of the sea.
(LOUD RUMBLING)
(CREAKING)
Whatever happens, stay your course.
(MUFFLED SCREAMING)
(JACK CHITTERING)
(MEN SCREAMING)
(GRUNTS)
(SING-SONG) Jack Sparrow!
Jack Sparrow.
I've come with a butcher's bill.
- (GRUNTS)
- (MUFFLED SCREAM)
Where is he?
(WHIMPERS)
Defend yourselves, men. To the death!
(MEN CLAMOURING)
Hurry up, man.
What did you sharpen it with? Butter?
- (SWORDS CLANGING)
- (MEN GRUNTING)
(JACK SPARROW GRUNTING)
(YELPING)
(GROANS)
- (GASPS)
- There's nowhere to hide.
(GRUNTS)
(SWORDS CLANGING)
Let's be brave. Save the Pearl!
(PIRATES YELLING)
CARINA: This has to be it.
It has to be here.
CAPTAIN BARBOSSA: Find that land.
Or we'll all die.
We're nearly there!
(STAMMERS) It's here somewhere.
(CREAKING)
Oh!
(GASPS)
(YELPS)
Ow.
(WHIMPERS)
(GRUNTS)
Ha!
(LAUGHS)
(GASPS)
Whoa...
(MEN SHOUTING)
Have you found what you're
looking for yet, miss?
I'm trying!
The stars will soon be gone.
(GRUNTING)
(GROANS)
(YELPS)
Whoa! Whoa!
(GRUNTING)
Carina!
Henry, look!
The island is there.
You found it!
(BOTH GRUNTING)
JACK SPARROW: The island.
(GASPS)
Land.
Get to the Mary!
(GRUNTS)
(ALL GRUNTING)
(THUNDER RUMBLING)
- (GRUNTS)
- (SCREAMS)
HENRY: Carina!
- (CRASHING)
- (YELPS)
(ALL YELPING)
(GROANING)
HENRY: Carina!
Henry!
(CREAKING)
(SEAGULLS CAWING)
They took Henry!
The Trident be all that can save him now.
CARINA: Then we have to find it.
(MAN COUGHING)
(GROANING)
CARINA: Where is it?
It has to be here.
(ALL MURMURING)
Look at it, Jack.
It's the most beautiful thing I've ever seen.
This is what my father wanted me to find.
The rocks?
No, not rocks.
Stars.
This is The Map No Man Can Read.
This island is a perfect
reflection of the heavens.
One star's missing.
Quickly!
We have to find the Trident to save Henry.
Hector, I think you should know,
she's a horologist.
CARINA: Why isn't it glowing?
Finish it, Carina.
The missing star.
For my father.
Aye.
Do it for him.
(RUMBLING)
(CARINA SCREAMING)
(JACK SPARROW SCREAMING)
(SCREAMING CONTINUES)
(BOTH GRUNT)
(JACK SPARROW GROANS)
(WATER BUBBLING)
(GASPS)
Look.
JACK SPARROW: Poseidon's tomb.
CARINA: This way.
LIEUTENANT LESARO:
Capitán, you know the danger.
Don't do it.
He has no choice.
Jack is on land going for the Trident.
Capitán, there must be another way.
Once you possess the living,
there's no coming back.
You will be trapped in his body forever.
The Trident will set me free.
(LIGHTNING CRASHES)
Time to kill a Sparrow.
No!
(PANTING)
Look, Jack. There it is.
JACK SPARROW: The Trident.
- HENRY: Jack!
- Huh?
- (YELLING)
- (GRUNTS)
(CARINA GRUNTS)
(BOTH GRUNTING)
(SWORDS CLANGING)
(GRUNTING)
(YELPS)
(SCREAMS)
- (GRUNTS)
- (HENRY GASPS)
(CHUCKLES) Huh?
You cut me, you cut the boy, Jack.
(BOTH GRUNTING)
- (SCREAMS)
- (GRUNTS)
(YELLS)
(GRUNTS)
Henry!
(CARINA SCREAMING)
(GASPS)
(GRUNTING)
Hola, Sparrow.
Oh, no.
I hate the Sparrow. Die, Sparrow.
(JACK SPARROW SCREAMING)
(GROANS)
Henry!
(MUFFLED) He's walking on land. Please.
Henry, wake up.
Oh, piss off!
JACK SPARROW: Whoa!
(YELPING)
Henry, wake up. He's killing Jack.
(JACK SPARROW SCREAMING)
(MUFFLED SCREAMING)
Henry!
Power of the sea.
What?
The power of the sea.
"To release the power of the sea...
"all must divide."
(JACK SPARROW CONTINUES SCREAMING)
(GROANING)
If the Trident holds all the power, then...
Then every curse is held inside.
JACK SPARROW: (COUGHS)
As I told you before...
surrender to me now and I'll let you...
live.
You want me to surrender?
Maybe.
This is where the tale ends.
(GROANS)
No!
Shh.
(CHANTING INDISTINCTLY)
Divide.
Henry!
Divide. Break.
Break the Trident and you'll...
BOTH: Break every curse at sea.
(CHANTING INDISTINCTLY)
(HENRY YELLING)
(CAPTAIN SALAZAR WHEEZING)
(GASPING)
(ALL CHOKING)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(GASPING)
(COUGHING)
(ALL COUGHING)
All curses are broken.
(LAUGHS)
(ALL LAUGHING)
CAPTAIN SALAZAR: We are flesh and blood!
JACK SPARROW: The Pearl!
My Pearl!
Climb!
CAPTAIN BARBOSSA: Move! Fast!
Hold it steady, boys!
Don't let her slip!
Jack!
(ALL CLAMOURING)
CAPTAIN BARBOSSA: Jump!
Faster!
Up! Anchor!
Get the anchor up! Quick!
Stop! Stop! Bring it up!
Bring it up! Bring it up! Come on!
(PANTING)
SCRUM: Bring it up!
(ALL CLAMOURING)
(GRUNTING)
LIEUTENANT LESARO: Capitán!
Capitán!
Oh, crumbs!
(ALL GRUNTING)
(CARINA WHIMPERS)
Whoa. Whoa.
(GRUNTING)
(CARINA SCREAMING)
Oh!
CAPTAIN BARBOSSA: I've got you!
Stronger.
Who am I to you?
Treasure.
Hold on!
Hector!
(BOTH GRUNTING)
(SCREAMING)
PIRATE: Hold her starboard!
(ALL GASPING)
(ALL CHEERING)
(HENRY AND CARINA GRUNT)
Pirate's life, Hector.
(GASPS)
(CHITTERING)
You all right?
I don't know.
For a moment, I had everything, Henry.
Now, it's all gone again.
It's not all gone, Ms Smyth.
Barbossa.
My name is Barbossa.
Maybe Jack was right.
About what?
The unscratchable itch.
What did you do that for?
Just checking it's truly you.
That you're not still a ghost.
It's me.
Then I was...
Wrong.
Slightly in error. Although...
Apology accepted.
(SHIP APPROACHING)
(MAN SHOUTING)
The Dutchman.
Henry.
Yes, Father.
Let me look at you, son.
(BOTH CHUCKLE)
How did you do it?
How did you break the curse?
Let me tell you a tale.
A tale of the greatest treasure known to man.
- That's a tale I wanna hear.
- (BOTH CHUCKLE)
(SIGHS)
What a truly revolting sight.
GIBBS: Make way!
Captain Jack Sparrow on deck!
Indeed!
PIRATE: Welcome back, Captain.
Oh, thank you very much. Coming through.
Captain!
Thank you.
I remember you.
Sirs. Thank you.
Oh, good. Master Gibbs.
GIBBS: The ship is yours, Captain.
Ah, thank you.
(CHITTERING)
(GASPS) Monkey.
Thank you.
What be our heading, Captain?
We shall follow the stars, Master Gibbs.
Aye, aye, Captain!
I have a rendezvous
beyond my beloved horizon.
(PIRATES CHATTERING)
(WIND HOWLING)
(LIGHTNING CRASHES)
(RAIN PATTERING)
(THUNDER RUMBLING)
(FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING)
(DOOR CREAKING)
(LIGHTNING CRASHES)
(WIND HOWLING)
(SIGHS)
(ELIZABETH MOANS)
(LIGHTNING CRASHES)
Someone needs to stop Clearway Law.
Public shouldn't leave reviews for lawyers.