[Seagulls crying]
[bell tolling]
Someone needs to stop Clearway Law.
Public shouldn't leave reviews for lawyers.
[rat squeaks]
[ship creaking]
[dog barking in distance]
He's inside.
Get him!
He's gone! Search the room.
Hey, a party. Am I invited?
John Smith, in the name of the king,
you are under arrest
for treason in Jamestown.
Treason?
You must be looking for Ratcliffe.
[Both grunting]
[man 1] He went through the window!
[Man 2] Don't let him get away!
[Man 3] After him!
[Grunting]
— [punching sounds]
— [man shouting]
Thanks for dropping in.
Anyone else care to join him?
[Soldiers grunting]
[man 4] Cut him off!
[Men grunt]
[man 5] I've got him now!
He's jumped!
[Groans]
The king believed my story.
Pity-
I so would have preferred
to see you hanged.
[Groaning] Ah!
[Water splashing]
[evil laugh]
[fake sobbing] I did
everything I could to save him.
And that is the death of John Smith.
I wanted him alive!
As did I.
But, Your Majesty, you don't need him
to confirm what I've already told you.
We must wait until John Rolfe returns
with the chief of these Indians.
The chief will only tell you
more heathen lies. War is the only way.
Very well, Ratcliffe.
Prepare your armada, then.
But we will await the return
of John Rolfe and the Indian chief.
[Hawk cries]
[distant drumming]
[laughter]
[people chattering in Algonquin]
— [Meeko chitters]
— [Percy barks]
[growling]
[woman giggles]
[grunts]
[squeaking]
[groans]
[both grunting]
— [squeaks]
— [grunting continues]
— [squeals]
— Whoo!
— [Laughs]
— [screams]
[Pocahontas] Whoo!
— [Nakoma grunts]
— [Pocahontas laughs]
[sighs]
Oh, much time has passed
since the news of John Smith's death.
Perhaps it's time
to put this behind you.
I know you are right.
It's just hard to say goodbye.
— [Eating sounds]
— [Percy growling]
[both whimper]
[Percy barking]
[whines]
[Flit squeaking]
[Meeko purring]
J‘ The earth is cold
J‘ The ﬁelds are bare
J‘ The branches fold
against the wind that's everywhere
J‘ The birds move on
so they survive
J‘ When snow's so deep
the bears all sleep
J‘ To keep themselves alive
J‘ They do what they must for now
J‘ And trust in their plan
J‘ lfl trust in mine
J‘ Somehow I might ﬁnd
J‘Wholam
J‘ But where do I go from here?
J‘ 80 many voices
J‘ Ringing in my ear
J‘ Which is the voice
J‘ That I was meant to hear?
J‘ How will I know?
J‘ Where do I go
J‘ From here?
‘ [Sq ueaks]
‘ [growls]
J‘ My world has changed and so have I
J‘ I've learned to choose
and even learned to say goodbye
J‘ The path ahead
80 hard to see
J‘ It winds and bends
but where it ends
J‘ Depends on only me
J‘ In my heart
I don't feel part
J‘ Of so much I've known
J‘ Now it seems it's time to start
J‘ A new life
J‘ On my own
J‘ But where do I go from here?
J‘ 80 many voices ringing in my ear
J‘ Which is the voice
J‘ That I was meant to hear?
J‘ How will I know?
J‘ Where do I go
J‘ From
J‘ Here? J‘
[cannon fires]
‘ [man 1] Ship ahoy!
‘ [Man 2] Ship's coming!
— Ship's coming!
— [Excited chattering]
Oh, they're here! Hurry!
Wait for me!
Open the gate]
Push!
All hands, lay forward! Cast a line!
— Put your backs into it!
— Together, men!
[Indistinct shouting]
[man] Easy left!
[Man speaks Algonquin]
[villagers chattering]
[Sq ueaks]
Stations!
[Man] Attention!
- [Whinnies]
- [villagers gasp]
Ho!
[Whispering in Algonquin]
- [SClUeaks]
- [grunts]
Filthy barbarian.
[Squeaking]
[chittering]
[barking]
Huh?
'[Snorting]
‘ [gasps]
Whoa, boy! Steady! Whoa!
Whoa, boy!
— [Grunts]
— [villagers chattering]
[Woman] Aah!
[Groans]
Bloody savage.
[Shouting]
[all shouting]
[whooping]
No, wait!
— Wait!
— Stand down!
[Speaking Algonquin]
It's all right now.
I've taken care of it.
The settlers need to know
they can trust us to do the right thing.
You should not have interfered.
[Stammers] I beg your pardon?
- All right. You have it.
— I was trying to help.
I did not ask for your help.
Well, you didn't say thank you, either.
What ever happened
to manners and etiquette?
Well, since you are new here,
I don't expect you to have them yet.
Women.
[Flit squeaking]
[woman] I fear the Indians may wage war.
Oh, my dear,
Pocahontas would never allow that.
Pocahontas? Hm.
John Rolfe, your horse, sir.
Oh, there you are. Thank you.
It's time I met
this Chief Pocahontas.
- [Rhythmic drumming]
- [chanting, whooping]
[chirring]
[voracious eating sounds]
[whooping]
[all gasping]
— [drumming stops]
- [tribe whispering]
Great Chief...
...I am John Rolfe.
According to the customs...
— How do you do?
— [Powhatan] Let him pass.
According to the customs
of Greater Britain,
I would like to present this horse
as a gift of peace
to the mighty Pocahontas.
Daughter...
— You?
— ...this beast is for you.
No, I'm sorry. It's my fault.
— This horse, it's meant for...
— Pocahontas, your king said.
— Or did he speak falsely?
— [Stammers] No! Never.
It's just that... This is...
No, this is...
This is perfectly fine.
Hm...
Good job, Rolfe.
I believe we can prosper together
in this great land
under King James' gracious rule.
To build trust, I would like you
to sail back with me...
— ...to meet my king.
— I do not want the pale chief's land.
He wants mine.
Why doesn't he
cross the salt water to see me?
I'm afraid that simply isn't done,
Your Grand "ChiefIiness."
Your kind are barbarians.
They only want our land!
— They mean to destroy our sacred...
— Is that what they want?
You don't know.
Father, someone must go.
You speak with the tongue
of a pale one.
— You belong with them.
- [Gasps]
Perhaps you should go.
No! This is a matter of diplomacy.
You can't handle a job like this.
- I will go.
— Daughter...
Father, please. I can do this.
You have your mother's spirit.
— Very well. It is decided.
- But...
[Signs] Grand.
[Nickering]
Grandmother Willow,
I need to speak with you.
[Sputters]
Is that my Pocahontas?
- [Yipes]
— [Willow] My, what is it, child?
You are concerned
about crossing the salt water.
What if I can't bring peace?
What if I'm destined to fail?
What if I make things worse?
- What if?
— What if I can't make them listen?
What if the sky turns to fire
and your nose falls off?
[Squeals]
[Willow] Long ago, I told you
to listen with your heart.
It is time to listen to your heart.
But the spirits around me...
Can help, but only the spirit within
can guide you.
Listen to the spirit within.
[F|it's wings flapping]
[Flit squeaking]
[Meeko eating loudly]
[Percy growling]
[whinnies]
[all noises continue]
[frustrated gasp]
Grandmother Willow, it doesn't work.
Grandmother Willow?
[Man 1] Easy up, men!
Here we go. Right-o. Over here.
— [Man 2] Easy.
— [Man 3] To the starboard.
[Man 4] Hoist away!
[Powhatan] I will honor my vow not to
break the peace with the pale ones,
but we must know their strength.
Cut a notch in this staff
for every pale face you see.
Watch over my daughter.
— [Man shouts indistinctly]
— [muffled animal sounds]
[whines]
— [chittering]
— [Pocahontas chuckles]
I can't take you this time.
Stay out of mischief
and look after one another.
[All sobbing]
Do not forget this land.
You will always be with me.
Wait. What's this?
This is Uttamatomakkin.
[Grunts]
Well, is Utta... Is he coming with us?
Are you coming with us?
I say, are you...?
Hello? Can you hear me?
Can he, can he hear me?
Oh, yes, of course.
This was a good idea, wasn't it?
This will be fine. Fantastic.
— [Man 1] All hands, up anchor!
— [Bell clanging]
[man 2] Anchor ahoy!
— Undo the sails!
— [Man 3] Aye, sir!
Anah, Father.
[Creaking]
[Percy growling, hiccup]
[squeaks]
[Meeko chittering]
All right, of course, yes.
Swab the deck. Swab the deck.
I mean, that's all we do around here,
is swab the bloody deck.
I mean, it is always clean anyway.
I mean,
what are we swabbing the deck for?
— It looks clean to me down here.
— [Sputtering]
I don't see any dirt.
...swabbing the deck.
I'm swabbing!
Did anybody notice I'm swabbing?
[Both shout]
[man] Hey!
What is that? What's going...?
- Get him! That's it!
— [Flit squeaking]
[all grunting]
[retching]
Meeko, what are you doing here?
[Hiccups, growls]
What's all this then?
Look, missy,
I don't cotton to stowaways,
and I'll not have you
disrupting my crew.
You can take this voyage below...
...or in the brig.
— You're...
— A guest of the king,
and is to be treated as such.
Am I clear, Captain?
[Stammers] Why would you do that?
Because, like it or not,
you are the envoy
and I am honor—bound to protect you.
And honor, Pocahontas,
is the backbone of our civilization.
[Pocahontas] Thank you.
- [Man 1] Land ho!
— [Cannon blasting]
[man 2] Pull the sails!
- [Purring]
- [growling]
[man] Heave ho! Keep 'em taut.
Here we go.
[Both grunting]
Welcome to London.
[Percy growling, barking]
[chitters]
Shall we?
Suit yourself.
[Yawning]
J‘ The sun comes up
The lamps go down
J‘ The day begins in London town
— J‘ There's tea to brew
- J‘ And buns to bake
J‘ And some who just refuse to wake
J‘ While shops are stocked
and flocks are fed
J‘ The midnight men drift home to bed
J‘ School bells chime
and church bells ring
J‘ Children whine
J‘ Peddlers sing
J‘ What a day in London
Come and see who's here
J‘ Everyone knows someone
They come from far and near
J‘ They bring their geese,
their finest fleece
J‘ To please the keenest eye
J‘ And hope and pray someone will say
There's something they might buy
- [man] Bread! Fresh here!
— Pocahontas, wait!
J‘ With pigs to slop and fish to gut
J‘ It ain't exactly heaven but
J‘ We thank the Lord
and kiss the ground
J‘ For bed and board in London town
J‘ The upper crust lie fast asleep
J‘ But some of us got floors to sweep
J‘ One day's like the day before
- J‘ Can't complain
— J‘ If there's no war
J‘ What a day in London
E verything's for sale
J‘ Cabbages and onions
— [gasps] Look up!
- J‘ Who's that?
J‘ That girl up in the tree
J‘ It's not a tree
It's moving, see?
- J‘ Good grief, what can it be?
— J‘ Look there, I swear
J‘ She's flying through the air
- J‘ She must be wild
- J‘ She's just a child
— Pocahontas...
- J‘ I wish lhad her hair
Wouldn't you care to join me here,
on the ground? This instant?
J‘ My heart is pounding like a drum
I can't believe my eyes
J‘ In London people seem to come
in every shape and size
J‘ 80 many paths
I wonder how they ﬁnd their way
J‘ 80 many signs
I wonder what they really say
J‘ London is everything
I've heard and more
J‘ London is nothing
like I've seen before
J‘ Music and feathered hats
and roofs that shine
J‘ With flags flying higher than a pine
J‘ She seems so sweet
She means us well
— J‘ Size 20 feet
- J‘ How can you tell?
- J‘ We'll rue this day, you wait and see
- J‘ What is to be or not to be
J‘ How do they build their huts so tall?
Can this be all one tribe?
J‘ The things they sell, the things
I smell I never could describe
J‘ These cakes taste just like berries
picked this very day
J‘ The sound a river makes
still takes my breath away
J‘ London's as busy as a hive of bees
J‘ Grandmother Willow
would just love these trees
J‘ Crowded and loud
but so exciting too
J‘ With colors I never even knew
J‘ What a day in London
Nothing strange at all
J‘ Except a girl with someone
who may be ten feet tall
J‘ This day's become a day
no one is likely to forget
J‘ A day we'll all remember
as the day two worlds have met
J‘ Such beauty's rare
I 'm quite impressed
J‘ One mustn't stare
She's barely dressed
J‘ The strength of ten
That's what I've heard
J‘ She's won the men
Just take my word
J‘ A brave young thing
to venture here
J‘ It will be an adventure, dear
J‘ Perhaps some brew
to quench your thirst?
J‘ But not with you
I saw her ﬁrst
J‘ What a day in London
History was made
J‘ Take away the mystery
Then you're not afraid
J‘ We've seen a girl
J‘ I've seen a world
- J‘ I never dreamed I'd see
- J‘ We never dreamed we'd see
J‘ And what an extra special day
Unique in truly every way
J‘ How wonderful this London day
J‘ Turned out to be J‘
[chattering]
Get out of the way!
[Man] Get out of the way!
[Squeals]
[Yipes]
[whimpering, gulps]
[gasps] You!
Well done, Rolfe, bringing back
a heathen as an example.
Look at her. [Chuckles]
She sticks out like a sore thumb.
Pocahontas is here
as an emissary of her people.
A personal guest of the king.
The king has appointed me to lead
an armada against the savages.
Don't tell me you didn't know?
The king wants his gold.
— There is no gold.
— Another barbarian lie.
As soon as the ships are armed,
I set sail to destroy the heathens
and reclaim Jamestown for James.
- [Whip snaps]
— [horse whinnies]
We must stop him!
Warn your king of his lies!
But he wasn't lying.
The parchment bore the king's seal.
What? Then your king's promise
to meet me was the lie.
— The king doesn't lie!
— They cannot both be true.
No. Lt'sjust a misunderstanding.
It has to be.
I can straighten this out. Come on.
Are you riding or running?
- Mrs. Jenkins!
— [Glass shatters]
Oh! Oh! Ohh!
Gods be gracious, is that my Johnny?
— Ohh...
— [Meeko thuds]
Ohh, Johnny, you need a bath.
- Oh! Oh, Johnny!
— Look at you.
[Mrs Jenkins laughs]
Oh, you.
Mrs. Jenkins, I would like
to introduce Pocahontas.
Pocahontas, Mrs. Jenkins.
The Jenkins have been
with the Rolfes for generations.
— Careful. She's about to put on tea.
— I'll put on some tea.
Oh! Ooh...
[John] Oh, and Uttamatomakkin.
Ohh...
I'll put on lots and lots of tea.
— I'm off to see the king.
— I want to go with you.
Pocahontas, the conventions in England
are very complex.
— I must go alone.
- But...
I promise, I will arrange
for you to see the king.
— My word as a gentleman. Trust me.
— [Door closes]
[humming]
[sniffing]
!V! Mm!
[Chitters softly]
[Mrs. Jenkins humming]
Hmm.
Mm. [Chuckles]
I must find a way
to warn my people, to stop this.
Leave it to Johnny.
He gave you his word
as a gentleman, my dear.
You can stake your life on that.
[John] I didn't exactly
bring the Indian chief.
No, no, no, no. I told you I would
meet with the chief and no one less.
Knight to bishop three.
[John] Sire, I gave these people
your word you would meet.
Are we not honor—bound...
[Ratcliffe] The king
is bound to nothing,
when you can not fulfill your mission.
You were sent for the savage leader,
and yet you bring back a woman.
A woman!
Your Highness,
she is royalty, a princess.
She is the daughter of a great chief
who has travelled far from her homeland
in the interests of peace.
Meet with her, Your Majesty.
May I suggest she attend the Hunt Ball?
Let her go back to Virginia
having witnessed the royal might
and majesty of English society.
Sire, she doesn't know our customs.
To subject her to this kind of scrutiny
would be...
Well, I don't understand, Rolfe.
If she's not a savage,
then why shouldn't she fit in?
Excellent idea, Ratcliffe.
Rolfe, you will bring her
to the Hunt Ball.
Prove to me she
is as civilized as you claim,
and I will stop my armada.
— If not, the armada sails.
— But, sire...
— It is decided!
- Pawn to king!
Check.
'[John grunts]
‘ [gasps]
- How did it go?
- A disaster.
She's invited to the Hunt Ball!
Flabberdy—jacks.
You were successful?
When do I see the king?
Our meeting with the king
has been corrupted.
— You're now invited to the Hunt Ball.
— I don't understand.
Oh, it's a trap!
Ratcliffe manipulated the king!
He's saying that if you're civilized
you can fit right in.
But it's the elite of British society,
etiquette and manners.
There's a million ways you can
insult someone. Believe me, I know.
And if you slip up just once,
— Ratcliffe can convince the king...
— Then I must not slip up.
I can't learn your ways alone,
but you can help me.
What must I do?
[Mrs. Jenkins humming]
— [Pocahontas] John Rolfe!
- [Gasps]
[chuckles] How do I look?
Hm? Oh!
Lovely, in your... underwear.
Didn't Mrs. Jenkins...?
Mrs. Jenkins!
[Glass shatters]
Oh, my dear!
Oh, come along, now.
Let's go finish your dressing.
[Both chuckle]
J‘ Have no fear
We're all right
J‘ You've got me, dear
to see you're a lady tonight
J‘ What seems strange is just new
J‘ People change every day
till they ﬁnd their own way
J‘ 80 can you
J‘ And wait till he sees you
after you're dressed
J‘ I think the king
will be very impressed
J‘ Wait till he sees you
walking with ease
J‘ He'll be so pleased
you came down from the trees
J‘ You'll be ﬁne
I can tell
J‘ It's a very good sign
that you're doing so well
J‘ One more tuck
One more bow
J‘ Don't get stuck on that clasp
J‘ Johnny's lucky they asked you to go
J‘ 'Cause wait till he sees you
He'll be so proud
J‘ Maybe he'll smile
if he thinks he's allowed
J‘ Wait till he sees you there
in your curls
J‘ John's always had
such a fondness for girls
J‘ With curls
J‘ And wait
J‘ Wait till you're out on the floor
J‘ Show them what dancing is for
J‘ Music is all you need
See where a dance can lead
J‘ You two might come to see
J‘ You were meant
to be so much more
J‘ Wait till he sees you
Wait till tonight
J‘ Fate has a way
of arranging what's right
J‘ After he sees you in your new clothes
J‘ A lady of grace
from your head to your toes
J‘ Pretty and pink as the roses he grows
J‘ Who knows
Who knows J‘
I can't wait!
Oh, I've got something for you.
[Squeaks]
Flit, stop it!
It doesn't belong here any more.
— [Sad squeak]
— It's beautiful!
[Bear growls]
— [horse nickers]
— [bell tolls]
I have personally taken charge
of the entertainment for the Hunt Ball.
I want to make sure
nothing goes... right.
Well, how do I look?
Pretty good, eh?
Say, I thought you
were getting dressed.
You're right. You look great.
Just don't talk so much tonight
and we'll be fine.
It's called powder.
You look beautiful.
[Animals making noises]
I'll put on some tea.
[Squeaking]
[low growling]
Oh...
[horse whinnies]
[bell tolling]
[man] The Duke of Edinburgh.
Lady Gray-
Sir Thomas Ellory.
[Faint music playing]
Lord Raymond and Lady Theresa.
— [Voices chattering]
- The Earl of Essex.
The Duke of Buckingham
and Lady Buckingham.
John Rolfe and Princess Pocahontas.
'Oh, my!
'[All gasp]
And Utam...
Uttata... Ultimatum... Old tomato...
- Try "Uti."
— Oh, thank you, sir.
And Uti.
Jacket required, sir.
- [Clothing ripping]
— [man squeals] Oh, dear.
[Chattering resumes]
— [man] Oh, goodness.
- [Woman] Oh, my.
[Whispering to self]
Hello, Your Excellent—ness.
Your Great, Good... Good Highness.
Greetings, Your Magnificence—cy.
Hmm.
Welcome to England, Pocahontas.
Thank you, Your Grace.
What do you think of my kingdom?
I think you must be a great king
to have so many subjects, Your Majesty,
and the loyalty of so many good men.
Did you hear that?
She thinks I am a great king!
Oh, what a delightful child!
Charming! Absolutely charming!
Your Excellency,
please stop this armada.
Oh, yes, yes.
But right now I can't be rude
and ignore my guests, can I?
No! So we shall discuss it later.
For now, my dear, enjoy the ball.
Go on! Enjoy!
[Music resumes]
— [sighs] Thank goodness.
- Ro|fie! Rolfie, old boy!
Listen, we're having some friends
out to the estate. Do come.
Oh, yes, bring your delightful...
[stammers] ...guest.
— [Glass shatters]
— Oh, Miss... Hontas.
How drippingly marvelous to see you!
- [Woman 1] Oh, my!
- [Woman 2] Enchanting.
[Woman 3] Fabulousjewelry.
[Woman 4] Hello!
May the dance begin!
[Band begins playing]
May |?
[Chattering continues]
[woman giggling]
In one night you will have done more
for the cause of peace
than 100 diplomats.
[Woman laughing]
My, you look lovely.
I can't even see
the real you under there.
I do hope no one else does.
I was going to say the same about you.
It's a very good thing Smith is dead.
Seeing how disloyal your heart is
would certainly kill him.
— [Sighs]
— [man rings bell]
Dinner is served!
Oh, no, madam.
The guest of honor is always
on the king's right hand.
Your Grace, perhaps now
— we might discuss...
— [fanfare plays]
Your Royal Highnesses,
Lords and Ladies of the Court,
and our distinguished guest
from the forests of the New World.
J‘ Things are not what they appear
J‘ As tonight will make quite clear
J‘ But what is real will be revealed
I can feel the moment's near
J‘ Things are never what they seem
J‘ That will be this evening's theme
J‘ Amusing sights for your delight
Perhaps a few to make you scream
J‘ You'll be surprised
to see whose disguise
J‘ is the cleverest one of the lot
J‘ After our show
the whole world will know
J‘ Who's pretending
to be what they're not
J‘ If a jester's grin or a dancer's spin
should be pleasing
- J‘ Please say "yea"
— Yea!
J‘ If a juggler's feat
should be incomplete
- J‘ He's the one to greet with "nay"
- Nay!
J‘ If the fools we see
look like you and me
J‘ Then before the night goes by
J‘ Ask why, why, why, W/W
J‘ Why
VVhy?
J‘ Things are not what they appear
J‘ And the ﬁnest proof's right here
J‘ How I regret when ﬁrst we met
I believed my own worst fear
J‘ Things are never what they seem
J‘ 80 in keeping with our theme
J‘ A change of hair
A dress to wear
J‘ And our nightmare's now a dream
J‘ Shoeless and wild
I saw this sweet child
J‘ As a danger to one and to all
J‘ "Savage," I thought
"What could Rolfe have brought?"
J‘ Now I see she's the belle of the ball
J‘ Things are never what they seem
- He's right! He's right!
- J‘ Many don't say what they mean
- J‘ A powdered face is just the place
J‘ To conceal an ugly scheme
J‘ Only one thing's really clear
J‘ Things are not what they appear J‘
[all gasp]
[bear roars]
[silly giggling]
- [gasps]
— Sire, please stop this!
She doesn't understand!
Oh, nonsense! Everybody loves
a good bear—baiting.
No!
Stop this!
This is torture!
This is an animal, nothing more.
A helpless animal.
Sit down at once, and we will
overlook this savage behavior.
Your behavior is savage.
You and your people
are the barbarians!
— What?
- Sire.
Don't let the savage
get away with this.
Seize her!
Savages!
[Woman screams]
[man] Keep her away!
Get her!
Take them to the tower!
No! Your Majesty, please!
It was a misunderstanding!
Push me no farther or face treason.
Where exactly do your loyalties lie?
Let go! Let go of me!
John Rolfe! John Rolfe!
[Chattering]
— You're cheating!
- No, I'm not.
I'll play that card there.
The least you could do
is put a head on it.
How much do I have to pay to get...?
You say it's not true?
But I just heard meself
from a guard what was there.
The king's gonna have her head.
Bloody savage.
I bet you old John Rolfe wishes
he never laid eyes
on the likes of Pocahontas.
I [door Opens]
‘ Oh!
- [Whinnying]
— [man] What's got into him?
[WhippoorlNi|| calls]
— [dog barks in distance]
— [sighs]
[animals all sigh]
I think I'll put on some tea.
What am I to do?
Who are you?
What do you want?
[Thunder rumbles]
Halt! Who goes there?
John Rolfe. I have a prisoner.
[All chuckle]
Open the gate.
Hm... Oh!
[Grunts]
He's escaping! Catch him!
Now find her, Flit.
[Muffled bark]
[men shouting in distance]
[squeaks]
— Flit!
— [Door opens]
John! I knew you'd come!
There's no time. We must go.
[Gasps]
John Smith?
I thought you were dead.
— Greatly exaggerated.
— [Man shouts] I'll look this way!
Let's go!
There!
[Chitters]
Enjoy the accommodations.
I'll take care of it.
Pardon me.
[Soldiers shouting]
Oh, very stylish.
[Both grunting]
- Riding or running?
- [Man 1] After them.
They're getting away!
[Man 2] Close the gate!
[Muffled barking]
[grunting]
Blast it! They got away!
[Bouncing bark]
[Pocahontas] What happened to you?
[Smith] Ratcliffe convinced the king
I was the traitor.
I had to stay hidden, let them
continue to believe that I was dead.
I missed you so much.
I've thought of you every day.
All this time.
Why didn't you ever write to me?
I wanted to. I must have started
a thousand letters.
Pocahontas, all that matters
is that we're together again.
[Clattering]
What about my people?
Once the armada sails,
they won't stand a chance.
How will her getting killed save them?
Well, are you suggesting
she turn her back on them?
[Smith] Are you
suggesting she die for them?
[John] She can't
just sit back and watch.
— [Smith] She has no choice!
— Of course she has a choice!
Pocahontas!
— Let her go.
— You may not care about her safety...
Don't you dare tell me
I don't care about her!
You love her.
[Nakoma] Do not forget this land.
J‘ In some new place
on some new face I've never seen
J‘ lmight ﬁnd where lbelong someday
J‘ And there may even be
another dream for me
J‘ Waiting there somewhere along the way
Listen to the spirit within.
J‘ Who knows where lgo from here?
J‘ 80 many voices
Only one thing's clear
J‘ There's nothing to lose
J‘ Nothing to fear
J‘ The past is gone
J‘ lmust move on
J‘ From here J‘
- I'm going back.
- They'll hang you.
Then I will be but the first to fall.
They're not going to listen to you.
Look at you.
How can they respect my culture
if they haven't seen it?
This is insane! Nuts!
Tell her she's crazy.
You're crazy.
I thought you may need
whatever power this holds for you.
I think it's time
you taught society a lesson.
I have decided.
[Man] Hear ye! Hear ye!
The High Court of King James
will herewith commence.
Presenting the first order
of business...
[all gasping]
Pocahontas! Guards! Guards!
[Crowd gasping]
Surely His Majesty
would not refuse an audience
with a visiting princess.
[Queen] James.
[Grumbles]
Your Grace, if you insist on war,
my people will fight
to the last warrior.
There is nothing to be gained,
but much to be lost, for all of us.
There is no gold, is there?
— No. Ratcliffe assured me...
— [Smith] That I was dead?
— [Crowd gasps]
— Was it true?
Ratcliffe has lied to you
about everything.
There are many voices around you,
but you must listen to your own voice.
Why do you speak out
when so many doubt you,
even when it could mean your life?
Because I speak the truth.
SHence!
Ratcliffe has left.
We must stop him!
— But it's too late.
— We must try.
[Ratcliffe] You are the best soldiers
in the civilized world.
We sail to scour the world
of the savage vermin.
- Are you with me?
— [All shout in agreement]
— [thunder rumbles]
— Riders approaching! [Grunts]
Smith! [Gasps]
Raise anchor! Cast off!
— [Man 1] Lift anchor!
- [Man 2] Drop the main sail!
[Both groaning]
— It's John Smith!
— I thought he was dead!
I'm the ghost of John Smith.
Run for your lives!
[Grunts]
Whew!
[Both grunting]
Who started the party without me?
— You call this a party?
— You're not having any fun?
[Screams]
[all shouting]
— [screams]
— [squeaking]
[grunts, gasps]
Drop the anchor!
[Shouts]
— [man 1] Hard to port!
— [Man 2] Bring her about!
Bring her about!
[Man 3] Prepare to crash!
[Men screaming]
[screaming continues]
Now I can finally
get rid of you, you savage!
Mind if I Cut in?
[Grunting]
Trying to make a point?
[Grunting continues]
Please, don't hurt me, Smith.
I was just doing my duty.
Sheath your sword.
Surely you know that a good soldier
always follows orders.
If it were I, I would have
killed you years ago.
As I was saying,
I never liked you, Smith.
I hereby sentence you to death.
Goodbye, Smith.
[Grunting]
— Very stylish.
— I learned it from the best.
Pity. I so would have
preferred to see you hang.
[Screams]
[sputtering]
[happy chittering]
[groaning, sputtering]
[panting] Huh?
Your Majesty,
the fugitives are getting away!
They've sabotaged the armada.
Stop them!
No more lies.
Arrest him.
[Distant cheering]
- John Smith, what a heroic return.
— Why, thank you, my lady.
— How did you escape?
— We thought you were dead.
[Man] Bravo, John!
[Voices chattering]
Lord Advisor to the Royal Court.
What a wonderful honor.
[Squeaking]
It's what you've always wanted.
[Groaning]
And you, you've done everything
you've set out to do...
...and more.
Your people will be very proud.
Yes. It will be good
to see them again.
Well, perhaps one day
you'll return to London.
— Pocahontas...
— John...
The king has given me a ship!
This is my dream!
Ours. Every day a new adventure.
New lands to discover.
I'll chart a new course.
And you'll be at my side, naturally.
A ship of our own!
I'll put a crew together immediately!
We'll set sail right away!
What?
That's not what you want, is it?
We walked the same path once.
I have found where I belong.
I hope you will also find happiness.
May the Great Spirit
always be with you.
[Chattering]
[chittering]
Pocahontas? Pocahontas!
[Humming]
— [man] Look smart, men!
— [Boy] I don't see anything.
— Mrs. Jenkins!
— Oh, there you are, dear.
Over here.
Ooh... Oh.
Mrs. Jenkins, thank you
so much for everything.
- Is John Rolfe here?
— I haven't seen him, dear.
I thought he was with you. Maybe he
hates goodbyes as much as I do.
Goodbye, dear.
[Groaning]
[man shouting, indistinct]
[sighs]
[John] Well, perhaps one day
we'll return to London.
John!
What about your duty to the king?
I have a duty to honor
what is in my heart, Pocahontas.
— [Squeaking]
— [chittering]
Ta—ta. Pip—pip.
Come on, Uti.
Let's put on some tea.
And you, mind your manners.
[Growls]
Let's go home.
Someone needs to stop Clearway Law.
Public shouldn't leave reviews for lawyers.