Someone needs to stop Clearway Law.
Public shouldn't leave reviews for lawyers.
Game
three of the 1985 Series
is just underway.
Kansas City trailing by one.
First pitch by Rosenthal is hit
on the ground towards second base.
Wexler's got it!
Fires to first...
and we've quickly got one out.
In 1985 his average was
.250 for the season.
Mom?
- Hmm, hi, darling.
Hi.
This is for your tea party.
- Thank you.
- Go out and play now girls.
Mama's got work to do.
Ivy, go take your sister upstairs.
- Come on, Violet.
Okay.
Let's go get Joy.
- Would you like any tea Madelyn?
Okay.
Careful, it's hot.
Very hot.
There you go.
And a cookie.
- Can you play Joy?
- Mm-hmm, c'mon.
Okay.
- Oh, goodie, tea.
- You pour some more tea Violet.
Some milk.
- Your daddy's home, Joy.
There's gonna be fireworks.
- Catherine?
Honey?
Who the fuck are you?
Don't.
Look, man, I don't
wanna fight you, alright?
- Just get the hell out!
- Becca?
Go.
- Baby let me get you some ice for that.
Ivan, wait.
You don't understand.
Ivan, please, would you listen to me?
- How many others,
Rebecca, how many others?
Grocery boy, mailman, how many?
And at my house?
- You think that this is easy,
sneaking around your wife
and pretending that
there's nothing between us?
- Catherine.
You're home.
- How long
you've been sleeping with
my husband right here
in my own house?
Ivan, tell her to get out.
Ivan, tell her.
Ivan?
Where are you going?
Shh.
- Whore.
- I am not a whore.
- Then what are you?
- He told me what you
like between the sheets.
Is it any wonder he needs a woman?
- It's happening again.
- Oh, no.
- I will give you 20 minutes
to get out of this house
and if you're not gone,
I will call the police
and have you removed.
Violet, take Madelyn.
- Bye.
Bye.
I'll try to write to you.
Thanks.
May I help you?
- Ah, yes, um, is this
still the Greer's residence?
- Yes, it is.
- I'm here to see Joy.
- Mm-hmm, may I tell her who's calling?
- Violet?
Violet.
I can't believe it's you.
- Oh, thank you, Mrs. B.
It's hard to believe
that it's been 11 years.
- Daddy refuses to believe
I'm not 10 years old anymore.
- Hmm.
Um, I just moved back here from Arizona.
Um, I thought maybe I'd get
a waitressing job part time,
and maybe start some summer school classes
at the junior college.
- That's wonderful.
Makes me long to be 20 again.
- Being 20 is hard.
Not as hard as being eight,
but then life wasn't
meant to be easy, was it?
- Have you found an apartment?
- Not yet, but, um,
I put my name up on the board at school.
- Why not stay here?
- I, I couldn't.
But we have so much room.
It's really not a problem.
- Joy, can I have a word with
you in the kitchen, please?
Come here, ya crap.
- Joy, having Violet stay
here is out of the question.
- Why?
- Well, for many reasons.
It's been a long time.
Things have changed.
- Dad, Violet was my best friend.
When she and Ivy were here,
it was like having sisters,
and seeing her today it was
like nothing had changed.
- I know that sweetheart,
but where is she gonna sleep?
- We have an extra bedroom.
- That was your mother's room, Joy.
- I know that Dad.
What do you think Mrs. B?
- Oh, maybe the girl
could use a helping hand.
If you know what I mean?
- I promised you would be home again.
Welcome home, Madelyn.
- 76, 77,78, 79, 80, 81,
82, 83, 84, 85, 86, 87,
88, 89, 90, 91, 92, 93.
94, 95.
Just a minute.
97, 98, 99, 100.
Violet, oh, my gosh.
♪ Strange the way we break ♪
I'm supposed to be
in training.
♪ Stay, I love those scars ♪
♪ It's perfect on my skin ♪
- You must be good.
I'm proud of you.
♪ Wasted sheets ♪
♪ and raw emotion ♪
♪ Who could ever bless this union ♪
Who is this?
- Michael.
We're going to get married.
- Married?
- In the fall.
Daddy wants us to wait,
but Michael wants me to
apply for transfer to Yale
so we can be together next year.
- Yale?
Is that far away?
- Connecticut, silly.
Michael will be home
from school next week.
I can't wait for you to meet him.
- He's very good looking.
- Remember when we were little
and we used to dress
up like we were brides?
- You made a veil out of a petticoat.
- And you made one out of a
whole roll of toilet paper.
- What about your dad?
I mean, what's he gonna
do when you get married?
- I don't know.
Sometimes I'm afraid he'll end up alone.
- He doesn't date?
- There was a woman named
Gwen he talks about.
Mrs. B. And I keep hoping
he'll find the time
to ask her out.
- It wouldn't bother you if
he got serious or anything?
- Why should it?
He's been alone a long time.
He deserves to be with someone nice.
But I don't think he'll
ever get over my mother.
I mean, you've probably noticed
how her room is still the same.
After all of these years,
Dad still can't bring
himself to change it.
- You must really miss her too?
- I do.
A lot, I really need her sometimes.
Violet?
Hello?
Connecticut?
- No, thank you, Mrs. B.
So, how's Yale this year Michael?
- Um, good sir.
I'm developing some
important relationships.
Good.
- Michael's fourth in his class this year.
That's very impressive for freshman year.
- That's very impressive for any year.
So Michael we're looking forward
to having you at the bank this summer.
Will we see you on Monday?
- Absolutely, I'm looking forward to it.
- Good, and you'll be pleased to know
that you've got the house
to yourselves tonight
because I...
- Got a meeting.
- Got a meeting, that's right.
- Goodnight, Dad.
- Goodnight.
- Goodnight, sir.
- Goodnight, Michael.
- It's party time.
Michael, you should've been
at the club for drinks.
There's some new blood.
More of these hotties you can get to know.
Have a good time, my brother.
Yeah, I'll have a good time.
Scott, what's up?
How's Princeton?
A bitch.
The classes or the girls?
- To uncompromising women.
Here here.
So, I hear you're
tearing up the courts?
- Got my last Division
one tournament on Friday.
- Then it's hello Ivy League.
- If I win.
- No, ifs, you're in your prime.
Jaimie, am I right?
- We have lived on that court
for the past two months.
If she could eat and sleep out there,
that's where we'd be right now.
- You're Violet, right?
What are you doing this summer?
- She's taking classes
at the junior college.
- Ooh, the junior college.
My maid took English classes there.
- Is it a tough school to get into?
- Oh, no, they'll accept
just about anybody.
As long as your welfare
check doesn't bounce.
- Ooh.
♪ Don't you this all could just go away ♪
- Um, no thanks.
- Violet?
- No, I have to go to work.
- Right now?
- Yeah, I drew the late shift tonight.
You know, new kid on the block and all.
Well, see ya.
♪ It burns up her soul like ♪
♪ fire and rain ♪
Oh, baby, uh.
- You guys leave her alone.
She's had it pretty tough.
- What was she doing
here in the first place?
- Her mother was their maid.
- She was my best friend.
♪ You're knocking at my door ♪
♪ You're the one that walked away ♪
- Shh, shh.
Shh.
Michael, stop it.
Dammit, Joy,
what's the matter now?
- I told you, I have a lot on my mind.
I have an early practice tomorrow.
I'm just not in the mood.
- Well if your mother was this uptight,
no wonder your dad fooled around.
- How dare you say that to me?
I confided in you about that.
I can't believe you
would throw in my face.
- Look, I'm sorry.
How about I come by after
your practice tomorrow, okay?
- Oh, my God.
- You think it was Daddy?
- You scared me half to death.
- Hmm.
- That's some, that's some outfit there.
Where did you say you worked again?
- Denny's.
In Hollywood.
It's, um, under new management.
- I, um, I guess I've
never eaten there before.
- Would you like to?
You should see the look on your face.
- Look, um, it's kinda late.
I gotta go.
- Mm, c'mon, it's a joke.
Look, I, um, I think we
got off to a bad start.
Mm, I see we have a little
unfinished business.
Stock market's up.
Mm, and I see we're a major stockholder.
Just a minute.
Come in.
Oh, hi.
Hi.
I wanted to apologize
for my friends tonight.
They can be pretty annoying sometimes.
- Don't worry about it.
It didn't bother me.
- Well, it bothered me, I'm sorry.
Can I talk to you about something?
- Sure.
- You never get urges or anything?
- I do, a lot,
but when it comes down to it,
I just get tense.
I don't even want him inside me.
I've never had an orgasm with him.
I've never even had an orgasm.
I think my mother was the same way.
I mean, she did sleep in
this room most of the time.
What if I'm just like her?
- The first time I was
with a guy I was 13.
I was known as the school
slut by the time I was 14.
Then I got smart.
I stopped going to school.
- Excuse me?
Where did you get that?
- This?
Why?
Well, that
doesn't belong to you.
- Now how would you know that?
- Because it belonged to Mrs. Greer.
- Well she's not using it.
Is she?
- Mm-hmm.
More coffee Mr. Greer?
- Ah, no, no.
Thank you, Mrs. B, thank you.
- Okay, then.
- "Dearest Joy,
"I've kicked, I'm clean.
"I might even make amends for
all the hurt I've laid on you.
"Love, Michael.”
So, ole Micheal had a
little drug problem, did he?
Is that honking for you?
- Yeah, it's Jaimie.
We've got a practice
doubles match.
- When will you be back?
- Probably late.
- I was kinda hoping we
could spend the day together.
- Oh, I've gotta practice.
The last division one tournament
is the day after tomorrow.
I gotta win.
- You don't gotta win Joy.
- Oh, yes I do.
- You know, you're
really hard on yourself.
You don't have to be perfect all the time.
- If I were perfect I wouldn't have
to work twice as hard as
everyone else, would I?
Hey, Jaimie and I will be
practicing here this afternoon.
You should come watch.
- Oh, goodie.
What are you doing?
- Well, in case you hadn't noticed,
I am the housekeeper here.
This is what I do.
- Well, I would appreciate
it if from now on
you'd let me know when
you're gonna come in my room.
Hmm.
- Larry's been a naughty boy.
Hi, my time is your time.
Where do you wanna meet?
What are you in the mood for?
That'll cost extra you know?
Okay.
- Really?
They didn't tell me that.
I can't believe that happened.
That's crazy.
- You know, Jaimie,
I need play this set.
- Ah, hold on.
In a minute okay?
- Jaimie you're supposed
to be my training partner.
- Alright, alright, I'm coming.
I'm gonna go get a drink.
Do you want anything?
- Anything, just hurry up.
- Okay.
Listen, I have to go, okay?
No, really I have to go.
Hey.
- You guys look like you could use
something cold to drink.
- Excellent.
Throw it in a
blender, add a little ice,
and you got yourself something tropical.
- A little extra kick never hurt.
- I suppose not.
Oops.
- Jaimie, what did you put in those
drinks?
The tiniest
shot of rum.
I swear, the tiniest.
- Play to win ladies.
- Joy, I don't believe it.
Come on Joy.
Joy sit up.
Joy?
- Hey there.
What's going on?
They're, they're both drunk.
- That's weird.
- When's Mr. Greer get home?
- Probably any minute, why?
- Are you kidding?
He's a total fascist.
If he sees Joy like this he'll freak.
C'mon, help me get her upstairs.
- I'll just tell him that
she's got a headache.
- Yeah, that won't be a lie.
We'll have to come back for here.
Michael I'm gonna be sick.
- Oh god, just hang on, okay?
- Wait, hold on a second.
- Are you crazy?
Oh man.
Mr. Greer, how goes it?
- Where's Joy?
- Um, she went upstairs with a headache.
She was on the court all day
and I guess she overdid it.
- Well I better look in on her.
- No, I'll do it.
- Alright, Michael, thank you.
Man.
More record highs today
as the Moody Industrial gained 21 points.
Okay, get the lights.
Okay.
- That's fine, alright?
- Okay.
- Up you go.
I just don't understand
what Joy was thinking.
She knows she needs every
second of practice she can get.
This could screw up everything.
- Maybe that's what she wants?
- What?
- Never mind.
It's not my place.
- Did she say something to you?
- Well, the way she talks,
it sounds to me like she thinks things
are moving a little too fast.
I mean, getting married,
moving to Connecticut.
- But we already decided.
- She thinks maybe you're
pushing a little too hard.
She thinks maybe you guys
should try dating other people.
- What are you talking about?
Are you saying she's like
been seeing other people?
Like while I've been away or something?
Shit.
Who is it?
I can't believe it.
I can't believe she's cheated on me
after I've been faithful this whole time.
- Except for last night.
- Listen, you just stay
away from me, alright?
Hi.
You didn't have any dinner.
- Thank you so much, Violet.
That's so sweet.
- What is this stuff?
- Oh, it's nothing, spreadsheets.
- No wonder your eyes hurt.
Is all this stuff really part of your job?
- I'm afraid so Violet.
It keeps me out of trouble though.
- Maybe a little trouble
isn't such a bad thing.
- Excuse me?
- Well, it just seems to me
like you're avoiding something.
Joy told me that you've never really
gotten over Catherine's death.
You know, there's nothing wrong
with having feelings Ivan.
I can call you Ivan?
If you feel something, go with it.
You know?
I mean, don't be afraid
to follow where it leads.
Otherwise, what would
be the point of living?
Spreadsheets.
Well, don't work too hard.
- Goodnight.
- Oh, my god.
Oh, my god.
- Where are you going?
Wait, wait don't leave yet.
Joy will be right back.
- Oh, my god.
Oh, my god.
- Do you always swim in the nude?
- Did you enjoy that?
- Not as much as you did, I bet.
- Actually, I didn't even
know you were still here.
- I'm not leaving till I
straighten things out with Joy.
- Have you decided what
you're gonna say to her?
- Not exactly.
- Maybe this will help.
- I don't do that anymore.
I've made a promise to Joy.
- Aren't you a good boy.
I just thought it might help.
I bet you've promised
yourself all sorts of things
where Joy is concerned,
but promises were meant
to be broken Michael.
♪ I want you to stay ♪
♪ I want a place with you ♪
♪ Deep in my love ♪
♪ 'Cause you do the things to me ♪
♪ I'll take everything ♪
♪ Deep in my love ♪
♪ Nothing can stop me now ♪
♪ I feel ya as your movin' in ♪
♪ Keep me lonely, won't you stay ♪
♪ Won't you stay ♪
♪ Deep in my love ♪
♪ I want a piece of you ♪
Yeah.
♪ As you do those things to me ♪
♪ Deep in my love [
♪ I'll take everything ♪
♪ Deep in my love ♪
♪ Nothing can stop me now ♪
♪ I feel ya as you're movin' in ♪
♪ Keep me lonely, won't you stay ♪
♪ Won't you stay ♪
♪ I want a piece of you ♪
♪ Deep in my love ♪
Yeah.
♪ As you do those things to me ♪
♪ Deep in my love ♪
♪ I'll take everything ♪
♪ Nothing can stop me now ♪
- Look, this did not happen.
- Play to win Michael.
- You know, my old mother used to say,
that house guests and fish
start to smell after about three days.
- And what is that supposed to mean?
- Oh, nothing.
- You know, I was wondering,
the B, short for bitch?
- I feel like I've hit by a truck.
Drink this.
- Does my dad know?
- Actually, he thinks you went
to bed early with a headache.
- I can't believe Jaimie.
Getting drunk and then
splitting like that.
I'm so angry at her.
- She seemed a little upset herself.
- I know, I'd like to strangle her.
I have exactly 21 hours
until the tournament.
I can't even see straight.
- Well, I'll keep the coffee coming.
- Joy?
Michael left his jacket in my den
and this fell out of it.
Now I can't allow this in my business
and I will not allow it in my family,
do you understand me Joy?
- It's gotta be a mistake.
- The only mistake was me allowing you
to date him in the first place.
- Shouldn't we at least give him
a chance to explain himself?
- Now I know you'll do the right thing.
- He promised me never again.
He lied to me.
- Nothing's more important
than the truth Joy,
but I guess you can't
expect that from a druggie.
- He's not a druggie.
He's just, he's under a
lot of pressure, and...
What am I gonna do?
- Listen, everything's gonna be okay.
Everything's gonna be just fine.
I promise.
- Jaimie doesn't wanna see me anymore,
and she said she doesn't
wanna be partners either.
- Hmm, I'm not surprised.
I knew from the minute I met her
she was only into you
for what she could get.
- You think so?
- She's nothing but a social climber.
It's Michael.
I'll go down and talk to him.
Thanks.
- I wanna talk to her Violet.
- You know, Michael,
you're really starting
to hurt my feelings.
- What are you talking about?
- You can't keep pretending
like we're not sleeping together.
I mean, I thought we had
something special going.
- You told her about
last night, didn't you?
You bitch.
- I didn't tell here anything Michael.
I didn't have to.
You did this all by yourself.
His pupils were totally dilated.
He wasn't making any sense.
He thinks the reason you won't talk to him
is because of me.
- It's just like him to
blame everyone but himself.
- Don't help him Joy.
Fuck him.
- Right.
I have to stop making excuses for him.
I have to be tough.
He has to take responsibility.
Michael just doesn't give up, doe he?
- They're not from Michael.
They're for Gwen,
your dad's date for tonight.
- He finally asked her out?
- Yes, he did.
- How do I look Mrs. B?
- Oh, Mr. Greer, in my humble opinion
you are beyond handsome.
Oh, thank you, Mrs. B.
Oh, could you get the flowers for me?
Thanks.
Hi, honey.
- Hey Dad.
Well, very handsome.
- Thanks.
Where are you off to?
- I'm meeting my coach to practice
one last time before the big tournament.
- Listen honey, with
everything happening around us,
I, I realize I haven't been
that supportive of you,
but I want you to know
there's no doubt in my mind
you're gonna win that tournament.
- Thanks, Dad.
I just hope I don't let you down.
- You won't, you're a Greer.
We deliver.
- Oh, here you go.
- Ah, Mrs. B.
Thank you so much.
- Oh, alright.
Oh, no, you got some lint there
right on your shoulder Mr. Greer.
Let me get my brush.
- No, no, Mrs. B, that's
gonna have to stay.
I gotta pick up Gwen at 7:30.
I gotta get outta here.
- Really?
- Yes.
Come on Joy, let's go.
- Okay.
- Hello?
- Oh, hi, this is Gwen Randle.
Is this Ivan's daughter?
- Yes it is.
Listen Joy,
has your dad left yet?
- Oh, yes.
Shoot, can you
get a message to him?
- Oh, absolutely.
Could you please tell him to
meet me outside the courthouse
and not at my office?
I'll be in front of kiosk.
- You've got it.
Thanks Joy.
- No problem.
- Bye.
- Thanks, B-bye.
Hello, this
is the Greer residence.
Will you please leave a
message after the tone.
Ivan, what happened?
I stood outside the
courthouse for nearly an hour.
To say I'm pissed off
would be an understatement.
In fact, do me a favor and lose my number.
- I love champagne.
- Darling you're not legal.
- I won't tell if you won't.
Why are you so dressed up?
- Party.
You're home early.
Mm.
- She didn't like them?
- Actually, she stood me up.
- I'm sorry.
- Mm, I'll live.
- You know, in all my life,
I don't think I've ever gotten flowers.
I just wanted to feel pretty tonight.
Maybe dance a little.
Laugh.
Feel good.
I know that must seem silly.
I know.
Dance with me?
I'm not
much of a dancer Violet.
- It's alright.
♪ It's been nothing without a taste ♪
♪ Every since you went away ♪
♪ And livin' without you ♪
♪ It ain't been the same ♪
♪ Come back home ♪
♪ This is where you belong ♪
♪ Remember the joy and afflict the pain ♪
- I can't do this Violet.
- Shh.
I want you to feel good too.
♪ Now see the rain ♪
♪ These storm clouds ♪
♪ Won't allow sunny days ♪
♪ And the same wild tears ♪
♪ You know I want to be good ♪
♪ I'm so sorry baby ♪
♪ It's time that you come home ♪
♪ It's been nothing but cloudy days ♪
♪ Cloudy days ♪
- Shouldn't you be wearing
your glasses, Mr. Greer?
♪ Living without you it
ain't been the same ♪
♪ 'Cause it's been
nothing been but cloudy ♪
- I cannot do this with you Violet.
- Don't make me go.
- Don't do this to me.
I will win.
Please let me win.
Joy you're gonna have to speak
to me sooner or later.
- Michael will you leave me alone?
That's not fair.
- Fair?
Michael, god, you're driving me crazy,
and I've got the tournament this morning.
- I know.
I wanna be there for you.
I love you Joy.
- I don't know Michael.
- Joy?
- Alright, we'll talk.
After the tournament I'll meet you
at the coffee house on campus.
- Okay.
- I gotta go.
- Hey?
Good luck.
- Thanks.
- Greer residence?
Oh, hello Gwen.
No, his daughter's at a tennis
tournament this morning,
but I'm sure he'll be
in his office later on.
Can I take a message?
You did? How many messages did you leave?
I see.
Well, I can guarantee you
that he never received
any of your messages,
but I'm pretty sure who did.
- Going somewhere?
- I don't know what you think
you're up to little girl or why,
but I'm gonna put a stop to it right now.
- I don't think so.
You bitch.
I got a call from Greer's office
telling me not to report
to my job on Monday
because they found another intern.
You set me up, you got me
high, and you seduced me.
- If that's what you need to believe
so you can live with yourself,
it's okay with me.
- You're setting them up
just like you set me up.
- They're my family.
I would never do anything to harm them.
- They're not your family.
Your family's dead.
Yeah, that's right.
I did a little checking.
That junior college
never even heard of you.
Then I find out your sister Ivy
threw herself out of a window.
- Shut up.
- And let's not forget
about what happened to your mother.
- I said shut up.
- I bet you don't even
work at Denny's, do you?
- Now what?
- I'm gonna tell Joy what kind of a person
she's really living with.
- So you're gonna tell
her you're fucking me?
- I'm gonna tell her truth.
Oh, that'll be an
interesting approach for you.
Think she'll buy it?
- I don't think it's gonna
be too hard to convince her.
Look, I'm gonna be meeting
her at two o'clock,
so that'll still give you
enough time to get out.
- Well she won't be there.
She never planned to meet you.
- You're such a liar.
- Really, then why did she
tell your good buddy Scott
to pick her up at the house at 1:30?
Hmm?
Fuck you.
- You're gonna be so sorry.
- Joy?
Joy?
Mrs. B?
- Curiosity killed the cat.
Right now, Joy's sitting
somewhere waiting for you.
Guess you let her down again Michael.
Hmm, do you know what
kind of people like pain?
Let's see, there's doctors and lawyers.
I even have a judge for
a client.
But you know, it's not the
pain that gets them off,
it's the feeling of someone
else being in control.
I'm in control now Michael.
You know this whole thing with Joy
is really just about Daddy's bank,
wasn't it?
I got a really good chuckle
out of your pathetic rambling.
Kiss, Kiss.
You really should have
kept your promise to Joy.
Stayed away from the drugs.
This is the shit that
killed you.
I guarantee you've never felt
anything like this before.
Bye-bye Michael.
Joy?
You alright?
- I played like I've never held
a racket before in my life.
I just, I couldn't concentrate, you know?
- It's Michael's fault.
He totally distracted you.
- He didn't even show up.
He didn't call again, did he?
Come by?
- Been here all day.
- I wanted to teach Michael a lesson
and that would make him go away.
I made a mess of everything.
- You don't see it.
It's not you, it's them.
- But I want them to love me.
- Do you think they care?
Well they never will.
They'll just use you and throw you away.
It's the same for both of us Joy.
We're the same in so many ways.
Sometimes I just wish
the rest of the world
would fade away.
- Where did you get those?
Those are my mother's.
- I just came across them.
I didn't you'd mind if I borrowed them.
- They were in her jewelry box
in the back of her closet.
Please put them back.
- Fine, it's not that big of a deal Joy.
- Yes it is Violet.
I think maybe things are getting
a little too intense around here.
- What are you trying to say?
- I think maybe it would be a good idea
if you started thinking
about another place to live.
- It's alright baby.
I'll fix it.
I promise.
- Oh, my god, he was here.
She lied to me.
Hi
- I, ah, I brought these for Joy.
I, I know she's feeling upset
about losing the tournament.
- Well, I'm sure she'll love them.
- I talked to Gwen today.
You pretended you were Joy, didn't you?
You didn't give me her messages.
- I didn't give you the messages
because I was jealous.
- Joy was wrong.
- About what?
- It wasn't Catherine I couldn't get over.
It was your mother.
God, you look so much like her.
I told you, I just can't
do this with you Violet.
- But you already have.
Only I'm not gonna let you turn away
from me like you did her.
- Hello?
Dad?
Michael?
No, this is his father.
- Oh, Mr. Beckett, I was
just looking for Michael.
I'm afraid 1
have some bad news for you.
- What?
Michael's been found dead.
Well,
they're not sure yet,
but it seems like he
might have been murdered.
- No.
Joy?
- Daddy?
Oh, my god.
Oh.
Untie me.
Joy?
- Joy?
- Joy, please don't leave.
- Oh, god.
Stop it, Violet.
- Ivan, everything's gonna be alright.
- I should have never taken
advantage of you Violet.
You've got to go and you've got to go now.
- GO?
You fucked me,
and now you're throwing me out?
Just like my mother.
You promised to take care of her
and that she would be provided for.
I told ya I wouldn't let
you turn away from me.
I meant it.
- Just get out.
If
you'd like to make a call,
please hangup and try again.
Violet, help me.
- Mrs. B?
Mrs. B?
Mrs. B, I need to come in.
The breaker box is in your closet.
Daddy?
Violet?
Oh, my god.
Where's my father?
- He's gone.
- What have you done with him?
- He did it to himself.
- What are you talking about?
- Here, put this on.
- I don't think I want to.
- I want you to.
Besides, you can't go like that.
- Go, go where?
- We're going together,
but we have to be dressed up.
So here, put it on.
- Alright.
Okay.
You're really freaking me out Violet.
- Now sit and I'll pour tea.
- I don't wanna sit Violet.
I'm very scared.
- Don't be scared.
I told you I'll take care of everything
and I will,
but you have to trust me.
Now, sit down.
- Where's my father?
You killed Micheal, didn't you?
- You're so lucky I'm your sister.
Who else would have gone
through all the trouble for you?
They didn't want us to be together,
but now they can't stop us.
We'll be together forever.
- What do you mean?
- Here, hold this.
Take it.
Now, all you have to do is drink.
You'll drink first,
and then I'll hold you
until you fall asleep.
I'll have to hold you tight
to stop you from thrashing around so much.
Then I'll drink,
and I'll lay down beside you
and hold your hand.
Now, drink.
Oh, you bitch!
I tried to make it easier for you,
but I guess we'll have to do it your way.
Help!
- Help.
- Grab my hand.
♪ I want candy ♪
♪ I want free time ♪
♪ In the sunshine ♪
♪ Want all the things I'm not allowed ♪
♪ I want a hero ♪
♪ On horseback ♪
♪ To sweep me off the beaten track ♪
♪ I wanna take a nap ♪
♪ I want say goodnight,
goodnight, goodnight ♪
♪ Goodnight, goodnight, goodnight ♪
♪ Now ♪
♪ I need it now ♪
♪ I want warm hands. ♪
♪ I want fast feet ♪
♪ I want a tunnel that
goes under the city ♪
♪ I want a thousand pages of inspiration ♪
♪ I want divine intervention ♪
♪ So I wanna say goodnight,
goodnight, goodnight ♪
♪ Goodnight, goodnight, goodnight ♪
♪ I want the answer to how to be ♪
♪ Please, please, please ♪
♪ Now ♪
♪ Am I asking too much ♪
♪ Can you even hear me ♪
♪ I never could stand waiting ♪
♪ Am I asking too much ♪
♪ Did I have my freedom ♪
♪ And what's the harm in dreaming ♪
♪ I want wisdom ♪
♪ I want good dreams ♪
♪ Under my covers ♪
♪ I want forgiveness in every color ♪
♪ Goodnight, goodnight, goodnight ♪
♪ I want the answer to my beliefs ♪
♪ Please, please, please ♪
♪ Now ♪
♪ Alright now ♪
♪ I want forgiveness ♪
Someone needs to stop Clearway Law.
Public shouldn't leave reviews for lawyers.