Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org
Donald.
Catherine...
This just isn't working out, all right?
♪ Never been a day ♪
♪ when I doubt for a moment ♪
♪ Maybe once or twice ♪
♪ ain't so bad ♪
♪ But deep inside, ♪
♪ I always knew ♪
♪ My time would ♪
♪ come my way, sure ♪
♪ Now it's on me ♪
♪ to make it last ♪
♪ There's nothing ♪
♪ I won't do ♪
♪ Nothing I won't try ♪
♪ For a change ♪
♪ to something new ♪
♪ Ain't no excuse ♪
♪ There's nothing... ♪
♪ Yeah, I won't do ♪
♪ Nothing I won't do ♪
♪ For a change ♪
♪ to something new ♪
♪ What's there to lose? ♪
♪ There's nothing... ♪
♪ I won't do ♪
You see, it doesn't matter
whether it's painting or sculpture
or computer-generated graphics.
And it doesn't matter
what style you choose to work in,
whether it's Neo-primitivism
or romantic realism or postmodern
deconstructionism.
The same rules apply.
Everything is governed
by the laws of nature,
and nowhere are the principles
of proportion
more perfectly manifested
than in the human form.
Excuse me.
Um, is this the, uh...
Life study.
Wait a minute. Don't tell me.
Let me guess.
Lily leonetti.
You're 2 weeks and 30 minutes late.
Sorry. Family emergency.
It's all right. Come on in.
You can get set up over here.
I don't think Catherine's coming back.
All right, let's try
to stay focused, folks.
I'm talking about learning the rules
before you break them...
Specifically, perspective and proportion
as it relates to the human body.
Which brings us back to Isabel.
So, see if you can discover
the hidden truths
in the shadows and the light.
Translate what you see through your arms
and fingertips onto the page.
Hi.
Is this 508 alta?
Yep.
♪ She could tell by the way ♪
♪ The light hit your face... ♪
I'm gredin.
I'm Lily.
I know.
Thank you.
Follow me.
The entrance is in the back.
Bye, Lily.
Yes?
I'm Lily, the new roommate.
Oh, you're here.
Yeah.
I'm Tanya, by the way.
Hi.
Um, anything in this cupboard is mine.
And the living room is off limits
because that's where I practice.
Bridgette, Lily.
English major, right?
No. Art. Painting.
That's funny. I never would have guessed.
Well, I can see we're
off to a good start.
Ha ha ha!
Come on.
♪ I wish you were here ♪
♪ God, god, I... ♪
♪ Wish you were here ♪
♪ I wish you were here ♪
Is she always like that?
Unfortunately, yes.
What about that guy gredin?
Oh, gredin's really cool
and an amazing sculptor.
And that's Robert,
a major talent.
Well, here we are.
It's not exactly the bel aire.
In fact, it's not even the ramada.
It's nice.
Where did you say you were from again?
Michigan.
Oh. First time to I.A.?
First time anywhere, really.
Well, the world of bytes is calling.
Got to run.
Hello.
How's I.A., kiddo?
Hi, dad. It's good.
It's nice.
Well, this place feels
pretty empty without you.
Hold on. Your mom wants to talk to you.
O.k.
Lily?
Hi, mom.
Did you find the surprise?
Hold on a sec.
What is it?
It's just a little something
to remind you of us.
You know, I don't know why
you have to go all the way to I.A.
To be an artist.
We could have bought you a car
if you went to state.
Mary Jane, Katherine's daughter,
she went to state, and she's very happy
making all sorts of arts and crafts.
Mom, do we have to have
this conversation again?
Where's daddy?
Bob!
Oh, he's gone off somewhere.
O.k., well, um, I got to go.
Go? We just got on.
Mom, I'm going to be late for class.
O.k., well, will we see
you at Thanksgiving?
I don't know yet, mom.
I haven't looked at my schedule.
Lily!
I'll try, o.K.?
Bye. Don't forget to call me.
Bye.
That's Peter the performance artist,
or as he likes to refer to it...
Self as show.
Someday, with any luck,
somebody will put him out of his misery.
Look at her, Lily. What do you see?
I see... A face... And a body.
And what else?
I see a naked woman.
Right. The whole naked woman,
not just parts.
Not just the head...
Get that... So let's go...
Include the breast...
And the waist,
the leg, and the whole thing.
Get it all on the page.
Just keep going over and over again,
and eventually...
Technique will give way to expression.
Thank you.
Or expression...
Will give way to expression.
You have some thoughts
you'd like to share with us?
Me? Thoughts? Share?
No. I couldn't possibly.
I'm here to listen and learn,
copy and conform.
From this masterpiece
you've just created,
it's obvious
that you've transcended all need
for traditional forms.
No.
This, my fellow students, was created
out of no other tradition
but that of boredom.
This... this is an a-plus.
This is a perfect example
of 100% surrender to the process
of tradition.
It's so lifelike
that you could almost fuck it.
You through?
Can we get back to work?
Jackass.
Lily?
You o.K.?
Yeah.
Lily?
Yeah?
Can I come in?
No. I'm not dressed.
I'm sorry about earlier.
It had nothing to do with you.
"January 28th. It's late. I'm wide-awake.
"Burning up. Bored. Feel like dancing.
"Having some fun,
like turning someone on,
"tease, taunt, twist him
around my little finger.
"Take him to places he never
knew he wanted to go.
Bad places. Dark places. Great places."
"February 1st. Self-portraits.
"To expose it all.
"To see myself the way a lover would.
"No shame. No fear.
Not a fear in the world."
"Nothing hidden.
No secrets."
Nothing hidden.
No secrets.
"With you, I'm so foolish it hurts.
"My mouth wants to speak
"but only knows the wrong things to say.
"Without you, there is no flower,
and nothing good grows
in the garden of my heart."
Hello.
Hello. Lily leonetti?
Yeah.
I understand you're looking
for a babysitting job.
Bridgette! Shut that shit off!
Bridgette!
I'm going to kill her.
You want to help? Good.
I was thinking fat pills.
She's always saying
if she gains one more pound,
she's going to kill herself.
Suicide's very good.
Thank you. Thank you very much.
Hey, you know what?
What?
I got a job.
Doing what?
Babysitting.
Well, how totally sweet.
Hey!
It is.
She hates me. I'm an insensitive male.
You two know each other?
We do, but she might not
want to know me now.
Tell her I'm not half bad, Tanya.
I wish I were half
as good as you, gredin.
Come on. I'll make it up to you.
Nothing ventured, nothing gained, right?
I got carried away with Donald.
I shouldn't have put you
in the middle of it.
Yeah, well, I probably overreacted.
I can sometimes be hypersensitive.
You shouldn't be. You got it.
Yeah. I'm the only person in class
whose hand the teacher
has to hold... literally.
Well, falk has a weakness
for his female undergrads,
especially when they look like you.
What is this?
This is my magical crap.
I'm sort of hoping
it will win me a guggenheim.
You'll get it.
You psychic?
No. You deserve it.
So where were you
the first two weeks?
Well... when I applied,
I never thought I'd get accepted.
Then I was,
and I just freaked.
No big family emergency.
Just my own little private one.
That's all.
That's enough.
You, uh, see that hill over there?
Mm-hmm.
That's Beverly Hills. That's my home.
Might as well be timbuktu.
My father and I... we don't talk anymore.
What are you thinking?
I'm making a wish.
What are you wishing?
That I could just...
Open my eyes and be different.
Listen to me.
I'm listening.
And I like doing that.
You're beautiful.
No, I'm not.
Yes, you are.
You're sweet, you're beautiful...
And different.
Um...
Lily.
"March 1st.
"How do you know what you can do
"until you do it?
"How do you know who you can have
"until you have them?
"I didn't know him from Adam,
"but I knew exactly what he needed.
What he needed was me."
"A dark club, loud music,
"a corner to ourselves.
"Anonymous...
"Shameless.
No past. No future."
♪ Never seen myself this way before ♪
♪ What's come over... ♪
Oh!
♪ Me? ♪
♪ All I know is that I need to explore ♪
♪ This feeling that's come over me ♪
♪ I can't control ♪
♪ This new beginning ♪
♪ Am I coming up or going ♪
♪ into a trance? ♪
♪ Deep inside ♪
♪ I feel the heartbeat ♪
♪ Of the part of me ♪
♪ that's come to life at last ♪
♪ Never seen myself this way before ♪
♪ What's come over me? ♪
♪ All I know is that I must explore ♪
♪ This feeling that's come over me ♪
♪ What's come over me? ♪
Tease.
Taunt.
Twist him around my little finger.
"No shame. No fear.
Not a fear in the world."
Ha ha!
Ha ha! Looking good!
That guy's a loser. It's me you want.
Besides, I have a lot more to offer
than just my fine young body.
I have it up here.
That's, uh, too bad
because all I was really interested in
was your body.
Same time, same place?
Maybe.
Hey there.
Hi.
Well, what do you think?
It's, uh...
Intense. Ha ha!
Either something very
tragic or terribly exciting
is happening in your life.
Women only change their hair
when it's one of the two.
Oh.
I don't know.
I... i think I was just bored.
I bet it was something exciting.
Like what?
I confess. I'm not
really a fortuneteller.
You have a pretty face.
You shouldn't hide it
behind that new hair style.
Donald?
Hey.
Hey! I thought I'd find you here.
Lily, meet Angela, my wife.
Angela, this is Lily,
your new babysitter.
Hi. Nice to meet you, Lily.
12 Mississippi.
13 Mississippi.
14 Mississippi.
15 Mississippi.
I'm ready!
16 Mississippi.
Lily, hurry up!
17, 18,
19, 20!
Daphna.
Oh, daphna.
Boo!
Aah!
Gotcha.
Oh, I must say, daphna.
You are a great hider.
Thank you.
Oh, you're welcome.
Those are pictures
of daddy's old paintings.
He doesn't like to paint anymore.
Why?
Mamma says it's because painting
makes him crazy.
Ha ha ha!
Daphna?
I'm going to hide again.
Oh, wait, daphna.
Hi.
Hello!
Hello?
Hi.
Hi, sweetie.
Hi. Hi, Lily.
Hi.
What you been up to?
Oh, I did the portrait.
All right.
Angela's getting back
into her photography.
She always said she'd give
daphna four years,
but lucky daphna got a full seven.
Ha ha ha!
Right.
Why don't you take Lily home?
Mom! I'm hiding!
No one's come to find me!
Bye, Lily.
I'll give you a lift.
Now from I.A.'s best station
for the sound of jazz,
another 30 minutes...
So... ha ha ha!
Why don't you tell me
a little bit about yourself, Lily?
Where was it you said you were from?
You'll laugh.
Kalamazoo, Michigan.
Ha ha!
Born and bred...
And stifled.
Well, that's a big move, huh?
All the way out to California
by yourself.
I was really scared at first, you know,
but I think I made the right decision.
Definitely.
Can't afford to be afraid
at your stage of the game.
Right up here?
Yeah, that's it.
Well, I guess I better let you out.
Thanks a lot.
Here's your bag.
Thanks.
If you want to show me
some of your other work sometime,
I'd love to see it.
Like when... like after class?
Yeah. I'm in the studio every afternoon
by the faculty building.
O.k. yeah.
Maybe I'll do that.
Great.
"June 1st.
"Ivy's philosophy number 21.
Never fall in love."
"As long as I can break somebody's heart,
that's love enough for me."
"How do you know what you can do
until you do it?"
Hi.
Ahem.
How are you?
Good, and you?
I'm good.
Thirsty?
Sure.
You don't like it.
No.
No, I think you look incredibly sexy.
I'm glad you like it.
Did Donald like it?
I saw him drop you off.
Seems like you're becoming
a regular teacher's pet.
No.
Just his babysitter.
Do you still think
that I'm different...
Beautiful?
Yeah.
Mmm.
May I?
Hmm...
O.k.
May I?
Ha ha ha!
♪ Hey ♪
♪ Don't go too slow ♪
♪ Don't go too fast ♪
♪ Baby ♪
♪ I've been waiting so long ♪
♪ I want it to last ♪
♪ Baby ♪
♪ Trembling inside ♪
♪ With burning desire ♪
♪ I'm 'bout to lose my mind ♪
♪ It feels so right ♪
♪ To feed this fire ♪
♪ All through the night ♪
♪ I can't deny ♪
♪ Don't want to hide ♪
♪ This aching for you ♪
♪ Deep in my soul ♪
♪ I need your control ♪
♪ Aching for you ♪
♪ Here in your arms ♪
♪ I feel so warm ♪
♪ Aching for you ♪
♪ I love your touch ♪
♪ It's never too much ♪
♪ This aching for you ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
"There I was again,
"going out into the unknown...
Just because."
Do you remember me?
Take me with you?
I can't.
You didn't think I'd come.
I wasn't sure.
Bring it here.
Great midwest.
Ha ha!
Mmm. That's nice.
Thanks.
Good student.
Student?
Well...
You're still very cautious...
Careful.
You know, it's...
It's sort of funny to me
the way you can...
Teach and judge,
and yet...
You yourself no longer paint.
Think that's funny?
Ha ha!
No. Actually, I think it's bullshit.
Hmm...
What do you propose to do about it?
I don't know.
You see...
To be an artist...
You know, to be a serious artist...
You have to be willing
to sacrifice everything.
You have to confront your demons
and go into battle with them.
That's what I want.
I'm ready for that.
Really?
I lost a few battles
along the way myself.
That's why I stopped painting.
Well, then...
Maybe...
I can help you face your fears...
And you could help me face mine.
Are you sure?
Sit down.
Do it.
Take off your clothes.
Ha ha!
Does that prospect frighten you?
Y-yeah, a little.
Then all the more reason to do it, right?
O.k.
♪ Seekin' for pleasure ♪
♪ In all the wrong places ♪
♪ Can't take the pressure ♪
♪ To keep gettin' wasted ♪
♪ Deeper and deeper ♪
♪ Goin' down ♪
♪ Without a sound ♪
♪ Deeper and deeper ♪
♪ Goin' down ♪
♪ Ooh, ooh, ooh ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah ♪
Yeah.
♪ Mind gets so tired ♪
♪ From too much thinkin' ♪
♪ Try to get higher ♪
♪ But you're always sinkin' ♪
♪ Deeper and deeper ♪
♪ Goin' down ♪
♪ Without a sound ♪
♪ Deeper and deeper ♪
♪ Goin' down ♪
♪ Ooh, ooh, ooh ♪
♪ Ahh ♪
See you.
♪ Ooh ooh, ooh ooh, ooh ooh ♪
Tomorrow?
♪ Ah ah, ah ah, ah ah ♪
Hi.
Um, I'm really late for work.
I'm starting to feel
like one of those seduced
and abandoned cases.
This isn't a boy/girl thing, gredin.
This is a work thing.
Are you sure?
Don't be so insecure.
♪ Deeper ♪
♪ Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh ♪
♪ Deeper and deeper ♪
♪ Goin' down ♪
♪ Without a sound ♪
♪ Deeper and deeper ♪
♪ Goin' down ♪
♪ Ooh, ooh, ooh ♪
♪ Ooh, ahh, ahh ♪
♪ Ahh, uh ♪
Hi. This is Lily.
I can't get to the phone,
so leave your message after the beep.
Thanks.
Boo! Ha ha ha!
Gotcha!
Um, we're having a party tonight.
It's going to be pretty loud.
I just thought I'd let you know. Bye.
Fuck her.
Gredin! Gredin!
Yo! Over here!
Hey, you beautiful man, come on!
Gredin!
Stop what you're doing!
Oh, god, I'm so tired!
Why do you have to have
this sculpture up here?
Here's a beer!
Is that lipstick on your face?
It is!
You better not be kissing anybody
but me tonight, o.K.?
Oh, you sexy man.
We're having a party.
Fuck him.
Oh, it's going to be so much fun.
Fuck them all.
♪ Maybe I'll never be ♪
♪ What you want me to be ♪
♪ Maybe I'll fall apart ♪
♪ There's no space in your heart ♪
♪ Let's pretend I'm a god ♪
♪ What are you wearing now? ♪
♪ Love's the perfect disguise ♪
♪ I can't be found there ♪
Are you out of your mind?
Why would you want to do
something like that?
Self-expression.
Wait a minute.
First you cut off all your hair.
Then you Pierce your bellybutton.
Now you're smoking?
What the hell is going on with you?
Tanya...
Don't you have some sort
of superhighway
that you need to get on?
Why don't you go have some fun?
I was just leaving.
Guess I won't introduce you to Roxanne.
Hi.
Hmm, what should I have?
How about an icebreaker?
And what exactly is an icebreaker?
Turn around, and I'll show you.
O.k.
Don't move.
Uh...
Hey, to icebreakers.
Thanks.
Whoo!
Whoo hoo hoo!
Dance with me.
Oh, my god.
No one's safe with you around.
Yeah. You got a problem with that?
Hi. This is Lily,
and I can't get to the phone.
Leave me a message after the beep.
Thanks.
Lily, it's your mom.
Lily, we're worried about you.
Your dad wants to talk to you.
Hey, kiddo. How are you doing?
Please call home, darling.
Your mother's driving me crazy.
We'll see you at Thanksgiving, right?
Ahem.
Is that the time?
We're late for Donald's class.
So we're late for professor fuck's class.
What's the big deal?
I want to go.
That's what the big deal is.
So go.
What do you think I'm trying to do?
So, what are you doing for Thanksgiving?
I don't know yet.
Uh, bridgette, Tanya, and Robert
are going to go home.
It's going to get rather
lonely around here.
What about you?
What are you going to do?
Gredin?
Hello? Hello?
Who was that on the phone?
Gredin?
I don't know.
Someone who didn't want to talk to me.
There seems to be a hell of a lot
I don't know.
Don't.
What's the matter?
What did I do?
You tell me.
What are you doing?
I want to know, Lily.
Um, I really can't
have this conversation right now
because I'm late for class.
I don't know who you are anymore.
I don't know
who I'm making love to anymore.
If this is some kind of contest, Lily...
I don't want to compete.
I thought you wrote these.
Hi.
Oh, what a nice surprise.
Thought you might be hungry.
As a matter of fact, I am.
Since when do you lock the door?
Since the last campus shooting.
Painting again?
Mm-hmm.
It's delicious, honey. Thanks.
Can I have a look?
No.
You know not to ask.
When I have something to show you,
I'll show it to you.
Donald...
Yeah?
You o.K.?
Yeah. I'm fine.
Why?
So who are you painting?
No one in particular.
O.k. fine.
What?
Do you want me to yak about something
I don't have the guts to do?
That's not what we're talking about.
I don't want to lose you again,
and especially not
to some 20-year-old undergraduate
who looks at you like you're god
and poses between fucks.
You and daphna are my life,
and I love you very much.
And we've both been fooled
by that before, haven't we?
Last time nearly killed us, Donald.
Whatever.
Well, where were you today?
What do you mean?
You weren't in class. Neither was gredin.
Any connection between the two?
You know, I'm going to go
because this is...
Wait. Wait. Just tell me.
Were you with him?
Yes.
Wait.
Don't go.
I don't want you to go.
I can't let you go.
I can't stop thinking about you.
I'm painting again
for the first time in years,
and it's because of you.
I've never felt this way before
in my life.
You helped me overcome my fear.
Big scaredy-cat.
Not anymore.
Donald...
What are you doing?
Kissing you.
Falling in love with you.
Don't.
Why?
Just don't.
Come here.
What?
Your beauty scares me.
It terrifies me.
Wait. Wait.
Who is it?
It's Diana.
Not right now, o.K.?
Oh, all right. I'll come back.
It's all right. Please stay.
I'm really sorry about the way
I've been acting lately.
It's just this is
a really hard transition for me,
and I, uh...
I've been confused.
But I'm not confused anymore.
Please don't give up on me.
Don't just stand there, Donald.
Invite them in.
Angela, hi. This is gredin.
I invited him.
I hope you don't mind.
No, not at all. Hi, gredin.
Do you two know each other?
Yeah. He's in my class.
Oh. Well, then we've got the posse.
It smells great in here.
Can I do anything?
You can set a place for gredin.
Hi, Lily.
Hey, little one!
Can I ask you something?
What?
Is gredin your boyfriend?
My boyfriend?
Is that you?
Yeah. Yes, it is.
Donald painted that a long time ago now,
but that's me.
Um, come in. Come on.
I'll show you around.
Very good.
Very nice.
Why didn't you tell me
you were inviting Lily?
Thought I did.
You didn't.
All set.
Need some help?
Yeah. Thanks.
Wow. You did good
with this one, Lily.
Thanks.
You bring the Cranberries for me?
Uh-huh.
Lily, grab the mineral water, would you?
It's in the fridge.
Sure.
I'm glad you're here. I wanted you here.
What's up? Where are you going?
Into the other room.
Where do you think I'm going?
Wait just a second.
Don't.
Just let me look at you.
Why did you bring him?
Because he's my boyfriend.
So, gredin, why don't you sit over here?
Lily, next to gredin.
Daphna, you're here beside Lily.
Donald, you're over here next to me.
Do you have a kit for Johnny?
Of course.
Hmm.
I'm finished, mom. I'm going to hide.
Fine, honey. You go ahead.
Lily tells me you're a photographer.
Mmm... i used to be. I'm
making a comeback.
And you're a painter?
I'm a sculptor, mostly.
An amazing sculptor.
With an aversion to life study.
That's not entirely true.
Really? News to me.
Me and Donald agree
on a couple of things.
Like your beauty, for example.
I've never seen your work before.
It's good.
It's amazing what you can
do with the right subject.
Donald's painting again.
First time in a long while. Quite...
I'm going to get some more wine.
Serious about it.
It's a secret.
So... um... how did you and Donald meet?
Wow... uh...
I wanted to do a life study class.
I... um... heard about this single,
brilliant, good-looking professor,
and, uh, weaseled my way into his class.
The rest is history.
Bit of a cliche, I know, but...
Some more?
Yeah. Thanks.
Angela was just telling us
how the two of you met.
Let's not bore them with our trivia.
Never actually thought of it
as trivia, Donald.
Where's daphna?
Sound asleep.
She should be in bed, shouldn't she?
Yeah.
Come on, sweetie.
Let's go.
I'll take her.
No. I want daddy and Lily to take me.
Oh, well.
Good night.
Let me give you a hand.
Yeah. Thank you.
There you go.
Sleep tight now, beautiful.
O.k.
Good night, little girl.
Good night, big girl.
What are you doing?
What does it feel like I'm doing?
It feels like you're fucking crazy.
I'm fucking crazy about you.
What was that?
Ah.
Ow!
Aah! I cut myself.
Here.
What are you going to do, huh?
You going to fuck me right here?
I love you.
You don't love me.
I do.
No, you don't.
Let me. Let me, please.
No! No!
No!
Lily, Lily...
Ohh! Oh!
Get off me.
Daphna!
Aah! No!
Daphna...
Don't you touch her!
Don't you... get your...
Don't you touch her, you bastard!
What's the matter with you?
Come on.
911, state your emergency...
Mamma?
Fuck you, Ivy.
Aah!
Shit!
Daphna's going to be fine.
I don't know if you care.
And you?
Am I fine, or do I care?
Oh, gredin...
I can't let you go, Lily.
Not after everything we've been through.
Oh, no. It's over, Donald.
Don't fight me, Lily.
Don't shut me out!
I can't let you go, Lily.
I love you too much. I...
Get off!
Aah!
No!
I won't hurt you. Just let me in.
The police are on their way.
I never meant to hurt you or your baby.
You have to believe me.
What are you doing?
Donald!
Aah!
Uh!
No! No! No!
Get away from me!
Go! Go! Go!
I know it's pointless
to ask you to forgive me.
O.k., well, I'm just going to talk,
and then you won't have
to deal with me anymore.
Um...
My whole life, I've... I've felt
like a freak.
You know, back home in Michigan,
I wasn't accepted
because I was different.
And then I come here,
and I'm not different enough.
So... i decided...
To become someone else...
Someone... tough and infallible...
Beautiful and sexy...
Fearless.
And it worked.
For the first time in my life,
I was accepted.
And I became intoxicated
by the freedom of it all...
Until it was too late.
It's too late, isn't it?
Well...
For what it's worth...
I love you.
Lily...
♪ Driving, hard, ♪
♪ stinging rain ♪
♪ Slapping me ♪
♪ in my face ♪
♪ Just like you, ♪
♪ screaming words ♪
♪ A side of you ♪
♪ I never heard ♪
♪ I want to go back ♪
♪ I want to go back now ♪
♪ Black as pitch, ♪
♪ vicious fights ♪
♪ All this pain ♪
♪ overnight ♪
♪ I won't cry, ♪
♪ I won't fight ♪
♪ Be the sickened ♪
♪ and be right ♪
♪ I want to go back ♪
♪ I want to go back now ♪
♪ Soaking wet ♪
♪ and torn apart ♪
♪ This can only ♪
♪ be the start ♪
♪ Broken down, ♪
♪ slapped around ♪
♪ Silence costs freedom ♪
♪ I'm raised again ♪
♪ Change of face ♪
♪ It's too late ♪
♪ to go back now ♪
♪ Go back, ♪
♪ never go back ♪
♪ Gone our separate ways, ♪
♪ and it's too late ♪
♪ Too late ♪
♪ Grown apart ♪
♪ It's too late ♪
♪ to go back now ♪
♪ Go back, ♪
♪ never go back ♪
♪ Gone our separate ways, ♪
♪ and it's too late ♪
Please rate this subtitle at www.osdb.link/j33m
Help other users to choose the best subtitles