[soft music]
Someone needs to stop Clearway Law.
Public shouldn't leave reviews for lawyers.
[music continues]
GIRL:
She was definitely a turnoff.
Too overt.
Look at her.
Obviously big problems.
I mean, most girls
don't fly through the air
with their skirt
around their waist.
Supergirl at least had
the decency to wear tights.
Not that I read comics.
I'm more the politically,
environmentally correct,
feminist, poetry-reading type.
You know...
boring.
I wonder if she posed
for that painting.
Great perm.
Blond hair.
Obvious bleach job.
Too bad it's six months old.
I don't know how she does it.
I mean,
I get airsick on a seesaw.
I guess she's sort of beautiful.
I don't know. Those lips.
You know, lips are supposed
to be a perfect reflection
of another part
of a woman's anatomy.
Not that I'm a lesbian.
Well, maybe I am.
No, definitely not.
I told my mother I was,
just for shock value.
She said, “Fine, just as long
as you don't smoke."
Which, of course,
is my main joy in life.
Probably oral compensation.
I don't think I was breastfed.
I can't imagine
where she came from.
I mean, none of the other kids
that go to my school
are that scangie.
I really wish
we could be friends.
[music fades]
Hey, a dog got hit!
Come on!
What did he say?
A dog.
[whimpering]
Ugh. Look.
BOY:
Someone should just kill it.
It's still breathing.
[thud]
Oh, God.
[eerie music]
[bell rings]
[kids shouting]
MAN: You kids pipe down!
BOY: Hey, Johnny, wait up.
Wait up.
WOMAN: Principal's office.
Please hold.
Take a seat in there.
It's a stick-on.
See?
I like the ivy.
Well, the cross makes me think
of death, but the ivy is life.
Sort of the tragic
and the hopeful, you know?
[thud]
What did you do to your hair?
Oh, it's Egyptian.
Cool.
So, what are you busted for?
I gotta keep
a certain grade-point average.
I'm slipping in biology.
Oh, you're one of those
scholarship kids.
You make it sound
like Jerry's Kids.
It's not a disease.
Oh, sorry.
Did it hurt?
Um, no. They used a gun.
It was really quick.
But you've got this wire
running through your nose.
It feels like you have a booger.
Who's the old dude who picks
you up in the pimpmobile?
Oh, it's my dad.
He's having a midlife crisis.
My name's Sylvie Cooper.
So, Cooper,
what did they nail you for?
I phoned in a bomb threat
to KTVM.
Wow.
Yeah, you know that lame guy
who does the editorials?
He said that teenagers
are too hormonally imbalanced
to have driver's licenses.
He said the age should be raised
to 21.
Well, how did they know
it was you?
Wait a sec.
I've seen your dad.
He is that guy.
That jerk on TV who does
those tweaked editorials.
You phoned in a bomb threat
to your own father?
Wow, that's great.
No, I mean it.
I'm gonna break this
to you real slow.
Your dad's an asshole.
I ought to slap you good.
Okay.
You can't put 200 people
out on a sidewalk
just because you
don't like an editorial!
They're trying to get rid of me.
Whose side are you on?
Sylvie, you hurt me.
I didn't mean to.
[scoffs]
I'm sorry, Dad.
No more than me.
'Q.
Hmm?
No more than I.
You're grounded.
[engine starts]
[horn honks]
You rich fuckhead!
I worked for it!
[lapping on window]
Hi.
It's nice and cool in here.
Um, I missed my ride.
Think you could you take me
to Olympic and Fairfax?
No.
Just a sec.
Dad, she's my best friend.
So why didn't you think
of that before?
Oh, come on.
Just this once, please?
And then
I'll be grounded forever.
What's her name?
N'! -
Oh, great.
Good Lord.
Get in.
I get carsick. Do you mind
if I sit in the front?
Sure.
Thanks.
[veins and giggles]
Your name is Ivy.
Is something wrong
with your mouth?
Oh, TMJ. It's stress-related.
It gives you terrible headaches,
makes your jaw stiff.
Almost killed Burt Reynolds.
Oh, do you have to buy condoms,
too?
No, I've gotta get a spermicide
with Nonoxynol-9 in it.
What?
Oh, it's a school project, Dad.
This HIV-positive guy
gave us a talk
about not shooting up
and using condoms.
It's not like we're supposed
to screw around or anything.
Uh, we're supposed to learn
to not be embarrassed, you know?
Don't worry, Dad. We gotta turn
everything in at the end.
Save the receipts.
[soft music]
Shit.
Hey, where have you been?
Oh, grounded.
You lost your boot.
It's my only pair.
Your turn.
No way.
Way.
Forget it.
Are you afraid?
No.
Come on. I won't laugh.
I gotta go.
HEY-
Who cares about
a stupid rope swing anyway?
What's your real name?
I like Ivy.
It sort of gives me the chance
to start over.
It's so beautiful.
Where did you get it?
From my Dad.
He must really love you.
Yeah, he also feels guilty.
I was adopted.
Oh.
See, my biological father
was black.
You can tell by my hair.
My mom is my real mom...
But, you know,
when Darryl married her...
he adopted me.
I'm pretty sure
it was to make her happy.
No, I think he really cares
about you.
My dad didn't want me
anywhere around.
He'd get so pissed
if you tried to talk to him.
He'd throw stuff at me,
like food or spitballs.
Ugh.
Your dad read Hustler?
[laughs]
I don't think so.
Well, one day I went
through his room,
and I found all this stuff,
and he had, like, 500 magazines
of the kind with the chicks
in the high heels,
and, like, they like they look
like they're ready for a...exam.
Sordid. Come on.
Hey, I bet that's why
you look so sexy...
so that your dad
would notice you.
Thank you, Doctor.
- So did it work?
- Nope.
He left anyway.
I tried to commit suicide once.
See?
- Where?
- There.
Used to be a lot worse.
Oh, is my hair thing covered up?
Yeah. Why?
My parents.
I tried to convince them that
it was female pattern balding,
you know, that my hair fell out
in the shape of an eye,
but I don't think
they really bought it.
Whoa.
Um, it's too big.
You can never find anyone.
So, um,
how are you getting home?
Hitch.
Not everybody gets to go home
in a Mercedes.
Maybe I'll see you around.
Uh...
You know, I don't really
have many friends.
[music]
Me neither.
Um, well, yeah, any friends.
Yeah. Everybody hates me.
Oh, well,
everybody hates me, too.
Um, so...
Do you want to come over?
Yeah.
We kind of have to be quiet.
My mom sleeps a lot.
She's got emphysema.
Oh.
Yeah, well,
I think it's to get attention.
She spends her life dying.
Do you got any booze?
- No. My dad--glug, glug, glug.
- Oh.
-[barks]
- Fred, quiet!
Hi, PUPPY-
Oh, um, he really only likes me.
It's this weird loyalty thing.
- You home?
- Uh, yeah.
They canceled.
Head Start.
I teach reading a couple nights
a week to some inner city kids.
MAID: Fred, no!
Well, that's mighty white
of you.
Watch it.
[music]
Wow, this is great.
[plays tune on piano]
Shh!
[tune Stops]
Sorry.
I like pianos.
If I was to kill myself,
I'd like to fall,
just close my eyes
and pretend I was flying.
Yeah, with a big splat
at the end.
Well, you wouldn't feel it.
Yeah, but everybody'd stand
around looking at your insides.
Yeah, well, it's a lot faster
than slashing your wrists.
Who slashed their wrists?
Oh, Ivy, this is my mom Georgie.
Hi there, Georg--
Did she tell you
she slashed her wrists?
Oh, Sylvia.
I'll be right back.
Hand me the Percodan.
You never stop testing, do you?
What kind of girl
is impressed by suicide?
I like her.
She has a hole in her nose.
Yeah, well, a lot of girls do.
Leave it open.
It's supposed to rain tonight.
Then open it wider.
I'd think you'd be embarrassed.
What?
Getting caught lying
all the time.
Did you tell her
you're black, too?
You don't want me
to have any friends, do you?
People you have to lie to
so they like you
aren't worth your friendship.
Look, when I'm gone you...
you can play your music
as loud as you want.
Your dad can turn this room
into a study
with leather chairs
and dead animals on the wall,
but in the meantime,
you are not
gonna hang out with a girl
who has a naked woman
with a sword on her back.
What do you think
that says to the boys?
"Try it, buddy,
and I'll cut your dick off"?
[coughs]
IVY: I'm causing a problem,
right?
- It's okay.
- Wait.
Look, I don't think your mom
wants me here right now.
Yeah, well, I want you here,
and she's sick,
and sometimes it makes her act
a little bit crazy.
She just cares about you.
Maybe I'll see you at school.
Do you go to Oakhurst, too?
Um, yeah. She has a scholarship.
I know.
I'm kind of out of place there.
I'm always out of place...
especially here.
Your home is really beautiful.
And Coop's the first girl
I've met in the city
that I can talk to.
She's a good person.
It's blocked.
So where do you live?
Um, well, my aunt gets money
for letting me stay there.
I get the picture.
Here. Let me.
What are you doing?
It was too low.
Try it now.
Aren't you afraid?
Of what?
Catching death.
Oh, Mom.
Energy never dies.
It just changes form.
Yeah, well...
you see if you're
ready to change form
when you're 38 years old.
Well, my mom died
in her forties...
but she was dead
way before that.
She only pretended to be alive.
She was so coked out
all the time,
looking out windows.
Every shadow was a cop
or a dealer she owed.
She was always asking
if I heard noises.
And she flinched
every time I touched her.
Even for a hug.
I bet you drove it with
the top down even in the rain.
Best time.
I hope that when I die...
I'll have owned a sports car...
had a family...
a home.
My mom died an old lady
who never did anything
with the top down.
Well, one day with the top down
is better than a lifetime
in a box.
[upbeat music]
SYLVIE: Groucho said he wouldn't
belong to any club
that would have him as a member.
I know what he meant,
but with Ivy it was different.
Her acceptance didn't make me
think less of her.
It made me think more of me.
At first we just
wandered around, shopped.
We developed an unspoken
division of labor:
She bought, I paid.
I got my first skintight
red leather miniskirt.
Of course, it wasn't for me.
Over the next couple of weeks,
Ivy sort of moved in.
No one seemed to mind.
I guess my parents just got used
to having her around.
Ivy's aunt was in heaven.
She kept the money, we kept Ivy.
Mom really liked her.
I think Ivy's energy
was good for her.
It's true, you know,
what Mom said.
A lot of people think
death is contagious.
Ivy's different.
Pretty phenomenal, really.
I mean, I never knew anyone that
looked that much like a slut.
Here she was, my best friend.
- Ivy?
- IVY: Yeah?
I didn't really try
to slash my wrists.
I was trying to go outside,
and--
- It's okay.
- I ran through the glass door.
And Darryl is your real father,
isn't he?
I'm afraid so.
You look more like him.
No offense.
None taken.
My mom's pretty, huh?
[smack]
[soft music]
DARRYL: Rare, huh?
Pardon?
Well, it's so clear.
I'm freezing my ass off.
Want me to get a jacket for you?
A sweater?
I hear you're having a party.
No, it's just business.
Yeah, Coop told me.
She's looking forward to proving
how hormonally balanced she is.
What are you going to do?
Well, I don't have time
to paint them over.
Don't worry. I'll get lost.
Can you hand me my boots?
Sure.
Um...
Those cost 150 bucks.
Hundred and fifty?
[rifling through cash]
Well, um...
that ought to do it.
You keep the change.
[phone rings]
Hello?
Um, no. Coop's not here.
This is her friend.
Jim from Head Start?
I really admire
your guys' dedication.
Um, wait, I'll check.
The 16th?
Yeah, she's free.
No problem.
Okay, great. I'll tell her.
No, I'm writing it down
on her calendar right now.
Okay. Bye.
“Twist on one half-turn."
More.
I'm following directions.
Hey, Dad, I noticed the Percodan
was out of Mom's room.
[grinding]
[sputtering]
You got any instant?
MAID: Espresso.
Dark bean, healthy bean.
So what's next, Dad,
you confiscate her shoelaces
and belt?
I want my pills back.
[vacuum starts]
Now!
I'll get you one, honey.
I want the goddamn bottle.
They're mine.
DARRYL: Isabelle!
Turn it off.
[vacuum shuts off]
Mom, he's only trying--
if I wanted to kill myself,
he couldn't stop me.
Ivy, would you take me
to my room, please?
Whoa, whoa.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry, Coop.
I don't want to go
to school today.
Let's do something
that'll make my parents cringe.
Come on.
[rock music]
So you're sure you're 21 now?
Twenty-two.
And how old's your friend?
[coughs]
- Thirty.
God damn, you ladies look fine.
- Could we change the music?
- No.
It helps me concentrate.
Let him concentrate, Ivy.
Yeah, 'cause you're next, honey.
No, thank you.
Oh, come on.
How about a little penis...
that says down the shaft,
"Plan ahead“?
[laughs]
Why does the penis
have to be so little?
It's one of my hottest sellers.
Usually the ladies like 'em
between their breasts.
You sure that's sterile?
You bet.
[belches]
[laughs]
Come on, Coop.
How about a little artsy one?
It'll be like we're sisters,
like blood sisters.
Yeah, if the infection
didn't kill me, my clad would.
Hello?
I thought you said you were 30.
What's happening?
She's having a little problem
leaving home.
Come on, what's more important,
death or friendship?
Please.
Look, I'm just not the type.
Well, what's that
supposed to mean?
Nothing.
Oh, but I am? Low-class?
[scoffs]
You rich little bitch,
with your socially
acceptable rebellion.
What am I, just another one of
your inner city charity cases?
Gee, I'm so sorry.
What?
That you don't have
to teach me to read.
Must break your heart.
Fuck you, Ivy.
You know what?
You don't have any class.
As a matter of fact,
you look like a slut.
Coop, wait.
I need 40 bucks to pay this guy.
I don't have any money.
Well, why don't you
just suck his dick?
Maybe he'll give you a deal.
You take American Express?
No.
Goodbye.
I don't think she's 30.
Oh, Shut...
Shut up.
N'! -
One of those bills is a hundred.
This one?
Yeah. I need it back.
I'm sorry.
What about?
I'm the asshole.
Yeah, but you're still
my best friend.
Till death.
That's beautiful.
Get away.
- Oh, my God.
- Yuck.
MAN ON TV:
And the forecast for today,
-tonight and tomorrow...
- Ow.
...in the city and outlying
areas, cool, cool, cool...
Where's the fucking bus?
I don't need no fucking bus.
I don't need no Mercedes.
I'm in charge of my own fate.
DARRYL:
Get the hell off the street!
Fuck.
Because the only people
safe there are the drug dealers.
Cosmic.
Whatever happened
to your freedom?
- Fuck, let's get out of here.
- They're armed.
They have more firepower
than the police department.
[soft rock music]
- Where are you going?
- Home.
Come on.
Carsick.
Thank you.
Well, I'll tell you one thing.
The kids are learning
the metric system here.
Kilos, grams,
that sort of thing.
We're in jail, and we have
put ourselves in jail,
while the people
who should be behind bars
are free on the streets.
This has been
A Piece of My Mind.
I'm Darryl Cooper.
General manager, KTVM.
Thank you.
And we're clear.
[indistinct conversation]
[sighs]
Can I get a juice,
a couple aspirin?
[melancholy music]
SYLVIE: I always seem
to be looking at life...
from the wrong side
of the window.
Maybe I should bleach my hair,
change my life, you know?
Platinum.
I think you'd look
like a little scangie ho.
I'm a geek.
You're beautiful.
Really?
I promise.
Do you think
I'll ever have big tits?
I mean, girls with curly hair
usually have big tits,
don't they?
Well, late bloomers always
turn out best anyhow.
Don't patronize me, Ivy.
I'm not patronizing you.
I'm loving you.
You love me?
I love you.
Well, I love you too.
Let's go.
[elevator music]
[sighs]
The FBI is gonna forget
about the bomb threat.
They figured it was some kid.
Nobody knows whose.
Do I look older?
What?
This is...
all I have.
I can't start over.
Darryl...
you must own half
the Valley by now.
What do you need a job for?
Is this party gonna help?
They're gonna eat your food,
drink your booze...
and do whatever
they already decided to.
Yeah.
What's really bothering you?
Try it.
Say something.
She promised
she'd never leave me.
Now she can barely breathe
enough to say "I love you."
[somber music]
[elevator dings]
What am I without her?
[music continues]
SYLVIE: Mom!
Sylvie?
What were you doing up there?
Nothing.
Just leave me alone.
Mom.
What?
Nothing.
Honey.
Can't I, like--I mean...
Isn't there anything
that I can do?
Like anything
to make you feel better?
Why?
Because I have a blank spot
in my schedule.
I mean, what do you think?
I feel bad all the time,
and I don't know what to do.
Do you believe in God?
[sighs]
I'm tired, okay?
Yeah, well, you know,
I'd like to know.
- Not now.
- When?
Please.
You're sick, and you don't know
what you believe?
I know I feel like shit.
I know that the idea
of taking a breath without pain
sounds like heaven...
and when you're dead,
you don't breathe...
SO...
[sighs]
I'm just tired.
Whoa.
Phenomenal.
I..-
Can explain?
[laughs nervously]
I like fuzzy things.
Like peaches, and kiwis,
and Hostess Snowballs.
I like you like this.
I think it makes you look...
- Ivy, I have--
-...more like a person.
You know,
when I first met you...
...I thought I was gonna
be intimidated by you.
Never met anybody on TV before.
But now...
you're more real.
See?
[romantic music]
I bet whoever bandaged it
forgot to do that.
[Playing piano]
[doorbell rings]
[dog barks]
Oh, my God, someone's early.
Tell Dad.
James.
Well, who died?
- What are you doing?
- Put some pants on.
I got a van
full of kids outside.
Most of them don't need the keys
to get it started.
We gotta get out of here.
Let's go.
I can't. I'm helping my dad
with his party.
- What?
- Oh, my God.
[sighs]
I must have gotten
the days mixed up.
Coop, I said you could go.
Look, 30 seconds,
and the Van's history.
Come on,
we gotta get out of here.
What's going on here?
- Hi, Mr. Cooper. How are you?
- Hi, James.
- What's this?
- What's it gonna be, Sylvie?
[sighs] You knew.
How could you do this?
I don't know.
I was counting on her help here,
James.
I promised my dad.
Great.
You know, she's the reason those
kids are even in school now.
If she doesn't show up,
why should they?
Well?
Well, maybe I could help.
I mean, I think I can handle
taking people's coats
and showing them
where the bathroom is.
Please. I feel so stupid.
Let me make it up.
I'll wear something nice.
You'll love me.
Sounds good.
Dad, what should I do?
Go ahead, honey.
We'll figure it out.
[upbeat music]
Yeah. That's right. Bob.
But I--I spell it backwards.
B-0-B.
God,
I hope they serve dinner soon.
MAN: Who cares?
I feel guilty eating his food.
MAN #2: Hey, kid. Over here.
Who's gonna tell him?
WOMAN #2:
I thought his kid had dark hair.
MAN #3:
Must be a caterer.
I wonder if Georgie
will make an appearance.
Think she will?
I heard she's getting worse.
Oh, you can cater my party
any time.
WOMAN #3:
Max, behave yourself.
MAN #4:
My fingers never left my hand.
MAN #4: His wife, remember?
Maybe she's still alive.
Hello, Mr. Cooper.
Care for anything?
That...dress fits you perfectly.
You look...
Beautiful?
Something like that, yeah.
Oh.
I almost forgot.
You're not allowed.
I'm not an alcoholic.
I used to have
a drinking problem,
but since I don't drink
anymore...
this is okay.
[somber music]
[romantic music]
[Click]
Honey,
I'm glad you're awake. I...
You look nice.
How stupid of me.
What a dumb,
sick jerk I've been.
Honey, quiet. Now, there's--
Which little party
are you afraid of me ruining?
[coughing]
Everybody's gone home.
It's okay.
[coughing]
I was so happy that Sylvie
had found a...little friend.
Honey.
Get away from me.
I thought you both
could use this.
Get out.
I feel so stupid.
I shouldn't have
worn your clothes.
Everybody said I look like you,
and he misses you so much.
I think he came
into the kitchen to cry.
And I saw him,
and I put my arms around him.
It seemed right.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
He doesn't drink.
Oh, right.
I'm sorry.
[soft music]
[glass crunching]
[romantic music]
[moaning]
SYLVIE: Fred?
Wild party.
Fred?
[whimpers]
SYLVIE: I know it's stupid
to be jealous about a dog.
It's probably because
I have low self-esteem.
The fact that Fred hated
every human except me...
really meant something.
My father never gave me
anything real.
I guess you give up
certain things
when you take on a friendship.
Come on, Fred.
I know you want some
of my special treats.
No one else gives you any,
do they?
You love me, don't you?
[music]
[grunts]
So, did it work?
What?
The party.
Well, let me tell you
about parties.
People eat your food,
drink your booze,
and do what they're
gonna do anyway.
Have you seen Fred?
Hmm?
Um...
I better get to school.
Oh, no.
Jesus.
[soft rock music]
What the hell are you doing
in my mom's car?
I found the key.
It's not yours. Get out.
Get out.
God, I wasn't doing anything.
And leave my goddamn dog alone.
You're kidding.
Gee, all my mom's stuff
seems to fit you fine.
Look, I didn't steal anything.
She said I could
borrow some stuff.
Yeah, well, you're not my
friend, and my dog's a traitor.
That's not true.
Oh, really?
Well, suddenly he seems to think
that he's yours.
Bullshit.
All right, let's find out.
Stand over there.
You know what this is?
Fuck you with a limp dick!
Do it.
Go! Do it!
- God, this is so stupid.
- Call him.
Do it!
Here, boy.
Fred.
Go ahead. Keep calling him.
[sighs]
Fred. Oh, Fred.
God damn it, Fred.
I called you.
Fred, come here.
No, Fred. Come here.
- Fred, I called you.
-[barks]
Come here, Fred.
[rattles treats]
Fred,
get your fuzzy ass over here.
That's a good boy.
Fuck you, Fred.
Here. Here's something
your mother didn't loan me.
[melancholy music]
Hi, Ivy.
L...got off work early.
I figured, what the hell...
give the girls a ride.
Coop's not here.
Oh.
Well, uh...
you want a ride?
Look, Darryl, why don't you
just give my books a ride home?
I feel like walking.
[engine starts]
Get in.
You're not my father.
That's right. I'm not.
Oh, no.
I just can't...
You already did.
Remember last night?
I can stop.
Okay. How about right here?
Stop.
Get out.
You heard me.
I hurt you?
Heard me.
[soft music]
I thought you said “hurt me."
No, I didn't.
Did I hurt you?
Ivy...
I can handle this.
Wow.
[romantic music]
[moaning]
[playing melancholy music]
[doorbell rings]
You have a key.
I didn't know
if I should use it.
Look, I'm really sorry
about your dog.
I've never had one,
and it was sort of fun
pretending he was mine.
He likes you best.
I'm sorry.
It won't ever happen again.
[soft music]
By the way, what was that record
you were playing?
Okay, Ivy, don't overdo it.
[Sylvie's piano music plays]
[gasps]
- Hi.
You think about it sometimes,
don't you?
Sometimes.
[suspenseful music]
Mom?
[somber music]
SYLVIE: I never thought my mom
would really do it.
She threatened,
but I didn't believe her.
She must have really hurt.
When she first got sick,
I thought she was faking.
I was embarrassed by her.
It made me angry.
This little oxygen bottle
she carried with her...
We'd be at the supermarket,
and she'd pull it out.
Hiss, suck. Hiss, suck.
I wanted to kill her.
Maybe if I hadn't
been so selfish...
maybe if I could have
told her I loved her...
maybe things
would be different now.
[rain and distant thunder]
[thunder crashes]
Leave it open.
The door.
You're in my mother's bed.
You looked like you
needed to be alone.
Come here.
Come here. It's okay.
Talk to me.
This is weird.
I wanted to talk to her,
you know?
Tell her stuff before she died.
Tell me.
What?
Pretend I'm her.
Come on. I'm your mom.
I don't know what to say.
Well, what couldn't you say
to me?
Come on. I'm Georgie.
But...
I was jealous of you.
When you walked into a room...
people shut up and stared.
I was glad when you got sick.
I thought I would
finally have my turn...
but I was wrong.
Everything was for you.
There was nothing left for me.
I don't buy it, Sylvie.
You were never afraid
to get angry at me.
That was easy and obvious.
What couldn't you say?
What were you afraid to say?
I love you.
MAN: The plan that's
federally supported...
would ease the debt burden...
and control the soaring
cost of medicine...
making health care
more readily available
to those who need it most:
small businesses...
independent contractors...
and the unemployed.
It's a shame
that in a country...
What the hell is this?
BOB: It's a tough way
for you to find out--
What do they think
they're doing?
I don't know.
I mean, I--
I tried to call you.
I'm sorry, Darryl.
This is Brad Daly,
general manager of KTVM...
in touch with you.
[soft music]
Hey, COOP-
Let's go for a drive...
all three of us.
All three of us?
We shouldn't be doing this.
It's completion.
A final memorial,
the kind she would have liked.
- I just feel like, I mean--
- Look.
It's your chance
to say good-bye...
and mine, too.
Well, they say it might rain.
[engine starts]
One can always hope.
Are you sure you can drive?
Yeah.
This is an automatic, right?
[laughs]
I'm just kidding.
I used to have to drive my mom
home when she was too blasted.
[tires screeching]
[shouts]
Slow down!
I thought you could drive.
Well, it was on an interstate.
All straight, no turns.
Aren't you supposed
to shift that thing
every once in a while?
Okay, forget shifting.
It's so weird.
What?
Some--like--
A whole person ending up
in something so small.
Watch it!
Whoa!
Sorry.
I'm not gonna say anything.
[Ivy singing]
What is that?
What?
That song.
What are you talking about?
You were just humming.
So?
So where'd you hear it?
I don't know.
I do. I wrote it.
Dad recorded it for Mom
for her birthday.
You heard it in her room.
So?
So...
she was playing it that morning.
Oh, my God.
You were there.
What did she say to you?
Ivy!
Come on!
She was about to kill herself.
She must have said something.
Why won't you tell me
what my mother said?
Please stop!
Say it!
I want to hear you say it!
Are you accusing me
of something?
Why, did you do something?
Everybody always
ends up blaming me!
I thought you were different!
I thought that
we were real friends!
Look out!
[both scream]
[soft music]
WOMAN ON P.A.: Dr. Shay, report
to the on-call cardiologist...
Mr. Cooper?
I know you probably feel
like strangling her,
but you're gonna
have to hold off.
She's had a head injury.
One of the nurses said
she's been hallucinating,
so I definitely want
to keep her here
for at least a couple of days.
Have fun. Nurse is gonna chase
you out in about ten minutes.
- Okay.
- I'm sorry.
Everything is Ivy.
- She did it.
- Shh.
Dad.
What the hell is this?
That's real.
Dad, she--
Where is she?
This is unbelievable.
I don't want her
at the house anymore.
What the hell's the matter
with you, Sylvie?
She killed my mother.
Your mother committed suicide.
You almost killed yourself.
You almost killed your friend.
Me?
Who drove the car?
Who took your mother's urn?
Ivy!
Oh, stop it.
Just stop the lying, will you?
- I'm not lying.
- I know you were driving.
She's gotten to you, too,
hasn't she?
That's enough.
I'll see you in the morning.
[door closes]
[soft music]
[ominous music]
[elevator dings]
Oh. Hey, Charla, room 828, OK?
We ought to put motors
on these things.
[punk rock playing]
Nice outfit.
Did you do the blood yourself?
- Thanks.
- Take care.
And enjoy the duds.
I stole them myself.
[ominous music]
DARRYL:
Oh, my God. It's Sylvie.
Sylvie;
Shit!
I can find her.
Ow! You're hurting me!
You were driving.
She made me.
- She what?
- Made me!
I was protecting you.
The car insurance.
Isn't it better
if Coop's driving?
I got to find her.
- You can't even walk!
- Aw, Jesus.
Stay inside, and I'll find her.
You just stay put.
Just stay.
[Sylvie's song playing]
[Sylvie's song playing faintly]
Mom?
I've got to tell you something.
I love you.
You killed her.
She wanted to die.
We can all be together now.
We can all be a family.
- Fuck you!
-[screams]
I can take you with me.
[shouts]
[screams]
[sobbing]
SYLVIE: I still think about her.
I guess I still love her.
She might have been even
more alone than I was.
I miss her.
[soft music]
Someone needs to stop Clearway Law.
Public shouldn't leave reviews for lawyers.