"Disturb not the harmony of
Fire, Ice or Lightning."
"Lest these Titans wreak destruction
upon the world in which they clash."
"Though the water's great guardian
shall arise to quell the fighting."
"Alone its song will fail.
Thus the earth shall turn to ash."
"Oh Chosen One. Into thine hands,
bring together all three."
"Their treasures combined
tame the beast of the sea."
Now it...begins.
Analysis indicates that the 'Titan of Fire'
referred to in the ancient inscription...
is the legendary Pokémon Moltres,
believed to have originated
in a remote region of the Orange Islands.
The 'Titan of Lightning ' is the Pokémon
Zapdos...and Articuno is the 'Titan of Ice. '
Historical documents confirm
that the three legendary Pokémon...
are unique species found only
in the vicinity of Shamouti Island.
Moltres, Zapdos and Articuno...
Any one of them would be
a priceless addition to my collection...
but together, they are the three keys
that unlock the ultimate treasure.
Pokémon matching subject parameters...
Moltres, Articuno, Zapdos...detected.
Then let's get started.
Which one is nearest?.
The Fire Pokémon, Moltres.
Good.
Now the chase is on!
Well I've taken the first piece
without much difficulty.
It's like a simple game of chess.
Next I'll capture Zapdos, and Articuno soon
after and that will flush out the 'king.'
And then... That's when the game
is going to get interesting.
"Bring together all three.
Their treasures combined tame..."
"the beast of the sea."...Lugia!
Another perfect day in paradise.
The weather:. warm. The breezes:. balmy.
The water:. calm and crystal clear.
Even Pokémon trainers deserve
a break on a day like today...
and as our heroes sail
through the Orange Islands,
Ash Ketchum dreams of
his next big adventure.
Little does he know
it will be his greatest!
Nice day.
It's beautiful...right Togepi?!.
Hey Ash you think we have time
to give the Pokémon a little fresh air?.
Sure Tracey.
It'll take us about an hour to get to
the next island. There's plenty of time!.
Well, what are we waiting for!?.
We're way off course.
That's Shamouti?.
We're right in the middle of
the end of the Orange lslands.
An island!
In a storm!
I've seen this movie!.
Do we have carp insurance?.
We're about to be...
Fillet of fish!??!.
Good morning, Delia!
Well you certainly do have a green thumb!.
Oh thanks, Professor!
But the truth is I've been getting
a lot of help with my garden lately...
the weather's been just beautiful!
Well this is the time of year
when the sun shines every day!
Say that was awfully strange.
And it passed by so quickly...
Oh my...it looks like snow!.
It is snow!.
But this is summer. How can it snow?.
I... I don't know.
What is it Mimey?!.
Mr.Mime is very upset.
Yes...and so are the other Pokémon.
Pokémon are more in tune
with nature than we are.
When something goes wrong...
they can sense it.
And I'm afraid something somewhere
is going terribly wrong.
We sure are lucky.
If we hadn't found this place
we'd be in real trouble.
I think we still might be!
How are you?.
It's been a while.
Carol I can't believe it!
It's great to see you!
What're you doing
back on Shamouti lsland?.
We got caught up in that storm
and floated in!
And it looks like we got here
at the perfect time!
You're right! The annual
Legend Festival starts today!
This is my favorite island holiday!
Are you gonna be
the star of the show again?.
No I'm too old to be
the Festival Maiden anymore...
So this year my little sister's gonna
take over for me...wonder where she...
I'm right here.
The only one not wearing
some stupid costume!.
You'd think after a few centuries
you'd alI've outgrown this dorky ritual!
It's our tradition...
you should be honored to take part!
Don't worry... I'll play
my role in the big 'legend.'
I've only seen
you do it like a zillion times!
Just be there!
Well unfortunately that's my little sister
...her name's Melody...
but don't get fooled...
she's not always this adorable.
Who's this?.
Oh sorry...this is Ash Ketchum,
he's a Pokémon Trainer.
POKÉMON TRAlNER?!.
The ancient legend foretells your arrival,
and only with you
can the Guardian of the Waters...
vanquish the great titans of
Fire, lce and Lightning.
"ln your hands...oh Chosen One..."
"...in your hands
rests the world and its fate!."
It does?.!
Don't let it worry you kid...
it's just for the tourists!
You're a Pokémon Trainer huh?.
I guess he'll do...
Here's your traditional...welcome kiss.
Are you his little sister?.
I am not!
Then I guess you must be...his girlfriend?.
That's gross!
Oh I don't think so. I'll be glad
to play for him at the legend banquet.
Starts around 8.
Oh and Misty try not to get jealous.
We have found our Chosen One!
Hurry Hurry! Deep fried Festival Cakes,
get them while they're hot!
And she says, "No, but I have Krabbys!"
It's ridiculous...me Ash's girlfriend!
It's totally ridiculous!.
I can't wait to see what my part
in the Legend ceremony is gonna be!
Ash that's her?.
The girl we met on the beach!
Melody.
Melody!.?.
Hm she's a big show off!
Hear Ye All! From the trio of islands,
ancient spheres shall you take...
For between life and death
all the difference you'll make.
Oh Chosen One! You must climb
to the shrine to right what is wrong.
And the world will be healed
by the guardian's song.
What do I do?.
I just told you, Ash!
Yeah I heard all that stuff but...
what do I have to do?!.
Oh it won't be very hard Ash...
not for you...
and besides almost all
the Chosen Ones come back alive!
Melody!.
All you have to do is get
these glass balls from three islands...
One from Fire lsland, one from lce lsland
and one from Lightning lsland,
And you bring them
to the shrine back here.
And then...
I celebrate by playing this song.
Then it's over... Oh Chosen One!
Do I get to wear a cool costume?.
Sorry but it's just come as you are...
Besides...you look perfect to me...
the handsomest Chosen One in years!
OK...get me a boat and I'm ready!
Oh there's no hurry...
you have all day tomorrow.
Tonight's just for the party!
Stay...have some fun!
Well some things're
more important than fun!
I'm Ash the Chosen One!
This is serious. I gotta be responsible.
That's a switch.
You know what?. I like your attitude!.
We can take my boat Ash!
Then let's go! You coming Misty?.
No thanks...if you want somebody to do
whatever you want whenever you want...
you should find yourself a girlfriend!
Pikachu?.!
Hey give me back my hat!
Our ship is ruined!
I'm sick over it!
I'm seasick over it!
Wasn't that...
...the twerp!
And Pikachu too.
"Disturb not the harmony of
Fire, lce or Lightening."
What a mess.
I hope the Legend Ceremony
doesn't include...a funeral!
This storm's bad...what if those two
can't make it to the island...
Carol I have to take your boat!
But Melody what can you do?.
They're caught in this storm
because of our stupid ritual...
and I'm the one who picked Ash for it.
I just hope they're alright.
What are you coming for?!.
To find Ash...and before you start saying.
It's because I secretly like him DON'T...
'cause I don't!
Hey chill out...you sure are sensitive
about somebody who's not your boyfriend!
He's NOT my boyfriend! He's a boy and
he's a friend but he's not a boyfriend!
You talking about me?.
What we won't do...
for Pikachu!
"Disturb not the harmony of
Fire, lce or Lightning."
It seems there's been a shift...
in the balance of power.
Pokémon Zapdos detected.
Experts now believe
that the weather disasters...
occurring in all parts of the globe...
are due to a powerful
and previously unknown phenomenon...
from deep beneath
the surface of the ocean.
This is a simulation of
the 'underwater river'...
that has snaked its way
around the planet,
disrupting ocean currents, weather
patterns, and the entire global climate.
I wonder if this is what's
been upsetting all the Pokémon.
The source of the disturbance
appears to be centered...
at the north central region
of the Orange Islands...
The Orange lslands?!.
But that's where Ash and
his friends are right now!
Someone's calling.
Professor we're having problems.
What is it, Professor lvy!?.
The Pokémon here are
behaving very strangely.
It looks like the storm's over.
But the sea keeps getting rougher!
The rudder!
At least we made it, but...
Pikachu, where're you going?!.
Ash we shouldn't split up,
the storm might kick up again!
Pikachu's been acting really weird!
I gotta find out why!
OK hold on guys!
Cool move.
I've been around boats all my life.
You don't have to be scared.
I never get scared out in the ocean.
I come from a Water Pokémon gym.
Hey! Are you guys OK?.!
Yeah we're fine...but I think
the boat's in pretty bad shape!
Where's Ash?.
Up there!
We're slipping!
It flies?!.
If you know how!
Awesome!
Hang on!
Let's find Ash!
Yeah, and if he needs any help...
his girlfriend's here.
But I'm not!
Well like you said you are a girl
and you are his friend...
Isn't that right?!.
Poor Moltres, you seem so miserable.
But they say misery loves company.
Zapdos approaching Fire Island.
Pikachu!
Hey look!
There they are.
I can't believe our luck.
Pikachu...
We'll get you!
The ancient sphere!.
Guess who...Pikachu!
Was that...?.
Prepare for more trouble
than you've ever seen...
And make it double,
we're on the big screen!
I'll get this on video!
I'm in a hurry, here...
and the weather's looking bad.
It has been bad.
Isn't that always our luck?.
But our luck changed.
And our ship has finally come in!
Well I hope you're happy Mr.Hero!
If you just listened to me
in the first place and...
stayed at the party like I told you to,
we wouldn't be stranded out
here on this island.
Welcome to my world.
I have to deal with
his stubborn attitude every single day.
Oh you'll get used to it...
it's just something
you're gonna need to work on...
when the two of you get married.
Take that back!
Listen to me kid,
when you get involved...
with the opposite sex
you're only asking for trouble.
Yes and that's the kind of trouble...
I stay out of.
You don't need the opposite sex...
'cause you got each other!
What does that mean?.
Pikachu...it's Zapdos!
Pikachu no!
Are you OK?!.
Pikachu's pretty tough...but Zapdos
isn't even feeling its attacks.
Those aren't attacks Jessie.
Pikachu's trying to talk to Zapdos!
It's saying, "What're you doing
over here on Fire lsland, Zapdos?"
"And where's Moltres?"
Good question.
Translation!
What's it saying?.!
It's saying "Moltres used to rule here."
"But now that Moltres is gone,
Lightning shall rule over fire..."
"and I claim this island
as my own from this day forward."
I guess Moltres flew the coop!
Absorbing Zapdos's electrical energy.
Drained of it's power...Zapdos will be
too weak to resist capture...
Once I've captured Articuno...
the real prize would appear.
Codo Blue Three. When capturing Zapdos,
we collected...something more.
More?.
Zapdos...
and Moltres!
Hey what's this?!. "Disturb not
the harmony of Fire, lce or Lightning."
"Lest these Titans wreak destruction
upon the world in which they clash."
Well this certainly is a pleasure...
though an unexpected one.
What do you think?.
Moltres, the Bird of Fire...
and Zapdos, the Bird of Lightning.
Of course without Articuno
it's not a complete set, but...
That's disgusting!
The way you talk it's like Pokémon...
are just things
to collect like dolls or stamps!
What kind of trainer are you?!.
I'm afraid I'm not a trainer young lady...
I am merely...a collector.
I began my collection with a Mew card
and now I have all this.
Legendary Pokémon have
always been my passion.
And soon my collection itself
will be legendary!
Sensors indicate
Articuno is changing course.
And now you'll have to excuse me.
The legend...could it be...
Here's a map of the area
around Shamouti Island.
The epicenter of the unprecedented
worldwide weather disasters,
though their purpose is not yet clear...
tens of thousands of Pokémon are now
making their way toward the island.
Water Pokémon are coming by sea,
flying Pokémon are coming by air,
and those unable to make the crossing are
massing on the land nearest the islands.
With me now are Professor Samuel Oak
and Professor Philena Ivy...
to help shed some light
on this phenomenon.
Near Shamouti lie the islands
of Fire, lce and Lightning,
home to the legendary birds Moltres,
Articuno and Zapdos.
I fear that they are somehow involved.
Ancient writings
from many different cultures...
name this area, specifically
the islands of Fire and lce...
as the cradle of the ocean...the source
if you will of all the waters of the world.
This has been disputed
by scientists for centuries,
but it does make some poetic sense...
when you consider what forms
what combining Fire and lce.
And...what about the island
of Lightning, Professor?.
Well imagine if an imbalance of power
occurred between Lightning, lce and Fire.
Here's potentially
how the underwater current has formed.
If the balance between the powers of...
Zapdos, Articuno and Moltres
were somehow disrupted,
it's conceivable that
a powerful underwater current,
this churning beast of the sea,
could in fact emerge from this region
and ultimately flood the entire planet.
The Pokémon seem to be gathering because
they feel a sense of impending doom.
Pokémon are acutely in tune
with the balance of nature.
The urge to correct this imbalance
is causing them to gather,
possibly to try to save the planet...
though they may be unable
to do anything about it.
And...who are you?.
My son and his friends are travelling
in the Orange lslands...
and if things get as bad as
Professor Oak says...
I may never see my boy again.
And Ash is the whole world...to me.
I could use pants!
Melody...
Well this sure beats an inflight movie.
"Disturb not the harmony of
Fire, lce or Lightning."
"Lest these Titans wreak destruction
upon the world in which they clash."
What if the ancient legend's coming true!
If it is true
all intelligent life will be destroyed.
That's right!
And I'll be...
You will be thumbed.
We gotta do something.
We have to set Moltres and Zapdos free!
Yeah...But how?.
Time to turn up the heat.
I choose you...Charizard!
Fire and electricity aren't enough!
We can't just give up.
We've gotta keep trying!
Well if things are gonna start to
get ugly! We might as well try Weezing!
Right! Go!
Come on ya big palooka,
get up and fight!
Let's try Arbok!
Now Arbok! Use your Poison Sting!
Squirtle...Bulbasaur...I choose you!
Mayday...Mayday!. Prepare for
clash landing on Lightning Island.
Look out!
I'd hate to get burned by their fire.
I'd hate to get zapped
by their lightning.
I'd hate to get hit by their droppings!
What's that sound!?.
Quick, we may need this!
Come on hurry!
Take the treasure...and put it there.
You can talk??!.
Oh right.
Fire lsland...
Lightning lsland.
So you're Ash...
You're one treasure short.
Yeah I know but...
how'd you know my name?.
Guardian help!
The great guardian...Lugia!
I can't believe it!
Lugia!?!.
That sound!
Finally...my prize!
It's magnificent. The 'Beast of
the Sea' will soon belong to me.
"Though the Guardian of the Sea
shall arise to quell the fighting."
"Alone its song will fail.
Thus the earth shall turn to ash!"
This looks bad.
What're Ash and his friends doing out
in this terrible weather?!.
I'm worried about them!
Save a little worry for us!
The fate of our planet is what we
should really be worried about...
and the Pokémon know that
better than any of us.
There's only one hope...
Only the Chosen One can
bring together the treasures...
to help the water's great guardian.
But the legend says its song will fail!
"...And thus the earth
shall turn to ash."
But how are we ever
gonna find the Chosen One...
if we don't even know where to look?.
It's right in the legend!...
"the earth shall turn to Ash!"
Ash...it's talking about you!
I'm the...Chosen One!?.
Whoa wait a minute...
training Pokémon is tough enough,
but saving the world is way too hard!
I know it doesn't sound easy, Ash...
but you're the only one who matches
the legend perfectly. What do you say?.
Well right now I wish my mom
had named me Bob instead of Ash.
Ash this whole thing is my fault... I...
I never should've dragged you into this.
Well I guess
I gotta go along with that.
Don't blame yourself.
Ash always gets us into trouble.
Yeah, but nothing like this!
Lugia...the sound it makes is
just like the song from the legend!
This song...the song has
restored my strength.
But it alone cannot bring harmony
to the three warring ones.
What do you mean?!.
When the treasures of Fire, Ice
and Lightning are aligned,
my song shall harmonize
with their powers
and tame the beasts both above,
and below the sea.
But this can come to pass
only with the help of the Chosen One...
But what can I do
that somebody else can't?.
Only in the hands of
the true Chosen One...
will the Ice sphere glow
like the others, its power awakened.
I have to go...there?.
The choice is yours.
You must go only where your heart leads.
Maybe l...
I can?.
You think so too?.
Okay...
I'll do whatever it takes
to get that third treasure...
but what if I mess up...what if l?.
You can do it.
We know you can.
Yeah you're right I CAN do it!
I'm the Chosen One!
Right now I feel more
like the Frozen One!
Maybe they got the wrong Ash.
This is a lot better than walking
Pikachu. We'll be there is no time now!
Good luck Ash.
He's always the hero.
We're always a zero.
We could be heroes too
if we ever caught a break.
I've got an idea!
We'll never get there now.
Who could that be?.
If that kid thinks
we're here for trouble...
we're certainly going
to burst his bubble!
Instead of causing tribulation...
we're undergoing a transformation!
Though it's way
outside our usual range...
we're going to do
something nice for a change!
Jessie!
James!
Up till now, Team Rocket's
been quite unscrupulous!
Being good guys for once
would be super-dupulous!
That's ri-ight.
What're they doing here?.
You wanna help?!.
Of course!
We don't want the world destroyed!
Even if we survived....
There would be nobody left
to steal from!
We'd be out of work!!
Come to think of this...when was
the last time we had a vacation?.
We'll be on a permanent vacation, if we
don't get to that island. Let's do it!
Evasive maneuvers!
On the double!
Up there!
Okay...you got the third treasure.
Now come on,
let's get back to the island!
Right!
I almost forgot!
Come on let's go!
The treasure...?.
I got it!
Get on.
Pikachu!
DON'T LEAVE WlTHOUT US!
Hold on tight!.
We're slowing Lugia down,
the three of us are too heavy!
Let's try Weight Watchers!
It's too late for that now!
I heard it's never too late
if you really stick to the program!
If we don't let go
they may not make it back!
Let's protect the world
from devastation!
Guess we gotta let go!
Are you guys ready?.
Let's do it!
What're you doing?!.
Team Rocket's blasting off
for goooooood!
Team Rocket!
Think we did the right thing?.
I know we did the right thing Jessie.
and it feels great.
Well this is it, then.
Let's not say "goodbye!"
Let's just say...
"we're gonna die!"
Lugia, why're all
those Pokémon down there?.
Because they feel they must be here
in case they are needed.
But what could they do to help?.
They are not sure,
and that is why they are here.
What do you mean?.
That just one Pokémon
could help the world...
would be worth the journey
for thousands of them any day.
But this day, the one that can
make all the difference...is you.
Please hurry.
Let's hope the... Iegend is...true.
Soon, Lugia you will be mine
and my destiny will be fulfilled at last.
I have failed.
Here...take this.
Legend or not...
Ash can't do this alone.
You'll have to play Lugia's song.
I'll go look for him.
And Ash is never really alone
'cause he's got...
me.
Ash!
Pikachu...just hang on!
Come on Ash...breathe!
You've got to.
Please Ash, please, you can't...
The sphere...?!.
Ash...!
Let me go! I've gotta do this!
He made it!
Have you brought
the final treasure, Ash?.
Here it is Slowking!
You must be the one to place it!
The song.
And as you can see
from these live pictures,
the severe weather that's caused havoc
around the globe has finally ended.
The beast of the sea has been tamed.
The fate of the world could not
have been in better hands.
Ash! Ash!
Oh...my lamega!
It's my mom!
All right...start talking!
You are in big trouble Mister!
But...Mrs.Ketchum Ash just
helped save the whole world!
Oh he did, did he!?....
Well I could've lost my whole world!
Every day I worry about you
and wonder if you're all right.
I know I can't stop you...from doing
the things you need to do.
I just can't help missing you
all the time.
You're a Pokémon trainer,
and that's just how it is...
But next time, could you try to save
the world just a little closer to home?.
I guess l...could give it a try.
And remember, every day,
you're my hero.
Thanks Mom!
We've got to get back to Pallet Town...
and tell the other Pokémon
researchers about this.
Come on!
How it all began...
and how I'll begin again.
Who'd believe it?.
For once we were heroes!
Too bad nobody saw us.
Guess again.
What...did you...say?.
Lots of people saw
what you did out there...
and all of them are
watching you right now.
Oh...then I guess the bad guys...
are finally...
good guys!
So then we're not bad!
That's good!
What if the Boss finds out?.
That's bad!
We'll start our own Team.
That's good!
But we got no money.
That's bad!
Then we'll just steal some!
That's good! Or is that bad?.