( Pikachu )
Pika!
( Announcer )
Pokémon.
Dazzling and awe-inspiring.
The amazing creatures
that thrive on this planet.
In numbers virtually too massive
to even begin to count,
hundreds-
thousands is the more likely total-
but numerous and varied,
to be sure!
Watch Movies, TV Series and Live Sports
Signup Here -> WWW.ADMITME.APP
People and Pokémon
competing together against
others in the Pokémon battle
and hoping to one day
become champions.
Living together
and reaching out to each other
as friends and comrades.
Which brings us
Ash Ketchum from Pallet Town,
working with Pikachu
to catch other Pokémon
and perfect the art of the battle.
Traveling far and wide
with good friends
while honing
his many battling skills.
And with every new Pokémon
our heroes meet along
their exciting journey,
a new adventure awaits them.
But now...
[thundering]
...amidst the fearsome distortions
of space and time,
one unfortunate encounter
has plunged the planet into crisis
and given birth to a new hatred.
In the unmoving,
intertwined strings of fate,
tangled and inextricable
and seeking an answer
beyond time and space,
even now there are those
who seek to find an answer.
It is time to return
the Jewel of Life.
Welcome.
Take it!
What are you doing?
I cannot give you
the Jewel of Life.
You have betrayed me
and you're trying to destroy me!
The time has come.
Human beings must be
brought to justice!
Piplup.
Pika.
( Pikachu )
Pika, Pika.
Pip, Pip, Pip, Pip, Piplup!
Pika!
Pip, Piplup!
[laughing]
Ash's journey to become
a Pokémon master continues,
as along with Pikachu and
his friends, Dawn and Brock,
he happily arrives in Michina Town,
a beautiful place
surrounded by nature.
All right, everyone, come on out!
Staravia!
Bui!
Grotle!
Monferno!
Gliscor!
- You guys, too!
- All right, and you!
Buneary!
Mamo!
- Sudowoodo, Sudowoodo. ..
- Happiny!
Croag.
Yeah!
[laughing]
- Buneary!
- Pika, Pika!
Piplup!
Pip, Pip, Piplup!
[laughing]
Oh, you think you're funny?
Gliscor!
Hap, Happiny!
Hap, Hap!
Happiny!
Hap, Happiny!
Hap, Happiny, Happiny!
Pip?
Huh, watermelons?
They sure are.
Wow.
This is our lucky day!
Hold on!
See, those watermelons are ours!
They were cooling down,
but the stream caught 'em.
Hmm, what a shame.
Tough break.
Okay, then you can have
'em on one condition.
Beat us in a battle!
( Both ) - Huh?
- Huh?
Yeah, we'll settle this
with a tag battle.
( Both ) - Huh?
- Huh?
Okay, I guess that's only fair.
Fair and square!
- Piplup!
- Pika!
♪ Sometimes it's hard to know ♪
♪ Which way you're supposed to go ♪
♪ But deep inside ♪
♪ You know you're strong ♪
♪ If you follow your heart ♪
♪ You can't be wrong ♪
♪ Sometimes it's hard to see ♪
♪ Just what's your destiny ♪
♪ But when you find
the path that's true ♪
♪ You'll know that's
the one for you ♪
♪Standup ♪
♪ For what is right ♪
♪Be brave ♪
♪ Get ready to fight ♪
♪ Hold on ♪
♪ We're friends for life ♪
♪ And if we come together as one ♪
♪ Complete the quest
that we've begun ♪
♪ We will win the battle ♪
♪Pokémon♪
♪ Woo-hoo ♪
♪ The time is now
the game's begun ♪
♪ Together we will fight as one ♪
♪ Each of us in our own way ♪
♪ Can make this world
a better place ♪
♪Standup ♪
♪ For what is right ♪
♪Be brave ♪
♪ Get ready to fight ♪
♪ Hold on ♪
♪ We're friends for life ♪
♪ And if we come together as one ♪
♪ Complete the quest
that we've begun ♪
♪ We will win the battle ♪
♪Pokémon♪
♪ Just when it seems ♪
♪ That you are lost and all alone ♪
♪ You will find the courage
and the strength ♪
♪ To carry on ♪
♪ And if you fall along the way ♪
♪ Have the faith you'll be okay ♪
♪ 'Cause your friends
are there for you ♪
♪ Reaching out
to pull you through ♪
♪Standup ♪
♪ For what is right ♪
♪Be brave ♪
♪ Get ready to fight ♪
♪ Hold on ♪
♪ We're friends for life ♪
♪ And if we come together as one ♪
♪ Complete the quest
that we've begun ♪
♪ We will win the battle ♪
♪Pokémon♪♪
[laughing]
Pikachu!
You really can't come to this town
without seeing the ruins!
Ruins?
Yeah, of a temple from
thousands of years ago.
Hey, the guidebook talks
about them as well.
Wow, I wanna see 'em.
You're gonna love 'em,
they're the best!
So what do you say
we check the ruins out?
Pika!
Piplup!
( Brock )
The ruins are way up there.
Mmm, I can feel positive energy
flowing through this place.
- Me too!
- Pika!
- It feels so great!
- Piplup!
Pi... Pika?
Piplup!
What's that?
Quick, Pikachu, use Thunderbolt!
Pikachu!
[panting]
A thunder creature
and creature master!
Let's hurry!
The Pokémon are running away!
Something's happening!
- Piplup!
- Let's move!
[screaming]
- Oh, no, Pikachu!
- Piplup!
Piplup!
Piplup, Lup, Lup!
Lup, Lup, Lup, Lup,
Lup, Lup, Lup, Lup...
Now, Dialga, come forth.
Dialga, please save
these Pokémon for me.
( All ) - Huh?
- Huh?
Lup, Lup, Lup, Lup,
Lup, Lup...
Piplup!
Piplup, Piplup!
The legendary Pokémon
that rules time.
- Dialga!
- But how?
And how did she talk to it?
Lup!
[screaming]
- Pip.
- Pika.
Hey, Dialga!
- Wow!
- Pika!
It's Giratina!
( All ) - Oh!
- Oh!
It's too dangerous!
Get away, quick!
( Dawn )
Right!
Giratina's after Dialga still.
Please, stop it, Giratina!
Pip, Piplup!
Yeah, come on!
Dialga saved Piplup
and Pikachu for us!
Pika!
Giratina...
Pikachu.
Now transcend the confines
of time and space.
Giratina.
Sheena!
Giratina's rage,
it's just too strong.
Huh?
Giratina, can't you feel
we're right here with you?
Pika, Pika!
[groaning]
- Giratina!
- Pikachu!
Pikachu!
Pika!
So you remembered us, wow!
Pikachu.
Giratina's rage, it's gone.
Now's the time.
Transcend the confines
of time and space.
You have misunderstood, Dialga.
Please don't battle.
It looks like Giratina gets it now.
That's nice if it's true,
but I should have
seen it in its heart.
Should have seen in its heart?
You see, I have the power
to connect my heart
to the hearts of Pokémon.
With Pokémon?
Then you can connect with Dialga?
Yes, and it's surely lent me
some of it strength.
- Dialga has?
- Pika!
Hi, my name is Sheena,
and I'm a guardian of these ruins.
Same here, too.
My name's Kevin.
So were any of you injured?
- No, we're fine!
- Piplup!
My name is Dawn.
My name's Ash.
And this is my partner, Pikachu.
Thanks for saving my buddy.
- Pika.
- Huh?
Long ago, there was a thunder
creature and its master
and they changed
the fate of this town.
Yes, you see, it's part of
the legend of this town.
Wait a minute, a thunder
creature and its master?
- You mean me and Pikachu?
- Pika.
I have a feeling our meeting
may have been fated.
So would you mind
coming with us?
I'll do whatever you want.
I mean, after all,
you saved Pikachu's life!
Pika, Pika!
Sheena.
I'm Brock, another fated person.
Why, just a short moment ago,
I took a fated tumble
and scraped my elbow
which then led to the fated fact
that you would kiss it
and make it better.
And also, fate would
have you stroke me
with that beautiful hand of yours,
which is the miracle that
took away all of my pain!
All because of the fickle
finger of fate!
And now, I know it is fated
that you and I go out on a date,
fated that we get to
know each other
and build our feelings
on the fated love
that I know is there inside!
Such a lovely silken hand- Huh?
- Croag.
- Uh...
Croag.
Ah!
[groaning]
Wrong hand!
Croag.
Dialga!
Look out!
Sheena, we've got to go
or we'll get caught in
the water spout!
But wait!
It's Palkia!
The legendary Pokémon
that rules space!
Hey, look at that!
Palkia saved Dialga!
- Cool!
- Pika!
Transcend the confines
of time and space.
Hold on, "transcend"?
It means rise above or go over.
You see, right now,
Sheena's connected to
the hearts of both
of those Pokémon.
- She's synching with them.
- Piplup!
Thank you...Palkia, Dialga.
Pika.
They're gone!
They've returned to
their own dimensions.
See that?
I don't believe it.
I don't get it.
I don't know what to get!
Duh, we saw the time-space Pokémon!
And a woman who can
control them as well!
Tapping into the hearts of
Pokémon rocks,
but I think she's got
control issues, too.
I wonder if I can do that.
Hmm...
You know what?
You're just creeping me out!
Wait, what's this?
No way!
You tuning in something?
Ah, ooh!
Oh, I sure am!
My good looks!
( Brock ) I can't believe
we're under the ruins.
- What's that?
- Pika.
The time-space axis.
Time-space axis?
Yes, that's right.
It indicates the condition
of every minute change
in the time-space continua.
( Brock )
Amazing!
( Sheena ) We use it to
investigate those places
where space and time
have been disrupted.
Space and time disruptions?
That's correct.
We watched the strange
mutations at Alamos Town.
( Sheena ) And when that
hole in space and time opened
near the glacier,
we were there, too.
( All ) - Hmm...
- Hmm...
Pika?
Here is our world, which is in turn
supported by this,
Giratina's reverse world.
Here we have
the dimension of Dialga.
Here, Palkia's dimension.
On top of that, Arceus' dimension.
What's Arceus' dimension?
I've never heard of it.
Is it a Pokémon?
Right.
The legendary Pokémon said to
have created its entire world.
Entire world?
By a Pokémon.
It's also said to have
created these worlds, too.
A Pokémon that creates
entire worlds, wow!
Well, isn't that special?
I wouldn't wanna
meet it in a dark alley!
( Sheena )
There is an omen that predicts
Arceus will soon
awaken from its long slumber.
Long slumber?
Massive whirlpools of energy
are beginning to form around Arceus
as it begins to awaken.
These whirlpools
are distorting space
and brought
Dialga and Palkia's dimensions,
which were designed to
remain eternally separated,
into contact with each other.
So Dialga and Palkia,
who shouldn't ever have met,
collided with one another
in Alamos Town.
( Brock ) While both of them
thought the other had tried to
threaten its territory!
( Sheena )
Exactly.
Their battle also affected
the reverse world,
which brought Giratina
into the conflict as well.
But, Sheena, you already
resolved the conflict
between Dialga and Palkia,
didn't you?
Yes.
Wait a minute!
Why didn't Giratina understand you?
When a Pokémon is
overcome with rage,
she can't connect...with its heart.
Rage.
( All ) - Huh?
- Huh?
You see, we've been using
the altar to pinpoint
the moment
when Arceus will appear.
( Ash )
Why will it do that?
It holds a grudge against humanity.
Arceus remains intent on
bringing us all to justice.
Pika!
Justice?
Yes, justice.
It's possible that Arceus
will destroy us entirely.
A Pokémon destroying all people?
No way, it can't be!
Have a look at this.
It's a legend of this place.
- Look at that!
- It's Arceus!
( Sheena ) When it appeared
that fragments from the stars
would destroy much of the Pokémon...
Arceus sacrificed itself
in order to fend off the danger.
So it stopped meteors?
Awesome!
What an incredible Pokémon!
Arceus had been carrying
the 16 life plates around with it
that could be used to counter
all possible attacks.
But it lost the life plates
in a collision with meteors,
Making its death a near certainty.
( Sheena ) Then Arceus was
saved by a man named Damos
who returned the life plates
to their rightful owner.
Back then, Michina was
little more than a wasteland
spreading out over the land...
but when Arceus saw this,
it was overcome with pity,
so it removed the powers
of water, grass, ground
and electricity
from the life plates
and on top of that, the dragon.
It then combined them into one,
making the Jewel of Life.
Whoa, the Jewel of Life?
Arceus trusted Damos
and bestowed upon him
the Jewel of Life,
even though this meant putting
its own life in grave danger.
Arceus' magnificent strength
flowed out of the Jewel of Life,
turning that wasteland
that was Michina
into a fertile paradise.
- Awesome!
- Piplup!
And then came the day
when Damos was to return the jewel,
the day when the moon
covered the sun.
A solar eclipse?
( Sheena )
Yes.
However, Damos broke his promise
and instead of returning
the Jewel of Life,
he attacked Arceus.
Why?
Well, Damos believed that
if he were to return the Jewel,
this area would go back to being
an uncultivated wasteland.
( Kevin )
Feeling profoundly betrayed,
Arceus fell into a rage
and destroyed the shrine.
And then, in order to heal itself
from its injuries,
Arceus began a long sleep.
I can see why Arceus was upset.
And Arceus went as far as
to give up a part of itself
to try and help Damos.
So in the end it was Damos
that acted so terribly.
Damos is...my ancestor.
What?!
And this...
is the Jewel of Life.
[all gasping]
The mother lode! That's it!
That jewel's what
I'm talking about!
A jewel of a jewel!
First things first, we need that!
And what about Arceus?
Duh, we need that, too!
The thrill of double prizes!
[humming]
♪ Catching legends
means one thing ♪
♪ We'll be legends too ♪♪
( all ) - Huh?
- Huh?
( Sheena ) "Return thus
to Arceus, the Jewel of Life.
Placate its rage lest
destruction visit this land."
See, it is written.
It's a message to us
from our ancestors.
So then that means
they realized their mistake.
Yes.
We must return
the Jewel of Life to Arceus
so that we may calm its wrath.
What's goin' on?
Now, Arceus is coming!
[all gasping]
The time has come!
Prepare for justice!
Damos.
Arceus, please, you've got to stop!
Who are you?
I am a descendant
of Damos, you see,
and I know my ancestor
did a terrible thing to you.
Please forgive us.
( Jessie )
That's the Pokémon, right?
Arceus, yes.
And I'd bet money
that hulk ain't too pleased.
( Sheena )
This is the Jewel of Life.
What?
Here, I humbly return it to you.
My family has been protecting it
so that one day we might
present it to you again.
Heads up, guys, grab it now!
James can, since he's a guy.
I insist, ladies first.
Meowths first.
No, James!
Whatever, James!
You're saying this is
the Jewel of Life?
The Jewel of Life is a part of me.
It cannot and will not break!
Sheena!
[screaming]
( Team Rocket ) - We're blasting off again!
- We're blasting off again!
( Piplup )
Piplup!
A forgery? But how?
I don't get it, Sheena.
What's going on?
I don't know.
I truly thought it was
the real thing all along.
Okay, so where's the real one?
I won't let humanity
deceive me anymore!
Arceus, wait!
I swear I had no idea
it was a counterfeit.
Please believe me.
Now transcend the confines
of time and space.
[screaming]
Sheena!
Arceus' rage is too strong.
You shall be brought to justice!
Are you siding with the humans?
Palkia's attacks aren't working!
Arceus has to be using
the life plates
to defend against
its opponents' attacks!
Out of my way!
What do we do?
Dialga...
It's trying to tell me something.
Huh?
Not even magical creatures
shall be forgiven
for siding with human beings.
Take this!
Dialga!
- Come on, Arceus, stop this!
- Pika, Pika!
Oh, no, if this keeps up...
Lup.
Pikachu, use Thunderbolt!
Pikachu!
- What?
- Did it work?
Remember that Arceus
lost several of its life plates
and one was a defense against
Electric-type attacks.
That's right!
Pikachu, use Thunderbolt again!
Pikachu!
Out of my way!
( Piplup )
Piplup!
You all shall be
brought to justice!
Everyone, get away!
- Giratina!
- Pika!
Giratina understands!
Palkia is distorting space
to stop Arceus now.
Dialga.
Huh?
Oh...
- Oh...
- Pika!
What's going on?
How is this happening?
It's nighttime.
Not exactly.
An eclipse! Yeah, but when-
Look, the ruins!
What's going on?
( Sheena ) Dialga must
have sent us into the past.
( Ash ) - What? (
Dawn ) - To the past?
Yes, back to the day
of the fated promise with Arceus.
Oh!
It's time to return
the Jewel of Life.
So that must be Arceus in the past!
It sure looks that way.
( Man )
Here is the Jewel of Life.
I welcome you inside.
Please follow me.
There, now take it!
No!
What are you doing?
Huh? What in the world?
The time-space axis showed this.
Damos never returned
the Jewel of Life.
Instead, he attacked Arceus.
Whoa! That's Damos!
Can it be?
It's not, it's counterfeit.
The real one is right here.
I could never give you
the real Jewel of Life!
You fool!
Michina will flourish for evermore
and never will it
turn into a wasteland!
You have betrayed me
and are trying to destroy me!
Ahhh!
They're falling!
It's too dangerous here!
What should we do?
Please, Dialga...
send us back further into the past.
[screaming]
[gasping]
Still breathing.
[screaming]
What is that?
Huh?
The sun's shining again.
Looks like Dialga
did what you asked!
Lup!
[gasping]
Pichu, Pichu, Pi.
- Lup!
- Pika!
What is this?
( Man ) Master Marcus,
strange people have appeared.
That man.
Heatran!
Bronzong, use Hypnosis.
Bronzong.
Zong.
You people are clearly
not of this land.
Yes, we have come here
from the future.
What?
To stop you from
battling with Arceus.
Such strange words you speak.
We know everything that's
going to happen in the future.
- Oh?
- Please believe me.
Well, then, let us hear
what this woman has to say.
Have the children wait in the cell.
Take good care of them.
( Man )
Sir!
Pi?
Pi...
Pichu!
Pi, Pichu, Pichu!
[groaning]
( Pikachu ) - Pi. (
Piplup ) - Piplup.
Pip, Piplup!
Pika.
- Piplup.
- Pika.
Piplup.
[ Snoring ]
- Pika.
- Piplup.
Pip, Piplup!
Pika, Pika.
Lup!
Piplup.
Pika!
Pip, Piplup!
Pika?
Pichu, Pichu.
Pi, Pichu, Pi, Pi, Pichu.
Pi, Pi, Pichu.
Pika, Pika, Pika.
Pi, Pi, Pi, Pichu.
- Pika!
- Piplup!
Pikachu.
Piplup.
Pi, Pichu!
Piplup!
Piplup.
- Pichu!
- Pika!
Pip, Pip, Pip, Pip, Piplup.
In here.
- Huh?
Hey, tell us where we are anyway!
What do we have here?
You see, this is
the underground prison
and one of Master Marcus'
mysterious creatures
just used Hypnosis on all of you.
Mysterious? He means Pokémon!
I see, that was Bronzong!
Whoa.
Where's Pikachu?
- And what happened to Piplup?
- And Sheena?
They're safe.
Sheena is speaking with
Master Marcus right now.
Marcus?
Yeah, remember?
I wonder who Marcus is.
( Damos )
The backstabber.
( All ) - Huh?
- Huh?
It's true, you see.
Marcus was an underling of mine,
but he tricked me
and threw me in jail.
- You must be--
- Damos!
Wait, you're saying you know me?
Yes, of course.
But you're not from here.
I wanna know why you won't return
the Jewel of Life to Arceus!
And why are you setting
a trap for Arceus, too?
I am doing nothing of the sort!
I have every intention of returning
the Jewel of Life to Arceus!
You're a liar!
It's the truth!
That's why Marcus put me in jail.
To keep me from
doing that very thing.
( All ) - Huh?
- Huh?
May I say something?
That man is definitely
speaking the truth.
I absolutely know
for a fact that Damos
was attempting to return
the Jewel of Life back to Arceus.
What I'm completely uncertain about
is whether or not
that's the correct action
for Damos to take.
So you're telling the truth?
Hey, the Hypnosis!
Right, Bronzong used it!
So Marcus must have used
Hypnosis on Damos
and manipulated him as well!
Of course!
Hold on.
What in the world
are you talking about?
We came here from the future,
you see?
The future?
Take a look at this.
Monferno!
Magical creature!
In the future,
this is called a Pokéball.
Return!
Of course,
you don't have these yet.
And back where we come from,
what you call magical creatures,
we call Pokémon!
Pokémon?
I understand it now.
You said you all came here
from the future
and you were telling the truth.
Damos has no intention of returning
the Jewel of Life back to Arceus.
I'm certain of that.
I see.
But then, if Arceus doesn't
get the Jewel of Life back,
terrible things
will start to happen.
What kind of things?
Concerning you and Damos.
What are you saying?
You have to trust me, please!
Chu, Chu, Chu, Chu!
Pi, Pi, Pi!
Pip, Piplup, Pip, Pip!
Piplup!
- Pika!
- Chu?
Pika.
Quit dillydallying!
Quil, Quil, Quil, Quil...
- Quil!
- No goofing off!
Quil, Quil, Quil, Quil!
[sniffing]
Pip, Pip!
Piplup, Piplup!
Lup...
Pika!
[gasping]
Don't come near me! Stay back!
What do you want?!
[groaning]
Pichu, Pi, Pi!
Pichu!
Quil, Quil...
Piplup!
Pichu!
Pi, Pikachu!
Chika, chika!
Pika, Pika!
Pichu!
Piplup!
Huh?
Hey, wait!
Okay, you guys, I think we'll
be able to chill out here.
Huh?
Could it be?
Say, it's a helmet
from ancient times!
Whoa, and check this out!
We're talking ancient crown here.
Feast your eyes.
Doesn't this antique tiara
set off my modern look?
This place is
teeming with treasure.
I love work when you're
using your head.
Palkia, please hold on.
I beg you.
So you're telling me that
I betray Arceus in the future.
That's it.
That's what the legend says, and. ..
The people of Michina
saw you as an evil man
from then on.
As if I could ever betray Arceus.
Arceus, who saved us all.
If this keeps up,
it's the end of the world!
It's Arceus!
[gasping]
[men shouting]
( Damos )
The world has escaped destruction.
Arceus, please.
Transcend the confines
of time and space.
[groaning]
Human...
are you the one who saved me?
Oh, no, no, Arceus.
It was you who saved us.
But then...
terrible things had happened
to the town of Michina.
It struggled for its survival.
If it keeps up like this,
we won't survive the winter.
Damos.
You want to revitalize this land,
don't you?
Yes.
How pitiful.
All right.
I shall lend you my strength.
These keep me alive.
They're a part of my being.
The power of ground,
water and grass,
and combined with this,
the power of electricity,
they all meld together.
And with the power of dragon,
they increase.
Use this Jewel of Life
for the greater good,
to make the land rich and fertile.
The Jewel of Life.
But...
without that jewel,
my life is diminished.
Damos, I am trusting you.
Trusting you with my life.
Arceus, I thank you.
You have my word.
I will return it back to you.
( Damos ) Through the
grace of the Jewel of Life,
the land blossomed and flourished.
Mr. Damos!
It looks like we'll be able to
harvest this year, too!
That's right, we shall
all work together.
Soon, I'll be able to return
the Jewel of Life.
I understand.
I will wait until the time
when the moon next covers the sun.
Thank you.
Until then, I will continue
revitalizing the land.
And so the days passed by
and I constructed a shrine,
dedicated to Arceus
to show my enormous
and eternal gratitude.
And soon the moon
will cover the sun.
[all gasping]
Then today's the day
of the promise!
From what you know,
would you mind telling me
what sort of attacks Damos
might have used on Arceus?
He used several Electric attacks
and then dropped
a boulder on Arceus.
What about silver water?
I guess he didn't use it.
Understood, I believe you.
I shall stop Damos at once.
We must return
the Jewel of Life to Arceus.
This is the Jewel of Life.
You shall return it to Arceus.
Let's go.
You shall change history.
Thank you, sir.
Chu, Chu, Chu, Chu...
Pip, Piplup, Piplup!
Pichu, Pichu.
Pichu.
Pichu, Pi.
Pi, Pichu.
Pi, Pichu...
Pika, Pikachu!
Lup!
[door opening]
Chu?
Pika!
Dile!
Pichu...
Pika...
Pi, Pi!
Pichu, Pichu!
Pichu, Pi!
Dile, Dile, Dile, Dile.
How do we get out of this joint?
( James )
And there's nary a trace of twerps.
( Jessie )
Twerps shmerps, I need a nap.
[groaning]
[shouting]
[screaming]
Enough already.
Huh?
Look at this.
[screaming]
( All ) - Huh?
- Huh?
I must go.
I must return
the Jewel of Life to Arceus.
But how are you going to get
yourself out of here?
I have friends as well.
Pi, Pichu!
Pichu!
Pichu...thanks so much.
Pika, Pikapi!
Pip, Piplup!
Pikachu!
Thank goodness you're safe, Piplup!
- What a relief.
- Piplup!
Pichu, Pichu.
Oh, so they helped you out, too,
did they?
Chu!
Damos, you can see the hearts
of Pokémon as well, right?
That's because he's
Sheena's ancestor.
- Yeah, that's right!
- Pika!
[humming]
Thank you...
children from the future.
Chu!
Hey, Damos!
It is time to return
the Jewel of Life.
My name is Sheena.
Here is the Jewel of Life.
Where is Damos?
He isn't coming.
Did something happen to him?
He was going to betray you.
It can't be.
Yes, it's true.
But I have the Jewel-
[gasping]
No!
You have deceived me!
That's not true!
Now, the silver water!
What's this?
Something's not right.
Maybe we're too late!
There's Sheena!
The Jewel of Life is right here,
but I'm not just going to
give it back to you.
You, how could you do this?
Many thanks for telling me
all about the future, dear,
because now history's
about to change!
Stop it, all of you!
[screaming]
Was that Damos just now?
Yeah!
Ash, wait!
I'm gonna go and get
the Jewel of Life back from Marcus!
Are you hurt?
Who are you?
Pichu.
Damos.
I know this wasn't your fault.
- You must be Sheena.
- Right.
I did something foolish.
If only I had realized Marcus
would betray me this way.
Sudowoodo!
Use Hammer Arm!
Good work, return.
Now Michina will forever flourish.
The end of desolation.
Marcus!
You give the Jewel of Life to
Arceus right now or else!
It's too late for that.
It belongs to us now.
Heatran!
Quick, Pikachu, use Thunderbolt!
Chu!
Bronzong!
Bronzong.
- Piplup!
- Look out!
I'm certain that one day
you all will thank me.
What for?
Because I am saving the future.
Saving the future?
Arceus will perish here,
which means there
won't be a way for Arceus
to appear in the future ever again.
I am changing history!
Damos, why did you betray me?
Why?!
( Piplup ) Lup, Lup, Lup,
Lup, Lup, Lup, Lup, Lup...
All right, Pikachu,
use Volt Tackle!
Pika!
Pika, Pika!
Zong!
Now, Piplup, use Whirlpool!
Pikachu, Thunderbolt, let's go!
Chu!
Sheena, give me your hand.
( Both ) Transcend the
confines of time and space.
Everyone.
Arceus sacrificed its
very life to save us,
and also, to save our land.
Pichu.
[ Pokémon talking ]
- Pika!
- Piplup, Piplup!
Magical creatures
live in the shrine?
Can you guys help us?
[ Pokémon talking ]
All right!
Everyone stop your attacks.
Huh?
They stopped attacking!
Pi, Pichu, Chu!
Arceus.
Please, look at me.
[screaming]
Chu, Pichu, Pichu!
Sheena!
[grunting]
Heatran, Bronzong,
take care of this!
Huh, what the...
Pika, Pika!
Heatran!
Pip, Pip, Pip, Lup, Lup!
Pika.
- Bronzong!
- Piplup!
[grunting]
[gasping]
Chika! Chi...ka. Chika?
Pikachu!
Pika!
Pikapi!
Okay, here it comes!
Pikachu!
Oh, whoa!
Way to go, Pikachu!
Pika, Pika!
Hey, Ash!
- Pikachu!
- Lup!
Hey, guys,
I've got the Jewel of Life!
Ash, great!
Return it to Arceus quickly!
Right!
- Let's go, buddy.
- Pika!
Lup, Lup, Lup!
[ Pokémon talking ]
Lup!
Arceus!
Look, I brought you
the Jewel of Life,
so please take it!
Pika.
Arceus.
Pikachu.
Pika.
Pikapi!
Pikachu!
Pichu...
Oh, what's going on?
Oh, no!
What's happening to me?
( Marcus )
You're disappearing.
With Arceus no more,
there's no reason for you
to have to come back here.
History has changed.
No, Arceus.
You can't die, you can't.
You can't leave
this world hating us.
I won't let you!
Pika!
Piplup.
[groaning]
Pika...
Pikapi!
Pikachu!
[grunting]
Arceus!
Damos?
The Jewel of Life. ..
Please take it.
Pikachu!
Pikapi!
Huh?
We're back!
- Piplup, Piplup!
- Piplup!
You're all fools!
We're alive!
Yes.
Pichu!
Who are you?
I'm Ash and this is
my partner, Pikachu.
Pikachu!
Ash and Pikachu.
Are you the ones who saved my life?
It wasn't just us.
Ash!
You're alive!
Everybody here did it!
Pika, Pika!
Arceus, please, forgive me.
I already saw it in your heart.
It's all right.
( Marcus )
This is the end.
I know it.
This place will once again
become a wasteland.
For us, there is no future.
[screaming]
Awesome!
Piplup!
I have used up all of my strength,
so for now I must rest.
Farewell, Damos.
Ash, Pikachu...
and you.
All of my beloved.
[ Pokémon talking ]
Dialga is calling.
- Dialga?
- Chu.
Time to return to the future.
But I wanted to speak more.
Pichu.
- Me too.
- Yeah, me too.
Same here.
But it's not to be,
future children.
Pichu!
Pichu.
The future.
Wow.
Are we back?
Giratina!
Huh?
And Dialga!
Palkia, too.
Arceus!
It's still angry!
( Dawn )
But how?
No, Arceus, no!
( Arceus )
Who are you?
I'm Ash, and this is
my partner, Pikachu.
Pikachu!
Ash.
[all gasping]
History's been corrected.
Wow.
( All ) - Huh?
- Huh?
Washed up again.
Everything's back to normal!
- Pika!
- Thank goodness!
Piplup!
Oh, wait a minute!
We returned the Jewel of Life
in the past,
which means this place
should be totally desolate.
Arceus?
This isn't my doing.
Your ancestors dedicated
their entire lives
to cultivating
and restoring this land.
This place was brought back to life
by the efforts of people
and Pokémon alike.
I understand.
Sheena, we did it!
Right!
( Kevin )
Sheena!
Kevin!
Ahh!
Bye!
Bye-bye!
Thanks for everything!
( Kevin )
Sheena, look at this!
( Ash )
Is that--
( Dawn )
It's us!
Damos must have left this
knowing we would see it!
There's something written here.
"To all of my beautiful
future children
"who taught me how to believe,
"I offer all of you now
my sincerest hopes and wishes
"that the future world will become
more and more beautiful..."
( Damos ) ...and that is
exactly the kind of world
you find yourselves in.
Thank you, Damos.
( Arceus )
Ash...
...this world of yours is
truly a magnificent place.
- It is!
- Pika!
And now, with great joy,
I have finally come to understand
that I am truly a part of it.
See ya, Arceus!
Pikachu!
Bye, Arceus!
And thank you for everything!
♪ I have seen the future ♪
♪ And the future is today ♪
♪ The songs for all the children ♪
♪Looking for a better way♪
♪ When people come together♪
♪ Nothing holds them back ♪
♪Because when we are united♪
♪ We're better that's a fact ♪
♪ The world is so much brighter♪
♪ There's nothing we can't do ♪
♪ If we trust each other♪
♪ There's no stopping me and you ♪
♪ One hope, one wish ♪
♪ That we will keep the faith ♪
♪ One chance for us ♪
♪ To make the world
a better place ♪
♪ Together we could do so much ♪
♪ If we only learn to trust ♪
♪ Can you find the courage ♪
♪ When others let you down ♪
♪ Do you have the strength ♪
♪ When there's no one else around♪
♪ Are you brave enough ♪
♪ To face the darkest night ♪
♪Don't worry 'cause
we're with you♪
♪ Ready for the fight ♪
♪ The world is so much better♪
♪ There's nothing we can't do ♪
♪ If we trust each other♪
♪ There's no stopping me and you ♪
♪ One hope one wish ♪
♪ That we will keep the faith ♪
♪ One chance for us ♪
♪ To make the world
a better place ♪
♪ Together we could do so much ♪
♪ If we only learn to trust ♪
♪Listen to the voice inside you♪
♪ Just believe the truth
will guide you ♪
♪ We will be right there
beside you ♪
♪ All the way ♪
♪ One hope one wish ♪
♪ That we will keep the faith ♪
♪ One chance for us ♪
♪ To make the world
a better place ♪
♪ Together we could do so much ♪
♪ If we only learn to trust ♪
♪ If we only learn ♪
♪ One hope one wish ♪
♪ That we will keep the faith ♪
♪ One chance for us ♪
♪ To make the world
a better place ♪
♪ Together we could do so much ♪
♪ If we only learn to trust ♪
♪ If we only learn to trust ♪♪
♪ Open your eyes ♪
♪ It's easy to do ♪
♪ Just take the time ♪
♪ And look around you ♪
♪ Never forget ♪
♪ This is a beautiful world♪
♪ Open your eyes ♪
♪ It's easy to do ♪
♪ Just take the time ♪
♪ And look around you ♪
♪ Never forget ♪
♪ This is a beautiful world♪
♪ It's a beautiful world ♪♪
♪ I'll always remember you ♪
♪ Carry your dreams ♪
♪ Until they come true ♪
♪ Each breath that I take ♪
♪ Each moment awake ♪
♪ I'll always remember you ♪♪
Watch Movies, TV Series and Live Sports
Signup Here -> WWW.ADMITME.APP