NARRATOR: The Pokémon world! An astounding place that almost
defies description, with its abundance and grandeur...!
NARRATOR: And, of course, Pokémon! Flying high above the
clouds, swimming deep under the sea, and roaming the rolling
expanse of its beautiful lands, they can be found everywhere
you care to look!
NARRATOR: Here, we find a young man named Ash Ketchum, who hails
from Pallet Town, working with his partner Pikachu to catch
other Pokémon and refine his Pokémon battling skills!
NARRATOR: As he travels with his friends,
there have been twists and turns on the road during Ash's journey
as a Pokémon Trainer...
NARRATOR: Indeed, his road has branched off
in many directions... Lost at times,
occasionally retracing his steps,
or forcing him to take the long way...
but through it all, continuing his journey just the same...!
NARRATOR: ...in order to find truths hidden within us all!
DONUKE: It's useless! No matter how often you ask...
DAMON: The People of the Vale have a place-
a place where we're meant to live!
GOTHITELLE: [ANNOYED]
DONUKE: But Damon, that's just a legend! So why don't you leave?
DAMON: I won't! I want to see Glacine, the village chief...!
BEARTIC A: [GROWL]
BEARTIC B: [GROWL]
BEARTIC A: [ANGRY / PROUD]
BEARTIC B: [ANGRY/ PROUD]
LILLIPUP: [EXCITED]
LILLIPUP: [PROUD]
LUIS: Look, Mom! We found it!
GLACINE: Please! Keep your voice down...
LUIS: Sorry, Mom... The Beartic haven't heard us...
GLACINE: You did a great job finding it!
They'll be thrilled to have this!
LUIS: Lillipup, great!
BEARTIC X 4: [SCARED]
STOUTLAND: [DETERMINED]
DONUKE: Glacine, over here!
BEARTIC: [FOCUSED]
STOUTLAND: [SHOCKED]
GLACINE: Stay close!
BEARTIC X 3: [SCARED]
LILLIPUP: [SHOCKED]
BEARTIC X 4, STOUTLAND, STOUTLAND: [ANGRY]
LILLIPUP: [SCARED / [SURPRISED]
LUIS: Lillipup!
GOTHITELLE: [PSCYHIC MOVE]
LILLIPUP: [RELIEVED]
GLACINE: Damon?!
ZEKROM: [FOCUSED]
LUIS: Who's that Pokémon?!
DONUKE: Could it be?
ZEKROM: [ATTACKING]
ZEKROM: [FOCUSED]
GLACINE: It's the Legendary...Pokémon, Zekrom!
DAMON: Please, Glacine...! Listen to what I have to tell
you just one more time!
DAMON: The People of the Vale must now reclaim their
bond with the land!
ZEKROM: Beyond hope, you will find your ideals!
MANDIBUZZ: [CALLING]
ASH: It's a Mandibuzz!
PIKACHU: [CURIOUS]
IRIS: Cilan, do you see it?
AXEW: [CURIOUS]
CILAN: Not yet, Iris,
but I think we should see it fairly soon...
PIKACHU: [EXCITED]
IRIS: That's IT!!
AXEW: [AWED]
CILAN: It must be!
NARRATOR: As Ash continues through the Unova region on his
quest to become a Pokémon Master, our heroes have arrived
at the mountain town of Eindoak,
just in time for the Harvest Festival!
DEERLING #1 : [EXCITED]
DEERLING #2: [EXCITED]
VICTINI: [CURIOUS]
DEERLING #2: [SHOCKED] / [SCARED]
DEERLING #1: [STRUGGLING]
DEERLING #2 : [SCARED]
DEERLING #1, DEERLING #2: [STRUGGLING]
VICTINI: [CONCERNED / STARTLED]
ASH: Don't worry! I'll help you out there...!
PIKACHU: [CONCERNED]
DEERLING #1,DEERLING #2: [STRUGGLING]
ASH: Here I come...! Hang on!
PIKACHU: [ENCOURAGING]
IRIS: Ash, I'm coming too!
CILAN: Iris, wait, don't do it! The ground won't hold...
IRIS: Okay.
DEERLING #1,DEERLING #2: [STRUGGLING / SHOCKED]
PIKACHU: [SCARED]
IRIS: Ash...!
ASH, DEERLING #1,DEERLING #2: [SCARED]
PIKACHU: [FRANTIC]
VICTINI: [DETERMINED]
PIKACHU: [SHOCKED]
VICTINI: [STRUGGLING / SHOCKED]
CILAN: Ash, NO!
DEERLING X 2, PIKACHU: [TERRIFIED]
DEERLING X 2, PIKACHU: [SHOCKED]
CILAN: He just jumped!
PIKACHU, DEERLING X 2: [SCARED]
PIKACHU: [RELIEVED]
VICTINI: [RELIEVED]
AXEW: [SHOCKED]
IRIS: Did you see what I saw...?
PIKACHU: [RELIEVED]
DEERLING #1 : [RELIEVED]
DEERLING X 2: [RELIEVED]
ASH: We're okay, guys! We all landed in one piece!
PIKACHU: [CALLING]
IRIS: And how are you planning on getting out of there?!
PIKACHU: [CURIOUS]
ASH: Hey, there's a breeze coming through!
We'll follow it out!
PIKACHU, DEERLING X 2: [DETERMINED]
PIDOVE FLOCK: [CALLING]
VICTINI: [STARTLED]
VICTINI: [EXCITED]
PIKACHU: [CURIOUS]
DEERLING X2: [NERVOUS]
VICTINI: [INSISTENT]
ASH: Follow me!
PIKACHU: [DETERMINED]
DEERLING X 2: [NERVOUS]
VICTINI: [CURIOUS]
ASH: Heyyy! Anybody hear me?!
ASH: Anyone?! Hello?!
ASH: What was that?!
VICTINI: [INSISTENT]
ASH: Again...!
VICTINI: [HAPPY]
PIKACHU: [CURIOUS]
DEERLING X 2: [CURIOUS]
ASH: Hey!
AXEW: [STARTLED]
ASH: Iris! Cilan! Come on! Get up here! You've gotta check out
this view! Quick! What're you standing there for?!
PIKACHU: [EXCITED]
CILAN: And to think we were worried...
IRIS: What a kid...!
AXEW: [AFFIRMATIVE]
ASH: Deerling!
ASH: Try hanging out in safer places, okay?!
PIKACHU: [ENCOURAGING]
DEERLING X 2: [AFFIRMATIVE]
PIDOVE FLOCK: [CALLING]
CILAN: This castle is called the Sword of the Vale.
ASH: Sword of the Vale?
PIKACHU: [CONFUSED]
CILAN: Look! Over there...
CILAN: They say it flew through the air from that valley and
landed right here on this spot!
IRIS: Flew through the air?!
AXEW: [SURPRISED]
ASH: But, how can a castle fly?!
PIKACHU: [QUESTIONING]
CILAN: It's a legend! It's impossible to know if it's
really the truth. But look! You can see with your very own eyes
that the berries in the surrounding orchards are
beautiful and delicious!
IRIS: Awesome! They look yummy!!
ASH: Gimme...!
PIKACHU: [DISAPPOINTED]
IRIS: Somebody hungry...?
ASH: In case you haven't noticed,
I'm always hungry and that's THAT!
PIKACHU: [AGREEMENT]
PIKACHU: [SHEEPISH]
IRIS: Why do I even ask...?
CILAN: Ash...I've got just the thing!
CILAN: My homemade macarons!
ASH: Wow! Thanks, Cilan!!
IRIS: Yeah, way to go!
ASH: Think I'll eat 'em right now!
IRIS: Good idea!!
VICTINI: [NERVOUS]
IRIS: The best!!
PIKACHU, AXEW: [PLAYFUL]
ASH: These macarons RULE! Best I ever ate...! Uh oh...!
IRIS: Ash, what's wrong?
ASH: It's gone...the macaron disappeared!
VICTINI: [HAPPY / EATING]
IRIS: Knowing you, you probably ate it...
CILAN: Hey, Ash, don't cry!
ASH: Ha, fooled you! Check it out. Still got one!
IRIS: What a kid...!
VICTINI: [TEASING]
VICTINI: [HAPPY]
VICTINI: [SHOCKED]
CILAN: The festival's beginning!
VICTINI: [STARTLED]
VICTINI: [FRANTIC] / [RESIGNED]
PIKACHU, AXEW: [HURRIED]
CILAN: Let's see...
IRIS: Quick! If we don't hurry,
we won't be able to register for the competition!
DAMON: I can take you...!
PIKACHU, AXEW: [STARTLED]
DAMON: Here! If you're in a rush, this way is much faster!
CILAN: That's so nice! Thank you!
ASH: Hi, I'm Ash! I'm working to become a Pokémon Master!
And this is my partner, Pikachu.
PIKACHU: [GREETING]
IRIS: My name's Iris! This's Axew.
I'm training to be a Dragon Master!
AXEW: [GREETING]
CILAN: I'm Cilan, a Pokémon Connoisseur...
DAMON: My name is Damon. I've been working on
restoring this castle. Please, follow me.
GOTHORITA: [HAPPY / DETERMINED]
BIG BOY: Wow, that tastes so good!
GOTHORITA: [PROUD]
GOTHITA: [FOCUSED]
MAID, GOTHORITA, GOTHORITA: [PROUD]
ASH, IRIS, CILAN: [HAPPY]
GOLURK: [FOCUSED]
CILAN: It's a Golurk!
ASH: It's huge!
PIKACHU: [AWED]
IRIS: Wonder what it's pulling...!
AXEW: [CURIOUS]
CILAN: Let's find out!
VICTINI: [STARTLED]
GOLURK: [ACCOMPLISHED]
IRIS: Look! They're so cute!!
JUANITA: They're Victini dolls... the Victory Pokémon!
IRIS: Victini?
JUANITA: Right, Victini!
They say it's lived in this town since long ago!
ASH: Wow! I wanna meet it!
JUANITA: Very few have ever seen Victini...
VICTINI: [APPEARING]
ASH: Oh. Got ya...
CILAN: Can you tell us more about it?
JUANITA: It's said to give people and Pokémon power...
ASH: Power?
JUANITA: That's right!
Long ago, it was said to have protected the Sword of the Vale.
IRIS: Really? Awesome!!
AXEW: [INTRIGUED]
IRIS: I'll take one of these, please!
JUANITA: Here you go!
JUANITA: And one day, may you receive Victini's power as well!
IRIS: Now, I know I'm gonna win the battle competition!
AXEW: [PROUD]
JESSIE: I'm well aware that our plan was to catch Pikachu and
all of the other Pokémon in the festival, but now...
MEOWTH: That story is a real game changer!
JAMES: Victini, the Victory Pokémon...
MEOWTH: A Pokémon that can give you power!
JESSIE: Simple. All we do ...is CATCH IT!
VICTINI: [TAUNTING]
PIDOVE FLOCK: [CALLING]
MANNES: Ladies and gentlemen! Moms and dads, girls and boys,
and of course, Pokémon - I welcome you all to the
Eindoak Harvest Festival!
MANNES: My name is Mannes, mayor of Eindoak Town!
MANNES: Folks, I'm happy to report our orchards have given
us a bountiful harvest this year!
MANNES: So, festival fans...are we having FUN?!
CROWD: YEAH!!
ASH, PIKACHU: YEAH!! YEAH!!
MANNES: All right! Then it's time to kick off what you've all
been patiently waiting for... our annual battle competition!
KLINKLANG: [DETERMINED]
KLANG: [FOCUSED]
KLINK: [FOCUSED]
MANNES: Here are our simple competition rules! Trainers who
have gathered here and wish to participate will have a
one-on-one Pokémon battle with no substitutions!
Whoever holds the competition necklace until the end WINS!
JUANITA: Carlita! Good luck, dear!
CARLITA: Thanks, Mom! Piece of cake!
MANNES: All right, let the battle BEGIN!
IRIS: Just watch me win!
CILAN: Watch ME win!
EMOLGA: [APPEARING]
PANSAGE: [APPEARING]
ASH: WE'RE gonna win, right buddy?
PIKACHU: [DETERMINED]
ASH: Scraggy, let's go!
SCRAGGY: [APPEARING / STARTLED]
ASH: Scraggy?
I want you to watch all the other Pokémon when they battle.
PIKACHU: [AGREEMENT]
SCRAGGY: [CONFIDENT]
ASH: Then let's go!
PIKACHU: [EXCITED]
It's always hard,
When the journey begins.
Hard to find your way;
Hard to make amends.
But there's nothing you can't do,
Cause you've got the power inside of you.
It's never easy,
To make a choice:
To keep things inside,
Or raise your voice.
But for everyone there comes a time
When the light inside begins to shine.
It's not always right or wrong,
As long as your spirit's strong.
It's not always win or lose,
It's the road you choose;
The answer's within.
It's not always black and white,
But your heart always knows what's right.
Let the journey begin-
So many choices;
How do we know?
So many places;
Where do we go?
What should I say?
What should I do?
Still, we're together: me and you!
It's not always right or wrong,
As long as your spirit's strong.
It's not always win or lose,
It's the road you choose;
The answer's within.
It's not always black and white,
but your heart always knows what's right.
Let the journey begin:
Pokémon!
There's nothing you can do,
'Cause you've got the power inside of you.
It's not always right or wrong,
As long as your spirit's strong.
It's not always win or lose,
It's the road you choose;
The answer's within.
It's not always black and white,
but your heart always knows what's right.
Let the journey begin:
Pokémon!
GOLURK: [FOCUSED]
JUANITA: Good luck to both of you!
ASH: Tepig, I choose you!
TEPIG: [APPEARING]
SAMUROTT: [THREATENING]
TEPIG: [NERVOUS]
IRIS: So Tepig, a Fire type, is up against Samurott,
a Water type...
CILAN: I'm afraid that this battle is going to leave a
bitter after-taste in Ash's mouth...
PIKACHU: [WORRIED]
ASH: Tepig! Don't worry! We'll show 'em how strong we are!
TEPIG: [AFFIRMATIVE]
ASH: 'Kay, T ! Use Ember!
TEPIG: [EMBER MOVE]
SAMUROTT: [TAUNTING]
ASH, TEPIG: [SHOCKED]
CILAN: Not very effective...
PIKACHU: [CONCERNED]
ASH: All right, use Tackle!
TEPIG: [AFFIRMATIVE]
LEEKU: Samurott, Razor Shell, let's go!
SAMUROTT: [AFFIRMATIVE]
TEPIG: [TACKLE MOVE]
SAMUROTT: [RAZOR SHELL MOVE]
TEPIG : [PAINED]
JUANITA: Oh my word!
TEPIG: [PAINED]
VICTINI: [CONCERNED]
VICTINI: [FOCUSED]
TEPIG: [STARTLED / DETERMINED]
TEPIG: [CHARGING] [DETERMINED]
ASH: Tepig, you okay?
TEPIG: [EXCITED]
ASH: Wow, you're fired up to win, 'Kay, Tepig,
Ember, once more!
IRIS: Ember AGAIN!?
CILAN: What for?!
TEPIG: [EMBER MOVE]
SAMUROTT: [SHOCKED]
SAMUROTT: [PAINED]
JUDGE E: Samurott's unable to battle! Tepig wins!
ASH: All right!
IRIS: You did it!
ASH: Tepig, way to go!
TEPIG: [PROUD]
CILAN: An unexpected flavor! Simply delicious!
IRIS: That last Ember was incredible!
AXEW: [AGREEMENT]
CARLITA: Hey, Mother?
That Tepig powered up quite suddenly, right?
JUANITA: Yes, it did...
CARLITA: So...do you think that could have been the
work of Victini?
JUANITA: Come on now...!
SCRAGGY: [FOCUSED]
AXEW, PIKACHU: [LAUGHING]
CARLITA: Say, why not battle me?
ASH: I never turn down a chance to battle! Let's do it!
SCRAGGY: [CONFIDENT]
PIKACHU: [SURPRISED]
HYDREIGON: [IMPACT/ GRUNT]
SCRAGGY: [DETERMINED / IMPACT GRUNT]
CARLITA: So Scraggy's your choice?
SCRAGGY: [DETERMINED]
ASH: You BET! 'Kay, Scraggy, let's go!
SCRAGGY: [EAGER]
IRIS: Wait, Scraggy?!
CILAN: This battle might not go down as easily as the
battle with Tepig...
IRIS: Maybe.
HYDREIGON: [THREATENING]
IRIS: But isn't Hydreigon just about the coolest EVER?!
ASH: All right, Scraggy, now! Use Headbu-...
SCRAGGY: [DETERMINED]
HYDREIGON: [IMPACT GRUNT]
SCRAGGY: [SHOCKED]
ASH, IRIS, CILAN, AXEW, PIKACHU: [CONCERNED]
SCRAGGY : [PAINED]
VICTINI: [FOCUSED]
SCRAGGY: [DETERMINED]
SCRAGGY: [TRIUMPHANT]
ASH: Okay, Scraggy, use Headbutt once more!
SCRAGGY: [HEADBUTT MOVE]
HYDREIGON: [PAINED]
IRIS, CILAN, PIKACHU: [SHOCKED]
AXEW: [CHEERING]
JUDGE F: Hydreigon is unable to battle! Scraggy wins!
ASH: We did it! We did it! All riiiiiight...!
PIKACHU, AXEW: [EXCITED]
CARLITA: Have a good rest.
Here!
JUDGE F: Thank you.
VICTINI: [STARTLED]
CARLITA: That was the work of Victini, right?
ASH: Victini?
CILAN: What are you talking about?
CARLITA: I saw it!
The way your Scraggy was getting power from Victini...
IRIS: Do you mean this?
IRIS: It didn't do anything. Really!
CARLITA: I'm talking about the real Victini.
ASH: The real one's here?!
IRIS: So where is it?!
ASH: C'mon, I wanna see Victini!
CARLITA: But Victini's invisible now... It can do that!
ASH: Invisible...?
PIKACHU: [CURIOUS]
ASH: Victini must've been the one who ate my macaron!
PIKACHU: [SURPRISED]
VICTINI: [INSISTENT]
ASH: I wonder what we heard back in the cave...
ASH: That sound could've been Victini's voice...!
PIKACHU: [CURIOUS]
ASH: Hey Victini! Did you give me power earlier?!
VICTINI: [PROUD]
AXEW, PIKACHU, SCRAGGY: [STARTLED]
ASH: Hey, Victini, that you?! If it is, come out and say hi!
PIKACHU: [ENCOURAGING]
CILAN: I've still got some macarons!
ASH: Way to go, Cilan! Bet this'll work...Victini,
I've got more macarons!
VICTINI: [EXCITED]
ASH, IRIS, CILAN, CARLITA, PIKACHU,
AXEW, SCRAGGY: [SHOCKED] [AMAZED]
VICTINI: [HAPPY]
VICTINI: [DELIGHTED]
ASH, IRIS, CILAN, SCRAGGY, AXEW,
CARLITA, PIKACHU: [EXCITED]
VICTINI: [EXCITED]
VICTINI: [APPEARING]
ASH: There it is!
PIKACHU: [EXCITED]
IRIS: Wow. It really does exist...!
VICTINI: [SURPRISED] / [TIMID]
PIKACHU: [ENCOURAGING]
VICTINI: [UPSET]
PIKACHU: [ENCOURAGING / SUPPORTIVE]
VICTINI: [HESITANT] [EXCITED]
CARLITA: To think Victini appeared for a macaron...
VICTINI: [HAPPY]
ASH: So, was it good?
VICTINI: [EXCITED]
ASH, PIKACHU, IRIS, CARLITA, SCRAGGY, CILAN, AXEW: [CURIOUS]
VICTINI: [DELIGHTED]
ASH: Hi! My name's Ash! This's my buddy Pikachu!
PIKACHU: [GREETING]
IRIS: And my name's Iris!
AXEW: [GREETING]
CILAN: Hi! I'm Cilan...
CARLITA: Hi! They call me Carlita!
SCRAGGY: [GREETING]
ASH: Victini...Is it true Tepig and Scraggy suddenly got
stronger because you gave them some of your power?
VICTINI: [PROUD]
ASH: Wow, you're incredible! Thanks so much!
VICTINI: [UPSET]
ASH: Victini! What's wrong?!?
IRIS: Poor thing! You've made Victini cry...!
CARLITA: You were playing just a little too rough...
ASH: Oh man...I'm sorry, Victini! Really...!
PIKACHU: [DETERMINED]
PIKACHU: [FRIENDLY]
AXEW, SCRAGGY: [CALLING]
PIKACHU: [ENCOURAGING]
VICTINI: [APPEARING]
VICTINI: [CURIOUS]
PIKACHU: [HAPPY]
AXEW: [HAPPY]
VICTINI: [EXCITED]
PIKACHU, SCRAGGY, AXEW: [HAPPY]
VICTINI: [JOYFUL]
PIKACHU: [HAPPY]
AXEW, SCRAGGY: [HAPPY]
CARLITA: It's so amazing Victini showed up! A true wonder!
CILAN: It's like an exotic and rare ingredient!
IRIS: It makes me feel... really, really happy!
JESSIE: She's not the only one who's really happy...
MEOWTH: It's a once-in-a-lifetime SHOT!
JAMES: A powerful Victory Pokémon...
now, if Victini were ours...
JESSIE: Imagine all that power in US!
JESSIE, JAMES, MEOWTH: Feel-ing GOOD!
PIKACHU, AXEW, SCRAGGY, VICTINI: [EXCITED]
VICTINI: [CONCERNED]
PIDOVE FLOCK: [CALLING]
VICTINI: [HESITANT]
ASH: Victini! Let's check it out! C'mon!
VICTINI: [PAINED]
VICTINI: [STRUGGLING]
PIKACH: [SHOCKED]
ASH: Victini, what's wrong?!
VICTINI: [SEARING SHOT MOVE]
VICTINI: [UPSET]
ASH: Victini, what happened?
VICTINI: [SCARED]
VICTINI: [UPSET]
ASH: Victini, wait!
PIKACHU: [CALLING]
PIKACHU: [WORRIED]
ASH: Aw, Victini...
JUANITA: You really met Victini?
CARLITA: Yes, Mom, we really did!
CILAN: Juanita! Where would someone go in this town to find
a place of comfort and peace?
CILAN: After a bad experience...Where do you want
to go to feel better?
PIKACHU: [QUESTIONING]
CILAN: A place... that feels like home!
PIDOVE FLOCK: [CALLING]
CARLITA: Perhaps - Victini didn't like the barrier...
ASH: Barrier?
JUANITA: Our village has an invisible barrier around it...
JUANITA: ...and it is said that Victini can't go beyond the
Pillars of Protection.
ASH: Go beyond the Pillars of Protection...?
CILAN: They form the barrier...!
IRIS: That must've been what that was back there!
ASH: Yeah...
DAMON: Hey, everyone!
ASH, PIKACHU, IRIS, CILAN, AXEW: [CONFUSED
DAMON: So we meet again...!
ASH: It's Damon!
CARLITA: My brother!
ASH, IRIS, CILAN, PIKACHU, AXEW: [SURPRISED]
IRIS: Your brother?!
CILAN: What do you know...
DAMON: It's been too long, Mother...
JUANITA: For your information, six months, to be exact!
CARLITA: What brings you back here?
DAMON: I'm just helping out with the restoration of the castle.
MANNES: Upon my special request!
JUANITA: Look, Mannes...Your position as mayor does not allow
you to boss my son around!
MANNES: Whatever you say, my dear Juanita...
CARLITA: Damon! Victini actually exists!
DAMON: Yes, I know...!
CILAN: Ah, the scent of growing grass...Lots of fresh air!
This area's as sweet as ripe fruit!
JUANITA: Yes!
MANNES: This orchard belongs to my family!
PIKACHU, AXEW: [CURIOUS]
IRIS: Slow down, Axew! You could slip and hurt yourself!
PIKACHU, AXEW: [CALLING]
ASH: Victini! We didn't know you couldn't pass the barrier!
Please come on out...!
IRIS: You don't have to hide from us!
CILAN: We've got delicious macarons!
ASH: Yeah, come out and have some!
PIKACHU, AXEW: [HESITANT]
PURRLOIN: [CONFIDENT]
PIKACHU: [SHOCKED]
DRILBUR: [GREETING]
PURRLOIN: [PERSUASIVE]
PIKACHU: [EXCITED]
ASH: They're telling us to follow them...!
PIKACHU: [CURIOUS]
PETILIL GROUP: [CURIOUS]
MINCCINO: [FRANTIC]
PETILIL GROUP: [EAGER]
COTTONEE GROUP: [EAGER]
COTTONEE GROUP: [RELIEVED]
PURRLOIN: [CALLING]
MINCCINO: [CALLING]
DRILBUR: [CALLING]
VICTINI: [APPEARING] [SCARED]
ASH: Victini!
VICTINI: [STARTLED]
ASH: Victini! You're here, right?!
PIKACHU: [CALLING]
ASH: I'm so sorry I frightened you before...!
ASH: I'm really sorry.
VICTINI: [STARTLED]
ASH: Victini, you don't have to hide! Come on out!
PIKACHU: [SHOCKED] / [STRUGGLING]
VICTINI: [STRUGGLING]
PIKACHU: [STRUGGLING]
ASH: It's Victini!
IRIS: You're back!!
CARLITA: I TOLD you!
VICTINI: [STRUGGLING / STARTLED]
PIKACHU: [SHOCKED]
PIKACHU: [WORRIED]
CILAN: Ash!
AXEW: [WORRIED]
VICTINI: [WORRIED]
ASH: It's coooooold...!
VICTINI: [SURPRISED] / [PLAYFUL]
ASH: Gotcha!
PIKACHU: [SURPRISED / CONFUSED]
COTTONEE GROUP : [AMUSED]
PIKACHU: [AMUSED]
IRIS, CILAN, AXEW, PURRLOIN, DRILBUR, MINCCINO: [AMUSED]
CARLITA: Victini's having fun!
DAMON: My plan...is to borrow some of Victini's power.
PIKACHU, AXEW, VICTINI: [PLAYFUL]
MANNES: You see, both Juanita and I are descendants of the
tribe called the People of the Vale.
ASH: People of the Vale?
CILAN: It's the tribe mentioned in the castle's legend!
CARLITA: Correct!
JUANITA: We'll tell you a story...of Victini - and the
People of the Vale.
MANNES: Here we go...
MANNES: Have a look! Over a thousand years ago, the People
of the Vale proudly lived under the rule of a mighty king!
ASH: It's Victini...!
IRIS: Was it the king's Pokémon?
MANNES: Yes, that's what the legend says...
JUANITA: The king ruled over what was called the
Kingdom of the Vale...
CILAN: Kingdom of the Vale...?
MANNES: The Kingdom drew its energy from the Dragon Force!
ASH: What's Dragon Force?
DAMON: It's the power that flows invisibly throughout our planet.
MANNES: By using that power wisely, people and Pokémon alike
were able to create an environment in perfect harmony-
at one with nature...
MANNES: The King had two sons: twin princes!
MANNES: And both princes were filled with wisdom and courage.
MANNES: Each prince possessed a unique quality
for which they were nicknamed.
MANNES: The Hero of Ideals!
MANNES: ...and the Hero of Truth!
MANNES: They were greatly loved...
IRIS: Are those...
CILAN: Pokémon?
MANNES: Both princes were accompanied by
great dragon Pokémon!
CARLITA: Zekrom and Reshiram.
DAMON: Both of them granted great wisdom and strength
only to those judged worthy. BUT...
DAMON: ...the country lost its way,
and the two princes became enemies...
RESHIRAM: [ANGRY ROAR]
ZEKROM: [ANGRY ROAR]
MANNES: ...which eventually led
to a great and destructive war...
RESHIRAM: [FUSION FLARE MOVE]
ZEKROM: [FUSION BOLT MOVE]
JUANITA: The two fought ferociously,
finally wounding each other...
ZEKROM, RESHIRAM: [PAINED]
MANNES: ...which used up all of their life energy.
MANNES: These great dragon Pokémon
were transformed into stone...
and fell into a long, deep slumber.
JUANITA: By the time the two princes realized the mistake
they had made, it was too late.
JUANITA: The Dragon Force energy became chaotic!
MANNES: Witnessing the destruction of his people's
land, the king decided to use the power of Victini.
IRIS: Victini's...
CILAN: ...power! Wow...
VICTINI: [SURPRISED]
KING: Victini, please... grant me the use of your power!
VICTINI: [ACCEPTING]
JUANITA: In order to harness Victini's power, the king
created a barrier around the castle using the
Pillars of Protection...
VICTINI: [FOCUSED]
DUOSION GROUP, SIGILYPH GROUP: [FOCUSED]
MANNES: So, with all the townspeople gathered
on top of the castle...
MANNES: ...it lifted up into the sky...
MANNES: ...and the castle was carried to this mountaintop!
VICTINI: [ANXIOUS]
VICTINI: [WORRIED]
VICTINI: [RELIEVED]
VICTINI: [QUESTIONING]
JUANITA: However...the king's power was spent, and the Pillars
of Protection and the barrier remained.
MANNES: Eventually the chaos within the
Dragon Force subsided.
MANNES: The two princes were filled with deep remorse,
and they moved the stone dragon Pokémon
to a safe and secret location...
DAMON: But- the People of the Vale lost their bond with the
land, and scattered everywhere!
PIKACHU, VICTINI, AXEW, VICTINI, AXEW, AXEW: [PLAYFUL]
DAMON: Even leaving behind Victini,
who had vanished from sight.
ASH: Victini's been here... for more than a thousand years?!
IRIS: A thousand years...?
CILAN: And trapped inside the barrier for all that time...!
PIKACHU, VICTINI, AXEW, VICTINI, AXEW, AXEW: [PLAYFUL]
ASH: Victini.
DAMON: Look over there!
DAMON: That's where the Kingdom once was...!
DAMON: My goal...is to bring the
Kingdom of the Vale back to life.
CARLITA: Back to life?
VICTINI, PIKACHU: [SURPRISED]
AXEW: [PLAYFUL]
AXEW: [STARTLED]
ASH, IRIS, CILAN, PIKACHU,VICTINI: [AMUSED]
VICTINI: [PLAYFUL]
AXEW: [AMUSED]
ASH: Victini!
PIKACHU: [EXCITED]
DAMON: You said it would be nice...
if the Kingdom of the Vale could be restored...
JUANITA: I did...
JUANITA: The energy of this land no
longer flows here...
JUANITA: ...so neither people nor Pokémon can live...
DAMON: Wouldn't it be great if they could?
JUANITA: That's my dream, Damon.
DAMON: And now...I can finally fulfill that dream of yours!
VICTINI: [DETERMINED]
AXEW, VICTINI, PIKACHU: [HAPPY]
PETILIL X 3: [CURIOUS]
DRILBUR X 2: [EXCITED]
PURRLOIN: [AMUSED]
MINCCINO: [EAGER]
COTTONEE X 3: [CURIOUS]
AXEW, PIKACHU, VICTINI MINCCINO, DRILBUR X 2,
PURRLION, PETILIL X 3: [EXCITED]
PETILIL X 3: [HAPPY EATING]
DRILBUR X 2, VICTINI: [HAPPY]
AXEW, PIKACHU: [HAPPY EATING]
COTTONEE X 3: [HAPPY EATING]
MINCCINO: [CURIOUS]
PURRLOIN: [PLEASED]
AXEW, PIKACHU, MINCCINO, DRILBUR X 2,
PURRLION, PETILIL X 3: [HAPPY EATING]
CILAN: It looks like Victini wasn't so alone after all!
IRIS: Yeah!
VICTINI: [OFFERING]
ASH: Are those for us?
ASH: Victini, thanks!
VICTINI: [OFFERING]
IRIS: Thanks, Victini!
CILAN: Merci!
CILAN, ASH, IRIS: Bon appetit!
VICTINI: [CURIOUS]
IRIS: It's yummy!
ASH: Yeah, it's delicious!
VICTINI: [DELIGHTED]
VICTINI: [HAPPY EATING]
MANNES: Three years ago
MANNES: Damon returned and paid me a visit at my home.
DAMON: I want to contact the People of the Vale who have
scattered everywhere and have them return
so we can rebuild our Kingdom!
MANNES: But that's impossible!
DAMON: I have to try.
Those who say "impossible"...
accomplish nothing!
DAMON: Since that time...
DAMON: I have journeyed far and wide in search of the
People of the Vale...
RAVINE: Legend. Nothing but legend. Now, get out!
DAMON: At first, no one would even listen to me...
GOTHITELLE: [CONCERNED]
LUISA: Here you go, Damon! It's for you!
DAMON: Thank you, Luisa.
DAMON: Suddenly, I heard a voice...
ZEKROM: Is that as far as you will go for your ideals?!
DAMON: What was that?!
ZEKROM: If they're so worthless, just abandon them!
DAMON: Again, the voice... I heard it coming from the
Sword of the Vale!
JUANITA: From the castle?
MANNES: So we went to the cave - located beneath the castle...
MANNES: We can't go farther for some reason...
Damon?
DAMON: Mannes!
MANNES: Damon! How did you get down there?!
DAMON: All I know is that I'm here now!
MANNES: Amazing! The path chooses the one it
allows to pass...
DAMON: I'll go alone!
DAMON: The path was filled with obstacles...
DAMON: But somehow, I made it through!
DAMON: The great Dark Stone...!
DAMON: So you're the one who led me down here...
ZEKROM: [ROAR]
ZEKROM: You have proven your determination...
to realize your ideals!
ZEKROM: [DETERMINED]
BOUFFALANT HERD: [ANXIOUS]
ZEKROM: [DRAGON PULSE MOVE]
BOUFFALANT X 3: [SCARED]
ZEKROM: [ROAR]
BOUFFALANT HERD: [CALM]
DAMON: I met... the great Zekrom!
JUANITA: You met Zekrom?!
CARLITA: Incredible!
MANNES: Yes, come in!
DAMON: I have found the answer! Zekrom has showed me how the
People of the Vale can use the Sword of the Vale to gain
complete control of the Dragon Force's energy!
IRIS, AXEW: [SLEEPING]
ASH, CILAN, PIKACHU, VICTINI: [SLEEPING]
VICTINI: [DREAMING]
VICTINI: [NERVOUS]
VICTINI: [STARTLED]
VICTINI: [DELIGHTED]
KING: I'm sorry, Victini...
VICTINI: [CURIOUS]
KING: Please forgive me for trapping you here...
I'm so sorry...
VICTINI: [CONFUSED]
VICTINI: [SAD]
VICTINI: [UPSET]
VICTINI, PIKACHU: [SLEEPING]
ASH: Poor Victini...
ASH: So you are lonely, aren't you...?
VICTINI: [SURPRISED]
VICTINI: [INSISTENT]
VICTINI: [AMAZED]
PIKACHU: [CURIOUS]
PIKACHU: [AMAZED]
VICTINI: [PLEADING]
ASH, IRIS, AXEW, CILAS, PIKACHU: [BEWILDERED]
ASH: Victini... Do you wanna go there?
VICTINI: [AGREEMENT]
ASH: Okay!
ASH: Victini, I promise I'll take you to the ocean!
VICTINI: [SURPRISED] [EXCITED]
ASH, IRIS, CILAN, PIKACHU, AXEW: [AMUSED]
SIGILYPH: [APPEARING]
DAMON: From this day forward, the People of the Vale will be
reunited with their land! Sigilyph!
SIGILYPH: [PSYCHIC MOVE]
SIGILYPH: [DETERMINED]
PIDOVE FLOCK: [SHOCKED]
VICTINI: [SCARED]
IRIS: The Pillars of Protection!
CILAN: But What's happening?!
PIDOVE FLOCK: [SCARED]
VICTINI: [SCARED]
PIKACHU: [CALLING]
ASH: Victini!
VICTINI: [SCARED]
PIKACHU: [FRANTIC]
MANNES: It has begun!
VICTINI: [ANXIOUS]
PIKACHU: [EXERTION]
VICTINI: [FRANTIC]
JAMES: Up there!
JESSIE: It's Victini!
MEOWTH: C'mon, let's go after it!
PIKACHU, ASH, IRIS, CILAN: [EXERTION]
VICTINI: [FRANTIC]
ASH: Victini!
PIKACHU: [CALLING]
VICTINI: [FRANTIC]
DAMON: Victini!
VICTINI: [HESITANT]
DAMON: Victini! I ask that you grant me your power...!
VICTINI: [EXCITED] / [SURPRISED]
VICTINI: [SHOCKED]
SIGILYPH: [DETERMINED]
SIGILYPH: [FOCUSED]
VICTINI: [SHOCKED / STRUGGLING]
SOLOSIS GROUP, DUOSION GROUP: [PSYCHIC MOVE]
JUANITA: Damon!
DAMON: Victini's power's increasing the Psychic-type
Pokémon's strength in the castle!
DAMON: Take a look!
CARLITA: Ash!
ASH: Carlita, where's Victini...?
IRIS, CARLITA, JUANITA, PIKACHU, AXEW, ASH, CILAN: [SHOCKED]
ASH: What was that?!
IRIS: The castle!
PIDOVE FLOCK: [ANXIOUS]
SIGILYPH: [DETERMINED]
VICTINI: [SCARED]
JESSIE: James, what's going on?!
JAMES: I think the castle's moving!
MEOWTH: It's FLYING!
CARLITA, JUANITA, ASH, IRIS,
CILAN, PIKACHU, AXEW: [CONCERNED]
PIDOVE FLOCK: [FRANTIC]
DAMON: I'm using the castle to change the flow
of the Dragon Force!
SIGILYPH: [DETERMINED]
JUANITA, CARLITA, ASH, IRIS, CILAN, PIKACHU, AXEW: [STARTLED]
JUANITA, CARLITA, ASH, IRIS, CILAN, PIKACHU, AXEW: [SHOCKED]
JUANITA, CARLITA, ASH, IRIS, CILAN, PIKACHU, AXEW: [AMAZED]
MANNES: It's finally happened!
DAMON: We're on our way!
SIGILYPH: [EXCITED]
DAMON: The Kingdom of the Vale will be renewed
when the castle is returned!
VICTINI: [PAINED]
PIKACHU: [SHOCKED]
JUANITA, CARLITA, ASH, IRIS, CILAN, PIKACHU, AXEW: [SHOCKED]
VICTINI: [WHIMPERING]
DAMON: Ash, Victini is lending me its power!
ASH: You're hurting Victini! You've got to let it go!
PIKACHU: [PLEADING]
DAMON: I won't! Not while I still need its power!
VICTINI: [STRUGGLING]
PIKACHU: [SHOCKED]
GOTHITELLE: [APPEARING] / [CONFUSION MOVE]
PIKACHU: [STRUGGLING]
GOTHITELLE: [DETERMINED]
VICTINI: [PAINED]
IRIS: Victini!!
ASH: STOP IT!!
PIKACHU: [STRUGGLING]
CARLITA: Stop, or Victini will die!
JUANITA: Damon, please stop it now!
DAMON: But, Mother!
ASH: Now! Pikachu, use Thunderbolt!
PIKACHU: [THUNDERBOLT MOVE]
GOTHITELLE: [PAINED]
IRIS, CILAN, PIKACHU, AXEW, ASH: [SHOCKED]
ASH: Pikachu, destroy the pillars! Electro Ball!
PIKACHU: [ELECTRO BALL MOVE]
JUANITA, CARLITA, ASH, IRIS, CILAN, PIKACHU, AXEW: [SHOCKED]
ZEKROM: [APPEARING]
ZEKROM: [ROAR]
CARLITA: Zekrom!
ASH: It IS?!
PIKACHU: [SHOCKED]
ASH, IRIS, CILAN, PIKACHU, AXEW: [AWED]
ZEKROM: [ROAR]
ASH, IRIS, CILAN, PIKACHU, AXEW: [SCARED]
JUANITA: Golurk! Stop Zekrom!
GOLURK: [ATTACKING]
ZEKROM: [IMPACT]
ZEKROM: [ZEN HEADBUTT MOVE]
GOLURK: [IMPACT]
GOLURK: [SHOCKED]
ZEKROM: [DRAGON PULSE MOVE]
GOLURK: [IMPACT]]
ASH, IRIS, CILAN, CARLITA, JUANITA, AXEW, PIKAHU: [WORRIED]
GOLURK: [PAINED]
IRIS: Golurk!
AXEW: [UPSET]
GOTHITELLE: [ANGRY]
DAMON: Gothitelle, use Confusion!
GOTHITELLE: [CONFUSION MOVE]
ASH, IRIS, CILAN, CARLITA,
JUANITA, AXEW, PIKAHU: [STRUGGLING]
CARLITA: Stop... Damon!
ASH: Pikachu, quick! Thunderbolt!
GOTHITELLE: [DETERMINED]
CILAN: Ash, NO!
VICTINI: [UPSET]
VICTINI: [STRUGGLING]
ZEKROM: [ROAR]
DEERLING X 2, SAWSBUCK X 2: [PANICKED]
VICTINI: [STRUGGLING]
KING: The Sword of the Vale must not be moved...
KING: If the Sword of the Vale is moved once more,
the Dragon Force will be disturbed...
KING: ...and that could destroy our entire world. Which means,
the castle should never be moved again!
VICTINI: [HAPPY]
VICTINI: [QUESTIONING]
IRIS: ASH!
CILAN: You're awake!
PIKACHU: [HAPPY]
IRIS: Thank goodness!
ASH: Where am I?
CILAN: In the castle's storeroom...
JUANITA: Ash, please forgive me...!
CARLITA: Forgive my brother...!
ASH: He shouldn't have moved the castle!
ASH: If the castle's moved, the Dragon Force will be disturbed,
and it'll destroy the world!
JUANITA: What did you say?!
ASH: Victini just told me so!
ASH: The castle was moved to the top of the mountain to keep the
disturbance in the Dragon Force from getting out of control!
CARLITA: It can't be
JUANITA: According to legend, the Dragon Force became
disturbed after Zekrom turned to stone.
Which means Zekrom doesn't know!
CILAN: So, what do we do?!
IRIS: Zekrom's too strong!
JUANITA: Reshiram!
ASH: Reshiram?
IRIS: The other great dragon Pokémon...
CARLITA: Reshiram has the power to stop Zekrom!
ASH: Okay, but where is Reshiram?!
JUANITA: Zekrom was beneath the castle... That's where Damon
found it! Then that means...
Reshiram must be nearby as well...!
CILAN: Beneath the castle...
ASH, PIKACHU: [SHOCKED]
CILAN: Ash!
KLANG, KLINKLANG: [DETERMINED]
MANNES: What is this?!
PIKACHU: [FOCUSED]
IRIS: Just how far does this path go?
CILAN: It feels like we keep going around in circles...!
CARLITA: Hold on! Where's Ash?
IRIS, CILAN, CARLITA, JUANITA, AXEW: [CONFUSED]
ASH: Hey, you guys! Come down here!
IRIS: But Ash...
CILAN: How did you get down there?
PIKACHU: [UNSURE]
ASH: Beats me...!
ASH: We're gonna go on ahead!
PIKACHU: [EXCITED]
PIKACHU: [FOCUSED]
IRIS: GO for it!!
CILAN: Find Reshiram!
ASH: You got it!
PIKACHU: [AFFIRMATIVE]
AXEW: [WORRIED]
VICTINI: [UPSET]
ASH: Victini's in a lot of pain!
PIKACHU: [CONCERNED]
PIKACHU: [FOCUSED]
RESHIRAM: Do you possess...
ASH, PIKACHU, PIKACHU: [STUNNED]
RESHIRAM: ...the courage to seek the truth?
ASH, PIKACHU: [SHOCKED]
ASH: We've gotta keep moving!
PIKACHU: [DETERMINED]
ASH: Pikachu, make sure you stay with me!
PIKACHU: [PERSISTENT]
ASH, PIKACHU: [FRANTIC]
PIKACHU: [SHOCKED]
PIKACHU: [SCARED]
PIKACHU: [FRANTIC]
ASH: Pikachu!
PIKACHU: [DETERMINED]
ASH, PIKACHU: [DETERMINED]
PIKACHU: [WORRIED]
ASH: I'm okay...
PIKACHU: [RELIEVED]
ASH: Where are we?
ASH, PIKACHU: [SHOCKED]
ASH, PIKACHU: [AWED]
RESHIRAM: What is your wish? Your truth?!
ASH: My truth? I really wanna help Victini...!
ASH: I've GOTTA help!!
ASH: Victini lived here all alone for a thousand years...
ASH: Lonely... Must've been so lonely...!
ASH: I promised...I'd take Victini to the ocean!
ASH, PIKACHU: [SHOCKED]
RESHIRAM: [ROAR]
RESHIRAM: It is your courage that shall become your truth!
ZERKROM: [ROAR]
CILAN: Juanita, look through the clouds!
CARLITA: Oh no!
AXEW, CARLITA, JUANITA, CILAN: [CURIOUS]
JUANITA: It's Mannes!
MANNES: Things look really BAD down there!
JUANITA: The Dragon Force is out of control!!
MANNES: How did you know?!
CARLITA: Because Ash told us it would happen...!
GOLURK: [GREETING]
JUANITA: Golurk! You must go and stop the castle!
GOLURK: [AFFIRMATIVE]
GOLURK: [THREATENING]
DAMON: Zekrom! Don't let it get in my way!
ZEKROM: [ZEN HEADBUTT MOVE]
GOLURK: [IMPACT]
IRIS, CILAN, CARLITA, AXEW, JUANITA: [SHOCKED]
JUANITA: ...Golurk, NO!!
MANNES: Everyone, get in!
GOLURK: [ANGRY]
JUANITA: Golurk, I know you can do it!
GOLURK: [IMPACT]
ZEKROM: [ZEN HEADBUTT MOVE]
GOLURK: [DETERMINED]
MEOWTH: C'mon, you can do it!
JESSIE: Easy for you to say...!
JAMES: You've got CLAWS!
JAMES: What's going on?!
GOLURK: [GYRO BALL MOVE]
ZEKROM: [ATTACKING]
GOLURK: [IMPACT]
GOLURK: [DISORIENTED]
ZEKROM: [ROAR]
JUANITA: Golurk, get out of there!!
ZEKROM: [ATTACKING]
GOLURK: [SCARED]
MANNES: Too late!
ZEKROM: [ROAR]
RESHIRAM: [ROAR]
IRIS: IT'S ASH!!
AXEW: [EXCITED]
CILAN: And he found Reshiram!
DAMON: It's Reshiram!
ZEKROM: [FUSION BOLT MOVE]
RESHIRAM: [FUSION FLARE MOVE]
ASH: Reshiram! Fly down and let us off at the castle!
DAMON: Gothitelle!
GOTHITELLE: [APPEARING]
ZEKROM: [FOCUSED]
RESHIRAM: [IMPACT]
ASH: Victini!
VICTINI: [PAINED]
GOTHITELLE: [DETERMINED]
ASH: Now, Pikachu, use Thunderbolt!
PIKACHU: [THUNDERBOLT MOVE]
GOTHITELLE: [IMPACT]
RESHIRAM: [ATTACKING]
ZEKROM: [FUSION BOLT MOVE]
RESHIRAM: [FUSION FLARE MOVE]
IRIS, CILAN, CARLITA, JUANITA, MANNES, AXEW: [ANXIOUS]
IRIS, CILAN, CARLITA, JUANITA, MANNES, AXEW: [SCARED]
ZEKROM: [SHOCKED]
ZEKROM: [PANTING]
RESHIROM: [ROAR]
ZEKROM: [ROAR]
GOLURK: [STARTLED]
JUANITA: You did well, Golurk.
IRIS, CILAN, CARLITA, JUANITA, MANNES, AXEW: [WORRIED]
GOTHITELLE: [PSYBEAM MOVE]
ASH: Pikachu, Quick Attack!
PIKACHU: [QUICK ATTACK MOVE]
GOTHITELLE: [IMPACT]
GOTHITELLE: [ENERGY BALL MOVE]
PIKACHU: [DODGING]
ASH: Pikachu, hang in there!
PIKACHU: [DETERMINED]
DAMON: Sometimes, in the search
for ideals...sacrifices are required!
ASH: My ideals don't need sacrifice!
GOTHITELLE: [FOCUSED] / [IMPACT]
ASH: Thanks, Pikachu!
PIKACHU: [EXCITED]
ASH: I'm coming...Victini!
VICTINI: [STRUGGLING]
ZEKROM: [THREATENING]
VICTINI: [PAINED]
PIKACHU: [ANGRY]
DAMON: Zekrom, stop those two!
ZEKROM: [HESITANT]
DAMON: Zekrom, what's wrong?
PIKACHU: [THUNDERBOLT MOVE]
VICTINI: [PAINED]
PIKACHU: [WORRIED]
ZEKROM: [DRAGON PULSE MOVE]
VICTINI: [WEAK]
ASH: Victini...!
PIKACHU: [CONCERNED]
VICTINI: [GRATEFUL]
PIKACHU: [RELIEVED]
ZEKROM: [ROAR]
RESHIRAM: [ROAR]
DAMON: But why, Zekrom?! But why...?!
ZEKROM: I can hear the land's anger!
DAMON: Anger...?
JUANITA: Damon...! The Vale is in deep trouble!
MANNES: The Dragon Force is out of control!
RESHIRAM, ZEKROM: [ATTACKING]
DAMON: Oh no...!
DAMON: Fulfilling my mother's dream...
How could that be wrong?!
PIDOVE FLOCK: [SCARED]
CARLITA: Damon, isn't there any way to calm the Dragon Force?
JUANITA: Please, Damon...
DAMON: I don't know. I just don't know!
ZEKROM: You must soothe the anger of the land!
RESHIRAM: Use the Sword!
DAMON: That's it...!
DAMON: The Sword of the Vale will once again restrain
the Dragon Force!
DAMON: Reshiram! Zekrom! Lend me your power!
ZEKROM: [DETERMINED]
RESHIRAM: [DETERMINED]
ZEKROM, RESHIRAM: [FOCUSED]
RESHIRAM: [FOCUSED]
ZEKROM: [FOCUSED]
SOLOSIS GROUP, DUOSION GROUP: [ANXIOUS]
SIGILYPH: [FRENZIED]
MANNES: The Dragon Force reversed on itself...!
DAMON: Look! Mannes! The castle is starting to crumble!
You must get everybody out!
MANNES: Right, Damon...!
MANNES: Everyone, this way!
VICTINI: [STRUGGLING]
ASH: Victini...!
IRIS: Ash, quick!!
PIKACHU: [SURPRISED]
HYDREIGON: [APPEARING]
JUANITA: Damon!
DAMON: You go on ahead!
ASH: Damon, wait...!
DAMON: Ash, you've got to get away from here!
ASH: But, Damon...
DAMON: Ash, go. I've got to do this alone.
CARLITA: Mannes! Behind you!
CILAN: Ash, hurry up!
PIKACHU: [URGENT]
MANNES: It's the barrier!
CILAN: Oh no! Ash!
PIKACHU: [CONCERNED]
ASH: Victini can't get past!
DAMON: And the barrier's closing in!
ASH, DAMON, VICTINI, PIKACHU: [SCARED]
ASH: Oh no, Damon!
SOLOSIS GROUP, DUOSION GROUP: [SCARED]
SIGILYPH: [SCARED]
ASH: Pikachu! Victini! Stay close to me...!
PIKACHU: [STRUGGLING]
VICTINI: [STRUGGLING]
ASH: It's so cold...Pretty soon...
we're gonna run out of air...!
PIKACHU: [SHIVERING]
VICTINI: [SHIVERING]
ASH: I've gotta think...What can I do...?
RESHIRAM: [DETERMINED]
ZEKROM: [DETERMINED]
GOLURK: [FOCUSED]
DAMON: Ash, listen...You'll make it!
PIKACHU: [RELIEVED]
ASH: Damon, it's you!
DAMON: Now, destroy the Pillars of Protection! We've got to
release all of the energy!
ZEKROM, RESHIRAM: [ROAR]
ZEKROM: [FUSION BOLT MOVE]
RESHIRAM: [FUSION FLARE MOVE]
PIKACHU: [THUNDERBOLT MOVE]
PIKACHU: [SHOCKED]
PIKACHU: [WORRIED]
PIKACHU: [CONCERNED]
VICTINI: [CONCERNED]
DAMON: Ash, you can't give up...!
DAMON: ...because you've been chosen by the great
dragon Pokémon!
ASH: Me give up? NO WAY!
PIKACHU: [CONCERNED]
VICTINI: [CONCERNED]
GOLURK: [STRUGGLING]
DAMON: We're coming!
PIKACHU: [UPSET]
ASH: I can't move... My body won't let me...
VICTINI: [CONCERNED]
ASH: Victini...I'm really sorry...
ASH: Victini... I know I promised you...
I'd take you to the ocean....
VICTINI: [SAD]
ASH: I'm sorry...
VICTINI: [UPSET]
PIKACHU: [UPSET]
ASH: Victini...What're you...
VICTINI: [SEARING SHOT MOVE]
VICTINI: [WEAK]
ASH: Victini!
VICTINI: [HAPPY] / [DETERMINED]
VICTINI: [CHARGING]
VICTINI: [V-CREATE MOVE]
ASH: No! Victiniiii!!!
PIKACHU: [CONCERNED]
ASH: Victini...
SOLOSIS GROUP: [CALLING]
GOLURK: [FOCUSED]
DUOSION X LOTS: [FOCUSED]
SIGILYPH: [DETERMINED]
PIKACHU: [RELIEVED]
ASH: Pikachu!
ASH, PIKACHU: [HAPPY]
HYDREIGON: [GREETING]
IRIS: Ash! Pikachu!
AXEW: [RELIEVED]
CARLITA: Are you all right?!
MANNES: The leading edge of the Dragon Force...!
I can see it up ahead!
CARLITA: Is that where the castle goes?
DAMON: Yes, exactly!
That's the only way to calm down the chaotic Dragon Force!
JUANITA: Damon! You've got one shot at this!
GOLURK: [DETERMINED]
PIDOVE FLOCK: [SHOCKED]
JAMES: We're alive...!
JESSIE: And on land...!
MEOWTH: Land is good...
JESSIE: Which means...
JAMES: Together...
JESSIE, JAMES, MEOWTH: Life is GREAT!
ASH, PIKACHU, IRIS, AXEW: [RELIEVED]
PIKACHU: [CONCERNED]
ASH: We're at the ocean... Victini...
ASH: You gave us...every bit of power you had! Even so...
I didn't give you anything!
IRIS: Oh, Ash...
ASH: Victini...I'm sorry...!
PIKACHU: [SAD]
ASH: Victini! You LOVE macarons! We've got some left!
CILAN, ASH, IRIS, PIKACHU, AXEW: [SURPRISED]
VICTINI: [EATING]
AXEW, PIKACHU: [EXCITED]
CILAN: This has a strangely familiar flavor...
IRIS: Sure does!
VICTINI: [EATING]
CILAN: Here's the rest...!
ASH: Guess I'll just have to eat all of these...
and here I goooo...!
VICTINI: [OBJECTING]
VICTINI: [DELIGHTED] / [CHOKING]
ASH: Aw, Victini...! Sorry! Are you okay?
MANNES, IRIS, CILAN, CARLITA, JUANITA, DAMON, AXEW: [HAPPY]
VICTINI: [DELIGHTED]
VICTINI: [HAPPY]
VICTINI: [EXCITED]
COTTONEE X 6, PURLOIN,
DRILBUR X 3, PETILIL X 4, VICTINI: [EXCITED]
VICTINI: [EXCITED]
DEERLING X 3, SAWSBUCK X 4: [HAPPY]
SWANNA FLOCK: [HAPPY]
VICTINI: [HAPPY]
ASH: Of course...
ASH: I get it! You're gonna head on back to the Vale,
aren't you, Victini?
VICTINI: [AGREEMENT]
ASH: Go make everyone happy, 'kay?
PIKACHU: [ENCOURAGING]
VICTINI: [PROUD]
PIKACHU: [AMUSED]
CILAN: I've still got some macarons...
VICTINI: [EXCITED]
CARLITA: Damon, what...?
DAMON: Everyone...please forgive me...
JUANITA: Damon...
JUANITA: The future's what's important!
JUANITA: Let's restore the land of our ideals...!
ZEKROM: [TRIUMPHANT]
RESHIRAM: [TRIUMPHANT]
You can reach for the stars
And know that in your heart
You have the strength deep inside.
Let it be your guide.
You can fly past the moon
And race all afternoon.
Don't be afraid to make a choice.
Raise your voice.
Just follow your star.
Spread your wings and be free.
Wherever you are
Is right where you should be.
So listen to your heart
And believe in what you dream.
And follow, follow your star.
There's a time when you know
How to find your destiny.
With each turn in the road
It's clear for you to see.
So push through the days.
Don't let your spirit fade.
Throw away all your doubts.
Oh, sing out loud.
Just follow your star.
Spread your wings and be free.
Wherever you are
Is right where you should be.
So listen to your heart
And believe in what you dream.
And follow, follow your star.
Just follow your star.
Spread your wings and be free.
Wherever you are
Is right where you should be.
So listen to your heart
And believe in what you dream.
And follow, follow your star.
Follow your star.
Just follow your star.