Pika!
[rhythmic drumbeats]
[rain pouring]
[swift whooshing]
[Zarude singing in unison]
♪ Sing now, Zarude ♪
♪ We are the strongest ♪
♪ We have no fear ♪
♪ Za-za-zarude ♪
♪ We are the voice of the jungle ♪
♪ Lift up your voices ♪
♪ The ground catches the water ♪
♪ The water nurtures the trees ♪
♪ The sun shines down the forest ♪
♪ The trees become the jungle ♪
♪ Woo, can you hear it? ♪
♪ Footsteps upon footsteps ♪
♪ Voices upon voices ♪
♪ We are the voice of the jungle ♪
♪ Lift up your voices ♪
♪ Under the Heart Tree ♪
[growls]
[all shrieking in panic]
Huh? Hmm.
[birds flapping]
Hmm.
-Hey, let's go.
-Right.
Hmm. Hmm?
[gentle music]
[vines crack]
[plops]
[crying in distance]
Hmm?
[sniffs]
[crying continues]
Huh?
[wailing]
[cries]
Hmm?
[gentle music continues]
-[sniffs]
-[coos]
-[giggles]
-[gasps]
[wary grunting]
[chuckles, grunts]
Hmm. Huh?
[baby coos]
[grumbling]
[babbles, hiccups]
-[baby giggles]
-[exhales]
[grumbles]
-[shrieks]
-[baby laughs]
[Dada groaning]
[sighs]
Huh?
-[screams in panic]
-[laughs]
[distressed breathing]
-[loud bump, groan]
-[baby giggles]
[Dada gasps]
[panicked exhale]
[thuds]
[groans]
[waterfall gushes]
[soft snoring]
[majestic music]
-[both growling]
-[all cheering]
[all sniffing]
[Dada exhales]
-[loud thud]
-[Dada] Hmm?
Hey, what's that?
I've come here to speak
to the Elder about it.
[grunts]
-Hmm…
-[sighs]
Have you forgotten that no one
is allowed inside our territory?
Have you?
[both snarling]
[Elder] Now, now.
It appears to me you've brought
something unusual along with you.
Elder.
It is human, correct? And a child, too.
Human?
-[Alpha] That?
-[sneezes]
[Zarude groaning]
-[Alpha growls, sniffs]
-[grumbles]
Oh, that stinks!
It smells like a Stunky's rear end!
[groans in disgust]
So, tell me, what do you plan
to do with it?
I don't know.
[Dada] But everybody heard it, right?
That sound.
If I leave it be, it will not survive.
That's not our concern!
Nobody can break our laws!
-I'll get rid of it!
-[both grunting]
[both growling]
-[Zarude 1] Beat 'em up!
-[Zarude 2] Get 'em!
[Zarude 3] Obey the laws!
-[Zarude 4] It can't be allowed!
-[Zarude 5] Get it out now!
Water raises the trees.
The light shines down
and turns the trees into jungle.
[Alpha] This revered water raises
the Zarude and gives us our rich bounty!
Allowing others onto our land
means we will wither and vanish.
That is the law of the Zarude!
-[Zarude yelling in agreement]
-[Zarude 4] We are Zarude!
Quit your complaining, I know that.
Then hurry up and…
I'm going to go find its parents.
-What?
-Hmm.
-[Dada] I will withdraw from the troop.
-[Alpha] Do you know what you're saying?
The law won't apply to me anymore.
[Alpha grunts]
You'll never return again!
You'll lose all of your friends!
[aggressive grunting]
It can't be helped.
[Dada grunts]
[Sub-alpha] What a piece of work.
[Alpha] I can't believe it.
I thought I could trust you.
[grumbles]
You traitor!
I'm sorry.
[grunts, thumps]
[hums in wonder]
[grand music]
♪ What's the matter, little bird? ♪
♪ It's hard to find a speed grower ♪
♪ There's a blue sky waiting for you ♪
♪ Got a lot to learn, yet, yeah, you do ♪
♪ Take the chance when ♪
♪ It's at your doorstep ♪
♪ I'll be close by ♪
♪ Watchin' you fly ♪
♪ Through the raging winds ♪
♪ Through the chaos, and back again ♪
♪ Know that I am always here ♪
♪ And you are safe ♪
♪ Through the thick and thin ♪
♪ Through what's scary and back again ♪
♪ Know that I am always here ♪
♪ And you are safe ♪
♪ You're always safe ♪
♪ There's no reason to cry ♪
♪ It takes more than just one try ♪
♪ When you fall down, get back up ♪
♪ I know there's more
Where that came from ♪
♪ Like lights in the sky ♪
♪ You glow through the night ♪
♪ I'm always close by ♪
♪ Watchin' you fly ♪
♪ You're always safe ♪
THE MOVIE
KOKO
Pocket
Monsters
THE MOVIE
KOKO
Pocket
Monsters
THE MOVIE
KOKO
Pocket
Monsters
THE MOVIE
KOKO
Pocket
Monsters
THE MOVIE
KOKO
Pocket
Monsters
THE MOVIE
KOKO
Pocket
Monsters
THE MOVIE
KOKO
Pocket
Monsters
THE MOVIE
KOKO
Pocket
Monsters
THE MOVIE
KOKO
Pocket
Monsters
THE MOVIE
KOKO
Pocket
Monsters
THE MOVIE
KOKO
Pocket
Monsters
THE MOVIE
KOKO
Pocket
Monsters
THE MOVIE
KOKO
Pocket
Monsters
THE MOVIE
KOKO
Pocket
Monsters
THE MOVIE
KOKO
Pocket
Monsters
THE MOVIE
KOKO
Pocket
Monsters
THE MOVIE
KOKO
Pocket
Monsters
THE MOVIE
KOKO
Pocket
Monsters
THE MOVIE
KOKO
Pocket
Monsters
THE MOVIE
KOKO
Pocket
Monsters
THE MOVIE
KOKO
Pocket
Monsters
THE MOVIE
KOKO
Pocket
Monsters
THE MOVIE
KOKO
Pocket
Monsters
THE MOVIE
KOKO
Pocket
Monsters
THE MOVIE
KOKO
Pocket
Monsters
THE MOVIE
KOKO
Pocket
Monsters
THE MOVIE
KOKO
Pocket
Monsters
THE MOVIE
KOKO
Pocket
Monsters
THE MOVIE
KOKO
Pocket
Monsters
THE MOVIE
KOKO
Pocket
Monsters
THE MOVIE
KOKO
Pocket
Monsters
THE MOVIE
KOKO
Pocket
Monsters
THE MOVIE
KOKO
Pocket
Monsters
THE MOVIE
KOKO
Pocket
Monsters
THE MOVIE
KOKO
Pocket
Monsters
THE MOVIE
KOKO
Pocket
Monsters
THE MOVIE
KOKO
Pocket
Monsters
THE MOVIE
KOKO
Pocket
Monsters
THE MOVIE
KOKO
Pocket
Monsters
THE MOVIE
KOKO
Pocket
Monsters
THE MOVIE
KOKO
Pocket
Monsters
THE MOVIE
KOKO
Pocket
Monsters
THE MOVIE
KOKO
Pocket
Monsters
THE MOVIE
KOKO
Pocket
Monsters
THE MOVIE
KOKO
Pocket
Monsters
THE MOVIE
KOKO
Pocket
Monsters
THE MOVIE
KOKO
Pocket
Monsters
THE MOVIE
KOKO
Pocket
Monsters
THE MOVIE
KOKO
Pocket
Monsters
THE MOVIE
KOKO
Pocket
Monsters
THE MOVIE
KOKO
Pocket
Monsters
THE MOVIE
KOKO
Pocket
Monsters
THE MOVIE
KOKO
Pocket
Monsters
THE MOVIE
KOKO
Pocket
Monsters
THE MOVIE
KOKO
Pocket
Monsters
THE MOVIE
KOKO
Pocket
Monsters
THE MOVIE
KOKO
Pocket
Monsters
THE MOVIE
KOKO
Pocket
Monsters
THE MOVIE
KOKO
Pocket
Monsters
THE MOVIE
KOKO
Pocket
Monsters
THE MOVIE
KOKO
Pocket
Monsters
THE MOVIE
KOKO
Pocket
Monsters
THE MOVIE
KOKO
Pocket
Monsters
THE MOVIE
KOKO
Pocket
Monsters
THE MOVIE
KOKO
Pocket
Monsters
THE MOVIE
KOKO
Pocket
Monsters
THE MOVIE
KOKO
Pocket
Monsters
THE MOVIE
KOKO
Pocket
Monsters
THE MOVIE
KOKO
Pocket
Monsters
THE MOVIE
KOKO
Pocket
Monsters
THE MOVIE
KOKO
Pocket
Monsters
THE MOVIE
KOKO
Pocket
Monsters
THE MOVIE
KOKO
Pocket
Monsters
THE MOVIE
KOKO
Pocket
Monsters
THE MOVIE
KOKO
Pocket
Monsters
THE MOVIE
KOKO
Pocket
Monsters
THE MOVIE
KOKO
Pocket
Monsters
THE MOVIE
KOKO
Pocket
Monsters
THE MOVIE
KOKO
Pocket
Monsters
THE MOVIE
KOKO
Pocket
Monsters
THE MOVIE
KOKO
Pocket
Monsters
THE MOVIE
KOKO
Pocket
Monsters
THE MOVIE
KOKO
Pocket
Monsters
THE MOVIE
KOKO
Pocket
Monsters
THE MOVIE
KOKO
Pocket
Monsters
THE MOVIE
KOKO
Pocket
Monsters
THE MOVIE
KOKO
Pocket
Monsters
THE MOVIE
KOKO
Pocket
Monsters
THE MOVIE
KOKO
Pocket
Monsters
THE MOVIE
KOKO
Pocket
Monsters
THE MOVIE
KOKO
Pocket
Monsters
THE MOVIE
KOKO
Pocket
Monsters
THE MOVIE
KOKO
Pocket
Monsters
THE MOVIE
KOKO
Pocket
Monsters
THE MOVIE
KOKO
Pocket
Monsters
THE MOVIE
KOKO
Pocket
Monsters
THE MOVIE
KOKO
Pocket
Monsters
THE MOVIE
KOKO
Pocket
Monsters
THE MOVIE
KOKO
Pocket
Monsters
THE MOVIE
KOKO
Pocket
Monsters
THE MOVIE
KOKO
Pocket
Monsters
THE MOVIE
KOKO
Pocket
Monsters
THE MOVIE
KOKO
Pocket
Monsters
THE MOVIE
KOKO
Pocket
Monsters
THE MOVIE
KOKO
Pocket
Monsters
THE MOVIE
KOKO
Pocket
Monsters
THE MOVIE
KOKO
Pocket
Monsters
THE MOVIE
KOKO
Pocket
Monsters
THE MOVIE
KOKO
Pocket
Monsters
THE MOVIE
KOKO
Pocket
Monsters
THE MOVIE
KOKO
Pocket
Monsters
THE MOVIE
KOKO
Pocket
Monsters
THE MOVIE
KOKO
Pocket
Monsters
THE MOVIE
KOKO
Pocket
Monsters
THE MOVIE
KOKO
Pocket
Monsters
THE MOVIE
KOKO
Pocket
Monsters
THE MOVIE
KOKO
Pocket
Monsters
THE MOVIE
KOKO
Pocket
Monsters
THE MOVIE
KOKO
Pocket
Monsters
THE MOVIE
KOKO
Pocket
Monsters
THE MOVIE
KOKO
Pocket
Monsters
THE MOVIE
KOKO
Pocket
Monsters
THE MOVIE
KOKO
Pocket
Monsters
THE MOVIE
KOKO
Pocket
Monsters
THE MOVIE
KOKO
Pocket
Monsters
THE MOVIE
KOKO
Pocket
Monsters
THE MOVIE
KOKO
Pocket
Monsters
THE MOVIE
KOKO
Pocket
Monsters
THE MOVIE
KOKO
Pocket
Monsters
THE MOVIE
KOKO
Pocket
Monsters
THE MOVIE
KOKO
Pocket
Monsters
THE MOVIE
KOKO
Pocket
Monsters
THE MOVIE
KOKO
Pocket
Monsters
THE MOVIE
KOKO
Pocket
Monsters
THE MOVIE
KOKO
Pocket
Monsters
THE MOVIE
KOKO
Pocket
Monsters
THE MOVIE
KOKO
Pocket
Monsters
THE MOVIE
KOKO
Pocket
Monsters
THE MOVIE
KOKO
Pocket
Monsters
[bright music]
[narrator] This is Milyfa Town
small and surrounded by jungle.
Continuing his journey
to become a Pokémon Master
with his partner, Pikachu,
Ash plans to enter the Forest of Okoya,
looking for adventure.
-Ha! Hey, buddy.
-Pikachu!
-Okay, I gotta go.
-Pika, pika!
-One minute!
-What, Mom?
-Are you sure you're ready?
-I'm all set. I'll be fine.
-See ya!
-[Delia] Hold it!
That attitude worries me the most!
What about potions,
extra clothes, and Pikachu's food?
You'll need all of them!
[sighs]
You worry too much, Mom.
That's what being a parent's all about.
Okay, I hear you. I'm hanging up.
There's that attitude!
[Ash] Uh…
[Delia] If anything bad
were to happen to you--
-[Ash] Ah! Somebody's calling me. See ya!
-Huh?
-[panting, grunts]
-Pika!
[Pikachu] Pika?
[Ash] Mom could talk until tomorrow
if she had the chance.
[Pikachu] Pi.
Oh, look at that, buddy.
-[Pikachu] Pika.
-[Ash] The jungle, it's huge!
[grunts]
Hurry up, Dada!
Slow down, Koko.
[Koko] The berries were
almost ripe last time.
[Dada] You don't have to rush,
the berries will wait.
You never know, right!
[Koko grunts]
[grunting]
[soft grunt]
Huh?
-What's wrong, everyone?
-[Pokémon chitter]
Calm down, I can't understand you
if you're all talking at once.
Amoon, Amoon, Amoonguss!
[Pokémon chitter]
[grunts]
What's wrong, Koko?
-They're mad.
-[all gasp]
Huh?
[sniffs]
So that's what it is.
[gasps]
Hey, Dada. Uh…
[Koko] Is that…
[Dada sighs]
[sniffs]
They're coming all the way out here.
-[whining]
-[Koko gasps]
[Pokémon whining continues]
Calm down. Quiet,
I have nothing to do with this.
[overlapping complains]
I was looking forward to having
some berries with my son, too!
[loud roar]
[all squealing]
-[farts, shrieks]
-Oh, what, that stinks. That smelly--
Hey, Dada…
[stomach rumbles]
What?
I'm so hungry.
Huh?
Hey.
-I think I've got a good idea.
-Huh?
It's not just good. It's a great idea.
We'll make one for ourselves,
a place where berries grow.
Huh?
Say, that makes sense.
I never thought of that.
Let's do it. Great idea!
-Really?
-There are seeds inside this thing, right?
Let's put it close to home.
They won't bother us.
And once we've got lots of berries,
we can share them with everyone!
Only my son would think of that.
[Dada] Ha, right, it's all decided.
[Koko] Then let's gather
what we can, and go home.
[Dada] Mm.
[squawks]
Look, Pikachu, do you see that?
-I've never seen that move.
-Pika…
-[branch cracks]
-[both gasp]
[squawks]
[water splashes]
Great! Let's battle and catch it.
Pikachu, Quick Attack!
Pika!
-[Pikachu] Pika!
-[Cramorant groans]
All right!
-[Cramorant squawks]
-[Pikachu] Pikachu!
[grunts]
Pikachu, use Thunder Bolt!
Pikachu. Pika-chu!
-[squawks]
-[Ash groans]
-Pika.
-Go, Poké--
[Cramorant squawks]
[sighs]
Oh, but it's still a funny Pokémon.
Talk about not holding back.
True. But if Pikachu weren't like that,
it wouldn't be perfect for Team Rocket.
Still, there's something disconcerting
about being electrocuted from the inside.
It zaps me just thinkin' about it.
Wobbu.
Pi, Pika!
-Flap, flap.
-[Ash] Check it out.
-This time, we'll stay cool.
-Pika! Pika!
[grunts]
This one's fast!
But I'll catch it for sure--
[screaming]
-[groans]
-Pika.
That was quite a fall.
-Are you hurt?
-Huh?
-I'm fine, really, see.
-[Pikachu] Pi.
[Ash] Oh, man.
Not again.
-Are you a Pokémon trainer by chance?
-Yep.
My name's Ash, and I'm from Pallet Town.
-And this is my partner, Pikachu.
-Pikachu!
I'm Sharon, a Biotope Company researcher.
-Nice to meet you.
-"Researcher"?
So what are you researching here?
You see, we're gathering samples
to see what components the water contains.
Wow. Components are so cool.
-That clueless twerp.
-[snickers]
As dumb as a fence post!
-So what are they doing?
-Ah?
-Here, found it.
-[both] Huh?
[James] "We at the Biotope Company
use cutting-edge technology
to discover and implement developments
that lead to peace and harmony
for both people and Pokémon."
-Sounds like the real deal.
-Really?
-Oh, who's this?
-[all gasp]
[James] "Our team leader, Dr. Zed.
Leading the search
and investigation of a spring
that has healing powers," it says.
A "healing" spring?
-Does such a thing even exist?
-Whether it does or not…
There seems to be a horde
of Team Rocket hi-jinx waiting to be had.
And the boss never gets tired of hi-jinx.
[all laugh evilly]
[Koko] There, that should do it.
-[grunts]
-[leaf swishes]
[Dada grumbling]
-[exhales]
-[twinkles]
[plant wobbles]
[Koko] Wow!
It's looking really good.
True, but there won't be anything
to eat for quite a while.
I wonder when my vines
will finally grow in.
You'll do fine without them.
-[Hoothoot hooting]
-[both] Huh?
[panicked hooting]
-Ah, Dada, I'll be right back!
-Hey!
[Dada] Where are you going?
-[Koko] Show me where.
-[Hoothoot hoots]
But…
[sighs]
I guess I shouldn't be all that surprised.
-[panicked gasps]
-[both grunting]
[thwacking]
[grunts]
Hey, stop it!
[both grunting]
Take a breath and calm down!
Ugh! Break it up!
[grunts]
Wha…
[Flygon yells]
-[Oddish squeals]
-[groans]
Hey, look, you're here,
so you should have stopped them.
Skwovet, Skwovet, Skwovet.
[Koko groans]
For crying out loud.
We've got to break it up.
And then try to take care
of Flygon's wounds, or it won't fly again.
[both grunting]
-[fruit thuds]
-Huh?
Mm? Mm-mm! Mm.
Skwovet!
[growls]
-Skwovet. Skwovet.
-That's just what we needed.
-Catch me if you can!
-[growls]
[rapid breathing, grunts]
It's a risky plan, but let's make it work!
-[Flygon yells angrily]
-[Koko grunts]
-[rapid breathing]
-[squeals]
[Koko grunts]
-[Flygon yells]
-[water splashes]
[mumbles indistinctly]
[mythical music]
[screams happily]
[yells joyfully]
-Shush, be quiet.
-Skwovet.
[blows raspberries]
You're healed.
All right now, go back home.
[Koko] If they find us, it could get ugly.
-[Alpha] Well, Koko.
-[Koko gasps]
Who are "they" supposed to be?
Uh-oh! Flygon, move!
-[Flygon shrieks]
-[Koko grunts]
[suspenseful music]
[both grunting]
[Koko] All we did was borrow the spring!
The spring is our territory! Not yours!
[vine thwacks]
How dare you talk about territory
after you came and ate all of our food!
It's only natural for the strong
to steal from the weak.
Everything in nature is part of our law.
-You singing that same song again?
-[Alpha grunts]
-[Koko grunts]
-[loud thud]
[wind gusts]
[grunts]
[Sub-alpha] That little creep.
-[grunts]
-[whooshes]
You have the gall
to think you can beat me?
Koko!
-[beams zap]
-[grunts]
-[rope whips]
-[both grunting]
[Koko grunts]
-Let me go!
-Shut up!
-[Koko groans]
-Huh?
-So you're here?
-[Dada exhales]
-Dada, it's you!
-I told you to stay away!
-But I--
-No excuses!
You think you can trespass
and not be punished?
[both grunting]
I know it was wrong.
I'm going to take my son and leave.
[gasps]
Elder.
[Dada] My apologies.
I will make sure this
never happens again. Please.
The law is still the law.
It's too late after it's been broken.
Now leave at once.
-Come on, Koko.
-The Elder's always been soft on you.
-[snarls]
-[thumps]
[Zarude growling]
[sighs]
[Dada] I can't believe you.
[Koko] They're the ones
that are hoarding everything!
Zarude will always have the Zarude law.
The law allows them to live.
Then who will care for the other
jungle Pokémon?
Jungle Pokémon are great. Nobody knows it.
Flygon picks fights, but it's so strong.
And Ninjask is super, super fast.
Cottonee stick together and don't let go!
-I'm aware. Come down.
-[Koko] Fine.
Is it really that bad?
[Dada] It is to the Zarude.
Then I guess I'm not a Zarude.
That's why I don't understand the law.
My hands aren't like theirs, or my skin.
You're wrong! You are a Zarude.
Then why can't I use just one single move?
-[Koko] Just what am I?
-[gasps]
What you are…
[gasps]
-[Koko grunts]
-[Dada] Koko!
[sighs]
[somber music]
Whenever it comes to Pokémon,
he always ignores everything else.
[Rufflet whimpers]
[Koko] Are you okay? Hang in there.
-Please, Rufflet! Please, Rufflet!
-[Rufflet whimpers]
Ah…
[Koko] Uh?
-What's wrong, Koko?
-[gasps]
[Koko] Oh, Dada!
[Dada exhales]
-It's not moving at all!
-[Rufflet] Rufflet.
[deep sigh]
-Skwovet?
-Hey, what do I look like to you, Skwovet?
-Skwo, skwo.
-That's not what I meant.
Skwovet? Skwovet!
[grunts]
If I'm not a Zarude,
then what in the world am I?
Just who am I supposed to be?
[Koko yelps]
-Skwovet!
-[metal clangs]
[Skwovet mumbles]
Skwovet!
[yelps]
[water gushing]
-[Ash grunts]
-[Pikachu blows raspberries]
[Ash] Hey, are you all right?
[coughs]
-Uh, he's alive!
-Pikachu!
-Hang in there. We're gonna get you help.
-Pika!
Skwovet. Skwo! Skwo…
Skwovet!
[engine hums]
[engine turns off]
[Sharon] The water composition
from Sector B came up negative
for the deposits.
-[Zed] Let's return to Sector D.
-[researchers] Yes, sir.
This water sample
will be all the proof we need
of the healing spring's existence.
Now there's no doubt
in my mind we'll find it.
We're one step away.
-[glass shatters]
-[gasps]
[panicked screaming]
We're so sorry.
We were just transferred here
from headquarters.
My apologies.
Injuries?
-[Meowth] We're all in one piece, sir!
-[sighs]
Very good, then.
Everything and everyone here
is vital to our research.
Please be more careful.
[all] Yes, sir.
All right, and make sure
you clean up this mess.
At once, sir.
Come on, don't do anything
you're not told to do.
And one thing I forgot to mention,
the doctor's room is off-limits.
[researcher] He gets prickly
if anyone else goes in there.
[Team Rocket] Right.
-You're awake, huh?
-Pika!
[Ash] How do you feel?
-Wah!
-Pika!
[Ash groans]
-[Koko grunts]
-[Ash] Whoa, chill out!
-[vase shatters]
-Pikachu.
Did you hurt anything?
-[snarls]
-[Nurse Chansey] Chansey!
-Pi?
-[Ash] What? Hey, hey!
-[man] How are you doing?
-[gasps]
[Nurse Joy] So are you feeling better now?
-What's going on?
-Pika!
[all gasp in surprise]
[laughs]
You're awesome!
Ah!
[grunts]
-[all gasping]
-Whoa!
[Koko] Huh?
[cheerful music]
Za?
Za-za-zaruda?
-[horn honks]
-[grunts]
-[tires screech]
-[trainer] Huh?
-Drednaw!
-What? No, Drednaw!
-Pikachu! Pika!
-This is bad. We've gotta stop it!
-[woman shrieks]
-Dred! Dred!
-Pika!
-Stay away from it!
-Dred!
-Za!
[panting]
[Ash grunts]
Out of its way!
-[Ash gasps]
-[Koko grunts]
-[yells]
-Drednaw!
-Huh?
-Pika?
[Drednaw grumbles]
[Drednaw sighs]
-[girl] Morpeko!
-[Morpeko chitters]
-Zarude, za-zarude.
-Drednaw!
You're really awesome.
How did you do that?
-Pika!
-Huh?
Oh, there you are. What do you know?
Drednaw doesn't normally take
to strangers like that.
Dred.
-Thank you so much, Mister.
-Wah!
-Hey, where are you going?
-Pika!
[Koko mumbles]
[Ash] Hey! How did you do that back there?
-The thing with Drednaw?
-Ah!
-Pika!
-Why are you running away?
[Koko mumbles]
-[screams]
-[zaps]
-What's the matter?
-[speaks Zarude]
Pika?
[zaps]
-Za, za.
-Pi?
Oh, that? Here, you wanna see a Poké Ball?
See? I have one of 'em too.
[sniffs, licks]
Hey, what are you doing?
Hey! Come on, let go!
Pikachu, you gotta help me out here!
-Pika-chu!
-[zaps]
-Pika.
-[both exhale]
[both whimper]
Pikachu!
[gasps]
Hold on a minute. Is this the first time
you've seen a Poké Ball?
-Za, za, zarude.
-Pika?
-Pikachu, what is it?
-Pika, pika!
Zarude, zarude.
No way! You can actually talk to Pikachu?
Pikachu.
-[both laugh]
-Awesome! So, my name's Ash.
-Pika, Pikachu, Pikachu, pikapi!
-[snickers]
Pikachu, Pikapi.
[gasps]
You can talk to each other.
Pika, pika!
-But my name is Ash. Got it?
-"Name is Ash."
-Yeah.
-Zarude!
[celebrates ecstatically]
-Hey, then what's your name?
-Pika, pika?
[grunts]
Koko.
Pipi!
So your name's Koko. Nice to meet you.
Zar?
-Ru…
-[Ash] Huh?
[Ash gasps]
[giggles]
Za!
Pika!
[groovy music]
♪ So much to see ♪
♪ New places I can show you ♪
♪ So cool, are we ♪
♪ It's like I've always known you ♪
♪ Whatever I can do ♪
♪ I'm sure you can ♪
♪ Let's take it easy ♪
♪ We don't need a plan ♪
♪ No way! ♪
♪ So much to learn ♪
♪ I just have to watch it ♪
♪ Let's all take turns ♪
♪ And if you fall, I got you ♪
♪ Sharing adventures
That's what friends are for ♪
♪ Can't wait for what the future
Has in store ♪
♪ Who-oh-oh ♪
♪ Everyone together ♪
♪ I hope this day never ends ♪
♪ Who-oh-oh ♪
♪ Nothing could be better ♪
♪ Playing and running around ♪
♪ With my new ♪
♪ My new friends ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah ♪
♪ Who-oh-oh ♪
♪ Nothing could be better ♪
♪ Having the time of my life ♪
♪ With my new ♪
♪ My new friends ♪
-It's pretty, huh?
-Pika.
-[Falinks squealing]
-Za?
[Koko breathes heavily]
-What's wrong?
-Pika!
Hey, Koko!
[indistinct chatter]
[woman] The fireworks are canceled?
[man] Those Pokémon
are getting in the way.
[foreman] Will you all just shape up?
-Come on, what in the world is with them?
-Is something wrong?
We're just trying to get ready
for tonight's fireworks,
but they keep getting in our way.
I wonder why that is?
[foreman] If we knew that, we'd fix it.
-We're gonna miss the starting time.
-Za.
[speaks Zarude language]
-[replying eagerly]
-[gasps]
[foreman] Hey! That's dangerous!
Get off there!
[Ash] Wa… wait a second, please.
-[sniffs]
-Huh?
He can understand what Pokémon are saying.
-Yeah, sure he can, kid.
-No, it's the truth.
-I think he figured something out.
-Ah!
-[cloth rustles]
-[Falinks whimpers]
Za, zarude.
[mumbles]
[Koko] Zarude! Zar-zar-zar!
Looks like he found something.
[foreman] Shut down the power. Now!
[grunts]
[soft grunt]
What's this for?
-Za!
-Hold on!
[Ash grunts]
Zar, zarude, zarude.
[Falinks chitters]
-[grunting]
-Everybody, pull! Slowly, slowly.
-Zarude, zarude, za.
-[Falinks groans]
There's a kid hanging on.
Ah, make sure you don't let it break!
[foreman] Easy now, slowly. Oh, he's out!
-Zaru-ru!
-[Falinks cheering]
One of their own was stuck in the tube.
[Ash] So that's why you didn't want
the fireworks to go off, am I right?
-[Pikachu] Pikachu.
-[Falinks chittering]
I had no idea.
I guess I was pretty harsh back there.
Falinks! Falinks! Falinks!
[both chuckle]
[soft grunt]
Good for you guys!
[Ash giggles]
-[Pikachu] Pika, pi!
-[Ash chuckles]
[whistles]
[explosion]
-Za, za, zarude!
-[Pikachu gasps]
-He sure is an odd one, huh?
-It's all right. They're just fireworks.
Pikachu.
[loud bangs]
"Just fireworks."
-[slurps]
-[gasps]
[Koko snarls]
[foreman] Mr. Mayor.
[Mayor] You seem to have put on
quite a show again this year.
[foreman] Thank you so much.
We owe it to these two.
They were the ones who saved Falinks.
Well, then, I should let you know,
my gratitude has no bounds.
-Thank you.
-[bleating]
[Mayor] And because of it,
we successfully launched the fireworks
to make our wish to Celebi.
Celebi, the mythical Pokémon?
Right, Celebi happens to be
our jungle guardian.
And can I see Celebi?
No, unfortunately,
it's been a very long time
-since we last saw it.
-[Ash] How come?
Za-za!
[Mayor] They say Celebi only appears
when all is peaceful.
So when it doesn't show itself,
it means that there could be something
very bad going on in the jungle.
-Man.
-But they also tell another story.
When Celebi vanishes
somewhere deep within the jungle,
it's said an egg is left behind.
It is also said that Celebi
brought the egg here from the future.
-Yeah, from the future?
-Remember, it's a story.
[Mayor] It's just that I'd like Celebi
to return to our jungle,
and for all of these people
and Pokémon to have a bright future.
It's because of that wish
that our magnificent fireworks display
takes place.
[loud explosions]
[grand music]
[Skwovet mumbles]
Koko! Oh, it's just you.
[Skwovet mumbling frantically]
Uh… Huh?
-[Koko] Zarude!
-[all laugh]
-Za? Zaru-ru?
-Huh?
[Ash] Oh, that family?
-What about them?
-We'll get to see them again next time.
[boy] Tomorrow? Please?
[father] I don't think tomorrow
will be possible, not until you're six.
"Family."
Za.
-Huh? What's up?
-Pika!
-[Pikachu] Pika?
-[Koko] Za, za, za.
[Ash] What's wrong, Koko?
-Za, za, zarude.
-You looking for something?
[sniffs]
Za!
[grunts]
[Koko] Ash, Zarude, za, za.
-Uh, what was that?
-Za, zarude.
Did you just ask me to come with you?
[pensive music]
[steady breathing]
[insects chirping]
[Pikachu panting]
[Ash] Hey, Koko, how far are we going?
Zaru-zaruza.
-Skwovet! Skw, skw, skwo, skwo.
-Za?
Zaru!
Skwo, Skwovet! Skwovet! Skwovet!
Skwovet! Skwovet!
Skwovet! Skwovet! Skwovet!
[laughs]
That's one's a cutie.
Zaru, zaru, za, zaruza?
-[both screaming]
-Whoa! It's a trap!
-[Ash] What's this all about?
-Ash!
-Zaru, za, zaru.
-[thuds]
[speaking in Zarude]
Zarude!
-A Pokémon?
-Pikachu.
Koko family.
-Your family has a Pokémon?
-Pika.
Did you use human language?
[grunts]
First, you just vanish without a trace.
-Now, you bring a human?
-[scoffs]
-You knew all along.
-[gasps]
I'm a human, aren't I?
Uh… Mm…
-[Koko] Come on, Dada, tell the truth!
-[grunts]
I'm human just like him!
I'm not a Zarude at all, am I?
Wrong! You're a Zarude!
Don't lie to me!
[gasps, groans]
[Ash grunts, screams]
Ow.
What do you think's going on?
-[Ash] They really do look like a family.
-[Pikachu] Pika.
I brought Ash here
so I could show him to you.
And there were a lot more people
like this back there.
[Koko] They launched something
up into the sky that sparkled.
Humans and Pokémon watched it together.
Smiled together!
-Pika.
-Skwovet. Skwovet, skwovet.
The Zarude can't do that,
you taught me everything!
You showed me how to get food.
How to run,
how to swing on vines, all of it.
So why? Why didn't you
tell me about humans?
[sighs]
I didn't want to make you sad.
-Don't give me that!
-Uh-uh.
Huh?
I thought I was weird for making friends
with all the Pokémon, but that wasn't it.
It was because I'm human.
If it means I can be friends
with Pokémon, I'd rather be human!
[gasps]
Pika.
[somber music]
I knew that this
would happen sooner or later.
-You're exactly right.
-[gasps]
You're really a human,
and I'm not your real Dada.
Now you know.
Then tell me who I am!
[vine snaps]
-[whooshes]
-[thuds]
Follow me, then.
[James] Mm. It appears they put a stop
to this research ten years ago.
[Jessie] Why is that?
There was some sort of accident.
-An accident?
-[emergency alarm blares]
This PC seems to be riddled with security,
so we'll have to employ the doctor's PC.
Didn't they warn us?
Not being allowed to enter
the doctor's room is a real red flag.
There's no doubt
that doc's hiding something.
[both sigh]
[water churns]
[metal clanks]
When I found you, it was raining.
[Dada] You were alone,
lying in a strange-looking box.
And there were no other humans around.
You were wearing this when I found you.
-[necklace clinks]
-Uh…
Why did you take me with you?
I honestly don't know.
I never knew my own family.
I really never knew where I came from.
You reminded me of me.
I couldn't just leave you there.
[picture frame clacks]
[gasps]
[Dada] The baby in that picture is you.
The two large humans
are probably your real parents.
-Pipi.
-They look just like you.
I looked everywhere,
trying to give you back to your family,
and that's how I found this place.
I think this was probably
your family's nest.
But by the time I found it,
it already looked like this.
It was then that I realized
I would be raising you myself.
[Dada] Looking back, it could be
that decision was a mistake.
In the end, I still made you sad.
Uh-uh.
So that's all. I've told you everything.
[grunts]
Now you must decide.
Do what you want with this place.
[vine cracks]
Dada!
Koko.
-[digital trill]
-[Jessie] Now to just--
Wa, wa!
What was that for?
-Hmm. Yes, I did it.
-No, I get to do it .
[Jessie] Let's see, I wonder
if there's anything nice
in the doctor's room!
Be careful with that.
It's the only one we have.
-I know, I know!
-[all scream in panic]
-[clacking]
-[all panting]
[all squealing]
[all screaming]
[all groaning]
-Ooh, got it.
-We're good.
-Yeah, for now.
-Wah.
[all] Huh?
[Meowth] That's the wacko
who tried to swallow Pikachu!
-[grumbles]
-[Jessie] No!
[Jessie screams]
Hey, let go! Behave yourself!
Get away from me! Grow up!
Bad wacko! Go find your own device!
[Jessie screaming]
Stop!
Cramorant! Cramorant! Crama!
-I've had enough of this.
-That thief has issues.
-Blah, blah!
-Huh?
[both gasp]
-[Jessie, James screaming]
-[Meowth] Oh, no!
Looking at the two of you,
I started thinking about my own dad.
When I was little, I told some other kids
about my goal, and they laughed at me.
But my dad told me something
I never forgot.
"The map to your goal is inside yourself.
If you give up, your dream's
never gonna come true."
Now, being on my journey with Pikachu,
I'm starting to get what he meant.
Don't let it get to you, you're family.
[grunts]
You can argue,
but then everything will go back
to normal in no time.
I'll tell you, families sure
can be a mystery, huh?
[uplifting music]
-Huh? What's up?
-Za.
[objects clatter]
Za.
What are you looking for?
[object clinking]
-Skwo?
-Pikachu?
[gasps]
Zaru, zazaru. Zarura!
Oh, yeah, you wanna find your family.
[Ash grunts]
I'll help you look.
-Pikachu!
-Skwovet, Skwovet. Skwovet?
-[sneezes]
-[Pikachu, Ash gasp]
Ah. I think I've seen this before.
See? I met someone
with this mark just today.
Pika!
-Zaru?
-Pika.
I'll bet she knows something about it.
Koko…
Go?
Koko… go.
Hm.
[water rippling]
Elder, is that you? This is rare.
So, you've told him the truth.
[Dada] I should have done that
from the start.
Mm. Are you sure?
How could I know anything
about being a Dada.
I never had one, so I never became one.
We haven't seen Celebi
in a long time, have we?
Celebi?
[Elder] The last time I saw it was…
Ah, yes, just a little bit
before you appeared to me.
[Dada] Are you saying
that this is my fault?
Wait till I'm done talking, please.
[vine cracks]
First, Celebi vanishes, then you appear.
And then you decide to raise Koko.
Don't you think there might be
a reason for these events?
Huh?
[Elder] You possess your own destiny.
The answer is known only
to the life-giving waters.
[Ash snoring]
[Skwovet snoring]
[gentle music]
[Koko] The spring!
Let's take it to the spring!
We can't! It's dangerous!
[Dada] How could I ever allow that?
But I'm holding a Pokémon
who needs our help now!
I've got to do something!
[soft sobbing]
[Dada] All right.
Let me have it.
-There's another way we can help cure it.
-Really?
It's true, now stand back.
Rufflet.
-[Rufflet whimpers]
-Huh?
[Dada hums seriously]
[vines crack]
[whirring]
[roars]
[grand music]
[Koko] Dada!
You all right?
I'm fine.
That move really takes it out of you.
-Rufflet.
-Huh?
Ruff… Ruff? Rufflet!
Ruff? Rufflet!
Wow, you're all better now, aren't you?
-[Rufflet cheering]
-That's incredible!
How did you do that? Tell me.
It's quite an amazing move
that only certain Zarude are able to use.
Ask the jungle for help
and it lends you its power.
But, son, if you use it too much,
it can drain away your life force.
So use it only
when you absolutely need to.
Thanks so much, Dada.
[sighs]
[lively music]
[lively music continues]
Uh, delicious Pokémon food.
There's no one here
to scoff it down but us.
-Pokémon food gives me gas.
-Just search for the winged wacko!
-[Wobbuffet mutters]
-Huh?
-[James] Who?
-[Jessie] Huh?
[Meowth] Twerp dead ahead.
-What would he be doing here?
-Who knows?
-[gasps in awe]
-[liquid burbles]
Skwo, Skwo, Skwovet!
-[Sharon] Right this way, please.
-[gasps]
Pika!
-Look at all this stuff.
-It is impressive.
-[Ash] Yeah.
-[hums sneakily]
You sit in those things.
[sniffs]
-Za.
-[Zed] Sorry for the wait.
I am the head of this laboratory.
My name is Zed.
You have a question for me?
Uh-huh. My name's Ash,
and this is my partner, Pikachu.
-Pikachu!
-And this is Koko.
-Uh…
-[Ash] See.
We're looking for these people.
-You know 'em?
-[Zed] Let me see.
[Ash] We thought they might be
working here at your lab.
We think it's a picture
of Koko's real parents.
I wanna reunite them.
-[Zed] Where did you get this?
-Huh?
[sighs]
Then this is Al?
[all gasp in surprise]
[Ash] Al?
The two adults
are Mr. and Mrs. Molybdenum.
-They used to run this lab.
-[digital clicking]
And the child they're holding…
-[Koko grunts]
-…is Al, their son.
Huh?
Those two were the leaders
of the Healing Spring Research Team.
You see, the spring
was considered only a legend.
Although a large number
of research labs pursued it,
they never actually found it.
[Zed] However, these two were able
to discover it in the jungle,
and they even obtained a water sample,
a historic breakthrough.
-Skwovet?
-Za, zaruza.
-Ah, um…
-Uh, ah, apologies.
-Is that really true?
-Correct.
That pendant definitely belonged
to the Molybdenums.
[Zed] Sharon, scanner, please.
[Sharon] Yes, sir.
[Zed] Al, would you mind?
-[Koko] Ah! Za, za!
-[Zed] Huh? What's the problem?
Koko was brought up by a Pokémon.
-He's not good at people language.
-He was what?
[Zed] Raised by Pokémon?
But it means he's able
to talk to other Pokémon.
Unbelievable.
-Doctor, here you go.
-Thank you.
-I'd like to know if you're truly Al.
-Zar.
A scan of your pendent will let me know.
Don't worry, it won't hurt you. Relax.
-[chimes]
-Zar!
Don't worry, I won't take it.
Please, Sharon.
[chimes]
Biometrics are confirmed.
What do you know?
Then that means there is something
I must tell this child.
[Zed] Mister and Missus Molybdenum
are not here at this lab.
Ten years ago, they passed away.
-You're kidding.
-Unfortunately, I'm not.
Pika?
[Zed] It was a car accident.
The couple were lost
along with their research,
and Al went missing.
We assumed that he perished as well.
But here you are, alive,
nothing less than miraculous.
Koko…
He just said that your parents
aren't in our world anymore.
Mm.
Pika.
Sharon? The data is up.
-[Sharon] Thanks.
-[digital trill]
-Doctor.
-What did you find?
-[Zed] Put it up on the screen.
-Huh?
-Sir.
-Is everything all right?
It seems the data we all thought was lost
was stored inside Al's pendant.
Nearly all of it's corrupted except for…
-On screen.
-[projector hums on]
Huh?
-[Zed] Can it be?
-Za!
[Zed] The healing spring.
[wondrous music]
-Pika!
-Skwovet.
-Pika?
-Skwo, Skwovet.
What is it, Koko?
Could he have a clue as to its location?
Of course. The jungle is Koko's home.
Al, if you know something,
you must tell me.
Do it for your parents' dream.
Do it for them!
[somber music]
Uh-uh.
[grunts]
-Al!
-Skwo! Skwovet!
-Koko! I'm sorry, gotta go.
-[Pikachu] Pi!
Doctor?
[Ash] Koko!
Wait up, Koko.
I'll go with you.
-[groans]
-Koko!
[Skwovet panics]
[somber music continues]
[Skwovet panting]
Skwovet!
Skwovet, Skwovet, Skwovet, Skwovet!
[panting]
[heavy breathing]
[Koko panting]
-[wind blows]
-[birds chirping]
[Ash] Oh, man, which way?
No matter which way we go,
all I see is trees.
-Pikachu, anything?
-Pika.
-[Skwovet calls]
-Pika?
Skwovet. Skwovet!
-[screams]
-Pika.
-Where's Koko? Do you know?
-Skwovet, skwovet, skwovet, skwovet!
[mumbles passionately]
[water gushing]
All of those people know who I am.
[Koko] Why was I left in the forest?
Was it because I couldn't be
with them anymore?
Was it because they had to leave me there?
[soft groan]
[Koko gasps]
[foreboding music]
What is this?
-[loud explosion]
-[Koko gasps]
[birds cawing]
[suspenseful music]
It's him.
[engines hiss]
-Oh, it really is here.
-Wow, Doctor!
-Excellent.
-We found it!
Yes, there's no doubt.
[Zed] It's the healing spring,
and this is its source.
Look, it's that tree.
Yeah, the same tree in the picture.
[grunting]
[Koko] Zaru, zaru, zaruza!
Al! You made it possible.
Hey, uh, no hard feelings.
Ah!
[snarls]
You wouldn't understand.
Forgive us,
we didn't wanna have to do this.
We're sorry, we mean no harm.
Zar!
-[metal crashes]
-[Koko grunts]
-Zar! Zar!
-[pilot] What do we do with him, Doctor?
We have no choice. He'll come with us.
We wouldn't want him to attack us again.
[Koko grunting]
-[loud thump]
-[panicked scream]
[groans]
[whimpers]
Oddish!
[thuds]
[groans]
-[zaps]
-[Koko] Zaru!
What happened?
[Zed gasps]
What's going on?
What is all this supposed to mean?
Forgive us, but we decided to use you.
How could we not when we found
what we've been searching for?
-Za, zaruza?
-Skwo, skwovet.
Wanna know why we came along?
That's what friends do.
"What friends do."
Hmm.
Pikachu. Pi!
-[web whooshes]
-[gasps in surprise]
[all yelp]
-[Team Rocket] Wow.
-[Ash] What are you doing?
[Zed] I beg your forgiveness.
[both yell]
-Pi!
-Skwovet!
Just keep quiet, okay?
-[loud thud]
-[Ash] Hey, wait!
[grunts]
Let us outta here!
[Zed] I'm entrusting the children to you.
[Team Rocket] Yes, sir!
Yeah, bleh! Big mouth, big deal.
-But this is our chance.
-How's that?
Where's Pikachu? It's in there.
You mean in the truck?
So what if we were to take
this truck for a little joyride?
Great idea! We're just so bad .
[all snickering]
-[Jessie] Indeed.
-[all] Huh?
[squawks]
-Pika?
-[Ash gasps]
-[screams]
-Huh?
[heavy footsteps approaching]
[loud crashing]
What do you think that was?
[Elder] Hmm, I'm not sure.
Would you go and see?
Mm, got it.
[hums in wonder]
We can grab the key
and Pikachu in one shot.
How do we coax it to spit the key out?
Urgh, you simply shove your hand
down its throat!
No sudden moves, please.
These paws aren't getting near that thing.
Then who does the honors?
[all gasp]
[zaps]
Say, are you two thinking
what I'm thinking?
Hold the phone.
That means Pikachu will be off the hook.
Oh, decisions, decisions.
-It's a no-brainer, the key!
-[James, Meowth] Huh?
Pikachu's around. We'll catch him later.
But the only time to crash
Big Mouth's room is when he's not in it.
-I'll be, sound logic.
-So, let's get in the groove and move!
Wobbuffet!
[suspenseful music]
[loud crash]
[hisses]
Come on, Dada, tell me, what do we do?
-[metal clonks]
-Huh?
No good.
Pikachu your tail,
if I can bite through it.
-[both grunting]
-Ash?
Hang on, we're gonna get you outta here.
And rescue the Pokémon,
your dad too, and the jungle too!
I'm not giving up until we win.
[tense music]
-Hey, what is all of this?
-That's what I want to know.
[chuckles]
They're coming here for one thing,
and that's the Heart Tree.
[Alpha] I want the rest of you
to report back to the Elder.
-What about you?
-I'll stop them in their tracks.
Great.
Now, would you like to go
along with me on a little rampage,
just for old times' sake?
Hmm, good idea.
If we don't, they'll tear our home apart.
[struggled grunting]
That's right, you can do it!
[Ash grunting]
[Pikachu grunts]
-Pika, pika!
-Iron Tail!
Pika, pika!
-All right! Koko.
-[web stretches]
-[grunts]
-Everything's gonna be okay now.
-Pika.
-Skwovet!
[Skwovet mumbles]
You were right.
-We just received word from the Doctor.
-[researcher] Huh?
Straight from the cab's radio.
-I'm to stand guard!
-Great. Thank you.
-Wobba!
-[James snickers]
-[squawks]
-[hums sneakily]
[both scream]
-Pikachu! Pik, pik, pik!
-[metal clangs]
-Hey, quick, hurry up!
-Just do it!
[all mumbling]
-Pikachu, one more time!
-Pika!
Ready?
Pika!
-Pi? Pika! Pikachu!
-[squawks]
-Yes!
-Pikachu!
[all grunting]
-[all whimper]
Pika, pika?
Ash, zaru, zarude, za, za.
-Pikachu, uh, mind if we run?
-Uh, do your thing.
Thanks.
On the contrary,
we should be thanking you.
Hey, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop!
[both growl]
[thrilling music]
Here it comes!
[Alpha growls]
[groans]
What was that?
-[Sharon] It's a Pokémon!
-[researcher] It's going to attack us!
[Zed] You must stay inside!
-Why are they attacking?
-How should I know?
[Dada grunts]
-[grunts]
-[thuds]
[whirring]
[grumbles]
[Koko panting]
Wait for me, Dada! Everybody!
[Alpha] Zar!
Zarude!
[explosion]
You all right?
-Yeah.
-This is not good.
[pilot] Doctor?
Please continue regardless.
They're all simply Pokémon.
[Zed] They'll run when faced
with real danger.
[both growl]
-[Zed gasps]
-[grunts]
[Zed grunts]
Don't you lay a finger on my Dada!
Koko!
[groans]
-Dada! Are you all right?
-Why did you come back?
You do nothing but get in the way.
-Do you think that Pokémon…
-It may have raised Al.
You two, get outta here!
[grunts]
[Dada] Hold on!
-Zarude!
-[wallops]
[Alpha groans]
-[robot humming]
-Pika, pika!
[crashes]
[speaking in Zarude]
-Doctor, think of what you're doing!
-Skwo! Skwovet.
I am uninterested in your opinions.
You know that one?
-Not very well.
-[chuckles]
He's my friend.
Hmm.
-[inhales deeply]
-[zapping]
Peekaboo! We'll find you!
-[Meowth] Secrets, treasure!
-[Jessie] Breakthroughs, secret info.
-It all works for me!
-[Meowth] Hmm, huh?
[Alpha and Dada sigh]
-[Alpha] Elder.
-[Sub-alpha] Hey, pull yourself together.
[Alpha] The ones who are ripping up
the forest are humans.
My wounds are insignificant.
Can't say the same for him.
I have no idea why, but this human child
actually fought alongside us.
The one Koko called "friend".
[Elder] First and foremost, we stop
the destruction of the jungle.
[Alpha] Right.
[water gushing]
[Sharon] Up close, you can feel its power.
Yes. How beautiful it is.
Doctor, over there!
The Pokémon from before.
It must be their nest.
It's a match!
Doctor, it's identical to the sample.
We've done it. We have location data too.
-Please do a scan of the giant tree.
-Huh?
-Right now.
-Sir.
[satellite hums]
-[whirring]
-[Sharon] What is that?
We've detected enormous energy
in the center.
That's the true nature
of its healing power.
[both gasp]
I want you to shoot the anchor
into the tree.
-But, uh, are you sure?
-[Zed] Do it!
-Yes, sir.
-Please, wait. No!
[blasts, whoosh]
[loud explosion]
[Zarude gasp]
They're taking this to the extreme.
[indistinct murmurs]
-The Heart Tree.
-[screams]
-[Zarude screaming]
-Ah!
Doctor, aren't we here for the spring?
Keep this up, and those Pokémon--
[laughs]
Wrong again.
My objective isn't the spring.
[Zed] Healing power is nothing more
than bits of energy carried by water
rushing through the tree.
My objective is the tree itself.
And to that end…
Right, I couldn't care less
what is sacrificed.
[somber music]
[Alpha] We can't just
sit around quietly in defeat.
-Any of you who can fight, follow me!
-[all roar]
You can't, you think you can win
against that thing?
-[Alpha] Huh?
-If you fight them head on,
-you'll get everyone hurt.
-But, Dada…
So you're saying do nothing?
[Alpha] How do we protect
the tree without fighting?
Hmm, but…
[Alpha] We are Zarude!
We are the strong ones!
We have no fear!
The jungle's lifeblood,
lift up your voices!
[Zarude troop growling]
-Amazing.
-Pika.
Let's go! For The Heart Tree!
[thrilling music]
[Zarude troop] Zarude!
-[Ash] Pikachu, let's go too!
-[Pikachu] Pika!
Dada, you just rest here.
[grunts]
Take the human child and run.
You can't win this.
But the jungle Pokémon,
what happens to them?
I just couldn't bear to lose you.
I know that. That's why I fight!
-[grunts]
-Koko!
-Pika!
-[steady breathing]
[groans]
[Dada] I should have known.
How can I protect the Pokémon…
protect our home, protect everyone?
How can I protect Koko?
-[squawks aggressively]
-Oh, oh, what did I do to you?
Stop, Braviary! He saved Rufflet!
[Dada] That's right! Now go away!
The nerve, not even a thank you.
They're together again,
that's the important thing.
Families are remarkable.
-Huh?
-You saw it.
It knew I was a Zarude,
and yet it still attacked.
Braviary threw caution to the wind.
That Rufflet should be pleased
with family like that.
But what about you?
Who knows, Koko.
There aren't many around
who are stronger than me.
You're right.
But, if the time were ever to come…
[Dada] If the time were ever to come…
all I can do is fight.
Yes, but aren't you taking this too far?
-[grunts]
-[Sharon gasps]
[Zed] I've gone over this
in my mind, over and over.
[grunts]
So why did they do this?
Humans and Pokémon
share the same life force.
[Zed] Why won't they understand
mine is the correct path?
It's right here under their noses!
[water gushing]
You're all the same.
[Zarude troop taunting]
Zarude. Lots of them.
-[researcher 1] "Zarude"?
-[researcher 2] They've come for revenge.
[Sharon] We've rekindled their rage.
Dr. Zed, now look at what you've done!
We're sorry. We'll be leaving right away.
-[pilot groans]
-[all gasp]
[Zed] We will not be leaving.
I will show you the truth path.
I'm afraid your parents
made the wrong decision, Al!
-[gasps]
-And they paid
the ultimate price in the end.
-Boss. I think I deserve an explanation.
-Look, Zed.
It turns out the source
of the healing power
is a great body of energy within the tree.
But there are Pokémon called Zarude
who live on that giant tree.
There's no doubt that tree
is special to the Zarude.
I ask you to reconsider.
We've searched for it so long,
and now we've found it!
We're suspending operations
until we find a way to resolve this for
-the good of both humans and Pokémon.
-[grunts]
Stopping for a bunch of Pokémon?
What is the matter with you?
Humans and Pokémon
share the same life force.
We share the same world.
I'm making the right decision, Zed.
I know it.
[James] Here's a video blog
from ten years ago.
-Ooh, let's watch.
-Sure.
-[mouse clicks]
-[computer trills]
[sighs]
Operations are suspended
on the Healing Spring Project,
though we could save countless people
with the power of that spring.
[grumbles]
And all for some worthless Pokémon.
[throws tantrum]
[Zed] The decision is wrong, I tell you!
[Zed aggressively breathing]
If I were in charge, I could lead
this research down the path to truth.
My way is correct!
If only I had the power,
I could prove to everyone
that my way is the right way.
Yes, yes, I can.
If the Molybdenums weren't around…
-[engine roaring]
-[Baby Koko crying]
-Come on, you two, where is that data?
-[clinks]
-[Chrom] We erased it.
-[Zed] But why?
-[thuds]
-It's to protect them!
[shouting]
Unacceptable!
-[Phossa screams]
-[tires screech]
-[groans]
-[vehicle explodes]
[Baby Koko cries]
[Phossa groans]
Will you please forgive us?
[grunts]
[Baby Koko crying continues]
[crying continues]
[approaching footsteps]
[Zed] This is best.
All for the best.
I will never give up.
I will revive this research
no matter what it takes.
This time, I choose the path.
[loud explosion]
[thunder rumbles]
In this moment,
my long-held dream has come true!
-How could he do that?
-It's so cruel.
I never knew any of this.
Al, you were a fortunate miscalculation
on my part.
But if you insist on intruding,
I will show no mercy to you or the Zarude!
[Pokémon chitter]
[groans, tumbles]
[exhales]
Well, well, hello.
-[Pokémon chitter]
-[Dada groans]
[Dada sighs, grunts]
Could you please give me a hand?
[Dada] If this continues,
everyone will lose everything.
I'm asking all of you for your help.
-[fruit thuds]
-[groans, gasps]
-Nuzleaf!
-[Pokémon chitter]
I know.
[Dada] I don't have the right
to ask anything of you.
But I have to do my best to help Koko.
You see, I'm his father,
and I must do something.
No matter what happens,
I have to do my best to protect Koko.
You are the friends Koko
is so very proud of.
Flygon, he says you pick a lot of fights,
but you're strong.
He says Ninjask is the fastest Pokémon
in the jungle.
And he says that Cottonee
stick together, and don't let go.
I know the Zarude can't win
this fight by ourselves.
But if you combine your strengths
with the Zarude,
I think we could save
both Koko and the jungle.
Please!
I'm asking you to come fight with us.
Please. Please!
I'm begging you!
[sobs]
-[growls]
-[zapping]
[Zed] You think a few Pokémon
and two immature children
have even a chance to stop me?
Course, we do!
Because we're working together!
How very quaint of you.
The world will see that I am right!
[all grunting]
[Zed] And now, I will accomplish
what the Molybdenums could not!
-Pikachu, use Quick Attack! Let's go!
-Pika!
-[Pikachu panting]
-[Koko grunts]
-Pika!
-Pikachu, are you okay?
-Pikachu…
[Zed laughs]
What happened
to that cockiness from before?
Were humans and Pokémon going to stop me?
-[emergency alarm blares]
-Huh?
-[thuds]
-[Koko groans]
-Huh?
-Pipi?
[majestic music]
It's Dada!
-Pi…
-He's got the jungle Pokémon with him.
[Alpha] Water raises the trees.
[Sub-alpha] The light shines down
and turns trees into jungle.
Of course, the trees are the Pokémon,
and that means you are the light.
Do you hear it?
The sound of stomping feet?
[all growl]
[both] Do you hear it? The many voices?
[all in unison]
Zar, zar, zar, zar, zar, zar, zar, zar.
Again? How can they stand against me?
The jungle's lifeblood,
lift up your voices!
With the Heart Tree!
[Pokémon aggressively grunting]
I'll stop you in your tracks!
-[Zed] Every one of you!
-[Dada roars]
Dada, you're wounded.
Are you gonna be okay?
Of course. Remember, it's me.
-So strong!
-Pika!
The Pokémon of the jungle
have gathered to protect their home.
[heroic music]
Braviary!
[squealing]
[grumbles]
-Nuzleaf!
-Braviary!
-[blasting]
[Pokémon growl]
[Elder] All the jungle Pokémon,
they're the roots circulating lifeblood.
And for the first time,
the jungle breathes.
Does this mean we were mistaken?
[uplifting music]
You impudent--
[tense music]
[roars]
[fire roars]
Zarude!
-[loud thwack]
-[groans]
Worthless Pokémon will not…
get in my way!
[dramatic music stings]
[gasps]
-[grunting]
-Dada!
[Koko] That's…
Please, don't worry.
As long as you're okay.
[all gasping]
[worried gasp]
[all gasp in surprise]
[grunting]
[growls]
Dada, no!
[Elder] Let's get him to the spring, Koko!
-Give them a hand.
-Mm-hmm.
You don't know when to quit!
[Zed] Well, I'll take care of that.
-[snarls]
-Now, Koko!
Huh?
He has to survive.
You're gonna have to fight us now!
No one's taking Koko's family away twice.
Pikachu!
[somber music]
[groans in pain]
Is it working, Dada?
What's wrong?
Hmm. Earlier, the water
inside the Heart Tree
was forced out, and its power
may have been weakened.
Oh, no. How do I…
I'll be all right.
Everything will be fine, really.
You don't have to make that face.
-Skwovet! Skwovet!
-[all aggressively yelling]
[Pokémon scream]
[loud explosion]
Pikachu, use Thunder Bolt!
-Pika! Pika, Pi!
-[zaps]
-How's that?
-Pika?
[robot whirring]
[Dada groans]
-I'm sorry.
-[gasps]
I was a failure at being your Dada.
Now there you go again, making that face.
Why are you still talking like that?
I've wondered for a long time
whether I was capable of being
a parent or not, but now…
Now what?
I'm glad you are my son.
[voice weakens]
Very glad.
[light splash]
Dada, no!
[Koko screams]
Dada!
[birds chirping]
I'll tell you one thing.
If someone I couldn't defeat
ever really were to appear…
[Koko] Yeah?
I'd have to protect you
by whatever means necessary.
[both chuckle]
I'll protect you too, Dada.
Uh…
[laughs]
[Dada] As if a tiny one
like you could do anything
[Koko] Yeah?
Don't you forget, I'm my Dada's son!
Uh…
[snickers]
-[Dada] You're the best son ever!
-[Koko laughs]
[Dada] You know, I think
I finally got it figured out.
I already was a father.
To be a parent is to have something
that's even more important
than one's own self.
[Koko grunts forcefully]
Koko.
I'm gonna use Dada's move to heal him.
[Elder] Koko, that isn't possible.
You heard it straight from his mouth.
You are a human.
Nuh-uh, I'm a Zarude. I'm my Dada's son!
And I'm going to save my Dada.
I know I can do it.
I'm the only one who can do it!
I'm his son! I'm my Dada's son!
[Koko grunts forcefully]
[grunting continues]
-[magical whirring]
-[grunts]
[screams]
Dada!
[grunting]
[magical music]
[all gasp in awe]
-[Ash] What's this?
-Isn't that his…
-The smell is different.
-[both] Koko?
[magical music continues]
[grunting]
-Hmm…
-Huh?
[thwacks]
[Sharon] The Pokémon are fighting
as hard as they can,
and all we can do is watch helplessly.
Hold on.
I think the control system
is on the machine's back.
Smash it, and the machine stops.
-Are you sure?
-Yeah.
-Listen, Ash--
-[Ash] I heard it!
[robot whirring]
[Ash] That's the spot.
Pikachu, quick, aim right
for that thing's back!
-Pikachu!
-Use Quick Attack!
-Pika! Pi, pi, pi, pi, pi--
-[Alpha] Look out!
-Pika!
-[smashes]
-I know what you're trying to do.
-Pika, pika!
-What are you planning?
-Pika! Pikachu!
-And that will take the machine down?
-Pika!
Got it. Then follow me!
-Pika?
-You're gonna help us out?
[growls]
[Alpha shouting in Zarude]
[groans slowly]
Dada.
Unbelievable.
I guess you saved me, didn't you?
Mm.
Now, Koko, what will I do with you?
-Pi!
-Zaruru!
[Alpha] Go!
-Pi!
-[screeches]
-[grunts]
Pika!
-Go!
-[yells]
-[blasts]
-Pika!
[both grunting]
Pika! Pi! Pi! Pi!
-Go!
-Do it!
-All right!
-[all cheering]
Pikachu! Iron Tail!
Chu… Pika!
-[Alpha grunts]
-Pika!
-Go, yellow one!
-[zapping]
-[whooshes]
All right!
-Chu!
-[gasps]
Pika!
[metal screeches]
[explosion]
[machine hums off]
That did it!
[relieved sigh]
-It's all over, Doctor.
-[both gasp]
[Ash] He's not there.
[Zed panting]
I will not let it be over.
Not until I prove that I'm right!
[tense music]
[Zarude grunt]
[Zed gasps]
-[Zed] He's still alive?
-[Dada] Wait, Koko! Don't chase him!
[growling in distance]
The Elder!
[suspenseful music]
[Zed panting]
[both grunting]
[Zed] Let me go!
Koko, that's enough! Stop it now!
-What's happening?
-[Dada] Koko's anger has taken over.
-Koko, Dr. Zed!
-Pika!
[grunts]
Don't mess with me!
[grumbles]
Za!
[intense music]
-[rope cracks]
-[gasps]
[water gushing]
[grunting]
-Koko!
-Let me go! What are you doing?
-[Zed] Weren't you listening to me, Al?
-[grunts]
If you think I'm going to let it end here…
[Zed sobbing]
[Zed] Al? Al!
[screams]
Al!
[somber music]
[bright music]
-That'll do it.
-Pikachu!
[researcher 1] Yeah,
get the rocks down that way!
[Sharon] Keep it up, you're doing great.
-Skwov.
-[chuckles]
What do you make of this?
We treated the jungle
as if it were ours alone,
rejecting all others,
and constantly stealing
anything we wanted.
[Elder] I compare this
to that wicked human and wonder,
what's the difference?
The jungle belongs to all
the Pokémon who live in it.
[Dada] Without lifeblood,
it will never recover.
And… we are part of that lifeblood.
No one's excluded.
Now we know, the law taught us that.
[pensive music]
-Pi! Pika!
-[Ash and Koko gasp]
Hey, Dada. Are you feeling better now?
Yeah, see for yourself.
-Oh, the Zarude.
-Pika?
-Dada, this isn't good. Huh?
-Just watch.
Dear jungle Pokémon,
we wanna give all of you
our solemn promise.
We're going to restore the jungle
even if it takes years.
I'm begging you to trust us.
Will you, Zarude?
-I don't think that they understand.
-Oh, they do.
[squeaks]
[twinkles]
-Look at that!
-So they can do it if they try.
-[gasps in awe]
-[all cheering]
-Skwovet?
-[gasps]
-Ah!
-[whimpers]
Such astounding power.
[upbeat music]
-Zarude are so awesome.
-Pika!
[upbeat music continues]
All right! Let's plant a bunch more trees!
-[Ash] We've got lots to do, Pikachu.
-[Pikachu] Pikachu!
-So do we.
-Ma'am.
♪ Sing now, Zarude ♪
♪ The tree holds us together ♪
♪ It stands forever ♪
♪ Za-za-zarude ♪
Elder.
When that one proclaimed
that he intended to raise you,
I wonder if anyone thought
this would be our future.
[gasps]
Look around.
[Elder] You helped to create
a bridge between humans and Pokémon.
Perhaps no one
could have accomplished that but you.
Koko, you are both human and Zarude.
Therefore, it is my opinion that you
possess the heart of both creatures.
♪ Voices upon voices ♪
♪ We're all the voice of the jungle ♪
♪ Lift up your voices ♪
♪ Lift up your voices
Under the Heart Tree ♪
[Koko] Ash, go?
Well, thanks to all the Zarude,
these trees are growing a lot faster
than I thought they would.
Is he about to leave?
Yeah.
[soft groan]
Now, Ash, Koko are friends.
-Yeah, forever.
-Pikachu!
-[Ash] I'll see you again.
-[exhales]
-Zarude, Koko, see ya!
-Pika, pika!
Hey, Dada.
[Koko] Dada?
Dada, Dada!
Dada?
-Why did you leave?
-Hey, Koko.
I was talking with everybody.
The Elder asked me to rejoin the troop,
and you've been invited too.
There is no reason for us
to keep you out anymore.
-[Koko] Uh, Dada, I was thinking.
-[Dada] Uh, what is it?
I really want to go out on a journey.
[Koko] I've thought about it
for a long time.
Helping humans and Pokémon bond,
that's what I really want to do.
Huh? You're kidding.
You want to abandon the jungle?
[Koko] That's not it.
I know this.
I love Pokémon and humans too,
so I want to help all of them out.
"All of them"? And just how
do you expect to do that?
You are a Pokémon. A small Zarude!
No! I'm a human and a Pokémon,
but I'm also your son!
[Koko] There are things I can do
because you raised me.
-The same things you can.
-That is such nonsense!
You'll end up running back in tears!
I'll show you, you're wrong.
[both grumbling in anger]
Do what you want.
I'm sorry, Dada.
Everyone, take care of my Dada!
-That's how you want it?
-Yeah. It's perfect.
[Dada] He's serious about it.
Once he made that clear,
it was the only thing I could do.
Hey, my son's heading out,
so do what I told you to do!
-[all] Right!
-Hey, have you seen what he's seen?
-Yeah.
-How was it?
It was… just as Koko said.
[peaceful music]
[Koko] Ash!
-Pipi!
-It's Koko!
[panting]
-[grunts]
-Koko!
Pikachu!
-Are you all right?
-Koko go too.
-[both gasp]
-You mean on a journey?
[peaceful music continues]
That was some trip and fall, huh?
-[Pikachu] Pika, pikachu!
-[gasps]
[breathes heavily]
What, Koko?
This. I didn't bring this.
[water gushes]
[uplifting music]
-That's awesome!
-Pika!
[gasps]
Dada.
Skwovet, Skwovet, Skwovet, Skwovet, Skwo…
[sobs]
[Dada] Give it all you've got,
but come back.
That bridge between humans and Pokémon,
you can help create it.
I know you can.
After all, you're my son,
and I'm proud of you.
-Koko?
-Pi?
Bye, Ash, Pikachu.
-Hey, I know we'll see you again.
-Pikachu!
See ya! Goodbye!
Pika, pika!
[uplifting music continues]
[Koko] My name is Koko.
I'm a human and a Pokémon,
and I'm my Dada's son.
[reporter] With an anonymously
sourced video of the car wreck
that occurred ten years ago,
Dr. Zed's involvement in the incident
appears to be almost certain.
Biotope will soon hold a press conference.
[Ash] Hi, Mom!
What a surprise. You're hardly
ever the one to give me a call.
Yeah, I just wanted to see your face.
Are you sick?
You didn't eat something bad?
[Delia] Do you have a fever?
-[Ash] Uh, no, I feel fine.
-[Pikachu] Pika?
-[Pokémon cheering]
-[Dada] Ripe berries!
Everyone, calm down.
There's plenty for all of you.
Hmm?
[grand music]
Well, well.
[Dada] Things have gotten better.
[squeals excitedly]
[narrator] The incredible
unpredictable world of Pokémon.
They help each other,
they help humans, living side-by-side.
There may be disagreement,
but they're family,
connected by so many different bonds.
And as many people and Pokémon
as there are in this world,
there are just as many dreams
and adventures.
Yes, filled with hope, filled with wonder,
the amazing world of Pokémon.
[heroic music]
♪ So you're kinda different ♪
♪ Feeling like a misfit ♪
♪ You were born to be
Someone who sticks out ♪
♪ It's okay, no doubt ♪
♪ I think there's a reason ♪
♪ These things don't just happen ♪
♪ You came to me ♪
♪ So we could figure this out ♪
♪ I'mma be okay, no doubt ♪
♪ If there's trouble
Just around the corner ♪
♪ Feelin' heavy weight upon my shoulders ♪
♪ When summer weather
Gets a little colder ♪
♪ I'm the color to your gray sky ♪
♪ Make it brighter, make it bolder ♪
♪ No matter what ♪
♪ You got a friend for life ♪
♪ I'll always pick your side ♪
♪ No matter what ♪
♪ I'll be there just in time ♪
♪ No ifs, ands, or buts about it ♪
♪ Count on it, no matter what ♪
♪ In our darkest hour ♪
♪ Found a superpower ♪
♪ Together, I know we can find a way out ♪
♪ Gonna be okay, no doubt ♪
♪ If there's trouble
Just around the corner ♪
♪ Need a pusher
Someone to get you further ♪
♪ Like some armor
Only make you stronger ♪
♪ I'm the good luck to your bad luck ♪
♪ Be your number one supporter ♪
♪ No matter what ♪
♪ You got a friend for life ♪
♪ I'll always pick your side ♪
♪ No matter what ♪
♪ I'll be there just in time ♪
♪ No ifs, ands, or buts about it ♪
♪ Count on it, no matter what ♪
-♪ No matter what ♪
-♪ No ifs, ands, or buts about it ♪
♪ Count on it, no matter what ♪