(Low rumbling)
(Both groan)
Kazam!
Alakazam!
Let's go, noivern.
# I stand tall
cos I know I'm a winner
# you've met your match
# you know I'm no beginner
# no beginner
# gotta catch 'em all
(guitar solo)
# I stand tall
cos I know I'm a winner
# knock me down
# I'll just get up again
# you've met your match
# yeah, I'm no beginner
# pokémon
# gotta catch 'em all
# you've met your match
# hey, I'm no beginner
# pokémon
# gotta catch 'em all
# I've got my friends beside me
# I'm keeping my eye on the ball
# with the wisdom of years
to guide me
# I'm gonna catch 'em all #
(guitar solo)
(Crash)
Huh?
Hey, pikachu?
Pikachu!
You ok?
Oh!
Whoa!
Argh!
Whoa...
(Whimpers)
Whoa-a-a-a!
(Groans)
Hey! you can talk!
Uh...
(gasps)
(Grunts)
(Machine beeps and whirrs)
Whoa!
Whoa-a-a!
(Grunts)
Oh-h-h!
Hold on!
Are you listening to me?!
(Panting)
Slow down! Man, my stomach hurts.
(Gasps for breath)
Argh!
Whoa-a-a-a!
(Yells)
Team rocket: Yummy time!
(All munching)
All: and that's delish!
(Ash screams in distance)
(All scream)
(Crash)
(All groan)
What are you doing?
Magearna? oh!
Alakazam!
Mega evolution?
(Screams)
(Gasps)
(Engine roars)
(Rockets fire)
Hey! it takes nerve to freeze it
and then ask it to understand.
I'm ash, from pallet town.
I'm a pokémon trainer.
Whoa-a-a!
(Screams)
So, they call you volcanion,
don't they?
Magearna! you really are
a one-of-a-kind pokémon.
Magearna, everything ok?
My name's ash,
and this is my pal pikachu.
It's nice to meet you too -
don't worry. If those guys show up
again, we'll chase them away.
Come on...
Everybody just calm down now.
I see.
You say that you know
that young boy trainer?
All: more? Sure!
(Bang)
oh!
(Groans)
Why me?
Kinda like a pokéball!
Hm.
Uh...
Really?
(All gasp)
Magearna!
(Both grunt)
Oh!
(Crowd whispering)
(Receding footsteps)
Huh?
Since we're stuck together now,
might as well have fun.
You fell out of the sky
with these bands, remember?
Oh!
(All gasp)
(Explosion)
(Groans)
Team rocket: Count on us, sir!
(Muffled) whoa-ho!
(All snoring)
Both: mega wave, team rocket!
Both: see?
We're mega wave team rocket!
Jessie and James: Mega wave!
(All cry out)
I see. So gengar and the others?
Both: let 'er rip!
Pikachu, use thunderbolt!
Get 'em, volcanion!
(Panting)
(All scream)
Team rocket:
We're blasting off again!
Huh?
Wow, nothing! Huh?
(Both pokémon roar)
Don't worry.
(Boom)
(Further explosions)
Huh?
So this is your real power.
Princess? whoa.
(Inaudible)
Mm-hm.
Argh!
Hey, why don't we just get on board
the thing they're riding on?
Oh, come on.
(Squeaks)
Huh? argh!
(Tweets)
Up ahead! Is that amaura?
Hang in there.
(All gasp)
(Clicks controls)
All right, pikachu, thunderbolt!
So, bad things like this,
do they happen a lot?
(All gasp)
(All squeak and growl)
(Grunts)
(Both squeak)
(Chirrups)
Everybody seems pretty afraid of us.
(Emits soothing music)
(All gasp and chuckle)
(All squeak)
(All squeak cheerfully)
(All grunt confidently)
(All squeak and bark)
(All squeak)
(Playful grunts and squeaks)
(Pained yell)
(Purrs)
(All squeak happily)
(Growls)
(Purrs)
(Pokémon all communicate happily)
Huh? volcanion, are you ok?
But what about you?
Argh!
Huh?
Wow.
Argh!
(Splash)
Huh? whoa!
Argh!
Whooooaa!
(Gasps)
So, you're always here,
watching out for everyone.
You're keeping watch, I am too.
(Pokémon squeak happily)
(Chirrups)
(Pokémon squeak)
(All exclaim)
All these pokémon, they've been hurt
by humans, haven't they?
It worked! Thanks so much, gulpin.
Even after all that's happened?
After everybody's starting
to get along so well?
Hey, I really like pokémon.
I wanna protect them too.
If you're gonna be a pokémon trainer,
then you've gotta learn how to
make pokémon feel safe.
(Pokémon chomp food)
(Both giggle)
(Squeaks and purrs)
Here, go ahead and eat.
If you like it, then why don't you
say you like it?
Bonnie: what is that?
(Pokémon all squeal)
Argh!
(All squeal)
(All gasp)
(All scream in pain)
Everyone!
(Grunts)
Huh?
(Chirrups)
(Pokémon scream in pain)
(All gasp)
(Scream louder)
Manetric!
(Both moan)
(Boom)
(Clicks button)
(All scream)
(Chirrups)
Pika!
(All sigh)
(Chirrups)
Everything's ok!
Alva, why don't we
tell them everything?
What an incredible creation
magearna really is!
(Rhythmic tick)
You don't have to remove
its soul-heart!
That's just as long as magearna
becomes a sphere.
Nikola said that... argh!
You can't! If you remove it then...
(Ticking stops)
Alva, what happened?
(Boom)
How could you lie to me?
It wasn't for the kingdom!
(All gasp)
(Sucks)
Huh?
In that case, it's retrieve
the soul-heart or bust!
(All wail)
(All grunt in agreement)
(Jessie and James groan)
Both: liftoff!
Princess, I have
something to report.
A previously unseen design diagram
by Nikola
was found in prince rali's room.
Part of the wall that defends
the azoth kingdom
can seperate and turn
into a floating fortress.
It was designed as protection
in times of an emergency.
However, an uprising broke out over
just who would claim that power.
Townsperson: what's going on?
(All growling)
Both: mega wave.
(Pokémon grunt, cry)
(Roaring)
(Screaming)
(Grunting)
Greninja, let's power up!
Champit!
(Shrieking)
Stop!
Huh?!
Meowth, what?
(Pokémon screaming)
(Sighs)
(All grunting)
Quick, pikachu, use thunderbolt!
Now use electroball!
(Grunting, groaning)
Chymia!
Volcanion, we got it!
(Fastener clicks)
Quick, greninja, water shuriken!
(Pokémon growling)
(Chiming)
(Pings)
(Crash)
(Alarm)
(All gasp)
Hold on!
You're out of water.
(Both grunting)
I've got it. Go for it, pikachu,
iron tail!
Hey, thanks.
(Straining)
It's moving.
That's right.
Know what I think?
You should head out on your own
journey with the pokémon.
(Crash)
Volcanion?
It is centre of the fortress,
so I do think it would be effective,
you said you're powerful enough
to level a mountain, right?
So why not follow the plan
and blow it up from outside?
(Crash)
huh? let's hurry.
(Crash, all gasp)
Ok, volcanion, go get 'em!
Volcanion!
Volcanion...
You've lied to us.
You said we'd all go back together.
Magearna?
The nebel plateau pokémon are safe.
Volcanion protected them.
I wish you could hear
what I'm saying.
(Sniffing)
All: huh?
(All gasp)
Huh?
Volcanion?
I said I want to protect pokémon,
right?
I would never tell a lie.
# one of a kind
# forged of steel
from a beautiful mind
# and with a mighty heart
# that drove men apart
# a forgotten plain
# where only the damaged remained
# that's where I found my destiny
# one more lost refugee
# come with me, feel my soul-heart
# if you've been seeking a new start
# let me be your guiding knight
# till the end of the night
# close my eyes, know my soul-heart
# keeping watch over the rampart
# let me be your shining star
# leading bright from afar
# from wherever you were
# to wherever you are
# feel my soul-heart now
# dry all your tears
# I've returned after so many years
# let the creatures I Cherish
flourish now
# this is my vow
# know forever, my soul-heart
# anyone seeking a new start
# let me be your guiding light
# till the end of the night #
(guitar solo)
(Piano instrumental)
Subtitles by deluxe