Watch Movies, TV Series and Live Sports
Signup Here -> WWW.ADMITME.APP
Yes, this battle of the
Pokemon league finals is
really picking up steam!
Gengar dodges it!
It's night shade!
But Blastoise withstands it!
Wait! That was an ice beam!
And gengar is frozen!
What will the trainer do now?
There goes the poke ball...
And the next Pokémon up is...
Venusaur!
It's a razor leaf!
But Blastoise's hydro pump
scores a direct hit!
Wow! Venusaur's solar beam,
and Blastoise's hydro pump...
What power!
Man! Oh, wow! Yes!
Yeah! Get 'em!
This is Ash Ketchum,
from pallet town.
Ash is almost ten years old.
When youngsters with aspirations
to become Pokémon trainers turn ten,
they can choose their first
Pokemon from professor oak.
They can choose
from Bulbasaur...
Charmander... And Squirtle.
Then, they can begin
their exciting journeys
as Pokemon trainers!
Bulbasaur... charmander...
Squirtle... Here we go.
All right, I choose you!
Ash ketchum,
are you still asleep?
You'll be late getting
to professor oak's lab!
Yeah, right,
professor oak's lab...
Mom, why didn't you wake me up?!
You said yourself
when you turned ten,
you could wake up on your own!
Hey professor oak!
I made it. I'm here!
Oh. Hello, ash.
So, professor oak,
where's my Pokémon?!
Ah, so you're the last of
the four young ones
starting out
on their journeys today.
I've thought about it a lot and
it took me a really long time,
but I finally decided.
I'm gonna choose squirtle!
I'm afraid squirtle was chosen
by a trainer who wasn't late.
I've got no one
to blame but myself.
Okay, then
I'll choose Bulbasaur!
Bulbasaur went with a trainer
who also got here on time.
All right! I mean
I really want charmander!
Being a second late for
a train, or even a Pokemon,
can be life changing.
Does that mean... I go on
my journey without a Pokémon?
Well, there is another, but...
Uh, I'll take it!
I think I should warn you
that there is a problem
with this last one...
So what? Since I was late, then
I've got a problem with me, too!
All right...
Awesome! All right then,
you're my Pokemon!
Whoa!
This Pokémon is called Pikachu.
It's so cute!
Looks like I got the best one!
You'll see...
Oh, yeah! Hi, Pikachu,
my name's Ash Ketchum!
You and I are gonna
be best friends!
It's the electric mouse Pokemon.
Pikachu can be rather shy,
but quite electrifying
when touched by humans.
Hey, I can take a little zap!
All right then.
If that's how you feel, then
this is Pikachu's poke ball.
Thanks a lot, professor!
Ash?
Remember, you were going to
head out on your journey
right after getting your Pokémon.
For goodness sake!
Here. I packed shirts,
underwear, a towel,
your toothbrush,
and a sleeping bag.
Let's go, Pikachu!
Don't Pokémon usually
go in their poké balls?
They sure do!
Come on, Pikachu, get in!
Get in your poké ball!
Oh, right.
This Pikachu hates getting
into any sort of poké ball.
Whoa, it does?
Now get in!
Wow! If you're playing catch,
then you're good friends already!
Yeah, you're right!
We're best friends already, right?
Pikachu? Are you gonna be
like this the whole way?
Is it because you don't like me?
Well, I like you a lot!
And no matter what,
I want to be your friend.
So we're all done with this.
Now. Put 'er there
you're a handful.
Hey, a Pidgey!
That's awesome! Yes!
Catching that Pidgey's gonna
be my first step
toward becoming
a Pokémon master!
Go, poké ball!
I caught it!
The way to catch 'em is
have a battle. Go, Pikachu!
Aw, come on,
aren't you gonna help me out?
Fine then. I'll do it myself.
It's a Spearow!
Let's get out of here, quick!
Knock it off!
I'm the one who threw the rock!
You should be attacking me!
Are you all right, Pikachu?
Pikachu! You're gonna be just fine!
Hang in there!
Pikachu!
No, Pikachu.
This can't be happening, right?
Pikachu! You've gotta go inside!
I know you can't stand going inside
your poké ball, but still...
In there, you'll be protected!
So come on...
Get inside, please?
Then leave the rest to me.
I'll take care of this!
All right, you!
I don't think you know who
you're dealing with!
But I'm Ash Ketchum,
from pallet town!
And I'm gonna be
the world's greatest Pokemon master!
Mess with me and
you're gonna lose!
I'm gonna catch all of
you Pokémon at once!
Pikachu, you've gotta get
inside your poké ball now!
All right, you,
hit me with your best shot!
Pikachu...
You'll stay?
Mean it?
What's that?
Pikachu? Someday we'll both
meet that Pokemon!
Pikachu, use quick attack!
Tangela, vine whip!
Tangela is unable to battle!
Thus, the winner is
ash from pallet town!
All right!
Man, you were awesome, Pikachu!
Very well. As proof of your victory
at the Celadon gym,
and by the authority of
the Pokemon league,
I now present you with
the rainbow badge.
I just got a rainbow badge!
How many badges does this make?
It's my third one!
I look forward to you
winning all eight
and entering the Pokemon league!
Thanks! I'll do my best!
Oh, hi, mom.
Well, well!
You finally decided to call!
Uh, yeah.
Do you have any idea how many
Pokémon centers
I've been leaving messages at
hoping you would be there?!
So what's this big emergency?
If I didn't say it
was a big emergency,
you wouldn't have called back,
would you?!
You're just like your father!
It wouldn't hurt to call me
once in a while, now would it?
Oh! Pikachu! Hi there!
That's all? I'm hanging up.
Now you just hold on!
I want to make sure
you're eating right!
I'm eating...
And eat your vegetables!
It's very important!
And what about laundry?
You're not wearing dirty
shirts every day, are you?
Come on, mom!
You worry too much.
You're all set.
Your Pokemon's completely healed.
Happy and in perfect health.
I was so worried!
Thank you, nurse joy.
Wanted posters?
Yes, that's team rocket.
Team rocket?
They're awful,
and they go around stealing
other people's Pokemon.
The worst of the worst.
Really? I wonder what
that's all about...
She's wondering what
we're all about.
Actions speak louder than words.
All we do is get our paws
on Primo Pokémon,
and they'll know how
magnificently we rock!
Excuse me! Nurse joy!
Please help my Pokemon!
My Vaporeon's been hurt...
Let me see.
It doesn't look good!
What happened?
That Entei
came out of nowhere...
En '7
tel. I'm sorry. Mom!
Gotta go!
Ash! But...
I thought for sure
we could catch it...
Don't worry. It'll be just fine.
Thank you so much!
Did you say Entei?
Yeah. One of
the legendary Pokemon.
They're so rare,
nobody ever sees them!
I tried to catch it, but it was
so overwhelmingly strong...
We were beat in no time,
and after, that it ran
into the forest.
It's probably still close!
I'm gonna catch it!
Let's go, Pikachu!
Some big deal!
And they're totally clueless.
I know you!
Entei's on the run!
Ain't we got fun?!
Where are you, Entei?
There it is!
Let's go, Piplup!
Hold it! I got here first!
I got here first!
Piplup, use bubble beam!
Pikachu, use thunderbolt!
Lucario, aura sphere!
Piplup, bubble beam!
All right! You let it escape!
I totally could've caught it
if you hadn't gotten in the way!
You were in the way!
No, you were!
Wanna see if you can beat me?
Good idea. I'm ash from pallet town!
Let's have a battle...
And I accept! I'm verity
and I'm from Twinleaf town!
Hey, dude! Once I Polish off this kid,
you're gonna be next!
I want a battle with you, too!
Hey! What do you mean,
Polish me off?!
I'm sorrel from Veilstone city.
I'll take a pass on the battles.
Running away?
Come on! Let's have a battle!
Here's a little warning for you.
You're going to feel
the wind soon.
I'd start looking for
shelter from the rain.
It's gonna rain?
Before you find shelter, I think
you'd better call your mommy!
Hey! Quit it! Let's do this!
Right with you!
I'll give you the first move!
Quit trying to be a gentleman.
You may wind up regretting it!
Now, Piplup, use drill peck!
All right, Pikachu,
use iron tail!
Now, quick attack!
Piplup, are you okay?
Then use hydro pump!
Dodge it...
My Piplup!
Here! Let's move!
Right...
Well, I'm here,
so where's Entei?
What's that?
Entei's coming to check us out!
We're blasting off again!
That rock!
Let's get on top of it!
Onix! Stop it! You're only
gonna hurt yourself this way!
Yelling at it is only
going to make it worse!
All right!
Ash! Be careful!
Stop it!
Use whirlpool!
I'm sorry for scaring you, onix!
I wish you'd just
calm down, please!
Onix, I'm sorry!
Piplup, your whirlpool
really saved the day!
Ash, thank you.
I've gotta tell you.
You do some dumb things,
but I'm impressed.
Forget it.
Rain!
Just like that kid said!
A charmander!
It doesn't look
like it's very happy...
Hey what are you doing out
in the rain like this?
That must be its trainer.
You're still here? Go away!
Hey wait, are you its trainer?
Who's asking?
Answer the question!
What're you worked up about?
Yeah. Originally I was.
Originally?
I ditched the weakling.
There are charmander like
that one all over the place.
But then, it just kept following me.
So I told it to wait here.
What an awful thing to say!
Ash is right!
When you've caught a Pokémon
and then you tell it to wait,
some of them will
actually wait forever!
So what's the problem?
Hold it!
Only a Pokémon's
strength matters.
If it's gonna survive,
it had better grow stronger!
What?!
Wait! Isn't it a trainer's job to help
their Pokemon grow strong?!
Nah. And what do you get
for that work anyway?
You get to become friends!
You're too soft.
The only thing friendship
does is make a Pokemon weak!
My name's cross.
I'm going to become
the greatest trainer ever.
Hey! Hold it!
Charmander!
Its flame is getting weaker!
And if Charmander's flame
goes out then...
Ash, we've got to do something!
Right!
You left it out in the rain!
What were you thinking?!
Calm down.
It isn't ash's fault!
It was in the rain after
its trainer abandoned it!
It would've stayed out
in the rain forever!
Can you help?
That's what I'm trying to do.
No Pokémon with that
much loyalty is going
to go untreated!
I know it's hard,
but please take this.
That should stabilize you.
Now all we do is wait
for it to recover.
Make sure it doesn't get cold.
I'll warm it up!
Don't worry, charmander.
You'll be fine!
How do you feel?
Are you still cold?
Things are looking a lot better.
'Cuz of you. Thanks a lot!
You're like nurse joy
at the Pokemon center!
I'm hoping to become
a Pokémon professor,
and you need medical
training for that.
Wow...
Right now,
I'm traveling all over,
gathering data
on legendary Pokemon.
So it's good that you ran
into Entei, isn't it?
Of course. It was
a priceless experience.
By the way, why did
you come here, verity?
You're a long way from home.
Well... long story.
Hey, ash, why are you here?
Who, me? I wanna be the world's
greatest Pokemon master!
Master? Do you mean
the world's best trainer?
Oh, no way!
Much more than that!
It's so cold!
Are you all right?
Sure! That was nothing!
Trying to warm me up?
Thanks, Piplup...
As a precaution, you're going back
in your poké ball.
We shouldn't let the Pokemon
spend the night out in the cold.
You're right. You, too, Piplup.
You know...
I'd like to do that.
But Pikachu really can't stand
getting into its poké ball.
Right, buddy?
No, you can't!
You'll catch a cold!
It's for the best.
Lucario...
Alright, Piplup...
Seeing the fearsome
forces of nature...
People and Pokemon are the same.
Yeah...
There's a legend, that proclaims
ho-oh gave life to Entei.
You mean it?!
You see, around
a hundred and fifty years ago,
there was
a magnificent bell tower.
And this bell tower
made it possible for humans
to actually make
contact with ho-oh.
But lightning struck the tower,
engulfing it in flames.
Suddenly, a great rain came down,
and the flames
were extinguished.
But three nameless Pokemon
succumbed to the inferno.
Amidst the destruction,
ho-oh descended and bestowed
life upon them once again,
and they were revived.
They represented
the lightning that struck,
the flame that engulfed,
and the water that
extinguished the tower.
Three natural forces made flesh.
Raikou, Entei... And Suicune.
Oh, I just love Suicune!
And this, is the Pokémon who guards
over their existences...
Ho-oh.
You've seen it?
The first day I started out
on my journey!
Are you serious?
Yeah! And as soon as I did...
This came floating down!
No way you got the rainbow wing!
What's the rainbow wing?
Few people have ever
even seen ho-oh,
and on rare occasions,
ho-oh is said to bestow a feather
on a human
it particularly likes.
Yeah? I guess that must
mean ho-oh likes me! Huh!
But, why would ho-oh do that?
There's a legend
that explains it.
It says there is
a rainbow hero who is led
by the rainbow wing
to seek out ho-oh.
A rainbow hero?
I don't know about any of this,
but it's cool...
Oh. Impressed with yourself, huh?
Oops!
Morning, Piplup. Sleep well?
Entei and its friends are gone...
Yeah.
Hey! Charmander!
You feeling better?
Let's see.
Your tail flame looks good.
Yup.
That tells me
you are back to feeling fine!
You're good to go.
Isn't that great, charmander?
Hey...
You wanna come along with us?
I'd like us to
become good friends!
Please?
Great! You really mean it?
Okay, here it goes.
I just caught a charmander!
Congratulations, ash.
You too, Pikachu.
It's a rainbow!
So beautiful!
They say that ho-oh lives
at the end of the rainbow.
The legend... Says the rainbow wing
will guide you.
So, what's over that way?
There are quite a number of
steep mountains over there.
The Raizen mountain range.
I know!
I'm gonna meet ho-oh
and have a Pokémon battle!
I'd love to meet ho-oh, too!
So would I!
Then I can determine for myself
whether the legend of
the rainbow hero, is actually true.
C'mon!
We've gotta get moving
and find ho-oh!
Right!
That's music to my ears...
Entei proved too elusive, but...
Catching ho-oh would rule!
We're so cool...
Yee-haaa!
Hah!
A bug type against a bug type!
Yeah! Caterpie, I choose you!
Caterpie, use string shot!
All right!
It's evolving...
It turned into a metapod!
Pinsir's getting away.
That's okay!
This is what counts.
Congratulations, metapod!
Really? Suicune?!
Standing right in front of me.
Man, I wish
I could've been there...
Our eyes met...
And it was like time stopped.
Yeah. We were so connected.
Wow. Must've been nice!
To meet suicune so soon after
seeing entei. Incredible luck.
I think so, too!
I wonder how
my mom would feel about it.
Oh. My mother... she's a famous
Pokemon trainer back home.
Nothing I ever do
is good enough for her.
If I'm honest, we haven't
talked since I left.
You know what I think?
I think she would
be proud of you.
He's right!
'Course she would.
Maybe...
Jigglypuff, double slap, go!
Charmander, use flamethrower!
Jigglypuff is unable to battle!
Ash is the winner!
Great work, charmander!
You evolved into Charmeleon!
That's awesome!
Nice to meet you! I'm verity.
I'm sorrel.
I hope ash hasn't been
causing you too much trouble.
Oh, well! He's rambunctious,
but he's got a big heart.
I hope you'll all
be good friends!
Mom, I wish
you'd stop worrying...
Sorrel? You find anything?
Yes, this is an excellent book.
So well researched.
Listen!
From high above,
ho-oh watched over the many works
of people and of Pokemon,
and they experienced
the aura of happiness.
And they received
energy from it.
And yet, the heart of evil
stole strength from it.
What's that?
When the rainbow wing
touches the heart of evil,
its color vanishes.
The heart of evil?
Its color vanishes?
Looks like mine's just fine.
Like your mom said, you may
be a little rambunctious,
but you sure don't
have an evil heart.
That's right! 'Cause I'm big-hearted
and rambunctious!
Knock it off!
That's not nice! Quit laughing!
Pikachu, use iron tail!
Pikachu, use thunderbolt!
Snorlax is unable to battle!
Ash is the winner!
All right!
Very nice!
So, since ash was victorious,
who is his next challenger?
What do you say, Piplup?
Lam!
It's cross!
So he's the trainer
you were talking about...
I heard a rumor,
you started working with
that useless charmander.
There's no such thing
as a useless Pokemon!
Charmeleon, let's go!
It actually evolved?
It doesn't matter.
A weakling is still a weakling!
You're not even close!
When a Pokémon works with
a trainer, it gets stronger!
All right, my strong fire-type
Pokémon, Incineroar, to arms!
Look at that...
An Incineroar.
Now come at me!
Charmeleon, use flamethrower!
That's it!
Use slash!
Yes!
That's odd...
Keep it up, charmeleon!
Seismic toss, now!
Incineroar? Let's do it.
Charmeleon, use flamethrower!
And we'll use flamethrower, too!
Charmeleon!
Of course.
When Incineroar takes
enough damage,
it gains more power.
But that means...
It took the attacks on purpose.
Charmeleon, use flamethrower!
It can't keep up!
Its newly-evolved
powers aren't ready!
Ash shouldn't be relying
on strength alone...
Use fire fangs!
Use throat chop!
Let's wrap it up.
Use cross chop!
We're not gonna lose this!
Use flamethrower!
No, ash, you can't!
Charmeleon!
Charmeleon is unable to battle!
The winner is Incineroar!
You're too soft!
You battled using cheap friendship,
and called moves your Pokémon
couldn't use, so you lost.
You're the worst trainer
I've ever seen and...
You'll never win!
Your Pokemon are
fully recovered and healthy.
Thanks very much.
Cheer up, Charmeleon's fine!
That guy...
His training is totally wrong!
I know I should have
won that thing, but...
Try as you might, you cannot
deny his convictions.
He and Incineroar
are bonded together
through their shared belief
in pure, raw strength.
Even so, it's wrong for
a guy like that to win!
Your first step needs to
be accepting that you lost.
Can't you channel
the frustration of losing,
into working hard,
so that you'll win next time?
Yeah, I hear you.
You know?
Pikachu would've won that thing.
Ash, you shouldn't say that!
What if charmeleon
had heard you?!
If winning's all
you care about...
Then you're no
different from cross.
Ash, wait!
Hold on!
Ash, come back!
What's with those two
thinking they're so smart?
Hey, I'm right,
don't you think?!
So you're saying
it's my fault, huh?!
Even Pikachu... man...
If only my first Pokémon had
been a squirtle or a Bulbasaur.
Pikachu...
Ho-oh, I thought
I was the rainbow hero.
Who needs Pikachu anyway?
I'm just fine... all by myself!
Ash ketchum,
are you still asleep?
You'll be late getting
to professor oak's class!
Yeah, right...
Mom, why didn't you wake me up?!
Professor oak!
Oh, if it isn't ash...
Am I on time?
There are four students
who came to school late,
and you were
the latest of them all.
Ash, you're late!
I overslept a little.
Where's your homework?
Aw, I forgot it!
What were you thinking?!
Ash, what is it?
Uh... it's nothing.
You're weird.
The subject of today's class
is rainbows.
Rainbows are caused by the sun's rays
moving through the atmosphere,
and when they encounter water vapor,
their light is bent and refracted,
causing a multicolored arc.
Children, have you ever...
How long are you
going to stand there?
Aren't you sick
of that view yet?
What's on your mind?
I was just wondering
what's way out there.
Let's see.
There are forests and rivers,
and mountains...
And there's the next town, too.
And past that?
More forests and rivers... And
eventually, you get to the sea.
And past that?
I'm sure it's more of the same.
The thing is...
You never know
until you go there.
For me... I wanna see what's out there
with my own eyes.
On a journey?
Sounds like fun.
You don't have to worry
about school and schedules.
You can see lots of
new things in places
you never even knew about.
And at night,
I can look at the stars
and talk things over
with friends I'm traveling with...
And as long as my buddy's
with me, I can go anywhere.
Your buddy?
What buddy?
You even have to ask?
My buddy's with me all the time!
Always...
Oh, yeah...
Ash...
You're crying.
I am? So?
So pull yourself together!
What's the matter?
Hey, wait!
Of course! We used to run
like this all the time!
But... but... I can't
remember who you are!
You were my very best friend, but...
Do it go!
Pikachu!
It was all my fault!
I'm sorry!
I just... I just...
Look, ash. Here.
Thank you very much.
Do you know how long
we've been looking for you?!
Uh... Sorry.
Do you honestly think
you're going to win every battle?
It's the times we lose
that we truly see
what a trainer's made of.
But that's just my opinion.
Charmeleon... I'm sorry.
You forgot that
Pokemon even existed?!
That had to have been
the worst dream ever!
But, you know,
it's not impossible for
Pokémon to leave us.
When I was young,
my parents were away for work
more than home.
My family had a luxray
who took care of me.
It was always with me.
But then...
There was one awful day
when I went out alone...
Luxray...
Luxray! Luxray! Luxray!
After that...
I was afraid to make friends
with Pokémon for a very long time.
The only thing that
snapped me out of it...
Was when I met lucario.
Awesome...
What was that?!
A Pokémon?
They're Primeape!
Once they're angry,
there's no calming them down!
What's going on?!
Ash, we need metapod!
But why?
If we try to fight back,
they'll only get angrier!
Got it!
Metapod! Use string shot!
Come on, Primeape,
don't be so mad!
Metapod, you were awesome!
It evolved into a butter-free!
They're after us again!
Butter-free, use sleep powder!
Butterfree, you're the best!
Now's our chance!
Well, lookee what
we have here...
A pack of primo Primeape!
And they're all
blissfully asleep.
This is a gotta
catch 'em all moment!
We're blasting off yet again!
A river!
We'll take care of this!
Now, it's your turn, Lapras!
Look! That Butterfree's
in trouble!
Right! Butter-free, I choose you!
Butterfree, now use gust, go!
Awesome!
That butter-free has
different coloring.
It's really cute.
I think that
Butterfree's a girl.
That's right.
Yeah?
There!
The source of the rainbow.
The Raizen mountains!
That's the highest mountain
in the range.
Mount tense“!
You mean that's
where we're going?
That's right.
Then I'll meet ho-oh real soon!
Pikachu. Let's go!
Ash!
You hear that?
With stereo ears.
We're ho-oh catchers!
Sneaky and snarky!
Oh wow, look at
all the butterfree!
All right...
Time for you to come out!
Isn't that the one
butterfree rescued?
Sure is!
This is the season when
butter-free gather in groups,
and head south to
their spawning grounds.
Whoa...
Look! Your Butterfree's
joining in.
That's their courtship dance.
I'd say they both agree...
Good for you, butterfree!
But, ash, you know if they
both fly off to the south...
That means goodbye
to butterfree.
But... That's...
Not what I want to happen.
I mean, Butterfree's
one of my good friends!
I don't want to say goodbye.
No way!
Yeah, I hear you.
It's your decision,
what do you say?
Hi. So what do you
think you wanna do?
Do you really wanna go with
the rest of the butter-free...
And say goodbye to all of us?
You should go with your friend!
Hurry up! If you don't go now,
you'll both get left behind!
You're both...
Really great butter-free,
so take care of each other!
You take good care
of yourselves!
Now you two be
careful out there!
Butferfree!
Take care of yourself!
They're gone...
Yeah...
But you know, I'm really
glad I met butter-free.
True, it's not here...
But we'll always be good friends.
One thing's for sure.
Trainers raise Pokemon, but
Pokemon live their own lives.
It's raikou!
It looks like something's
made the wild Pokémon upset.
It does.
It's ho-oh!
All of them gather here!
All of these wild Pokemon want
to receive power from ho-oh.
It's faint, but I'm
catching a whiff of ho-oh.
Hey, could it be this?
Wow! It's the rainbow wing!
You know of it?
Hey! I know you!
You wrote the book!
What was your name?
Why don't you just
call me Bonji?
For the past twenty years,
I've been on a quest,
searching for ho-oh as
part of my research.
Twenty years?
You see, I've pulled
data from many places,
which led me to this mountain
for ho-oh's next appearance.
Then let's all go together!
Yeah we're on our way
to see ho-oh as well.
All right. That shine is
the shine of youth.
How I missed it.
It's almost too beautiful
for me to look upon.
It's probably thanks in large part
to the rainbow wing...
That you were able to come across
entei, suicune, and raikou.
Ho-oh wants to know if there
is a young person out there
suited to be the rainbow hero.
You mean me?
That means you may
have someone guiding you.
A guide from the shadows.
Have you noticed anything?
From the shadows?
Wait, yeah there was something...
I wonder if it's still there...
I suspect it's an extremely
rare Pokemon. Marshadow.
Marshadow?
Yes. They say it's a guide
from the shadows.
When a color of
the rainbow fades,
marshadow seals it back up
and makes it right.
There's the summit...
The rainbow wing!
When a rainbow flower
blooms upon rainbow rock,
ho-oh shall appear.
Well, I can't just
stand here waiting!
Let's go, buddy!
Hey, wait for me!
Time flies, and rainbows
quickly vanish.
Yes, young ones. Hurry!
The "young ones" have to hurry!
I'm not feeling
all that young...
Hurrying's for the harried...
And all on an empty stomach.
That's where you should
place the rainbow wing.
I'll do it!
It's cross! What's going on?!
I'll take that!
The trainer who battles ho-oh
is the strongest,
and that trainer is me!
That's not how it works!
Now look! The one who gets to
battle ho-oh is the chosen one!
The rainbow hero!
You're too soft.
Remember might makes right.
And that's it.
So, what about the weak then?
They're trash!
And people who lose?
Worse than trash!
There's no way I can
afford to let you win this!
You're marshadow!
That's the Pokémon
we saw that night!
Marshadow is so cute...
That's the guide
from the shadows? Wow.
Marshadow... Its only purpose
is to observe the proceedings.
Bony?
Charmeleon! I choose you!
Use flamethrower!
Charge, charmeleon!
Charmeleon, now use slash!
Perfect!
Throat chop, go!
Use slash again!
Use flamethrower!
Charmeleon!
You evolved into a Charizard!
Go Charizard!
Aw, who cares?
Even when weak Pokemon evolve,
they're still weak!
Now use throat chop!
Charizard, use slash!
Use flamethrower!
Now use dragon rage!
Charizard! We've gotta
wrap this up quick!
Build up your power.
Let's end this one
with a big attack!
All right, fire fang!
Dodge it, quick!
Grab and drag it down!
Use seismic toss!
Incineroar, use flamethrower!
Charizard, use flamethrower!
Go!
Alright!
You did it, Charizard!
Ho-oh...
I saw ho-oh, too!
But it didn't gift me
with the rainbow wing!
And here
I did everything I could
to become
the strongest trainer of all!
Why must it be you?!
If ho-oh doesn't consider
me the strongest,
I'll just crush ho-oh!
But, cross...
I wanna get stronger, too, you know.
But still, I only got this far
with the help of my friends!
So I know it's not
only about strength!
Then what do you
even battle for?!
I do it...
Because I wanna make friends!
Not just with ho-oh!
I wanna make friends with
all kinds of Pokémon!
That's why I battle!
Not good!
Now come to me, ho-oh!
You see, the rainbow wing...
Loses its color when touched
by one with an evil heart.
What?!
Marshadow seals it back up,
and makes it right.
I'll pound you down, too!
Lycanroc, use crush claw!
Oh no!
Marshadow's
controlling lycanroc!
It wants to tear people
and Pokémon apart!
You just...
Don't you see?!
That means it never forgot
you were once its trainer!
That's just like Charizard
to be awesome!
Lucaflo!
Pikachu! Use thunderbolt!
It looks like marshadow wants
to control all of you as well!
No way!
Ho-oh will never appear
now that it's come to this!
Is everyone all right?
Yeah... I think so...
Young man, you have got to
get the rainbow wing back.
Marshadow is getting its
power from the rainbow wing!
And there's only person who
can get it back.
That is you!
Then I've gotta do it!
We'll do whatever
we can to help out!
All right!
This way!
Charizard, use flamethrower!
Use hydro pump!
No, don't!
Cross!
I've gotta do this! Go!
You bit me the day we met too,
remember?
Remember?
Lycanroc, remember!
Lycanroc.
Marshadow!
Give me the rainbow wing.
Hit it right back
with iron tail!
Keep it up!
Lucaflo!
Cross!
Pikachu!
Let's go, buddy!
Dodge it!
Pikachu, use thunderbolt!
Pikachu!
Oh, ash...
Pikachu! Get inside, please?
I know you can't stand going
inside your poké ball, but...
You'll be protected!
Now you look, I don't think
you know who you're dealing with!
I'm Ash Ketchum,
from pallet town!
And I'm gonna be the world's
greatest Pokemon master!
Mess with me
and you're gonna lose!
Pikachu, why won't you
get in your poké ball?
It's because...
I always want...
To be with you...
Pikachu, you...
Pikachu... you guys...
Where are you?
Pikachu!
We used to run like
this all the time!
Pikachu!
Pikachu...
Ash!
You're alright!
Verity! Sorrel!
When a rainbow flower
blooms upon rainbow rock,
ho-oh shall appear.
Yes! Now go, young man!
The one who is guided
by the rainbow wing...
May meet ho-oh...
And become the rainbow hero.
Ho?
Oh!
Yo, ho, ho-oh ho!
It's all downhill from here!
Looks like everybody's
healthy again!
And that's the power of ho-oh!
Pikachu?
Ho-oh! Let's have a battle!
Pikachu! I choose you!
Alright! Use thunderbolt!
Excuse me!
Oh, my! You were battling,
weren't you?
Who was it this time?
It was ho-oh.
That's nice...
What?
The atmosphere is crystal clear!
Somewhere in the world...
There's a new trainer,
soon to be the rainbow hero.
Young men and women, live on!
Just keep on living on!
And if you do,
a path will open for you!
The future is bathed in
a rainbow-colored light!
I'm going to get even stronger.
And someday we'll battle again.
Okay! And I'll give it
everything I've got!
Just don't lose
to anyone before then.
This is where
our paths must part.
I'm off to learn
about the legends of
Articuno, Zapdos, and Moltres.
I think I'm going
to head on back home.
I'd really like to see my mom!
What about you?
You know me!
I'm going my own way!
Working to become
a Pokémon master!
I hope we get to meet again
in the future.
Then we'll have a battle!
Let's go, Pikachu!
The always-fascinating
world of Pokémon,
the most diverse and
unusual creatures on the planet.
They can be found up in the sky,
under the sea, in forests,
and living in towns.
One can see Pokémon in
every corner of the world!
People and Pokémon,
forming all kinds of bonds,
and living
harmoniously in a world
made just for them...
And this young man,
Ash Ketchum from pallet town,
together with his partner Pikachu,
continues to work
toward his goal of
becoming a Pokémon master.
And as many
Pokémon as there are...
Well, our hero has just
as many dreams to follow,
and just as many
adventures to come!
Watch Movies, TV Series and Live Sports
Signup Here -> WWW.ADMITME.APP