Someone needs to stop Clearway Law.
Public shouldn't leave reviews for lawyers.
pursuing his goal of
becoming a Pokémon Master!
Pikachu?
Ew?
Axew!
Pika, Pika!
- Pika!
- Axew!
- Pika, Pika!
- Axew, Ew, Axew!
Ash: Ah...
I feel awesome!
Me too!
I'm so happy,
I could fly!
The gentle warmth of
the sun filtering through
So are you lost
or something?
Lost?
Don't know
where you are.
I mean, lost!
How can
I explain this?
When you're lost, it's
like, "Mommy, Mommy!
Where are you?"
You get it?
- Pika...
- Ash!
- Is that a Pokémon?
- Ew?
I've never seen it!
Yeah, I think
it's lost.
But how do you know?
- It told me so.
- Yeah?
- It changed!
- Ew!
Hey, it's all right.
- They're friends of mine.
- Pikachu!
Do it!
Yes...
Ew!
Wait, stop!
Do it!
- I said stop!
- Pika!
- Do it!
- Yes, I must...
Stop it, now!
Let's go!
- It just changed!
- Hold on.
You're...
I am Mewtwo.
Cilan: Mewtwo?
Are you all right?
- Yeah.
- Axew!
We're fine!
I am not speaking
to you.
I am asking
Pikachu and Axew.
- Ew?
- Pika, Pikachu!
That was dangerous.
Pika, Pika!
Thanks for getting us
out of that trouble!
I don't need
your gratitude.
I was only trying to
save the Pokémon.
Wait a minute!
Who was that Pokémon
we were with before?
Please tell me,
I've gotta know!
Hold on!
It didn't act like
that at all...
- But it attacked us.
- Right.
- Yeah, but...
- Pika, Pika!
I want you to forget
that you saw me.
Mewtwo...
You saw that,
didn't you?
With both my eyes!
(sirens wailing)
Bello, Bell, Bello!
- Ledy!
- Deerling, Deerling!
- Saws!
- Herd, Herd, Herd, Herd!
Durant,
Durant, Durant!
- Dwebble!
- Geodude, Geodude!
- Dwebble, Dweb!
- Geodude!
Surskit, Surskit!
Surskit, Surskit,
Surskit!
Gatr!
- Beau, Beautifly!
- Beautifly, Beautifly!
- Shroomish!
- Roserade!
Masquerain, Masquerain!
Starly, Starly,
Starly, Starly!
Starly, Starly, Starly!
Sab, Sable...
Sableye!
Sab, Sab, Sab, Sab, Sableye,
Sableye, Sableye!
- That's weird...
- Ee?
- Eevee...
- Watchog!
- What's for dinner?
- Watch, Watchog!
- I wanna have sandwiches!
- Watchog!
Woman: Okay, that
sounds great!
Soon as we're done, I could
go for some sandwiches myself!
- Durr!
- Great!
Man: You pick up the tab.
Gurrdurr!
Man: Not again!
Hey!
Thanks a lot, Ampharos!
So let's... get
this wrapped up!
Watchog!
All: Yay, time to eat!
- Pikachu!
- Wow, this is so good!
- Yeah!
- Pika!
- Axew, Ew, Ew!
- It's the local specialty.
- Axew...
- It's delicious!
What's going on?
Woo, Woobat, Woobat!
- Woobat.
- Swoobat, Swoobat!
Swoobat!
What's all
the hubbub?
They're saying they were attacked by
some wacko Pokémon.
I'll bet you it's
the Genesect!
You'd win that bet!
Ready or not, little
Genesect, here we come!
- Pika, Pika!
- Axew!
- Ew, Axew!
- Pika!
- Ew, Axew, Ew!
- Pika, Pika, Pika!
- Axew, Ew!
- Pika!
- Axew, Axew, Axew, Axew!
- Pika?
Sab, Sableye,
Sableye, Sableye!
Sableye, Sableye,
Sableye!
- Sableye, what?
- Pikachu!
- Sableye!
Eye, Eye, Sableye!
It's Pokémon Hills.
Something must
be wrong!
Sab, Sab, Sab!
Sableye, Sable,
Sableye.
Deerling, Deerling,
Deerling!
Something's up,
that's for sure!
- Sableye!
- Deer?
Feraligatr!
Fer!
Eric: Feraligatr!
It's Genesect...
So that's what
they look like...
Why are they chasing
away the Pokémon?
Axew!
Roserade.
This Ralts has been
badly hurt!
I'll run to
the Pokémon Center!
Thank you!
Eye!
- What are you doing?
- Pika!
We should turn back!
But why?
There's no need
to upset them here.
Ash!
This way!
Sable, Sableye,
Sable, Sable!
Eric: The workers use
this corridor.
It connects to
Pokémon Hills.
What's up with that?
Who cares?
Let's catch
them all pronto!
Off we go!
What's this?
Power.
It's the transformer
substation.
It sends electricity
to the whole city.
Look...
Sable!
(sirens wailing)
Mewtwo: I always thought
I was alone...
I rejected everything.
- Ccino!
- Nido!
- Oddish!
- Furret, Furret?
- Tang, Tang?
- Tangrowth?
Ccino,
Ccino, Ccino...
- Whim!
- Lil!
Whim!
Mewtwo: But...
I wasn't alone
after all.
- Swanna!
Swanna!
- Vul, Vulpix?
- Tangrowth.
- Ccino, Ccino.
- Teddiursa!
Oddish!
Finally, I had discovered
a place where I belong.
The Genesect
deserve as much!
Starly, Star,
Star, Star!
Starly,
Starly, Starly!
Starly, Starly,
Starly!
What?
I understand.
Starly, Starly,
Starly, Starly, Starly!
Where did that
thing come from?
- Whoa, it's huge!
- Pika!
Sable!
Sableye!
Sableye, Sableye!
Pikachu?
Pikachu!
- Hey, it's you!
- Pika!
Please... forgive me.
It's apologizing...
- Yeah, but why?
- Axew!
I know.
It can't disobey
the red Genesect!
Over here, this way!
I guess you must really
like this flower, huh?
I like this flower.
- There.
- Pika?
It bloomed in our home...
In your home?
I get it!
This has to be
the Genesect's nest!
Ew, Ew!
Of course!
They thought it would
be perfect in here!
Pika!
Eye?
Sableye!
- This is bad!
- What's wrong?
It's out of control.
If we don't
fix this...
We've got to stop
the Genesect!
And not just for
Pokémon Hills.
The entire city
is in danger!
We've gotta
do something!
- Yeah, but what?
- Pika, Pika!
Gatr...
Feraligatr!
No way!
Gatr!
Ral?
Feraligatr!
- Mewtwo!
- Pika?
- Incredible!
- Sab!
Tr, Gatr!
Oh, no!
I'm off to
the substation!
All of you, get
out of here!
You mustn't hurt the other
Pokémon in the city!
I want you to
come with me!
Don't give me orders!
Pika!
Pikachu, Iron Tail!
Chu, Pika!
Pika.
Pika?
Pi... Pi, Pi!
Pika, Pika,
Pika, Pika!
Pikachu!
Axew!
You must
listen to me!
All right.
If you refuse to
listen to reason,
I'll have no other choice
but to battle you.
Eevee?
Vee...
Stop it!
People live
in there!
Interfere and you
will be destroyed!
I guess I'm simply
wasting my breath.
What?
Quick, Pikachu,
Electro Ball!
Pika, Pika, Pika,
Pikachu, Pi!
Pikachu!
- Eye!
- Pika?
Pika!
(alarm beeping)
- Sable...
- Pika!
Sab, Sab,
Sab, Sableye!
Crustle!
We came as fast
as we could!
Golem!
- Cilan!
- Pika!
- Saws, Saws!
- Breloom!
- Loom, Loom!
- Golem!
Feraligatr!
Gatr!
Genesect: Enemy!
Destroy them!
We must destroy...
Ash: Stop it!
You don't understand!
All the Genesect want is
to have their own home!
Pika, Pikachu!
So what does
that mean?
Look!
- Enemy.
- Destroy them.
Destroy them!
Pika?
Pika!
Are you okay?
Pikachu!
Feral!
Gatr!
Breloom, Breloom!
Golem!
Ew!
Persian!
- Geodude!
- Geodude, Dude!
Golem!
Lem!
- Feral!
- Brel, Brel, Breloom!
Feraligatr!
Sableye!
Ferali...
Persian...
Sawsbuck!
Get in formation.
Destroy them!
Pika!
Saws!
Gatr!
Pika!
Sawsbuck,
Sawsbuck...
- Saw!
- Persian!
No...
Don't do it!
Please stop
it now!
Sab, Sableye!
- Bellossom!
- Deerling!
- Saws!
- Sableye!
Pika, Pi!
Pika!
- Pika!
- Genesect!
You were trying
to protect me!
I'm glad you're
all right...
Oh, no.
- Genesect, wake up!
- Pika!
Pikachu?
- Golem!
- Breloom!
Grav, Grav, Graveler!
- Saws, Saws?
- Deerling, Deerling!
Pika!
- Grav, Gravel!
- Sawsbuck!
Golem!
- It's Mewtwo!
- Pikachu!
The Genesect.
Maybe they don't
belong in this world.
The very same as it
once was for me.
I can't allow
this anymore.
If you do not stop now,
I will defeat you.
You cannot defeat us!
- It's so fast!
- Ew!
Pika?
- Sableye?
- Are you all right?
Pika?
The flowers...
- Sawsbuck.
- Feraligatr!
Sableye!
Home.
I want to go home.
- Ew.
- Pika...
Eye...
- Herd.
- Gatr.
- Bello...
- Deerling, Deerling.
Kirlia...
Now!
Now what?
- Pika?
- Ew!
I don't see an exit!
Oy.
Durant, Durant!
All: We're sorry!
Durant!
All: We're blasting
off again!
Nurse Joy: No light?
I'm going to go check
on the other Pokémon.
- Crust?
- Golem!
Crustle?
- Ew!
- Pika!
Oshawott, I choose you!
Osha!
Quick, use Hydro Pump
and put out that fire!
Oshawott!
Wott!
Osha, Osha,
Oshawott!
Gatr!
Feral!
Oshawott!
Golem, Golem!
Deerling, Deerling,
Deerling!
Pika?
- Geo, Geodude.
- Golem!
Deerling,
Deerling, Deerling!
Sableye!
Everyone...
Feral!
Deerling, Deer!
Deer!
Persian!
Feral!
- Gatr, Tr!
- Persian!
- Ew, Axew!
- Pikachu!
- Ew!
- Pika!
- Genesect!
Pika!
Pi?
- It was you three...
- Pika, Pika!
- Hang in there, please!
- Pikachu!
Mewtwo!
- Wait, stop!
- Pikachu!
The thing is, this place
isn't your home.
But there's gotta be
a home for you somewhere,
I'm sure of it!
- Ash, run!
- Hurry up!
Move away from there!
I will not!
Tell you what.
We'll help you get back
home, I promise.
Pika, Pikachu!
You see...
I gave my word.
I promised I'd take
it back home!
Mewtwo.
All Pokémon
belong somewhere.
There's a place
for every Pokémon!
- Both of you stop fighting now!
- Pika, Pika!
Don't give me orders!
- Stop...
- Pikachu!
Stop!
Enough!
How can you?
Pika, Pika...
Pikachu!
- Breloom!
- Sawsbuck, Sawsbuck!
- Golem!
- Graveler!
- Breloom, Breloom!
- Bello, Bello, Bellossom!
All of you.
All of you...
Enemies!
You stubbornly refuse
to understand!
Mewtwo!
I have only
one choice!
To go, where no
one else exists!
Beyond the limit!
Genesect: This place...
Yes.
This is the planet
we both come from.
The planet on which you
and I were created.
Created because there is
a reason for us to be here...
The inhabitants
of this planet,
people and
Pokémon alike,
live together
as friends.
Here, we are
all friends.
You and
I are friends.
All... friends...
Let's return...
to our home!
Genesect: Mewtwo!
Return... home...
- They're falling...
- Pika?
Iris: Mewtwo and Genesect?
'K ay, Charizard,
go with them too!
Char!
Dragonite!
You go with
Charizard!
Dragonite!
- Dragonite!
- Char!
- Osha, Osha!
- Sableye, Sableye!
Axew!
- Dragonite!
- Charizard!
- It's no good!
- Then we'll catch them!
But how do
we do that?
Some kind of
giant cushion?
Cushion?
Feraligatr!
That's it!
Pika, Pika!
- Ralts!
- Sableye!
- Sawsbuck, Sawsbuck!
- Breloom!
Deerling!
Pika!
- Osha!
- Gatr!
Osha, Osha!
- I'm all right.
- Osha?
Everyone on my planet...
is my friend.
We're all friends.
Yeah, that's right!
Every one of us
is a friend!
Pikachu!
Yes, we are
all friends!
Osha, Osha,
Oshawott!
Starly, Star, Star, Starly!
Starly, Starly, Starly!
Starly, Starly!
- Axew, Ew!
- Pika!
Pika?
It bloomed in
our home...
I know the place where
they can make a home!
James: Brilliant!
The sun also rises.
As surely as night
follows day.
Call me crazy, but for
some strange reason...
all: Mornings can be
an absolute blast!
Starly, Starly, Starly!
We're safe.
It looks like
the power's back on!
Audino!
Eric: You figured
it out, Ash.
Good work!
They say the Panna Lotus
has been around
for 300 million years.
That's when the
Genesect were around!
I like this place!
- That's great!
- Ew!
I like you all, too!
And we like you!
- Pika, Pika!
- Ew!
You've got enough
room in this park
to build the biggest
home in the world!
Pika, Pika!
Mewtwo: Ash...
You found a place for
the Genesect to live.
Thank you.
Well, I had
a lot of help!
I'm glad to have
met you all.
- I'm glad too!
- Pikachu!
- So am I!
- Axew!
A pleasure...
We'll always
be friends!
Yes, you're right.
I trust in
those words, Ash.
I do now, and will
forevermore!
- Ew, Ew!
- Pika!
Ax!
Take care of
yourself, Mewtwo.
- Pika, Pika!
- Maybe someday...
- We'll meet again.
- Ew, Ew!
- Count on it!
- Pikachu!
Oh we had some fun
out there now didn't we
I never knew the world had
so much for us to see
We'll have to go
and say hello another day
We're on our way
Oh we're
coming home
The only place that's
never too far
Oh
We're coming home
It's time to listen
to their call
When adventure
comes our way
We'll go back
and play
We'll go back and play
Oh we're
coming home
The only place that's
never too far
Oh
We're coming home