1
00:00:51,760 --> 00:00:54,470
Please wait, Diancie-sama!

2
00:01:18,010 --> 00:01:22,150
Diancie-sama, it is time! Princess!

3
00:01:24,690 --> 00:01:26,410
Hide-and-seek is so much fun!

4
00:01:28,830 --> 00:01:32,590
Ssh! Not right now, everyone!

5
00:01:32,590 --> 00:01:33,650
Diancie-sama!

6
00:01:36,410 --> 00:01:37,470
I got caught.

7
00:01:37,640 --> 00:01:40,030
Do not "I got caught" me!

8
00:01:40,260 --> 00:01:42,160
Princess, you said yourself that...

9
00:01:47,780 --> 00:01:49,540
Majima, are you all right?

10
00:01:52,780 --> 00:01:54,370
I am.

11
00:02:01,060 --> 00:02:02,720
This is not the time to laugh!

12
00:02:04,020 --> 00:02:05,490
Princess!

13
00:02:10,630 --> 00:02:11,530
Elder!

14
00:02:12,090 --> 00:02:12,770
Di!

15
00:02:17,800 --> 00:02:18,580
Diancie-sama,

16
00:02:19,450 --> 00:02:22,450
you have an important mission.

17
00:02:23,040 --> 00:02:25,110
You must not forget that!

18
00:02:31,020 --> 00:02:38,110
For a long time, that Sacred Diamond has provided our country with great power and tranquility.

19
00:02:39,150 --> 00:02:47,790
However, unable to fight the passage of time, its life is now ending and it is about to lose its sacred radiance.

20
00:02:48,370 --> 00:02:51,050
But it is shining so beautifully...

21
00:02:51,830 --> 00:02:54,400
Worrying too much will be bad for your health.

22
00:02:55,950 --> 00:02:57,810
Please take this seriously!

23
00:02:58,080 --> 00:02:58,750
All right, all right.

24
00:02:59,220 --> 00:03:01,410
Answering <i>once</i> will suffice!

25
00:03:02,070 --> 00:03:02,320
All right.

26
00:03:03,370 --> 00:03:09,690
If the Sacred Diamond is lost, our country will go down the path of destruction.

27
00:03:10,140 --> 00:03:11,480
You are exaggerating.

28
00:03:11,790 --> 00:03:13,150
I am not!

29
00:03:13,800 --> 00:03:19,150
Diancie-sama, you are the only one who can give birth to a Sacred Diamond!

30
00:03:20,690 --> 00:03:25,030
Today is the day you will show me your powers.

31
00:03:25,880 --> 00:03:28,850
I got it. I will do it. I will do it, all right?

32
00:03:30,830 --> 00:03:32,310
...Not that I think I can do it.

33
00:03:32,310 --> 00:03:33,480
Princess!

34
00:03:34,760 --> 00:03:35,780
Yes.

35
00:03:57,310 --> 00:03:58,710
Keep it up!

36
00:04:23,190 --> 00:04:25,800
As I thought, I cannot do it.

37
00:04:25,800 --> 00:04:27,710
I am sure you will be able to!

38
00:04:28,050 --> 00:04:31,120
That is what you were born to do, after all!

39
00:04:32,050 --> 00:04:35,290
I am grateful that you have raised me.

40
00:04:35,900 --> 00:04:37,960
But I...

41
00:04:38,690 --> 00:04:39,840
Xerneas...

42
00:04:41,090 --> 00:04:42,270
Go meet it.

43
00:04:42,820 --> 00:04:43,940
"Xerneas"?

44
00:04:44,360 --> 00:04:45,090
That's right.

45
00:04:46,310 --> 00:04:49,090
Years ago, while I was on a journey,

46
00:04:49,860 --> 00:04:54,830
the terrifying Great Destruction occurred in a place called the "Alearth Woods".

47
00:05:28,340 --> 00:05:30,400
My life is getting absorbed...

48
00:05:31,140 --> 00:05:32,430
It's over...

49
00:06:07,640 --> 00:06:08,280
This is...

50
00:06:09,040 --> 00:06:10,030
Fairy Aura.

51
00:06:10,840 --> 00:06:11,100
Oh.

52
00:06:19,300 --> 00:06:23,380
It was thanks to Xerneas that I survived.

53
00:06:31,880 --> 00:06:33,000
If I meet this... uh...

54
00:06:33,580 --> 00:06:34,820
Xerneas.

55
00:06:35,390 --> 00:06:40,700
...meet this "Xerneas" and receive the Fairy Aura that will let me unleash my true power,

56
00:06:41,250 --> 00:06:44,280
will I really be able to create a Sacred Diamond?

57
00:06:44,780 --> 00:06:45,420
You will!

58
00:06:46,050 --> 00:06:47,960
Believe in the Fairy Aura!

59
00:06:57,890 --> 00:06:58,990
Then I will go.

60
00:06:59,420 --> 00:07:01,850
I have long wanted to see the outside world.

61
00:07:02,080 --> 00:07:04,620
Please take this more seriously!

62
00:07:05,210 --> 00:07:05,870
All right, all right!

63
00:07:06,410 --> 00:07:07,140
You answer...

64
00:07:08,690 --> 00:07:09,640
Once, right?

65
00:07:10,190 --> 00:07:10,430
All right!

66
00:07:32,500 --> 00:07:35,800
Pocket Monsters, or "Pokémon" for short:

67
00:07:37,300 --> 00:07:40,330
The strange, mysterious lifeforms on this planet.

68
00:07:52,840 --> 00:07:53,470
In the forests...

69
00:08:03,120 --> 00:08:03,820
In the skies...

70
00:08:10,340 --> 00:08:10,980
In the seas...

71
00:08:16,670 --> 00:08:20,410
Wherever you are in the world, you can be sure to see them.

72
00:08:24,780 --> 00:08:25,390
Also...

73
00:08:25,870 --> 00:08:31,300
Humans and Pokémon have bonded in many different ways as they've lived together in this world.

74
00:09:09,900 --> 00:09:12,840
This boy, Satoshi of Masara Town,

75
00:09:14,780 --> 00:09:18,410
battles and gets Pokémon alongside his partner Pikachu.

76
00:09:23,260 --> 00:09:26,930
As a Pokémon Trainer, he continues his travels in the pursuit of new knowledge.

77
00:09:30,060 --> 00:09:32,110
There are as many dreams as there are Pokémon.

78
00:09:32,920 --> 00:09:36,540
There are as many adventures to be had as there are Pokémon.

79
00:12:24,730 --> 00:12:26,570
Mega Evolutions sure are powerful.

80
00:12:27,880 --> 00:12:28,190
Heheh.

81
00:12:33,230 --> 00:12:35,730
Let's keep the Mega Absol lady!

82
00:12:35,920 --> 00:12:36,180
Huh?

83
00:12:36,570 --> 00:12:38,080
Have my big brother, s'il-vous-plaît!

84
00:12:39,190 --> 00:12:43,150
Hey, Eureka! Your small act of "kindness" is a big bother to me!

85
00:12:44,190 --> 00:12:45,500
Think about it!

86
00:12:56,910 --> 00:12:57,470
Pikachu!

87
00:13:08,450 --> 00:13:09,120
Riot.

88
00:13:09,870 --> 00:13:11,560
I won't let you get in my way.

89
00:13:11,760 --> 00:13:13,270
I was about to say the same to you.

90
00:13:13,710 --> 00:13:15,900
Well then, I shall excuse myself.

91
00:13:16,830 --> 00:13:17,560
No you won't!

92
00:13:26,660 --> 00:13:28,340
Stop this! Two against one, that's not fair!

93
00:13:29,490 --> 00:13:31,080
And you call yourselves Pokémon Trainers?

94
00:13:33,120 --> 00:13:34,180
Don't interfere.

95
00:13:34,750 --> 00:13:37,630
I have use for the diamonds that little one can create.

96
00:13:38,820 --> 00:13:40,430
You speak too much, Marilyn.

97
00:13:41,060 --> 00:13:43,920
You're not a classy bandit, you're a <i>chatty</i> bandit.

98
00:13:44,830 --> 00:13:45,550
Bandit?

99
00:13:46,040 --> 00:13:46,990
Run while you can.

100
00:13:50,420 --> 00:13:52,030
Pikachu, Thunderbolt!

101
00:13:59,100 --> 00:13:59,600
Over here!

102
00:14:00,040 --> 00:14:00,480
What the?

103
00:14:01,280 --> 00:14:02,260
What's going on?

104
00:14:02,590 --> 00:14:03,730
Should we call Junsa-san?

105
00:14:14,170 --> 00:14:15,850
We should be fine now.

106
00:14:16,510 --> 00:14:20,250
Everyone, you have my gratitude for saving me.

107
00:14:20,250 --> 00:14:21,010
It talked.

108
00:14:21,340 --> 00:14:21,900
You're right!

109
00:14:22,080 --> 00:14:23,040
It is telepathy.

110
00:14:23,360 --> 00:14:24,380
How cute.

111
00:14:24,940 --> 00:14:25,860
I'm Satoshi.

112
00:14:26,320 --> 00:14:26,960
Satoshi.

113
00:14:27,300 --> 00:14:28,810
This is my partner, Pikachu.

114
00:14:30,380 --> 00:14:31,300
Pikachu.

115
00:14:31,610 --> 00:14:32,590
I'm Serena.

116
00:14:32,990 --> 00:14:33,530
Serena.

117
00:14:33,980 --> 00:14:35,010
I'm Eureka.

118
00:14:35,420 --> 00:14:36,130
Eureka.

119
00:14:36,660 --> 00:14:37,840
I am Citron.

120
00:14:38,350 --> 00:14:39,060
Citron.

121
00:14:39,900 --> 00:14:41,690
This is a Pokémon, right?

122
00:14:43,250 --> 00:14:43,980
Let's see...

123
00:14:44,750 --> 00:14:46,090
So it's called "Diancie".

124
00:14:46,540 --> 00:14:50,340
That bandit earlier mentioned it too, but it looks like it has the ability to create diamonds.

125
00:14:50,340 --> 00:14:51,280
Diamonds?

126
00:14:51,540 --> 00:14:53,240
So that is why they were after it.

127
00:14:55,460 --> 00:14:57,410
We came here in pursuit of Pikachu...

128
00:14:57,650 --> 00:14:59,750
...and found an incredible Pokémon in the process.

129
00:15:00,030 --> 00:15:02,120
If we get that Pokémon...

130
00:15:04,610 --> 00:15:06,020
Those people were bandits.

131
00:15:06,570 --> 00:15:08,900
What might such "bandits" be?

132
00:15:09,390 --> 00:15:12,440
Bandits are people who take what's precious to others without asking.

133
00:15:13,960 --> 00:15:15,060
They're bad people!

134
00:15:16,830 --> 00:15:19,930
So "bandits" are deplorable folks, then.

135
00:15:21,310 --> 00:15:23,140
I have learned a lot.

136
00:15:38,340 --> 00:15:38,910
Diancie...

137
00:15:39,530 --> 00:15:40,670
These are great.

138
00:15:42,290 --> 00:15:43,680
Thank you very much.

139
00:15:49,480 --> 00:15:50,420
It is delicious.

140
00:15:50,940 --> 00:15:52,750
Just help yourself; there's no need for self-restraint!

141
00:15:55,070 --> 00:15:57,210
It appears you have considerable appetite.

142
00:15:57,480 --> 00:15:58,000
Yeah.

143
00:16:00,040 --> 00:16:01,420
Eat much, sleep much.

144
00:16:01,900 --> 00:16:03,520
Those are the basics of good health.

145
00:16:06,640 --> 00:16:08,360
I'm going to grab seconds.

146
00:16:08,990 --> 00:16:10,000
Diancie, wanna come along?

147
00:16:10,280 --> 00:16:11,140
Oh... Yes.

148
00:16:12,120 --> 00:16:15,340
Well then, I shall be going along with you.

149
00:16:19,500 --> 00:16:19,950
This way.

150
00:16:23,660 --> 00:16:25,580
Diancie is so polite.

151
00:16:26,040 --> 00:16:27,690
She acts just like a princess, don't you think?

152
00:16:28,440 --> 00:16:29,380
You can say that again.

153
00:16:30,540 --> 00:16:32,690
There are so many different things.

154
00:16:33,010 --> 00:16:35,470
Yeah. Let's just grab a whole bunch!

155
00:16:36,370 --> 00:16:38,400
Same here. Let's <i>grab</i>...

156
00:16:38,810 --> 00:16:39,630
Grab...

157
00:16:39,820 --> 00:16:41,140
Grab as we please!

158
00:16:41,680 --> 00:16:48,270
Diamonds are minerals formed over hundreds of millions of years and an extremely rare substance.

159
00:16:48,750 --> 00:16:53,240
They're very sturdy. They say a diamond's shine lasts forever.

160
00:16:53,700 --> 00:16:55,000
That's why they're so valuable.

161
00:17:07,100 --> 00:17:08,290
This one looks delicious.

162
00:17:14,860 --> 00:17:15,880
It's the Rocket Gang!

163
00:17:20,890 --> 00:17:23,940
To think it'd be this easy to get our hands on Diancie.

164
00:17:25,640 --> 00:17:26,620
What luck.

165
00:17:28,190 --> 00:17:29,980
You are also bandits, correct?

166
00:17:30,350 --> 00:17:32,140
We're the Rocket Gang!

167
00:17:32,440 --> 00:17:36,820
Bandits are those who would take what is precious to others without asking, are they not?

168
00:17:37,200 --> 00:17:38,650
Such is an evil act.

169
00:17:38,960 --> 00:17:41,240
I have learned about this.

170
00:17:41,760 --> 00:17:44,640
And you'll be learning a <i>lot</i> more from here on.

171
00:17:44,640 --> 00:17:46,800
All about the harsh realities of the world.

172
00:17:46,800 --> 00:17:47,170
Yeah.

173
00:17:47,780 --> 00:17:49,950
I am immensely grateful for that.

174
00:17:50,270 --> 00:17:52,490
However, I must be going back.

175
00:17:53,080 --> 00:17:54,820
Well then, good day to you.

176
00:17:55,500 --> 00:17:56,840
Good day to you... Uh...

177
00:17:57,380 --> 00:17:59,230
W-Wait, hold up!

178
00:17:59,570 --> 00:18:00,410
Woah there.

179
00:18:00,660 --> 00:18:02,180
We can't let you leave.

180
00:18:02,450 --> 00:18:05,180
We've got some work you gotta do for us.

181
00:18:05,620 --> 00:18:08,300
I have never worked.

182
00:18:09,420 --> 00:18:11,600
You can create diamonds, right?

183
00:18:11,890 --> 00:18:13,700
We've done our research, you know?

184
00:18:13,700 --> 00:18:15,530
Make us some diamonds.

185
00:18:15,530 --> 00:18:17,110
Some really sparkly ones.

186
00:18:17,860 --> 00:18:20,080
So that was the kind of work that you wanted done.

187
00:18:20,720 --> 00:18:22,690
I could do that much for you.

188
00:18:23,010 --> 00:18:23,410
Huh?

189
00:18:24,040 --> 00:18:25,050
You will?

190
00:18:25,050 --> 00:18:25,900
That was fast.

191
00:18:25,900 --> 00:18:28,250
How nice, you're surprisingly obedient.

192
00:18:28,250 --> 00:18:30,380
However, please do not be disappointed.

193
00:18:30,510 --> 00:18:34,200
Of course we won't. Come on, give us some diamonds!

194
00:18:34,200 --> 00:18:35,550
Carats, carats!

195
00:18:37,170 --> 00:18:37,490
Well then...

196
00:18:48,960 --> 00:18:50,520
She did it!

197
00:18:50,520 --> 00:18:51,480
Amazing!

198
00:18:52,880 --> 00:18:55,580
With just this single one, we can eat as much Salisbury steak as we want for the rest of our lives!

199
00:18:55,580 --> 00:18:57,580
We can eat as much tofu fritters as we want, too!

200
00:18:58,030 --> 00:19:00,410
We can even eat as much ice cream as we want for dessert...

201
00:19:00,600 --> 00:19:02,040
Give us more!

202
00:19:02,420 --> 00:19:03,310
Very well.

203
00:19:06,980 --> 00:19:08,620
So pretty!

204
00:19:08,620 --> 00:19:10,120
There's a second one!

205
00:19:10,120 --> 00:19:11,970
With this, we can build a luxurious house!

206
00:19:11,970 --> 00:19:14,040
And we can build a vacation home with a hot spring!

207
00:19:14,040 --> 00:19:16,300
We can even buy a resort condo!

208
00:19:17,380 --> 00:19:19,260
Come on, come on, more! Give us more!

209
00:19:25,100 --> 00:19:27,220
Here they come!

210
00:19:33,470 --> 00:19:35,610
It's a diamond bath!

211
00:19:35,880 --> 00:19:38,270
It might just cleanse my body... ow, ow!

212
00:19:41,220 --> 00:19:43,470
They hurt, but they feel so good!

213
00:20:05,600 --> 00:20:06,610
Step back!

214
00:20:06,800 --> 00:20:07,200
Huh?

215
00:20:16,090 --> 00:20:17,290
Over here. Hurry.

216
00:20:19,240 --> 00:20:20,450
Look, she's over there!

217
00:20:21,300 --> 00:20:22,200
Diancie!

218
00:20:25,730 --> 00:20:26,320
Are you okay?

219
00:20:27,500 --> 00:20:28,510
You haven't been hurt or anything, have you?

220
00:20:28,830 --> 00:20:30,460
Nothing has happened to me.

221
00:20:30,940 --> 00:20:34,270
As soon as I made some diamonds, I was allowed to go back.

222
00:20:35,550 --> 00:20:38,800
I knew it, the Rocket Gang wanted diamonds as well.

223
00:20:39,930 --> 00:20:41,650
It's good that you're safe, Diancie.

224
00:20:43,040 --> 00:20:47,950
But right about now, I suppose those bandits will be disappointed.

225
00:20:48,240 --> 00:20:48,720
Huh?

226
00:21:04,820 --> 00:21:06,740
Eh? Huh? Ah!

227
00:21:07,040 --> 00:21:07,570
Nyah!?

228
00:21:07,570 --> 00:21:09,250
Huh? Wha? What, what, what!?

229
00:21:09,450 --> 00:21:11,250
The diamonds are...!

230
00:21:11,920 --> 00:21:13,020
No! Eh?

231
00:21:14,130 --> 00:21:15,400
They disappeared!

232
00:21:21,040 --> 00:21:25,810
I am still unable to exert my true power.

233
00:21:26,190 --> 00:21:27,920
The diamonds you make disappear?

234
00:21:28,440 --> 00:21:28,690
Yes.

235
00:21:29,280 --> 00:21:31,530
That is why I am searching for Xerneas.

236
00:21:32,000 --> 00:21:32,830
"Xerneas"?

237
00:21:33,360 --> 00:21:34,810
It is a legendary Pokémon.

238
00:21:35,260 --> 00:21:38,330
If I remember right, it is said to be able to grant life.

239
00:21:38,740 --> 00:21:39,520
Wow.

240
00:21:40,270 --> 00:21:42,030
It was explained to me that Xerneas' Fairy Aura...

241
00:21:42,680 --> 00:21:46,520
...would bring out my true power.

242
00:21:47,140 --> 00:21:49,080
It is because you are also a Fairy-type, right?

243
00:21:49,840 --> 00:21:50,840
Xerneas, huh?

244
00:21:51,620 --> 00:21:52,930
I want to see it too!

245
00:21:52,930 --> 00:21:53,750
Me too!

246
00:21:54,010 --> 00:21:55,660
Here, here! Eureka too!

247
00:21:56,120 --> 00:21:57,140
Of course, I do too.

248
00:21:57,650 --> 00:22:00,120
Diancie, could we go with you?

249
00:22:01,520 --> 00:22:03,390
That would delight me as well.

250
00:22:05,440 --> 00:22:09,300
Satoshi, everyone, I shall permit you to accompany me on my journey.

251
00:22:09,720 --> 00:22:12,190
Huh? Permit?

252
00:22:12,750 --> 00:22:14,830
She really <i>is</i> a princess.

253
00:22:14,830 --> 00:22:17,020
Huh? Diancie's a princess?

254
00:22:58,360 --> 00:23:02,570
If Diancie returns underground, we won't be able to find it again.

255
00:23:06,280 --> 00:23:07,710
Marilyn and Riot...

256
00:23:08,290 --> 00:23:09,780
They're desperate for it too.

257
00:23:10,820 --> 00:23:11,860
Gotta watch out for them.

258
00:23:13,420 --> 00:23:13,830
Hm?

259
00:23:14,350 --> 00:23:15,240
These people...

260
00:23:17,700 --> 00:23:19,370
Hah! No need to bother with them!

261
00:23:25,940 --> 00:23:27,170
Diancie's safe.

262
00:23:27,850 --> 00:23:29,250
Good work, Miriss.

263
00:23:29,940 --> 00:23:31,330
How about some chocolate?

264
00:23:31,740 --> 00:23:34,000
Dad, aren't you eating too much of those?

265
00:23:34,000 --> 00:23:36,680
They just came out with a new mint chocolate.

266
00:23:37,360 --> 00:23:39,930
I ordered these all the way from the Houen region.

267
00:23:40,680 --> 00:23:43,980
Besides, the cocoa that's used in chocolate is good for you.

268
00:23:44,400 --> 00:23:45,620
Cocoa contains...

269
00:23:45,620 --> 00:23:48,720
I'm worried about your health, Dad!

270
00:23:48,970 --> 00:23:50,510
I know that.

271
00:23:58,240 --> 00:23:58,600
Geez.

272
00:24:05,580 --> 00:24:06,170
Diancie...

273
00:24:06,800 --> 00:24:09,490
Is Xerneas really going to be in this direction?

274
00:24:11,060 --> 00:24:12,810
I do not lie.

275
00:24:13,260 --> 00:24:16,390
I was told that lying is something that should not be done.

276
00:24:17,160 --> 00:24:19,610
Then how do you know that it's this way?

277
00:24:21,090 --> 00:24:27,320
I am able to feel the traces of Fairy Aura that Xerneas left behind.

278
00:24:38,700 --> 00:24:40,840
Xerneas will certainly be there.

279
00:24:41,960 --> 00:24:42,800
It will...

280
00:25:25,140 --> 00:25:27,150
I suppose it is futile.

281
00:25:33,740 --> 00:25:38,270
If you make a wish before a shooting star disappears, it's said that it will come true.

282
00:25:39,450 --> 00:25:40,480
A wish?

283
00:25:40,910 --> 00:25:41,170
Yeah.

284
00:25:42,810 --> 00:25:44,500
I shall try.

285
00:25:45,580 --> 00:25:46,360
I'll join you.

286
00:25:50,600 --> 00:25:51,100
Now!

287
00:25:52,780 --> 00:25:58,280
I wish that Diancie will be able to make diamonds.

288
00:26:37,700 --> 00:26:39,640
It is a group of Buoysel and Floasel!

289
00:26:40,190 --> 00:26:41,930
Ya-ho-hoi!

290
00:26:42,800 --> 00:26:45,130
Everyone, you all swim wonderfully.

291
00:27:04,290 --> 00:27:08,770
This is the most fun I have had since I began my journey.

292
00:27:09,310 --> 00:27:11,820
That's because it's fun being with friends!

293
00:27:13,370 --> 00:27:15,780
What are "friends"?

294
00:27:16,180 --> 00:27:17,200
Friends are...

295
00:27:17,720 --> 00:27:19,100
They're friends. Right?

296
00:27:19,870 --> 00:27:23,700
They're fun companions you play and talk together with.

297
00:27:23,920 --> 00:27:25,640
You help them, they help you.

298
00:27:26,430 --> 00:27:28,120
It refers to an equal relationship.

299
00:27:28,810 --> 00:27:30,020
"Friends"...

300
00:27:31,380 --> 00:27:33,380
We're friends now, aren't we?

301
00:27:40,920 --> 00:27:46,310
Well then, I permit you all to be my friends.

302
00:27:47,790 --> 00:27:50,030
Diancie really is princess-y.

303
00:27:52,770 --> 00:27:54,480
But that's wonderful, Diancie.

304
00:27:55,240 --> 00:27:57,620
Friends... I am so happy.

305
00:28:03,770 --> 00:28:04,420
Is this...?

306
00:28:05,050 --> 00:28:06,030
It's a diamond!

307
00:28:06,030 --> 00:28:07,260
That is incredible!

308
00:28:07,530 --> 00:28:08,540
So pretty!

309
00:28:08,850 --> 00:28:11,460
However, it will disappear before too long.

310
00:28:11,900 --> 00:28:12,520
It will?

311
00:28:13,370 --> 00:28:15,390
Even if it does disappear, could you let me have it?

312
00:28:16,020 --> 00:28:18,730
I will give it to you, Eureka.

313
00:28:18,970 --> 00:28:20,700
Yay! All right!

314
00:28:29,020 --> 00:28:30,890
Thank you, Diancie.

315
00:28:41,500 --> 00:28:44,260
Whose castle might this be?

316
00:28:44,900 --> 00:28:46,290
Hm? It's not a castle.

317
00:28:46,690 --> 00:28:47,880
It's a shopping mall.

318
00:28:48,280 --> 00:28:49,760
It's a place to go shopping.

319
00:28:50,940 --> 00:28:53,210
What is "shopping"?

320
00:28:53,720 --> 00:28:54,980
You've never done it?

321
00:28:55,360 --> 00:28:55,720
No.

322
00:28:56,190 --> 00:28:58,200
How about giving it a try then, Diancie?

323
00:28:58,880 --> 00:29:01,420
Forget about Xerneas for just a little bit.

324
00:29:03,170 --> 00:29:04,040
Very well then.

325
00:29:04,720 --> 00:29:06,320
I shall permit shopping.

326
00:29:06,910 --> 00:29:08,440
There she goes, giving us permission again.

327
00:29:10,760 --> 00:29:11,810
Diancie, let's go!

328
00:29:12,770 --> 00:29:13,770
Wait up!

329
00:29:14,160 --> 00:29:15,230
There they go.

330
00:29:15,230 --> 00:29:16,970
Girls will be girls.

331
00:29:22,270 --> 00:29:23,570
How cute!

332
00:29:25,450 --> 00:29:26,600
What <i>is</i> this?

333
00:29:26,930 --> 00:29:28,020
There's a hat, too!

334
00:29:28,020 --> 00:29:28,740
Shoes as well.

335
00:29:29,390 --> 00:29:30,200
Ta-da!

336
00:29:59,740 --> 00:30:01,620
You really look like a princess!

337
00:30:02,240 --> 00:30:02,600
Right?

338
00:30:03,000 --> 00:30:03,520
Yeah.

339
00:30:08,460 --> 00:30:09,070
Diancie?

340
00:30:09,570 --> 00:30:10,420
What's wrong?

341
00:30:16,280 --> 00:30:17,960
Hey! Bro!

342
00:30:18,660 --> 00:30:20,160
Are you done shopping?

343
00:30:20,800 --> 00:30:21,760
We're still in the middle of it.

344
00:30:22,100 --> 00:30:23,630
What? You're still at it?

345
00:30:23,850 --> 00:30:25,930
We just wanna look at a few more before we decide.

346
00:30:33,580 --> 00:30:34,280
Diancie?

347
00:30:36,800 --> 00:30:38,490
I have been caught.

348
00:30:38,780 --> 00:30:39,070
Eh?

349
00:30:56,570 --> 00:30:56,990
Here.

350
00:30:57,330 --> 00:30:58,410
Nice recovery.

351
00:31:10,760 --> 00:31:11,290
Where'd they go?

352
00:31:13,540 --> 00:31:14,720
Oh, there they are!

353
00:31:18,490 --> 00:31:20,380
What are those Pokémon?

354
00:31:20,810 --> 00:31:21,920
Do they work with the bandits?

355
00:31:23,340 --> 00:31:24,110
We have to help!

356
00:31:24,600 --> 00:31:25,970
Leave it to me!

357
00:31:26,410 --> 00:31:28,530
It is time for science to open up the future!

358
00:31:29,000 --> 00:31:30,450
Citronic Gear, on!

359
00:31:40,030 --> 00:31:42,350
It is the Super Stretch Ladder DX!

360
00:31:42,690 --> 00:31:44,140
Satoshi, get on!

361
00:31:44,140 --> 00:31:44,810
All right!

362
00:31:46,570 --> 00:31:47,210
Here we go!

363
00:31:47,470 --> 00:31:47,960
Yeah!

364
00:31:57,470 --> 00:32:00,390
Technology is incredible!

365
00:32:08,590 --> 00:32:09,440
Okay!

366
00:32:09,440 --> 00:32:11,230
Luchabull, I choose you!

367
00:32:23,530 --> 00:32:24,460
Diancie!

368
00:32:26,130 --> 00:32:26,880
Jump!

369
00:32:47,230 --> 00:32:48,400
What were those Pokémon?

370
00:32:48,850 --> 00:32:50,770
Those were the Jewel Pokémon Melecie.

371
00:32:51,620 --> 00:32:54,200
It's rare for them to show up in the middle of a city like this.

372
00:32:54,600 --> 00:32:56,860
They have finally found me.

373
00:32:57,210 --> 00:32:59,210
Then they really were the bandits' underlings?

374
00:32:59,500 --> 00:33:00,320
Well...

375
00:33:02,460 --> 00:33:03,540
Diancie...

376
00:33:04,160 --> 00:33:06,460
Did you have fun shopping for the first time?

377
00:33:07,440 --> 00:33:08,680
You're the bandit from back then!

378
00:33:10,610 --> 00:33:12,800
Come on, get over here.

379
00:33:13,100 --> 00:33:14,220
I will not!

380
00:33:14,410 --> 00:33:15,650
Then I have no choice.

381
00:33:16,340 --> 00:33:16,990
Mafoxy!

382
00:33:19,450 --> 00:33:21,560
Leave this to me! You guys get out of here!

383
00:33:23,740 --> 00:33:24,280
Go!

384
00:33:25,210 --> 00:33:26,060
Where do you think you're going?

385
00:33:26,560 --> 00:33:27,840
Keromatsu, I choose you!

386
00:33:31,610 --> 00:33:34,450
Keromatsu, Water Pulse! Pikachu, Thunderbolt!

387
00:33:34,450 --> 00:33:36,130
Get out of my way! Flamethrower!

388
00:33:46,560 --> 00:33:49,200
Those are some good Pokémon. I can't bring myself to dislike them.

389
00:34:02,720 --> 00:34:04,310
Please, help us out.

390
00:34:06,320 --> 00:34:07,040
Everyone, get on!

391
00:34:08,660 --> 00:34:09,730
Sihorn, go!

392
00:34:25,460 --> 00:34:26,540
Go!

393
00:34:32,890 --> 00:34:34,280
Thank you, Sihorn.

394
00:34:35,070 --> 00:34:35,970
You were a big help.

395
00:34:37,060 --> 00:34:38,010
Bye bye!

396
00:34:42,500 --> 00:34:44,340
Will Satoshi be all right?

397
00:34:44,670 --> 00:34:46,380
Satoshi's going to be fine, count on it!

398
00:34:46,380 --> 00:34:46,690
Yeah.

399
00:34:47,340 --> 00:34:50,680
This is entirely because of me. I am causing everybody trouble.

400
00:34:53,080 --> 00:34:55,480
Of course we help our friends when they are in trouble, that is a given!

401
00:34:55,710 --> 00:34:57,820
I was going to say that!

402
00:34:59,200 --> 00:35:00,010
Everyone...

403
00:35:07,610 --> 00:35:08,690
What was <i>that?</i>

404
00:35:09,400 --> 00:35:10,080
Diancie!

405
00:35:11,700 --> 00:35:13,370
I am fine.

406
00:35:14,800 --> 00:35:15,240
Diancie!

407
00:35:15,240 --> 00:35:15,470
No!
Diancie!

408
00:35:15,470 --> 00:35:15,720
No!

409
00:35:23,690 --> 00:35:25,580
Dedenne, Nuzzle!

410
00:35:30,580 --> 00:35:31,140
Now!

411
00:35:40,890 --> 00:35:43,300
I'm pleased! I'm truly pleased!

412
00:35:43,820 --> 00:35:48,450
To think you would oppose my Gekkouga using such a primitive method.

413
00:35:49,410 --> 00:35:51,670
I've taken a liking to your bunch.

414
00:35:51,900 --> 00:35:53,890
Again! It's one after another!

415
00:35:53,890 --> 00:35:55,090
You're pesky!

416
00:35:56,380 --> 00:35:58,380
Gekkouga, Double Team!

417
00:36:02,490 --> 00:36:04,050
Harimaron, help us out!

418
00:36:09,040 --> 00:36:10,030
Fokko, you too!

419
00:36:12,930 --> 00:36:14,460
Harimaron, Pin Missile!

420
00:36:14,780 --> 00:36:16,170
Fokko, Flamethrower!

421
00:36:19,880 --> 00:36:20,860
Water Shuriken!

422
00:36:29,800 --> 00:36:30,420
Satoshi!

423
00:36:30,640 --> 00:36:31,370
I am glad you are safe!

424
00:36:34,650 --> 00:36:35,790
Run away, Diancie!

425
00:36:36,220 --> 00:36:36,610
I will!

426
00:36:45,680 --> 00:36:46,550
Princess!

427
00:36:49,460 --> 00:36:50,040
Majima!

428
00:36:50,260 --> 00:36:53,000
Diancie-sama, we will protect you.

429
00:36:53,950 --> 00:36:54,850
You...!

430
00:36:56,030 --> 00:36:57,220
The Melecie from before!

431
00:36:59,340 --> 00:37:00,050
Don't get in my way!

432
00:37:00,520 --> 00:37:00,820
Attack!

433
00:37:06,220 --> 00:37:07,000
Princess!

434
00:37:15,040 --> 00:37:16,780
A Sacred Diamond!

435
00:37:27,340 --> 00:37:28,170
Diancie!

436
00:37:33,320 --> 00:37:34,490
Princess!

437
00:37:36,590 --> 00:37:38,840
Brigarron, use Pin Missile once more!

438
00:37:44,800 --> 00:37:45,420
Who's that?

439
00:37:45,820 --> 00:37:49,950
She is the woman who rescued me from the Rocket Gang's place.

440
00:37:50,490 --> 00:37:51,620
Then she's on our side?

441
00:37:52,100 --> 00:37:54,500
Diancie, better get moving!

442
00:37:55,410 --> 00:37:56,890
Princess, this way!

443
00:37:56,890 --> 00:37:58,960
Yes. Pardon me.

444
00:38:02,280 --> 00:38:03,330
Miriss Steel.

445
00:38:04,510 --> 00:38:06,010
If you're here...

446
00:38:06,980 --> 00:38:08,820
...then I take it Algus is here too?

447
00:38:11,230 --> 00:38:12,580
I wonder.

448
00:38:16,240 --> 00:38:20,110
We serve to protect Diancie-sama.

449
00:38:21,950 --> 00:38:23,870
So you're the princess' bodyguards?

450
00:38:24,260 --> 00:38:27,130
So Diancie was a real princess all along.

451
00:38:27,360 --> 00:38:29,050
Who are these people?

452
00:38:29,470 --> 00:38:30,330
We're...

453
00:38:30,820 --> 00:38:31,580
My...

454
00:38:32,240 --> 00:38:33,140
...friends.

455
00:38:41,960 --> 00:38:43,500
Hup.

456
00:38:45,100 --> 00:38:48,220
We have been traveling for several months.

457
00:38:48,690 --> 00:38:50,010
To search for Xerneas?

458
00:38:50,490 --> 00:38:50,940
Yes.

459
00:39:11,010 --> 00:39:12,660
I feel the Fairy Aura.

460
00:39:25,260 --> 00:39:30,560
We constantly moved to new locations, but we were never able to meet Xerneas.

461
00:39:39,360 --> 00:39:42,100
One day, I saw a city far in the distance.

462
00:39:45,650 --> 00:39:48,320
I wanted to go see it.

463
00:39:49,330 --> 00:39:51,810
Somehow, it seemed as if it would be fun.

464
00:39:54,010 --> 00:39:56,000
And that's when you met us?

465
00:39:56,480 --> 00:40:02,420
Diancie-sama might have felt confined after being with us all this time.

466
00:40:03,250 --> 00:40:05,210
I am sorry for acting according to my own convenience.

467
00:40:05,890 --> 00:40:08,970
Please, do not do something like this again.

468
00:40:09,410 --> 00:40:09,770
I will not.

469
00:40:23,310 --> 00:40:23,880
What's this?

470
00:40:24,720 --> 00:40:27,980
It is one of our countries, which can found all throughout the world.

471
00:40:28,670 --> 00:40:33,400
All these countries are connected through these diamond paths.

472
00:40:39,660 --> 00:40:41,700
Thank you for coming out to greet me.

473
00:40:55,240 --> 00:40:56,720
What is this?

474
00:40:58,300 --> 00:40:59,360
Princess.

475
00:41:00,840 --> 00:41:01,400
Di!

476
00:41:03,950 --> 00:41:08,270
The Sacred Diamond has finally expended its lifespan.

477
00:41:08,770 --> 00:41:09,710
What are you saying?

478
00:41:29,060 --> 00:41:30,520
No...

479
00:41:31,640 --> 00:41:35,180
I have come all this way to let you know that.

480
00:41:36,640 --> 00:41:38,110
What's the Sacred Diamond?

481
00:41:38,360 --> 00:41:39,200
Tell us!

482
00:41:39,520 --> 00:41:42,050
We'll do anything we can to help.

483
00:41:43,450 --> 00:41:43,810
Yes!

484
00:41:44,590 --> 00:41:45,610
Everybody...

485
00:41:48,350 --> 00:41:55,180
The Sacred Diamond is the source of the energy glow that is sent throughout our countries around the world.

486
00:41:55,800 --> 00:41:58,200
It has vanished.

487
00:42:07,600 --> 00:42:11,490
Only Diancie-sama is able to forge a Sacred Diamond.

488
00:42:12,040 --> 00:42:15,850
But I still do not have that power.

489
00:42:16,420 --> 00:42:22,380
Xerneas' Fairy Aura is sure to awaken your true power.

490
00:42:23,290 --> 00:42:24,730
So that's how it is.

491
00:42:29,560 --> 00:42:32,220
I had no idea about the state the country was in.

492
00:42:32,220 --> 00:42:33,400
I...

493
00:42:33,970 --> 00:42:38,140
I have no right to be called a princess.

494
00:42:41,850 --> 00:42:43,210
Don't cry, Diancie.

495
00:42:45,610 --> 00:42:47,440
Crying never solves anything.

496
00:43:02,530 --> 00:43:03,260
Princess.

497
00:43:06,080 --> 00:43:07,610
It is as you say.

498
00:43:08,050 --> 00:43:09,550
This is no time to be crying.

499
00:43:10,320 --> 00:43:12,600
Let us go, to meet with Xerneas.

500
00:43:13,020 --> 00:43:14,020
That's the spirit.

501
00:43:15,410 --> 00:43:16,750
Princess.

502
00:43:37,760 --> 00:43:38,800
Diancie-sama!

503
00:43:59,220 --> 00:44:00,080
Wow!

504
00:44:00,920 --> 00:44:04,050
I feel a strong Fairy Aura from the forest over there.

505
00:44:04,580 --> 00:44:06,090
Then, Xerneas is...?

506
00:44:06,090 --> 00:44:06,810
Right there!

507
00:44:08,660 --> 00:44:09,180
Princess.

508
00:44:10,000 --> 00:44:12,140
Those are the Alearth Woods.

509
00:44:13,500 --> 00:44:14,840
The Alearth Woods?

510
00:44:15,150 --> 00:44:21,770
Long ago, the Alearth Woods gave rise to the Great Destruction, which would wipe out all life.

511
00:44:25,970 --> 00:44:31,440
Since then, it has become forbidden land that nobody must set foot in.

512
00:44:32,080 --> 00:44:35,730
There is also something else I must tell you.

513
00:44:36,840 --> 00:44:39,490
It is about the cause of the Great Destruction.

514
00:44:40,780 --> 00:44:45,240
The Great Destruction was caused by Yveltal, the embodiment of Destruction.

515
00:44:46,830 --> 00:44:51,570
After destroying everything, Yveltal turned into a cocoon.

516
00:44:53,650 --> 00:44:58,380
Alearth became forbidden land because that cocoon resides there.

517
00:44:58,820 --> 00:44:59,520
"Yveltal"?

518
00:44:59,930 --> 00:45:04,100
If I remember right, it is a legendary Pokémon said to be able to take away all life.

519
00:45:07,250 --> 00:45:09,360
According to legend,

520
00:45:10,110 --> 00:45:15,680
those who disturb the sleep of the Cocoon of Destruction shall receive judgment of fury!

521
00:45:16,180 --> 00:45:16,500
Huh?

522
00:45:33,360 --> 00:45:34,860
These are the Alearth Woods?

523
00:45:35,390 --> 00:45:38,090
It is hard to believe the Great Destruction happened here.

524
00:45:38,600 --> 00:45:42,920
The ruined forest revived over the many years that passed since then.

525
00:45:47,700 --> 00:45:54,900
It is said that Yveltal caused the Great Destruction in order to bring out the forest's ability to regenerate.

526
00:45:57,010 --> 00:46:01,100
So you are saying that even the Great Destruction might just be another part of the law of nature...

527
00:46:01,570 --> 00:46:02,920
The law of nature?

528
00:46:03,600 --> 00:46:08,320
The birth of new life, death... that kind of "rules", so to speak, the natural world follows.

529
00:46:12,840 --> 00:46:16,110
Isn't this considered forbidden land?

530
00:46:16,370 --> 00:46:19,560
But Diancie is inside this forest.

531
00:46:19,560 --> 00:46:22,120
We can't give up after coming this far.

532
00:46:22,490 --> 00:46:22,840
Nay!

533
00:46:44,560 --> 00:46:45,440
Xerneas!

534
00:46:45,700 --> 00:46:46,320
You mean that?

535
00:47:04,920 --> 00:47:07,130
Xerneas, please wait!

536
00:47:34,840 --> 00:47:35,800
Xerneas.

537
00:47:38,370 --> 00:47:41,420
You have pursued me all this time, haven't you?

538
00:47:42,530 --> 00:47:44,450
I have finally been able to meet you.

539
00:47:45,780 --> 00:47:48,360
I know what it is...

540
00:47:49,100 --> 00:47:51,130
...that you are seeking.

541
00:47:51,680 --> 00:47:52,140
Eh?

542
00:47:52,580 --> 00:47:53,940
I shall bestow it upon you.

543
00:48:02,880 --> 00:48:03,940
It's the Fairy Aura!

544
00:48:16,000 --> 00:48:20,880
It is you yourself that will have to foster life.

545
00:48:35,690 --> 00:48:38,280
Xerneas, you have my gratitude.

546
00:48:38,990 --> 00:48:40,100
Diancie-sama!

547
00:48:40,380 --> 00:48:41,490
Princess!

548
00:48:42,100 --> 00:48:44,560
I felt the Fairy Aura too!

549
00:48:45,390 --> 00:48:47,600
I kinda feel like <i>I</i> was given strength too!

550
00:48:49,760 --> 00:48:51,950
Now you can definitely save your country!

551
00:48:52,420 --> 00:48:56,370
So have I become able to forge a Sacred Diamond, I wonder?

552
00:48:57,000 --> 00:48:57,890
Try it out!

553
00:48:57,890 --> 00:48:59,060
I'm sure you can do it!

554
00:48:59,490 --> 00:49:00,290
Princess!

555
00:49:16,600 --> 00:49:18,020
Congratulations, Diancie!

556
00:49:18,480 --> 00:49:21,640
Now you're finally able to make real diamonds, right?

557
00:49:22,220 --> 00:49:22,940
You are...

558
00:49:23,440 --> 00:49:25,100
You're the one who helped us the other day?!

559
00:49:26,370 --> 00:49:28,910
We will be taking Diancie!

560
00:49:35,250 --> 00:49:36,170
What's this about?

561
00:49:36,480 --> 00:49:37,490
We knew all along.

562
00:49:38,090 --> 00:49:44,620
The reason you were trying to meet Xerneas was because Diancie still didn't have the power to make real diamonds.

563
00:49:45,960 --> 00:49:46,730
Thanks for helping.

564
00:49:48,880 --> 00:49:55,240
A Diancie that can't create diamonds is as pointless as a chocolate without cocoa.

565
00:49:56,020 --> 00:49:57,300
Algus Steel.

566
00:49:57,480 --> 00:49:59,100
The big-shot bandit...

567
00:49:59,500 --> 00:50:01,140
And that's his daughter Miriss.

568
00:50:01,440 --> 00:50:05,210
It was quite hard, you know? Watching over you to keep others from interfering.

569
00:50:05,490 --> 00:50:06,810
Okay, Vine Whip!

570
00:50:23,220 --> 00:50:25,080
I'll be taking Diancie!

571
00:50:26,700 --> 00:50:27,860
Hitotsuki, after them!

572
00:50:30,000 --> 00:50:30,590
Brigarron!

573
00:50:31,490 --> 00:50:32,250
Diancie!

574
00:50:33,280 --> 00:50:34,670
We must save the princess!

575
00:50:45,880 --> 00:50:49,280
If you want diamonds, I shall give them to you! So please, let me go!

576
00:50:49,280 --> 00:50:52,130
I have to hurry back to my country!

577
00:51:18,810 --> 00:51:20,260
Thanks for your excellent work.

578
00:51:20,850 --> 00:51:21,380
Marilyn!

579
00:51:23,650 --> 00:51:25,960
You look fantastic even when you're angry, Riot!

580
00:51:26,510 --> 00:51:27,630
Later!

581
00:51:42,260 --> 00:51:42,990
Hold it!

582
00:51:44,440 --> 00:51:46,330
Here! This way, Diancie!

583
00:51:47,890 --> 00:51:49,570
Diancie!

584
00:51:59,700 --> 00:52:00,650
You brat!

585
00:52:00,650 --> 00:52:01,490
Excuse me!

586
00:52:05,620 --> 00:52:06,190
Why?

587
00:52:06,510 --> 00:52:07,640
No, I just sort of...

588
00:52:15,500 --> 00:52:16,300
What <i>is</i> this?

589
00:52:16,590 --> 00:52:17,170
I don't know.

590
00:52:21,180 --> 00:52:22,860
Hand over Diancie!

591
00:52:22,860 --> 00:52:23,940
No way!

592
00:52:25,080 --> 00:52:26,670
When adults talk, you listen!

593
00:52:27,460 --> 00:52:28,480
There's too many of them.

594
00:52:28,700 --> 00:52:29,620
What do we do?

595
00:52:29,790 --> 00:52:31,740
It's impossible for us to get in there.

596
00:52:56,680 --> 00:52:57,090
Oh no!

597
00:52:58,000 --> 00:53:00,300
Diancie-sama! Satoshi, my boy!

598
00:53:00,750 --> 00:53:02,030
Get out of there!

599
00:53:33,000 --> 00:53:34,670
The Cocoon of... Destruction!

600
00:53:54,480 --> 00:53:57,290
"Those who disturb the sleep of the Cocoon of Destruction...

601
00:53:57,920 --> 00:54:00,050
...shall receive judgment of fury!"

602
00:54:00,880 --> 00:54:01,300
That's...?

603
00:54:02,440 --> 00:54:03,120
Yveltal.

604
00:55:26,190 --> 00:55:27,800
Princess!

605
00:55:29,950 --> 00:55:30,920
Gotcha!

606
00:55:32,290 --> 00:55:33,350
Diancie!

607
00:56:17,220 --> 00:56:18,740
Pikachu, Thunderbolt!

608
00:56:30,180 --> 00:56:31,500
Diancie, are you all right?

609
00:56:32,340 --> 00:56:32,740
Yes!

610
00:56:34,670 --> 00:56:36,510
We're getting out of this dangerous forest right now!

611
00:56:36,800 --> 00:56:38,080
Never mind the diamonds.

612
00:56:38,080 --> 00:56:40,020
Our lives are more important!

613
00:57:00,920 --> 00:57:02,960
What <i>is</i> that Pokémon?

614
00:57:03,630 --> 00:57:05,100
My Mafoxy has been...

615
00:57:07,920 --> 00:57:08,620
Riot?

616
00:57:09,060 --> 00:57:09,930
It's no good.

617
00:57:10,490 --> 00:57:10,760
Eh?

618
00:57:12,720 --> 00:57:14,200
Let's give up on Diancie.

619
00:57:24,900 --> 00:57:25,540
Watch out!

620
00:57:49,850 --> 00:57:51,420
I can't believe this is happening.

621
00:57:51,770 --> 00:57:53,440
The forest will vanish once again.

622
00:57:53,440 --> 00:57:55,360
Hey, everyone!

623
00:57:58,780 --> 00:57:59,800
Princess!

624
00:57:59,800 --> 00:58:00,790
You're all right!

625
00:58:01,080 --> 00:58:02,490
Luchabull, thanks a lot.

626
00:58:20,540 --> 00:58:22,520
It's warding off Yveltal's power!

627
00:58:22,520 --> 00:58:23,900
That means she's finally...

628
00:58:31,800 --> 00:58:32,610
Princess!

629
00:58:40,220 --> 00:58:43,290
I still do not have the power...

630
00:58:48,840 --> 00:58:49,540
Diancie!

631
00:59:08,060 --> 00:59:09,440
Pikachu, Thunderbolt!

632
00:59:18,620 --> 00:59:21,560
My dear Satoshi, Diancie-sama must be protec...

633
00:59:23,790 --> 00:59:24,380
Majima.

634
00:59:43,080 --> 00:59:43,710
Pikachu!

635
00:59:44,620 --> 00:59:45,740
Hang in there!

636
01:00:00,010 --> 01:00:02,350
I need to protect everybody...

637
01:00:02,920 --> 01:00:03,610
And yet I...

638
01:00:04,360 --> 01:00:05,600
...cannot do anything.

639
01:00:07,340 --> 01:00:08,490
Don't give up!

640
01:00:09,820 --> 01:00:11,830
It's only when you give up that it's all over!

641
01:00:12,080 --> 01:00:12,740
He is right!

642
01:00:12,980 --> 01:00:14,540
You can't give up!

643
01:00:14,540 --> 01:00:15,760
Hang in there!

644
01:00:20,240 --> 01:00:21,630
Pikachu, are you all right?

645
01:00:29,340 --> 01:00:29,950
Okay...

646
01:00:45,890 --> 01:00:46,700
Thunderbolt!

647
01:01:11,200 --> 01:01:13,140
It is you yourself...

648
01:01:14,430 --> 01:01:16,600
...that will have to foster life.

649
01:01:17,970 --> 01:01:20,100
I will not give up.

650
01:01:47,760 --> 01:01:48,850
A Mega Evolution!

651
01:02:18,180 --> 01:02:18,890
Wow!

652
01:02:19,220 --> 01:02:20,120
You did it!

653
01:02:20,320 --> 01:02:22,550
<i>This</i> is a Sacred Diamond!

654
01:02:50,530 --> 01:02:51,500
Little boy and Pikachu...

655
01:02:52,090 --> 01:02:53,680
Thanks for helping us out back there.

656
01:02:54,180 --> 01:02:55,240
We'll return the favor.

657
01:03:13,620 --> 01:03:14,090
Yeah!

658
01:03:14,510 --> 01:03:15,060
We got it!

659
01:03:28,650 --> 01:03:29,020
Miriss!

660
01:03:29,260 --> 01:03:29,700
Dad!

661
01:04:04,640 --> 01:04:05,520
Xerneas.

662
01:05:12,530 --> 01:05:13,280
It left.

663
01:05:13,690 --> 01:05:14,970
We are safe.

664
01:05:20,410 --> 01:05:20,780
Pikachu.

665
01:05:21,160 --> 01:05:21,460
Huh?

666
01:05:22,010 --> 01:05:23,130
Pikachu, what's wrong?

667
01:05:29,480 --> 01:05:30,070
Back then...

668
01:05:45,140 --> 01:05:45,870
Pikachu!

669
01:05:47,160 --> 01:05:48,890
What's wrong? Hey!

670
01:05:49,420 --> 01:05:49,920
Pikachu!

671
01:05:50,690 --> 01:05:51,390
Pikachu!

672
01:05:51,790 --> 01:05:53,210
Answer me, Pikachu!

673
01:05:58,420 --> 01:05:59,260
Pikachu...

674
01:06:00,690 --> 01:06:01,870
Pikachu!

675
01:06:17,170 --> 01:06:18,000
Xerneas...

676
01:06:34,080 --> 01:06:35,080
Pikachu!

677
01:06:45,400 --> 01:06:46,260
Princess!

678
01:06:46,680 --> 01:06:47,280
Majima!

679
01:06:47,810 --> 01:06:48,580
Everybody!

680
01:06:50,180 --> 01:06:53,530
Xerneas has granted you life.

681
01:07:15,450 --> 01:07:16,640
It is turning into a tree.

682
01:07:17,440 --> 01:07:18,470
Xerneas...

683
01:07:19,240 --> 01:07:21,920
...has chosen to sleep here on this land...

684
01:07:22,740 --> 01:07:24,880
...in order to protect the law of nature.

685
01:07:27,960 --> 01:07:28,990
It's dying?

686
01:07:29,240 --> 01:07:29,930
No way...

687
01:07:35,100 --> 01:07:37,130
Do not be sad.

688
01:07:37,960 --> 01:07:39,600
Xerneas is talking!

689
01:07:40,600 --> 01:07:41,200
What is it saying?

690
01:07:41,970 --> 01:07:44,510
This is not a death.

691
01:07:45,640 --> 01:07:47,610
This is a sign of birth.
This is a sign of birth.

692
01:07:48,820 --> 01:07:49,530
And...
And...

693
01:07:50,240 --> 01:07:52,240
...the beginning of hope.
...the beginning of hope.

694
01:07:54,410 --> 01:07:55,180
Birth...

695
01:07:55,720 --> 01:07:57,710
...and the beginning of hope...

696
01:08:09,000 --> 01:08:09,580
I see.

697
01:08:11,470 --> 01:08:13,300
Thank you, Xerneas.

698
01:09:02,910 --> 01:09:04,200
It's so pretty.

699
01:09:04,200 --> 01:09:05,710
Yeah, it's like...

700
01:09:05,710 --> 01:09:07,410
...we've been reborn.

701
01:09:08,110 --> 01:09:10,000
Somehow, this feels...

702
01:09:10,600 --> 01:09:12,890
...<i>really</i> good.

703
01:09:47,450 --> 01:09:48,570
Princess!

704
01:09:48,810 --> 01:09:49,930
Well done!

705
01:10:06,210 --> 01:10:10,170
Satoshi, Pikachu, Serena, Eureka, Citron...

706
01:10:10,880 --> 01:10:13,630
Everybody, thank you oh so very much.

707
01:10:14,330 --> 01:10:15,850
I'm glad to have met you, Diancie.

708
01:10:17,320 --> 01:10:18,600
Me too.

709
01:10:18,600 --> 01:10:19,460
Eureka too!

710
01:10:19,800 --> 01:10:22,130
We are friends forever.

711
01:10:22,490 --> 01:10:22,850
Yeah.

712
01:10:27,060 --> 01:10:27,390
Huh?

713
01:10:29,530 --> 01:10:30,490
This diamond!

714
01:10:30,780 --> 01:10:32,380
It stayed without disappearing!

715
01:10:32,650 --> 01:10:33,130
Huh?

716
01:10:33,760 --> 01:10:37,060
Then that's the first diamond that Diancie made?

717
01:10:37,460 --> 01:10:37,710
Ah...

718
01:10:38,240 --> 01:10:39,900
It's a proof of our friendship!

719
01:10:43,870 --> 01:10:44,290
Yes!

720
01:10:45,340 --> 01:10:47,550
Diancie, you keep this.

721
01:10:50,620 --> 01:10:51,970
I shall treasure it!

722
01:10:52,440 --> 01:10:52,750
Yeah.

723
01:10:53,320 --> 01:10:53,620
Yeah.

