Everyone has a dream
that fills their heart...
a journey they must take...
a destiny to fulfill.
As close
as your imagination...
exists a magical place...
where wondrous creatures
with incredible powers...
help make dreams come true.
It's the world of Pokemon.
People can capture Pokemon
to be more than just pets.
Human trainers
and their Pokemon...
compete against others
in amazing contests...
of skill and strategy.
The best trainers one day
become Pokemon masters.
That's a dream that
burns brightly for many...
but none more so
than Ash Ketchum.
The pride of Pallet Town
began his Pokemon journey...
on his tenth birthday.
That's the day he qualified
to become a Pokemon trainer.
Professor Oak gave Ash
his very first Pokeball.
Inside was
an electric Pokemon...
with whom Ash would spark
a lifelong friendship--Pikachu.
Pikachu!
Together, Ash and Pikachu
are determined...
to fulfill his dream...
of becoming the world's
greatest Pokemon master.
Joining them on their quest
are Misty...
and yours truly, Brock...
in the incredible world
of Pokemon.
Bi.
Bi!
Bi! Bi!
Hound!
-Bi! Bi!
-Scyther! Scyther!
Scyther! Scyther!
Bi!
Huh?
Ohh.
If you're going in,
be careful.
Huh?
Don't forget--if you hear
the Voice of the Forest...
don't move a muscle.
Huh?
Don't tell me
you haven't heard about it.
No, I haven't.
What's the Voice
of the Forest?
Well, it's only a legend...
but everyone around here
believes it.
They say there's a sound
you can hear...
when the spirit
that protects the forest...
is time-traveling.
Time-traveling?
That's one of
its special powers.
It can go back and forth
between the past and the future.
Wow.
So if you hear
a weird sound...
stop and stay
completely still.
If the spirit
catches you...
it could carry you off
to a different time.
Don't worry.
I'll be careful.
Mm.
Thanks. Bye.
Wait.
Huh?
T ake this. It's a loaf
of bread I made...
that's full of berries
from the forest.
It might come in handy
if you get hungry.
Here.
Thanks, Miss.
I appreciate it.
Bye.
Furret.
Furret!
Bi!
-Scyther!
-Bi!
Hound!
Bi!
Bi! Bi! Bi! Bi!
Scyther!
Bi!
Ho-o-o-ound.
Scyther!
So...
Bi...bi...
You've been givin' me
the slip for a long time...
but you won't today.
Bi!
Don't let it get away!
Let's go!
-Scyther!
-Hound!
Bi! Bi!
Bi-i-i-i-i-i!
Huh?
Cele?
Cele!
Oddish. Oddish. Oddish.
Whoa!
Bi.
Huh? Uhh!
Hound!
Huh.
Uhh!
Huh?
Scyther!
Bi! Bi!
Let it go!
Two against one isn't fair!
Doom...hound!
Aah!
Bi!
Scyther! Scyther!
Hou-hou-hound!
Bi!
Huh?
All right,
hand over that Celebi.
Celebi?
Why should I hand it over?
What do you want with it?
I'm a Pokemon hunter, kid.
I make good money
off of rare Pokemon.
First I catch 'em,
then I auction 'em off...
to the highest bidders.
Well, you're not gonna get
your hands on this Pokemon!
Give it to me!
No! Go away!
Bi.
Bi-i-i-i-i-i!
Could that be time-traveling?
Uhh.
Huh?
Bi-i-i-i-i-i!
I'll tell you why I'm here.
I'm here
because I heard a story...
that you almost
caught a Celebi...
somewhere in this forest
about 40 years ago--true?
I'm still a Pokemon hunter!
I'm not gonna tell you anything!
Heh heh.
We'll see about that.
OK.
Sneasel! Sneasel!
Sneasel!
What's that thing?
A Dark Ball.
What's it do?
Allow me to demonstrate.
The Pokemon I catch
with the Dark Ball...
become evil Pokemon...
and their power instantly
increases to the highest level.
Come on out, Tyranitar!
Hyper Beam Attack!
No, please!
It's gonna destroy everything!
Uhh!
Aah! Aah! All right!
All right!
I'll show you!
I'll show you the spot...
where I found that Celebi!
Heh heh heh heh heh.
Ha ha ha ha ha ha!
I thought
you'd see it my way.
Today we find our friends...
waiting for a ferry
that will carry them...
to yet another Pokemon gym...
as they continue
their Johto League journey.
Brock and Misty are ready.
The passengers
are hurrying aboard...
and it's almost time
for the boat to leave.
But where are
Ash and Pikachu?
Well, if they don't come soon
they're gonna miss the boat.
T ogepi!
Crobat, go!
Crobat!
Cro!
My name's Dundee...
and I'm the best Pokemon
trainer in the whole town.
Well, my name's Ash...
and I'm a pretty good
Pokemon trainer, too.
Why don't you pick a Pokemon,
and we can have a battle.
Pika!
Croconaw, go!
Croconaw!
A Croconaw, huh?
Never battled
one of those before.
OK, Pikachu, let's go!
Pika!
Pokemon, Pokemon, Pokemon,
Pokemon, Pokemon
Let's do it
Thunder Shock Attack!
So, sounds like
you're all...
pretty interested
in Pokemon, huh?
Yeah.
I come from a place
just up the river...
and a lot
of real unusual ones...
Iive in the forest nearby.
Hey, if you could show us
where it is...
maybe we could stop
and check it out.
No problem.
We can get off...
at the next stop,
and I'll take you...
the rest of the way
in my boat.
Great. Thanks.
Pika!
ALL: Huh?
ASH: Ohh.
Hey, was that a Pokemon?
Looked like one to me.
You'll see the woods
around here are full of them.
There's one more possibility.
Did it look
anything like this?
Yeah, that's it, Professor.
It was a Suicune.
A Suicune?
What kind of Pokemon
is that, Professor?
It's one of the legendary
Pokemon, Brock...
and not very much
is known about it.
And according
to folk tales...
Suicune personifies
the north wind...
and it's believed
to have the power...
to purify tainted waters.
Wow, I hope I get
to see Suicune again.
Its sounds like
it's a pretty cool one.
Believe you me, kids...
those tales
are definitely true.
Really? How do you know that
for sure, Professor?
Have you ever seen
a Suicune before?
Yes, I sure have,
but only one time.
Wow! Where?
Hey, Ash, come on!
We've gotta go!
OK!
Uh, bye, Professor.
I wonder if I should've told him
before he hung up.
Hmm.
The quicker we get
into that forest...
the quicker we can look
for those Pokemon.
Maybe even that Suicune.
Those twerps won't get away now.
They're right beneath us.
Of course, they're
beneath us. They're twerps.
Now all we do is
swoop in and swipe Pikachu.
Uh-oh. Something's wrong
with my leg.
All this pedaling
is giving me a cramp.
Oh! Ow!
Aah! You can't cramp!
We'll crash!
All right.
What do we do now?
Don't worry, Misty.
You'll see.
-Whoa.
-Pi?
Toge?
Toge! Toge!
Ha ha ha!
Toge-togepi!
Well, we're here.
Here? Where?
Look closer.
Tree houses?
Togepi!
That's right, Brock.
Welcome to Arborville.
Pika?
-Whoa.
-Prrri!
Stop right there!
Huh?
I suppose you kids
are heading into the forest...
to look for Pokemon.
Yes, ma'am.
Then you're gonna love
what you see in there.
I love what I see here!
My name's Brock...
and I'm studying to
become a Pokemon breeder...
but my specialty
is human relations.
Oh?
Please tell me your name!
My name's Diana,
and that's my grandma.
She's been guarding
the entrance to the forest...
since she was my age.
Listen for The Voice
of the Forest...
and if you hear it,
stop and be still...
or you will not get away.
The Voice of the Forest?
It's an old village legend.
Yes, it's a legend,
and a true one.
If you hear The Voice,
stop where you are.
Uh, we gotta hurry...
but thanks a lot for
the warning, ma'am.
Pika!
Diana, why don't you
come, too, and protect us?
Then she'd need
protection from you.
I wonder what
Diana's grandmother meant...
by 'The Voice
of the Forest. "
Maybe the sound of the wind
or the trees...
the water, or maybe
the voices of the Pokemon.
Pi?
Ohh. I wonder what that is.
Maybe it's The Voice
of the Forest.
-Come on!
-Pika!
Ash, no!
Hey, shouldn't we stand still?
Uh...wait up!
Bi.
Hey, it's a kid.
Is he OK?
He's still breathing.
Yeah.
Let's take him
back to Diana's house.
Good idea.
Yeah.
Bi...
I wonder what that light was.
Hey! Diana!
Diana! We need help!
Oh, dear. What's happened?
Hey, Ash, he's waking up.
Take it easy.
You're gonna be OK.
Pika.
Uhh.
Uhh!
What'd you do with that Celebi?
Hey, I'm trying to help you!
That's enough, you two.
Knock it off.
Settle down!
Who are you anyway?
Huh?
Where am l?
Howd I get here?
I carried you here
on my back, that's how!
What's going on?
MlSTY:
We found him unconscious...
when we were out
in the forest.
Oh!
Oh-oh-oh!
I can't believe it.
It's really you.
Huh?
You've come back.
Oh, thank goodness!
Uh, Grandma...
where did he
come back from?
Diana, I've told you
the story...
about what happened
when I was a young girl.
A little boy disappeared
from the forest.
But this boy can't be him.
Well, maybe it can't be...
-but it is.
-Huh?
Ah! You're the girl...
who gave me
the loaf of bread.
Yes.
Here.
I've kept this all these years
in case you ever came back.
This is my sketchbook.
How--
You've been away...
on a 40-year-long journey,
young man.
40 years?
What do you mean?
The legend says
The Voice of the Forest...
can catch a person and take them
on a trip through time.
-Huh?
-Through time?
Stantler?
Stan--
Stantler!
Uhh!
Where's Celebi?
What happened to Celebi?
Celebi?
Was there a Pokemon
with me in the forest?
We didn't see any.
The Pokemon you met
that day was a Celebi?
Yes.
We know Celebi
as The Voice of the Forest...
the spirit that protects it.
They say that Celebi
can travel through time.
You two must've been
in danger...
and Celebi just picked
the fastest way...
to get you out of it.
It's must've
escaped to the future...
and taken you along with it.
I'm afraid you're right.
Celebi lives
deep in the forest...
in a place we call
"The Lake of Life."
That's probably where
it's gone back to now.
I've got a feeling Celebi
still may be hurt.
I have to go back into
that forest and find Celebi.
I'll go, too!
Me, too!
So will l!
Togepi!
My name's Brock...
and I'm a Pokemon breeder.
I'm Sam.
And I'm Misty.
My specialty is water Pokemon.
My name's Ash Ketchum...
and I'm trying
to be a Pokemon master.
Pika!
Oh, yeah,
and this is Pikachu.
Pikachu!
Hi, Pikachu. I'm Sam.
Our glider
didn't glide very well.
Next time
we spring for a motor.
I wonder where
those twerps are.
We may never know.
Huh?
-Huh?
Well, well.
I can't believe my eyes.
Looks like it's a good thing...
we crashed after
all, eh, Meowth?
Come on, let's get down
and tail them twerps!
Pika!
Pikachu!
Pi--pi--pi--pi--
Pi--Pika!
Guys, look up there!
The Pokemon
are all together.
I'm coming, too!
Ash climbs just like a Mankey.
Togepi!
Pi!
-Aah!
-Pika!
Sam, maybe you should wait
down with Brock and Misty.
No. I have to find Celebi.
I couldn't
protect it before...
so I've gotta help it now.
I know how you feel, Sam,
but take it easy.
Pi! Pi! Pi! Pi!
Uh. Ah!
Bi...bi.
Hey.
Is this the Celebi?
Mm-hmm.
Come on, Celebi.
Bi. Bi!
Whoa! Unh!
Hey! What'd you do that for?
I think Ash just evolved
into a primate.
We're only trying to help you.
Bi!
Whoa!
What's going on?
Pika--
No, Pikachu, don't!
Don't be mad at it.
It's just afraid...
and it's hurt, too.
A hunter attacked it.
That's why it's scared.
OK. Here goes.
Celebi, we're your friends.
We don't want to hurt you.
We just want to help you.
Bi!
I tried to help you before.
Don't you remember, Celebi?
I got you away
from the Pokemon hunter.
It's OK.
Bi?
You just take it easy.
And we will, too.
There...
Bi.
Bi?
Uh...
Ha ha!
You're safe with me, Celebi.
Bi.
Pik--Pik--Pik...
Brock, it seems really weak.
Yeah, we better hurry.
We'll take it
to a Pokemon center.
Pika-pi!
Who are they?
Prepare for trouble.
Your future looks grim.
And we're not afraid
to go out on a limb.
To protect the world
from devastation.
To unite all peoples
within our nation.
To denounce the evils
of truth and love.
To extend our reach
to the stars above.
Jessie.
James.
Team Rocket...
blast off
at the speed of light.
Surrender now
or prepare to fight.
Meowth--that's right.
Wobbuffet!
Aah!
Hmm.
Do you think
they're gonna be OK?
Unfortunately, yes.
Hmm.
You twerps got lucky this time.
They're always lucky.
Wobbuffet!
Don't press your luck, blubbo.
Hang in there, Celebi.
Look, that's
the village up there!
Aah!
I've been looking
for that little Celebi.
Who are you?
A Pokemon lover.
Leave us alone!
What does he want?
He must be trying to steal
our Pikachu away.
Well, we won't let him!
Weezing. Weezing.
Huhh!
What's that?
A Tyranitar...
but there's something
funny about it.
Hyper-beam!
Here it comes!
Pika! Pika!
Weezing!
Two can play
the Celebi-stealing game.
Who are you three?
Look at that mask.
I've seen him before.
Yeah, wasn't he in
that Mexican wrestling movie?
No, Meowth,
he's from Team Rocket.
The lron Mask Marauder!
So you heard about me.
Yeah!
Oh, yes, we've heard
a lot about you.
As you can tell
from the uniforms...
we're also members
of Team Rocket.
Me, too, but Pokemon
get to go naked.
Go!
Scizor!
Sneasel!
Aah.
Misty!
I think Misty's hurt.
Brock, I twisted my knee.
You better stay off it.
Pi--Pika!
Something's coming!
Sneasel!
Scizor!
What are they doing here?
They must want Celebi.
Scizor!
Snease!
All right, then they're
in for a battle.
Brock, take care of Celebi.
Right.
All right,
I'm with you, Ash. Ready?
Uh...
Char!
Go!
Bay!
Scizor!
B-bay!
Bay.
Quick, Bayleef,
use your razor leaf!
Bay...
Scizor! [Echoes]
Bay!
Bay.
Scizor!
Scizor! [Echoes]
Bay...
Char. Char!
Scizor! [Echoes]
Bay! Bay.
Are you OK?
Ash, you gotta find
the real one.
It's using double team.
Mm.
Bayleef, listen,
you gotta concentrate!
Then you can find the real one!
Scizor! [Echoes]
Bay. Bay.
Scizor...Scizor.
Bay!
Scizor!
Yeah, Bayleef, you did it!
You're a great trainer, Ash.
Well, it helps
when you have great Pokemon.
Look out. Sneasel!
Sneasel!
Char.
Charmeleon, use head butt!
Char! Char!
Snease.
Hey, you're not
a bad trainer yourself.
We make a good team.
-Scizor!
-Snease!
Those kids aren't as wimpy
as I thought they'd be.
This makes things interesting.
We gotta find the way out.
Pi?
This is getting bad.
Pppi.
Bi. Bi. Bi. Bi.
We better keep moving forward.
If we stop now,
we might be too late.
-Pika!
-Huh?
It's Ursaring.
Huh?
Daddy Ursa.
Goom-um.
Oh...
What are they doing?
I think they're telling us
to follow them.
Pika!
Should we?
Yeah.
Stantler.
-Goom.
-Stantler.
Stantler.
Furret.
-Stantler.
-Furret.
Furret.
Furret. Furret.
Hey, do you think this
could be The Lake of Life...
that Diana's grandmother
was talking about?
Bi...Bi...
Bi...Bi...Bi...
Hey, Sam, look.
Huh? Uh--
Look, guys, Celebi's swimming.
And it's glowing.
Pika!
This must be the Lake of Life.
Hey, that's it!
The lake water...
must have brought
Celebi back to life.
Oh.
Ha ha.
Pika. Pika!
Bi!
Celebi!
All right!
Pikachu!
Bi!
Ha ha ha.
Whee! Whee!
Pikachu!
Whee! Bi!
Bi!
Toge! Toge!
Whee!
-Bi!
-Whoa.
All right, then!
Let's do it!
Yeah!
Mm! Mm!
-Whoa!
Pika! Pika!
All right!
Bi.
Oh.
Hey!
Heh heh.
My knee's better.
Thanks, Celebi!
Bi!
Hi! Hey, you guys!
Bi! Bi!
-Whoa!
This is great!
Oh...
There's the village
over there.
Jaj, jaj...
Ja, ja, ja...
Bi! Bi!
Bi!
Bi-bi!
Bi.
Bi! Bi! Bi! Bi!
Huh?
Awesome!
These are really good.
Yeah?
Pika.
Ah, you're right.
Pika, Pika!
Huh.
Mmm, they're tasty.
They're delicious.
Bi!
I'm gonna keep some for later.
Pikachu!
Thanks for taking us here,
Celebi.
Yeah.
These are good ones.
Have some, Celebi.
Bi-bi-bi-bi!
Don't you worry.
We'll find Celebi.
I'd rather find some lunch.
So would l.
Or a bathroom.
-Huh?
Lucky us!
It's a peach tree!
Grab that big one there, Meowth.
You got it, Jessie!
Eee!
Ah! Ah!
-Hey!
Nice catch.
It was peachy.
Huh?
There goes our driver!
Wait! Come back!
Don't leave us!
We'll even chip in for gas!
Sammy, it's the middle
of the night.
I know, but I can't sleep.
Hey, that's great.
Thanks. When I meet
a new Pokemon...
I sketch him in this book.
Can I take a look?
Mm-hmm.
Hmm.
Oh, these are amazing!
This is like
a handmade Pokedex.
That's this machine that
has pictures of Pokemon.
I guess you know a lot
about the future, huh, Ash?
At least more than I do.
Yeah, I guess so...
but I'm sure glad I'm not stuck
in it like you are.
Oh, hey, I'm sorry.
Hey, I didn't mean
to make you feel bad, Sam.
Honest, I didn't.
That's OK.
I think I'll like
living in the future...
but it'll take
some getting used to.
Yeah. Probably.
But then I think about my mother
worrying about me...
and wondering where I am.
And I wonder
if she still wonders.
Oh. Yeah, me, too.
Hey, what about your mom, Ash?
I bet she worries about you...
when you're out on
your Pokemon journey.
Yeah, she worries, I guess.
Maybe that's just what moms do.
Mm.
Thinking about my mom...
gets me thinking
about her cooking.
Hey, I have something.
Huh?
Diana's grandmother made this...
but that was about
40 years ago.
Still looks
pretty fresh, though.
-Mm.
It's great!
Tastes like it was
made yesterday.
Pika?
Bi? Bi?
What's the matter, Pikachu?
Hey, Ash, look.
Huh?
Oh.
Oh, cool.
Wow.
Look at all the Butterfree.
I hope you'll be free, Sam.
Huh?
I mean, to go back in time.
Oh.
-Oh.
Free!
Wait for me!
Bi! Bi!
Pika!
Ah. Whoa.
Oh, cool.
Pika!
Bi!
Well, the village
is real close now.
Bi! Bi!
Look!
Pika!
Bi-i!
Bi! Bi!
Bi!
Thought you'd gotten rid of us...
didn't you, twerps?
But Team Rocket doesn't
give up so easily!
Not you again.
All right...
we ain't leaving
without that Celebi.
Pikachu!
Nice try!
Togepi!
Oh!
Bi!
Celebi!
This ought to calm you down.
Bi!
Hey!
Pika-pi!
Dark Ball, go!
-Aah!
Celebi is mine.
Let it go!
Stupid kids.
Aah! Hey! Aah!
Pika!
-Whoa!
-Aah!
Don't worry. I got ya.
Aah!
I think that Dark Ball
belongs to me.
Aah--aah!
Ash!
-Pika-pi!
-Toge!
Huh?
Don't waste your time.
It's too late to save
your friend Celebi.
Stantler.
Because the sweet little
Pokemon you used to know...
doesn't exist anymore.
Here, see for yourself!
Celebi, get rid of them all!
Aah!
Pika!
I don't understand.
If Celebi's their friend,
I'd hate to see their enemies.
Excellent.
You're very strong, Celebi.
Now show me even
more of your power!
[Laughs]
With a Pokemon like you,
no one will ever stop me!
Celebi.
Celebi's building a nasty nest.
Oh, no!
Oh.
Oh, what is that?
I don't know.
Grandma.
We'd better go find out.
Right.
Mm...uhh.
Uhh!
Celebi! Uhh!
I've gotta--
Uhh!
Take it easy, Ash.
You might be hurt.
Hey!
Hi, guys! Just stay
right where you are.
We're coming down to get you!
Diana!
I can't believe
they found us!
Uhh, this is awful.
Forcing the Spirit
of the Forest...
to destroy the forest.
This is just despicable.
Do you think Jessie's
going to be all right?
Yeah, but I ain't so sure
about Celebi. Heh.
Ha ha ha ha ha ha!
Uh, excuse me,
Mr. Masked Person...
but could you let me
out of here?
Not yet. I need a witness who
can report back to Giovanni.
I want the head
of Team Rocket to know...
just how powerful Celebi is...
and how powerful I am, too.
Celebi, the time has come!
I'm very impressed.
You and Celebi
are extremely powerful!
Now just get me down
from here...
and I'll recommend you
for a big promotion...
when you give Celebi
to the boss.
Ha ha ha ha ha!
I control the most powerful
Pokemon in the world!
Why would I want to give
something that valuable...
to the boss?
What do you mean?
Now the boss
has to be afraid of me...
because Celebi gives me
the power to destroy him!
With Celebi,
I can rule Team Rocket...
and the whole world,
if I want to!
Ah ha ha ha ha ha ha!
What is that?
The evil Celebi
must've created it.
Pika?
Celebi!
Pika!
Oh, you again.
Celebi, get rid of 'em now!
Celebi!
Hold on! Uhh!
Is everybody OK?
I think so.
I'm still alive.
SAM: Me, too.
ASH: So am l.
Pika!
Grandma!
I'm alive, too, but just barely.
Hmm.
We have to stop
that horrible thing.
We're no match for
that big twig monster.
I know.
Poor Jessie.
All right, Pikachu,
try a Thunder Bolt.
Pika...
chuuu!
Celebi, get rid
of these children!
Pika!
Celebi, do it now!
Huh?
Toge?
The north wind.
The north wind saved them.
Suicune!
Uhh! Uhh!
Aah!
Hmm.
You must've come here
to help us out.
Then we need you to take us
to Celebi right away!
Heh heh heh heh.
Nows my chance...
to capture a Suicune, too!
Tyranitar, Hyper Beam!
We've gotta stop him!
Go, Onix! Uhh!
Hmm.
Ohh.
Celebi.
Celebi!
Good work, Onix. Return!
Heh heh heh heh.
Playtime is over, children.
Get them, Celebi.
Be careful. This thing could
destroy the whole forest!
And the Pokemon!
Suicune!
Good job!
Now teach 'em a lesson!
Ha ha ha ha ha ha!
That's what'll happen...
to anybody
who tries to stop me!
Pika!
Huh?
You have to be careful.
Celebi's just above us.
Thanks a lot.
Let's go, Sam.
-Right.
-Pika!
Uhh! Where are you going?
Get me out of here! Hey!
Celebi, you have to stop!
You're supposed
to protect the forest...
not destroy it!
Celebi!
Bi!
Bi.
Bi! Bi-i-i-i!
What are you
waiting for, Celebi?
They're your enemies!
Bi!
-Uhh!
-Pikachu!
Celebi, we're not your enemies!
We're trying to save you!
Pika!
Bi-i-i-i-i!
Try to remember!
Celebi...
you brought me with you
here to the future!
Celebi, destroy them!
Bi-i-i-i-i!
Huh?
Uh, where's it going?
Bi-i-i-i-i!
Celebi, it's me.
Don't you remember?
Bi. Bi.
Bi!
Pika!
Pika! Pika!
Look at me!
Bi.
Remember?
Pika!
Celebi, don't help that hunter.
Fight him.
-Aah!
-Pika!
Pika!
I won't give up!
Bi.
Hmm?
Huh?
What in the--
What's going on?
Aah!
Bi.
Huh?
Bi?
Celebi!
Pika!
We did it!
Oh, no! Aah!
Aah! Aah!
Meowth, look!
There goes Jessie!
Bi!
Oh, no!
Bi-i-i-i!
Oh, Ash is all right!
Yeah, and so is Sam.
They've got Celebi, too.
Huh?
What's wrong?
I don't know.
Something bad.
The water.
Get it into the water!
ASH: It's not working.
But why not?
The forest is hurt.
The water's tainted.
The lake is dying.
But then-wait a second.
Suicune has the power to make
the water clean again.
Suicune,
if you clean the water...
we can save Celebi.
The legend's true.
The north wind
saved the lake.
Celebi, the water's clean again.
Pika.
It isn't working.
All right, then.
We'll keep trying.
See? These are those berries
we found in the forest.
Here you go.
Uhh.
Uh...
Heh. That's OK.
Uhh.
Uh, Celebi?
Celebi, you can't die!
Pika?
Celebi didn't do
anything wrong.
It was a human being
who forced Celebi...
to destroy the forest.
Celebi never even had a choice.
Uhh! And now--uhh--
it can't have a choice.
Now it's too late to choose
'cause Celebi is gonna die!
Toge-to?
Huh?
Pika.
-Ohh.
-Grandma.
I know that sound.
The Voice of the Forest.
Ahh.
Bi?
Bi!
Bi.
Bi?
Ohh.
Pika!
Bi.
Bi?
Bi!
Bi-i-i-i-i!
-Ha ha.
-Togepi!
The spirits of
the future and the past...
can travel through time
as well...
and so they've all come.
They've must've sensed...
that their friend
was in trouble.
Pika.
And now they're here to help.
Ha.
Bi.
Bi! Bi!
Bi-i-i-i-i-i!
Bi!
Bi! Bi!
Bi? Bi.
Pika!
Bi! Bi! Bi!
Bi!
Pika-pi!
-Ha ha!
-Hey!
Bi! Bi!
Bi!
Bi-i-i-i-i!
Bi! Bi!
It's the hunter!
And now I have everything I need
to rule the world!
Give Celebi back!
Bi-i-i-i!
Ha ha ha ha!
Celebi!
Get off me, kid!
Give it back!
Pikachu, use your Thunder Bolt!
Pika!
Uhh! No! Wait! Pikachu!
Aaaaah!
Pika-pi!
Pikachu! Uhh!
Aaaaah!
Pika!
Uhh! Uhh!
Huh?
Pika.
-Oh. Ha ha.
-Bi!
Celebi.
Aaaaaah! [Echoes]
Ash!
-Hey!
-Togepi!
Huh? Huh!
You tried to destroy
our forest, mister...
and we don't take kindly
to that kind of behavior.
Scizor, Sneasel!
Uhh!
This is all a mistake--
a big misunderstanding.
Ohh!
Weedle!
I think the Pokemon
understand perfectly.
Ah ha ha ha ha ha!
Suicune!
Thank you!
Maybe we'll see you
again someday.
Pika!
Good-bye, Suicune!
Bi.
-Huh?
-Bi?
Uh...
Bi-i-i-i-i!
It looks like
Celebi's getting ready...
to travel back in time...
and I think it wants
to take you along, Sam.
Can you really
bring me back, Celebi?
Bi!
Looks like
you're goin' home, Sam.
Yeah, I guess so.
Don't worry.
It won't matter...
'cause wherever you are,
or whenever you are--heh--
we'll always be friends.
Bi.
Thank you, Ash.
You're a great friend.
Thank you all
for everything.
Maybe I'll see you
again...someday!
I knowwe will!
I'll see you!
Good-bye!
Pikachu!
You were right,
Professor.
That Pokemon we saw
was a Suicune.
Yeah, and we met
a Celebi, too.
It even traveled through time.
Well, well,
it sounds like you saw...
some very rare and highly
unusual Pokemon out there.
Huh? What's the matter, Ash?
Uh...
You haven't said
a single word yet.
Didn't you enjoy your little
adventure in the forest, too?
Oh, sure, Professor.
But, you see...
I met this Pokemon trainer...
and we got to be friends.
But l--
I just don't think...
I'm ever gonna
see him again.
He decided to go back...
to where he came from,
Professor--
to another time.
Pika.
I wouldn't worry, Ash.
Oh?
True friendships can withstand
the test of time...
and I have a feeling
this one will.
I'm sure you and Sammy
will be friends forever.
Mm. Heh heh.
Thanks, Professor.
I think so, too.
Pikachu!
I think we'd better
get going.
Yeah, I don't want
to miss the boat again.
We'll tell you everything...
when we get
to Pallet Town, OK?
Fine. I'm looking forward to it.
Hey.
What's the matter, Misty?
Howd Professor Oak
know Sammy's name?
We never mentioned
it to him.
Yeah, that's right.
[Toot]
Pika!
Professor Oak's amazing!
He knows everything!
Pika!
Pikachu!
Hmm. It seems like
it happened only yesterday.
This is amazing.
This wonderful water's
washed away...
all my annoying aches
and pains.
I could just float along
like this forever.
Ahoy!
-Huh?
Jessie, thank goodness
you're safe.
Hurry up. Climb aboard.
What took you so long?
What have you been doing?
We had to wait
till it was safe.
But now the coast is clear.
Oh, good.
Hey, guys,
I feel all tingly.
So do l.
Heh. Isn't it fabulous?
Looks like Team Rocket's
floating away.
Yo, man,
we forgot to vamp out.
This ain't
the end of the song?
-No.
-Oh, man.
Translation and subtitles:
Blake_rsh (Mormegil.inc)