Pocket Monsters.
Pokemon for short.
They are this world's strange,
mysterious creatures.
The number of species are 100,
200,
300...
No, possibly even more than that.
Pokemon and humans put their powers
together as friends and partners.
In other times, they face off
against opponents.
They exist all over the world.
This boy is Satoshi of Masara Town.
Aiming to become a Pokemon Master,
he battles and catches them.
His journey of training continues.
With as many meetings as there are Pokemon,
and with just as many partings,
many stories have been woven in this way.
Yes.
It has been this way since a long,
long time ago.
A long time ago...
In an era before monster balls had
come into existence...
Aaron-sama.
Aaron-sama!
I can hear you, Lucario.
An incredible number of troops are coming!
If we get caught up in them, our castle won't stand a chance!
At this rate...
The fight can't be stopped anymore.
I cannot leave this place.
As Queen, I will share the same fate as the castle.
Leen-sama.
Aaron-sama!
Aaron-sama.
Lucario.
Your eyes...
I am fine.
Leave this place.
I've abandoned the castle.
I can't return ever again.
What are you saying?
Please wait!
Aaron-sama!
Why?
The tree...
The Tree of World's Origin is weeping.
Aaron!
Queen Leen believed
that the Wave-user Aaron had used the power
of the Tree of World's Origin where Mew is said to live.
And then what?
The hatred and anger that shrouded the land subsided.
The Pokemon returned to their respective homes.
And so peace again returned to this land.
That's good!
And so, Aaron became known as the "Hero of the Wave."
Tell me the Hero of the Wave story again sometime!
Sure.
And now...
Pocket Monsters
Theatrical                          Edition
Mew and the Hero of the Wave
Lucario
Aiming to become a Pokemon Master, Satoshi and the others continues their journey,
and they have arrived here, at Aldoran Castle.
They are here to participate in a festival commemorating the Hero of the Wave, Aaron.
Whoever wins the Pokemon battle in the castle...
will be named the Hero of the Wave for that year.
When you go to an event in a castle, you have to wear old-fashioned garments!
I don't have any!
It says that they have some prepared in the castle.
Really?
I wonder if they have the hero's outfit too!
We should dress Pikachu up too!
That might be good!
We can pick from any of these?
Which one should I wear?
I can't decide!
Where's the hero's outfit?
I'll take... uh...
Ta-da!
How's this, Pikachu?
Onee-chan?
That is correct.
It suits you.
Doesn't it?
I'm a hero!
How's this, Pikachu?
This might be cute!
It looks good on you!
The Pokemon Battle is starting soon.
All right.
Pikachu, let's go!
While everyone is preoccupied with that,
we'll take all the Pokemon in the castle!
We need to change clothes first.
What should I pick?
Hurry up!
This is so wonderful!
So fast!
The Queen of this country
and Lady of Aldoran Castle...
Eileen-sama!
The Queen...
This might be wonderful!
In tribute to the Hero of the Wave, Aaron, who saved the world,
we will now begin the Pokemon Battle!
hikaru daichi ni tachi
Standing on this shining land
towa no batoru chikau
I vow to battle eternally
egao choppiri namida
A smile with a bit of tears
minna wasurenai yo
I won't forget any of you
omoi wa kyori wo tobikoe
My feelings leap over the distance
ima kimi ni todoku kitto
They'll reach you now, surely
Oh yeah!!
GANGAN susume kaze kitte
Intensely move ahead and cut through the wind
GANGAN iku ze saigo made
Intensely I'll go all the way to the end
kanzen nenshou
Completely ablaze
YES, I'm OK!!
Oh yeah!!
DONDON pawaa moriagatte
Steadily my power rises
DONDON yuuki waite kuru
Steadily courages bursts forth
kagari nai chikara wo shinjiyou
Let's believe in limitless strength
Oh yeah!!
GANGAN susume kaze kitte
Intensely move ahead and cut through the wind
GANGAN iku ze saigo made
Intensely I'll go all the way to the end
kanzen nenshou
Completely ablaze
YES, I'm OK!!
Oh yeah!!
DONDON sakusen hirameite
Steadily a plan comes to mind
DONDON atakku tomaranai
Steadily my attacks become unstoppable
kanzen muketsu da
Absolute perfection
Are you OK?
Oh yeah!!
GUNGUN pawaa moriagatte
Steadily my power continues to rise
GUNGUN yuuki waite kuru
Steadily my courages bursts forth
kagayaku gooru wo kakenukero
Run through the shining goal
Manyula is unable to battle!
Pikachu wins!
Therefore, this year's Hero of the Wave is Satoshi of Masara Town!
All right! We did it!
Pikachu!
You are Pikachu are the best partners, aren't you?
A woman?!
I'm Kid.
Nice to meet you.
I'm Satoshi.
I am called Takeshi.
I would like to become the best partner with a beautiful lady like...
Right, right.
Ow, ow, ow!
Let's look over there.
This is the Hero's Staff, which belonged to Hero of the Wave, Aaron.
Only the one who wins the battle at the festival
and is chosen as the hero is allowed to hold this.
Awesome.
Now, please accept this, Satoshi.
Okay.
So this is the Hero of the Wave's staff...
Why?
Did you say something?
No.
In commemoration of the Hero who protected this country, Aaron,
let the festivities begin!
K... Kid-san!
M-M-May I have a dance with you?
Of course.
I'm honored!
You don't have to be so nervous.
I'll lead you.
I'm so moved!
Oh yeah!
All right.
Everyone, join the party!
Excuse me for a moment.
There!
All right! I'm going to have a feast!
Wait there.
You can't do that.
The Hero must not leave his seat.
No way...
Isn't this our chance to steal the Pokemon?
I want to dance more!
I've finally got a chance to wear such a nice dress!
Excuse me.
Your dancing is quite skillful.
N-No...
What a man! I could be in love!
Feels good!
Have we met somewhere before?
N-No, we couldn't have...
What a feast! This is the best!
Takeshi-kun, could you get me a drink?
Of course!
Just wait a moment!
It's morning there already, isn't it?
Have you finished breakfast, Banks?
I had a croissant and coffee.
You should have a salad too.
I think I'll have a vegetable juice.
Make sure you put celery in it.
That's a little...
You can't just eat things you like.
Sorry to trouble you.
Have you finished dinner, my lady?
It's a castle party, so I'm sure they have quite a selection.
I'll save it for later.
It can wait until I'm done with work.
What a pity.
I'm used to it.
Besides that, transfer a map of the castle to me.
Would you mind if I send it after I shower?
No way.
I'm holding off dinner for this.
Then please wait 30 seconds.
20 seconds.
As you wish.
Sorry I kept you waiting.
I shall transfer it now.
Thanks.
Don't push yourself.
Right, right. I know.
Chief butler, Banks-sama.
Those could be our rivals.
Where did Pikachu and the others go?
Gonbe?
Um...
Err...
Could you be...
Grand swing!
Amazing.
I found you.
Put this locator beacon on Mew, got it?
It's you guys!
It's Mew!
They're overdoing it.
They only need to put on the beacon...
What?
You sure have a lot of free time.
You guys have a lot of free time too.
Pikachu!
And Nyasu too!
Mew?
Instant teleportation?
Pikachu, you're heavier than you look...
You guys always get caught in the moment.
This is trouble.
So someone had this hundreds of years ago.
It feels so strange.
Why?
I heard it again.
We will now begin the evening party.
The Hero of the Wave will see it off.
Now, the Hero's pose!
The Hero's pose?
Why?
What's wrong?
There's something in this!
Aaron-sama!
Why did you abandon the castle?
Telepathy?
Why?!
What are you saying?
That's...
Lucario.
Lucario?
He was the Hero, Aaron's, Pokemon.
Yes.
He was in here?
Is this Aldoran Castle?
Lucario.
This is the castle where we'll both live starting from today.
The training will be tough.
Yes, sir.
I intend to teach you everything I know as a Wave-user.
Aaron-sama!
The Wave is within us.
Believe in your Wave.
Lucario.
Leen-sama!
I am not Leen.
Queen Leen is my ancestor.
My name is Eileen.
You have been asleep all this time.
I've been asleep?
Time has passed.
Impossible...
This room was ours just yesterday...
It might feel like it was yesterday to you, however...
For us, it happened long ago.
We heard that you disappeared within the battle.
What happened exactly?
Two troops closed in on us
and attempted to get this castle caught up in the fight.
I was sent out as a scout.
But...
It was already too late to stop the fight.
The Hero Aaron stopped that, didn't he?
What?
According to the legend, Aaron saved the castle.
That couldn't...
Is that wrong?
Aaron-sama abandoned the castle and ran.
And he sealed me away...
This might be different from the legend.
What's this all about?
There's no way to tell the truth now.
What should I do?
Lucario.
You're free to stay here until you've sorted out your feelings.
Aldoran Castle welcomes you.
My Queen.
I'm grateful.
I'm Satoshi.
Did you mistake me for someone?
Aaron?
Oh, because of these clothes?
No.
Your Wave is the same as Aaron's.
We haven't seen that Pokemon before, have we?
They said that Pokemon's been sealed away for hundreds of years!
I want! I want him!
There's trouble!
Mew was...!
What's wrong?
Mew was...
Mew was here!
My!
So this boy saw Mew!
Those who see Mew are said to be granted happiness.
That's not it!
What is it?!
Mew disappeared with Pikachu and Nyasu!
Mew?
A Pokemon?
This is Lucario, a Pokemon the Hero Aaron had sealed away.
He just woke up.
No way!
Did you really see Mew?
Are you mistaking things?
I saw it too.
From a tower I was touring, I saw Mew take Pikachu and Nyasu,
then it transformed into Pidgeot and flew away.
Why did Mew do that?
It was probably a prank.
Mew occasionally appears in this castle and plays pranks.
He often takes toys, but he's never returned them.
He took Nyasu too?
We planned to steal Pokemon, but our own got stolen instead.
Well, that's not what I meant...
Please tell me where Mew is!
I'm going to find Pikachu!
That appears to be a large tree,
but it is actually an enormous, stone mountain.
That might be amazing.
We call that the Tree of World's Origin.
The Tree of World's Origin.
Mew lives there.
All right.
But Mew has the ability to transform into any Pokemon,
so it rarely shows its true form to anyone.
So how can we find it?
Lucario can read the Wave of all things.
He is said to be able to guide the Hero even in bleak darkness.
Lucario, you will be able to find Mew, right?
Yes.
Will you lend your power to Satoshi?
If the Queen wishes for it.
Satoshi-kun.
I'll lend you a hand too.
Kid-san!
You're that adventurer, Kid Summers!
I've been next to you all this time, but I never realized it!
I have failed!
I am deeply, deeply regretful!
I'm so honored to meet you!
She's famous?
Certainly!
According to my ranking book,
she's quite high up!
The record for the quicket trip around the world in a hot-air balloon,
the record for the deepest independent submarine dive,
the longest solo space walk, and it goes on!
She holds various world records.
She's a super woman!
Wow!
I'll feel safe with someone like you around!
Please!
I would also like you to help.
Actually,
I came here to go to the Tree of World's Origin
and unlock its mystery.
Is that so?!
I'd go with you even if you didn't ask.
Roger!
Then you will depart tomorrow morning.
Pikachu must be playing with Mew right now.
I hope so...
What are you doing?!
Be quiet. It's only because you were standing behind me.
I'm counting on you tomorrow.
I absolutely have to find Pikachu.
Are you that Pikachu's master?
Master?
It's not like that.
Pikachu and I are friends.
Friends?
If your friend disappeared, you'd look for him too, right?
I'm guiding you on the Queen's orders.
What's with him?
May the Wave protect them.
It's as if we're in the clouds.
Lucario's fine in this, isn't he?
He's using the Wave.
Wave?
Hey, didn't Lucario say that Satoshi's Wave was the same as Aaron's?
That's right.
Just what is a Wave?
Everything has this thing called a Wave within them.
Then there's a Wave within me too!
People normally call them something like chi or auras, right?
And Lucario can see those!
Yes.
In legendary times, people who mastered the Wave were called Wave-users.
Aaron was one of them.
If this Aaron's Wave was the same as Satoshi's...
Maybe Satoshi can use the Wave!
Maybe!
Maybe not.
No good.
What's that...
He'll wake up eventually.
It's all done!
This is Satoshi's.
Here.
This is Masato's.
This is Haruka's.
Here!
This is Kid-sa...
Huh?
What Pokemon is this?
Hey!
That's Kid-san's!
You made it cry!
Bullying's not nice!
This is Usohachi!
It specializes in fake crying!
Hey!
Don't take other people's belongings.
Have this instead.
This feels kind of nice.
What was that?
It's huge!
Geysers.
We'll have to wait until they calm down.
That's...
A hotspring?
So relaxing...
You followed us.
Why don't you come in with us?
Usohachi!
Usohachi's a rock type, so it's not good with water.
No way!
I wish Pikachu could be with us in this hotspring too.
He'd definitely be happy.
Yeah.
Lucario.
Put your feet in too.
It feels nice.
I'll pass.
Don't hold back.
Then...
Right?
Yes.
Lucario!
Come in!
It feels great!
What's with him?
Maybe he doesn't like hotsprings?
Satoshi!
Over here!
What's up, Haruka?
Look there!
Is that a flower?
I'll take a look.
Satoshi's pretty flexible.
Like an Aipom.
You shouldn't pick out the flowers from the mountain.
Sorry.
Well, it couldn't be helped.
Let's re-plant it later.
Yeah.
This is a Time flower.
Time flower?
This flower shows a miracle of time for Wave-users.
Will this be okay?
Sure.
Haruka, give it to me.
Here.
What?
What was that?
It's a Time flower.
A Time flower?
According to the legends, it reveals a miracle of time for Wave-users...
So this is what they meant.
How mysterious.
The miracle must've happened because Satoshi and Aaron share the same Wave.
Pikachu and I weren't like this when we first met.
Is that so?
We didn't get along at all.
I got shocked by his electricity so many times.
How did you become friends?
Tell us!
I want to know how you and Pikachu became friends too, Satoshi!
One day on our journey, a flock of Onisuzume attacked us...
and we became friends thanks to overcoming that hardship together.
So that's what happened.
From then on, Pikachu trusted me,
and I trust Pikachu too.
You should be able to do it too.
I trust you, Lucario.
All right, that's enough!
What's with all this trust?!
People can't be trusted!
Wait a second!
Are you talking about me?
If it becomes inconvenient for you, you might abandon Pikachu.
I'll never abandon Pikachu!
How would you know?
Besides, someone called a legendary hero
couldn't possibly have abandoned his Pokemon!
You're just spouting nonsense!
What?!
Stop it!
But this guy...
Maybe Pikachu ran off because he was fed up with staying with a master like you.
What did you say?!
Satoshi!
Cut it out!
Stop fighting!
They've started fighting among themselves.
Who cares about that? I'm hungry.
I'll go fi...
No!
Don't open it...
Satoshi, you said too much.
But...
He said Pikachu ran away from me.
That's because you said some rude things to Lucario.
Yeah.
I bet you've never had this before.
Here.
It's called chocolate.
Chocolate?
They say it's good to eat sweet things when you're upset or irritated.
Right?
I'm at peace...
It's about time you got back to that brat boy and the others, isn't it?
He wants to play some more.
Wait until the morning.
Pikachu.
Lucario, what's wrong?
This is where I was sealed away.
Why?
A Time flower...
Aaron-sama!
Stop it, Lucario!
These aren't real!
That was scary.
This was a battlefield in the past.
Lucario was telling the truth.
Does that mean the legend was wrong?
But Aaron didn't seem like a bad person.
Maybe he sealed Lucario to protect him from those troops?
Why?
Sorry.
I sad all those rude things without knowing your feelings...
Satoshi.
Never abandon Pikachu.
I know.
Lucario!
Hey, what's wrong, Lucario?
Regirock!
What's going on?
Everyone, this way!
Let's go!
In here.
I wonder if they reached the Tree of World's Origin.
Why did Regirock come out and attack us?
It told us not to get closer.
It was a warning?
It might be protecting the Tree of World's Origin from intruders.
This is...
The lowest level of the Tree of World's Origin, isn't it?
Then, Pikachu is...
Above us.
All right. I'm coming, Pikachu!
Do you know where you're going?
Either way, we're just going up!
Right, Lucario?
For now.
All right!
Ah, Satoshi!
What are those?
Survey modules.
Survey modules?
I'm gathering more data around here.
Banks, time for work.
Wake up.
I've been waiting, my lady.
Look.
The Tree of World's Origin has, for thousands...
No, for tens of thousands of years, protected Pokemon here from outside interference.
Congratulations on the new discovery.
Save the celebrations for when we solve everything.
Yes, ma'am.
I'm counting on you to analyze the data.
As you wish.
I'm getting excited!
Me too!
I'm getting pretty excited too!
This is a treasure mountain swarming with rare Pokemon!
No, an underground treasure!
This stone mountain is alive!
It is a mineral lifeform created by nature.
The Tree of World's Origin has been living off of light energy for tens of thousands of years.
An amazing discovery!
Yeah.
But...
The mystery hasn't been solved yet.
Mew must have some connection to the Tree of World's Origin.
Hey!
Pikachu!
I'm over here!
What?
Pikachu!
If you're there, answer!
I'm coming now!
Regice!
We're not enemies!
We're only here to look for a friend!
It doesn't look like someone you can convince.
Let's go back!
Lucario!
What's going on...
Everyone, run!
What's wrong?
It's Regice!
It's here!
We'll find another path!
In here!
Someone!
Save us!
Team Rocket?
I don't care if it's brat boy or whatever!
Do something about those guys!
Everyone, this way!
Registeel's here too!
That's...
Musashi! Kojiro!
Musashi, wait up!
Geez, you're such a slowpoke.
I'll leave you behind!
Behind you!
Now wait here.
Come on, we're not kids.
That won't...
W-What's this?!
Go, Sabonea!
Sabonea, Pin Missile!
It didn't work?
What's that?!
I really don't like this feeling!
Musashi!
Kojiro...
Chiriin!
Get away from here!
What's going on here?
They're here again!
It's coming!
Now, while we still have time!
Okay.
Banks, what is this?
This is likely what can be seen as the Tree of World's Origin's immune system.
It's trying to get rid of the bacteria inside it.
Bacteria?
You mean us?
No way!
That's the proof that this Tree of World's Origin is alive.
Banks, find an escape route for us.
I am.
Wait for a little longer.
Watch out!
Lucario!
Pokemon aren't treated as bacteria.
I'll hold them back.
Kid-san, take care of everyone.
I got it.
That way!
Lucario.
Until you meet with Pikachu...
I'll stay with you.
Thanks.
Jupitol, Bullet Seed!
Heigani, Bubblebeam!
All right.
Let's go!
This way, this way!
What?
Masato!
Onee-chan!
You guys, run!
Takeshi!
Masato!
Everyone, come out!
How horrible...
Pikachu's voice!
Satoshi?
Pikachu!
Wait right there!
Kid-san!
Pikachu!
Satoshi!
I met up with Pikachu.
Pikachu, this is Lucario.
He guided us all the way here.
Mew!
Mew just wanted to play!
Nyasu!
Thanks.
Regice.
We should get out of here.
Let's go!
Heigani!
Jupitol!
Kid-san, what about the others?
Everyone was sucked up by those things...
Musashi and Kojiro too?
Oh no!
This way!
My lady, the escape route is right above you!
Roger!
Sunlight!
We'll make it!
It's above this!
Lucario!
Satoshi.
You guys get out of here.
Pikachu, sorry.
Just when I met up with you...
This tree sees us as intruders...
Satoshi!
Pikachu!
Okay!
Okay, I got it!
Kid-san, just what...
Mew told the tree that you guys weren't bacteria.
Mew did?
This Tree of World's Origin and Mew share their powers
and live together in symbiosis.
Mew.
Thanks.
Mew!
He's heating up.
Just when I thought we were saved...
Doesn't this seem kind of bad?
Let's find Nyasu and get out of here!
OW!!
Kojiro?
Everyone, come back!
My lady.
There is an abnormality in the Tree of World's Origin's life signs.
It seems so.
There's a disturbance in its energy flow.
What do you mean?
The sudden activity within the immune system might have caused a great deal of damage.
At this rate, if the energy flow stops,
the Tree of World's Origin will collapse!
My Queen, are you all right?
I am fine.
But...
I'm worried about the children.
Mew and the Tree of World's Origin are one.
That's why when the tree is weak,
Mew is also...
Is he telling us to come with him?
This is...
Could it be?
Aaron-sama!
This is...
I see!
Aaron came here by himself after sealing away Lucario.
This has to be the Tree of World's Origin's heart.
A Time flower.
Come out, Mew!
Mew.
I know that you and this tree are one.
Please, lend me your power!
The Wave is within me!
Take my Wave!
Aaron sacrificed his own life to stop the fight.
So this was the truth.
Aaron-sama.
You want me to use my power to save the tree this time?
All right, I'll...
Wait, Lucario.
If you use your Wave here, then you'll follow the same fate as Aaron did.
I know.
Lucario.
The Wave is within me!
My Wave isn't enough by itself?
If my Wave is the same as Aaron's, then...
What?
I should be able to do it too...
Don't, Satoshi!
If you do this, then you'll also...
If we don't do this now, then this tree will collapse,
and all the Pokemon below will die!
Satoshi...
I'll do whatever I can!
Leave the rest to me!
Lucario!
The Wave is within me!
Thanks, Mew.
That's good.
You're all better!
The tree's life signs have returned to normal.
Everything's fine now.
Yeah.
Banks, keep everything here confidential.
You won't publicize it?
Put it away carefully.
As you wish.
Lucario!
Satoshi...
Lucario.
I'm sorry.
Aaron-sama.
I didn't...
I didn't have a choice but to seal you away.
If I hadn't...
You would've followed me no matter what...
...and followed the same fate as me.
Of course!
Meaningless fights...
and throwing away lives...
Just myself will be enough.
But...
I have no regrets.
In that castle...
I was able to live such beautiful days with you and Leen-sama.
That's what it means to live.
I doubted you...
Thank you...
Lucario.
Every day I spent with you...
was a lot of fun...
Aaron-sama!
Lucario.
If I could, once more...
I'd like to see you one more time.
My friend...
Aaron-sama!
I was foolish.
Lucario.
That's not it!
You're a great Wave-user!
Satoshi.
Lucario!
Hang in there!
Don't die!
I won't be dying.
I'll be... going back to Aaron-sama's... side...
Hey, everyone!
Satoshi!
Pikachu!
Kid-san!
You made it out okay!
Yeah!
Kid-sama, I'm so glad you're safe!
Where's Lucario?
He...
He went back to his friend's side.
Did he...
It can't be...
The Wave is within me.
atarashii maku ake
A new curtain rises
toomawari shita kedo
We've come about a roundabout way
yatto meguri aetanda
But we finally met
kusubutteta kimochi ni
On my smouldering feelings
mahou wo kakete kureta
You cast a magic spell
omoi tobira wo akeyou
Let's open that heavy door
iza ikou
Come on, let's go!
bouken no hajimari
It's the beginning of an adventure
hora tobidasou
Look, let's jump out there!
ano sora no mukougawa e
To the other end of that sky
Lucario managed to meet Aaron.
egakidasu mirai zu
The map of the future I imagine
kimi to nara itsu datte
If I'm with you, I'll always
kitto omoi no mama da
Do as we please
konnan ni tachimukau
Facing these hardships
makenai tsuyoi booru wo
This ball of unrelenting strength
motte aruite ikou
Let's carry it and walk out
sou sa koko kara
That's right! Everything began
subete ga hajimatta yo
Right here
konna daichi wo
On this land
yurugasu hodo shinjite
We'll trust so much that it shakes
donna chiisana
No matter how small
yume datte nakusanai
Dreams are, we won't lose them
sonna sekai wo
In the world out there
nakama tachi ga matteru
Our friends are waiting
toki ni wa chotto namida porotto
Sometimes a few tears plop out
dechau yoru ni wa
On nights like that
hitori de jitto nayamazu honto
Without sitting still and worrying
kaketsukeru kara
I'll come running
mizu kusa denki
Water, Grass, Electric
mushi tori gasu
Bug, Bird, Gas
iwa koori honoo
Rock, Ice, Fire
jimen hikou esupaa
Ground, Flying, Psychic
noomaru kakutou minna
Normal, Fighting, all of them
tomodachi dakara
Are my friends, so...
sou sa koko kara
That's right! Everything began
subete ga hajimatta yo
Right here
konna daichi wo
On this land
yurugasu hodo shinjite
We'll trust so much that it shakes
minna honto wa
Everyone, in reality
samishii no sa hitori ja
Is lonely when they're by themselves
konna choushi de
At this pace
nakama ga dekitekundakara
I'll just keep on making friends
dondon
Rapidly
yuuki
Courage
waite
Comes forth
dandan
Gradually
yuusha
Heroes
minna
Everyone