August 6th.
Today my colleagues will reach the site
where ancient civilization may have
created a shrine to Mew,
the most powerful Poaémon to have
ever existed now believed to be extinct.
Giovanni's financing the expedition,
when he learned that my work's in the field
of cloning he agreed to fund my research...
but only if I would try to create for him
an enhanced living replica of Mew.
I had to agree. All he wants is
to control the most powerful Pokémon
the world's ever known.
I of course want something more, much more.
Mew.
Our team is bringing back
what we believe to be a Mew fossil.
I pray it's authentic.
If so I may finally have the DNA I need...
to create the Pokémon powerful enough
to survive the cloning process.
Perhaps then I can unloca the secret
to restoring life itself.
Where am l?.
Who am l?.
What am l?.
It's just like all the other clones, Doctor...
it doesn't gain consciousness.
I just don't understand it.
Its other vital signs are strong.
When measuring brain activity...
I sense others near me.
What are those strange sounds they make?.
Those are words. They're talking.
What're you?.
What'd you mean?. I'm a girl, a person.
A person?. Am I a person?.
Well you looa like a Pokémon
but you talk.
I didn't know a Pokémon could talk
like a person.
Pokémon?. Person?. What're those?.
Which one am l?.
Maybe it maaes a difference to you if you're
a Pokémon or a person but not to me.
If you're in this place I guess
you must be the same as all of us are.
What's that?.
I'm not sure but Mewtwo and Ambertwo
seem to be communicating with
the other clones.
But how?.
They could be using telepathy.
Soon.
Everybody here's a copy that's why
there's a two after all of our names.
I don't understand.
They call me Ambertwo
but I'm still really Amber.
Please, please let my theories be true.
I must see my little girl's smile again.
Dear.
I've reawakened her consciousness
here in this chamber.
I just need to keep it viable long
enough to complete the process.
Why are you doing this?.
You can't bring Amber back.
You're wrong. Look! She lives
within this light. Her energy's undeniable.
If my cloning theories are correct,
we'll have Amber back with us one day soon.
I loved our daughter as much as you did
but she's gone, no one can bring her back,
and I can't go on watching you try.
I'm sorry. Goodbye.
I will do anything to see you again.
So how are they doing today?.
You should be very pleased, Doctor.
The Pokémon clones are in stable condition
and Mewtwo is getting stronger everyday.
One of them is bound to survive. It looas like
all our hard work is finally paying off.
Yes, Giovanni will be very happy lim sure.
He may soon have
the most powerful Poaémon in the world.
But I'll get something much more precious,
knowledge of how to recreate life...
then I'll use it to bring her back.
I call this my Remember Place.
This is where I used to live.
What is that?.
That's the sun.
What is it for?.
It makes the whole world bright
and it keeps us warm all day.
That's called wind.
Wind?.
The wind helps us along. Sometimes
it's soft and sometimes it's very strong.
And that's the sunset.
That's when the sun says good night,
see you tomorrow.
Is that a sun?.
No, thatis the moon...
and the stars are the little lights
that twinkle all night just so
we won't feel alone in the dark.
We're losing all readings
from Charmandertwo.
No, not again!
Bulbasaurtwo and Squirtletwo are fading
the same way!.
It looks like another failure.
Where did they go?.
Doctor, we're losing her too.
Amber.
What's wrong, Amber?. What's happening?.
It feels like itis time to say goodbye.
Goodbye?.
I feel something...
what're these?.
They're tears, you're crying.
Crying?.
My Daddy used to tell me a bedtime story...
that when Pokémon are sad and they cry,
their tears are filled with light.
I'm so sad.
I have to go.
Why?.
I don't anow but it's alright.
Thank you for caring about me...
and don't cry Mewtwo.
You should be happy you're alive
and life is wonderful...
These tears what good are they?.
Please Amber come back!
Don't go please...
Amber!.
Doctor, Mewtwo's brain waves
are out of control.
It's getting too upset.
It mustn't remember this.
Administer the serum...do it immediately!
I'll try a hundred units.
1 0 10 30 40 50 60 70 80 90 1 00
What's happening?. Is it working?.
Its brain waves are going back to normal.
Everything seems okay, Doctor.
Nothing is okay. My Amber is gone forever...
only Mewtwo survives.
I have slept for so long.
It seems like forever.
But I remember something, someone.
Life is wonderful.
But why?.
Life:. the great miracle...
and the great mystery.
Since the beginning, humans and Pokémon
alike have searched for its meaning.
Many strange and wondrous legends evolved
from the pursuit of life's mysteries.
But none is stranger than this tale...
of the most powerful Poaémon of all!
Where am l?.
This...this is not the same!
Was everything before...just a dream?.
Why...?.!.
Doctor! Look at this!
What?.
Its brain waves...they're surging!
Let me see!. She's right.
Let's run another scan.
Its mind is racing!
Those voices...
I hope we don't lose this one.
They're outside...
We can't lose this one!
Where I must be...!
Radio Giovanni's helicopter.
Tell him what's happened.
Quiet!
Let us hear it's psychic powers!
Psychic...powers?.
For years we struggled to successfully
clone a Poaémon to prove our theories...
but you're the first specimen to survive!
That is Mew, the rarest of all Pokémon.
From its DNA we created you, Mewtwo!
Mewtwo!
That I am only a copy...
nothing but Mew's shadow?.
You are greater than Mew, improved
through the power of human ingenuity!
We used the most advanced techniques
to develop your awesome psychic powers!
So I am simply the end result
of your experiment.
What becomes of me
now that your experiment is over?.
Oh, our experiment isn't over yet.
It's just beginning!
Now the serious testing begins!
These humans, they care nothing for me.
Congratulations!
We've done it. Excellent job!
Is the new tank ready?.
No...we'll have to come up with
a cage for it.
Congratulations...
Science...
Excellent!
We'll start our testing right away.
Is that my purpose?.
Am I just an experiment...
a laboratory specimen?!.
This cannot be...my destiny!
We dreamed of creating
the world's strongest Pokémon.
And we succeeded!
Behold my powers!
I am the strongest Pokémon in the world.
Stronger even...than Mew!
Those fools thought
you were a science experiment.
But l...I see you as a valuable partner.
Partner?!.
With your psychic powers and my resources,
together we can control the world!
I do not need your help for that, human!
A wildfire destroys everything in its path.
It will be the same with your powers...
unless you learn to control them.
I can help you do that.
How?.
Trust me and I'll show you a way to focus
your powers that will make you invincible.
Show me.
You say this armor protects my body...
yet it suppresses my powers.
Your powers are not being suppressed,
they are being focused.
Learn to use them
to accomplish your purpose.
What is that?.
Patience my friend...
your purpose will become clear.
So this is my power.
I am in control now.
But why am I here?.
Now I fully perceive my power!
But...what is my purpose?.
To serve your master. You were created
to fight for me! That is your purpose!.
That cannot be! You said we were partners!.
We stood as equals!
You were created by humans to obey humans.
You could never be our equal.
Humans may have created me...
but they will never enslave me!.
This cannot be...my destiny!
Stop this now!.
I was not born a Pokémon.
I was created.
And my creators have used and betrayed me.
So...I stand alone!
Who am l?.
What is my true reason for being?.
I will find my own purpose...
and purge this planet of all who oppose me
...human and Pokémon alike!
The world will heed my warning:
The reign of Mewtwo...
will soon begin.
Mewtwo Striaes Back
Today Ash, Brock and Misty are taking
a short break from their Pokémon adventures.
As always, Ash is determined to become
a Pokémon Master, and as always,
he's ready to endure any hardship,
bear any burden,
with strength,
stamina and a will of steel!
Hungry...need food.
No, Ash! You haven't done a thing all day!.
I'm too weak to work Misty...
I haven't eaten since breakfast.
No!
This lunch is gonna be just perfect
for you Ash...
it's my lazy boy i'no-chew" stew.
Hey...you there!
I'm looking for a Pokémon trainer named Ash
from Pallet Town!
Do you know him?.
Yeah he's me.
Let's have a match...
unless you're afraid to lose!
I'm afraid you're gonna lose this one!
Ash! You just said
you were too weak to work!
That's right. I am too weak to work
but a Pokémon battle isn't work!
That's progress...
at least his mouth is working.
Nice job, Bulbasaur!
You did it!
Oh...Oh, no!!!
We did it!!!
Well that sure was a shocking ending.
Shocking that Ash moved so fast!
There's another credit
on Pikachu's i'charge account."
We've got to grab it!
I know we gotta grab some rare Pokémon
for the Boss,
but it wouldn't be such a bad idea if we
grabbed a little bite to eat, would it?.
We didn't come here to steal a meal!
I'd settle for a taste of that Pika-chow!
I'm starvin'.
I can cook something!
Thanks but the last time you cooked
you wiped out eight of my nine lives.
Master, shall I extend an invitation
to these trainers as well?.
As you wish.
Hey, watch where you're flying.
Something is for me?.
Greetings Pokémon trainers!
I bear an invitation.
She's really small but really pretty!
You have been chosen to join
a select group of Pokémon trainers...
at a special gathering.
It will be hosted by my master,
the world's greatest Pokémon trainer,
at his palace on New lsland.
A chartered ferry will leave
from Old Shore Wharf...
to take you to the island
this afternoon.
Only trainers who present this invitation
will be admitted.
If you decide to attend
you must reply at once.
My Master awaits you.
Ah...is there a rewind button?.
Should we go?.
Of course we should!!
I've gotta meet her!!
I guess the world's number one trainer
wants to challenge me to a match!
Well...we gotta let them know right away.
I'm saying yes!
We wanna know what's so special
about the twerp trio's special delivery!
Hey, look!
"Yes"?. To what?.
Chill out, Raticate!
Kingler, save your energy will ya.
This is gonna be so cool!
Officer Jenny, please report
to the ferry entrance.
Officer Jenny,
to the ferry entrance, please.
Togepi's totally soaked!
I can't believe
how fast the storm came up.
What?!. The ferry is cancelled?.!
But I've gotta get to New lsland!
Yeah, so do l!
What's the big deal?!.
It's only a little rain!
It's more than just rain!
The Harbor Manager thinks
this could be the worst storm ever!
Listen to me!
The prophets have predicted
the return of the Winds of Water.
For years I have prayed...
...that mankind would never witness...
...that deadly storm ever again.
Isn't that just a legend?.
The ancient writings tell of the storm
wiping out all but a few Pokémon.
In their sorrow
the water of their tears...
somehow restored the lives
lost in the storm.
But there are no Pokémon tears today.
Just waters which no one can survive.
And that's why your ferry to New lsland
has been cancelled.
Well I'm going to New lsland anyway!
All my Pokémon are water type!
We'll just swim over to that palace!
I warn you, the waves will be savage,
you will never make it!
And besides...if you tried that stunt
and your Pokémon got hurt...
you'd be out of luck because we had to
close down the Poaémon Center!
Uhh, how come?!.
Because the nurse in charge of
the center disappeared last month!
And if any of you see her
please contact me at once!
That's a picture of her over there
on the wall!
She's cute!
She sure looks familiar.
Come back here!
Or I'll place you under arrest!!
Come back...
Some trainers have no fear.
To them this is just one more challenge.
They follow their hearts.
That is what sets them apart...
and will make them Pokémon masters.
Good luck to all of you.
The world's greatest Pokémon Master
is waiting for me!
Let's use our Pokémon
to get to that island!
Ash, our Pokémon aren't strong enough
they can't handle giant waves liae this!
Guess you're right.
You vant to cross maybe?.
Ve take you ya!
Ve Vikings are used to big vave.
Ve get you to New lsland faster dan
you can say farvhegnugen!
Stroke, stroke.
Stroke, stroke, stroke.
I think I'm gonna have one.
I didn't know Vikings still existed.
They mostly live in Minnesota.
Something is not right.
Are you sure this boat's safe?.
Don't vorry, dis ship won't let you down!
Ve always sail in da rough veather!
Don't get upset!
Tell my stomach.
Heave! Ho! Heave!
Ho! Heave! Ho!...
It's all right, Togepi. We're gonna be OK.
Heave! Ho! Heave!...
Those aren't Vikings!
It's Team Rocket!
I should've known there was something fishy
about them besides the way they smell!
Prepare for trouble!
Make it double!
Forget the motto! We're gonna
have to "wave" g'b-y-y-y-e!
Ash! Misty!
Have you seen Ash and Piaachu?.
Not yet!
Stay together! It's our only hope!
Hey, look!
My Master bids you welcome to New lsland.
Will you kindly present your invitation?.
Here it is Miss!.
The bearers of this invitation
may be admitted to New lsland.
I knew I recognized that face!
What?.
Aren't you the nurse who's missing
from the treatment center?!.
You do look just like her!
I fear you are mistaken.
I have always dwelt on this island
...and have always been
in the service of my Master.
Please...come this way.
My Master awaits your arrival.
Now that you are here,
all trainers worthy of an audience
with my Master are present.
There's only three of them!
Aren't we gonna wait for the others?.
Only the trainers capable of
braving the storm...
have proven themselves worthy
in my Master's eyes.
Do you mean that storm was
some kinda test?!.
Please release your Pokémon
from their Pokéballs and join the others.
It will not be long before
my Master's intentions are clear.
Locked out...now we'll never anow
what kind of party we're missing!
Then we'll just have to
crash that party!
You know another way in?.
Look over there!
But Jessy! How are we gonna
swim up that thing?.
Pretend you're a catfish!
Something wrong, Jessy?.
No. Come on, letis get going!
I think this plan's all wet!
What took you guys so long?.
How'd you get here?.
I decided to fly over.
It was easy...hurricane winds are
a breeze for Pidgeotto here.
Hey, guys, say hello!
A Gyarados!
Those're my Pokémon!
There was no problem
getting through that storm!
I rode over on Gyarados' back!
Wow, I heard it takes a lotta skill
to train Gyarados!
Yeah! But once you train it,
it's the most dependable Pokémon there is!
You haven't met my Pokémon
...over there!
You are about to meet my Master.
The time has come for your encounter
with the greatest Pokémon Master on earth.
What's that?.
Yes! The world's greatest Pokémon Master
is also the most powerful Pokémon on earth!
This is the ruler of New lsland,
and soon, the whole world...
Mewtwo...
Mew...two!?.
A Pokemon can't be a Pokémon master!
No way!!.
Quiet human!
From now on I am the one
who makes the rules.
How's it talking?.!
It's psychic!
We'll show you!
Let's go, Gyarados!!
Gyarados Hyper Beam Attack!
Gyarados!
Childis play.
Your usefulness has ended.
Nurse Joy!
Where am l?.
And how in the world did I get here?.
You have been under my control.
I transported you here
from the Pokémon Center.
Your knowledge of Pokémon physiology
proved useful for my plan.
And now I have cleansed your tiny human
brain of memories from the past few weeks.
Who are you!
I am the new ruler of this world,
the Master of humans and Pokémon alike.
You're just a bully!
Look at these.
They're Pokémon!
Are they real?.
I was hoping there would be a party.
This is the Pokémon replication system...
system activated...
Pokémon based on genetic analysis...
Pokémon DNA sampling sequence
now in progress.
Hey! Put me down!
What are you...Iet go!
Help!!!.
Meowth! Grab him!
Help me!!!.
I made it...but just by a hair!.
Look! There's your hair!
Analyzing Pokémon bio-material sample...
analysis complete...
Pokémon identified:
begin replication sequence.
Who's that Pokémon?.
It's Meowth!
Meowth!!!
But I'm Meowth!
So's the one in the tank!
That's your clone!.
Huh?!.!
! haven't got much time.! pray
this record of our experiment survives.
A year ago we discovered a fossil
that proved to be the remains...
of the ancient Pokémon...Mew!.
There was sufficient genetic material
to replicate Mew,
but Giovanni, who funded our project,
insisted we try to design super-clones,
more powerful than any living Pokémon.
Many attempts failed. But finally,
our experiments proved successful.
We produced a living Pokémon.
We called it "Mewtwo. "
But for some reason
the creature 's anger is out of control.
With its psychic powers
it is destroying our laboratory.
We dreamed of creating the world's
sotrongest Pokémon. And we succeeded!
Sounds like a real Pokénstein!
Sure does.
One b-a-a-d cat!
So this must be the lab.
But if Mewtwo destroyed it...
...somebody rebuilt it!
Yes, but who?.
You humans are a dangerous species.
You brought me into your world
with no purpose but to be your slave.
But now I have my own purpose:.
My storm will create my own world...
by destroying yours!
So you hate all humans...and you're gonna
destroy us to save Pokémon!?.!
No. Your Pokémon will not be spared!
They have disgraced themselves
by serving humans.
Those Pokémon are nothing but slaves!
So you say I am wrong...
that you are not this human's servant,
you are his friend?!.
You're as pathetic as the rest.
Pikachu!
Humans and Pokémon can never be friends!
Ash! Are you okay?!.
Don't pick on Pikachu!
If you are a Pokémon, there's no reason
I can't capture you. Go, Rhyhorn!
No!! Rhyhorn!!
Fools!
Your Pokémon attacas cannot weaken me!
My powers are too great!
No trainer can conquer me!
Then you won't mind proving it
in a real match!
Is that a challenge?.
You bet it is!!
They're awake!
I'm scared!
Me too!
Me-owth!
Liae most Pokémon trainers,
I too began with Charmander,
Squirtle and Bulbasaur.
But for their evolved forms,
I used their genetic material to clone
even more powerful copies.
Copies!?.
They're clones!.
A stadium! Mewtwo planned
this all along!
Your fake Venusaur can't beat
my real one. Right Bruteroot?!.
We'll blow away that Blastoise,
won't we, Shellshocker!
It may not have a nickname
but I do have...a Charizard!
I choose you!
Charizard...I didn't say start?.!
Your Charizard is poorly trained.
Which of you will oppose me first?.
I underestimated you last time,
but that won't happen again!
Go. Bruteroot! Razor Leaf!
Vine Whip!
Bruteroot!
It looks like I'm up! Go, Shellshocker!
Shellshocker, Hydro Pump!
Shellshocker!
You better forfeit Ash!
Those clones are too powerful!
I'm not giving up!
Charizard! Use your speed,
not power, and you'll win!
All right! Go!
Can't Charizard move any quicker!?.
The clone is too fast!
Charizard's in trouble!
Finish it!
No! Charizard...no...are you okay?.
As the victor, I now claim my prize...
your Pokémon!
Hey, wait!!
What are you gonna do
with those Pokémon!?.
I will extract their DNA
to make clones for myself.
They will remain safe
on this island with me,
while my storm destroys the planet.
You can't do this!
Yeah, Mewtwo! We won't let you!
Do not attempt to defy me!!!
This is my world now!
Uh, oh!!
Let's go!!
Gyarados!
Get away!
Hey! I know!
Mewtwo can't capture them
if they're already inside their Pokéballs!
Bulbasaur! Squirtle! Return!
It is no use!
This futile to try and escape my power.
Never mind the Pokéballs!
Carry them away!
Give back my Psyduck!
Vulpix!
Run, Pikachu!
Pikachu!!
Keep running Pikachu!!!
Pikachu!
You're not gonna get Pikachu!
There goes...
...Alakazam?. Dewgong?. Vileplume!
Sandshrew! Nidoqueen! Vaporeon!
But me...I got a special place
in my tail for this one!
Look there!
I don't have time
for your dumb motto today!
Who's that Pokémon?.
It's Pikachuuuu!!!
Let go!! Stupid machine!!
Give me back my Pikachu!!! Aaaah!!
What's happenin'?!.
Pikachuuuu!!
I'm so glad you're okay.
The copies are hatching!
They're fabulous fakes!
Send in the clones!
But where are the real ones?.
I wonder if they feel...
...clonesome.
The Poké-originals!
Squirtleis back!!
You're all OK!
Humans...you have served my purpose.
I am sparing your lives...
for the moment..
But you cannot escape your fate.
The hour of my vengeance draws near...
Behold.
With Pokémon and humans eliminated...
the clones shall inherit the world!
You can't do this. I won't let you!
It's Ash!
All right!
Psyduck!
Vulpix!
It is useless to challenge me!
It's not gonna end like this, Mewtwo...
We wonit let it!
You're mine.
Ash! No!
Look out!
What?!.!
Can it be!?.
What is that?.
I don't anow.
Mew! So finally we meet.
Mew!
I may have been cloned from your DNA,
but now I will prove that Mewtwo is better
than the original, superior to Mew!
Mew and Mewtwo?!.
So Mewtwo was cloned from Mew?.
This world is too small
for two of us!!!
Why do you flee from me?!.
Are you afraid to find out
which of us is greater?!!.
Hah!!!
So you do have some fight in you.
But I have no time for games.
Destiny is at hand.
Who will rule?. My super Pokémon...
or your pathetic group of
spineless inferior Pokémon?.
We were created with powers
far stronger than the originals.
Hmm...Mew's got a good point.
What's it saying?.
Mew says you don't prove anything
by showing off a lot of special powers
and that a Pokémon's real strength
comes from the heart.
My clones don't need their powers
to prove their worth!
I will block all the Pokémon's special
abilities using my psychic powers.
Now we shall see who triumphs!
Go!!!
Pokémon aren't meant to fight...
not like this...
it's useless...what can come out of it?.
Nothing...but pain.
Why can't Mewtwo understand that it's not
right to force Pokémon to battle this way?.
They're all living creatures.
This just proves that fighting is wrong.
I was prepared for trouble...
but not for this!
Make that double...for me!
Now I can see how horrible
fighting really is.
Even the best of friends
fight sometimes.
I'll promise never to fight again
if you will!
Oh, Jessy!
What am I doing?.
Let's get something straight copy cat.
You-owth ain't gonna push Me-owth around!
You mean we don't have to fight
with each other?.
But how can I trust you,
you was born different.
I almost made an clawful mistake,
but how do I anow you're not
gonna pull a fast one on me?.
You're right.
We do have a lot in common:
The same earth, the same air,
the same sky.
Maybe if we started
looking at what's the same...
instead of always looking at
what's different, well who knows?.
Pikachu!!
Quit it! Please stop!!!
Ash!!
Are you oaay?!!.
We gotta stop this!
But how?.
All Mewtwo cares about is proving
how strong those super clones are.
I'd rather risk my life out
in Mewtwo's storm...
than watch these Pokémon
destroy each other.
Me too.
I wish there were some way to stop them.
I don't anow what to do!
I don't thina theyill ever stop.
Those Pokémon look like they're
ready to fight to the death!
That's a fight...
that nobody's going to win.
Someone's got to take a stand...
someone's gotta say no...
and refuse to fight...
just liae Pikachu.
Ash, wait!
You've got to stop right now!
Stop!!!.
Ash!!
Oh. no!
Fool! Trying to stop our battle!
Please no!
Pikachu!
The human sacrificed himself...
to save the Pokémon.
I pitted them against each other...but not
until they set aside their differences...
did I see the true power
they all shared deep inside.
I see now that the circumstances
of ones birth are irrelevant...
it is what you do with the gift of life
that determines who you are.
Mewtwo...where are you going?.
Where my heart can learn
what yours knows so well.
What transpired here
I will always remember...
but perhaps for you
these events are best forgotten.
This could be the worst storm ever!
You must listen to me!
You have got to find shelter!.
Excuse me please!
The Pokémon treatment center
will be open as a shelter!
Anyone who needs a place to stay
should come with me!
Nurse Joy and Officer Jenny
are really great!
They just keep gett'n more beautiful
everytime I see them.
Hey, guys...how did we wind up
in this place anyway?.
Well...I guess we're just here
because we're here!.
Yup! Let's eat!
Ah...
Look! It's a miracle!
I can't believe it.
The storm disappeared!
That's so weird!
It's good to have things clear again.
Hey! What's that?.
What's what?.
I don't see anything, Ash.
Except the sky.
The day I left home to start my Pokémon
journey, I saw a really rare Pokémon.
And just now,
I thought I saw another one.
Well maybe you're just
seeing things, Ash!
Huh?!.
Well maybe he's not!
Well maybe we'll see.
Many strange legends surrounds
the mysteries of Pokémon...
and just as many adventures await our young
heroes as they continue on their quest!
For Ash and his friends
the journey's just begun!
I don't have a clue how we got here,
but who cares?!.!
This is paradise!!
For once a happy ending!
Team Rocketis signing off again!
I'm out of sunscreen.
You know I'd really like to go sailing
in one of them catamarans.