Watch Movies, TV Series and Live Sports
Signup Here -> WWW.ADMITME.APP
The awe-inspiring,
mysterious and powerfuI
worId of Pokemon,
in aII of its many
shapes and forms!
A weaIth of creatures
that grace
every nook and cranny
of our beautifuI pIanet
in numbers that may never be
truIy known
in their entirety!
Some, masters
of the heavens above;
caretakers and heIpmates
of the earth beIow;
watchfuI eyes and ears throughout
recorded history,
and beyond!
Living shouIder to shouIder
with peopIe,
whiIe others Iive soIitary Iives
in their naturaI environment.
And then, there are Pokemon
who form vast communities;
aII expressing Iife
in their own unique way!
Setting off Iargerthan Iife,
breathtaking forms
with equaI majesty
in miniature,
the worId of Pokemon
truIy is a worId of wonder!
Capturing the fantasy of many,
incIuding
a certain young man
who, aIong with
his partner Pikachu,
is battIing his way
to attain the titIe of
Pokemon Master!
Ajourney of adventure,
hard work and training,
shared with friends;
with new friends
around every corner,
and new experiences
at every turn.
Case in point,
the newest adventure -
dead ahead!
The Space-Time Rift.
And there,
a reaIity exposed-
heretofore
unheard of!
Poised to redefine
the undiscovered,
and the mysterious.
Two entities
that never shouId have met,
cross paths
in the Space-Time Rift.
This iII-fated
meeting
has brought forth
their unbridIed wrath,
enveIoping the city.
And as a resuIt,
aII is coIIapsing.
What couId be
the true meaning
of this
horribIe nightmare?
Godey's diary, huh?
Wow, what an interesting
find!
It appears our Heroes
have found themseIves
a beautifuI day on which
to continue theirjourney!
Ash's quest for
Pokemon Mastership
is shared with Pikachu,
Dawn and Brock,
whiIe aII quest
for excitement.
And the next site
of both quests
is the Pokemon Contest
Iocated in AIamos Town!
ShouIdn't we have
gotten there by now?
AImost.
And there it is!
AIamos Town,
right over that hiII!
I'II bet ya,
as soon as we get there,
we'II find
some great battIes!
Pikachu!
I've got to get ready
forthe Contest.
So many dresses to wear
and so IittIe time!
Huh, hoId on!
Looks Iike
we're on the wrong shore!
Huh?
Pika.
And I'm exhausted.
Me too!
WouId you aII Iike
a Iift?
Huh?
Pika.
Hi there!
We can't thank you enough
for your kindness!
So, my name, dear,
is Brock.
WouId you honor us
by teIIing your name?
My name's AIice.
So it's AIice
from AIamos Town!
I can't beIieve
I don't have you
written down
in my IittIe
bIue book of babes.
SiIIy me.
Aah, I'm such a dummy!
Huh?
There's onIy one thing
to do.
Let me take you out!
After Croagunk
takes me out.
Pikachu!
Now, my name's Dawn.
I'm entering the AIamos Town
Pokemon Contest.
Hi, I'm Ash.
And this is my partner,
Pikachu.
Pikachu!
Awesome,
we're reaIIy movin'!
What a pretty Iake!
Yeah?
Not as pretty as AIice!
You're quick.
He's used to it.
Pika.
WeII, I work part-time
as a hot air baIIoon
tour guide,
but I aIso spend
most of my time
as a music student!
Huh?
Leaf whistIe?
Pika!
You see,
the Pokemon are showing me
which way
the wind's bIowing.
Okay, Chimchar.
Say, this baIIoon thing
is catching on!
Like we're gonna catch
Pikachu!
More baIIoons?
Three DrifIoon
and a DrifbIim.
Ah-ho, they're
so round and cute!
Say, I think they want us
to take them for a waIk.
Come to Jessie!
WiII you pIease stop pIaying
hard to get?
What did I do?
Same thing
ya aIways do.
Okay now,
a IittIe humor
wiII go a Iong way
to stop that sweIIing!
They busted us
with Gust!
We're bIasting off again!
Look at those towers!
The Space-Time Towers.
Here, Iisten to this!
The briIIiant architect,
Godey,
designed
the Space-Time Towers
100 years ago.
And that's where we hoId
our Pokemon Contests, Dawn.
Oh, wow!
Hundred years?
That's Iike
10 years times --
Times 10.
You're right!
Let's see.
It expIains why
they're caIIed Space-Time.
The tower on the right
represents time,
and the one on the Ieft
represents space.
Hey, I couId've
toId ya that!
PowerfuI forces
coIIiding with each other.
Something big's
going on.
Is everybody okay?
Yeah.
What was that?
I suppose it couId've been
the air currents.
But it sure was
strange.
Sorry if you guys
got scared!
I know what;
I'II give you
the grand tour!
That'd be great!
Pika!
This has got to be
my favorite pIace
in the whoIe town!
This whoIe garden was
designed by Godey, you know?
What a beautifuI spot!
It says:
The design theme
of architect Godey's
briIIiant garden
is the harmony between
humans and Pokemon.
I've been pIaying
in this garden
ever since
I was a IittIe girI.
So everyone here
is my friend.
CooI!
Everyone,
Iet's go!
Great idea!
I'm in too!
Come on out!
Guess that's their way
of weIcoming us.
Knock it off!
Stop fighting!
What a beautifuI song!
My grandma
taught it to me.
It was just so moving!
Thank you, Brock.
GaIIade --
What, GaIIade?
GaIIade,
gaII -- gaII.
What happened?
GaIIade,
gaII -- gaII.
Something's very wrong.
Chimchar!
Guys, Iet's go too!
Return, now!
GaIIade,
gaII -- gaII.
This is terribIe!
Who couId've done this?
It was Darkrai!
Huh?
AIberto!
It appears there have been
recent sightings in town.
Uh, excuse me.
Who's Darkrai?
The Pokemon
who wreaked this havoc.
Pokemon?
Darkrai must Iive here
in this garden.
I've heard of Darkrai
before.
It's a Pokemon
that makes you
have nightmares.
Nightmares?
Handsome hunk spotted
in cIose proximity
to Pikachu!
Looking Iike a Joe
we shouId get to know!
Never hurts to rub eIbows
with a rock star,
I aIways say.
Huh?
Hearthat?
Darkrai.
LickiIicky,
Hyper Beam!
Huh?
Now what did you
do that for?
Huh?
Tonio!
You okay?
Uh-hmm.
This is my friend, Tonio.
He's a scientist.
I was investigating
a space-time abnormaIity
that I had detected.
Something
has happened.
It isn't possibIe.
No, no, I'm fine.
I'm fine, reaIIy.
AIice, you don't
have to be so nice to him.
AIberto.
After aII,
my dear,
you are to be my wife,
remember?
-- No way!
-- Huh?
Excuse me, but I thought
I toId you no aIready!
Come on, I'm too young
to think about marriage.
PIease forgive me.
This isn't the time or pIace
for that kind of taIk.
Now that that's done,
why don't you come over
to my pIace,
for a IittIe dinner?
CooI it.
AIice is so not
interested.
Excuse me,
young Iady.
Butt out!
Tonio,
who is that guy?
Baron AIberto.
So AIice,
Iet's get going.
Huh?
You see, Tonio's
the one I Iike.
Uh, I am?
You have quite
a sense of humor, my dear.
So, this was aII
just a IittIe joke.
Joke? Umm.
Oh AIice --
Not again.
What is it?
Such strange phenomena.
Something's there!
Do not come here.
It's Darkrai.
I'd say so.
Ahh!
Darkrai?
'Fraid so.
So it was you after aII,
Darkrai.
Go LickiLicky!
Ooh! What's that?
That's Darkrai.
What a nice-Iooking chap.
What?
It's gone!
Huh -- huh?
Hey guys --
Pikachu,
where are you?
Hey!
Brock!
Dawn!
Oh man,
what's goin' on?
Aah!
Huh?
Darkrai!
Darkrai's doing this.
AII right, Turtwig,
I choose you!
Aah!
Huh?
Hey, Pikachu!
Pikachu!
Huh?
Pikachu.
Pika pi!
You're okay!
Ash, stop!
Pikachu's suffocating.
Huh!
Where am I?
The Pokemon Center.
You were having
such terribIe nightmares
after Darkrai
put you to sIeep.
Nightmares, huh?
That means
it was aII a dream.
Creating bad dreams
is Darkrai's
speciaI abiIity.
If you ever faII asIeep
near Darkrai,
you'II have
terribIe nightmares.
You were reaIIy
in a bad way.
You woke me up;
didn't ya, buddy?
Pikachu.
Darkrai doesn't
normaIIy come out
when peopIe are around.
So I don't think
the townspeopIe
are Iiking this
one bit.
Because of aII those
nightmares,
even the other Pokemon
stay away from Darkrai.
WeII, no one wants
to have a nightmare, right?
If I ever come across
that Darkrai again,
I'II give him
a battIe, but good!
Wait.
Remember,
it was Baron AIberto
who attacked first.
This is
an incredibIe force,
enough to
actuaIIy warp space.
Huh --
I have to Iook
at more data!
Tonio?
There's a strong
possibiIity
the same thing
has happened before.
That must be it!
Maybe there's something
in Godey's diary --
That is so him.
Once he starts thinking
about something,
that's that.
That's AIicia.
She met Darkrai
in the garden.
AIicia --
AIice's grandmother!
Rose red --
Luxray!
And so, Darkrai,
who was hated
by everyone eIse,
opened his heart
to AIicia
and began to Iive
in the garden.
Oh, what an amazing story!
Huh?
Hmm --
It turns out
that the nightmare
toId me just what
I needed to do.
For the future,
I needed to Ieave Oracion
for the worId.
Huh, Oracion?
Hmm --
T.V. peopIe, eh?
That's us!
And being the great Baron
that drove away
the eviI Darkrai,
an interview with you
wouId be quite a coup!
Conducted by me,
the IoveIy reporterette JessiIina!
Directed by
yours truIy Jamison,
and photographed by Meowth;
now that's a name!
Hmm.
WeII, I suppose.
After aII, the pubIic
does have a right to know.
Thanks for
the pubIic service!
I'II take that one,
pIease.
Of course.
This Lunar Wing
wiII make bad dreams
a thing of the past.
So, come again!
No need to worry
about nightmares now!
Man, I sure hope
that thing works.
Hey, is something
bothering you, Ash?
And this
is the site
of the AIamos Town
Pokemon Contest.
I am so psyched!
I can't wait
for tomorrow!
Oh!
The Towers are
just as impressive inside,
as outside.
And we're
right in the middIe.
This is the Space Tower,
and this is the Time Tower!
The architect
Godey who designed
the Space-Time Towers
was Tonio's
great grandfather.
Tonio's Iaboratory
is directIy beIow us.
Tonio?
It's AIice.
Sorry to bother you.
Wow!
Tonio?
Tonio!
Are you aII right?
Huh?
Oh, AIice!
Good morning.
WeII, don't sIeep
on the fIoor.
Sorry.
I found a reference
to the nightmare
in Godey's diary
Iast night.
Wish I couId have
a nightmare.
Huh?
Hah?
Not onIy that,
I found a picture
of your grandmother.
It shows her
with Godey.
Grandma AIicia.
Looks just Iike you.
It's music.
Huh?
That was a nice save,
I guess.
Pikachu.
What're those?
Music disks.
Excuse me?
That's how the tower's music
is abIe to pIay.
Oh, can I try it?
But, to do that,
we'II have to waIk
aII the way
to the top.
No need to worry.
Me and my big mouth.
Come on, move it!
Run!
Race ya to the top, Dawn!
Pika pika pikachu!
Oh man,
me and my big mouth!
Pika --
The onIy way to fIy.
Hey, that's not fair!
Sorry,
but you were fast!
You can cIimb.
Hey, Iet us on too!
Pika!
Godey buiIt
the Space-Time Towers
as a beacon of hope
for the happiness
of peopIe and Pokemon.
The happiness
And here's our very own
beacon of hope now!
FinaIIy!
Pika pi --
NormaIIy, it's set to pIay
automaticaIIy on the hour.
But if there's
something speciaI
you want to pIay --
You put in
the disks you need.
Great!
Hey!
I wanna do that.
No way.
This was my idea.
Umm.
Pika.
Then push it down.
Brock, wouId you mind?
Not at aII.
You see, this Tower
is the worId's
Iargest musicaI
instrument as weII!
Wow!
Pika!
You know,
baIIoons rock!
Pika!
Huh?
Ah, if it isn't Ash!
So Iet's battIe again.
I need someone
to pIay with Torterra.
Torterra.
Come on.
Me too.
Sudowoodo!
BuizeI!
Let's go!
Pikachu, get movin'!
It's coming
from a different space.
From between
the dimensions!
What was aII that?
The sky just Iit up!
Go away!
Huh? Huh?
Darkrai!
Ah ha!
LickiIicky!
Leave it to the brave Baron
to find Darkrai in a fIash!
With such
daring and dash!
There is no escape.
AII right, LickiIicky,
Gyro BaII!
Dark Void!
GibIe, no!
Sudowoodo!
What in the worId
is that?
It's Darkrai!
Quick BuizeI,
use Water Gun!
BibareI!
Pikachu,
use ThunderboIt!
My neck!
You saw that, right?
Pika!
Huh!
Quick, Pikachu,
use ThunderboIt!
Okay Pikachu,
now use VoIt TackIe!
Look Darkrai, the onIy one
Ieavin' here is you!
No, I stay.
What?
Huh?
Let me handIe this.
Darkrai is mine.
Baron!
LickiIicky,
use Hyper Beam!
LickiIicky!
Get up LickiIicky!
This is no time
for a nap!
Again?
What's that thing?
Huh?
An uItra-rare Pokemon?
That fIies
through waIIs?
It can't be reaI.
Maybe so, but --
care to expIain
what you're up to?
WeII, what?
The camera
does add a few extra pounds.
B-b-b-b-b-buh Baron!
Spit it out, I say!
Man, I must be havin'
another nightmare.
Pikachu, I want you
to hurry and wake me up!
My royaI tongue!
Nurse Joy,
I think
I couId use
an exam too, hah --
It's these haIIucinations!
But I'm
seeing them too!
I guess you're aII stiII
a IittIe shook up.
I think you're right.
Guys, we've got
a probIem!
We've got a probIem
here too.
Huh?
ReaIIy?
WeII, excuse me, peopIe.
But you don't even know
the meaning of the word
probIem!
Since when
can LickiIicky taIk?
I am not LickiIicky.
I am the Baron AIberto!
No way!
Quick, Tonio.
Turn me back at once!
You act Iike AIberto.
He's teIIing the truth.
He turned into LickiIicky
right in front of us!
Pika pikachu.
And us!
We saw the whoIe thing
with our own --
beady eyes!
Here's the reaI deaI
as proof!
The reaI worId merging
with the dream worId.
What are you taIking about?
AII of these Pokemon
are dreaming
that they're being chased
by something frightening.
And what about me?
I guess LickiIicky
must be dreaming
that it turned into you.
Say what?
The space
around our city
is being acted on
by a powerfuI force,
creating
a space-time anomaIy,
resuIting in aII of
the strange things
we've been witnessing.
But why?
I don't know.
It's that Darkrai!
Every time it appears,
strange things happen;
don't you see?
Perhaps.
LickiIicky,
you must wake up
this instant
and go destroy Darkrai!
Hey guys, what about
our in-depth report?
We ain't got enough depth
to fiII a kiddie pooI!
Look, first we get Darkrai,
and then, we'II dig deep.
Huh?
Listen peopIe,
we're stuck!
It's the craziest
thing!
We're trapped in town,
and we can't Ieave.
Now Honchkrow, Defog!
Defog didn't do
a thing!
No matter which way
we try to escape,
we aIways end up
where we started!
I'II be back!
Pikachu --
Pika!
But I know
we ran straight.
Pikachu!
It's that Darkrai!
No doubt up to
one of its eviI tricks.
And nothing's
going to change
untiI we destroy
the nasty demon.
It's nice to see
Baron LickiIicky
back up to speed.
Baron AIberto!
Oh, my makeup!
Pokemon trainers,
Iend me your ears,
your strength
and your expertise.
We must destroy
this Ioathsome
and eviI Darkrai.
And now, foIIow me
into the fray!
Right!
What do you think?
They need us.
Yeah!
They need us too!
Yeah.
Hmm.
HoId on.
Huh?
AIice?
The truth is,
I don't think Darkrai
is behind any of this.
What?
But, it must be
Darkrai.
No, it's a bit too earIy
to be certain.
You see,
back when I was a boy,
AIice and I were pIaying
together in the garden.
Tonio.
Huh?
Yoo-hoo!
I'm up here.
Come on up
and pIay with me.
It's dangerous
up there.
Look where you're going!
Don't worry,
I'm fine!
AIice!
Huh?
Hah -- Huh!
AIice, are you okay?
Say something.
AIice!
Tonio.
Oh, you saved my Iife,
Tonio!
Uh --
Tonio, I Iove you!
But the truth is,
I didn't save AIice
that day.
Now I'm sure of it.
It was Darkrai
who saved you that day.
Oh, Tonio!
Godey's diary aIso says
that it was
your grandmother AIicia
who opened up
Darkrai's heart.
I don't beIieve that
Darkrai is eviI, either.
Then why is Darkrai
fighting with everyone?
Pika pika --
Something's keeping
everybody
from being abIe
to Ieave town!
I don't have
aII the answers yet.
For now,
we just hang on.
We join the venerabIe
Baron LickiIicky
and his posse of
Pokemon trainers
as their quest
to destroy Darkrai
gets into fuII swing!
That's Baron AIberto.
There it is!
Huh?
It's Darkrai!
Let's see.
These space-time anomaIies
began occurring
after Darkrai appeared.
But at this point,
the nightmares
hadn't yet materiaIized.
It didn't take Ash
very Iong to wake up.
Soon after that, Darkrai
appeared in the square.
After that, that's when
the nightmares materiaIized!
Hah --
Now I see!
That has to be
the defining event!
What's this?
Infernape!
Mach Punch, go!
EmpoIeon, use Ice Beam!
Torterra,
BuIIet Seed now!
Darkrai's in a bad way.
CouId this be the end?
Do not interfere!
Infernape!
No, wake up!
That move
was simpIy IoveIy.
I mean,
Darkrai's eviI rampaging
must be stopped.
And since there's no one
better to Iick that brute,
why don't you?
You do strike
an imposing pose.
I guess I couId
take advantage
of the situation.
I've got it,
and I'm going with it!
Go, Gyro BaII!
Then it's wrap!
Huh?
Not bad.
We're bIasting off again!
Look at this!
Aah!
Hey, that's the same thing
from my dreams!
Look cIoseIy.
I'II digitaIIy enhance
the image.
Oh my!
PaIkia!
Isn't it?
Yes.
It is said that PaIkia Iives
between dimensions
and ruIes space,
a Pokemon
that's been caIIed a deity.
A deity?
When the garden was turned
into a wasteIand,
it was a sign of
PaIkia's appearance.
Do not come here.
Darkrai sensed
what was about to happen.
It was at the moment
when the sky Iit up
that PaIkia
burst into the city.
But Darkrai
was the onIy one who saw.
Right.
Go away.
Darkrai said
that's a PaIkia!
Pika --
And that's just what Darkrai
was trying to teII me,
in my dream.
About PaIkia!
So that means
PaIkia's here.
But where's that?
Here!
Is that --
Darkrai!
Darkrai, no!
That's PaIkia.
Oh my!
Pika --
Go away!
BuizeI --
Houndour!
BeIIsprout!
AII right!
I'm me,
wonderfuI me!
Enough for one day!
The town is fIoating
in another dimension.
BuizeI!
Sudowoodo!
Everyone's awake.
Of course.
PaIkia transported the town
to another dimension.
So when Darkrai's
nightmares became fixed
in its unstabIe space,
they acquired materiaI form!
It Iooks Iike
PaIkia's hurt.
What's that?
Darkrai!
Huh?
Who's that?
That's the Pokemon
said to govern aII of time.
DiaIga!
They're both
considered to be deities.
Hmm --
Huh?
PaIkia and DiaIga
must have battIed
in between dimensions,
and so the wounded PaIkia
must have fIed here,
seaIing the town
in yet another dimension.
Attempting to hide itseIf
from DiaIga!
Two entities
that never shouId have met,
crossed paths
in the Space-Time Rift.
Their unbridIed wrath
has enveIoped the city.
And the resuIt?
Destruction!
What do you mean?
The nightmare that I read
about in Godey's diary,
it's happening here and now,
right before our eyes!
Wait.
You're saying
Godey was dreaming
about future events?
Yes.
Tremendous energy!
Everyone okay?
Yeah.
Guess so.
AIice, wait!
Stop fighting
right now!
Darkrai!
Go away!
Darkrai,
you aII right?
AIicia --
My name's AIice.
You see, AIicia
was my grandmother.
AIice --
You tried to protect
ourtown.
I'm sorry
I didn't understand.
Yeah, me too.
Pika --
Darkrai,
forgive us.
Darkrai, no!
Check it out, guys.
What's happening?
It's the town's
perimeter waII.
It's begun to coIIapse!
If we don't act,
everything wiII disappear
into another dimension!
This kind of bIasting off,
we don't need!
But,
what can I do?
Hah!
It turns out
that the nightmare toId me
just what
I needed to do.
For the future,
I needed to Ieave
Oracion forthe worId.
But it didn't say
what Oracion couId be.
Oracion?
AIice,
you've heard of it?
Yes.
Oracion is the name
of the song
my grandmother taught me
to pIay on the Ieaf whistIe.
That's it!
Godey foretoId the disaster
threatening the future
and Ieft Oracion
for us.
The Sound Disks?
Uh-hmm.
Oracion,
the song with the power
to soothe
the fiercest rage.
There's no song
named Oracion
in the research Iab.
But, it might be -- here!
But, which one's Oracion?
There are so many.
It's caIIed Oracion.
Oracion?
That's right.
It means prayer.
My mother taught it to me
a great many years ago.
Umm --
Promise me
you'II aIways remember it.
Sure.
Oracion
means prayer.
Remember.
That's it!
Got it!
Let's hurry to
the Space-Time Towers.
Right!
Chimchar,
Iet's go!
That's it.
Move into the garden
as far as you can.
And don't push.
Take it easy,
and stay caIm.
Ready?
Way to go, Croagunk!
The evacuation's
nearIy compIete.
I'm going to wait
with the others
at the rear
of the garden.
Good.
I'II handIe things
here.
Thanks,
Brock.
[ Skipped item nr. 839 ]
But Ash and Dawn --
PipIup, no!
Staravia,
Iet's go!
Now, Chimchar,
Iet's get moving!
ExceIIent work.
Tonio, oh!
Huh?
Oh, Baron.
I owe you thanks
as weII.
I'm over here.
Huh?
Aah!
Not again!
Turtwig, Aipom,
watch my back, okay?
Dawn, Iet's go!
Right.
Here it comes!
Way to go,
you two!
Darkrai.
Darkrai,
you aII right?
Are you hurt?
Are you in pain?
Oh, you are.
I'II heIp you.
AIicia,
make you weII.
Huh?
Oh no!
HoId on.
BuizeI,
Water Gun!
Buneary,
Ice Beam!
Perfect!
Great!
CarefuI.
Pika pika.
Stop this
right now!
You don't have to Ieave,
you can stay here.
Do you mean that?
Of course.
You can stay here
for as Iong as you Iike.
This is everyone's
garden.
Oh no!
If those two coIIide
one more time --
our dimension
is through!
Stop!
This garden
is everyone's!
Darkrai.
The disk!
Let's hurry!
Hey, come on!
Darkrai's bIocking
the expIosion's energy,
but --
for how Iong?
BuizeI,
thanks a Iot!
Hey Pikachu,
take care of everyone!
Pickachu!
Huh?
Ash, come back!
Darkrai, no!
But how?
I am not gonna Iet
Darkrai down now!
Pikachu!
Pika pi.
It won't fit!
This is it.
If those two
coIIide once more,
then it's over
for aII of us!
Huh?
But Ash
and Dawn!
PIease get there
in time.
This is Oracion,
isn't it?
It must be.
Try the one
in the middIe!
Hah! --
It's in!
AII right!
The power.
It's dead.
Too Iate.
Pachirisu,
discharge!
And Pikachu,
use ThunderboIt, fuII bIast!
That's it.
That's Oracion!
PaIkia, can't you see
what you've done?
You've destroyed
the whoIe town.
AII the Pokemon,
you bring this town
back to the way
it was!
You've gotta
do it!
PaIkia,
pIease!
We're back!
Thank you,
Darkrai.
For everything.
I'm sorry,
Darkrai.
I shouId've known
you were just trying
to do
the right thing.
Pika.
Pikachu.
Darkrai!
Darkrai,
you're okay!
Pika!
I'II aIways remember you
Carry your dreams
UntiI they come true
Each breath
that I take
Each moment away
I'II aIways
remember you
Everywhere I waIk
I see your shadow
And when I cIose my eyes,
I see your face
Every song I sing,
I hear your meIody
Because not a moment
that goes by
And you're not
on my mind
You wiII aIways
be my hero
Never scared
braver than us aII
Guiding Iight
for me to foIIow
AIways showing me
the way
Right beside me
everyday
I'II aIways
remember you
Carry your dreams
untiI they come true
Each breath
that I take
Each moment away
I'II aIways remember you
Oh oh yeah, I remember
Hey yes yes I remember
Oh, forthe sacrifice you made
And aII the gifts you gave
I'II aIways remember you
Carry your dreams
untiI they come true
Each breath that I take
Each moment away
I'II aIways remember
you you you
I'II aIways remember you
I'II carry your dreams
untiI they come true
Each breath that I take
Each moment away
I'II aIways remember
AIways remember
I'II aIways remember you
Watch Movies, TV Series and Live Sports
Signup Here -> WWW.ADMITME.APP