[Pikachu] Pika!
[Narrator] The Pokéball.
An invention that's captured the imagination
of people everywhere.
Thanks to its ability to capture the most
marvelous of creatures,
Pokémon.
And to catch one is an
experience like none other.
Each of these spectacular
species has amazing powers and
attributes that set them apart
from one another in ways too
numerous to list.
What unique is they are individually,
together they make up the
incredible world of
Pokémon.
Watch Movies, TV Series and Live Sports
Signup Here -> WWW.ADMITME.APP
[Roaring]
Pokémon and people like Ash Ketchum
can come together as a team.
For once they're captured in a Pokéball,
Pokémon bond with their human trainers as
friends, partners, family.
On their journey of discovery
trainers and their Pokémon
learn as much about themselves
as each other.
And they also realize that
there will always be more
Pokémon than they could ever
have imagined.
You see, for each Pokémon
that's discovered, there are
dozens, perhaps hundreds more
we have yet to meet.
One thing's for sure,
with each of these new
Pokémon come new possibilities,
new sToryes, new friendships
and new adventures.
Perhaps Pokémon trainers aren't the only
ones to seek out new species.
The Pokémon themselves
seem to have an innate
curiosity for the
creatures of this world
and of Worlds Beyond.
After all, we may live on a Pokémon Planet,
but nobody ever said
that it's the only one.
Professor, have you seen Tory?
Take a look.
Uh-huh.
Impossible Keeping up with him.
[Laugh]
Spheal!
Wow, it's a Spheal.
Spheal! Spheal!
Hi.
Spheal. Spheal.
Spheal.
Spheaaalll!
Spheal
Spheal, Spheeeeaall..
[Laughing]
Aah!
[Roaring]
[Roar]
Ah!
[Explosion]
Aahh!
Aah.
Aah!
Tory!
You're okay,
I've got you.
Thank you Daddy.
[Panting]
Oh!
[Humming]
It's some kind of Pokémon,
isn't it?
Yes,
Hmmm.
It's a Pokémon from outer space.
[Roaring]
[Roar]
Rayquaza never leaves
the ozone layer.
Why Now?
[Roar]
It regenerated.
But how's that possible?
Let's go, it's too dangerous.
Yeah.
[Roaring]
Ah!
Are you okay?
[Gasp]
[Roaring]
[Growl]
Quick, follow me.
I'm right behind you.
Whoa!
[Pained roar]
Oh!
-What is it?
-Look at that!
[Gasp]
[Roaring]
[Snarling and growling]
[Helicopter whirring]
Rayquaza is furious.
Another Pokémon crossing
into its territory has
obviously threatened it.
Mmm.
Huh?
Fire the laser.
Raise our trajectory by point five.
Right.
That's the frequency.
Finally in sync.
That means..
Yes, the crystal should regenerate
if we keep the laser on target.
We will succeed.
We have to.
Hmm.
[Machine powering down]
We overloaded the regulator.
Hmm..
It was just one small component
that malfunctioned.
A simple replacement.
Good.
We'll try again after it's fixed.
Yes, sir.
Huh?
[Laughing]
Guess what?
I'm gonna tell you all
about this book I'm reading.
It's so good.
Once that parts replaced
we're almost home.
Yeah, we're so close.
Huh?
I was right.
I did see a glow.
[Humming]
Wow!
[Laughing]
[Narrator] On his journey to become a
Pokémon Master, Ash Ketchum and
his friends arrive in LaRousse City.
The headquarters for anything
and everything high-tech.
But he's not here for the
gadgets and gizmos.
Ash is itching for action at the
town's famous battle tower.
Pelipper!
Seel?
Ah!
[Gasping]
Aaah!
[Panting]
[Pant]
[Minun chattering]
[Plusle chattering]
Aah!
Minun!
[Giggling]
[Giggles]
Munch!
MMmunch.
Munch.
Munch?
Muunch..
Munch!
Munch..
Munch.
Welcome!
You are now in
LaRousse City.
Welcome again.
Cool.
It's so cute.
A robot.
What can be better than
that?
Pika!
Being greeted by a real live
beautiful girl could be one thing.
Smile!
[Computer] Visitor data confirmed.
Citizenship and point of origin recorded.
These will serve as your passports.
Our passports?
While in LaRousse City,
keep them with you at all times.
Your passports can be used
for shopping and needs.
Hmm.
Don't think I'll be sending
this one home.
So I wonder which way to go for
the battle tower.
Pika.
Aah!
Help!
Pika!
Ah!
Hey Ash! Quit messing around! a
A moving sidewalk.
Dude, you're swimming upstream.
There is an easier way.
Well, if I ever get off of this thing,
then maybe you can show it to me!
Pika!
Nice fall.
Nice fall. [Giggles]
Blaze.
Help him out, Blaziken.
Okay?
Hey, thanks a lot.
Sure, no need to thank me.
I just couldn't continue
watching you look like a fool.
What?!
So I guess you're all new in town, huh?
Well, if you're heading for the
battle tower, you should try
going this way.
Be careful.
Don't fall.
My name is Ash from Pallet Town.
How'd you like to battle with me?
Watch out my brother
rates really strong.
Blaziken too!
Bla-a-aze.
Yeah, I'd love to have
a battle with you, Ash.
Let's get together at the
battle tower, okay?
So we're finally gonna
settle this today. Right Ray?
Hello, My bespectacled duty.
I'm Brock.
Stop!
[Groaning]
Well, I guess you could say
that your friend here has
really fallen for Rebecca, huh?
She's a good Metagross Trainer.
Likes to use her
laptop for strategy.
So my name is Sid.
Blastoise is my partner.
Hi, I'm May
And this is my brother,
Max.
Hey, you're kind of cute.
Kinda?
I'm kinda crazy too.
Look! The Battletower!
Look Pikachu.
It's right there.
Oooh!
I can't wait.
Pika!
I'll be back, as soon as I'm
registered.
Okay, then we'll head to the
stands.
See ya.
There, let's hurry!
Oh! [Laugh]
Uh-oh, now where are we?
Oh wow, there's a library too.
Pika.
Excuse me?
Huh?
Pika!
Aah!
Hold on.
What are you running away for?
Pika?
Wait!
Hold up!
Hi, let me start that again.
We're on our way to a battle,
but we don't know how to get there.
So we're kind of lost.
Pika Pika!
Ah!
Wait! We just wanna
Are you ready for your battle?
Right this way, gentlemen.
I, you don't understand.
If you hurry up,
you two might just make it.
But I haven't registered yet.
That will all happen
automatically.
Now, good luck you two!
[Computer] Passports confirmed.
Two Youth Level participants
entered successfully.
Great! And just in time.
Pika!
[Computer] Entry for participants in the
first round is closed.
Please try again next time.
What?
Now introducing our first entry.
Here we go.
Pikachu!
Our first match will be an official
Battletower tag team event!
Remember to cheer for your favorites!
Tag team, huh?
Yeah!
We have Ash Ketchum in the Blue Corner.
- Yes!
A trainer all the
way from Pallet Town.
And his tag partner,
Tory, a local trainer.
All right, Tory. Good luck.
Wonder how Ash got entered so quickly.
By cutting in front of me.
Rebecca.
There comes a time in a
man's life when he's
presented with the gift
of love at first sight.
How about pain at first pull?
Not the ear!
[Girls giggling]
Hm?
Professor Lund?
Take a look at this
Tory? In a Pokémon Battle?
And in the Red Corner, we have
to two Trainers from South City.
Rafe and Sid!
Hey Ash, you sure didn't
waste any time.
'Course not, I couldn't wait to beat you!
Hey, May!
Make sure you watch.
I'm dedicating this battle to you.
Basic rule that all Tag Team
battles is teamwork.
Each trainer uses a single Pokémon
and works with his teammate.
And now traitors bring out your
Pokémon!
All right, here goes!
Blaze!
Blastoise!
Pikachu, I choose you!
Pika!
Pikachu!
Tory, what Pokémon are
you going to use?
No Ash, I don't have any Pokémon.
But..
Pika?
There seems to be a problem.
We've seen only one
Pokémon from the Blue corner.
See, I was trying to tell you
I'm not a trainer.
I can't battle.
But this could end up being my
only chance to battle Rafe.
Hey, I know what! I'll loan you
one of my Pokémon.
What do you say?
- Come on, that'll work.
- But..
Will the Blue corner forfit?
Don't let me down Tory.
Well, if I have to!
Tooor.. koal!
Oh! Looks like we have our Pokémon!
Ready for a battle?
cause here we go.
Let's do it!
Blaziken, use Blaze Kick now!
Dive Pikachu!
Go Blastoise, Hydro Pump!
Blast!
Pika!
It's a dazzling combination
from the Red Corner!
Blastoise, Bubble Attack!
Blastoise!
Torkoal! Tory, you have to tell
Torkoal to do something!
But, I don't know what
to tell it.
Blastoise, Rapid Spin!
Blast.. Toise!
Blaaas..
Toise!
Toooor.. koooal!
Blaas..
[Panting]
Blastoise
Blast.. toise!
Pikachu, use Thunderbolt!
Cover Torkoal!
Piiika-chuuu!
Blaziken!
Blastoise, Skull Bash go!
- Pika!
- Toise.
Torkoal..
Looks like the Blue corner just
can't seem to get it together as a team.
Man, Ash's partner isn't doing
anything to help him out at all.
I don't see how he could win.
Come on, do something!
Tory, don't worry.
I'll take care of it.
Flamethrower Torkoal, go!
Torkoal.
Tooor..
- ..Kooal!
- Pika!!
Whoa! A Flamethrower
from Torkoal.
But it hit Pikachu!
How embarrassing.
So Rafe, want to finish this one up?
Let's go!
Blaziken Overheat.
Blaziken!
Pika!
Pikachu! Torkoal!
And that's it.
Pikachu and Torkoal are unable to battle.
Rafe and Sid are the winners!
Congratulations!
Tory
Daddy.
We just watched your
Pokémon Battle.
I'm incredibly
proud.
Don't be. It was all an accident.
It wasn't even supposed to
happen.
Yugo. Meeting you reminds me of
a time in my life when I too
spent long hours toiling as a
professor's assistant.
I'm sure Professor Ivy would be
happy to vouch for my work.
- Oh yeah.
- I'll be happy to vouch for his insanity.
We apologize for the mix-up
with your battle.
The truth is, Tory is
completely afraid of Pokémon.
How could he be afraid of
Pokémon?
Well, about four years ago, he
had a very traumatic experience
and it left him terrified of
them.
Sadly, he still hasn't managed
to get over those fears.
[Plusle chattering]
Waaa! Shoo! Shoo!
[Plusle and Minun chattering]
[Plusle chattering]
Wow, I shouldn't have pushed
him so hard.
But underneath it all, I think he loves them.
All he really needs is the chance
to get to know them that's all.
I'm sure that's all it'll take.
Fine. Then I'll give him that chance.
All he needs now is to become
friends with me and Pikachu.
Right pal?
Pi. Pika.
Yay, I want to help too!
- So do I.
- Me too.
Cool.
So what do you say we all go
and look for Tory, okay?
Yeah!
You're awfully kind.
Thank you.
[Plusle and Minun chattering]
[Groaning]
Tory?
Pika?
Min!
[Plusle and Minun chattering]
[Laughing]
Aahh!
Later!
Pi?
Pika.
Munch
Munch.
Munch!
Huh?
Hey, come on out.
Where are you?
I want to tell you
something important.
You'll never guess
what I just did.
I helped out a Pokémon.
Cause it had it's head stuck inside
a garbage can
and so I helped to get it out!
Isn't that cool?
[Laughing]
[Humming]
[Gasp]
[Gasp in amazement]
Hey, what are those lights?
And I was even part of a
Pokémon battle too.
Course, I wasn't very good.
So that part kind of stunk.
Hey, who are you talking to?
Pika?
Hey, it's gone.
Come on.
Who was it?
None of your business!
What would it hurt to tell me?
Stop! Leave me alone, okay?
- Pi!
- Wait a minute!
If this town is so high-tech,
why don't they have moving sidewalks?
Or robots that serve hamburgers?
Yeah... Keep dreaming.
[All groaning]
[All groan]
I'll take a hamburger please!
[Robot] Hamburger.
Yum!
[Excited chattering]
[All] Hamburgers please!
Passport. Passport. Passport
What's a passport?
Well, I have no idea what kind
of pass he's talking about.
But Meowth, please
stop calling me sport.
You idiot!
Hamburger!
Hey, that ain't right!
Cheeseburger!
Alert!
- Alert! Alert!
- Now! Now! Now!
Come on!
[Groaning]
- Alert!
- Aah!
Alert!
That was rude.
Maybe she takes our order?
Yeah..
Well, I'm pretty good at
giving orders.
So, I'm gonna have five hamburgers
well done. And don't
forget the french fries.
Well done it is.
[Screaming]
Jesse got fried!
Without the burgers!
I think we should battle
together again.
Bet we'll get it right next time.
Why do you keep following me?
Aah!
Are you Okay?
Pikach-
Ah!
Pika?
Gee, thanks.
Why'd you have to go
and push me?
Ash, stop!
Don't start something.
Okay.
Oh. Hey, I know!
Pika?
Mmm. Perfect.
Dig in!
I'll go first!
Second.
Hold on!
O-o-oh! It's hot!
Yum!
There's nothing that
can stop an argument
better than a
bunch of full mouths.
Try some Tory. It's really good.
You're right.
Told you so!
[All laughing]
Guys. Look at all those Pokémon!
Well, hi!
There's plenty of Pokémon food.
So don't be shy!
There. Dig in guys.
Tory, don't you think
they're the cutest?
Yeah.
Hey, I bet they let you pet them.
Pika!
Piika.
Pika?
Thanks guys.
I'm sorry.
Well, we tried.
Pika.
Ah, I'm sure we'll get through to
him eventually.
Ah! Guys!
Oh no! It's a Munchlax. And
they love to eat.
Well, guess it's doing
what it loves.
Hey you! That was our lunch!
Munch!
Munch. Munch. Munch
Munch.
Wow.
Hey, it's a Plusle and Minun.
Hi cuties.
Pika, pika!
[All three chattering]
Murkrow!
[Humming]
There's that light in the sky
again.
Awesome.
It's beautiful.
Huh? But that's impossible.
What is?
That's called an aurora.
But it can only be seen at the
North and South Poles
Strange.
Well, then, I guess we're lucky
to be able to see it here.
Right?
The same kind of luck that
brought you and me together.
Right babe?
Haha!
Not sure what kind of luck that
was.
Hi beautiful.
If you're looking for a real phenomenon,
stop looking in your computer
and spend some time with me!
Oookay..
You leaving her alone.
That's a phenomenon.
Well, look who's still in town.
So?
So well, after that devastating
defeat in front of thousands of
people, I thought you might be a
little embarrassed to show your face.
Oh yeah? How about a rematch
tomorrow? In the battle tower?
No problem.
I'll beat you anytime and anywhere
I wouldn't count on that!
Pika?
Hey, I know you
Tory.
Hey, you guys.
Yuko and I made these for you.
Cool! Pokémon cookies.
- Cute.
- Yummy.
Come on out everyone.
When is a sandwich more than a
sandwich?
When the sandwiches are meal..
..for Team Rocket to
steal.
Dinner!
Aaah!
Huh?
Did that just happen?
Munchlax munch!
It's stealin' da' food we were stealin'!
Oh, no it's not!
[Growling]
Come back here you little..
[Muttering]
It's gone.
[Humming]
[Roaring]
[Roar]
You know, I've never done that
before.
What?
Just playing together with a
big bunch of friends.
Really?
Yeah, I guess it's because I've
always been so
afraid of Pokémon.
So I'm afraid to get close to
Pokémon trainers too.
Guess I've missed out on a lot.
That means you're always alone.
Pika.
Pikachu.
But that's all in the past, right?
Pika!
Corphish!
[Pokémon chattering]
Phish! Corphish!
It's okay.
There's no rush.
Okay.
That's Corphish.
Cor?
Piiika..
Phish.
Come on guys, There's someone I
want you to meet.
Where are we going?
Wherever it is, I hope there's
a kitchen. I'm starving.
Your passports please.
Verified!
My dad's lab is right over there.
So that's why there are so many
security robots all over.
Haha!
Come on out.
I'm with my new friends!
Come and meet 'em!
So, this is your friend Tory?
Hmm.
Wha-what is it?
It's gorgous!
And weird.
It's always here for me.
Whenever I call for it.
Yesterday, I played with all
these guys and their Pokémon too.
[All gasp]
Well Tory, that's so cool!
And even understands what I say.
Is it a Pokémon?
Not one that I've ever seen.
This is just fascinating.
What do you say I introduce
my Pokémon to it?
Go!
Blaaze!
Yeah, mine too!
[Both] Don't forget ours!
Now, let me introduce mine.
Metagross.
A Metagross!
Awesome!
Meta.
Pika.
Pi?
I.. Gotcha!
Missed it.
Pika!
Piika.
Pi.
[Chuckles]
[Roaring]
Unidentified object
approaching the building.
Can you analyze it, please?
It appears to be Rayquaza.
Rayquaza? Contact Professor Lund
right now.
Right!
Professor.
How could a Rayquaza
be coming here?
I don't know.
But for it to leave the
ozone layer again,
there must be a powerful reason.
[Gasp]
Do you see that?
Huh?
I'll magnify it.
That's what I thought.
It's Deoxys.
[Humming]
[Computer] System malfunction.
Losing regulatory control.
Rayquaza must have come here
after sensing that Deoxys
was here as well.
If those two battle it out in our city,
The result will be catastrophic.
Evacuate LaRousse City immediately.
Right away, sir.
Initiating emergency evacuation
Fellow citizens.
We are facing an emergency situation.
Please evacuate immediately.
Hey! It's party time!
Please be patient.
The next ferry will arrive shortly.
[Humming]
What's that?
It sounds like the police.
Huh?
Tory's out in the garden.
I have to go out and get him.
Everyone, evacuate immediately!
Right.
Why won't your passport work?
This never happens.
Maybe the system is shutting
down.
It stopped.
[Computer] Rebooting.
Oh!
Hey!
[Gasp] It's moving
- Where we going?
[Gasp]
- Excuse me.
- Watch it!
Ooh!
Professor Lund!
Oh.. Some vacation this turned out to be.
Whose bad idea was this?
Let's just say Meowth and I
were overruled.
- Oh?
- Hm?
[Humming]
Aah!
[Screaming]
What's happening here?
Those things are carrying
people away.
Deoxys.
Why are you doing
this to us?
Huh?
[Roaring]
[Humming]
The forcefield!
[Computer] Losing power. All systems will
now shut down.
[Humming]
[Roar]
[Roaring]
[Groaning]
[Humming]
You got it!
Hold on a sec.
[Humming]
It's multiplying.
What is that thing?
Deoxys.
You know its name?
You guys, come back!
[Gasp]
No! May look out!
Hey, what do you want?
Blastoise use Hydro Pump, go!
Blastoise!
Blast!
- Toise!
- Put me down!
Blastoise!
Blast!
Sid, no!
May, get in here!
Blaziken use Flamethrower.
Blaaaze!
Pikachu, Thunderbolt!
Pika-chuuu!
Tory, is there another way out?
Yeah, there's an underground exit.
Can you show us?
Yes, follow me.
Everyone, let's go.
Blaaze!
Chuuu!
Way to go Rafe.
Heh, all in a day's work.
What do they want?
Let's hurry.
Come on Brock, it's open.
Okay.
All right, Ash. Rafe. We gotta go!
- [Ash] Pikachu!
- Pika!
Blaze.
[Grunting]
- [Ash] Ahh!
- Blaze.
Guys, this way!
Pika.
Pika!
Pikachu, use Thunderbolt now!
Pika-chuuu!
Thanks Pikachu. Good Thunderbolt..
[Groan]
Ash, what are you doing? Let's go.
This is the way to get out of here!
Wonder where we are now?
It seems to be safe.
There you are.
It's Yuko.
[Various Pokémon chattering]
Huh?
Min?
Munch.
[Gasp]
Munch?
Munch.
[Growling and roaring]
Professor, take a look at all
of these people shown here.
Their evacuation hasn't been
confirmed that any of the
passport check points. I'm
afraid that could mean
they're still stuck in LaRousse .
The entire town is enclosed
within a force field.
It's impossible for anyone to
come in or to leave.
All communication with the outside
is jammed as well.
They've switch to backup generators.
But all systems are still down.
Even the Pokéball management
system isn't functioning.
Yeah, won't work.
How can we call out our Pokémon?
Guess we can't.
Hey Tory.
What did you call that thing?
Was it Deoxys?
Mhmm.
That's right.
A Pokémon from outer space.
What?
Four years ago, a meteorite came
down and struck the North Pole.
And located inside of it was a
completely unknown Pokémon.
It was Professor Lund who gave
that Pokémon the name Deoxys.
But then, almost immediately
Rayquaza appeared from
the ozone and attacked Deoxys.
Apparently, Rayquaza was
threatened and thought Deoxys
was invading its territory.
Deoxys vanished deep into the
sea.
I don't get it.
How could it be the same Deoxys?
After getting beaten by Rayquaza,
Deoxys must have
slowly been regenerating.
Regenerating?
That's right. It has astounding
regenerative powers.
And that's what Professor Lund and I
have been studying all these years.
It sounds more like science
fiction.
This is something I'd love to
research.
But I wonder if..
..it could somehow get
in through a crack
in the wall.
[Gasp]
Knock it off Max!
Stop scaring us right now!
Haha. Just kidding.
There's no way it's coming in
through a crack.
[Screaming]
What was that?
Come on, Blaziken.
Blaze.
Pika.
[Chattering]
Pika!
Munch.
Hey, that's the Pokémon that
ate every bite of our food.
Are you stuck in there Munchlax?
Let's see.
[Groaning]
Oh, our sandwiches!
Everything but the peanut
butter.
Hmm.
And of course, that one was
mine.
[Minun and Plusle chattering happily]
Hold on.
Okay,
Please, just don't come any
closer you two.
Pika. Pikachu.
Munch.
- Aww, I'm so hungry.
- So am I.
Me too.
Muu? Munchlax!
Really? I can have it?
[Gasp in amazement]
Hmm?
[All] No, thanks.
Oh! [Groan]
[Groan]
We have to find food
and water right away.
Great.
And I'll try and find out where
those people were taken.
Yuko.
Take care of my sisters, please.
Of course.
But don't you worry about us.
You take care of yourselves.
We will.
All right, let's go.
Muuunchlax.
I'm worried, Max.
I really hope they're all okay.
Yeah, me too. I wish
they'd hurry and come back.
Plu-uh!
Min. Minu-min!
[Minun and Plusle chattering]
Still no good. Nothing's happening.
Yeah, it must be tied into the
town system.
I can see the food in there too.
We just need to figure out a
way to break in.
Pika-pika!
Hm?
Piika-chuuuu!
[Gasp]
It worked!
Pikachu, great idea.
Pikachu!
Whoa! Gotta catch 'em all!
Hah hah!
Pika-Pi.
Piikachu.
Pi?
Pika?
What is it, Pikachu?
Oh!
Look out!
- Run!
- Pika!
Pikaa!
Plusle! Minun!
Pluu! Min!
Get down!
Let go!
Chuuu!
[Yelling]
[Both Grunt]
Pikachu!
- Whaaa!
- Min!
Oh!
Nooo!
[Groaning]
[Minun yelling out]
Pika!
[Plusle chattering]
Here they all come, guys!
Pika!
Come on Tory. Let's go.
Looks like they're all gone.
That was close.
Oh Plusle.
It's all my fault.. I shoulda.
Mmm.
I'm sorry.
Pika.
Pika Pika.
Pikachu.
Ash.
Look what I just found.
Precious water.
All right!
Okay. So that's where they're
holding everyone captive.
I guess..
But what in the world for?
Release immediately.
[Fading voice] Release immediately..
[Powering down] Release.. Imm..edi..ate...
It let go.
But why?
[Roaring]
Hm? Go back.
Let me just take
another look at that.
Sure.
Skit?
Sur! Surskit! Surskit! Sur!
What is it?
What's wrong?
Pika?
Hm?
Blaze?
[Scream]
Let's get out of here.
Yes. There's an underground
laboratory.
Let's go!
Follow me.
Munchlax!
Try and stay calm.
Now go.
We should be safe down here for
the time being.
That's good.
Blaze. Blaze.
Pika.
What's this?
The lab where we studied Deoxys
and it's regeneration.
There were actually two of them
before.
Rayquaza defeated one, while
the other Deoxys was still
dormant inside of this meteorite.
- So then you're saying that..
- Yes, that crystal.
It's a part of Deoxys.
Part of what do you mean?
Pika.
[Gasp]
What?
Hey Tory, it's your friend.
Pika.
Wait a second.
Then Tory's friend is..
Right, it's Deoxys.
[Gasp]
Oh!
That's it.
It all makes sense.
This is Tory's friends, light
pattern.
And this is the pattern of the
aurora that covered LaRousse .
It's the same.
Yeah, I think it might be how
they communicate.
Oh, I see.
So, can you tell what it says?
Well, let's start with the
green pattern.
This one means friend.
And this one seems to be asking
"Where are you?"
So it's just looking for its friend?
Pika!
Of course! Deoxys carried off
all those people
and Pokémon because they were interfering
while it's searched for its friend.
What?
Deoxys see certain types of
electrical fields.
But it's not only electrical
devices that give off those fields.
So do people and Pokémon.
And they were blocking its vision.
That's why it's moving them out
of the way, to find it!
Mmm!
[Humming]
Please Yuko. You got to help
this Deoxys regenerate.
It's so sad.
It's been alone all of this
time.
You're right! Once Deoxys finds
its friend, it'll go back home.
Pikachu!
But the problem is the
emergency power were running on
now isn't nearly enough
necessary to operate this device.
If it's electricity you want,
then I'm your guy.
I can get the wind generators
going.
Can we help?
Yes, we'll need everyone's help
to save those people and Pokémon.
Let's start working on a plan
and then we'll go out to where
they're being held.
I'll zero in on it.
That's where they all are.
Great.
Let's go get them guys.
[All] Alright!
I'll never take an escalator
for granted again.
[Humming]
Oh!
Deoxys! We're not your enemies!
We're your friends.
[Humming]
If you just trust us, we can
help you find your friend.
I promise!
[Humming]
Blaziken use Flamethrower now!
Pikachu Thunderbolt 'em!
[Pikachu and Plusle yelling out]
Metagross, use Reflector.
Metaaa..
Quick! Now's our chance!
This way!
Now, Overheat!
Blaaaze!
Ooh.
You okay?
We're fine Ash, just go on!
Rafe can handle it.
Just don't let anything happen
to my sister's Ash.
You can count on that.
Blaziken, Overheat!
Blaze!
[Humming]
[Roaring]
[Roaring an attack]
Rayquaza has broken through.
What have I done?
[Humming]
Relax, Blaziken.
[Roar]
[Roaring]
Rayquaza!
Now what's that?
[Roaring]
Alright, now let's do it just
like we planned.
Okay, guys?
Gotcha.
We're with you Ash.
Munchlax!
Come on! There's no time for
you to go back for it.
Munchlaaax!
You ready?
Just about.
All we need the electricity,
But.. If we had that, we
wouldn't need to fix it.
What are they doing over there?
I'm hoping he pulls a sandwich
outta that box.
From your lips to my stomach.
You guys! We've come to help you!
Hey Ash. We're up here!
You got Pikachu and
Plusle, right?
Yeah.
We're all set.
- Pika!
- Plusle!
[Roaring]
[Humming]
[Growl]
[Ash] Pikachu,
[Troy] Plusle,
[Both] Thunderbolt, now!
[Both yelling out]
There's your electricity.
That's good.  Stop.
Alright.
We're recharged!
Yeah!
Alright!
Min mu-min!
Oof! Ouch.
[Plusle and Minun chattering happily]
You were great Tory.
[Roaring]
[Humming]
[Panting]
[Humming then roaring]
[Roaring]
[Roar]
[Humming]
[Roaring]
- Let's go.
- Yeah.
Pika.
That should do it.
Coming down.
Hey May, I'm coming for ya!
Was that Sid?
[Both] Oh! And Rafe!
Maaaay!
Oof!
Gross.
Metagross.
Audrey. Catherine, you okay?
Uh-huh! We're fine.
Where's Ash and the others?
They went back to the
laboratory.
Okay.
Are you ready to get started on
this?
Perfect.
The powers back on.
Yeah, those guys pulled it
off.
Mhmm.
Blaziken!
Metagross.
My cramp's getting a cramp
We're always spinnin' our wheels
but dis is ridiculous.
Just petal!
I'm set.
Are you both ready to use the
laser?
Yes.
I think you should turn it on Tory.
It is your friend, after all.
So you should do it.
Hmm!
Pi?
Here goes.
Still no good.
Oh, no, we're still 20 percent
short on energy.
Wow, we're so close.
Okay, Pikachu,
Plusle, Minun. You know what to
do.
- Pika!
- Min!
Plusle!
Great idea.
We got just what we need.
It works.
Alright!
[All gasp]
We did it!
Deoxys.
It's really you.
[Humming]
Deoxys.
Do you want to go find your friend now?
[Humming]
Oh!
Pika!
[Humming]
[Roaring]
Oh!
[Trilling]
The force field's gone.
Just like that?
[Roaring]
[Humming]
[Roar]
Pika!
[Humming]
[Laughing]
- Pika.
[Roaring]
- Oh!
- Pika!
[Roaring]
Hey, knock it off!
Stop Rayquaza!
Pika!
[Roaring]
Warning! Warning! Warning!
Danger.
Danger. Danger.
Evacuate. Evacuate.
What happened?
Security somehow started up.
[Roaring]
Warning. Evacuate.
Warning.
Ee..vacuate.
Ee..vac..uate..
Somehow security has
gone on overdrive.
It won't shut down.
- Yuko!
- Professor Lund.
[Roaring]
[Humming]
Everything's totally out of control!
Ash, I'm scared.
[Roaring]
Rayquaza! Deoxys!
Pika!
Whoa!
Plusle. Minun.
Pikachu!
They almost hit us that time.
Let's try and get back to Yuko.
Tory can you hear me?
- Tory!
- Daddy!
You must listen to me
very carefully.
As you can see, all of the
block robots are malfunctioning.
The chief robot, which controls all
other block robots should be near you.
We no longer have power over
that robot from the booth.
Understand?
So here's what you have to do.
And I need for you to be brave
Tory, do you have your passport?
You must present your passport
to the chief robot.
Then everything should unlock.
But, only for a very brief moment.
That should allow us just
enough time to regain control
and shut down the
security system.
Block robots are surrounding
the battletower.
Making any approach by us impossible.
Son, the fate of our
town is in your hands.
I know we can count
on you to...
Aah!
Warning. Evacuate
Warning.
Evac...
Don't you worry sir.
Pikachu and I are gonna
help Tory save this town..
..together.
Pika!
We've gotta get to that tower.
Look at that quick.
Let's go.
Okay. Just a little more.
Snorlax.
A Snorlax?
Uh, that's it!
Uhh. Sorry!
- Oh!
- Pika!
Hey, Ash!
Tory, don't worry. I'm okay!
I'll take care of this.
Pika!
Uhh, Pikachu!
Pi!
Pika Pi!
Wow. Cool. I'm right behind ya!
[Grunting]
Whaa!
Uhnn!
Pika-chuuu!
Whaa. Nooo!
Oh no!
Pikachu.
Ash!
Use my passport!
Throw it!
Ooh-ah!
Pika!
Pikachu!
Oh, ah! Pikachu!
Pika pika!
Pikachuu!
Uhhn.
Aaah!
This better wooork!
[Computer] Passport has been verified.
Disengaging all locks
I'm almost there.
Disengage!
[Ding]
It worked guys.
[Plusle and Minun chattering]
Oh no, Tory.
[Humming]
Deoxys!
Pika!
Pikachu
[Growl]
[Humming]
Pika pika!
[Laughing]
Hahaha!
Piikaaa!
[Roaring]
Snoor..Laax
Hmmm, snor.
Tory!
Daddy!
Tory.
Hi Dad.
I'm so happy you're safe,
but I'm only okay because of my
friends.
Come on guys, that tickles.
[Trilling]
[Humming]
Pika.
Goodbye.
I'll miss you.
I wonder where they're going.
Yeah.
But now wherever they go. They'll
always have each other.
Pikachu!
Hmm.
- Plu!
- Min!
Hey, Pikachu.
I'm glad that you and I will
always have each other
Pika
Pikachu!
I must've lost 20 pounds so far.
And you already lost your mind.
And I'm losing my patience.
So just shut up and keep pedaling!
Watch Movies, TV Series and Live Sports
Signup Here -> WWW.ADMITME.APP