These are legendary Pokémon, Molly.
Lots of people believe in them,
even though they've never seen them.
And in this book...the artist imagined
what some of them might look like.
This is the one
you're looking for, isn't it.
Yes...I've been looking for it
ever since...
for a long time now.
It looks funny.
There's Entei!
Entei looks a little scary to me.
But you like Entei!
Entei's real big and strong...but
it's still nice...just like you are Papa!
I'm like Entei, am l?. Imagine that.
Well, then I am Entei!
You're Entei!
Here we go!
Another e-mail!
It must be Schuyler again.
It's always him.
Professor... we found something. A hidden
chamber with new clues about the Unown.
Please come quickly.
I've got to go now, Molly.
Papa, I'm gonna miss you.
And I'll miss you.
I'll be back just as soon as I can.
Keep me close, in your dreams.
I love you.
Pleasant dreams Molly.
Here it is Professor.
I've never seen markings like this before
but they seem to be about the Unown.
What do you think?.
We'll see.
Well if anybody can figure out
what this says, it's you!
It's the Unown!
Professor?.
PROFESSOR!
This is awful...now the poor young Miss
is all alone in this world.
Papa, I saw the car and...
Molly...
I should tell her.
Papa...what happened to you?.
Unown!
They look...just like letters.
I can spell our names with the Unown.
Papa...
and Mama...
They're together...with me.
Unown!
Do you all wanna play with me?.
What's this?!.
What are they?!.
Those're the...Unown!
These are legendary Pokémon, Molly.
And in this book, the artist imagined
what some of them might look like.
Papa...
I'm like Entei am I?.
Well, then I am Entei.
Papa...please come back.
Are you the one
who has called me here?.
Are you my...
I am Entei.
Papa...it's you!
You look just like the Entei
in the storybook but it's you!
Papa...
Papa?.
If that is what you wish.
Step by step, Ash, Misty and Brock
continue their Pokémon journey...
wondering what adventures await them
as they travel into unknown territory...
never suspecting
that's exactly where this road leads!
Are any of you guys Pokémon trainers?.
Yeah...I'm Ash Ketchum from Pallet...
and I wanna be a Pokémon Master!
I'm Brock from Pewter City...
and I wanna be your boyfriend!
Thanks but no thanks.
I'm a trainer too wanna battle?!.
Go ahead Ash!
All right! A work out'll help me
stay in shape for the Johto League!
Excuse me, but first let's see
if you're even in my league.
Well get ready...
because I always play to win!
I have to admit I'm impressed Ash...
you're one of the toughest trainers
I've ever seen!
Aww thanks Lisa
but you almost beat me!
This is Ash's fifth battle this week...
his Pokémon are getting pretty tired.
Hey Lisa, would you happen to know...
if there's a Pokémon Center
anywhere around here!
There's one just over the mountains
in Greenfield.
Just over the mountains in...
Everyone's heard of Greenfield.
I've wanted to see it
ever since I was a little girl.
Me too! And I know
the quickest way to get there!
Greenfield's supposed to be
a beautiful little town,
with beautiful gardens and
a beautiful mountain...
with a beautiful mansion
right at the top.
Yeah, everything in Greenfield's beautiful.
Everything's beautiful in Greenfield, huh?.
Then I can't wait to see all the girls!
You can see Greenfield
from up at the top of the hill!
Greenfield's just as I imagined it
beautiful fields of flowers that...
turn into a bizarre crystal waste land
that obliterates the entire...
Hey what's going on?!.
I thought Greenfield was supposed
to be pretty...it looks horrendous!
Not only that...it looks b-a-a-a-d.
Yes, and things look bad enough
without you...back inside!
Officer Jenny!
Ready?.
Almost.
Tell me when.
In three, two...Hit it!
Behind me lies
the normally peaceful town of Greenfield.
But these green fields have suddenly
undergone a disturbing transformation.
Officials are baffled
by this shocking phenomenon,
which appears to have originated
from the hilltop mansion...
of renowned Pokémon researcher
Spencer Hale...
His wife mysteriously disappeared
two years ago...
How much more can Spencer go through?!.
Professor Hale is well-known as a leading
authority on so-called legendary Pokémon.
Hey, wasn't that Spencer Hale
one of your top students, Professor?!.
One of my very best ever.
In fact he recently sent me
some of his latest research.
What're they!?.
They're called Unown.
Unown?!.
Professor Oak, have you seen
the news about Greenfield!?.
I'm going there...this may be
connected with Spencer's research.
I'm going with you.
You've known Spencer
since you were a schoolgirl, haven't you.
I'm worried about him Professor...
and I'm worried about Molly.
So am I Delia. So am l.
I'm here in front of
the Greenfield Pokémon Center...
where an emergency response team
is just arriving.
I'm really glad you could come.
Professor!?.
Hello Pikachu!
And MOM?!.
Oh hi honey!
I didn't expect to see you kids here.
We didn't expect you either Professor!
We should've known
you'd come here to help.
How's my Pokémon Master?.
I'm doing great!
Papa...I want a Mama, too.
If that is what you wish.
I've known Professor Hale for years.
He used to study Pokémon
at Professor Oak's lab.
Then he moved away and became
a big famous Pokémon expert, right Mom?!.
Yes, but he and his family
came back to Pallet Town...
for a visit a few years ago,
don't you remember?.
Oh, yeah...sort of.
First Spencer's wife disappeared...
and now all this happens.
Really weird.
What's the matter Pikachu?.
What is that?.
Some weird kind of Pokémon?.
What are you doing here?.
I have come...for you.
You are...Mama!
Take me to her...
take me...to my...child.
MOM...PlKACHU!
I can't let them get away!
Ash, wait...you don't know
what's out there!
She's gone...I couldn't save her!
I have brought you what you wished for.
Mama!
You called me...Mama.
Yeah...And I'm Molly...remember!?.
Molly...
Mama...
Thank you Papa.
Can we all stay here forever?.
If that is what you wish.
Your world is getting bigger.
It's so pretty Papa.
I am happy...that you are happy.
The Pokémon that took
your mother was Entei.
Yes, one of the legendary Pokémon.
Professor, the other Pokémon must have
something to do with Entei's appearance.
You mean the Unown...
...the Pokémon you and Professor Hale
were researching when he disappeared.
They're inside that mansion.
Yes. I was afraid of that.
The mystery at Greenfield has taken
an even more disturbing turn...
as early this afternoon
our camera shot this startling video...
of a woman identified
as Delia Ketchum being abducted...
by a mysterious creature
as her son gave chase.
Now a bulldozer will try to break
through the crystallized landscape...
surrounding the Hale Mansion.
Go away!
Leave us alone!
I know it's...hard to believe...
but there's...no other explanation.
First Professor Hale disappears...
then this crystallization and now Entei.
The Unown must be behind it.
E-mail.
Mama and Papa and me just wanna stay
by ourselves forever so stay away!.
Everybody leave us alone!.
Did she just say her mother
and father were with her?!.
That couldn't be...you said
Professor Hale disappeared, didn't you?!.
And what about her "Mom?"
Very strange.
This is just like before Papa.
I'm not gonna wait
around anymore...Pikachu.
It's up to us to save Mom on our own!
Stop right there!
I'm going too!
And you're not leaving me behind!
Guys you're...the best!.
What's this?.
If you're gonna do something crazy,
at least take my Poké Gear.
Lisa!
You can use it to stay in touch
with the Pokémon Center.
And if Professor Oak finds out
what you're doing, it won't be from me!
You're a real pal.
At least the water didn't
turn to crystal.
We should be able to get to the mansion
if we follow this stream.
Hey it's the twerps...
they're walking through a stream
coming from that wacky building!
There must be
some valuable Pokémon inside!
And the only way to get there
must be by wading!
That's right!
But they're walking through the water!
They're wading.
No they're walking!
They're wading!
How could they be wading
if they're walking?!.
They're walking through the stream?!.
THEN THEY'RE WADlNG!
What's that!?.
It looks scary.
Do you think it'll attack us?!.
It's probably...harmless.
Team Rocket's...
A sneak attack...it's not fair!
Yeah, that's usually our job!
What is all this!?.
Well it's not my idea of decorating!
Will you be serious James?. We've got to
find a way to get out of this predicament!
You think we could shimmy
up to the tower?.
It might take us hours
to get to the top.
We could try to go to the bottom.
That's where we usually wind up anyway.
Wonder how long it would take.
About three seconds...if we jump!
Did you make them go away?.
Yes...they won't bother us again.
Look Mama. They're showing our house
on television. It looks nice!
We're coming to you
again live from Greenfield,
where just a few moments ago
a hot air balloon was shot down...
after invading the air space
above the unusual crystal structure.
Seemingly nothing can break...
through the fortress-like growth
that has engulfed...
Huh?. It's a Pokémon!
Now...Bulbasaur, Chikorita,
use Vine Whip!
You'll be nice and dry in here Togepi.
What's he...!?.
That boy's looking for trouble.
He's looking...for his mom.
I don't understand Mama why is
that boy trying to get into our house.
That looks like...
Ash, get down from there this second!
Mama...what's wrong?.
Oh...nothing.
Isn't that a Pikachu on that boy's back?!.
A Bulbasaur and a Chikorita!
I think that boy must be
a Pokémon trainer, don't you Mama?!.
Uh...yes.
I bet he has lots of other Pokémon
with him too...right Papa!?.
Papa?!.
Thanks for a great job Noctowl.
And we couldn't made it without you guys
...you deserve a rest.
Are you guys OK!?.
Ash, we just saw you on TV
what do you think you're doing?.!.
I just had to come here Professor Oak
...I shoulda told you.
That's right you should have but
we'll talk about that later...
after you get your mother
out of that place.
Ash, this is Schuyler,
have you seen any Unown?.
No...not yet.
Listen...we've been examining
some of Professor Hale's research,
and we think we've finally
come up with an explanation...
for why all of this has been happening.
What is it Professor?!.
Unown have the ability to read
the thoughts of other life forms.
Even people!?.
Yes...and not only that. We believe
the Unown can create new realities...
...altering the world
using thoughts and dreams.
The Unown may be tapping into the
imagination of Professor Hale's daughter.
That crystal fortress could be one of
Molly's wishes...made real by the Unown.
Cyndaquil...Flamethrower!
Let's do it...
FLAMETHROWER!
Good job Vulpix!
All right...second team!
Use your water gun!
OK you go first Pikachu!
All right here we go!
Thanks Staryu, you were perfect!
Yeah, you too Totodile.
Hey what's goin on?!.
Maybe the Unown are creating a new reality
just like Professor Oak said.
That's it!
Whatever it is, we can't stop now!
Where are we?!.
This must be part of Molly's dream world
that the Unown created!
Oh no...what now?!.
Are they...Pokémon?!.
They kind of look like alphabet soup
without the soup.
I don't know about soup but if we're
not careful we'll wind up in hot water!
If we're quiet,
we can sneak by them...come on!
I haven't seen this many strange letters
since the last time I placed a personal ad!
I think that boy and his Pokémon
must be here in the house somewhere!
Shall I send them away?.
I wanna be in a Pokémon battle Mama!
But I don't know if I can.
You can...if that is what you wish.
Do you really...think I can?!.
That would be so great Mama.
A Pokémon trainer...
I could just imagine it.
Papa, maybe I'm not old enough
to have Pokémon!
You must believe you are.
I do Papa!
Entei!
The three of you're
Pokémon trainers, aren't you?.
What'd you do with my mother?!.
Then let's have a battle.
Don't change the subject...
now where's my mother!
You're not any fun.
You took my mother now where is she!
There's no Entei! There's just
my Mama and my Papa and me!
You liar!
Easy.
By any chance
would your name be Molly?.
That's right...my name's Molly Hale!
Brock, she can't be Professor Hale's
daughter. She's too old!
Don't forget Professor Oak said this is
Molly's dream world created by the Unown.
They can make anything
that girl wants to come true.
Anything?.
Are you gonna battle me or not?!.
Why waste your time battling him
when you can battle me.
All right.
No way!
They both came from that staircase...
that's gotta be where they've
been keeping your mother!
Let Brock battle her...
we have to go and find your mom!
Let's go Pikachu!
Would a three on three Pokémon battle
be all right with you Molly?!.
That's fine.
Zubat! I choose you!
This is for luck...
I choose you...Flaafy!
Zubat, Super Sonic Attack...
It's working Zubat...
OK now let's try a Wing Attack!
Look out Flaafy...evade it!
Nice Flaafy...
but it's coming back...use Headbutt!
Now use your Thundershock Attack!
Zubat, return!
You did your best!
You did it! You were great Flaafy.
This battle's just getting started.
Go, Vulpix!
I'm just getting started too.
And I choose Teddiursa.
A Teddiursa, huh?. Figures a cute
Pokémon trainer'd have a cute Pokémon.
Teddiursa's a lot more than just cute.
Teddiursa, Dynamic Punch!
Vulpix, use your Quick Attack!
Use your Fury Swipes Teddiursa.
At this rate
the match may not last much longer...
her dreamed up Pokémon're
tougher than real ones!
Hurry...before that kid sees us!
I don't like
the looks of this place Jess!
It's like a storybookland invented
by a five year old!
That's ridiculous James...just keep running
and leave the thinking to me!
Vulpix, return!
You're a great trainer Molly!
You are too!
If I even wanna have
a chance at beating you...
I better start to really rock'n roll!
And my Onix is just
how I like to "rock'n roll!"
"Rock'n roll" huh...that's funny.
Hey I made you laugh,
that's my first victory today!
I choose Phanpy!
Phanpy, use your Rollout Attack!
My little Phanpy's stronger
than Brock's giant Onix!
Molly have...you seen this?.
That's the book Papa always
used to look at with me.
Mama...I'm really glad you're here.
You're by yourself a lot,
aren't you Molly.
Have you been lonely?.
Maybe a little.
But I don't feel that way anymore...
I have a Mama and a Papa now.
Which one of you trainers
wants to battle me this time?.
I guess Brock couldn't beat her.
Molly cannot be beaten.
Entei must be...an illusion too!
Which one of you is
a stronger trainer than your friend?.
I am!
Hold it Ash...
Iet me battle Molly this time!
And who are you?.
My name's Misty.
I'm a Water Pokémon trainer...
and I used to be the leader
of the Pokémon Gym in Cerulean City.
You're a Pokémon gym leader?.!
You bet I am and one of the best!
You mean you don't have to be
a grown up to be a gym leader?.!
You can become anything you wish.
The real Molly must still be up
in that mansion with your mother.
Hurry up and find them Ash!
Since I'm a Water Pokémon trainer,
I'll just use Water Pokémon to battle!
OK. I'll only use water Pokémon, too!
I forgot...you can do
anything you want to here.
Come on, let's battle!
I'll take first.
I choose you...Kingdra!
I choose you Goldeen!
Nice job Kingdra, now try a Headbutt!
Goldeen, use your Fury Attack!
Good job Goldeen.
You earned a good rest.
You were great Kingdra!
How'm I doing Misty!?.
Not bad Molly!
How can we breathe underwater!?.
Go with the flow James. Sometimes
it's better not to ask questions!
Hey Jessie I got a question
that's better I shouldn't ask:
Do you think we're gonna get
a bigger part in the next movie?.
OK Mantine Tackle!
Mantine...try your Whirlpool!
Staryu's in trouble!
Now use Bubble Beam!
Staryu use Rapid Spin!
Beat that!
Wow Misty!
Mantine use your Take Down Attack!
Tackle it Staryu!
Papa...this makes me so happy!
I am happy...that you are happy.
I love you...Papa.
Mom!
Ash...is it really you!?.
Of course it's me. Are you OK?!.
I'm just fine now...
the one I'm worried about is you.
I wish I knew where you got
such a reckless streak!
I guess I got it from you!
That's her right?.
And the Unown...have you seen any?.
If you mean the Pokémon that brought
me here, no it left a while ago.
That was Entei. The Unown're
the Pokémon that made Entei...
and turned this place to crystal because
of the things in Molly's imagination.
Oh dear!
Come on Mom, we gotta get out of here!
OK.
Molly... Wake up, Molly.
Wake up.
I was dreaming Mama.
Molly...Iisten to me.
I'm very sorry Molly
but I'm not your real Mama.
You'll have to know the truth
sooner or later:. I'm really Ash's mother.
Don't you remember
when we played together Molly...
we were at Professor Oak's house
in Pallet Town.
We'll talk about it later
but we have to go.
But why?.
We have to leave now Molly!
I won't.
I won't!
N-O-O-O-O-O!
Hey Mom!
Mom are you OK?.
I'm fine.
Come on...Iet's go!
What is it Molly?.
Papa...that boy's taking Mama away.
Ash help!
Leave her here
and leave this place!
I won't do that Entei...
she's my mother!
No...now she is Molly's mother.
Well she's coming with me.
She is staying here. Leave this place
or you will be made to leave.
That's what you think!
Totodile...I choose you!
You think you can defeat me!?.
I'm not gonna lose to some illusion!
Totodile, Water Gun Attack!
You fool!
See if this is an illusion!
Totodile, return!
Well if water won't work
then I'll use fire!
I choose you Cyndaquil!
OK Cyndaquil, Flamethrower Attack!
Cyndaquil, return.
You're strong.
Now have I proven that I am real?!.
I don't believe anything
you're just the illusion of an Entei,
dreamed up by this little girl!
You're wrong Ash...you're wrong!
I am no illusion!
I am this girl's father.
And I must protect her.
PlKACHU!
Molly, only you can stop this...
think about your real mother
and your real father!
Think about them!
It's a little chilly in here!
What's going on!?.
This must be a battle.
And this must be the battlefield.
I can't believe it!
Charizard, you saved our lives.
Thank you!
Thank goodness!
Are you all right Molly?.
What is this?.
My friend Charizard!
Your friend?!.
All of my Pokémon are my friends...
we all work together like a family!
A family?!.
Then I will defeat your "family" too!
We won't let you fall!
We're like family too!
Brock...Misty.
I'd...say..."prepare for trouble"
but you're already in it!
That's right!
Hey don't steal my line!
The Team Rocket's helping out again!
Why're you helping out?!.
You're bad guys!
Uh, well...
You see...
...it's really very simple!
If anything ever happened to you
we'd be out of show business!
If you come with us...
you can have real Pokémon!
I already have real Pokémon...
now go away!
Charizard!
I don't care
if you're a real Pokémon or not.
You can't take
the place of her real father!
I am Molly's real father!
As long as that is her wish.
Molly!
Charizard, use your Flamethrower!
Quick Charizard, try another one!
Papa, no!
Don't hold back.
Give it everything you've got!
Please Entei listen to me...
don't do this!
If you really care about Molly...
you'll let her come with us!
It's not right for her to stay here
with you...you have to let her go!
Whether it is right or wrong...
I will do as she wishes!
Flamethrower!
We've gotta do something charizard.
We've gotta get Molly out of here!
Entei don't!
This will end it.
Stop!
No more fighting...
Please Papa, no more.
You're a great Pokémon trainer, Molly!
A big part of battling
is knowing when to stop.
You already have the right instincts.
I bet you could be a gym leader easy...
if you wanted to.
You see Molly?.
We always battle hard but...
we always stay friends.
Because we all love Pokémon!
Come with us Molly!
On the outside,
the battles might be hard...
But the friends are real.
What dou you say?.
It's just what your...
Papa would want.
I want things real again.
Papa!?.
I was created to be the father
who could make you happy here.
If you would be happier outside
in the real world...I must go.
Let's stay calm!
This way!
Charizard...you take Molly.
Come on, let's go!
Professor...something's happening!
It's the Unown. They've generated
so much psychic energy...
that they're unable
to control it any longer!
The crystallization is
heading straight this way!
Listen to me...get out of there
or you could be trapped forever!
Right.
There's pandemonium here
at the Greenfeild Pokémon Center...
as the entire structure is being engulfed
by the crystal formation.
We can't stay!
Right...Iet's go!!
The Unown're causing this!
We have to find a way to stop them!
Some kind of barrier's protecting them!
Try to break through it!
You try Pikachu...use your Thunderbolt!
Pikachu are you OK!?.
This is a very dangerous situation!
Well whenever the going gets tough,
Team Rocket gets going.
Yeah, on the double.
Go Team Rocket!
Let's turn back!
It's too late, somebody H-E-L-P!
Let us out of here, now!
Molly...
I was...happy...and proud...
to be your father.
The last thing I can do for you
is to take you out of this place.
But how?.
I was born of your dreams.
If you believe in me,
there is nothing I cannot do.
Papa!
Molly...help me!
Molly...you have to believe in Entei!
Believe it can stop the Unown and it will!
Believe in me, if that is what you wish.
You can do it Entei.
Molly...
Molly.
I must go now Molly.
Entei!
I'm gonna miss you.
And I will miss you.
Just keep me close in your dreams.
Papa...
You were right about Greenfield!
I told you it was beautiful!
And it's real!
Great job...everything's back to normal!
You can tell officer Jenny that we've
got the situation under control here...
Molly's OK. It's all good!
Thank you Entei.
Come on Molly...
you wanna go see everybody?.
They were really worried about you!
Young Miss!
Well we can't get out
of this tower now!
Not with all those police around!
Guess we're stuck here all alone.
We should be happy!
How could we be happy,
we didn't capture one new Pokémon!
I'm happy for that little girl.
She was adorable yet indomitable
...just like me!
And that Entei was powerful
and inscrutable...just like me!
And that Meowth was lovable
just like...ME!
What does it matter if we failed
at catching a Pokémon this time!?.
We'll get another chance
to fail next time!
And so until next time...
Team Rocket's fading out again!