Watch Movies, TV Series and Live Sports
Signup Here -> WWW.ADMITME.APP
[Fanfare plays]
NARRATOR: In the world
of "Pokémon"...
there are as many stories...
as there are these
incredible creatures.
[Caw]
Some remain secret to all
but a select few.
Others have become
the stuff of legend.
And there are those
who were born of our dreams.
Rahr!
Like the Pokémon themselves...
these tales have survived
the test of time.
[Bing]
And with each passing day,
countless adventures unfold...
from the top of the world
to the bottom of the sea.
There are
over 300 known species...
that continuously add
to the "Pokémon" lore.
But they don't do it alone.
Humans and Pokémon
often team up...
for sporting competitions.
By combining strength,
courage, wisdom, and trust...
the partners hope
to emerge victorious...
in what are known
as Pokémon battles.
Together, Pokémon and humans
share the world...
in friendship, peace,
and harmony.
But not all intentions
are pure.
Rahr!
There are those who
would take advantage...
of the most
fearsome Pokémon...
to achieve goals of control,
domination, and power.
Groudon,
an ancient Pokémon...
is so coveted
by the evil Team Magma.
And that is where
our story begins...
with a misguided search
by a relentless man...
hoping to fulfill
his lifelong wish for Groudon.
[Boom]
What he unearths instead
is an even bigger mystery...
and an even greater power...
that could make his wish
come true.
Ash Ketchum has wishes
of his own.
First and foremost is to be
the greatest Pokémon master.
And with Pikachu by his side,
he's well on his way.
Together, they travel
on a Pokémon journey...
meeting along
the way friends...
with hopes and dreams
of their own:
To discover new Pokémon,
to explore the world...
to become the very best
trainer ever...
and to meet lots and lots
of girls.
Well, I didn't say all their
wishes involved Pokémon!
The funny thing about wishes...
sometimes they really do
come true.
And that is why you must be
especially careful...
for what you wish...
because you just might get it.
[Dramatic music plays]
So, where's
the Millennium Comet anyway?
It won't appear for another
23 hours and 42 minutes.
Know-it-all!
Uh, oh!
Are we getting close to where
the festival is supposed to be?
It should be
in that valley up ahead.
Well, then I want
to get the first look.
Last one there is a slowpoke!
Max, you're a slow-bro!
Very funny, sis.
BROCK: Hey, I don't want
to be the slowpoke!
[Breathing hard]
Pika!
[Everyone breathing hard]
[Sigh]
Not much of a party.
Are you sure this is it?
This... is the spot.
Where is everyone?
Whaa! Boy, I'm starving!
Me, too.
Ash and his friends
have taken a detour...
from their Pokémon journey to
witness what few get to see...
the Millennium Comet, which
appears for only 7 nights...
once every thousand years.
They had hoped to take part
in the Millennium Festival...
but their true role
in the legend of the comet...
will be far greater than they
could ever have dreamed.
[Rumbling]
Pi.
Pika.
Unh...
[Moaning]
Aww...
- Aww...
[Brakes screech]
ALL: Aww!
- Aww...
- Pika.
Hhmm!
Hhmm-huh!
Hhmm...
Huh!
Haa!
- Ahh!
- Pika!
Hhmm!
ALL: Ahh!
[Ding ding]
- Ha ha!
- Pika!
Yeah!
Got ya!
Hey, come back here!
MAY: Wait up!
Excuse me.
How about we share a ride
that's built for two-ooo!
JAMES: This is
the best job ever!
We just have
to throw around paper!
And clean manure,
whatever that is!
How bad could it be?
Huh?!
ASH: Check this out!
So, what is it?
Hey, that's the magician
we saw last night.
- You're right!
- Pika!
ASH: If that's how "The Great
Butler" builds his tent...
then I can't wait
to see his show!
Hah!
[Chirping]
ALL: Ahh!
Whoo-hoo!
Kirlia!
Kir... lia!
Ahh!
Hhmm... hhmm.
Whoa! What a trick!
ALL: Ahh!
VOICE: Wish... the star!
Huh?
Making beautiful girls appear
magically from thin air...
I've finally found
a career for me!
[Applause]
You are too kind!
For me the real magic's
when I hear your applause.
Thank you very much!
I am known as
The Great Butler!
[Applause]
And this is
my assistant, Diane.
I couldn't do the show
without Mightyena!
Rahr!
BUTLER: And Kirlia!
- Kirlia!
- Rahr!
VOICE: Wish Maker...
the comet.
Huh? The comet?
Aww.
Uh... where are you?
VOICE: I wish you were here...
with me!
You're... in there?
- Aah!
- Uhh... huh.
- Max!
- Ohh!
Hmm?
Hey! You have to get
back to your seat.
Sorry, but I thought
I heard a voice.
BOTH: Huh?
- Oh.
- Hmm.
ASH: Max!
Sorry about my friend.
Max, what's gotten into you?
Wait...
Ladies and gentlemen!
It seems we have some volunteers
to help us with our next trick!
Gentlemen, you must be
in show business...
because your timing
is impeccable!
BOTH: Huh?
Fellow magicians,
what are your names?
My name is Ash.
I'm Max... the Great.
Pikachu!
Let's do it!
Since you're obviously
great magicians...
feast your eyes
on Butler's burning box!
You must simply escape the box
before it bursts into flames!
- Burning box?
- Pika.
That's your cue.
But, Diane,
we're not really magicians.
Yeah, yeah, sure.
And we're not really clowns.
It's just not fair
that Max and Ash...
get to be in the show
and I don't!
You said it!
If there's anyone
who should be sharing...
the same stage as Diane,
it's me!
- Uhh...
- Ohh...
BUTLER:
Dusclops, step forward!
Dusclops.
BUTLER: Real magicians
like Ash and Max...
should have no trouble easily
escaping from a box like this.
So, to make it interesting...
they only have ten seconds
'til Dusclops destroys it...
with his hyperbeam!
Ten...
Ooh, they're stuck
in a dark place...
with impending
doom and no way out.
- Eight...
- That sounds like my life.
How are we supposed
to get out?
I don't know, Ash.
Must be some trick...
- five, four...
- I hope, or this could end bad.
- Three...
- Dus...
- two...
- Ooh!
One!
Dusclops, hyperbeam!
Dus!
ALL: Oohh!
Oohh!
Ohh... unh!
Not only did they escape
from the box just in time...
but they made bouquets
of flowers appear as well!
Let's thank those
amazing magicians...
Ash, Pikachu,
and Max the Great!
[Fanfare]
Ha ha! Thank you!
Thank you!
- Bravo!
Do you think they'll tell us
how they did it?
Do you think they'll
introduce me to that girl Diane?
Aw! Yeah!
- Pikachu!
- Pika!
Now that's magic!
Pika...
chuuuu!
Give it up! Your Pika-power
won't work in our zap-trap.
Aah! Aah!
BOTH: And now
on with the show!
Team Rocket,
give me back my Pikachu!
Ladies and gentlemen...
For our final trick
of the evening...
we're going to make
all the Pokémon disappear!
This is the best part
of the show!
[All laughing]
MEOWTH:
So who's the clowns now?!
You can keep our salary.
We'll take our pay
in Pokémon!
- No!
Stop 'em!
- I'll get 'em...
- I'll do it!
Behold!
We have one final performance
as our encore!
Now, Dusclops...
Capitata!
Dus... clops!
Aah!
Pika!
Pikachu!
Ha! Let's have
an encore of our own!
Pika... chu!
Rahr.
No magic show would be complete
without a vanishing act...
and so we saved
the best for last.
Dusclops, use Night Shade!
Dus... clops!
Looks like Team Rocket's
blasting off again.
Bravo! Bravo!
Everyone thinks that Team Rocket
was part of the show.
Yeah. But they won't be back
for a curtain call.
[Ash and Max laughing]
Ha ha...
[Screaming]
ASH: Jirachi?
Mm-hmm.
According to the legend...
Jirachi is a very special
Pokémon that awakens...
just once every thousand years.
I think... it's sleeping
right inside here.
BROCK: It's like a cocoon.
- Awesome.
- Pika.
Oh, that's amazing.
So the voice that Max heard...
Yes. It is said that in order
to awaken from its slumber...
Jirachi needs for
two things to happen:
The Millennium Comet must be
visible in the night sky...
and Jirachi must find itself...
a friend.
It needs a friend?
Is that why
it was talking to Max?
So now we just need
the Millennium Comet.
Hmm, and that's tonight.
Aww!
Hello... Jirachi.
First, Max was
hearing things...
and now he's made friends
with a big rock.
Cut it out!
You're just jealous
that Jirachi chose me...
to talk to as his friend
instead of you!
They also say Jirachi has
the power to grant wishes...
but it can't do anything without
first having you as its friend.
Oh, OK, I'll do it.
Max, meet Jirachi.
How do you do?
- Aww...
- Pika.
Wow. Max, can I see
what it feels like?
Let me see!
I thought it's crazy
to be friends with a rock!
Yeah, well, I was just kidding.
Please, let me just hold it.
No way!
Hey, get back here!
MAX: I can't hear you!
MAY: I said I was sorry!
- Hmm.
[Riders screaming]
MAY: Wow, look at this!
You have excellent taste,
young lady.
That's a wishing star.
A wishing star?
It works with
the Millennium Comet.
On each of the seven nights
that the comet appears...
all you have to do is fold down
one of the sections...
and make a wish.
ALL: Ohh.
If you do it all seven nights,
then your wish will come true.
Wow! I'll take it!
A wise choice.
But you only get one wish,
so make it count.
Uhh.
Whoa. Would you look at that!
Won't be long
before the comet appears.
Can you see that, Jirachi?
Fireworks!
It's getting cloudy.
We may not be able
to see the comet tonight.
No fair.
Oh. You and I are gonna
be best friends, Jirachi.
Mmm.
- Ha ha.
- Pikachu.
Ahh.
- Pika.
- Ahh.
Ahh...
Ahh.
BROCK: The Millennium Comet...
right on schedule!
- Ahh...
- Pika.
I'd better make my wish.
Once every thousand years.
We're so lucky.
It's been a long time since
people looked up in the sky...
and saw the Millennium Comet.
I wonder how different
our world looks from up there.
A lot of things have changed
in a thousand years.
And a lot hasn't.
Oh... huh?
Ohh...
Good night, Max.
Ohh... Mommy.
Hmm.
[Humming]
That's a lullaby
our mother always sang.
[Humming]
[Snoring lightly]
[Humming continues]
[Gasps]
PIKACHU: Pika.
JIRACHI, THINKING: The star...
the star is calling.
[All gasp]
You hear that?
Was that Jirachi's voice?
It's telepathy.
[Dramatic music playing]
Absol.
Ohh.
[All gasp]
Pika.
[Gasping]
Heh.
Uhh. Uhh...
Jirachi.
It's true.
Pika pika.
It's really kind of cute.
Hi. I'm Max.
[Thinking]
Hello, Max.
I'm Ash, and this is Pikachu.
And my name's May.
I'm Brock. Nice to meet you.
Pikachu.
Hello, Ash, Pikachu,
May, Brock.
[Pants]
Diane, it's Jirachi.
It woke up.
I'll go tell Butler
the good news.
Meanwhile, you guys can camp out
in our bus tonight.
BROCK: Thanks.
It was true.
I knew it!
Jirachi will be the star
of our greatest show!
[Dramatic music playing]
I've waited forever
for this day.
Hmm.
MAX: Hey, Jirachi,
can you really grant wishes?
Wishes?
Let's test it out.
I got to figure out
what to wish for.
Do you think I can try, too?
- Let me make a wish.
- Hey, I was first!
Hmm. Candy...
I wish for lots of candy.
- That's a dumb wish.
- No, it's not.
Candy?
Hmm.
[Chimes tinkling]
Hmm...
So, where's the candy?
MAY: It didn't work.
Yeah, I don't see
any candy anywhere. Hmm.
There's no such thing as someone
being able to grant your wishes.
I knew it.
Then how come your mouth
was watering?
Uh...
ASH: Hey, look.
- Huh? Ohh.
Candy!
Candy! Candy! Candy!
- Candy!
- Pika!
MAY: His wish...
It came true.
Way to go, Jirachi.
JIRACHl: Candy, candy!
[Gasps]
What's happening?
Whoa. Jirachi,
thanks for all the candy.
Candy, candy!
Hey, Jirachi, how about you
grant my wish next?
Wait, Jirachi.
It's my turn.
I wish for lots of girls.
You're after me, Brock.
And you're both after me.
[All talking at once]
ALL: Whoa!
[Gasps]
Huh?
[Both groaning]
- Pika.
- Uhh!
Where's Jirachi?
Jirachi's right here.
[Thinking]
Right here! Right here!
Uhh.
What happened?
I wished that I had
lots and lots of candy...
and then Jirachi
granted my wish for me.
Those are from the snack bar
in the park.
That's because Jirachi has
the power to teleport things.
- Huh?
Then the candy is all... yaah!
Free at last.
- Pika.
- What's the matter?
I'm ruined, I tell you!
I'm ruined!
[Sobs]
I knew something was funny.
Max, this is all your fault
with your stupid wish.
MAX: So what am I
supposed to do now?
Jirachi can put the candy
back where it came from.
That's it.
Jirachi,
get rid of the problem.
[Thinking]
Get rid of problem?
OK.
Huh?
- BROCK: Aah!
- She's gone!
- Disappeared!
- Pika!
Jirachi, what did you do
with my sister?
MAY: Help! Help me!
Someone get me out of here!
In there.
[Brock and Ash grunt]
JIRACHI, THINKING:
Sleepy.
Getting very sleepy.
Uhh.
Jirachi.
Is that all he stays awake?
He's just recharging
his energy.
Jirachi won't
hibernate again...
until the comet
is gone next week.
Ah. Thank goodness.
MAY: That wasn't
very funny.
Now what are we going to do
with all this candy?
We're going to have to carry it
back there ourselves.
We've got no choice.
Pika.
[Gasps]
Boy.
[Birds chirping]
Mmm.
[Dramatic music playing]
[Thinking]
Uhh.
Ahh.
Good morning, Jirachi.
How'd you sleep?
[Yawning]
Are you OK?
- Max.
- Yep. That's me.
Wish Maker.
[Both laugh]
Ha ha ha! Ta-da!
What do you think, Pikachu?
Pika pika!
You both look great.
And you look great
yourself, Diane.
Hey, guys. I'm going
to play with Jirachi.
Don't go too far.
And come back
before the show starts.
Don't worry.
JIRACHl:
Don't worry. Don't worry.
Max is sure in a great mood.
He and Jirachi
are already best friends.
Like brothers.
Mmm.
- Ha ha! Aah!
- Aah!
Aah!
[Laughs]
[Both laughing]
- Ah.
- Oh.
- Mmm.
[Both laugh]
- Ah.
JESSIE:
Jirachi?
Hey, that's the Pokémon
they say can grant wishes.
And it can teleport stuff, too.
Then our first wish
should be...
that it doesn't teleport itself
away from us once we capture it.
Could you have said something
even more ridiculous than that?
What if Jirachi grants
us just one wish only?
- You'd waste it on that?
- I didn't even think about that.
You might be right.
We might only get one wish,
and that's it.
We're going to need
the perfect wish.
JESSIE: I've got it.
Why don't we just wish
for a hundred more wishes?
It's genius.
JAMES: But, Jessie...
what if Jirachi teleports away
from us after the first wish?
MEOWTH: I wish I could teleport
away from the two of youse.
[Dramatic music playing]
Absol.
ASH: Hope you
enjoyed the show.
BROCK: Thank you very much.
[Crash]
Aah!
Unh! Help me, Max!
OK.
[Grunting]
[Thinking]
Max, let's go play some more.
[Straining]
Just a second!
Bet you can't catch me.
What are you doing?
- Wait!
- Aah!
JIRACHl:
You can't catch me!
Give it back!
Give me my glasses!
Come back here!
I'm going to get you!
JIRACHl:
You can't catch me!
May, what happened?
Jirachi happened.
- Pika.
- Uhh!
Ha ha! Here I am.
Jirachi!
- Got you!
- Gotcha, gotcha.
Come here.
[Both laughing]
- Huh?
[Wind blowing]
Huh?
Absol.
Uhh.
[Crash]
[Dramatic music playing]
Absol.
An Absol!
Sol!
Aah! Aah!
[Panting]
What is that?
An Absol.
It's a Pokémon that appears
only before a great tragedy.
Sol!
Aah! Uhh!
Max!
[Gasping]
Absol.
Torchic, I need you.
[Snap, energy surges]
[Chirps] Torchic.
Torchic, ember!
Torchic!
Sol!
Pikachu, use thunderbolt!
Pika.
Pi... chu!
Absol!
[Grunts]
Sol!
[Thinking]
Absol is here... for me.
- Huh? Aah!
- Pika!
- Pi! Pi!
- Aah! Aah!
- Pi!
- Torchic!
- Pika.
- Tor.
Sol.
Think it hates clowns?
Sol!
- Aah!
Absol.
[Thud]
A good magician always has
a trap door standing by.
[Click]
Ab... sol.
Final trick.
[Snap, energy surges]
[Growls]
Absol.
Kirlia.
Kirlia, hypnosis.
Ab...
sol.
Hmm.
Pika pi!
Pikachu.
Torchic, you're all right.
ASH: Why was Absol
attacking us?
Jirachi said Absol
came for him.
Is it possible
that they know each other?
Unlikely, since Jirachi's been
asleep for a thousand years.
What can you tell us?
[Thinking]
I am so sleepy.
[Sighs]
[Both snoring lightly]
[Panting]
With all the excitement,
I almost forgot.
It's night two of the comet.
Millennium Comet, won't you
please make my wish come true?
[Door opens]
Huh?
What's Butler's doing?
DIANE: I think Absol's here
to take Jirachi back to Forina.
Probably.
He belongs there. We should've
never taken him away.
I know what I'm doing.
Butler, please listen to me.
I have a sinking feeling...
that something terrible
is going to happen.
I've worked so hard
and waited so long for this day.
Now it's showtime.
[Moaning]
When you see the comet
with your true eye...
you will absorb
its tremendous energy...
and help make my own wish
finally come true.
Uhh! Uhh! Uhh...
Esteemed council
of Team Magma...
observe this fossilized
remnant of Groudon.
I have invented a device...
that will generate
a living, breathing Groudon...
right here, right now,
from this one small piece.
I give you...
a Groudon!
[Electricity crackling]
[Energy surging]
Uhh!
Aah!
[Crash]
[Gasps]
Huh? Uhh.
MAGMA BOSS: So, that's
a living, breathing Groudon?
I must say, it's not quite
as big as I had imagined.
I need a more powerful
energy source...
to spark
the regeneration process.
Enough of your mumbo jumbo.
[Grunts]
[Laughter]
We'll find Groudon ourselves.
You're no longer welcome
at Team Magma.
That's just fine. Uhh.
[Grunts]
This isn't the last
you'll hear from me.
Team Magma made
a mockery of my work...
but finally, I'll show them.
[Jirachi moaning]
Butler...
Now, Jirachi,
get me the energy that I need.
Open your true eye
and absorb the comet's power.
[Thinking]
I don't want to.
I'm afraid you don't
have a choice.
Dusclops, psychic.
Dusclops.
[Moaning]
Whoa!
Absol!
No!
MAY: Ash, Brock,
wake up. Wake up.
Huh?
I'm tired.
- Jirachi is gone.
- Huh?
[Grunts]
Jirachi!
[Pants]
[Jirachi screaming]
Ab... sol.
Uhh! No!
[Straining]
[Screaming]
Aah!
Pikachu!
[All gasp]
[Boom]
[Energy surging]
Aah!
[Boom]
Pika pi.
Uhh. Uhh.
Aah! Jirachi!
[Pants]
Uhh. Uhh.
Jirachi, I've got you.
What energy.
Now I just have to harness it.
What have you done to Jirachi?
- I'll take care of it.
- No way!
Butler, it's not
too late to stop.
Why would I stop
now that I've gotten so close?
Just have faith in me, Diane.
I'm doing it for you.
It's not for me.
I've never wanted this!
Diane!
Uhh! Dusclops, stop them now!
Dusclops!
[All gasp]
Pikachu, thunderbolt!
Pika! Pikachu!
- Ohh!
- Uhh!
Aah! Unh!
- Ab!
- Aah!
JIRACHI, THINKING:
I wish I was home.
I wish I could go to Forina.
Uh, where's Forina?
Max, hurry!
Everyone, follow me!
- OK.
- Chu!
Dusclops, after them!
Dus!
Sol!
Ab... sol!
- Uhh!
- Ohh!
Ab...
sol. Ab.
Uhh. Go, Mightyena!
[Snap, energy surges]
Grr! Yena!
[Dramatic music playing]
JAMES:
That's Butler's bus.
Yeah, but that magician
ain't inside.
But Jirachi is.
Very interesting.
Wobbuffet!
- Oh!
- Mmm.
[Panting]
Yena!
[Beeping]
[Music ends]
DIANE: Jirachi said
it wanted to go back to Forina?
Mm-hmm.
He wants to go home...
back to where Butler
found him.
Now that I have this...
we can finally have
the last laugh on Team Magma.
[Laughing]
DIANE: Butler was once
a scientist for Team Magma.
He was working
on the Groudon project.
MAY: Groudon?
Isn't that
the legendary Pokémon...
rumored to have
incredible powers?
Yes. And Team Magma
will stop at nothing...
to get their hands
on Groudon.
Butler tried
to make them a Groudon...
but his experiment failed.
I don't get what Jirachi
has to do with all this.
Well, in order to power
his machine...
Butler needed
an energy source...
that's available once
every thousand years.
Every thousand years?
- Pi?
- Ohh.
MAY: The Millennium Comet.
DIANE: Jirachi can absorb
the comet's power.
Butler would use this energy
to make a Groudon...
by draining all of the comet's
power from Jirachi's body.
Sounds like that could
really hurt Jirachi.
Yes.
Uh...
[Moans]
Why is Butler doing this?
DIANE: He wants revenge
against Team Magma.
Well, let him get revenge
some other way.
We can't let him hurt Jirachi.
Spoken like a true
best friend, Max.
Pika.
BROCK: So, what's the plan?
Jirachi said it.
Take him to Forina.
Right, Diane?
- Let's go.
- Ah.
[Beeping]
[Dramatic music playing]
[Click]
Diane, I thought you
of all people...
would understand my feelings.
Huhh. It's time.
[Music ends]
[Groaning]
[All groaning]
Pika!
[Laughing]
[Beeping]
[Beeping stops]
Night three.
Hmm.
PIKACHU: Pi.
[Snoring lightly]
Pi.
- Mmm.
- Uhh.
Huh?
So, what's everyone doing?
Well, Ash, Max, and Jirachi
have fallen asleep.
[Turns on water]
Butler and I have known
each other since we were kids.
I knew even then
that we'd always be together.
He always had a way
of making me smile.
BUTLER: And now
for my greatest trick.
Unh.
One, two, three!
Ah!
Please, hold your applause...
until you see
the Butterfree!
[Claps hands] Oh!
That was really great, Butler.
Hey, I like that...
the Great Butler.
[Laughs]
[Dramatic music playing]
It sounds like you guys
had lots of fun.
It's been a very long time...
since I've seen Butler
laugh like that. Mm.
[Snoring lightly]
I just hope that
once the comet leaves...
the real Butler comes back...
and we can get on
with our lives.
[Snoring lightly]
[Music ends]
[Dramatic music playing]
ALL: Uhh!
Uhh!
[All slurping]
[Straining]
ALL: Uhh!
Uhh. Yeah!
[All laugh]
ASH: It's all
in the wrist, Max.
MAX: Here goes. Unh!
Yeah! I did it!
Yay! Yay!
[All laugh]
[Sighs]
- Huh?
[Laughs]
Ohh.
[Music ends]
Just two nights left.
MAX: Cut it out, May!
Huh?
Unh! Quit counting already.
Sorry.
[Dramatic music playing]
Huh?
- What's wrong?
- Pika.
I just have a couple of days
left with Jirachi.
Jirachi's going to be with you
your whole life...
not just a couple of days.
You know that's not true, Ash.
You see, sometimes
friends have to go away...
but a part of them
stays behind with you.
It's especially true
when the friends...
are best, best friends.
You'll remember
Jirachi forever...
and he's gonna always
be in your heart.
A good friend left me, and...
I miss her every day.
But I...
I know we'll always
be friends forever.
Pikachu!
Mm.
[Music playing]
- There's Forina.
- It's awesome.
Jirachi's home.
[Music playing]
[Chattering]
[All gasp]
[Slurps]
[Buzzing]
Nuzleaf.
Do you like it?
What's not to like?
- I love it.
- Pika!
Uhh! Ha!
Uhh! I'm stronger
than you, Max!
Stronger than Max!
[Both grunting]
[Both laugh]
Max, it's time
to go to sleep.
I want to stay up
a little longer.
You have a big day
ahead tomorrow...
and you don't want to be tired
for it, do you?
Aw, I hate it when you make
more sense than me.
[Grunts]
But I doubt I can sleep knowing
it's my last night with Jirachi.
I got it. Once they fall asleep,
we'll get up and play.
Good idea.
Mm.
[Laughs]
[Sighs]
[Breathes in]
[Singing lullaby]
Pi...
[Chuckles]
[Singing fades]
[All gasp]
Sol.
Absol's going to lead the way.
- ALL: Ahh!
- Pika!
[Squawking]
- Breloom!
Breloom!
Ohh.
Hey, check it out.
[All gasp]
[Hisses]
Linoone.
- Electrike.
- Nuzleaf.
[Squawks]
[All gasp]
A Flygon!
Oh! They're all here
to welcome Jirachi back home.
Yeah.
Ohh.
- Ohh.
The spot where Jirachi slept
for 1,000 years is just ahead.
Ab...
sol!
[All gasp]
JIRACHl: The star...
it calls me.
Huh?
Jirachi!
I don't want you to go!
[Crying]
I'm gonna miss you.
I don't know if you can really
grant wishes, but if you can...
then I have a big one
for you right now.
I wish you didn't have to go
so we can stay together forever!
Pika.
Max, the star...
I must.
Oh.
Jirachi is getting ready.
Ready for what?
DIANE: Jirachi will open
his true eye...
and use it to absorb energy
from the Millennium Comet.
What does it do
with the energy?
Where's it go?
DIANE: They say that
during the 1,000 years...
that Jirachi sleeps...
all the energy
he absorbed from the comet...
is slowly released
into the earth.
Everything that grows in Forina
feeds off that energy.
So, then Jirachi
helped make all this?
Wow.
[Clanging]
Jirachi!
[All gasp]
What's happening?
It's a trap.
[Both gasp]
Showtime!
And, like every great magician,
I saved my best trick for last!
- Butler.
- Let Jirachi go!
For their finale, most magicians
would probably end their show...
with something very obvious,
like making a Pokémon disappear.
But, since I'm not
like most magicians...
for tonight's show, I'll be
making a Pokémon reappear!
You're mad!
Not mad. Just a little angry...
and maybe a wee bit impatient
to get on with the show.
[Surging]
Ladies and gentlemen,
boys and girls...
it's the moment
you've all been waiting for!
- Jirachi!
- Uhh!
[Dramatic music playing]
So, Jirachi, let's do this
just like we rehearsed it.
[Zap]
See that?
- Do you think I'm blind?
- That would explain the hair.
[Whoosh]
[Clicking]
[Machines whirring]
Now Team Magma will learn
to never have doubted me!
Pika... chuuuu!
It's no good.
Pika.
Absol!
[All gasp]
Pika!
Sol!
[Squawking]
Flygon!
[Squawks]
Flygon, you've gotta try
to get us up there if you can.
[Squawks]
All right!
I'm coming with you!
Pika pika!
All right. But just hang on
as tight as you can.
- Pikachu!
- Time to save Jirachi.
[Squawks]
Yeah!
Careful.
[Both grunt]
[All gasp]
Just seconds from now...
Groudon will return to life
and prove that I was right!
[Flygon squawks]
Ohh!
Jirachi!
Uhh!
[Squawks]
[Rumbles]
[Roars]
BUTLER: Salamance,
get rid of them!
[Roaring]
[Squawking]
Salamance!
[Roaring]
Hunh!
Flygon, watch out.
[Squawking]
Max and Pikachu,
you go free Jirachi.
Flygon and I
will distract Butler.
- Mm!
- Pika!
ASH: Stop that machine!
Pikachu!
Jirachi.
Pika... chuuuuu!
[Machine powers down]
Uhh! Uhh.
[Machine stops]
ASH: Good job, guys.
Get on.
[Grunts]
Jirachi, can you hear me?
Say something.
[Gasps]
He's closing his true eye.
Uhh...
M-Max!
Jirachi!
Pika!
You're OK!
Sol.
Hmm?
[Squawks]
[Both grunt]
Thank you, Flygon.
[Squawks]
MAY: Max!
BROCK: Ash!
Jirachi?
He's OK.
Same with you?
Yeah.
[Crying] I was really
worried about you.
I'm OK.
[Rumbling]
Hmm.
[Snarls]
[Crackling]
[Roars]
It can't be.
What's that?
That's Groudon?
[Metal screeching]
[Snapping]
[Crash]
[Trees cracking]
[Roars]
Uhh. That creature's
not Groudon.
The trees are all dying!
The earth...
It's sucking energy
from the earth.
Huh?
Sol!
- Absol!
- Pika!
Sol!
[Roars]
Linoone! Linoone!
Chyena!
[Chattering]
Electrike!
[Shrieks]
[Roars]
[Panting]
[All gasp]
[Grunts]
Butler, please tell me
you have a plan to stop this!
No. I don't.
I have nothing up my sleeve.
No tricks left.
Maybe now's not
a good time...
For us to drop in
unexpected.
MEOWTH: Yeah.
[Altaria chattering]
[All screaming]
Sol...
Absol.
[All chattering]
They're trapped inside!
It's sucking up
all the Pokémon!
[All shouting]
ALL: Breloom!
Breloom! Breloom!
ALL: Nuzleaf!
Nuzleaf! Nuzleaf!
This wasn't supposed
to happen.
That's not Groudon.
It's evil. It's pure evil.
[Gasps]
[Both grunt]
- Aah!
- Diane!
[Screaming]
Ohh! My darling,
if this is the end...
then I'm glad
the last thing I see is you.
Uhh!
[Gasps]
Diane!
It got her!
Oh, no!
ASH: And now it wants us!
Uhh!
[Roars]
[Panting]
[Screaming]
- It got 'em!
- Oh, no!
Max!
- Aah!
[Panting]
[All screaming]
Pi! Pi! Pi!
[Screaming]
[Zap]
[All grunt]
- Pika?
- Huh?
[Roars]
[Panting]
[Screaming]
[Roars]
[All scream]
Pika.
Watch out!
It's after Jirachi's energy!
It is?
[Roars]
[All screaming]
[Squawks]
It's Flygon!
[All grunt]
[Squawks]
[Squawking]
It's too fast!
It's catching up!
Pika!
[Jirachi grunts]
[Squawks]
[Squawking]
[Roaring]
Listen to me.
I'm going to need your help.
We have to stop
this creature...
and there's only
one way to do it.
Yeah, what?
Jirachi should be able to absorb
energy out of that monster...
if we put him back
on my machine.
We just have to reverse the
polarity and it should work.
I'm not sure I trust
any plan of yours.
You've got to!
Uhh! I just want to save Diane.
Uhh...
Pika!
[All gasp]
Aah!
[Roars]
Uhh! Aaah!
- Butler!
- Aah!
[Grunts]
[Shrieks]
Aaaaah!
[Roars]
Uhh!
[Roaring]
Jirachi, you saved him.
Butler can't be all bad.
Uh...
He loves Diane.
Uh.
Mm-hmm.
[Both screaming]
[Groaning]
BUTLER: The monster
will keep chasing Jirachi.
Keep it distracted
and I'll set everything up.
ASH: You got it.
You ready?
We're gonna have to do...
whatever it takes
to save May, Brock and Diane.
- Mm!
- Pika pika!
[Dramatic music playing]
[Squawks]
Let's go!
[Squawking]
Yeah, our plan's working.
[Roars]
Uhh!
[Gasps]
[Metal creaking]
[Grunting]
[Cranking]
[Squawks]
Once I reverse this,
it should be ready to go.
[Rumbling]
Aah! No!
Aah!
Uhh!
[Squawks]
[Sighs]
Way to go.
Mm.
Good.
Now place Jirachi there.
OK.
Jirachi, are you ready?
Let's do it!
Watch out!
[All scream]
[Roaring]
[Squawking]
This switch should do it.
Uhh!
[Screaming]
Butler! No!
Aaaah!
[Roaring and squawking]
[Roars]
- That's Flygon!
- Pika!
Uhh!
[Grunting]
Jirachi, it's up to you.
Ready? Here goes nothin'!
[Roaring]
Oh!
[Grunting]
Butler, careful!
Pika!
[Grunting]
This way...
I'll be with Diane.
[Roaring]
Ohh!
Chuuuuu!
[Screaming]
Pika! Pi!
Pika!
[All gasp]
Ahh!
[Dramatic music playing]
- Electrike!
- Breloom!
- Chyena!
- Nuzleaf.
Tar.
Pius.
- Tar.
Linoone.
Tar! Tar!
Sol!
Ab... sol.
Flygon!
[Roars]
[Groans]
[Grunting]
Ohh. Diane.
Ohh.
Oh, Butler.
- Oh!
[All grunt]
Pika.
[All gasp]
[All panting]
ALL: Ohh.
[Moaning]
Jirachi!
You're OK!
We did it!
You're the best.
No, Max. You're the best.
I made lots of wishes,
and you made them all come true.
He's right.
You made his wishes come true.
- Yeah.
Pika.
Now, Max, will you grant me
one final wish?
One final wish?
I'm feeling so sleepy.
I wish you'd sing
that song for me.
Jirachi...
The song.
He wants the lullaby.
We can all grant your wish.
That would make me happy.
Mm.
[Singing lullaby]
[All singing]
[Sighs]
Sol.
Thank you, everyone.
I couldn't have wished
for anything better.
[Singing continues]
[Choking up]
Bye!
[Dramatic music playing]
[All gasp]
- Hmm?
Good night, Jirachi.
I hope you have sweet dreams.
Pikachu.
Ahh.
Uh... Jirachi...
My heart...
That's where you'll be.
Mmm.
Is this an illusion
or am I just seeing things?
This all could've been just
another trick by that magician.
Maybe, but I feel
like I got my wish.
I'll tell you mine
if you tell me yours.
Meowth, maybe
you should go first.
Why don't we all say ours
at the same time?
ALL: If I could only have
one wish...
it would be
to always feel like this.
Diane and I will be
staying in Forina.
We both finally realized
what's most important...
and that's to be together.
I'm so happy for both of you.
You got your wish, Diane.
Yeah.
How about we give you guys
a ride back to town?
So just what was Diane's wish?
Well, I can't tell.
My lips are sealed.
That would be a first.
Hey, wait.
What about your
Millennium Comet wish?
Ohh!
Ohh.
I forgot to wish
the last night.
It doesn't matter.
We all have to make
our own dreams come true anyway.
Yeah, wishing would take
all the fun out of it.
Pikachu!
JIRACHI, ECHOING:
Max!
Huh?
I'll never forget you!
We'll be best, best friends
forever and ever.
Mmm.
[Music playing]
When daytime turns
to night
When the moon
shines bright
When you're
tucked in tight
When everything's
all right
Slip softly
to that place
Where secret thoughts
run free
And there
come face to face
With who you want to be
So swim across
the ocean blue
Fly a rocket
to the moon
You can change
your life
Or you can change
the world
Take a chance
Don't be afraid
Life is yours to live
Take a chance
And then the best
is yet to come
Make a wish
It's up to you
Find the strength
inside
Then watch your dreams
come true
You don't need
a shooting star
The magic's right there
in your heart
Close your eyes
Believe
And make a wish
[No audio]
[Singing in Japanese]
Ooh
I've always hoped
for happiness
And finally
fulfilled my wish
'Cause I just need
To see you smile
[Singing in Japanese]
Make a wish
It's up to you
Watch your dreams
come true
The magic's
right there in your heart
Believe
Make a wish
It's up to you
Find the strength
inside
Then watch your dreams
come true
You don't need
a shooting star
The magic's right there
in your heart
Close your eyes
Believe
And make a wish
Ooh
Make a wish
[Song ends]
Watch Movies, TV Series and Live Sports
Signup Here -> WWW.ADMITME.APP