Pika!
(narrator) The world of Pokémon...
a spinning globe of wonderment!
Home to an infinite array
of creatures
too varied to fully comprehend!
Hundreds, perhaps thousands,
meticulously fashioned
by the forces of nature
in all its glory,
as only nature can.
And no matter what corner of
the world you find yourself,
rest assured you'll find
Pokémon there as well!
Soaring overhead,
skimming the clouds,
and riding the currents undersea'
Sharing the mountains' majesty,
and animating our many
lush green forests/
Happily making their home
In fields of grass.
Exeggcutor!
While even our sprawling cities
are teeming with them!
Electrode, Electrode!
People and Pokémon
find common ground
sharing the goal of victory
in the Pokémon battle,
vying to become friends,
comrades and Pokémon masters!
Mag!
Mortar!
Magmortar!
Rhyperior!
Rhy!
— Rhy!
— Magmortar!
Which brings us to a young trainer
who has dedicated his life
to the love of Pokémon
and battling.
Ash Ketchum of Pallet Town
with his partner Pikachu,
working side-by-side,
catching Pokémon
and perfecting
the art of the Battle!
Traveling with good friends and
training with boundless energy!
For every Pokémon
our Heroes meet.
A new adventure
waits around the corner!
And, right now,
somewhere in this world,
a new Pokémon ls waiting,
poised to soon make itself
known to our heroes,
heralding the start of a new,
and fantastic adventure...
Combee!
Combee, Combee!
Min?
[sneezes]
Watch Movies, TV Series and Live Sports
Signup Here -> WWW.ADMITME.APP
Min!
[loud thud]
Min?
♪♪
(computer) Currently
making contact with Dialga.
Min!
Giratina has captured Dialga
and is returning to
the Reverse World.
(man)
They won't make it.
Find the next point of appearance.
As you wish, Zero.
Min!
Sheldon!
Has Giratina captured Dialga?
What is this?
What's it doing here?
Min!
Min?
(Zero)
What was that?
(computer) That was
not the work of Giratina.
It seems to be because of
that Pokémon.
Giratina approaches...
It's trapped!
Dialga must have
done something to it...
We've come too late.
(computer) lt appears after
coming in contact with Dialga,
Giratina is unable to leave
the Reverse World.
Time is now running in
an infinite loop around Giratina.
What this?
Min!
Min, Min!
♪♪
Pika!
(narrator) Wonders never
cease for Ash and Pikachu,
as their Pokémon journey continues!
With a little help from
his friends Dawn and Brock.
Piplup!
And in a beautiful setting
such as this,
a bite to eat
will never taste better!
There! Piping hot
- and straight off the grill!
- Wow!
Cool!
Let's dig in!
Pika, Pika!
Hold on a minute.
Did you wash your hands?
Uh...
Look, they're clean as a whistle!
Pika.
Ash Ketchum!
You should always remember to
wash your hands before you eat!
All right, whatever...
- Man what a pain...
- Piplup!
Piplup!
- Piplup, Pip!
- Pikachu!
I made more than
enough for everybody!
Pika!
Tada!
- My extra special Pokémon food!
- Lup!
- Piplup!
- Pika!
All right!
It's time to eat!
- Chi, Pachirisu!
- Ambipom!
- Bun, Bun, Bun, Bun!
- Swinub, Nub!
Hey, I'm not gonna
leave you guys out
Chimchar!
Char, Char, Char, Char!
- Twig, Twig, Twig!
- Bui, Bui!
Staravia!
Gliscor!
Wait'll you feast
your eyes on this feast!
Sudowoodo!
- Happiny!
- Sudowoodo!
Croag...
(Brock)
C'mon guys, quiet down a little!
(Dawn)
No shocking, Pachirisu!
(Ash)
Gliscor, don't push Chimchar!
Tasfy, huh?
- Calm down and eat...
- Min?
I'm getting hungry
watching them chow down!
Me too!
So, let's eat!
Hey, stop!
Those're our pancakes, you know!
- What is it?
- A Pokémon?
- Pika?
- Pip?
Pika, Pikachu!
Pip!
Piplup, Piplup, Piplup!
Pip, Piplup!
- Min, Min, Min, Min, Min!
- Pip?
Pi?
Piplup, Piplup!
- Pika?
- Pip, Piplup, Pip, Pip, Piplup!
Min, Min, Min, Min...
- Pip!
- Pika!
Piplup, Pip.
Uh-oh!
Min...
Pip!
- Pika!
- Piplup!
Piplup, Piplup,
Piplup, Piplup, Pip!
Min!
[Pokémon talking]
Min...
Stop it right now!
No need to worry.
Don't be afraid...
Min!
♪♪
Gliscor!
Gliscor...
Min, Min, Min, Min, Min...
Min?
There!
Nice and clean!
(Shaymin)
That did feel nice...
I'll bet it did.
Although it was a little chilly.
And perhaps if you'd
been the tiniest bit gentler...
- Huh.
Did you...?
Yeah, I heard it!
It's telepathy!
Okay, so where did you come from?
From over there.
From over where?
I said from over there.
And I said what do you
mean by over there?
Pika!
Well, if you head a little further
from over here
and then you head over there...
Something's not right!
It's got a fever!
Pika!
We should go to the Pokémon Center!
Yeah, let's hurry!
'Kay gang return!
Scor!
(Dawn)
Return!
Ambi!
(Brock)
Return!
Sudowoodo!
- You too!
- Croagunk!
(Nurse Joy) It's a Shaymin,
the Gratitude Pokémon.
It does look awfully tired...
Min.
Chansey!
But everything's just fine!
And this little Shaymin's
back to full health!
Shaymin...
- That's what it is.
- Pika.
- Pip, Piplup!
- The Gratitude Pokémon...
And my name's Brock,
the gratitude person!
I'm grateful to have met
you Nurse Joy!
Grateful!
Now, will you go out with me?
So grateful!
Of course we could
always just be friends!
Still more grateful!
Of course, perhaps...
Let's stick with the friend line...
Croag...
Piplup.
Min?
Chansey, Chansey.
Pip?
Piplup, Pip, Piplup!
Dear...
Where...where am I?
At the Pokémon Center!
Nurse Joy treated you,
and now you're all better!
Oh, please!
I never need healing!
But I do get hungry...
That sure doesn't sound
like gratitude to me...
Well, you sound fine now!
I'm glad you're feeling healthy.
My name is Dawn!
And my partner Piplup is over here!
- Pip!
- Pika!
I've got just the thing.
Try this, it's called a poffin.
I made it myself.
Oh, thank you!
So?
It's okay, I guess...
Okay?
Hey! I'm Ash!
I want you to meet
my partner Pikachu!
Pikachu!
Pika!
[coughing]
Whoa, you're not
gonna blow up, are you?
It breathed in smoke
from our stove...
A-ha!
That would be called Seed Flare.
Wha-? Seed Flare?
When a Shaymin
breathes in polluted air,
it purifies it in its body,
separating it into light and
water and then expelling it.
That process is called Seed Flare!
- Pika!
- Lup!
Shaymin, you're really
something aren't you?
I am aren't I?
(Nurse Joy)
One thing...
There was a Shaymin
who used Seed Flare,
and when it inhaled toxic air
it destroyed an entire forest!
You're all lucky your stove
had very little toxicify.
I would say you owe
me a big thank you!
We're supposed to tell you that!
And don't forget we're
the ones who brought you
- to the Pokémon Center!
- Pika!
- That was your idea!
- What?
But wait...
What in the world would
a Shaymin be doing here,
of all places?
- I shouldn't be here should I?
- Piplup!
So what happened?
I was tossed all over the place!
It was horrible!
That's how you got
covered by all that dirt!
I know!
So you're going to bring me
to the Flower Garden right?
Look here, I have to go to
the Flower Garden
and that's that!
For the Flower Bearing of course!
- Flower Bearing?
- Never heard of that before...
(Nurse Joy)
Shaymin have a custom.
Once every season a group
of them gather together
in a garden, and migrate,
then a brand new garden grows
wherever they decide to stop.
That's where the name
Flower Bearing comes from.
I'm going to fly off from
the Flower Garden!
Wow... You can fly?
Don't tell me you can't...
Of course I can't!
Aw, what a shame!
Man...
Come on...
Let's go to the Flower Garden!
So where is it?
It's right over there!
Let's go now!
I thought you said you could fly
I can but not now.
What's that supposed to mean?
No need to worry!
You'll get to the Flower Garden
'cause we'll all take you!
Piplup!
Pika, Pika!
(Brock)
Shall we get moving?
(Ash)
Right... Let's do it!
- Gratitude Pokémon...!
- Shaymin!
Of course we're talking primo rare!
Giving a gratitudinous gift
of Shaymin to the Boss
would certainly gift
back to us in spades!
Wealth beyond our wildest dreams!
We'll be bursting
at the money seams!
So, it's Operation Swipe Shaymin!
- Right!
- Yeah!
Wobbuff-
(Ash)
Okay which way should we go?
That way!
No, this way!
Make up your mind!
Now, Ash...
So, which way, Shaymin?
Pika!
It's like a bouquet!
It's that way!
Lup?
Piplup!
Someone please tell me
which way that way is?
Pip, Pip, Pip, Pip, Pip, Pip...
Min!
Oh, no!
They're here!
But who's here?
Them! They are!
Min!
Pika!
We put the "they" in them!
And of course you
put the "T" in twerps!
(Meowth)
Kinda says it all, doesn't it?
Stop, Team Rocket!
[screaming]
Shaymin!
(Team Rocket) - Slippery fingers!
- Slippery fingers!
What's that?
[screaming]
Pika!
Dawn!
But how?
Lup!
Pip, Piplup!
What's going on?
- I feel like I don't weigh anything!
- Lup!
I don't like this place...
Please get me out of here now!
Piplup!
Pip, Piplup, Piplup!
Was that a Pokémon?
Pika!
It's going to eat me!
Pikachu, quick! Thunderbolt!
Pikachu, Pikachu!
Is it gone?
Lup, Piplup!
There it is!
Piplup! Use Bubblebeam!
Piplup!
Pip, Pip, Pip!
Stop it, all of you!
You can't upset Giratina!
Giratina?
That's what that is?
Shieldon!
- Over here!
- Right...!
- Piplup!
- Pika!
Lup!
Pika, Pika!
Shieldon!
- Piplup!
- Shieldon!
Piplup, Piplup!
Be careful!
My body feels normal again!
We made it through
the low-gravify zone!
This is some weird place, for sure. ..
Piplup, Pip, Piplup!
Pika!
Pika, Pika!
Pika...
Is anybody hurt?
Well, I managed to not get eaten!
Are you the Shaymin from before?
Are you...
Who are you?
Newton Graceland is the name!
I'm in the process of
researching the Reverse World.
And just so you know,
among those in my field
I'm considered a genius
if I do say so myself.
Why doesn't he tell us
what he really thinks?
- Humble guy.
- Pika.
What a weirdo!
Come on!
That's no way to treat someone
who saved your lives.
(Dawn)
I'm sorry.
Thank you for saving us!
My name's Ash!
And I'm Dawn!
- Pikachu!
- Piplup!
Uh, what exactly
is the Reverse World?
And what's a Giratina?
Ahh, excellent questions, those.
Allow me to explain!
We're now in the middle
of an alternate world
the location of which
is exactly opposite
the world of reality!
- World of reality?
- Pika?
The force of gravify gets
weaker and stronger here
depending on where
you happen to be,
which means here,
we have a distorted world!
(Newton)
Even though these two worlds
exist side by side with each other,
they do not intersect at all.
However, Giratina,
and only Giratina,
has the power to travel
between these two worlds.
Moreover, Giratina's
the only Pokémon
that exists in this world,
which is to say Giratina's
the master of the Reverse World,
as it were.
Well, I don't like Giratina.
That monster tried to eat me!
Huh...
Why would that be?
Would you all perhaps like to
go back to the real world?
You bet!
Pika!
I have to get to
the Flower Garden right away!
Then in that case there's
not a moment to lose.
- Pika?
- What does that mean?
All right, there's still time.
Come on, be lively!
Pip?
Piplup!
This place looks like
a circus funhouse.
But we're not having fun
and we're all alone.
Hey, I've heard of not having
any idea which end's up,
but this?
This is ridiculous, even for us!
(Team Rocket) - That's saying something.
- That's saying something.
Whoa, man!
(Newton) I became obsessed
with the Reverse World
and started researching
it exhaustively.
The next thing I knew
five years had gone by.
Funny guy...
Well he seems impressive!
(Shaymin)
He's a weirdo!
(Dawn)
What's that?
(Newton) When there are
imbalances in the real world,
this world then corrects
them to maintain the balance
between time and space.
Whenever this occurs
a black cloud appears!
Lup!
- Pip, Piplup!
- Pika?
Pip?
- Piplup!
- Pika!
Don't breathe it in!
Piplup!
Pi, Pi, Pi, Pi, Pi, Pi, Pi!
It's poisonous!
One quick breath
and you're done for.
Shieldon, Shield!
Piplup!
Pikachu!
You see, once time and space,
two dimensions that never
should've met, collided
and unraveled each other!
♪♪
Dialga and Palkia both
thought that their territories
had been violated,
so they began fighting fiercely.
Whoa...
Remember that?
Back in Alamos Town!
As a result, both time and
space were bent violently,
and the sum total
of the Reverse World
started overflowing with
all of this toxicify.
♪♪
Giratina was absolutely
furious with Dialga and Palkia
for defiling its home,
so it made its way
to the real world
and proceeded to capture Dialga!
Dialga?
However...
Min, Min!
Shield!
Min!
(Newton) Thanks to Shaymin's
Seed Flare, Dialga managed to escape!
That's why Giratina's angry.
Right, angry with Shaymin!
Really, really angry!
(Newton)
But that's not all.
Giratina can no longer
go into the real world
because of Dialga!
- Serves Giratina right!
- Pika...
Let the punishment fit the crime!
Pika?
Look, it's Brock!
You're right!
He's still back there!
Come on.
You guys...where are you?
Hey, Brock!
Can you hear us?
- Stop it!
- Pika!
If something gets destroyed here,
it has a big influence
on the real world.
Any changes to those bubbles
are reflected in the real world.
Now gravify gets strange
again starting right here.
- But it can be kind of fun!
- Shieldon!
There! Our destination's
straight ahead!
♪♪
Look out!
Let's run!
Min!
Min, Min!
Oh, no!
No Shaymin!
- Piplup!
- What do we do?
Pika?
Pika!
- You people need to get on the ball!
- Pikachu!
Piplup, Piplup!
But...
Substitute!
I've got to say,
I'm thoroughly impressed!
Sorry but flattery will
get you nowhere.
Whatever!
We've got to go!
Hurry!
Shieldon!
It's over there!
You can't come in there
but you should be able to get out!
- Jump in quickly!
- Lup?
Piplup!
- Pikachu!
Dawn!
But what about you?
I've still got some things
to tend to here.
Now hurry or you
won't be able to get out!
Right.
Giratina can see
into the real world,
so watch your step
and also beware of mirrors!
You made it!
- Piplup!
- I think so...!
Pika, Pi!
(Jesse)
Wait!
We want to go home too!
Yeah, leave this weightless stuff
for the astronauts!
(computer)
Giratina is surfacing.
(Zero)
ls Dialga nearby?
No, it's outside
of the radar's field.
Infi, zoom in on the spot where
Giratina tried to surface...
Right!
(Brock)
Where'd you all go?
(Ash)
To the Reverse World!
What's that?
Where's Newton?
He stayed back there.
Pika?
He said "beware of mirrors"...
The mirror?
It's coming this way!
This place's dangerous
Let's go!
(Brock)
Tell me what's going on!
I see...
So that's how it is.
(Infi)
Be careful.
I await your return.
(Brock)
A Giratina?
In the Reverse World?
I wish I could have seen that...
(Dawn) Then you would've
seen how dangerous it was!
Thanks to me you're
all safe and sound!
Aren't you grateful I'm around?
Don't forget it was you
that got us in this mess
in the first place!
It's time to step up to the plate!
It's time for you to get me
to the Flower Garden!
'Stead of yappin'
about the Flower Garden,
tell me where it is!
It's over there!
- No, wait, it's over here!
- Magnemite!
Magnemite!
- Piplup?
- Pika?
- Magnemite!
Magnemite! Magnemite!
Man now what's going on?
Pika!
Magneton!
Magnemite! Magnemite!
I'll just take that Shaymin
off your hands.
You're popular...
He must want to eat me too!
I don't think that's what he wants. ..
Okay, who are you?
And how do you know our Shaymin?
(Shaymin)
I don't know him!
(Brock)
Well, he's not a trainer.
Magnezone, Mirror Shot, now!
Magnezone!
Pikachu, use Thunder Bolt!
- Pikachu!
- Magnezone!
Let's go!
Lup, Pip, Piplup!
Piplup, Whirlpool!
Pip, Piplup!
Piplup!
Magnezone!
Can't you smooth out
this bumpy ride?
What do you think?
Lup, Pip, Lup, Piplup!
Magnemite, Magnemite!
Magnezone!
Magnemite! Magnemite!
Magnemite!
♪♪
Magnezone!
There were, like,
a million of 'em...!
I'm hungry!
Stop it!
I loved whatever
we had this morning.
You mean pancakes?
We're out of those.
It's okay!
I still have some Poffins.
Here!
Dawn you're wonderful!
Way nicer than Ash...
Oh, yeah?
Why you little...
I'm scared!
Now you just stop that!
You saw that burp!
Shaymin didn't mean to.
- Right?
- Certainly not.
Told you.
So, let's go then.
Chop chop!
Piplup!
Man...
I'm glad we made it onto
this train and everything
but where are we going?
Good question...
Pi?
(man) I used to hike in the
mountains when I was a kid.
And one time,
I actually got to see
the Shaymin's Flower Bearing!
Wow!
Yeah, what a lucky guy!
Hey, I'll bet that's why
you've got such a cute wife!
It's so cute!
It's gonna bite!
It's all right.
I don't bite.
Hey!
May I hold it?
Of course!
There, there...
Giratina's moving again!
- Professor!
- Don't leave us in the lurch!
Then come with me if
you want to learn something!
If you can't beat 'em, join 'em.
Amazing! They're like twins!
Yeah!
What're those?
Gracidea flowers, Dawn!
Gracidea flowers?
Around these parts if you
really want to show someone
your gratitude you send them
a bouquet of Gracidea Flowers,
since they look like
Shaymin the Gratitude Pokémon!
But it's wonderful that I'm
getting to hold the real thing!
- You're grateful, right?
- Yeah!
You'd better be
careful with that one!
It might blow up at any moment!
I don't do that to nice people!
Layla and all her friends are
going back to their hometown.
It's my great-grandmother's
hundredth birthday!
She took such good care of
me when I was a little girl,
so I figured I would give her
a bouquet of Gracidea Flowers
to show my gratitude!
Min?
Piplup!
Pika!
Pika?
Shaymin!
Pika!
[laughing]
Whee!
- It's flying!
- Piplup!
What happened?
See, Shaymin changes into Sky Form
when it comes in contact
with Gracidea pollen!
Is that part of the Flower Bearing?
Right! The Shaymin gather
at a Gracidea Garden
where they change into
Sky Form and fly off!
Pika!
Do you know where
the Gracidea Garden is?
We're lookin' for it!
Excuse me, coming through!
Follow me!
Okay, check out this map.
Here's where we are right now!
If you transfer to a boat
at the next station,
the Gracidea Garden
will be around here.
You picked a good time 'cause
the flowers are ready to bloom.
You see?
I have to go right away!
My friends are all there!
If I do not make it
before the flowers bloom,
I'll be left behind.
That's why you were in a rush!
Exactly!
Giratina was a problem,
but I'm fine now.
I can fly there anytime I want!
I wanna see the Flower Bearing too!
- Piplup!
- Yeah, me too!
Can't wait to see it!
Pika!
It's something to see.
I love when things turn out right!
Pika?
Magnezone!
What do they want?
They're all trying to
capture Shaymin!
No chance you're
ever going to get me!
Magnemite, Magnemite!
Shaymin!
Told ya!
Now Pikachu, Iron Tail!
Pi, Pi, Pi!
Pi, Chu, Pika!
Pika!
Wow, well done!
Pikachu, Pika!
Quick, Piplup, Bubblebeam!
Piplup, Lup, Lup!
Pika, Pika, Pika, Pika, Pika!
- Pika, Pika!
- Magnemite.
Piplup!
Pip, Piplup, Piplup!
Magnemite!
Magnemite, Magnemite!
Pika, Pi!
Pika, Pika!
Pika...
Chu!
Magnemite, Magnemite!
- Pika!
- Piplup, Piplup!
- We did it!
- All right!
Magnezone!
Pikachu, Thunderbolt, let's go!
Now, Piplup, Bubblebeam!
- Pika, Pikachu!
- Lup, Lup, Lup, Lup!
- Magnezone!
- Shaymin!
Magnezone...
Magnemite!
- Pikachu!
- Yes!
Pikachu!
Every last one of them!
Have you changed a little
or is it just me?
It's thank Shaymin time!
- It's just you, Brock!
- Pikachu.
Gull!
Wingull!
- Piplup, Piplup!
- Thanks for everything everybody!
Pika, Pika!
Have a safe trip!
And make sure you don't
get off in the wrong place!
(Dawn)
No need to worry!
(Ash)
We'll be fine!
(man)
Be careful!
(Infi)
Welcome back, Sir.
How's Giratina?
Giratina's surfaced just once.
I knew it.
Calculate where
Giratina will surface next.
Already in process.
(Dawn)
Brock, isn't this part of the sea?
(Brock) The fact is, a glacier
wore away the mountain here
and created this valley
a long time ago...
(Ash)
A glacier?
Like this!
Ice has been covering and
wearing away at this mountain
- for tens of thousands of years!
- Pika!
Whoa!
Looks cold!
And there's a glacier located
deep in the Flower Garden
we're headed to as well.
- Wow...
- Pika!
Pika!
Piplup, Pip?
Spheal, Spheal...
Sealeo.
Sealeo, Sealeo!
♪♪
Pika!
Pika?
Yeah!
Whee!
Pikachu!
Pip!
Piplup!
- Piplup, Piplup!
- Pika!
Piplup!
Piplup, Pip, Piplup!
Pip, Piplup!
Piplup!
Pika, Pika!
Pikachu, you flying with 'em?
Pika!
- Staravia!
- Pikachu!
Pika!
Staravia!
Star!
Pika!
Min!
Pika, Pika!
- Piplup!
- Pika!
Piplup!
Pika!
Oh, no!
You're coming as well!
Pity...
Much too heavy.
Ouch!
- Pika?
- Staravia!
Pika!
- Altaria!
- Star!
Altaria! Altaria, Altaria!
Pika!
Yeah!
Shaymin's sure having fun!
Just like it'll be
at the Flower Garden!
Flying off with all its friends.
Guess we won't have
much more time together.
Shaymin...
Know what?
It's kind of a relief.
Hey!
Ow, ow!
As you can see,
we've finally succeeded
in entering
the Reverse World!
(man)
Watch out!
Master!
Only Giratina can move freely
in and out of this world!
Then let's grab
that power ourselves!
Right!
Soon, it will all be mine...
(Infi)
Giratina has surfaced.
Pip, Pip, Pip, Pip, Pip, Piplup.
What's that?
That's the same thing
we got sucked into before!
Uh-oh!
Let's get out of here!
I'm not going anywhere!
Pika, Pika!
Piplup!
- Pika!
- Star!
Magnezone.
That's the entrance
into the Reverse World.
Let's go!
Magnezone!
Magnemite!
Piplup!
Star!
Staravia!
This is the Reverse World?
(Ash)
We're back again!
- Oh no!
- Pip!
- It's Giratina!
- It's huge!
Giratina, I'm challenging you!
You go, Shaymin!
Shaymin!
That's what I was afraid of!
Pikachu, Thunderbolt, let's go!
Help Shaymin!
- Pikachu!
- Staravia!
Star!
Pikachu!
Pika!
Shaymin!
Lup!
Min!
Staravia!
Pikachu!
Star!
- Pika!
- Staravia!
Min!
Pika!
I guess I didn't want to be eaten!
But, what happened to
all your strength?
I'm not so good at night...
It could be be that Shaymin
can only take on Sky Form
during the daytime...
Why can't you run any faster?
Why're you always on me
when we're running'?
So we'll be eaten together!
That's why!
Very Funny!
Quick Pikachu, use Thunderbolt!
Pikachu!
Pika!
(Newton)
Hello!
Ash, Dawn, up here!
- Wow, it's Newton!
- Pip?
Newton?
- Pikachu!
- Pika!
Hi, Newton, I'm Brock!
Nice to meet you!
This isn't a place people
usually come back to!
But, this way!
Staravia!
(Ash)
Staravia, return!
You're all quite a handful,
aren't you?
Okay, whatever, you're taking me
to the Flower Garden right?
Giratina's out there.
We can't just waltz out of here.
You'll all abandon me, I know it!
Where's all that confidence
you had back in Sky Form...?
I left it back in the sky!
- I should have known.
- Pikachu!
Home sweet home.
I'm finally back...
Such a beautiful,
quiet and unspoiled world,
where no one can bother me...
At last!
Welcome, Master, sir!
We brought you some cool stuff!
How about a hot towel?
And something to wet your whistle?
Well, thank you, thank you.
Team Rocket?
What're you doing here?
Isn't it obvious that we've
become his star pupils?
His top trio of
Reverse World wonks!
Actually we just
go and get him junk.
Hold it, Newton!
These guys...
...are actually quite
helpful to be honest!
Well, I don't care, I'm hungry!
Give me food.
Gimme a break, greenback!
I ain't got any grub.
Give me food!
(Ash)
Shaymin!
Pika!
Sheildon!
Piplup!
The Shaymin's mine.
- Shaymin!
- You again?
Pika!
Pikachu!
Who's that dude?
Not sure but I think
we should sit this one out.
Hide this one out too...
No use, can't move!
Zero!
You!
Zero was my assistant once!
If it isn't the good doctor
Newton Graceland.
Long time no see.
You haven't changed a bit...
Save it!
Why did you come here?
You know why. ..
To make this wonderful world
all mine!
You're still on that?
You have no claim to this world.
I never said I did!
Perhaps...
But you're trying to keep
this beautiful place
all to yourself!
Look!
The Reverse World is vital in
that it sustains the real world!
I've already figured that out.
However...
This place is beautiful.
But people destroy it!
Defile and pollute it!
Wrong!
Don't you realize
that's this world's job?
Magnemite, Magnemite, Magnemite,
Magnemite, Magnemite...
Ah, yes, that's right...
I've forgotten to mention
that I've finished building
your invention for you!
Oh, no!
Don't breathe in!
Piplup!
Min!
Magnemite, Magnemite!
Shaymin!
Dawn!
Min!
Shaymin!
There we go.
Min...
What a pity, Giratina...
Because of Dialga,
you lost your ability to travel
back to the real world,
but I'll help you...
Pika!
Min...
Of course!
That's Seed Flare!
Giratina's here!
Now, open a hole using Seed Flare!
Help Giratina...
Allow it to leave now!
Hole?
- Magneton!
- Magnemite, Magnemite!
- Magnemite!
- Magneton, Magneton!
It's getting rid of the Magnemite!
Giratina has no interest
in eating Shaymin!
Min!
It's going to eat me!
Shaymin doesn't understand!
Here we go!
Pika!
Min!
Pika, Pi!
Pika!
And now, Giratina...
Realize your dream and
go to the real world!
Pika...
It's a glacier!
(Dawn)
Shaymin!
Shaymin, you all right?
It was about to eat me!
You're wrong.
Giratina wasn't trying to eat you...
Giratina only wanted to
get you to use Seed Flare
so it could come forth
into this world.
It was also trying to get rid of
all the Magnemite!
Piplup!
It looks different!
It probably has to do with
the gravify change...
Pika!
♪♪
- What's that?
- Piplup!
Magnezone!
Giratina, I have been waiting
such a long time now
for you to come here!
Pika?
What is Zero up to?
(Infi) Giratina is
returning to its condition
before making
contact with Dialga.
It is already capable of
entering and leaving
the Reverse World.
Giratina's Reverse World arrival
has shattered the time loop.
Infi, now,
commence scanning process!
Understood.
Beginning scan immediately.
It's true...
I designed that machine.
I built it so I'd be able to absorb
all of Giratina's Abilities!
But why would you do that?
So I could enter and leave
the Reverse World at will!
At that point...
I realized Giratina
would then be sacrificed!
This project is terminated!
Master...
What are you saying?
We can't use Giratina
as a sacrifice
just for the sake of our research!
What are you doing?
My blueprints...
I'm deleting all of them!
(Newton)
But...
Obviously Zero never forgot them!
And if that thing was built
to my specifications,
Giratina will soon be no more.
- You mean Giratina's...
- Pika!
It won't be long before
the Reverse World is all mine!
And then I will rule there
like a king!
[laughing]
Sheildon, Sheildon, Sheildon!
Sheildon, Sheildon!
Shield!
Where're you going?
This whole thing is my fault.
I have to make
sure Giratina's safe!
I'm comin' too!
- Me too!
- Piplup!
Shaymin, you wait here.
Piplup!
Finally!
This is the Gracidea Flower Garden!
Well, I'm going on ahead!
Shaymin!
Let's go!
- Right!
Hey!
I'm starting to sense a pattern...
He can't...
- He won't!
- Pika!
We will all help Giratina!
Take care of them.
Magnemite!
Magnezone!
Zone! Zone!
Shaymin!
Magnezone!
Magnemite!
Prepare to enter the Reverse World.
(Infi)
As you wish.
Pikachu, Thunderbolt, now!
Bubblebeam, Piplup, let's go!
- Piplup, Lup, Lup!
- Chu!
It didn't do a thing!
They bounced right off!
Then I'll have to go in
and stop him myself!
Magnezone!
Zone!
Shaymin!
- Lup, Lup, Lup!
- Chu!
Shield!
Newton!
I should be able to
get in through here!
- Pikachu!
- Piplup!
Chu!
We'll take care of the Magnemite!
(Shaymin)
I'll help too!
- Chu.
- Great, thanks!
Shieldon, Flash Cannon!
Shieldon!
Yes!
(Infi)
Scanning is now 50% complete.
Chu!
Bui!
Ambipom!
- Piplup, Lup, Lup!
- There Buneary Icebeam!
Buneary!
- Shaymin!
- Magnemite!
Zero!
Stop this at once!
Shieldon, Shieldon!
You're too late...
I invite you to sit and watch
as the execution
of my beautiful plan
is made real!
Chu!
Come on, Newton...
Hurry up!
I guess he forgot...
This thing is my design!
(alarm beeping)
(Infi)
The system has just been hacked.
But what about the scan?
Over 91 o!o complete.
♪♪
All right!
How do you like this?
- It stopped!
- Pip, Piplup!
Newton, great job!
Pikachu!
- Pika!
- Hey, Newton!
I'm sorry.
To shut down the system I had to
shut down the engines, too.
So what does that mean?
It means that
this thing's going down!
(Ash)
Everybody return!
(Dawn)
Return!
Oh, no...
Ash, Dawn!
♪♪
Pidgey!
Pidgey, Pidgey! Pidgey!
♪♪
Hey, guys! You all right?
Uh-huh.
Giratina!
Pikachu!
Pika, Pika!
Piplup, Pip, Piplup, Pip!
We're too late...!
Sentret, Sentret, Sentret?
Furr, Furret?
Stant...
It's breathing!
Giratina, come on!
- Pika, Pika!
- You must pull through!
Shay...
Giratina, stay with me!
Shay, Shay...
Pika!
Aromatherapy!
That's one of Shaymin's moves!
Shay...
Shay!
♪♪
- Lup?
- Pika?
♪♪
Giratina!
It's Shaymin who
made you feel better!
Pika, Pika!
Pikachu!
Pikachu.
Wait for me!
Thank goodness you're all right!
Sentret!
Bidoof!
Guess they were all worried
about Giratina, huh...?
They would know what was at stake,
and just how important
the Reverse World is!
Pika!
Is that...?
Zero!
♪♪
I couldn't care less
what they think they've done.
No one gets in my way!
Pi, Pi!
Quick, Pikachu, use Thunderbolt!
Piplup You use Bubblebeam!
- Piplup, Lup, Lup, Lup!
- Now Shieldon, Flash Cannon, go!
Shieldon!
I said stay out of my way!
- He's gone!
- Pika!
He went to the Reverse World!
Shield!
Zero's managed to acquire
all of Giratina's powers!
What is that?
Not sure, but it's no doubt
sporting someone on the inside!
We don't care if you're nastier
than we are, save us!
Look at you all in
your pathetic, filthy world!
Disappear, all of you!
What was that?
Zero's attacking the real world
from the Reverse World!
- I'm going, too!
- Pikachu!
But, Ash!
Wait for me!
My lovely Reverse World...
They won't tarnish
its beauty again!
The Reverse World's true power
will forever shine through!
[ethereal rending]
Regigigas...
- Shield...
- Piplup!
♪♪
Piplup!
The glacier!
It's moving!
Zero's doing this!
But how?
(Infi) The Glacier has lost its
support in the Reverse World
and has begun moving.
Excellent!
Just as I planned!
Continue to collect data!
As you wish, sir.
Perfect!
(Newton) The Real and Reverse
Worlds support each other!
Zero...
Do you really want to destroy that?
- Chu!
- Min!
Zero, give it up now!
Stop this!
Why?
You just don't understand...
I'm protecting this place!
(Dawn)
Swinub, Ice Shard!
Buneary, Ice Beam!
- Nub!
- Buneary!
- Bidoof!
- Bibarel!
- Froslass!
- Abomasnow!
Snover!
♪♪
All of your powers
now belong to me!
Chimchar, use Flamethrower!
Turtwig, Energy Ball!
- Now, Pikachu, use Thunderbolt!
- Chimchar!
- Twig!
- Chu!
Char!
No use, it's not stopping!
If this keeps up it's going
to crush the Flower Garden!
That's not all that'll be crushed.
All the villages and towns
just ahead...
♪♪
They're all doomed to be destroyed!
- Oh, no!
- How could he?
Piplup, Piplup, Piplup!
- Buneary!
- Swinub!
Is that a...?
Regigigas!
Mamo! Mamoswine!
Mamo!
Mamoswine!
There're some more!
Mamo! Mamo, Mamoswine!
Mamo!
The Reverse World belongs to me!
- Pika!
- No, Giratina!
Mamo!
Look at Regigigas
and the Mamoswine!
They're all trying to
stop the glacier!
Piplup!
♪♪
I'll bet him helping us
is not going to happen...
Safe bet.
I've got four-to-one odds.
(Team Rocket) - Losers take all!
- Losers take all!
Giratina, this will
be over very soon!
Chu!
Pikachu, use Thunderbolt
and Chimchar, use Flamethrower!
- Pikachu!
- Chimchar!
Out of my way!
Pika!
Pi!
All right, are you okay?
- Pikachu!
- Chimchar!
Pi, Pi, Pi, Pi...
Pikachu!
Shaymin!
A simple "thank you" will suffice!
Pika!
- Twig...
- Char...
Turtwig, Chimchar!
Return!
Hey! You stop destroying
this place, Zero!
Pika!
If anything is destroying
this place, it's the real world!
Pika!
There! Look at that toxic cloud!
Don't you see this glorious world
is constantly being polluted?
So don't you understand,
I'm protecting it!
The real and reverse worlds
support each other!
Pika!
Ash! I'll take care of this!
Shaymin!
Min...
Regigigas...
Can they really hold it back?
You can do it, Regigigas!
Piplup!
We've gotta do something!
Min!
'Kay Shaymin, use Seed Flare now!
We've gotta knock Zero out of here!
I don't think so!
All right Pikachu, Thunderbolt!
Chu!
Oh, really?
Your turn to be knocked!
What the...?
Pika!
I warned you to
stay out of my way!
- No, Giratina...!
- Pika!
Shaymin, it's up to you!
I'm ready!
Min...
I have had enough of you!
Now, Shaymin! Go!
Min!
Pika!
What's that?
Shaymin opened up a portal!
Shaymin did?
Pika!
(Infi)
Systems down.
Mamo!
Quick Buneary, use Ice Beam!
Swinub, Ice Shard!
- Swinub!
- Mamoswine!
(Infi)
All systems have been shut down.
(Zero)
Recover data on Giratina.
All systems down.
Unable to recover.
Oh, no!
All systems down.
Every single one of
my glorious plans...they're ruined.
All systems down...
(Team Rocket) - Lousy weather for flying!
- Lousy weather for flying!
I am really not
that good with the cold!
Shaymin, are you okay?
I am the teensiest bit scared.
Where's Ash and Pikachu?
They must still be there!
Bunear?
Plup?
♪♪
Gigas...
Gigas.
Mamo! Mamo!
- It stopped!
- Piplup.
What's that?
Swine, Swine!
Hello down there!
Pikachu!
Dawn!
Hey, Brock!
Pika!
- It's Ash!
- Bunear, Bunear!
Piplup, Piplup!
Yeah!
- Piplup, Piplup!
- Ash! Pikachu!
I'm glad you're safe!
Thanks! Giratina saved us.
Where is Giratina going?
♪♪
I'm wondering if Dialga's near.
Pika.
Piplup.
- Pika?
- Pip, Pip?
Min?
Min!
- Min?
- Piplup!
Pika!
- Min!
Min, Min!
Shaymin, are they your friends?
Sure are!
It's a good thing we weren't late.
True, thanks to you all!
Pika!
Lup!
♪♪
Quick, look!
It's the Gracidea Flowers!
- Beautiful!
- Pika!
Shaymin...
It's great to be
able to see this place!
Does that mean you are
grateful to Shaymin?
Yeah, you bet I'm grateful!
Ash I must say
I am grateful to you too!
Thanks, Shaymin.
Min!
- Min!
Dawn, Ash, Brock...
All of you...
I'll never be able to
thank you enough, but I'll try!
Thank you!
Shaymin!
Here is where I say goodbye.
Yeah, we know.
Pika!
♪♪
Lup!
Pika!
It's the Sky Bouquet!
(Shaymin)
Farewell my good friends!
Shaymin!
Pika!
- Bye, Shaymin...
- Piplup!
Make a pretty garden, everybody!
And someday, I hope...
I see you again!
Oh, Ash...
And make sure you guys
don't get lost!
♪♪
♪ Every day we just keep going
through the motions ♪
♪ And we don't know why ♪
♪Seems like we never
stop to take the time ♪
♪ To notice life as it goes by ♪
♪ But there's
a whole world out there ♪
♪ It's a miracle to see ♪
♪ Like the colors of a rainbow ♪
♪ It's a living symphony ♪
♪ So open your eyes ♪
♪ It's easy to do ♪
♪ Just take the time
and look around you ♪
♪ Never forget ♪
♪ This is a beautiful world♪
♪Do we realty
celebrate the beauty♪
♪ That surrounds us
every single day ♪
♪ Or ever realize the gifts
that we've been given ♪
♪ That just go away ♪
♪ We can't let it happen ♪
♪ It's up to you and me ♪
♪ We've got to work together♪
♪ It's our responsibility ♪
♪ So open your eyes ♪
♪ It's easy to do ♪
♪ Just take the time
and look around you ♪
♪ Never forget ♪
♪ This is a beautiful world♪
♪ It's a beautiful world ♪
♪ There's a whole world out there ♪
♪ Be thankful every day ♪
♪ And grateful for the magic ♪
♪ That touches us so many ways ♪
♪ So open your eyes ♪
♪ It's easy to do ♪
♪ Just take the time
and look around you ♪
♪ Never forget ♪
♪ This is a beautiful world♪
♪ So open your eyes ♪
♪ It's easy to do ♪
♪ Just take the time
and look around you ♪
♪ Never forget ♪
♪ This is a beautiful world♪
♪ Just take the time. ♪
♪ And open your eyes. ♪
♪ Never forget ♪
♪ This is a beautiful world♪
♪ This beautiful world. ♪
♪ Just open your eyes ♪
♪ This is a beautiful world♪
♪ It's a beautiful world ♪♪
Watch Movies, TV Series and Live Sports
Signup Here -> WWW.ADMITME.APP