Downloaded from
YTS.MX
Official YIFY movies site:
[Naru, in Comanche] Soobesükütsa tüa
pia mupitsI ikÜ kimai.
[in English] A long time ago, it is said,
a monster came here.
[deer grunts]
[duck quacks, beetles chirping]
[wind gusts]
[fire crackling]
[footsteps approaching]
[grunts]
[whines]
-[tribespeople chattering]
-[baby fusses]
-[birds singing]
-[sighs]
[dog sniffs, grunts]
[dog barks]
[thwack]
[bird squawks]
[dog grunts]
[grunts]
[sighs]
[shouts]
[dog snuffling]
[bird cries in distance]
[insects buzzing]
[dog panting]
A white tail.
[pants]
[deer snorting]
Sarii.
[in Comanche] Mahoinitü.
-[loud rumble]
-[birds squawking]
[barking]
[grunts]
[panting]
[grunting]
-[barking]
-[deer grunts]
-[barking continues]
-[panting]
-[deer grunts]
-[grunts]
-[metal clanks]
-[Sarii yelps]
[whining]
[whining continues]
[barks]
[growls]
[whining resumes]
[shushes]
[Sarii panting]
-[loud rumble]
-[bird squawks]
[barking]
[rumbling continues]
[bird crying]
[Taabe, in English] I remember when
Father told me I was ready for kühtaamia.
My big hunt.
You were little.
So, Mother took you to gather medicine.
But Father and I,
we went up into the hills.
The rain was bad. Everything was wet.
We crawled through the mud
and my bowstring…
-[snores]
-…got ruined and--
[gasps]
-[squawks]
-You were sleeping.
I was waiting for it to circle back.
Now you're gonna have to
cross the river to get it.
[children] Whoa.
Don't get your bowstring wet.
Taabe,
this morning in the sky,
I saw a sign. The thunderbird.
I've been practicing.
It's time. I'm ready for my kühtaamia.
You really think you're ready?
You wanna hunt something
that's hunting you?
[chattering in Comanche]
[Naru, in Comanche] Petsü.
[mother chuckles]
-[in English] Trained him well.
-It's easy. He's smart.
Not every smart creature is easy to train.
-[Naru] Is that for War Chief's bad knee?
-Mmm.
[mother] He's getting worse.
You didn't put orange totsiyaa.
Who taught you about orange totsiyaa?
You.
Hmm.
Your father left you that
to cut breadroot with.
I almost got a deer with it.
Yeah. Well, we can't eat "almost."
My girl, you are good
at so many other things.
Why do you want to hunt?
Because you all think that I can't.
[sighs]
Ah!
In this wind, he brings home a red-tail.
[Taabe chuckles]
You should have listened to my story.
Didn't think we had time for a nap.
-[scoffs]
-[mother laughs]
[Taabe, in Comanche] Posa.
[in English] It's sharp enough.
Go get us some orange totsiyaa.
[birds calling]
[loud rumbling]
[rumbling]
[Predator clicking]
[barks]
-[Sarii snuffles]
-[sighs]
[tribespeople ululating]
[tribespeople chattering, shouting]
Itsee.
-[in Comanche] Hina?
-[in English] A lion. It took Puhi.
We gotta find him.
[bushes rustle]
[stones tumble]
[Predator clicking]
[footsteps approaching, clicking]
[Sarii panting]
You could get shot sneaking up like that.
-Who's sneaking?
-[Taabe chuckles]
Who invited you?
We won't be gone long enough
to need a cook.
[Paaka laughs]
She should stay.
She tracks well.
And if we find Puhi alive,
she knows medicine.
You have to find that cat now.
-I will.
-I know.
'Cause you have to.
[chuckles]
[pants]
[electronic hum]
[mouse squeaks]
[crunching]
[squeaks]
[rattling]
[Predator growling]
Oh, good. The dog found shit.
-We're not looking for wolves.
-[Naru] It's not wolf.
You see that crushed bone?
That's lion scat.
And the cat that made it was big.
[barks]
[Sarii whining]
He's breathing.
[Taabe, in Comanche] Petsü.
[grunts]
[Itsee, in English]
So much could kill him.
[Naru] It won't kill him.
Just cool his blood.
[gulps]
[in Comanche] Anaa. Anaa.
[Wasape, in English]
Taabe wants to stay and hunt.
Let's go.
-I'm coming with you.
-I can handle the lion.
No, it's not just the lion.
Why is Puhi alive? There's something
that scared the cat away from its den.
I've got this.
Stay with Puhi. He needs your help too.
We don't have time to waste talking.
We need to get him home.
[in Comanche] ManamÜsohi.
[animals calling]
[Puhi, in Comanche] Üts'tü nü.
Tobo'ihupitü.
[Naru] Kee.
[in English] The cold is good.
The medicine slows his blood.
If he gets warm, he'll bleed out.
Hey.
Do you want him
to be comfortable or alive?
[in Comanche] Mia.
[Sarii whimpers, snuffles]
[whimpering]
[snuffling]
[rattles]
[Sarii barking]
[in English]
We don't have time to wait for you.
-Look.
-[Paaka] Could be bear tracks.
Maybe.
But that's a big bear.
And why was it on its hind legs?
And what skins a snake like that?
-We need to keep moving.
-No.
I have to warn my brother.
Paaka, go with her.
[bushes rustle]
Naru, we don't need the torches.
They'll scare the cat.
We're in its hunting grounds.
Why'd you come back?
I found tracks, and they were huge.
[sighs] I'm not frightened by a bear.
I don't think it was a bear.
I don't know what it was.
I've never seen anything like it.
It skinned and gutted a snake.
Well, whatever it was,
we're in the cat's den now.
We have to deal with it first.
Come on.
[Naru] The lion won't think
that we're hunting it here.
[sighs] It'll think it's hunting us.
We get some bait,
then climb up and wait for it.
A hunter doesn't wait. He hunts.
We could be here all night.
We could stalk the forest all night
and not find anything too.
If you're too afraid to hunt,
go back to camp where you belong.
We'll try it Naru's way.
We'll bait it,
then I'll lead the cat to you.
Wait.
It's time, Naru.
Your kühtaamia.
When the lion comes, you tell that thing,
"This is as far as you go.
No more. This is it."
[insects buzzing]
[sighs]
It won't matter how sharp it is
if you're too afraid to use it.
You think you're ready?
You've never faced a lion.
Its mouth full of teeth like arrows,
ready to tear your flesh
and crush your bones.
When your brother comes back,
he and I will find the lion
-and kill it. [screams]
-[animal roars]
[Paaka yells]
[Paaka screaming]
[lion growls]
[roars]
[growling, roaring]
[growling, roaring continue]
[branch creaking]
[distant roar]
-[gasps, shrieks]
-[roaring]
-[sniffs, sighs]
-[splashes]
[gasps, pants]
[grunts, pants]
Your brother carried you home.
[pants]
Wha-- What about the lion?
-Taabe went after it.
-Okay.
I have to find him.
No, you need to rest.
[Naru grunts]
[in Comanche] Ihka.
[in English] Drink this tea.
[slurps]
[in English] Puhi survived
because of your medicine.
There's something else out there.
Taabe needs my help.
If your brother needed you,
he wouldn't have brought you back here.
You think the reason for kühtaamia
is to prove you can hunt,
but there's only one reason.
To survive.
[tribespeople chattering in distance]
[child, in Comanche]
Taabe kima! Taabe kima!
[chattering in distance continues]
[groans]
[no audible dialogue]
[ululating]
-[ululating]
-[all whooping, shouting]
[chanting]
[whooping, shouting]
-[in English] Naru.
-[tribe member chuckles] War Chief.
Naru.
Where are you going?
-We did it.
-[sighs]
No.
We didn't do it.
What do you think left those tracks
and skinned that snake?
And before I fell,
-I saw lightning in the trees.
-Naru.
-There's something else out there.
-And if there is, I'll get it.
We need to go back out.
-Far, beyond the ridgeline.
-No.
-Okay. Well, I'll hunt alone if I have to.
-You can't.
-Do I need your permission, War Chief?
-[sighs] It's not about permission.
You can't. [stammers, sighs]
I had to carry you back.
I can hunt.
You're right.
[sighs] We didn't do it.
I did.
You tried it. You just… [sighs]
You couldn't bring it home.
[Taabe whoops]
[tribespeople whooping, yelling]
[footsteps approaching]
[grunts]
[tribespeople chattering]
[baby crying]
[Naru] If they don't see,
then show them.
[in Comanche] Kima.
[growls]
[sniffing, squeaking]
[squeaks, sniffs]
[growls, panting]
[growls]
[growling]
[Predator growling]
[barks, growls]
[barks]
[splattering]
[bellows]
[grunts]
[in English] Next time, you're cooking.
[Sarii whines]
[in Comanche] Kima.
Nüma'ai kima.
[in English] We have to go find
whatever left those tracks.
-[in Comanche] Ühkitsi.
-[barks]
[spray hissing]
[Predator clicking]
[growls softly]
-[Sarii barks]
-[hisses]
[Sarii barks]
[birds squawking]
[insects buzzing]
[in Comanche]
Tasiwoo Atsabi, yütsü tsaaku.
Ürako taa ahpü yühmuku.
[sniffs]
-[whooshing]
-[branches creaking]
[clicking]
[growls]
[barks]
[twigs snap]
Sarii?
[gasps, pants]
[insects buzzing]
[Predator growling softly, clicking]
[pants, grunts]
[grunts]
[sighs]
[mud gurgling]
[Naru grunts]
[mud gurgles]
[grunts]
[pants]
[panting]
[Sarii whines]
[in English] There you are.
-[whimpers]
-[animal growls]
-[Sarii panting]
[whines]
[grunts]
[snuffling]
[growls]
-[twangs]
-[gasps]
[growling]
[snuffles]
[barks]
[growling]
-[growling]
-[barking]
[roars]
[Sarii barking]
[grunts]
[panting]
[Sarii barks]
[barking]
[bear growls]
[bear grunts]
[gasps, grunts]
[bear growling]
[growling]
[growling fades]
[bear snuffles, growls softly]
[bear growls]
[Predator shrieks]
[bear groans]
[roaring]
[roaring stops]
[Predator clicking]
[bear growling]
[bear growls softly]
[Predator roars]
[growls]
[Naru grunts, groans]
[groans]
[twigs snap]
[Naru sighs]
-[Naru] What are you doing here?
-Looking for you.
Your brother sent us to bring you home.
Where is he?
Searching for you
on the other side of the pass.
Where are you going?
-I saw it.
-[Wasape] Saw what?
I saw what left those tracks.
-The bear?
-There was a bear,
but there was something else,
and it was huge.
I couldn't see it until it was
covered in blood, but it looked like--
-like a mupitsI.
-[Wasape scoffs]
You saw a monster from a children's story?
It fought and killed a bear
with its hands, easily.
How come it didn't kill you?
Stop!
You're going home.
-Enough!
-[shouts]
[both grunt]
[Naru screams]
[both grunting]
[Wasape yells]
[Wasape grunts]
-[Naru screams]
-[yells]
[both grunting]
-[Naru shouting]
-[Wasape grunting]
[Naru screams]
[grunts]
[Wasape, in Comanche] Aitü.
[both yell]
[both grunting]
[Wasape shouting]
[in English] You wanna leave? Then leave.
[pants]
-[Wasape grunts]
-[Naru exclaims, grunts]
[Wasape] We're going home.
[Predator clicks, growls]
[Naru] There's something out there.
[conversation continues, distorted]
[Wasape] Quit it!
Just sit.
You need a leash for your weapon?
Get some water.
We'll rest a minute. Stay together.
-[Itsee] What about Taabe?
-[Wasape] He'll meet us back at camp.
I said stay together.
[distant clicking]
[Itsee] I gotta go take a squat.
You want me to do it here?
[Wasape] Water.
[branch snaps]
-[birds squawking]
-[wings flapping]
[grass rustling]
[rustling continues]
[possum squeals]
[chuckles]
You should see your face.
[sighs] What do you think
drove the possums our way?
[chuckles]
[electronic hum]
[possum thuds]
[hum continues]
[hum intensifies]
-[weapon fires]
-[Wasape screams]
Hey. Cut me loose.
Stay down.
[Predator clicking]
[pants]
[sighs]
[metal grating]
[roaring]
[both panting]
[grunts, gasps]
[yells]
-[growls]
-[grunts]
-[Ania yells]
-[Predator growls]
[Ania screams]
-[weapons clanging]
-[Predator growls]
[Predator growls]
[screaming, yelling]
-[Huupi babbling, yelling]
-[Predator clicking]
[screams]
[yells]
[Predator roars, growls]
[Ania yells]
[roars]
[clicking]
[Naru pants]
Shh.
[Naru panting]
[thudding footsteps]
[Predator clicks, growls softly]
-[Itsee] We have him.
-[electronic hum]
No. He has us.
[Predator growls]
[metal clangs]
-[Itsee yells, screams]
-[Predator growls]
[panting]
[Predator growls]
-[metal clanks]
-[grunts, exclaims]
[gasps]
[grunting]
[grunting continues]
-[twig snaps]
-[gasps]
-[Predator growling softly]
-[footsteps approaching]
[people chattering in French in distance]
[Predator growls softly]
-[person, in French] Regardez ici.
-[people chattering, laughing]
Regardez ici.
Une femme ?
Qu'est-ce qu'elle fait ici ?
Je vais la porter.
Elle va nous ralentir.
Non. Par la façon qu'elle courait,
je crois qu'elle l'a vu.
[people speaking indistinctly, distorted]
[people laughing]
[trapper, in French]
C'est ton nouveau blonde, hein ? [laughs]
[trappers shouting, chattering in French]
[gasps]
[kicking, grunting]
[chattering in French continues]
[groans]
[sighs]
[dog barking]
[in French]
Dégagez-moi ce putain de chien !
[sighs, grunts]
[Naru, in English] Sarii?
J'ai pas un bon sentiment avec ça.
[whispers, in English]
You killed the buffalo.
-[footsteps approaching]
-[trapper chuckles]
[chuckling]
Ah…
[trapper grunts, chuckles]
-[Naru grunts]
-[chuckles]
[trapper grunts]
[yells, groans]
-[grunts]
-[grunts, sighs]
[in French] T'es fâchée ?
Maintenant, tu vas payer.
[trapper 2]
On va voir qu'est-ce qu'elle sait.
-Parle, sale Raphael.
-Qu'est-ce que tu fais ici, hein ?
-C'est un piège ?
-[Raphael] Qu'est-ce qui se passe ?
[in English] What did you see?
I speak a lot of languages.
You are Comanche, yes?
-[in French] Je vais la tuer.
-Non, non, non, non, non, non, non.
On peut toujours l'utiliser.
Ah.
[in English] You should be helping us.
I think this creature is a hunter,
looking for the strongest beast.
What do you know?
It killed your whole party.
[trapper, in French]
Je vais la faire chanter.
[in English] No.
It didn't kill everyone.
[Raphael]
If you were smart, you'd help us.
[trapper, in French] Sors le sauvage.
Sortez-lui de la sacrée boîte !
[in English] What?
[gasps]
[in French] D'une façon ou d'une autre,
tu vas nous aider.
[pants]
-[trapper] Fais-le saigner.
-[Taabe grunting]
[Taabe groaning]
-[yelling]
-[trappers laughing]
[Taabe, Naru grunt]
[Naru, in English] Are you hurt?
[Taabe spits]
Oh, they tried. [sighs]
[horses whinny]
[horses whinnying]
[in French]
On n'aurait pas dû amener les chevaux.
Fais-les taire ou la bête ne viendra pas.
[hisses]
[grumbles, speaks in English]
Son of a bitch.
[in English] The thing the white men
are trying to catch… [pants]
-…that's what you went out after?
-[grunts]
-It's what you were tracking?
Yes.
And that's what you chose for kühtaamia?
[laughs, sighs]
[in French]
Elle est où cette pute de bête ?
-J'ai faim et j'ai besoin de pisser.
-[trapper on horse grunts]
[horses whinny]
-[trapper in furs speaks indistinctly]
-[trapper 2] Qu'est-ce qui arrive ?
[trapper in furs] Oh, non, non, non.
Qu'est-ce qui se passe ?
-[trapper 2] Qu'est-ce qui arrive ?
-Qu'est-ce qui arrive ? Rambert !
Tire, Rambert !
-[Rambert panting]
-[footsteps approaching]
[Predator clicking]
[metal clangs]
Merde.
[horses whinnying]
[in English] I need to get me a horse.
[sighs]
[trapper screams]
[trapper, in French] Il est là !
-[Taabe, in English] It's coming.
-[in French] Il est là !
[weapon fires]
[trapper grunts]
[in Comanche] Orü posa kwitapÜ.
[in English] Naru.
[grunts] Can you get your side loose?
[grunts]
[growls]
[both grunting]
[Taabe] Naru.
We're the bait. He's coming for us.
No.
No. It doesn't want bait.
It doesn't hunt that way.
Before the trappers captured me,
it saw me.
It came right up to me
and then left.
It didn't think I was a threat.
[pants]
You wanna know how I killed that lion?
[pants] Your plan. The tree.
You weakened it.
You had it, Naru.
You can see what I miss.
You always have.
I don't know that this thing
can be killed.
If it bleeds, we can kill it.
[roars]
-[in French] Maintenant !
-[yelling]
[yelling]
[Taabe] Naru.
Naru!
[in French] On l'a ! [laughs]
[metal clangs]
[trapper 1 screams]
[trapper 2 yelling]
Salopard !
[growls softly, clicks]
[trapper 3 screams]
[grunts, growls]
[growls softly, clicks]
-[Naru panting]
-[gunshots in distance]
[trappers screaming, yelling]
-[screaming, yelling continues]
-[gunshots continue in distance]
[grunts]
[trapper 4 yelling]
-[yells]
-[Predator clicks]
[trapper 5 yelling]
-[trapper 6 screams]
-[Predator growls]
[grunts]
[in English] What are you doing?
-I have a plan. Get down.
-[screams in distance]
[grunting]
Do you remember the flood
when we were young?
I saw a beaver that had its legs
pinned between two rocks.
The water was rising so fast,
it knew it was going to die.
So it chewed off its own leg.
[in French] Tirez !
On va frapper les autres !
Tirez !
[beeps, hums]
[in English]
It was worth it to the beaver…
[Taabe] Wait.
…losing its leg to be free.
Wait. Naru.
What are you doing, Naru? Naru, stop!
I'm smarter than a beaver.
[chuckles] Come on, we gotta go.
-Where are you going?
-I gotta go get us those horses.
I'll get Sarii.
[Predator squeals]
[digital timer beeping]
-[whirs]
-[beeping accelerates]
[beeping accelerates further]
[in French] Écartez. Écartez-vous !
-[trappers scream]
-[weapons blast]
[trapper 1, in French] Hâtons-nous un peu.
J'ai besoin d'aide.
On peut rien faire pour eux.
Simplement on doit continuer d'avancer.
Et le chien ?
-J'aime le chien.
-[Sarii whimpers]
Ça goûte mieux que le castor.
[whimpers]
-[Naru grunts]
-[bone crunches]
[both grunt]
-[Naru grunts]
-[yells]
-[groans, grunts]
[Naru gasps, grunts]
[screams, grunts]
-[Naru yells]
-[grunts]
[trapper 1 exclaims]
[all grunting]
-[trapper 2 grunts]
-[Naru gasps]
[trapper 1 grunts]
-[trapper 1 yells, grunts]
-[Naru grunting]
[Naru gasps, grunts]
[trapper 3 yells]
[both grunt]
[trapper 3 grunting]
[trapper 3 yells]
[panting]
[Sarii panting]
Sarii.
[in Comanche] Owehkimia, Taabe.
-[in English] Go!
-[barks]
[panting]
[whirring]
[groans]
[grunts]
[panting]
[hammer cocks]
[in English] Help me! Help.
You have medicine?
[groans, grunts]
[panting]
Help me, and I'll show you how to use it.
Please.
[Raphael panting, grunting]
[whimpers]
[Raphael panting]
[Raphael] Take the powder
and put it in the gun.
Not too little, not too much.
[gasps, grunts]
[groans]
And then what?
Then you take the ball and the cloth.
Put it in the gun. [pants]
After that, take the stick you see there.
[gasps, sighs]
You put in the gun, uh, three, four times.
[pants] Here. [grunts]
Last thing.
It's okay.
Put powder here.
[pants]
Then pull that back and it will fire.
That's all?
Please. It hurts.
Please.
What is it? [grunts]
[grunting]
[breathing shakily]
What's happening? I'm freezing cold.
-[groans]
-[twig snaps]
Please. [whimpers]
Don't leave me.
[panting]
[thud]
[footsteps approaching]
[Predator growling softly]
[growls]
[growling softly]
[clicks, growls]
[growling continues]
[Naru] It can't see him.
[Raphael screams]
-[Sarii barking]
-[growls]
[whirs]
[barking]
-[Taabe yells]
-[Predator grunts]
[beeping, humming]
[Taabe whoops]
[growls, roars]
[whoops]
[panting]
[Taabe whoops]
[whoops]
[growling]
-[Taabe whoops]
-[growls]
[Taabe whoops]
-Hey!
-[growls]
[Predator screeches]
[Predator squeals]
"Not too much, not too little."
[Predator grunts, growls]
[in Comanche] Isa'ai!
[branch snaps]
[pants] We should go.
Taabe.
Run, Naru.
It thinks I'm the threat.
This is as far as I go.
No more. This is it.
-No.
-Bring it home.
[Predator clicks]
[grunts]
[Predator roars]
[no audible dialogue]
[growling softly]
[yelling, distorted]
[growls softly, clicks]
[no audible dialogue]
[gasps, pants]
[Sarii whines]
[grunts]
[crickets chirping]
-[animal squeaks]
-[gasps]
[crunching]
[animal squeaks]
-[groans, coughs]
-[squeaking continues]
[grunting, gasping]
[yells]
[screaming]
[in French] Non ! Ah, non ! Non, arrête !
[screams]
Putain !
[gibbering]
[gasps]
[grunting, exclaiming]
[laughs]
[giggles]
[in English] You bled my brother.
So now you bleed.
[in French] Idiote sauvage !
[trapper grunts]
[in English]
You think that I am not a hunter like you.
[grunts, gasps]
[in French] Tu ne sais même pas
l'erreur que tu viens de faire. [laughs]
[in English] That I am not a threat.
[in French] Je vais mettre
une balle dans ton crâne.
[in English]
That is what makes me dangerous.
[in French] Tu vas mourir, chienne !
[in English]
You can't see that I'm killing you.
[Predator clicks]
[gasps]
[whistles]
[Predator clicks]
-[yells]
-[hammer clicks]
And it won't either.
[grunts]
[growls softly]
[in French] Démon !
[trapper] Non !
[Predator clicks]
[Predator shrieks]
[groans]
[roars]
[growls softly]
[clicking]
[gasps]
[squeals, growls]
[grunts, pants]
[growls, clicks]
[barks]
[growls]
[Predator shrieks, growls]
[growls, clicks]
[Predator growls softly]
[Naru grunting]
[screams, grunts]
[roars]
[Naru grunting]
[Predator roars, groans]
[Predator growling]
[roars]
[shrieks]
[grunts, growls]
[bellows]
[in Comanche] Petsü!
[Predator shrieks]
[Predator gurgles, groans]
[yells]
[mud gurgles]
[panting]
[growls]
[in English]
Come on, come on, come on, come on.
Do it.
Come on, do it.
[electronic hum]
This is as far as you go.
No more.
This is it.
[beeping]
-[grunts]
-[beeping accelerates]
[roars]
[yells]
[child, in Comanche] Naru iku kima!
Arüka ikÜ! Arüka, Naru kima.
Naru kima.
Hina ma yaa?
[sighs, speaks English]
There is danger nearby.
We need to move
to easier protected ground.
[tribe member chanting in Comanche]
[chanting]
[ululating]
[Sarii barks]