Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
Let's keep those hammers working.
Rambo!
Let's go.
How are you, Johnny?
Good.
That's all.
John, I'm sorry they sent you
to such a hellhole.
- I've seen worse.
- Yeah, you have, haven't you?
John, I told you
that I'd help you when I could.
You interested?
You can't possibly want to stay here
for another five years.
In here, at least I know where I stand.
Yeah, just hear me out first.
A covert operation's
gearing up in the Far East.
Your name was dug out as one of three
most able to complete the mission.
- Mission?
- Recon for POWs in Nam.
Why now? Why me?
Prison camp you escaped from
in '71 is a target area.
Nobody knows that terrain
better than you do.
The risk factor's very high.
You'd be temporarily reinstated.
If the mission's successful,
there may be a presidential pardon.
You interested?
Yeah.
Good. Good.
I'll get the necessary clearance.
Next we'll meet with a Special Ops
designate who haunts the operation.
Yes, sir.
- All clear?
- Yes, sir.
I want you to know I did what I could
to keep you outta here.
I know.
- Yeah.
- Sir?
Do we get to win this time?
This time, it's up to you.
[RAMBO FIRST BLOOD PART II]
That'll be all.
How you doing, Rambo?
I'm Ericson.
Why don't we make it
over to the hangar?
So, you're the chosen one, huh?
You made a hell of a rep
for yourself in Nam.
Anyway, I'm glad to be
working with you.
It may not be heaven,
but at least you're outta the joint.
He's here.
- Morning, John.
- Sir.
Murdock's in charge of Special Ops
from Washington.
Thank you. Rambo,
been looking forward to meeting you.
- Problems on your trip?
- No.
Except for the damn heat, right?
Never felt anything like it.
Come on in.
Let's get down to business.
I was glancing over your files.
Makes for some pretty interesting reading.
"Rambo, John J., born 7/6/47, Bowie,
Arizona, of Indian-German descent."
That's a hell of a combination.
"Joined the army 8/6/64. Accepted Special
Forces. Specialization - light weapons.
"Medic. Helicopter, language-qualified.
"59 confirmed kills, two Silver Stars,
four Bronze, four Purple Hearts,
Distinguished Service Cross,
the Medal of Honor."
You got around, didn't ya?
That's incredible.
You're probably aware
that almost 2500 Americans
are still MIA in Southeast Asia.
Most are presumed killed,
but to the League of Families,
Congress and lots of Americans,
it's still a very emotional issue.
Give me something cold, please.
Rambo, you certainly don't know
as much about me as I do you.
I honched with the 2nd Battalion
3rd Marines in Kon Tum in '66.
I lost a lot of good men,
so I know what you and every vet feels.
Maybe the government and certain
segments of the population didn't care.
My committee cares.
What it needs is proof
that Americans are being held.
Once done, we'll get our men back.
If there's any of our men
at this POW target camp,
you're to confirm their presence
by taking photographs.
- Photographs?
- Photographs.
Under no circumstances
are you to engage the enemy.
- I'm supposed to leave 'em there?
- I repeat, do not engage the enemy.
Phase two Delta Force assault
led by Colonel Trautman
will handle the extraction.
OK?
I'd like to say
that I feel with your participation,
this mission has
a better-than-average chance
to succeed where others have failed.
I'll meet you both
in the operations center in one hour.
Thailand across Laos into
the mountains of Vietnam to the drop zone.
You'll be flying a ceiling of 250 feet
when you bail out.
- Think you can you handle it?
- Try.
Since you're going in solo, you'll rely
on more equipment than ever before.
And use it.
Don't try the blood-and-guts routine.
Let technology do most of the work.
I want you to try to forget the war.
Remember the mission.
- The old Vietnam's dead.
- Sir, if I'm alive, it's still alive, isn't it?
You may find this hard to believe,
but all this is for you.
Impressed?
Besides monitoring devices,
you'll get all the ultramodern equipment
we have to insure your safety.
You can feel totally safe. We have the
world's most advanced weapons available.
I've always believed
the mind is the best weapon.
- Times change.
- For some people.
Don't let me interrupt.
Upon insertion,
call into base camp on Transat,
then proceed to Hawk September
to rendezvous with your contact,
indigenous agent Co Bao.
Is he listening?
Indigenous agent Co Bao.
Colonel. Are you sure he's still
not unbalanced from the war?
We can't have somebody who might
crack under pressure in that hell.
Pressure?
Rambo is the best combat vet
I've ever seen,
a pure fighting machine who only desires
to win a war that someone else lost.
And if winning means he has to die,
he'll die - no fear, no regrets.
And one more thing.
What you choose to call hell,
he calls home.
Stand by to start APU.
T minus 20.
Switching now.
Analyze.
T minus 5.
You've got 36 hours
to get the hell in and out.
- So don't stop and smell the roses, OK?
- Yeah.
Run into trouble, try to get to the hilltop
extraction site marked on your map.
Ready to roll, Colonel.
- Good luck, son.
- Thanks.
Let's go.
Murdock said he was with 2nd battalion
3rd Marines at Kon Tum in '66.
Yeah.
The 2nd Battalion was at Kud Sank.
You're the only one I trust.
- Think he'll find someone?
- POWs? Doubtful.
But there's people to satisfy,
questions that have to be answered.
- You don't sound too emotional about it.
- Wasn't my war.
I'm just here to clean up the mess.
AWACS 25 has arrived.
Holding time line.
- Insertion minus one.
- Affirmative, Wolf Den. Over.
Back in the badlands, my man.
Stand by your position.
Insertion minus 15 seconds.
Party time.
Five seconds. 4, 3, 2...
Jumper away.
- What's happening?
- Turbulence! He's hung up!
He'll be torn apart.
Condition red. He's hung up.
- What?
- What happened?
He's being dragged.
- Lifer, cut him loose.
- I can't free him!
- Ericson, abort mission. Pull out.
- He'll be torn apart.
He's cutting away his equipment.
He's out!
This is Dragonfly 1.
Do you read? Over.
Dragonfly 1, come in.
I read you.
- Any visual by flares?
- Negative.
We didn't see anything.
Maybe it's smart to abort
before there's any more complications.
Who could have survived that?
He deserves the benefit of the doubt.
He's got 36 hours to complete the mission
and reach the extraction point.
- We owe him that.
- Well, of course we do.
But understand something now.
In 36 hours, we pull out.
Rambo!
Did not expect a woman, no?
We'd better go.
Go to river.
How come you so late?
Got hung up.
I have arranged boat to take us down river.
Old ways not safe.
You come a long way, Rambo,
to see empty camp.
You're using pirates?
Best way down river.
Not get army suspicious.
What about patrol boats?
Russian.
Rambo.
Want to eat?
Maybe later.
How you get into this?
- It's a long story.
- Long ride.
Well, after I left the Special Forces,
I moved around a lot.
Why you leave army?
When I... came back to the States,
I found there was
another war going on.
What war?
Kind of like a quiet war,
a war against...
all the soldiers returning.
That's the kind of war you don't win.
It's... it's my problem.
How about you?
How'd you get into it?
My father worked for intelligence agency.
He killed, and I take his place.
It's too much death here.
Death everywhere.
Just want to live, Rambo.
Maybe go America.
Live the quiet life.
What you want?
Well, to win.
To survive.
Not so easy to survive. Still war here.
To survive a war,
you gotta become war.
That why they pick you?
'Cause you like to fight?
No, I'm...
I'm expendable.
Expendable.
What mean "expendable"?
It's like if someone invites you to a party,
and you don't show up,
doesn't really matter.
What is this?
It bring me good luck.
What bring you good luck?
I guess this.
- No further reports.
- I wanna go out with the extraction team.
- Denied.
- Denied?
- Unnecessary risk.
- We have a schedule to keep.
- We don't know if Rambo's alive.
- The odds are against it.
You said we'd go through as planned.
OK. If you want to go
through with it, we will.
Colonel's joining the extraction team.
You're a damn good man, Trautman.
See? Camp empty.
We move closer.
Cycle girl whore from village.
Come on.
- What is it?
- A bow. No sound.
You're not going in there. But I thought
you're supposed only to take pictures.
- What about orders?
- No more orders, Co.
I've come to get you out.
Don't talk.
- There are others.
- I'll be back.
Come on.
All right. Let's go.
- You have clearance.
- Minus one hour to extraction.
I hope for his sake
we're not just wasting fuel.
Let's get moving.
- Good thing you came when you did.
- Why is that?
They move us around
to harvest the crops.
- Only been there a week.
- When's the last time you were there?
A year. Yeah.
- What year is it, anyway?
- 1985.
Camp's supposed to be empty.
Yeah, it's supposed to be.
Come on.
LZ two clicks up river.
- What has happened?
- We've been sold out.
You little bastard.
All right, jump!
- I fight.
- Jump! Go on!
The boat - it's gonna blow!
Jump!
You made it, Rambo!
Come on.
Here. You take this.
We go on from here.
- It better I stay till end.
- This is the end.
Come on, let's go.
Rambo.
You not expendable.
Colonel, three minutes.
Come on.
Move.
That's Rambo.
Christ, he's found one.
Come on.
Rambo's found one of ours.
Dragonfly reports the ground crew
has what appears to be
an American POW with him.
- What did you say?
- They've got one of ours.
Condition Bravo.
Meyers, Harrison, Goodell.
Everybody, out! Come on, move!
COMINT priority frequency.
Give me the mike.
Dragonfly, this is Coach 1. This is
an Alpha Kilo Victor command priority.
Come on!
Abort the mission immediately.
I say again, this is a recall.
- Confirm. Over.
- Say again, Coach 1. Say again.
I'm telling you to abort.
Colonel, I've been ordered
to abort before pickup.
For chrissake, we've got him in sight.
Murdock, do you read?
Come on!
- We're going down.
- You're not going anywhere.
You goddamn mercenaries.
- There's men down there! Our men!
- Come on!
No, your men. Don't be a hero.
Down. Don't leave!
Come on!
What are you doing?
Do you know what the hell you've done?
Don't act so innocent.
You had your suspicions.
And if you suspected then,
you're an accessory.
Don't ever count me
with you and your scum.
It was a lie, wasn't it?
Just like the whole damn war!
- It was a lie.
- What are you talking about?
That camp was supposed to be empty.
Rambo goes in, a decorated vet.
He finds no POWs.
Congress buys it. Case closed.
He gets caught, nobody knows he's alive
except you and your computers,
and you can reprogram that.
Who the hell do you think
you're talking to, Trautman?
A stinking bureaucrat
trying to cover his ass.
No, not just mine, Trautman.
We're talking about a nation's.
It was your hero's fault. If your warrior had
done what the hell he was supposed to,
we'd be out of this clean and simple.
He was just supposed to take pictures.
If they showed something,
they would have been lost, wouldn't they?
I don't think you understand
what this is all about.
The same as it always is - money.
In '72, we were supposed to pay the Cong
4.5 billion in reparations.
We reneged. They kept the POWs.
And you're doing the same thing
all over again.
What would you do?
Pay blackmail money
to ransom our own men and finance
the war effort against our allies?
What if some burnout POW
shows up on the 6:00 news?
What do you wanna do,
start the war over? Bomb Hanoi?
Want everybody screaming for invasion?
Do you think somebody
on the floor of the senate
will ask for billions of dollars
for some forgotten ghosts?
Men, goddamn it!
Who fought for their country.
That's enough!
Trautman, I'm gonna forget
this conversation ever took place.
- You bastard.
- And if I were you,
I'd never make the mistake
of bringing this up again.
- You're the one making the mistake.
- Yeah, what mistake?
Rambo.
Damn Russian bastards.
He's dead now.
Bring him up.
The knife. These people are so vulgar
in their methods.
They lack compassion.
I am Lieutenant Colonel Podovsky.
I do not know who you are yet, but I will.
Take him and clean him up.
That's all.
Thank you, Captain Vinh.
Leave one guard, please.
I see you are no stranger to pain.
Perhaps you have been among
my Vietnamese comrades before?
No answer.
Do you wish to give your name?
Now, what possible harm
can that cause?
Pride is a poor substitute
for intelligence.
What you must understand
is that we have to interrogate you.
To Sergeant Yushin, you are a piece
of meat, a laboratory experiment,
but to me, you are a comrade,
similar to myself,
just opposed by an act of fate.
I know you are trying
to facilitate the release
of war criminals
held by this republic.
I can appreciate this,
but this incident - your capture - is...
...embarrassing.
We must have explanation.
First of all, I wish you
to radio your headquarters
and say that you have been captured
and condemned for espionage activities,
and that no such criminal aggression
should be attempted in the future,
or they will meet
with the same fate as yours.
Fuck you.
You wish to test your strength.
Good. Good.
Yushin.
Comrade, here is something
that might be of interest to you -
a transcript of the conversation
between your helicopter pilot
and his commander we intercepted.
Dragonfly. Wolf Den.
Colorful names.
Here we are.
"We have them in sight."
And the reply.
"Abort the operation immediately."
"This is a recall. Confirm.
Over."
It seems you were abandoned
on direct command.
And these are the people
you protect with your pain.
You may scream. There is no shame.
You are strong, very strong,
the strongest so far,
but you're nearly dead.
For what?
Make a radio call.
To talk, to obey
would be so much easier.
Yushin!
Yushin has a momento for you
of this occasion.
Put it in his eye.
If your life means nothing to you,
then perhaps his does.
Don't tell them anything.
You will talk.
Yes?
Don't do it.
Do it now.
220... 56.
Lone Wolf. Receive.
This is Lone Wolf. 22056.
Lone Wolf, this is Wolf Den.
Transmit location and status. Over.
- What is it?
- It's Rambo, sir.
...Receive. Over.
We read you, Lone Wolf.
What is your position? Over.
I say again, what is your position?
Over...
Your friend dies if you do not answer.
Lone Wolf.
Johnny, where the hell are you?
John, come in.
Murdock?
He's here.
This is Murdock.
We're glad you're alive.
Where are you? Give us your position,
and we'll come to pick you up.
Murdock...
I'm coming to get you.
Come on.
Come on!
Down.
This way!
We safe for now.
You look like hell, Rambo.
Tough night.
Maybe need this.
- You hurt bad.
- It's all right.
Listen...
what you did back there...
I won't forget it.
Thanks.
What you do now?
Try get across through Thailand?
- Yeah.
- Then go America?
Yeah.
You take me with you?
You take me?
Yeah.
I think you make good choice.
- We go?
- Let's go.
You're all right. You're all right.
- Rambo?
- Yeah. Yeah.
You...
You not forget me?
No.
No. No.
- I want the rescue team ready to go.
- Your career,
reputation, your family's security...
- You think any one man's worth all that?
- Yes, I do.
- I'm giving you an order to withdraw.
- Do I get the team or go over your head?
You don't seem to understand something.
I'm in charge here.
You're just a tool.
We're the machine.
I want him placed under arrest.
He's not to leave the base.
- He never had a chance, did he?
- Like you said, Colonel, he went home.
Hey, up here!
Hurry!
Get back!
- Get out.
- Go on! Get moving!
Come on, get on the chopper.
Move it, move it. Move it! Keep going.
Get on the chopper.
Get 'em on the chopper.
Come on!
In the chopper. That's it.
Come on, move it, move it, move!
Come on, let's go.
Keep going! Keep going!
Come on! Move it, move it!
Hurry up! Get on.
Come on, go, go, go!
Man the gun.
Yeah. Yeah.
All right, we made it!
Chopper on our tail!
Hang on!
Hold on!
Fire in the tail!
Lone Wolf calling Wolf Den. Over.
Wolf Den, this is Lone Wolf.
Do you read?
- Wolf Den, this is Lone Wolf. Over.
- Yes, we hear you, Lone Wolf. Over.
Prepare for emergency landing.
Arriving with American POWs.
You heard.
Prepare for arriving POWs! Let's move it!
Get in there!
Let's go! Let's go, let's go!
All right, come on.
Easy, easy now. Easy.
All right, easy now.
Glad you made it!
Come on, you're doing good.
OK, easy with that now.
Rambo, I don't make the orders.
I take 'em, just like you.
I swear to God, I didn't know
it was supposed to happen like this.
It was just supposed to be
another assignment.
Mission...
...accomplished.
You know there's more men out there.
You know where they are.
Find 'em, or I'll find you.
Right over there.
Easy. Easy.
John.
Where you going?
I don't know.
You'll get a second Medal of Honor for this.
You should give it to them.
They deserve it more.
You can't keep running, John.
You're free now.
Come back with us.
Back to what?
My friends died here.
Part of me died here.
Everything that happened here
may be wrong,
but damn it,
don't hate your country for it.
Hey.
I'd die for it.
Then what is it you want?
I want...
...what they want
and every other guy who came over here
and spilt his guts
and gave everything he had wants.
For our country to love us
as much as we love it.
That's what I want.
How will you live, John?
Day by day.
♪ we gave our hearts
♪ we gave it all
♪ Flame in the fire
♪ Burns forevermore
♪ The sorrow in believin'
♪ Honor and truth
♪ Gray spires climbing
♪ wrapped around our youth
♪ Peace in our life
♪ Remember the call
♪ Oh, a cheer for my brothers
♪ Think of them all
♪ Home of the brave
♪ We'll never fall
♪ The strength of our nation
♪ Belongs to us all
♪ Time is the healing
♪ Of souls laid to rest
♪ Peace is the virtue
♪ Never forget
♪ Tomorrow's an angel
♪ Watching us all
♪ Tellin' the people
♪ She wraps around our hearts
♪ Peace in our life
♪ Remember the call
♪ Oh, a cheer for my brothers
♪ Think of them all
♪ Home of the brave
♪ We'll never fall
♪ The strength of our nation
♪ Belongs to us all
♪ All
♪ Peace in our life
♪ Remember the call
♪ Oh, a cheer for my brothers
♪ Think of them all
♪ Home of the brave
♪ We'll never fall
♪ The strength of our nation
♪ Belongs to us all
♪ Peace in our life
♪ Remember the call
♪ Oh, a cheer for my brothers
♪ Think of them all
♪ Home of the brave
♪ We'll never fall
♪ The strength of our nation
♪ Belongs to us all
Please rate this subtitle at www.osdb.link/3aqnp
Help other users to choose the best subtitles