-== [ www.OpenSubtitles.org ] ==-
Subtitles by Prospero
prospero.13t@gmail.com
Do you know him?
Rambo!
Rambo! Rambo.
John!
John.
John Rambo!
I don't believe this.
So where did you come from?
Washington.
Good to see you again.
Yeah, you too.
Do you want to tell me about it?
About what?
How about yesterday, I've seen you stick
fighting in a warehouse in Bangkok.
You saw that?
Yeah.
And today I find you
working in a monastery.
They let me live here
and I help out, fixing things.
And the stick fighting?
I just do that for a
little extra money.
Yeah I...
...saw you give it
to the monks.
You see a lot.
Colonel, who are they?
They're partly the
reason I'm here.
Bob!
This is Robert Griggs,
he's a field officer
with our local embassy.
John Rambo.
Pleasure.
Well, You're certainly
not easy to find.
Why are you keeping track?
Well, like the Colonel says,
good men are hard to find.
John, I'd like you to take a
look at some of these photos.
I don't know how much
you know about Afghanistan.
Most people can't
even find it on a map.
But over two million civilians,
mostly peasant farmers
and their families
have been systematically
slaughtered by invading Russian armies.
Every new weapon,
including chemical warfare,
has been used to eliminate these people.
And they've been very successful,
on many levels.
I assume that you're out of touch
with the current status of the war,
but after nine years of fighting,
the Afghan Forces are now getting
shipments Stinger missiles,
and are beginning to hold their
own against the air strikes.
Except for one region,
50 miles over the border.
Apparently, the Soviet commander
there is exceptionally brutal,
as those photos indicate.
And he's managed strangle
off all aid from the outside.
So, we want to
investigate the problem
firsthand.
And what's that got
to do with me?
They've asked me to go in.
You're not gonna do it?
Yes, and I want you
to come with me, John.
I put in my time.
What's that mean?
It means my war is over.
I thought you said he
was this great soldier.
Well, Colonel...
...looks like we got a
long walk down those stairs.
Don't be down on him,
just following orders.
This mission's important, John.
Do you really think we are
gonna make a difference?
If I didn't,
I wouldn't be going.
It didn't before.
That was another time.
Come with me, John.
I don't know what you
think about this place,
but I like it.
I like bein' here, I like workin' here.,
I like belong into something.
You do belong to something.
Not this.
When you're gonna
come full circle?
What are you talking about?
You said that your war is over.
I think that the one out there is,
but not the one inside you.
I know the reasons you're here, John,
but it doesn't work that way.
You may try, but you can't get
away from what you really are.
And what do you think I am?
A full-blooded combat soldier.
Not any more.
I don't want it.
That's too bad, 'cause
you're stuck with it.
Let me tell you a story, John.
There was a sculptor and he
found this stone, a special stone.
He dragged it home and
he worked on it for months...
...until he finally finished.
When he was ready,
he showed it to his friends,
and they said he had
created a great statue.
The sculptor said he
hadn't created anything.
The statue was always there.
He just cleared away
the small pieces.
We didn't make you
this fighting machine.
We just chipped away
the rough edges.
You're always gonna be
tearing away at yourself...
...until you come to terms
with what you are!
Until you come full circle.
I guess I'm not ready yet.
Well, I got to move.
Promise me you'll look me
up when you get stateside.
I promise.
Colonel!
I'm sorry, but it's got
to end for me sometime.
I understand.
Take cover!
Fire the rocket.
Drop your weapons
and remain where you are!
You cannot escape.
Drop your weapons.
You have no chance of escape.
Drop your weapons!
Now!
Rambo!
Something went wrong.
What happened?
Soviets intercepted the
team just over the border.
From what we've gathered,
Trautman and the rest of his party...
...have been taken to the
regional command post.
And what are you doing about it?
I can't do anything about it.
I'm sorry.
I just thought you should know.
What about me?
What about you?
Can you get me in?
You're not serious.
Oh yeah, I'm serious.
It can't be done officially.
Make it unofficial.
If it can be done, I want you to
know upfront that if you captured,
or if any of this leaks,
we'll deny any participation or
even knowledge of your existence.
I'm used to it.
I'll get back to you.
You want to buy?
Many guns here!
No. I'm looking
for Mousa Ghani.
What's your name?
John Rambo.
Wait here.
They sell many in Afghanistan.
Many land mines.
Land mines everywhere.
I am Mousa Ghani.
What is it you want?
I was sent by Griggs.
You do not look like men
Griggs sent before.
You not look like you
are with military.
I'm not.
What you are? A mercenary?
No.
You're not with military. You're
not mercenary, what are you?
Lost tourist?
I'm no tourist.
Sorry.
Now, do you know
where the American is?
Yes. In a Soviet fort,
near the village of Khost,
30 miles over border.
Mr. Griggs send you
the supplies you asked for.
You wish to see them now?
Yeah.
Is this what you asked for?
Never seen these things before.
What are these?
Detonators.
And this?
What is this for?
It's a blue light.
What does it do?
Turns blue.
I see.
Can you tell me how many
more men come with us?
There's no rescue team.
It's just me.
Just you?
Come on, this is no good.
I can not take only
one man to the fort.
You need more men to help.
Griggs said you'd take me in.
Take me in.
I am needed to take
medical supplies.
If I not take it,
many people will die.
Do you understand?
Well, I do not know
who you really are,
but by the way you look,
I can see you have...
...no experience in war.
Do you?
Come on, do you?
I've fired a few shots.
A few shots?
Come on, maybe you
should go back home,
and think it all over again...
...for a very long time.
I did think it over.
You did?
Well, this is your choice.
But let me tell you, you cannot
get this American alone.
If you fail, do not blame me.
I will accept no responsibility.
Sounds familiar.
My name is Colonel Zaysen,
Regional Commander of this sector.
Do you realize you're the first
American captured in Afghanistan?
Congratulations.
I believe you're planning
to supply enemy rebel forces...
...with stinger missiles
intended to destroy Soviet aircraft.
If I'm gonna be interrogated,
I wanna be interrogated
by your superiors.
Out here, I have no superiors.
I am in full command.
You are alone here.
Abandoned by your government.
What do you want?
Cooperation.
This sector has been under
total control for over five years.
There is little more
I can do here.
It is, as you say,
without challenges.
If you supply to me
worthy information...
...about most stinger missiles
you're planning to deliver,
it could provide a way
out of this for us both.
After all, in the end
what everyone really wants...
...is peace.
The Kremlin's got a hell
of a sense of humor.
Please explain.
You talk peace and
disarmament to the world,
and here you are,
wiping out a race of people.
We are wiping out no one.
I think you are too intelligent to
believe such absurd propaganda.
Now again:
where are the missiles?
I don't know anything
about any missiles!
Of course you do.
But you do not seem to realize
I'm providing a way out for us both.
You expect sympathy?
You started this damn war,
now you have to deal with it!
And we will. It is just a matter of time
before we achieve a complete victory.
You know there
won't be a victory.
Every day your war machines lose
ground to a bunch of poorly armed,
poorly equipped freedom-fighters!
The fact is that you
underestimated your competition.
If you'd studied your History,
you'd know that these people
have never given up to anyone.
They'd rather die than be
slaves to an invading army.
You can't defeat
a people like that.
We tried. We already
had our Vietnam.
Now you're gonna have yours.
So, you wish to test me.
Good.
This is Afghanistan.
Alexander the Great
tried to conquer this country,
then Genghis Khan,
then the British, now Russia.
But Afghan people fight hard,
they never be defeated.
Ancient enemy make prayer
about these people.
Do you wish to hear?
Very good. It says:
"May God deliver us
from the venom of the cobra,
the teeth of the tiger and
the vengeance of the Afghan."
Understand what this means?
That you guys
don't take any shit?
Yes, something like this.
We go now.
To the north there are many caves,
we'll travel through them.
It'll be safer. We go.
This cave leads us to the
"Valley the Five Lions".
In ancient days, the Afghan
King was asked to send...
...500 of his warriors
into battle.
He sent only five.
His greatest five,
and they won.
He said, "It's better to send
five lions than 500 sheep."
What do you think of this?
I think the King was lucky.
Lucky?
How much longer to the village?
About two hours.
Where in my sector are
the missiles being delivered?
I don't know.
You're a liar.
Where?
All right, I'll tell you.
I knew you were lying.
Now, where are
the missiles located?
Close.
How close?
In your ass!
You've tried
my patience long enough.
I tried to be civilized.
The name John Rambo...
...do you know it?
No?
He says there are plans
for a rescue attempt...
...with the help of
some of the rebels.
He also says he knows
where this man is going.
We will welcome him.
It's the last village in the valley.
About 100 men here.
They have a lot of kids here.
Yeah.
And they are
good fighters too.
I'll tell the leaders
we want to talk.
They never see man
look like you.
These are Mujahideen horsemen.
There are 10,000 horsemen
more waiting at the border.
They are waiting to get weapons.
When they'll get it,
they come back here to fight.
Let's go to the hospital.
He's the only doctor
for 500 kilometers.
The first medicine
they get in two months.
More gifts from the Soviets.
They look like toys, but they're mines.
We teach the children not to touch.
Some learn too late.
Who's that?
His name is Uri.
He's Russian.
Deserter?
He calls himself a defector.
There are many like him.
He's the one who can help the most.
He knows the inside of the fort.
I think we should go now.
Mine starts here at 1 meter like
this, then go 2 meter like this,
and like this.
There have four towers,
four guards,
here, here, here and here.
Where do they keep
the prisoners?
Here.
If we get in there,
is there another way out?
Underground,
where is all the bad water.
I do not know words
for this place.
He means sewer.
Where is it?
Here. Outside, it goes there.
Guards patrols there.
I do not think
you go this way.
Now, we should go through the
mine fields. They'll never expect it.
This can not be done. In there
are many Spetsnaz commandos.
We are only this.
We have lost many men.
We lose more men
if we go there.
I don't need many men.
What is it you want to do?
I need two men to get me
through the mine field,
and two to help
with the escape.
If this is done, Soviet will
come here like before,
and more people will die.
I can't wait.
You must wait for help
the way we wait!
Then I'll go alone.
And you will die.
Then I die.
Wait!
Please don't go.
My name is Masoud.
You must not judge us...
...before you understand
why we are not ready to help.
Most of the Afghan
people are very strong,
and we are determined not
to be driven from our land.
Our children die of disease,
mines, and poison gas,
and the women
are raped and killed.
Last year, in the valley
of Laghman, the next valley,
6,000 Afghans were killed.
Pregnant women
were cut with bayonets,
and their babies
thrown into the fires.
This is done, so they will not have
to fight the next generation of Afghans.
Yet nobody sees anything or
reads anything in the papers.
What you see here...
...are the Mujahideen soldiers,
holy warriors.
To us, this war is a holy war.
And there is no true
death for a Mujahideen,
because we have
taken our last rites,
and we consider ourselves
dead already.
To us, death for our land
and God is an honor.
So, my friend,
what we must do is to stop this
killing of our women and children.
If getting this man free,
so he can return to the free world
and tell what happens here, is necessary...
...then of course we will help.
Leave us now, so we may
speak among ourselves...
...and find the best way
to free this man.
Thank you.
We thank you.
Don't worry,
they will decide soon.
Got to get in there tonight.
What is your name?
This boy is very hard inside.
His parents were
killed last year.
His brother died in the fort
where the American is.
He looks like a boy,
but he fights like a man.
What is your name?
Rambo.
Where are you from?
Arizona.
Arizona?
How much days walk?
About two years.
Two years.
Are you a soldier?
No more.
I am a soldier.
Yeah?
Are you here to fight?
No.
Are you scared?
What is this?
It's a knife.
Can I see this?
Sure.
Very good. Can I have it?
No.
What is this?
You want everything!
This is for luck.
What is luck?
Luck is...
Can I have it?
I need luck.
So do I.
Look what a child.
Always like this.
Look there!
It's our national sport.
Old insane game,
maybe 3,000 years old.
No, they never
stop playing it.
War, not war,
they don't mind.
You like it?
I'll take football.
Football? What's football?
You play it with your foot?
Not really.
Come on, let's go.
Hey, American!
What are they saying?
They want you to try.
It's a way to welcome you to be with them.
If you want to try, go ahead, but...
...I'm not responsible for it.
I'll try. Yes?
What are the rules?
Well, you have
to take the sheep...
...once around, and then
thrown it in the circle.
Why?
Because there is a circle there.
That's it?
That's it. Very simple.
Like football.
God must love crazy people!
Why? He makes
so many of them.
Take cover!
Move! Move!
Now you see how it is here.
Somewhere in war,
there's supposed to be honor.
Where is the honor here?
Where?
We are taking the survivors to
the border. Are you coming?
I'm going to the fort.
Have you not seen
enough death?
Go. Go while you can.
This is not your war.
It is now.
So be it.
You are a good friend.
I stay. I will
show you the way.
I will go too.
No, you go with them.
I will not. They killed all
my family. I want to fight.
Not with me. You go.
Go on.
Why must you do this?
Because he'd do it for me.
Have you decided to talk?
No?
Very well.
Soon you will be my
guest down the hall.
Come on.
Go back!
No.
Go back.
Come on!
Stay here! Stay back!
I know this place.
You need me.
I don't need you dead.
Now go back. You understand?
Let's go, sir.
Come on!
American?
Colonel? Colonel?
John? How the hell
did you get in here?
Can you move?
You damn right I can.
Let's go!
John, behind you!
Go!
John, get out of here.
Get the hell outta here!
Go on!
Over here!
Come on!
Help me!
Take him!
Go on!
Hurry!
Give me the boy!
Come on!
Okay!
Take the kid.
Get down!
Give me the boy!
Who is this terrorist? What
makes you so valuable to him?
This bastard tried to destroy
me tonight, but he failed.
At sunrise, I will hunt him down,
and have his skin hanging on the wall!
You don't have to hunt
him. What?
He'll find you.
Are you insane?
One man against
trained commandos?
Who do you think this man is?
God?
No, God would have mercy.
He won't.
It's all right.
There's nobody there.
All right.
This will hold a while.
What's the fastest
way outta here?
Northwest, there's trail
between mountains,
about 3 kilometers from here.
The trail is very difficult.
Now, you take the boy
and go. I want to stay.
You can't.
You cannot go back there.
We must all go to Pakistan.
No, I gotta go back.
I know he's your friend,
but you cannot do this!
You both will die.
For what? Come with us!
Just do what I say.
Give me your gun.
All right, let's go.
Come on!
I see you again?
Sure.
Come on! Move! Move!
Come on!
Can you fly that thing?
Let's find out.
Let's go!
Hurry! Hurry!
Get on board!
Hold on!
Over there!
There!
Hold on!
Get him up!
Take my hand!
We're going down!
Hold on!
Get out of here. Quick!
Come on, move it!
It's gonna blow up.
Take what you can, John!
Come on, move it!
Come on!
We gotta get to the border.
We'll stay here.
We know where to go.
Which direction, John?
Northeast.
Hold it, John!
I gotta rest a minute.
How's the wound?
You taught us to
ignore pain, didn't ya?
Has it worked?
Not really.
Don't take it personally.
Thanks.
You go on ahead and see
if you can find some cover.
No!
John!
That was close, John!
How are you?
Well done!
We don't want to make it easy for
them. We'd better split up.
I'm sorry I got
you into this, John!
No, you're not.
Are you listening?
Who are you?
Your worst nightmare.
That's good timing.
What are friends for?
You get back to the hole.
I'll cover you and see
if there's anyone left.
John!
Across the valley is the border.
We did it, John.
Yeah.
Wait!
What the hell is that?
The son of a bitch!
Do not try to retreat!
You can not escape!
We will not attack
if you do not run.
We do not want to hurt you.
Somehow I don't believe him.
I order you to come forward
and you will be given a fair trial.
Drop your weapons and
remain where you are.
You got any ideas?
Drop your weapons!
Surrounding them is out.
Helluva time for humor, John!
Drop the weapons!
Now!
You have no chance
of escape.
Come forward!
I wish to take you back alive.
This is your last warning.
The choice is yours.
What do you say, John?
Fuck 'em!
If we're gonna go, I wish we could
have taken that bastard with us!
What is that?
It's the rebels.
Come on!
John, get out of there!
John!
You sure you don't want to stay?
You fight good for a tourist.
Maybe next time.
You want this back?
No. You keep it.
Can you not stay?
I've got to go.
Goodbye.
Hard to believe, John.
What's that, sir?
Well, I hate to admit it,
but the truth is I think
we're getting soft.
Maybe just a little, sir.
Just a little.
Subtitles by Prospero
prospero.13t@gmail.com
Please rate this subtitle at www.osdb.link/757hf
Help other users to choose the best subtitles