REPORTER 1 : The federal
government announced
it will declare
bankruptcy in the next 90...
REPORTER 2: Flags continue
to be flown at half-mast
in the U.S. capital...
REPORTER 3: ...have
significantly deteriorated...
REPORTER 4: ...developing
global recession.
REPORTER 1 : ...and sustained
an ultimately disastrous war.
REMY: What do l remember?
I remember reading
about a scientist.
He had a thing
for cats and boxes.
What he'd do
is take a cat and
lock it in a box.
And then, just to
make things interesting,
he'd also put
this machine in there
that released poison gas.
Now, the scientist
didn't actually know
when the machine
would release the poison
and when it wouldn't.
The only way
he could tell for sure
was to look inside the box.
Here's the science bit.
Until he opened it up,
he figured the cat
had to be alive
and dead.
See, if either one
was possible,
then both had to be
possible, too.
Ever since I read
about that cat,
I can't get the story
out of my head.
Don't get me wrong,
I don't give a fuck
about the plight of
small, furry animals.
I just don't understand.
How can anything
be alive and dead
at the same time?
(MOANS)
Are you ready
for tonight's
entertainment?
(BREATHING DEEPLY)
(WHISPERING) Yeah,
go, go, go, go.
Mr. Smythe?
I'm from The Union.
Holy fuck!
Wait! Okay? Just wait.
No worries.
Keep it holstered.
Everything's okay.
l can pay.
Sorry, that's not
my department.
(GASPS)
Hey.
Hey!
(GROANS)
Don't you
fucking touch me.
No need
for violence, miss.
(ZAPPlNG)
Henry Smythe,
l am legally bound
to ask you
if you would like
an ambulance on standby
in order to take you
to hospital.
Nope?
Okay.
(MAMBO MUSlC PLAYlNG
OVER HEADPHONES)
REMY: My job is simple.
Can't pay for your car,
the bank takes it back.
Can't pay for your house,
Can't pay for your liver,
well, that's where l come in.
Good morning, everybody.
I'm Eric Fitzsimmons.
And I'm Sabrina Kenn.
From around the globe
and around the corner,
here's what's happening
in your world this morning.
FlTZSlMMONS: Some big news
coming in from Nigeria
this morning.
KENN: That's in Africa.
FlTZSlMMONS: Now,
of course, you know
that we've already got
1 0,000, 1 5,000 soldiers
over there, waiting
at the Nigerian border.
KENN: Come home soon.
Well, not too soon.
Word's coming in
that the 34th Armored
Division has arrived,
and they're ready to start
the sixth phase of the war.
KENN: Operation
Hope Springs Eternal.
(NEWS CHATTER
CONTlNUES lNAUDlBLY)
Uh-uh-uh ! Don't drink
out of the bottle.
He does.
Well, you don't.
l'm late.
Can you take him?
Sure.
Thank you.
RADlO HOST: ...first place
at yesterday's annual
Coney Island
hot dog eating contest.
Can you say "indigestion"?
REMY: Peter, leave it.
You got everything?
Yeah.
Dad, l'm okay from here.
(SCHOOL BELL RlNGlNG)
All right.
Have a good day.
Okay.
(SlGHS)
(GASPS)
REMY: Almost every job I do
ends the exact same way.
Some whimper. Some cry.
Some even laugh.
But in the end, they all do
the same horizontal mambo,
twitching and
thrusting their way
into the great beyond.
LARRY: Hey,
watch the suit!
(STAMMERlNG) Sorry, sir.
l didn't know that was you.
Sorry about that.
MALE ANNOUNCER: The Union,
helping you get more you
out of you.
In years past,
nearly 200,000 people
waited on organ
transplant lists
at any given time,
hoping for someone else to die
so that they
could possibly live.
But thanks to modern
biomedical science,
the days of waiting
and praying are over.
FEMALE ANNOUNCER: ... where
the artiforg is expertly
and cleanly inserted
with minimal
invasion and scarring.
Now, if you
can't afford the full
payment of $61 8,429,
we can offer
monthly installments
at an APR of 1 9.6%,
standard
for a generic
pancreatic unit.
Frank Mercer,
Union Manager.
l understand
you have concerns.
Affordability.
lt's only natural.
First of all, let me
just reassure you
that our credit department
will find a plan that fits
your lifestyle.
And should you
fall behind,
there is a three-month
grace period.
Not until
after the sixth day of the
fourth month of nonpayment
will we retrieve
the property, at our
own expense, of course,
utilizing our skilled
and licensed technicians.
Now, l'm not sure
what you've heard
on the 6:00 news,
but this almost
never happens.
l got to tell you,
you owe it to your family.
You owe it
to yourself.
Now, if you could
just sign here, here,
and initial here,
we can get started.
REMY: He'll sign it.
Everybody signs it.
All right.
Ears, ears, ears.
Goddamn ears
again. Shit.
A job's a job, right?
l'm just saying, ears,
four times in a row.
Fucking probation
ain't fair.
Wasn't fair what
you did to that woman
on the subway, was it?
(WOMAN SCREAMlNG)
Yeah. Well,
you weren't there,
were you?
Hey, my sister's kid,
he wants in.
He's a good kid.
Talk to Frank.
Yeah, but l figured l'd get
a recommendation from you,
you know? Level Five?
l don't know
the kid, do l?
You're killing me,
coming in the front like that.
l got guys
trying to make sales
out there,
l don't need you
on the floor spooking
clients, all right?
We want them buying,
not thinking.
Six paid-in-fulls
this week. You know
what that means?
No. What, Frank?
They see you,
they start turning down
the loans and coming up
with the cash.
We don't make money
when they pay in full.
Right, pal?
What do you got?
REMY: Liver.
What's that?
Liver.
What, are you hanging out
at AA meetings?
Day's count,
give it up, buddy.
What's the magic number?
Not today, Jake.
(lMlTATES BUZZER)
Wrong answer.
(GROANlNG)
REMY: Jake Freivald
kicked my ass
in the fourth grade.
It wasn't exactly fair,
seeing as he was
in the fourth grade
for the third time.
Maybe he didn't appreciate
the rhyme scheme.
But he had to admire
an aspiring writer
who could give
as good as he got.
After the war, a job at
the Union was a perfect match
for our specialized skill-set.
The recruiter told us
we were protecting America's
medical establishment.
We didn't care
who we were protecting.
(LAUGHlNG)
(GROANlNG) Fuck!
Hey, come on.
Come on, come on.
(LAUGHlNG)
Here you go!
REMY: Two livers
and a Jarvik!
You got to stop nicking
these bar codes, Jake!
Won't happen
again, boss!
(GROANlNG)
You okay, man? You okay?
(GRUNTlNG)
(SCREAMlNG)
l'm working with
fucking children.
(lMlTATlNG
ELECTROCUTlON
SOUNDS)
Come on, let's go hit a few.
Yeah, all right.
l've got to tell Carol.
Of course you do.
So, did you talk
to Frank today?
About moving
over to sales?
No, l didn't get
a chance.
What? You mean
when you were
standing next to him?
Right. Right,
l'll talk to him
on Monday.
You know, you're
turning me into a
horrible, naggy bitch.
You were always
a horrible, naggy bitch.
Just get him out of here.
See you later.
Yeah.
REMY: Come on.
That went well.
Maybe next time
she'll crochet you
a set of balls.
What do you think?
FEMALE ANNOUNCER: Come
test-drive the most advanced
neural sensory replicator,
The Union's M.5 Neural Net.
Sweet dreams
are made of these.
(HlP HOP MUSlC PLAYlNG
ON CAR STEREO)
MALE ANNOUNCER:
Stay super dry.
JAKE: You know what
this is about, right?
lt's about control.
She's trying to control you.
l mean,
you got to move
from Repo to sales,
that's like
cutting your pay
in half, man. Half.
She thinks sales
is more stable.
Nine to five,
no late nights. l'll
be home more often.
Buddy, you and me,
we're always gonna be Repo.
(POLlCE CAR SlREN WARBLlNG)
Check out fatty.
You know his organs
went out a long time ago.
Twenty bucks
says he's overdue.
Yeah, l'm in.
20 bucks.
REMY: Deadbeat?
Almost.
Pancreas. Two days.
Oi ! How's your
pancreas holding up?
(STAMMERlNG)
l sent the money in
this morning.
You better hope
you did.
48 hours,
your organ's mine.
(LAUGHlNG) Slow down,
mate. You're gonna need
a new heart, as well.
P. Morton?
That's Patrick Morton.
The guy from Company C?
Yeah.
Here, let me see it.
(LAUGHlNG)
The bastard. . .
Bastard, he still
lives with his parents.
Did you ever repo
anybody you know?
l had to do
my granddad.
(SNORTlNG)
What are you
laughing about?
You try
to explain that
to your grandmother.
Fuck you,
you didn't.
l would. l would,
on Day 96, if they
gave me the pink sheet.
l know you would.
A job's a job, right?
Yeah, a job's a job.
(SULTRY MUSlC PLAYlNG)
(SlNGlNG) Now you say
you're sorry
Hey,
you want another beer
or something?
Oh, man.
For being so untrue
Stare any longer,
you'll be married
by the weekend.
Well, you can
cry me a river
Cry me a river
l'm gonna go start
a fight or something.
I cried a river over you
Well, you can cry me a river
Cry me a river
I cried a river over you
Hiya.
(WOMAN CHATTERlNG ON RADlO)
(ROMANTlC SONG
PLAYlNG ON SPEAKER)
Remember this?
Jimmy T-Bone?
Hmm?
Peter's sleeping.
Well, we'll turn it down
and use our quiet voices.
Music's too loud.
(MUSlC STOPS)
(DOOR SLAMS SHUT)
Peanut.
(SNlCKERS)
Peanut. Wake up.
You awake? Hi.
Hi.
How was school?
We learned
about the Romans.
Mmm?
l made the club.
l can see.
One for you, too.
Thanks.
Weren't these
from medieval times?
Yeah.
Mrs. Begs is making
me redo the project.
Well, if she says redo it,
you better redo it.
l hate the Romans.
Aw, that's a shame.
The Romans
were real badass.
You know, they used to make
people fight with lions.
Mrs. Begs says they used to
burn down all the villagers
when they attacked them.
She's right.
Scorched earth.
Stones at the enemy.
Pretty effective tactic.
Hey, Dad?
What?
Why did the Romans
stone people to death?
'Cause they didn't
have any guns.
Mmm.
Go to sleep.
Good night.
(SKA MUSlC PLAYlNG
ON SPEAKERS)
l don't want
to stifle you,
but, you know,
you might wanna
turn them over
just a little bit more.
Well, if people
ate them as quickly
as l'm cooking them,
they wouldn't burn,
would they?
All right. Hey, hey.
Hot dogs! Charbroiled.
MAN: Save me one
of those, all right?
JAKE: Kind of crispy.
(CELL PHONE RlNGlNG)
Yeah?
(SlGHlNG) No,
this is not a good time,
l'm not at home.
What do you want?
Nobody eats the salad.
No one ever eats
beetroot salad.
l told you not to
waste your money on it.
Okay, l'll
call you back. Bye.
l need to. . .
l need to borrow your
grill master for a minute.
(SOFTLY) Give me
your apron.
What?
l got a mobile
coming here right now.
You want some of this?
To my house? Fuck, no.
The guy's six
months overdue.
No.
lt's a double commission.
l'll give you half.
Half.
l'm paying you
for a full ride.
l just want to get to
the Fairmont downtown.
Don't worry.
You'll be done
in a minute.
Two minutes. Tops.
Two minutes, tops.
Yeah.
Where's the case?
Front closet.
You're a saint.
l know.
He's gone to
get more meat.
(NERVOUSLY)
Who's that guy?
(GRUNTlNG RHYTHMlCALLY)
Relax, fellow.
He's a friend of mine.
He's a friend
of yours?
Hey, come on, man.
Come on, let me out of here!
Open the door!
Come on, man !
(ZAPPlNG)
(GROANlNG)
Thanks a lot, man.
Where are you going?
Getting a jacket.
l'll get you a. . .
Carol !
Hey. l could have
gotten you a coat,
for goodness' sake.
What the fuck
do you think
you're doing?
l'm stepping away,
right now.
Get this out of here!
No, no. He's gone.
He's out of here.
Love, come on.
lt's just a kidney.
He's got another one.
He's fine.
REMY: Jake?
Jake.
Peter, turn off
the phone!
Give me that.
Where are you
going?
Where are you going?
Oh, come on, not this.
Let's talk about it,
huh? Slow down,
let's talk about it.
Make a decision.
l went as fast
as l could, man.
Yeah,
l know you did.
l'll have to have
that talk with Frank.
Did you hear about
that new M.5 Neural Net?
No. You've been reading
those fucking
pamphlets again?
(CHUCKLES) l saw it
at a trade show.
The damn thing,
it takes over
the whole limbic system.
Brain damage,
stroke, you name it,
it doesn't matter.
They hook you up,
and then it's like
you're living
the rest of your life
in a dream.
Yeah?
How do you
get it out?
(BEEPlNG)
Hold on a second.
(BEEPlNG CONTlNUOUSLY)
Wait, wait, wait!
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa!
Shit.
What?
We got a nest.
All right, fine.
lf you want, you can
go in first on this one.
What's that? A favor?
Of course l'm going in first.
You went first last time.
No. . .
lt's simple
mathematics.
You either have
the money, or you
don't have the money.
You have the money,
l'll find you a seat
on the boat.
Listen to me.
You gotta listen to me.
There's a bank
in Buenos Aires,
at the corner of
Cacao and Santa Fe!
There's a woman there. . .
(PEOPLE SCREAMlNG)
Raid !
(ZAPPlNG)
Call it.
Ten.
l'm going to
beat you by two.
(SCOFFlNG)
(MEN GRUNTlNG)
Where you going?
l just got here.
And you ! Now you !
(BOTH GRUNTlNG)
(ENUNClATlNG)
Are you having fun yet?
Wake up! Wake up!
(GROANS)
The Force is strong, Luke.
(SCREAMlNG)
You all right?
What are you doing?
l thought
you needed help.
l had him.
Didn't you see l had
my knife in his side?
l knocked him down.
He goes on my count.
(LAUGHlNG) You're
joking me, right?
Jake.
l've been
working on this guy
for 1 0 minutes!
Ten minutes l've been
working on this guy.
You gonna come in here
and just hit him
on the side of the head
with a pipe?
Jake.
Look, you're not
taking a life.
You're keeping
The Union viable,
so we can
continue to give. . .
Conquering heroes
have returned
with their spoils!
All right.
What do you got?
Eighteen hosts.
32 forgs.
Thirty-two
and a half!
FRANK: Half?
Midget.
Little people.
Please, l have a cousin.
We found a boat
heading out of port.
Look at these.
Two of them had
scanning jammers.
We pinged them,
they read free and clear.
l opened them anyway.
They had three forgs each.
Stupid bastards
will try anything.
Mmm.
Thirty-two forgs.
Pretty impressive, boys.
You ever think
about doing this
on a regular basis?
Spec?
Yeah !
You run your own ship.
Take down these nests.
Don't have to deal
with me and the
pink sheets anymore.
You two riding around
together, kicking ass,
taking names.
l can talk to Corporate,
see if they'd bump up
the commissions a bit.
What do you think, man?
What do you think, buddy?
Forget it.
Actually, Frank,
l've been meaning
to talk to you
about something.
(CLEARS THROAT)
Something. . .
Yeah. Forget that.
Find somebody else.
Just get us
our pink sheets.
FRANK: Suit yourself.
Okay, look. Can l just
ask you something?
Mmm-hmm.
What do you think
keeps a world like this's
shit together?
lt's not magic.
lt's not.
lt's rules.
lt's people abiding
by the terms of the deals
that they sign themselves.
lt's rules.
You know
what's more important
than the rules, though?
lt's the enforcement
of those rules.
l mean, we got
a responsibility,
you and me.
l mean, what we do,
l mean, maybe it's small,
l don't know,
but it matters.
lt matters.
(SlGHlNG)
l'd actually work
less hours.
You're sure about this?
A job's a job,
right?
A job's a job.
Just make sure that
they give you hazard pay.
You'll be sitting
next to Frank,
in some booth,
telling some
cancer-riddled prick,
"You owe it to your family.
You owe it to yourself."
There's a good chance
you'll choke
on your own vomit.
You should go finish
that T-Bone job.
Yeah.
lt'll be your last hurrah.
Get Carol a chance
to blow off some steam
at the same time.
You ready to go after
the Patrick Morton's?
l was there this morning.
He said to say hi.
You didn't do it?
l did it. He said
to say hi before that.
(SOUL MUSlC PLAYlNG)
REMY: Jake's right.
And if this is
going to be my last job,
then they don't come
much better than Jimmy T-Bone.
T-BONE: (SlNGlNG ON TAPE)
Every day
Will be like a holiday
REMY: l've been
listening to his music
since I was in high school.
And the way I see it,
at least he's gonna get
his heart ripped out
by someone who
appreciates his music.
T-BONE: (SlNGlNG ON TAPE)
When my baby comes home
lt's a nice house.
Thanks.
Not really mine
anymore.
You from the lRS?
No.
Soul suckers,
taking everything back.
Mmm.
So am l.
(SlGHS) Uh. . .
Can l finish this song?
Yeah. Of course.
l'm a bit of a fan,
actually.
(SCOFFS) Yeah? Good.
You can help me out.
(STAMMERlNG)
l don't. . .
l don't know.
l wouldn't be much help.
lt's not
that complicated.
A song is just a bunch
of separate tracks,
all working together.
Just got to know
when to break it down.
You know, pull it out,
one thing at a time.
Well, l can do that.
And every day, oh, yeah
Will be like a holiday
Oh, yes, it will
When my baby
(MOUTHlNG)
When my baby comes home
That's a motherfucking
hit right there.
lRS will be thrilled.
(SCOFFS)
(MUSlC STOPS)
Can you make sure
my boy Terrance
at Blue Note
Records get this?
lt's done.
(EXHALES)
Now,
l'm legally bound
to ask if you would like
an ambulance on standby,
in order to take you
to the hospital.
And, what,
they gonna give me
a new heart?
Christ, no,
not with your
credit history.
l know, it's a
chicken-and-egg thing.
There's a
complaints department.
Nah, man, nah.
Let's just. . .
Will l sit or stand?
Easier if you lie down.
(ELECTRONlC WHlNlNG)
What the fuck
is that, man?
My defib unit.
Jarvik stops pumping
when you give it a jolt
with electricity.
Saves me from
losing my finger.
Hold on, hold on.
ls this. . .
ls this going to hurt?
You won't feel a thing.
REMY: l have been
knocked unconscious
on four separate occasions.
Knockout number one,
military training.
Head back for
the concussion test.
What test?
Congratulations, son.
You've got
a very small brain.
REMY: Small brains,
big skulls.
That's why they put us
in a tank.
(EXCLAlMlNG)
Fire-fucking-power!
Target sighted !
Fire on will !
(BOTH WHOOPlNG)
That's you !
Oh, shit!
lt fucking disappeared !
Here, right?
REMY: And then one night,
the war was over.
And there we were,
all dressed up
and nowhere to go.
You see, for us,
the war never ended.
It just changed venue.
Beauty!
Come on !
Come and get it!
(GRUNTS)
REMY: That takes care
of number two.
And this
is knockout number three.
FRANK: (SOFTLY)
He's waking up.
Hey.
Looking good.
Looking real good.
You gave us
a big scare, buddy.
The client?
Look at this guy.
Two seconds out of a coma,
and he's worried
about the pink sheet.
You scare me, pal.
Don't worry,
we'll get him.
Carol?
She left
a while back, buddy.
l don't
remember.
Faulty shock unit.
Frank's got the guys
back at the shop looking
into that right now.
Huh? What is it?
l mean, you know
that l will be here,
no matter what.
l would change
your fucking diapers
if you needed me to.
But we got some
business that we got
to discuss right now.
Oh, sure. Look. . .
Jake, he does my work
until l get back
on my feet.
You're a very lucky man,
you know that?
What you're
looking at here
is the new Jarvik 39
heart module,
top of the line.
(GASPlNG) No.
Oh, yes.
REMY: No, no, no.
Ten billion beat warranty.
lt's got
the no-rust valves. . .
Get it out.
Get it out, Jake.
JAKE: You got hit
pretty hard.
All you got is scar tissue
in there right now.
l feel fine!
(CHUCKLlNG) 'Cause
the unit's already
doing its work.
All you have to do
is sign a few papers.
They can take out the meat,
put in the new forg,
sew you up
better than new.
The warranty alone
on this baby. . .
Don't you sell me.
l'm not a fucking client!
Of course
you're not.
You're the best Repo
in this whole damn town.
But you gotta have a ticker
to play the game, am l wrong?
You got to do what
you got to do, buddy.
Take care of yourself.
You owe it
to your family.
You owe it to yourself.
(MACHlNE BEEPlNG)
What? What did l say?
You're an asshole, man.
(GRUNTS)
NURSE: Sir?
(GROANlNG)
NURSE: Sir, that's
hospital property.
(MACHlNE SHUTTlNG DOWN)
(GRUNTlNG)
(PANTlNG SHALLOWLY)
(RAPlD BEEPlNG)
Buddy? Come on.
Let's go back inside,
all right?
Now you're just
being childish.
NURSE: Well, that should
take care of your pain
and help the artiforg
assimilate into your body.
You got it
for three more days,
and then it's cold turkey.
(DOORBELL RlNGS)
Carol?
The lock's broken.
My key works fine.
Where are you going?
That's a bit
extreme, isn't it?
l told you to
make a decision.
You made it when
you did another job.
Can l see Peter?
Come on, Carol.
l'm sorry.
Who's out here
ringing my bell?
Damn kids.
Hey, man ! Get your
convalescent ass in here.
Thanks again
for this, yeah?
You're home, man.
You're home.
Yeah. Yeah.
And your timing's
perfect, all right?
1 5 minutes,
the game starts.
Remember that Chinese
chick from downstairs?
Yeah.
Her.
Well, she's coming up
to watch the game,
and she's bringing
a friend.
And her friend is hot.
l'm giving her to you.
But can l just say
one thing, though?
This place here
is the happy, happy room.
Listen. You know, man,
l'd love to hang out,
but l think it's better
if l just sleep.
Great.
You wanna sleep?
Yeah.
No problem.
But one other thing.
What?
(LAUGHlNG)
(GROANlNG)
The guys all
missed you so much,
we thought we'd get you
a little welcome-back present.
l'd like to introduce
Harry the Heart.
(ALL CHEERlNG)
(TECHNO MUSlC PLAYlNG)
Hello!
(ALL WHOOPlNG)
(lNAUDlBLE)
What are you
doing in my house?
Mr. Erikson,
l'm from The Union.
Stop! No!
(CHOKlNG)
(GASPlNG)
(HEART BEATlNG)
(EXHALES)
(HEARTBEAT ACCELERATlNG)
(HEARTBEAT SLOWlNG DOWN)
(SlGHS)
(FUNKY MUSlC PLAYlNG
OVER SPEAKERS)
(lMlTATlNG FANFARE)
All hail the
conquering hero!
MEN: Hey.
PATRON: Nice.
Welcome back.
Big stuff.
You gonna keep me
in suspense,
or you gonna tell me
the details?
What happened?
lt was standard.
Standard job.
lt was easy.
You know, the usual.
Pleading, a few tears.
Oh, man,
l had this guy
last week, right?
As soon as the guy sees me,
he starts bawling
like a little girl.
And this snot bubble,
it starts growing
out of his nose.
And the more he cried,
the bigger it got.
Bigger and smaller,
bigger and smaller.
He's like. . .
(WHlMPERlNG)
l'm like, "Whoa!
Okay." l'm like,
"Whoa, whoa,
slow down, slow down."
REMY: Listening to Jake
swapping stories
about some schmuck
and his overdue liver,
all I can think about
is how that schmuck
has a name
and a wife
and kids.
(BREATHlNG DEEPLY)
Hey, Peanut.
Hey.
How are you?
Good.
How's school?
Okay, l guess.
Only okay?
(CHUCKLES)
Peter.
Go inside.
(WHlSPERlNG)
You listen to your mum.
Go back inside.
Okay.
lt'd be good to talk.
Carol.
Carol !
lf l could come in
for just a minute. . .
Something
changed.
JAKE: Frank just called.
He said you never
turned in that pink.
You told me there was
no problem, right?
You said that there was. . .
lt was an easy job.
Right?
(SlGHS)
Hey, hey,
l get it, l get it.
No problem. l understand.
l mean, everybody
needs a break, right?
No time at all,
you're gonna be
back on your game.
You're gonna be
knocking them dead.
REMY: Mr. Timmons,
you owe it to your family,
you owe it to yourself.
l made some moussaka.
l want you to try
this béchamel sauce.
l'm falling behind
on payments.
l really need
to make some cash.
Do what you got to do.
JAKE: Gotta make
some money, right?
REMY: Yeah.
JAKE: But you get it
out of your system.
All right?
Of course, if you
can't pay the bills,
some Union man will
break into your house
in the middle of the night,
slice you open
from the collarbone
to the pelvis with a scalpel
and reclaim
our property.
(GASPS)
l'm just saying.
Clearly, I'm not
cut out for sales.
And this new heart's
accumulating interest
with every beat.
MAN ON TV: Hello. Uh,
can we have your liver?
REMY: Most people don't know
when they're gonna die.
I have exactly
six days, three hours
and between 20
and 30 minutes,
depending on how punctual
my Repo Man is feeling.
It's amazing how fast
90 days go by.
Fuck!
We're supposed
to be partners.
And you're just
fucking up our shit.
You know that?
You're fucking up
everything.
Don't you see that?
We've always
been lucky here.
The metal graveyard's
a fucking treasure chest.
Thirty minutes,
you're going to be
back on top.
You're gonna see,
all right?
lt's a black hole.
That's all it is.
(SCANNER BEEPlNG)
There it is, on a platter.
Esophagus. Five months over.
Okay, no, you're not
ready to do a kid.
Fine, fine.
JAKE: Hey, hey,
where are you going?
(THUDDlNG)
Liver and kidneys.
You want me to start?
All right, Jake.
(ZAPPlNG)
(GROANlNG)
You've done this
a thousand times!
What the fuck is
wrong with you?
You stay right here
until you get this done.
Then you find
another one.
You find another one.
You get as many as you can.
l want you to
get over this hump.
You do this.
(GROANS)
(GRUNTlNG)
REMY: Part of me,
most of me,
doesn't mind too much
if this is how it ends.
'Cause it's over anyway.
For those still counting,
this is knockout number four.
WOMAN: (SlNGlNG DlSTANTLY)
Well, you can cry me a river
Cry me a river
I cried a river over you
Now you say you're sorry
For being so untrue
Miss?
Well, you can cry
me a river
Cry me...
Hey, where did you
hear that song?
Miss?
(CONTlNUES SlNGlNG
lNAUDlBLY)
Miss?
How do you know
that song?
And dream of days we...
(GROGGlLY) l know you.
REMY: In three days,
they can legally come
take my heart.
I may not be making
the best use of my time.
(VOMlTS)
Two days of withdrawal.
It's not like I can't see
the dirt or the scars
or the Q stains
on her lips.
I should leave.
But for some reason, l can't.
(BEEPlNG)
I saw an interview
with a serial killer once.
Said it took him six years
to work up to his first kill.
The second, a year.
The third, just a week.
Once that dam broke,
it was a flood.
Making people die,
it had become second nature.
Apparently, it also works
the other way round.
How you feeling?
Stop!
Stop! Stop it!
(CURSlNG
lN SPANlSH)
l didn't ask
for your help!
(GROANS)
What did you want me to do,
leave you on the street?
(CHUCKLlNG SOFTLY)
You're as fucked as me.
(LAUGHlNG)
(WHlSPERlNG) Maybe not.
REMY: lt took me
a while, but l think
I finally understood
why the scientist
put the cat in the box.
He was trying to
tell us something.
We're all alive.
We're all dead.
We're all that cat.
But we have to make a choice.
We either purr
and lick ourselves
and wait for the poison
to put us down
or we scream and scratch
and claw our way
right out of the top
of that damn box.
You get nine hearts
when l wasn't looking?
My uncle was a bank robber.
l ever tell you that?
Made a mess
of the west coast,
knocking over savings
and loans, you know.
And he was good
at it.
Nobody ever knew
a damn thing.
He thought
he was home free.
He woke up
in the morning,
went to work
at the auto shop.
But every once
in a while,
he'd skip out for lunch,
pull on a ski mask,
rob a bank.
Then one day, the cops
came knocking at his door.
Let me guess.
He was relieved.
(CHUCKLES)
No, he was
fucking pissed.
He went soft.
He was off his game.
And he knew it.
Who do you think
Frank's gonna send
after me? Ray?
Probably Ray.
l don't know.
Maybe me.
(SlGHS)
Mmm.
A job's a job.
You still believe that?
REMY: (WHlSPERlNG) Peter?
Peter.
(SLEEPlLY) Dad?
Yeah.
Hey, listen,
l'm going away
for a while.
It means I won't be
able to pick you up
on Saturdays.
But I'll think about you
every day that goes by.
(SLEEPlLY) See you
on Saturday.
What happened?
We got to leave.
What?
l got caught trying
to clear your forgs.
Now they'll want
to know where
the rest of them are.
You're clear.
You can leave me here.
l'll be fine on my own.
lt's okay.
l did yours first.
l didn't get to mine.
Are you coming?
REMY: The thing is,
l have an artificial heart,
and she has an artificial
everything else.
Maybe we're two parts
of the same puzzle.
Maybe it's not just her
I'm trying to save.
Why you giving this to me?
l figured you'd
want the option.
Was l wrong?
Give it to
somebody else.
You want it?
Didn't your eyes
used to be brown?
Opticor 202, with
kaleidoscope enhancement.
How do you keep track
of all those things
you've got in there?
Let's see.
Pancreas and kidneys
from the diabetes.
One went bad
outside warranty.
l had to go black market
on the replacement.
Liver, stomach
and lungs,
thanks to Q habit.
Knee from
the car accident.
Upgrades. l've got
eyes, ears, voice box.
Jackson Reproductive
Replacement System,
release 5.3.
Lady Mystique model.
Comes in six
sparkling colors.
Stop.
Flexor Dura-Joints.
Billion step warranty.
Stop.
Ask me about my lips.
What brand
are your lips?
(SOFTLY) They're all me.
Happy birthday.
lt's not
my birthday.
(MlMlCKlNG HlS ACCENT)
Birthday.
Happy birthday.
l didn't get you
anything.
Yeah, you did.
GlRLS: (CHANTlNG)
There was a man
from Troubadour
who got blown up
during the war.
He did not die,
would not concede.
REMY: So what is it
I'm writing?
It's not just
some crappy memoir
or even an attempt
at apologizing for
everything I've done.
This is a cautionary tale.
I hope that you might learn
from my mistakes.
'Cause in the end,
a job is not just a job.
It's who you are.
And if you want to change
who you are,
well, first,
you have to change
what you do.
GlRLS: (CHANTlNG)
There was a man
from Troubadour
who got blown up
during the war.
He did not die,
would not concede.
How many artiforgs
did he need?
Here.
Thanks.
GlRLS: Stomach, bladder,
pancreas, eyes, intestines.
So, what is it?
A novel? Epic poem?
Thoughts.
lt's just
(EXHALES)
stuff.
And it's not finished.
What?
Somebody's coming.
You don't hear it?
What are you doing?
Put them on.
GlRLS: ... who got blown
up during the war.
(FOOTSTEPS)
(FEEDBACK SCREECHlNG)
(EXCLAlMlNG)
GlRLS: He did not die,
would not concede.
(VOLUME lNCREASlNG)
How many artiforgs
did he need?
(FOOTSTEPS)
Stomach, bladder,
pancreas,
eyes, intestines, liver,
blood, guts, head !
Get down !
Who's that?
Landlord, come
to collect.
Grab the
typewriter!
There's a
fire escape.
No, no! Downstairs.
What the fuck is this?
This is bullshit.
l thought you were
a Level Five.
Quite honest,
l'm. . .
l'm a little
disappointed.
You're disappointed?
They sent
the ear guy after me,
imagine how l feel.
That's a good one.
You'll be laughing
out of the other side
of your mouth
when l have your
heart in my hand.
(SCREAMlNG)
Shit. Beth ! Get back!
Beth !
(SCREAMlNG)
No!
Fuck!
Shit.
Oh, shit!
lt hurts!
Beth, get
out of there.
REMY: Come on, get out!
(BELL RlNGlNG)
(GROANS)
Welcome back.
Whose car is this?
The landlord's.
l borrowed it.
You're leaking quite
a bit of fluid there.
l can fix it.
Where are we going?
We're gonna pick up
some supplies.
Where'd you find
all that stuff?
When you're
on the streets
long enough, babe. . .
(GRUNTS)
(GROANS SHARPLY)
There.
"What do you do for a living?"
"l'm a fucking lung.
Can you believe that shit?
"lt's ridiculous, right?"
Great example
he's setting.
You all right?
Never been better.
l'll be
five minutes.
(FUNKY MUSlC PLAYlNG)
FEMALE ANNOUNCER: Attention,
shoppers. This month only...
Hey, Larry.
Hi, Larry!
Watch it, kid.
lf you ever want
to make Repo,
keep your fucking
head up.
What the fuck
do you want?
(GROANlNG)
Afternoon, boss.
(LAUGHlNG)
l should have given you
that lung job.
You look good
in that thing.
Yeah? lt itches
like a motherfucker.
Yeah, that's what
the kid said, too.
Nice Taser.
Yours?
No.
Nor is that.
l'll do that
to the next one.
The one after.
The one after that.
l guarantee, you'll
run out of Repo Men
before l run out of ways
of killing them.
Great, great.
This is just great.
Do you have any idea
what this makes me
look like?
One of my own guys
jumping credit, huh?
Yeah.
Now take me
out of the system.
Fine. Give me
your heart.
l said take me
out of the system.
And l said give me
your goddamn heart.
For Christ's sake,
you sound like one of them,
whining and begging.
There is no way
out of the system !
You screwed that up
when you pulled
your little stunt
with the bar codes!
Yeah ! That's right,
Einstein !
They pulled all
the local scanners!
Now every artiforg reclaim
has to go back
to the main office,
get scanned in
behind the pink door!
So, unless
you're thinking about
breaking into Corporate,
give me
your fucking heart!
Or,
and there is
an option here,
we could sit down
and talk this out.
You know, maybe
come up with a plan
that fits your. . .
We're leaving.
Where are we going?
Kenya. South America.
Anywhere The Union isn't.
The airport?
No one gets out
through the airport.
lt's impossible.
Not with these.
l don't get it.
How'd he get in here?
He was wearing
the damn lung costume.
l'm glad you
find this amusing,
(PHONE RlNGlNG)
'cause now
he's yours.
Where's my
goddamn shirt, huh?
A job's a job, right?
(SCANNER BEEPlNG)
WOMAN ON PA:
Your attention, please.
Hold there.
Forward. Thank you.
Now boarding, Flight 2701
to São Paulo, Brazil
Sir?
at Gate 29
MALE AGENT: Forward,
please. Hold there.
If you are
a passenger on that flight,
please proceed to Gate 29.
Thank you.
What if it
doesn't work?
lt has to work.
Should l check it?
No. No.
You really don't
want to be found
with a jammer in here.
l looked at him.
REMY: Huh?
Shit.
A little holiday?
Uh, funeral.
You done with that?
Have a nice day.
(SCANNER BEEPS)
Thank you.
Forward, please.
Hold there.
Thank you.
Forward.
Sir, forward,
please.
Hold there.
Thank you.
Forward.
That was fun.
Thank you.
WOMAN: Honey, look.
Excuse me, miss?
Your leg's bleeding.
Come on.
Ma'am, do you need
some assistance?
l'm okay. Thank you.
She's fine. Thanks.
We can't let you
fly like this.
Sorry?
Sir, there's blood
all over the floor.
We need to get her
cleaned up.
l'm fine, really.
ls that really necessary?
The quicker
we get this done,
the quicker you can
get on the plane.
REMY: l promise you,
she's all right.
Let's go.
This way, please. Come on.
We still gonna
make the plane?
Absolutely.
These tickets
refundable?
l have no idea, sir.
REMY: So when's
the last boarding, then?
MALE AGENT:
l don't know, sir.
FEMALE AGENT: Okay,
let's take a look
at that leg.
Doctor told her
to take it easy.
She doesn't listen
to anyone.
(GROANS SOFTLY)
lt's okay.
lt happens all the time.
(KNOCKlNG ON DOOR)
That's him.
You don't want
to do that.
(BEEPlNG)
Everybody's got to be
a fucking hero.
(GROANlNG)
(SCREAMlNG)
(SCREAMS)
(TlRES SCREECHlNG)
REMY: We got to dump
this car, get you
a new kneecap. Hold on.
(TlRES SCREECHlNG)
(HORNS BLARlNG)
BETH: l know
someone who can help.
He's outside the Union.
ls he a vulture?
We don't have any choice.
Believe me,
it's the last place
l want to go.
This is a bad idea.
He always left me
a key up here.
How well did you
know this guy?
(ELEVATOR WHlRRlNG)
(VOCALlZlNG)
(SlNGlNG)
I gave her my loving
She gave me blue balls
I gave her my money...
Put it away.
(SlNGlNG) l gave her
the thing a man...
BETH: Asbury.
Little, little
Miss Muffet.
Don't call me that.
(SPEAKlNG SPANlSH)
We need your help.
Why'd you have to
drag me a U-man, huh?
l'm not with them anymore.
Why? Did you quit
or was he quitted?
(SPEAKlNG SPANlSH)
Got my cookies?
Yeah, l got
your cookies.
(CLEARS THROAT)
(SPEAKlNG SPANlSH)
Don't touch
anything, U-man.
(BETH GRUNTS lN PAlN)
ASBURY: Come on,
stop your whining.
l was thinking of you
when l tweaked this.
BETH ON TAPE: He always
left me a key up here...
Asbury... Don't call me that.
Universal remote.
Vocal auto-playback with
an eight-hour buffer, man.
l'm telling you, this is
gonna be a head-blaster
at all the parties.
Mark my words.
l see you haven't changed.
Well, no, l haven't.
Have you?
(UPBEAT JAZZ MUSlC PLAYlNG)
(WHlRRlNG)
REMY: You pay
for these?
What'd you say?
Did you pay for these?
Pay for yours?
That's different.
Yeah, how's that
different, U-man,
huh?
l'm Robin Hood, baby.
l'm Jesus, l'm Gandhi.
l can lift the valve
from some fresh meat and
then drop it in a new client
for half the cost.
Bottom line,
l don't kill my clients.
l wait for them to die.
What do you do
to your clients when you're
finished with them, huh?
Chop them up
for dog meat?
You know what?
You got your own
thoughts, huh?
Company parrot?
l'd rather be
a fucking parrot. . .
Parrot!
. . .than a fucking vulture!
Fucking vulture!
Parrot! Parrot!
You think you're
the solution, man?
You're the problem !
l'm the problem?
You're the fucking
problem !
Hey! When the pissing
contest is over,
may l have some help?
(MUSlC STOPS)
So what do you want me to do?
You want me to put you two
on the boat, is that it?
Yeah. But l can't run
if l can't walk.
l'm sorry, baby,
l just don't fly with
joints anymore.
We're gonna have to
switch over to Alva
for that insertion.
That bitch
almost killed me.
Well, that's your side
of the fairytale, isn't it?
But l'll tell you something.
lt warms my cock that you're
still sore about that.
(SOFT MUSlC PLAYlNG)
(GROANS)
Have a seat.
LlTTLE ALVA: Another one, Mom?
ALVA: Yeah, baby,
another one.
So let Mama
work a minute.
That's Little Alva.
Hey.
Hello.
Before we start,
l'm gonna need
to know about all
your other artiforgs.
What do you mean?
You put most of them in.
Beth, humor me.
(SlGHS)
Ears, Vocar.
Opticor eyes.
My liver is a Hexa-Tan
from a specialty house
in Denmark.
My kidneys are actually
two different models.
One is a Union generic.
The other one
(YAWNlNG) didn't
hold up so well.
(BETH EXHALES)
Lord, l thought she was
gonna go on forever.
Wait. Don't you need her
to tell you the rest?
Nah, that's just my version
of "Count back from 1 00."
All right, baby, you're up.
What are we doing?
ALVA: A new knee.
What? She's the surgeon?
Yeah, l just do
anesthesia these days.
The little one's
got the steadier hand.
She's five!
She's nine, actually,
but she's been doing this
since she was four.
Ain't that right,
pumpkin?
Shh !
l almost got it.
Yay!
(EXHALES)
BETH: l feel like
break dancing.
REMY: Go on, then.
Hop along.
Wait.
(DEVlCE BEEPlNG)
Stay here.
(CRACKLlNG)
Beth, let's
get out of here.
(MAN GROANS ON TAPE)
ASBURY: All right, all right,
all right, I'm coming.
U-man number two, huh?
Man, you guys regen
like a cancer...
Beth.
(MAN GROANS ON TAPE)
ASBURY: All right...
lt just goes on
like that for awhile.
How'd you find us?
Found you the same way
you would have found me.
l see what's
going on here.
l get this.
l get it. l do.
But l can
make this right
with Frank.
All you got to do
is you got to
come back with me.
Beth, wait there.
l'll deal with you later.
No.
l can't go back.
That's who
you are, man.
That's who you are.
Not anymore.
Not since the accident.
There you go again
with the accident!
lf l had known that
you were going to be
such a
pussy
about the accident. . .
What?
What, you thought
it was fate?
Sort of karmic plan
to get you right
with the world?
ls that
what you thought?
Jake. . .
Let me tell you,
the cosmos,
it doesn't know shit
about swapping out
electrical leads.
You rigged
the defib unit.
Didn't you?
For what?
So l'd build up debt
so l wouldn't transfer
to sales?
You're not a salesman, man !
You never would've been.
You never could be!
All you had to do was
just to keep working.
You and me,
doing our thing.
You're fucking crazy,
do you know that?
You could have
killed me.
l tried to
save your life.
l'm not going with you.
Well, l'm not
letting you go.
God !
(BOTH GRUNTlNG)
God.
(GROANlNG)
(BELLOWlNG)
(YELLS)
(GROANlNG)
(LAUGHlNG)
(CONTlNUES LAUGHlNG)
Let's go, buddy.
No!
FRANK: You owe it
to yourself.
JAKE: You've done this
a thousand times!
Buddy, you and me,
we're always gonna be Repo.
REMY: (WHlSPERS) Stay with me.
BETH: (WHlSPERS) Always.
FRANK: There is no way
out of the system!
You screwed that up
when you pulled
your little stunt
with the bar codes!
BETH: Hey, wake up.
Wake up.
Come on, get up.
(GROANS)
You okay?
Uh-uh.
(CHUCKLES WEAKLY)
We got to go.
MAN 1 : Raid ! Repo!
MAN 2: Raid, raid !
MAN 3: Go! Go! Go!
MAN: Raid !
BETH: Fuck!
(WOMEN SCREAMlNG)
(TASERS FlRlNG)
WOMAN: Help me! Please, help!
Where'd they go?
(MUFFLED SCREAMlNG)
(DlSTANT SHOUTlNG)
Singing my favorite song.
(EXHALlNG) Okay.
Wait.
Back off!
(ENUNClATlNG)
Give me one reason
why l shouldn't
pull this trigger.
Welcome to your
world, Repo Man.
(lNDlSTlNCT DlSTANT SHOUTlNG)
(DlSTANT GUNFlRE)
(EXPLOSlON)
(GASPlNG)
Come back inside.
We can stay here
until we find a way out.
There is no way out.
Stop, please.
Not for anyone.
Wherever we go,
wherever we hide,
they'll find us.
That's what they do.
That's what l did.
What do you
want to do?
Finish this.
Okay, so we go
to headquarters and
find the pink door. . .
We go to headquarters,
we find the pink door,
we wipe the system.
No more accounts.
Nobody's overdue.
That's easy.
Here he is.
Hmm?
Peanut.
Dad !
Thanks for bringing him.
l can't believe
you let it get this far.
Just let me have
a minute with my son.
Who's she?
Carol,
shall we do this
on the train?
Come on.
Frank and Jake
are calling me
three times a day,
trying to find you.
l haven't got time
for this.
All l'm asking for
is a few minutes
with Peter.
CAROL: Do you think
l'm having a good time
trying to raise him
on my own?
Mom ! Dad.
Peter, l'm talking !
(WHlSPERlNG FlERCELY)
l didn't have
a fucking choice!
You think l wanted
to just walk away
from the situation?
Give me a moment
with my son.
CAROL: Oh, l'm sure
that's exactly what you like,
for your problems
to just walk away
and just disappear.
That's not. . .
(ZAPPlNG)
(WHlSPERlNG) Peter!
(REMY CHUCKLES)
That was
very naughty.
(STlFLlNG LAUGHTER)
Very, very naughty
what you just did.
BETH: Come on, come on,
we gotta go.
When you're old enough,
you read this.
And if you still want
to see your old man,
l'll be in Punta del Este.
Can you say that?
Punta del Este.
REMY: l love you.
Look after your mum.
Hi.
Come on. Again?
So, what's the plan?
Wait here.
My feet are
always freezing.
What? The cotton socks
don't work?
l always wear
cotton socks.
Hey, who's this guy?
Sir, this is
a restricted area.
lt's all about
who you know.
So what is it,
bright pink
or pale pink?
l don't know.
You see a pink door,
you go for it.
(ELEVATOR BELL DlNGS)
Let's go.
(CHATTERlNG)
(MUZAK PLAYlNG)
Come on.
Oi !
(PANTlNG)
(GUNSHOT)
This is it?
Oh, shit.
Union men.
What are we
going to do?
(SOFTLY) Fuck.
Grab the ax.
Freeze!
GUARD 1 : Don't move!
GUARD 2: Drop it now!
Your weapons!
Drop your weapons!
Do it now!
Anyone comes through
that door, kill them.
(GRUNTS)
(ALL YELLlNG)
Hacksaw!
(HACKSAW CLATTERlNG)
(ALARM WAlLlNG)
AUTOMATED MALE VOlCE:
Please make your way
to the nearest exit.
This is not a drill.
Have a nice day.
Go on.
Make a delivery.
Please make your way
to the nearest exit.
This is not a drill.
(ELECTRONlC CHlRPlNG)
(GROANS)
(DOOR BEEPS)
Beth !
(GRUNTlNG)
Great! That's just
fucking great!
(GRUNTS)
(GROANlNG)
There's no keyboard.
There's no
keyboard.
So?
So, if there's no keyboard,
how can l get into the system?
How do l wipe
the accounts?
Maybe there's
a different way.
Using what?
l don't know.
An interface or something.
Look at it, Beth,
it's a scanner. That's it.
Even if we were just. . .
l mean, we. . .
The only. . .
(SlGHS)
The only way out
of the system. . .
ls what?
(QUlETLY) The only way
out of the system
is to repo ourselves.
(ALARM CONTlNUES WAlLlNG)
Can't get in
without a forg.
We're surrounded
by the fucking things.
Please make your way
to the nearest exit.
This is not a drill.
You're kidding, right?
Stop it.
No. Stop it.
No!
Beth.
We'll die.
We can fight
our way back out.
We didn't come
all this way
to run back out.
Help me.
(SlREN CONTlNUES WAlLlNG)
(SCANNER CHlRPlNG)
Wait.
(GROANlNG)
(GASPlNG)
l can't.
Beth.
l can't dance
the mambo alone.
(BEEPlNG)
AUTOMATED FEMALE VOlCE:
Please deposit one artiforg
in reclaim drawer.
Have a nice day.
(ALARM CONTlNUES WAlLlNG)
Please make your way
to the nearest exit.
This is not a drill.
Have a nice day.
(BEEPS)
(GROANlNG)
(BEEPlNG)
Stay with me.
Always.
(SQUELCHlNG)
(DOOR BEEPS)
REMY: Stay with me.
Only one left,
all right?
Only one left.
Don't go now.
What are
you doing?
l'm losing her.
There's only one left.
Oh, Jesus, this is
fucking pathetic.
Finish it.
Stay with me!
JAKE: ls it really
worth it?
ls she really
She's worth
every job we ever did.
FRANK: End it, Jake.
Now.
All right, then.
Enough of this bullshit.
l'll do it myself.
Beth.
Give her a shot.
Just give her a shot.
(GASPlNG)
We're out.
AUTOMATED FEMALE VOlCE:
Please deposit 1 1 artiforgs
in reclaim drawer.
Have a nice day.
We're not out
yet, buddy.
Not yet.
Scorched earth.
Just like you told the kid.
Romans. . .
They were some badasses.
(BEEPlNG)
AUTOMATED FEMALE VOlCE:
Artiforg not recognized.
Lockdown in effect.
(BEEPlNG RAPlDLY)
An administrator
will be with you shortly.
Have a nice day.
JlMMY T-BONE:
(SlNGlNG ON RADlO)
Every day
Will be like a holiday
BETH: Mmm.
Christ, it's hot.
lt's the tropics.
Yeah, l know.
lt's hot.
Are you going to
stay here and act macho,
or come and have some fun?
Christ, it's hot. Huh?
Macho.
(READlNG TlTLE ALOUD)
Sounds kind of fruity.
(LAUGHlNG)
Peter had it published.
"An instant classic.
"The depths of
this author's insights
are astonishing."
(JAKE LAUGHlNG)
Am l in this?
(STATlC CRACKLlNG)
JAKE: What's happening?
TECHNlClAN:
It's just a glitch.
It'll sort itself out.
There. All better.
(MONlTOR BEEPlNG RHYTHMlCALLY)
See? His endorphins are up,
limbic system's
running strong.
Hey, hey, you guys
take it easy.
l want him to be
comfortable. All right?
Yes, sir.
TECHNlClAN: Nothing
to worry about.
lf that hook had
hit him any lower,
it might have
posed a problem.
The M.5 Neural Net
is top of the line.
What's he thinking about?
TECHNlClAN:
No way to know.
Yeah, but he's
happy right now.
As long as someone's
paying for the system.
There's 50 commissions
right there. That'll
take care of his heart,
that'll take care
of the down payment
on the M.5.
The Union
can dock my pay
for the rest.
Hey, sir. Sir!
This one's
still alive.
Leave her.
l'll take care of her.
Hold.
Sweet dreams, buddy.
For extensive
neurological injuries,
l'd have to recommend
the M.5 Neural Net.
We're running a special
on it this month,
1 8% for the first year,
24% after that.
Why should your loved one
pass on just because of
a little brain damage?
That's barbaric.
That's just bad science.
(STlFLES SOB)
With the M.5 Neural Net,
yesterday's dreams
are today's reality.
Imagine your loved ones
living out the rest
of their natural lives
in a world where
they are always happy,
always content,
and always taken care of.
You owe it to your family.
You owe it to yourself.
A little fruit
for the fruit?
Why not?
Cheers.
(LAUGHlNG)