Created and Encoded by --  Bokutox -- of  www.YIFY-TORRENTS.com. The Best 720p/1080p/3d movies with the lowest file size on the internet.
My name is Alice.
I worked for Umbrella Corporation
in a secret laboratory...
...developing experimental
viral weaponry.
There was an incident.
A virus escaped.
Everybody died.
Trouble was...
...they didn't stay dead.
This was the start of an apocalypse
that would sweep the entire world.
The men responsible for this disaster
took refuge underground...
...and continued to experiment
with the deadly T-Virus.
They felt secure
in their high-tech fortress.
But they were wrong.
Biohazard terminated.
Central Shibuya.
Confirm?
I confirm.
Nice shooting.
And I lead three to one.
The night is young.
Plenty more fish in the--
Toshi, are you okay?
Toshi, where are you?
Sentry three respond.
We lost contact with another one.
- Chairman Wesker.
- Report.
Sir, a half-hour ago,
we began to lose contact...
...with some of our perimeter sentries.
- How many have we lost?
- All of them.
And you waited 30 minutes to tell me?
We thought it was a communications
problem. I didn't want to disturb you.
Give me the surface gate.
- This is Chairman Wesker.
- Sir.
Report your situation.
Everything is quiet here.
No sign of intruders?
- Hotaka.
- We have movement.
Multiple targets.
Surface gate, identify targets.
Repeat, identify targets.
Sir, Elevator 2 is moving.
I want security at that entrance.
Hey, boys.
Is that any way to treat a lady?
Tell security to flood
the main entrance with nerve gas
Sir, our men are still up there.
Any more questions?
Intruders in Sectors 1 through 5,
7 and 8.
Reports of gunfire
in Sectors 10 and 11.
Stay at your stations.
All security protocols
are now in full effect.
Lock down all elevators.
Seal all internal blast doors.
And I want damage reports.
Come on, move.
- Go, go. Everybody-
- Get out.
Turbulence. Turbulence. Turbulence.
Turbulence. Turbulence.
Turbulence. Turb--
Any last words?
How nice to finally meet the real you.
Hurts, doesn't it?
Well, that's just the start
of the bad news.
All those powers of yours:
Speed, strength, accelerated healing.
- Well, you can kiss all those goodbye.
- What have you done?
The serum I've injected you with is
neutralizing the T cells in your body.
Put simply...
...the Umbrella Corporation
is taking back its property.
You just didn't work out,
so you're being recalled.
I'm what you used to be.
Only better.
Please wait.
Last words?
Thank you.
For killing you?
For making me human again.
Pu/I up. Terrain. Terrain.
This is Arcadia, broadcasting
on the emergency frequency.
There is no infection.
We offer safety and security,
food and shelter.
This is Arcadia, broadcasting
on the emergency frequency.
There is no infection.
While I took revenge on Umbrella...
...the last handful of survivors
took a chopper to safety.
They were headed for a town
in Alaska called Arcadia.
We'd received radio transmissions
from there.
They offered food and shelter,
safety and security.
A haven, free of infection.
May 3rd, 1600 hours.
A hundred and seventy-seven days
without signs of life.
I'm at 58.37 degrees north,
134.58 degrees west.
Closing in on the coordinates for
Arcadia, but no signs of it on any map.
I hope Claire and the others made it.
You're not coming?
Take care of the others.
Good luck, K-Mart.
Claire.
May 3rd.
1930 hours.
Arcadia.
No such place exists.
Just an empty field.
And a beach.
But we all heard the transmissions.
Someone must have sent them.
Someone must have brought
all these people here.
But Why?
And where did they go?
Day 177. Signing off.
I don't know
if I can do this much longer.
What if I'm the last one?
What if there is no one else?
No one to watch these tapes.
Is this my punishment...
...for letting all this happen?
Hey. Wait!
Wait, please! Stop!
Hello.
Hello?
Answer me.
Hey, he)'
It's okay.
Sorry about that.
But I had to get this thing off of you.
What is this?
Who did this to you?
Do you even know who I am?
My name is Alice.
We met in the Nevada desert
18 months ago.
Any of this sound familiar?
Mikey, Carlos, L.J.?
K-Mart?
You left in a helicopter...
...with a group of survivors
headed for Alaska.
Arcadia, remember?
May 4th, 0800 hours.
Plotting a course for Prince Rupert
in British Columbia.
I'll pass Vancouver,
drop down to Seattle.
After that, it's San Francisco
and the rest of the Western seaboard.
My passenger
is still as talkative as ever.
Whatever that thing was...
...it was injecting her
with some sort of drug.
Something that causes memory loss.
I just hope the effects
aren't permanent.
Your name...
is Alice, right?
She speaks.
Look, I'm sorry about back there.
I don't know what happened.
I don't remember anything.
I don't even know my name.
It's Claire.
Claire Redfield.
Claire?
Sound familiar?
Not really.
You'll get used to it.
Perhaps you can cut me loose now.
We should get to know each other
a little better first.
City of Angels.
May 6th, 1800 hours, Los Angeles.
No signs of life.
Not even the undead.
Some must have burnt with the city.
But what about the rest?
Oh, my God.
What?
Look over there.
Damn.
It's a plane.
It's a plane!
I knew it.
- I told you they would come.
- Hey, we're down here. Hello!
No way we're getting in there.
Where is he going?
Why is he flying away?
- It's not flying away. It's circling.
- Circling?
Damn, he's low.
Down!
What the hell is he doing?
He's gonna land.
Get the stuff out of the way.
- Land?
- Yeah.Land.
That is one crazy son of a bitch.
This may get a little rough.
Then cut me loose.
Thanks.
Just don't do anything crazy, all right?
Nothing as crazy
as what you have in mind.
- Come on, Kim, move it.
- I'm trying.
Well, try!
All right, hold on.
Hurry, he's coming.
Come on.
- Come on, pull it. Come on.
- Come on, pull!
Good. Good.
Good work.
That's it.
Good job.
- Nice landing.
- I think technically it's called crashing.
Luther West.
Alice. That's Claire.
Luther West. A pleasure
to make your acquaintance.
Hi, my name's Crystal.
No, no. Enough with the introductions.
So you're here to help us, right?
- Can you get us out?
- You from Arcadia?
- What did you say?
- Are you from Arcadia?
- What do you know about Arcadia?
- They said they'd help.
There are survivors.
Civilization and safety.
Infection free.
- So they sent you, right?
- No.
But there are others out there
like you?
It's just us.
There's to be no rescue?
I'm sorry.
- Sorry.
- Look, don't take it so bad.
They had their hopes up and...
Thought you could take them
to the promised land.
Angel Ortiz.
That was some fine flying.
Thanks.
- What's the prognosis?
- She'll live.
Yeah.
You know...
...I have the strangest feeling
I know you.
Yeah, I get that a lot.
You're a sports fan, huh?
Do you like basketball?
Not really.
No?
Well, maybe just a fan
of fine timepieces.
Yeah.
Luther here is our resident superstar.
So tell me about Arcadia.
What exactly do you know?
Just from their transmissions.
We've been receiving their broadcast
all week.
Food and shelter, safety and security,
no infection.
We thought they sent you.
We've been launching flares for days
to get their attention.
- Flares?
- Yeah.
Who's gonna see flares
from Alaska?
- Alaska?
Arcadia. I've been there.
It's in Alaska.
It's a town, or so we thought.
A town?
I don't think so.
Take a look.
At what?
You see?
It's not a town.
It's a ship.
I recorded this from the shortwave.
This is Arcadia,
on the emergency frequency.
There is no infection.
We offer safety and security,
food and shelter.
It's the same message.
They must have sailed the coast,
picking up survivors.
This is Arcadia, broadcasting
on the emergency frequency.
What is that?
I don't know.
That was the last we heard from them.
Then it just stopped.
That was two days ago.
We've been sending up flares
on the hour.
So when you arrived, of course,
we thought they sent you.
Claire.
That ship over there.
That's Arcadia.
I know.
- You remember?
- I remember the beach.
People were coming to help us.
What happened?
Why didn't you go with the others?
I don't know.
I can't remember.
We have to get to that ship.
Welcome to your new home,
cell block B.
Crystal's our cook.
The menu's not extensive,
but she is a master of what she does.
Sorry I didn't bring better news.
Get used to disappointment, right?
That's what my agent used to say.
Were you an actress?
I came to Hollywood,
ended up waiting tables.
Why are we waiting?
Excuse me. I'm hungry. Thank you.
- Get out of here, man.
- Thank you.
I met plenty of creeps like him
in my time.
What's his story?
Back in the world, he was some
kind of big movie producer.
The boy's got a stick up his ass.
Kim Yong used to intern for him. Still
hasn't figured the world has changed.
That plane,
do you think it could still fly?
- It can fly, but it only seats two.
- So take us to Arcadia one at a time.
Look, I think she was lucky
to land here once.
Five or six times would be suicide.
No offense.
None taken.
There has to be another way out.
We have to get to that ship.
Well, there is the--
What?
Nothing.
Look, it would be a waste of your time.
I have time to waste.
When the shit hit the fan,
we took refuge in the prison.
It seemed like it had the biggest,
strongest walls.
The best chance
of keeping those things out.
By the time we got here, the guards
and inmates were already long gone.
I guess when people started eating
one another...
...there wasn't much point
in keeping anybody locked up.
We thought the place
was abandoned...
...until we made a discovery.
Wendell...
...time to take a break.
It's about goddamn time.
I hate being down here.
I'm hearing movement in the walls.
So let's check it out.
I'll be back in a minute.
Come on.
Name's Chris.
You were the one flying that plane.
How do you know that?
Wendell isn't the only one
that hears things.
I'm glad you made it.
Maybe you can talk some sense
into these people.
What do you mean?
Isn't it obvious?
I'm not a prisoner.
I shouldn't be in here.
I was working with a military unit.
We were using this place
as a staging post.
Things were already bad
when the order came through...
...to release all the inmates.
We needed as many people
on the streets as possible...
...to fight those things.
And it was chaos.
We were pulling out and a gang
of the prisoners jumped me.
I guess they thought I was a guard.
I woke up, my unit was gone.
I was in here.
Their idea of a joke.
You don't believe me.
Do the others?
You need to get me out of here.
- We're all trapped here.
- That's true.
But I can help you.
Seen enough?
- You find anything?
- No.
I know a way out of this place.
If you get me out of here,
I'll do the same for you.
You're gonna need me!
Have you checked
what he's talking about?
His way out?
He's not telling us shit till we
let him out. And I'm not letting him out.
The man is a killer.
- Really?
- I can see it in his eyes.
How can you be so sure?
I know people.
Interesting. So tell me.
What do you see
when you look into my eyes?
Holy shit.
Girl's gotta be prepared.
What would you possibly want
with those?
It's a hobby.
A hobby?
All right.
Well, I'll see you in the morning.
No sign of anyone on deck.
Your friends are out there?
I think so.
You don't remember?
It's coming back.
Slowly.
Nothing that makes any sense.
We still have running water.
That's very civilized.
We do our best.
It's cold.
Our best only goes so far.
- These are for you.
- Thank you.
I guess I should leave you to it.
I guess you should.
I'll be right outside.
Thank you.
Luther?
- Take it easy, honey.
- Move it.
Okay,
I'm just gonna be on my way now.
Okay, take it easy. Take it easy.
Get out of my sight.
What is that smell?
Must have burrowed up
from the sewers.
Wendell said he heard things moving.
What? So these things can
just burst out anywhere?
We gotta get out of this place.
Arcadia will send help.
No one's coming to get us.
Okay? No one.
We have to help ourselves.
- This plane that you have.
- Won't hold everybody.
- Well, we can draw straws.
- No.
We all get out of here
and no one gets left behind.
Great.
How are we gonna do that?
Walk out of here, just single file?
Are you crazy?
- They didn't want him getting out.
- He's dangerous.
Angel, what do you think?
I think we don't have much of a choice.
This is insane.
Crystal, Crystal, look at me.
What do you think?
- I mean, not even you're that dumb.
- I guess I am. I agree with Angel.
If this guy thinks he knows a way out,
I wanna hear it.
All right.
Seriously?
This is a mistake.
This is a big mistake.
You better keep your eyes on him.
I was wondering how long
it would take.
_I__
- All right, let's get the hell out of here.
- Claire?
- What?
Claire, it's me.
It's Chris.
I don't know you.
Claire.
I'm your brother, remember?
What the hell's happened to you?
It's okay.
Let him go.
Look, she suffered
some sort of memory loss.
If you really are her brother...
...it'll come back.
All right, this is touching.
Family reunion.
If we could just get a move on, please,
before we're all eaten the fuck alive.
Behind those doors is a UPV,
urban pacification vehicle.
The prison kept it
in case of a serious riot.
Sixteen-wheeler, steel plate,
water cannon. It seats 20.
Ten tons of fun.
We roll on out in style,
drive right over them.
The lock's jammed.
But we can cut through it.
When we hit the coast,
we have to transfer to a boat.
- We're gonna need more firepower.
- I got you covered.
When I was stationed here,
we used the basement as an armory.
It's got every weapon
you can dream of.
How do you know your unit
didn't take them with them?
Because by the end...
...there were more guns
than there were people to use them.
You go get the guns. Luther.
Oh, my God.
What is this?
They had pumps to keep the water
out of the foundations.
When the electricity failed, some of
the lower levels started filling up.
There's another two floors down there.
And how far down is the armory?
All the way.
Luther, come on.
Get back. Get back.
Where do you think you're going?
I was a swim champ
back in high school.
- Is that right?
- Here.
You're gonna trust me with a gun?
Yeah. Why not?
Luther, just shoot that motherfucker.
What the fuck is that thing?
All right. Let's go.
Let's go.
Nice.
Damn.
There must be hundreds of them
out there.
We can't go back that way.
- Oh, shit.
- What do you mean, "oh, shit"?
What--? What is this?
What do you think it is?
Don't tell me
that thing fits inside of there.
Can you put this back together?
Maybe, but it could take a week.
What do we do now?
I know.
Bennefi...
...what have you done?
Luther, we gotta get out of here.
Come on.
Did you hear that?
Come on, baby. Come on.
- What are we doing?
- Getting out.
- But the others.
- Fuck the others.
Now, get on board.
Bennett, what are you doing?
- Hey!
- Kim Yong! Don't do this.
Open this door.
Bennett, please.
Bennefi!
Oh, shit!
That's right, bitch. Fuck you.
Yes! Yes!
Son of a bitch.
I'm sorry. I'm so sorry.
He's headed for the Arcadia.
Alice.
Come on!
Head for the shower block.
- Move.
- I'll meet you there.
This thing has no power.
We won't need power.
Oh, shit.
Hold on!
Hey, head to the shower block. Go.
Over here!
- Are you all right?
- I'm fine. Thanks.
This is some kind of joke, right?
The tunnels lead to the sewers,
the sewers lead to the storm drain.
This storm drain leads to the sea.
- It's our only chance.
- I'll take point.
I got your back.
Ladies.
All right, you're next.
- I can't do it.
- You can.
Let's go!
Those things are close.
We found a way out just down there.
The tunnels drop into a storm drain.
Go. Be careful.
Where's Kim Yong?
Go. Go.
I knew you'd make it.
Luther!
Help!
You can't help him now.
We have to move on.
No welcome party, huh?
It looks like Bennett made it.
Let's check inside.
- Did you find anyone?
- Nothing.
I checked the crew quarters.
They're all gone.
Looks like they left in a hurry.
This is Arcadia, broadcasting
on the emergency frequency.
There is no infection. We offer safety
and security, food and shelter.
Fuel, power,
everything's running normally.
Look at this.
It's the ship's log.
The crew launched the lifeboats
three days ago.
Exactly when
the transmissions stopped.
But it says
there are still 2000 survivors on board.
We have to search every inch
of this ship.
Umbrella.
Of course.
I remember them coming for us.
This whole thing, Arcadia, was a lie.
No, it's worse than that.
It's a trap.
Where is everybody?
I don't understand.
I think I do.
They're underneath our feet.
They're holding survivors
to experiment on them.
Look.
It's K-Mart. She's here.
Bring them up.
All of them.
Here she is.
K-Mart.
Get her out.
K-Mart, it's okay. It's okay.
- K-Mart, it's all right.
- I'll get this off her. Let everyone out.
We're your friends.
Right now, we need your help.
Let me get this off you.
Why am I not surprised?
You weren't too hard to find.
Our satellite system is still operational.
And there aren't too many people
flying nowadays.
And besides, I always knew
you'd be drawn to your friends.
L_Qyal'£y...
...highly overrated.
Stop.
Down.
Wouldn't want you harming my pets.
Drop your guns.
Thank you. Kick them to me.
Good.
You don't look so good, Bennett.
Yeah, I'm looking forward to playing
with your pretty face.
What do you want from me?
The T-Virus brought me back.
But it's so strong.
It fights me for control.
I thought if I ingested
fresh human DNA...
...I could redress the balance.
No wonder your crew abandoned ship.
No matter.
Now I have a new subordinate.
And a new plan.
You were the only one who
successfully bonded with the T-Virus.
Your DNA is stronger than the others.
I ingest you...
...I gain control.
That's pretty smart thinking.
There's only one problem
with that plan.
Stop right there.
And what is that?
I'm not on the menu.
Well, isn't this one big family reunion?
Chris and Claire Redfield.
You've really become quite
an inconvenience for me.
I told you I'd be bringing a few friends.
You should have brought more.
Claire. Claire!
Chris!
Don't even think about it.
Who the fuck are you?
I don't think so.
Don't-- Don't you shut them.
I'm a producer!
Open those doors.
You are gonna deal
with some serious consequences.
You motherfuckers.
Open the--
You're gonna live to regret this,
all of you!
Oh, God.
I just wanna go home.
Hey...
...it's gonna be okay.
No.
Chris! Alice!
Come on!
I didn't want you to miss that.
That's right.
Star power, bitches.
It's a miracle.
I never dreamed there would be
this many of us left alive.
So, what's next?
This is Arcadia, broadcasting
on the emergency frequen--
I say...
...we live up to the promise.
This is Arcadia, broadcasting
on the emergency frequency.
Location 118.30 degrees west,
34.05 degrees north.
There is no infection.
Repeat, there is no infection.
We offer safety and security,
food and shelter.
If you are out there, we will help you.
There is hope.
- What is that?
- Trouble.
Deployment in T-minus 57 seconds.
When you hit the deck,
you watch your formation.
Take no prisoners and shoot to kill.
Total enemy numbers are unknown...
...but will include Umbrella fugitives
and prime targets.
Claire Redfield, Chris Redfield
and Project Alice.
So, people...
...whatever's waiting for you out there,
just know one thing:
You are gonna be in for the fight...
...of your lives.
Hey, boys.
Is that any way to treat a lady?
Best watched using Open Subtitles MKV Player