Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
(FOOTSTEPS)
(♫)
LEON: When I was a kid...
I used to think about the kind
of man I'd grow up to be.
(SNARLING)
I never thought my life
would turn out this way.
(♫)
MAN: So you're Chris Redfield.
The expert on the living dead.
The big hero.
Bet you killed a lot, huh?
So, Mr. Expert...
any advice on dealing with them?
Yeah.
- You got friends?
- Heh, heh.
Sure. I got friends.
- Family?
- Yeah.
Got a wife. My folks.
A little sister.
CHRIS: There's corporations
out there creating viruses...
turning people into Bioweapons.
People like you and me.
Your friends. Family.
There will come a day when
you'll be faced with a decision.
Kill them...
or be killed.
Doesn't sound very
heroic, does it?
Sorry.
We're approaching the target,
so let's go over everything...
so there's no mistakes.
The target is Glenn Arias.
He's wanted internationally
for weapons trafficking.
And we're not talking
about M16s and IEDs here.
We're talking cutting-edge shit.
He likes doing business anywhere
there's a major conflict.
Intel says that Arias is now
in possession of a B.O.W.
A.K.A. Bioorganic weapon.
That's why the BSAA is here. They
know how to handle those things.
Our undercover agent,
Cathy White...
went missing weeks ago,
along with her son, Zack.
We have two objectives today;
Find them...
and grab Glenn Arias.
(♫)
CAPTAIN: Comm check.
SOLDIER: (OVER HEADSET) No
movement outside the compound.
Split up into three teams.
We're going in.
(HEADSET BEEPS)
Clear.
(♫)
(CLOCK TICKING)
(CLOCK CHIMES)
Jesus.
(CLATTERING)
Are you okay?
(GUNSHOTS AND SCREAMING)
Go!
(♫)
(GRUNTS THEN YELLING)
(ZOMBIES SNARLING)
Zack?
Yeah.
(SNARLING)
(♫)
Go!
(ZACK YELLS)
(PANTING AND WHIMPERING)
(YELLING AND SNARLING)
Redfield, come in.
Anybody. What the
hell's going on?
(ZOMBIE SNARLING)
Emergency Evac. Get
the chopper now.
(SOLDIER SCREAMING)
(SNARLING)
Get out of here!
(♫)
Arias.
(GROANING)
Thanks to you, I'll have to move
my business somewhere else.
You son of a bitch.
Please.
I'm a businessman.
I make good products available
to anyone who wants to buy.
And at reasonable prices.
For example, this...
exquisite specimen.
(♫)
(SNARLS)
CHRIS: Cathy.
Bastard.
The last moments on Earth are the
most beautiful, don't you think?
The wonderful thing
about my products...
is that they know the
difference between ally...
and enemy.
(♫)
(SNARLING)
(SCREAMS)
(♫)
WOMAN: Congratulations!
MAN: Congratulations.
(ALL CLAPPING AND CHATTERING)
(PLANE ENGINE DRONING)
(GRUNTING)
(PEOPLE WAILING AND GROANING)
(♫)
No!
This is all for you, my dear.
My Sara.
AARON: Is that it?
Is that the virus that's
making everyone flip out?
Yes.
AARON: It keeps getting
worse and worse.
Attacks are happening
all over the place.
(WOMAN SCREAMING ON MONITOR)
Where'd you get this?
I haven't seen this
footage before.
It hasn't been released yet.
They don't want the
public to panic.
Are you kidding me?
There's been like 20 attacks
in the U.S. already.
The BSAA is working to keep
it under control, but...
But it'll just keep happening until
we find the cause and stop it. Right?
Exactly.
This is being done
intentionally.
If we can just find out
who's behind it...
Caramel Macchiato? Did you
remember the chocolate chips?
And the whipped cream on top.
Good boy.
That's dessert, not coffee.
You know that, right?
Your point?
Nothing. Nothing at all,
Professor Chambers.
REBECCA: The dead coming back to
life and being used as Bioweapons.
These insane corporations have caused
far too much tragedy in this country.
You think this is more
of the same, then?
I don't know.
Based on what's
happened before...
this time it feels different.
Someone new could be behind it.
AARON: Is that the vaccine simulation?
REBECCA: Mm-hm.
The infected are exhibiting
different traits this time around.
I'm attempting to suppress
the artificial virus...
because it seems to be the
base of the infection.
I saw the computational
chemistry system running.
- Are we making a test drug already?
- Of course.
Our technology's come so
far over the years...
making a sample doesn't
take that long.
Oh, by the way...
We got another delivery
of infected bodies.
A lot. More than 30.
Who's getting the samples?
The students are all out today.
And?
Oh, no. I'm postdoc.
I don't do that.
Hmm?
Fine. Anything you say,
Professor Chambers.
My hero.
What the...?
(ALARM BLARING)
(PEOPLE COUGHING)
(♫)
(GASPING)
(MAN GRUNTING)
(♫)
Aaron.
No.
(AARON YELLS THEN
REBECCA GASPING)
(AARON GRUNTING)
(GROWLS)
Why? Why now?
Here?
It's like it was planned.
(ZOMBIES SNARLING)
(♫)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(ZOMBIES SNARLING)
(CLATTERING)
(SNARLING)
(REBECCA SHRIEKING)
(GASPS)
(♫)
(GUNSHOT)
Rebecca.
- Chris?
- You all right?
(HELICOPTER WHIRRING
AND SIRENS WAILING)
CHRIS: It's been a while.
You should be wearing a
clean-suit or at least a mask.
Yeah, well...
How you doing?
I'm fine for now.
But shouldn't I
be in quarantine?
Look...
if the virus really was that
contagious, we'd all be dead already.
Besides, quarantine takes too
long, and I need you now.
So don't worry.
We'll get you to a hot shower,
and everything will be okay.
Same old Chris.
REPORTER 1: (ON TV) Police reports say
the suspects were armed terrorists.
So far, the number of dead
is reported to be over...
REPORTER 2: The mass killing in this
town outside of Chicago is under...
REPORTER 3: Outbreak of violence
claimed dozens of victims today.
Ontario's special task force has
declared the situation under control.
While that might be the official
statement on the incident...
(KNOCKING ON DOOR)
CHRIS: It's me.
That doesn't look
like you're resting.
A hot shower does wonders.
- Is that the data you took from the lab?
- Yes.
Now that we know the test
drug works as a vaccine...
we have to send this out
to other labs ASAP.
The faster we get this mass-produced,
the more lives we can save.
Yeah, maybe.
There's a reason you're
here, isn't there?
You're after someone.
Yeah, a man named Glenn Arias.
Who's that?
He took over Neo Umbrella
and Tricell's operations.
He's selling the weapons they created to
crime syndicates and countries at war.
He's a merchant of death...
using mercenaries and B.O.W.s
to do his dirty work.
And now...
the dead are rising again.
And you're sure
Arias is behind it?
Yes. After I found out that your research
was the most advanced in the world...
You hopped on a chopper
and came to see me.
Yes.
And after I saw how
trashed your lab was...
it looks like the bad guys
knew about your research too.
Oh... I reported our initial
findings to the WHO.
And then they sent it to
facilities all over the world...
that specialize in vaccines.
The leak could've come
from any of those places.
- Exactly.
- Arias wanted to disrupt your research.
And now that he's got your data,
he's even more dangerous.
I compared the new virus's DNA to
all the Bioweapons we have on file.
The sequence is extremely close
to the parasitic weapons...
used by the Los lluminados cult.
You think Arias might
be one of them?
Based on information I
have now, I'm not sure.
Looks like we should go
talk to a real expert.
Real expert?
I can't believe you can read
a book at a time like this.
Huh?
I guess it's one way
to pass the time.
Well, someone once said,
"Knowledge is power."
Francis Bacon.
It only takes one bullet
to bring your enemy down.
But with knowledge, you
can defeat all evil.
Hey, is it true what they say?
You switched from special
ops to science geek?
Mm-hm.
Man, the BSAA's chock-full of
people with weird Résumés.
Bet you were pretty
brainy to start with.
So Why'd you switch?
That's a story.
I used to be a Medic in the S.T.A.R.S.
Unit in Raccoon City.
I guess, in a way, I've always been
interested in Medical science.
Then one day, I decided to make it my
duty to stop people from abusing it.
I thought, "Here are these corporations,
run by scum, preying on the weak."
They're like a
disease on humanity.
I want to find a
cure, same as Chris.
The difference is, he uses his
brawn while I use my brain.
So brains and brawns working
together to save humanity.
What do you think
your chances are?
- What's that supposed to mean, Damian?
- Nothing.
It's just, like, uh, what if
this disease don't got no cure?
The assholes we're after,
they treat life and death...
like they shooting craps.
Bunch of dicks.
Hey, I just realized D.C.
and Damian...
aren't talking about
Breaking Bad for once.
- Hey, don't go there, Chris.
- That shit's ahead of its time.
It's a goddamn masterpiece.
(CHUCKLING)
(♫)
LEON: Careful you don't
scare the locals.
Your stealth's for shit.
It's a little early to be that
deep in the bottle, Leon.
Well, look who it is.
The BSAA's golden boy and Dr.
High Hopes.
- What the hell do you want?
- I got a job.
We need your help.
(LEON CHUCKLES)
I'm on vacation.
Let's talk about Los lluminados.
Remember the type of
B.O.W.s they were using?
That's so long ago,
I don't remember.
So, what? You just gonna sit around
here another week and do nothing?
I never make plans
that far ahead.
- Hey. Another bottle here.
- Cancel that.
LEON: Hey, who the hell do you...?
- Enough! All right?
What do you want, Redfield?
- What do you want, Leon?
- Heh.
- Cut the shit.
- Guys, come on.
Leon, I'm sorry to
interrupt your vacation...
but we wouldn't be here
if it wasn't serious.
We think you might have some
intel, and we need it now.
What intel?
(♫)
(INAUDIBLE DIALOGUE)
Second target confirmed.
ARIAS: She stays alive.
Finish the rest.
Copy that.
Look, this shit's
spreading fast and thick.
All of the researchers and staff
at my university were infected.
This again, huh?
It's like I'm stuck
in a goddamn loop.
CHRIS: What?
- What are you talking about?
You know that bomb
that went off in D.C.?
Well, it was my mission
to stop the terrorists.
We got to our
rendezvous point...
and some asshole ratted us out.
The bomb went off and
everyone on Metro SWAT...
my whole unit, gone.
I keep fighting...
and fighting, and fighting.
Instead of seeing an end to this
shit, it just keeps getting worse.
Is this what my life's
supposed to be?
(♫)
Fighting the living dead and
the bastards that make them?
What's the point of it all?
Look.
This is Glenn Arias,
an arms dealer.
His deals on the black
market are so shady...
they landed him on a certain
government's hit list.
A smart bomb was dropped
on his wedding.
He lost his family and his wife.
And now he's got a grudge.
After the attack, he
went underground...
but now he's back with B.O.W.s
and a score to settle.
Here's the kicker, he said his
products have targeting capabilities.
From what I've seen,
I believe him.
So you got an arms
dealer on one side...
and on the other...
a government dropping
bombs on weddings.
- Who's the bad guy here?
- Arias!
And it's our mission
to bring his ass down!
- Your mission, not mine!
- Goddamn it, Leon!
Stop! Leon.
With everything that's going on, you just
sit here and feel sorry for yourself.
And you? You're letting a
grudge get the better of you.
God.
- I cannot believe how alike you two are.
- What are you talking about?
You're acting like a couple
of selfish brats right now.
(♫)
The virus is right
under our noses.
Always has been.
I don't follow.
We don't need to look for some new virus
that Arias is infecting people with.
The virus is lying dormant
inside of everyone.
Even you.
What we need to find
is the trigger.
Something activates the latent virus
and only Arias knows what it is.
But until we find that out...
everyone, living and dead,
are his potential weapons.
If we don't figure
this out now...
there won't be little towns like this for
you to drink your sorrows away in...
ever again.
I created a vaccine. And I tried
it on myself and it works.
But until we find out how
Arias triggers the virus...
who knows if it'll work the
same for everyone else.
My blood holds the answers.
If I die, get this
to a lab you trust.
I can't imagine what you
two have been through.
But I know that neither one of
you are the type of person...
who would sit here and argue
while the world dies.
That's not who you are.
Or is it?
(DOOR OPENS THEN CLOSES)
(FAUCET RUNNING)
That wasn't very nice of me.
(TURNS OFF FAUCET)
(DOOR OPENS)
(♫)
(REBECCA GASPS)
(CHOKING)
MAN: Leon!
- Patricio!
- Wait, wait! Let me explain. Unh!
- Leon!
- That guy I was telling you about.
- The one that sold out my unit.
- You don't understand. Unh!
LEON: This is the guy.
- Please, stop.
BARTENDER: Hey! What do you...?
- Official business. It's okay.
- Leon, come on!
- What do you want?
Please. You're the only
one I know from the DSO.
It's my family. You've
got to save them.
What?
(♫)
My wife and my
daughter are in Spain.
An arms dealer is
getting paid...
by the surviving members
of Los lluminados...
to launch a large-scale
Bioterror attack.
I know too much. They're going
to kill me and my family.
Did you hear what he said?
It's our lucky day.
"Lucky"? Are you crazy?
- He's gonna lead us to our guy.
- What are you talking about?
- The name Glenn Arias ring a bell?
- How do you know?
I'm psychic.
I need your help. My family.
Let me get this straight.
You try and get me killed...
and now I'm supposed
to save your family?
Well, how about this?
You tell us what you know first,
and then we'll decide if we help.
(VEHICLE APPROACHING)
(♫)
Son of a bitch!
He was followed!
My family.
Please.
Save them.
Damn it.
Rebecca!
Target one down.
Target two secured.
(TRUCK ENGINE REVIVING)
D.C., they hit us at the hotel
and took Rebecca. Track them.
I know the big guy.
He's with Arias.
What's Arias want with Rebecca?
I don't know. I just
want to get her back.
There goes my vacation. Again.
(CELL PHONE RINGING)
WOMAN: Hi, honey, it's me.
Were you able to get the
man you said would help?
I'm so scared.
Selena misses her daddy.
- Patricio? Hello?
GIRL: Can I talk to Papa?
WOMAN: Patricio? Who is this?
GIRL: Can I talk to Papa? Please.
Where's Patricio? Put my
husband on the phone right...
(LINE DISCONNECTS)
There's a reason he gave
that to you before he died.
It might have the
answers we need in it.
We have Rebecca's laptop.
We have leads.
Look, man.
I need you.
(♫)
(INDISTINCT OVERLAPPING VOICES)
(GRUNTS)
(SNARLING)
I succeeded in
reanimating them...
but I haven't figured out how to keep
the bodies from rotting away yet.
Practice makes perfect.
Meet my guests.
My family and some of
my dearest friends.
Professor Rebecca Chambers.
Welcome.
I'm Glenn Arias.
I heard you found a cure
for my merchandise.
For someone so young,
you're quite brilliant.
A cure isn't the
only thing I found.
Really?
(♫)
Please, tell me more.
I figured out how the
latent virus is activated.
Animality Virus, Professor.
A-Virus, for short.
Your B.O.W.s can tell who
they're supposed to attack.
That's a good selling
point for a weapon.
Engineering them with that trait
must have been difficult for you.
But I know how you did it.
There are three
strains of the virus.
One infects them.
A second acts as a trigger.
The third gives you the option of
choosing who your target will be.
A sort of inactivation virus.
The vaccine.
Bring up the map again.
CHRIS: She must have thought
these outbreaks were related.
See how they're all concentrated
around the Great Lakes?
If what she said is true...
and this thing can lay
dormant inside people...
God knows how many are infected.
REBECCA: You mixed the base
virus in drinking water.
I'm impressed.
How did you figure it out?
I noticed a huge concentration of
outbreaks around the Great Lakes.
Which just so happens to be a
major source of drinking water.
But they weren't planned by you.
They happened by accident.
It seems under certain
rare conditions...
the latent virus can activate
without the trigger virus.
Speaking of, the trigger virus is
probably distributed through the air...
by a gas.
By themselves, these viruses
either have no potency...
or they run the risk of
activating on their own.
But when combined...
they become an effective,
controllable bioweapon.
Nicely done, Professor.
It's no wonder you
survived Raccoon City.
(♫)
If the trigger's airborne, it's harder
to control where it goes or who gets it.
So then Arias has to be
using some type of vaccine.
Uh-huh.
That's how he controls the
spread of an outbreak.
He vaccinates anyone he
doesn't want infected first.
Which makes for a more
accurate weapon. See?
You've done your
homework on the A-Virus.
So now what's next?
It wasn't hard for me to
engineer a test cure.
And now that I know it works, my
team has my research and my blood.
Your "merchandise,"
as you put it...
will soon be obsolete
on the marketplace.
I hate to say this, but your
research is incomplete.
If you had found the cure, you wouldn't
have been attacked after you took it.
But you were, weren't you?
Not that it matters.
No, you and your vaccine
will soon be out of time.
Tomorrow, the world will
be a different place.
LEON: Arias is planning
something big.
Patricio knew way
too much about it.
And that's why he was killed.
REBECCA: I know what happened.
They came to kill you...
but killed everyone
you loved instead.
It was your wedding day.
ARIAS: The day time
stopped for me.
That's Sara.
My wife.
(♫)
You look so much like her.
It's not a coincidence
that we met.
It's fate.
Wait.
Where are you going with this?
I'm redoing the wedding.
This time with you.
I'll rewrite the past.
Rebecca...
meet Sara.
We're going to be so happy.
(BOTH GRUNTING)
(ARIAS SOBBING)
On second thought...
I'm going to replace
your arm with Sara's.
Maybe that will change
your mind about me.
CHRIS: He's gonna use the
trigger virus on New York?
That's what it looks like.
He's out of his mind.
"If the outbreak is
deemed uncontrollable...
tanks labeled with a green A contain
the vaccine and are ready to deploy.
Location classified."
(♫)
All we have to do is find that stuff
and we can change everyone back.
Like flipping a safety switch.
But if you were Arias,
where would you keep it?
Someplace he can get to fast.
Someplace secure.
His hideout in New York.
CHRIS: I bet we'll find
Rebecca there too.
- We need to expedite the release.
MARIA: We're set for morning rush hour.
I have a feeling the BSAA
will be heading our way...
so we need that countermeasure.
You're planning another attack.
I'm planning our future.
Our time starts now.
- "Our"?
- Yes.
With the last of my
remaining friends...
we will begin our
new life together.
(KEYBOARD CLACKING)
MARIA: It's time.
Dad.
Wish me luck.
(♫)
(GRUNTING)
(COUGHING)
(GROWLS)
- Unh!
- Oh, my God.
Alex. Alex.
I'll call the ambulance.
(PEOPLE SCREAMING)
Not now, goddamn it.
(ALEX SNARLS AND WOMAN SCREAMS)
(♫)
Everybody get a dose
of Rebecca's vaccine?
Mm-hm.
CHRIS: Good.
What's the status on
the reinforcements?
BSAA and N.Y.P.D. SWAT are on
the ground in the thick of it.
The state police won't get
there for another three hours.
So that means we have to nab
Arias all by ourselves.
Fantastic.
Yo. The signal's getting worse.
LEON: They're using tanker
trucks to spray the virus.
He's not trying to turn
a couple thousand.
He's trying to turn them all.
We need to take out
those tankers.
Professor Chambers' research says
the virus can't handle heat.
It's got the same flash
point as gasoline.
Perfect. Let's light a
match, watch it burn.
I wish we could get to Rebecca first,
but the priority is those tankers.
So we got three things to do.
One, blow up the tankers.
Two, get Rebecca.
Three, grab the vaccine and
deploy it on the city.
- And grab Arias. Four things.
- Whatever you say, boss.
D.C., Nadia, you guys
work from the Osprey.
Roger that, C.
(♫)
Gifts from the BSAA.
They said that's the best
they can do for us for now.
(♫)
Dibs on the bike.
CHRIS: Once the tankers are down,
rendezvous at Arias' place.
We might have to put
Rebecca on hold...
- until we find that vaccine.
- Got it.
Well, you ready to rock?
Are you kidding?
Let's do this.
(THUMPING)
(♫)
(GROWLING)
(SCREAMING)
Damian! Shit.
Damn it.
Any ideas?
(GROWLING)
I'll lead the dogs away.
You go blow up some more tankers.
Good?
Yeah.
LEON: Here, boy. Come on!
(♫)
(HORN HONKING)
(GROWLING)
(WHIMPERS)
(REBECCA GRUNTING)
(DOOR OPENS)
(FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING)
This version of the trigger
virus is better than the last.
Stronger. Your
blood was the key.
Thank you so much.
Unfortunately, increasing
the toxicity means...
it can't be administered
via gas anymore.
So it's back to the old
needle, I'm afraid.
MY apologies.
If our simulations
were correct...
it should start working
in half an hour.
(GASPING)
(♫)
Three down. Going
for the next one.
(♫)
(GUNFIRE ON MONITOR)
ARIAS: (OVER PA) Nice to see
you again, Mr. Redfield.
Arias.
Thanks to Professor Chambers, we
made the virus much stronger.
If you can stick around for,
oh, another 20 minutes...
you'll see how strong.
I can't wait for you to meet
the new and improved Rebecca.
The question is...
do you have it in
you to kill her?
My army of the dead
will change...
the world for the better.
It will correct the imbalance
caused by recent wars.
If you stay alive long enough...
you can watch with me as my B.O.W.s
bring down the most powerful nations...
one by one.
You belong in a
nuthouse, asshole.
Unfortunately, I'm not crazy.
I want revenge.
(GRUNTING)
I'm hitting the reset
button on the world.
And my merchandise,
my B.O.W.s...
are the right tool for the job.
(GROANING)
- Leon.
- Sorry I'm late.
I had to take the stairs.
(ELEVATOR BELL DINGS)
(SNARLING)
(SIRENS WAILING IN DISTANCE)
(EXPLOSIONS IN DISTANCE)
(GUNFIRE IN DISTANCE)
Maybe this is what
I've always wanted.
A world in flames...
where only the dead remain.
(♫)
- Rebecca's running out of time.
- Then let's split up.
(DOCTOR YELLING)
(REBECCA GROANING)
CHRIS: Rebecca.
(CREATURE SNARLING)
(♫)
Aw...
(GROANING)
(METALLIC CLANG)
(SCREAMING)
You Okay?
Chris.
No, no, no. Wait, wait.
Where's the vaccine?
Tell me!
(GUNSHOTS THEN REBECCA SHRIEKS)
ARIAS: You just had
to try to save her.
You're so predictable, Chris.
That's your weakness.
(GUN CLICKS)
Shit.
(♫)
(BOTH GRUNTING)
(NECK CRACKS)
(♫)
(YELLS)
(SCREAMING)
Rebecca.
(GASPING)
You have to kill me.
No.
We'll find the vaccine.
Just hang on a little longer.
(GROANING)
(FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING)
Diego...
the final stage.
Unleash it.
(GRUNTS)
(♫)
(GROWLING)
(GRUNTING)
(ROARING)
(HEAVY FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING)
(♫)
Redfield.
(GROANING)
(ELEVATOR BELL DINGS)
(PANTING)
(GASPING)
Found you.
(♫)
(GROANING)
I'm going to spill
your guts all over.
(DIEGO LAUGHING)
Nadia!
(GROANING)
Diego!
(♫)
Shit.
(SCREAMS)
(LAUGHING)
(ENGINE REVIVING)
Catch.
(SCREAMS)
Bye-bye, asshole.
(♫)
(REBECCA GASPING)
(BEEPING)
Rebecca?
One more thing left to do.
So let's do it.
(♫)
(GRUNTING)
LEON: When I was a kid...
I never thought my life
would turn out this way.
REBECCA: And once again, we find
ourselves back where we started.
What do you mean?
We got the bad guys.
Hope we made the world
a little safer.
LEON: Hey, Chris.
Yeah?
How much longer can we
keep going on like this?
I don't know.
I never make plans
that far ahead.
(CHUCKLES)
(♫)
(FOOTSTEPS)
Translated by: Will Motomura
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org