Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
Â™ª Ran out of money
♪ She ran out of love
♪ What more can she say?
Â™ª "If you love me, baby
pay the rent"
♪ Don't throw stones
You don't know
♪ It's not what you say
It's what you do
♪ Don't throw your stones
Go ahead, sir.
Â™ª Twice as bad at work
♪ "If you love me
buy me a big TV
♪ "You good-for-nothing
lazy jerk"
No, no ifs,
ands and buts.
Â™ª It's not what you say
It's what you do
♪ Don't throw your stones
♪ Don't throw stones
You don't know
How about
some gold plastic?
You asshole.
What do you take me for?
For 100 bucks.
Get the fuck away from him.
Get off of him! Let go!
I think it's time
for you gentlemen to leave.
Yeah. It's all right.
We were just
having a little fun.
It's okay. Sorry.
Okay, Dalton.
I've always
wanted to try you.
I think I can take you.
Outside.
Okay.
So here we are.
Let's go.
Come on, hotshot.
Come on.
Let's do it.
Hey,
dirtball, where you going?
Moose lips, get back here.
You dickhead.
What are you guys,
the seven dwarves or something?
Â™ª It's not what you say
It's what you do
♪ Don't throw your stones
♪ Don't throw your stones ♪
Can I talk to
you for a minute?
The name's Dalton, right?
I don't know you.
My name is Tilghman,
Frank Tilghman.
I have a little club outside of
Kansas City called the Double Deuce.
It used to be a sweet deal.
Now, it's the kind of place
that they sweep up
the eyeballs after closing.
Anyway, I've come into
a little bit of money.
I'd like to make
a better life for myself.
I need somebody
to help me clean the place up.
I need the best.
Wade Garrett's the best.
Wade Garrett's getting old.
He's still the best.
I want you.
$5,000 up front,
$500 a night, cash.
You pay all medical expenses.
I can live with that.
I run the show completely.
When the job's done, I walk.
I've got your plane
ticket right here.
I don't fly.
Too dangerous.
- Well, when do I expect you?
- Don't. I'll get there.
Dalton, you all right?
Just a scratch.
By the way, Oscar,
Band Stand's all yours.
What's that supposed to mean?
I'm out of here.
Great.
You know, I thought you'd be
bigger.
Yo.
What do I look like? A valet?
Keep it, it's yours.
Â™ª Well, I'm so tired of crying
but I'm out on the road again
♪ I'm on the road again
♪ Said I'm so tired of crying
but I'm out on the road again
♪ I'm on the road again
Ladies!
All right, boy.
Hey, hotshot,
what's wrong
with Detroit cars?
...shitting me for.
Come on, let go.
Don't come back, peckerhead.
Bring on the real band.
Â™ª Take a tip from me
Baby, please
♪ Don't you cry no more
♪ But I ain't going
down that long
♪ Old lonesome road
all by myself ♪
You son of a bitch!
How many times did I tell you
not to cheat on me?
Yo, Steve.
Fuck 'em, they're brothers.
God damn it,
you're ripping my best fucking shirt.
You know,
I get off at 2:00 and
I'd just love to get you off
about a half an hour after that.
My God,
you're a put-together woman.
Ladies first, asshole.
Come over here, baby.
Come here and sit with us
for a little while.
Damn it!
He's making me damn mad.
Jesus, not here.
Follow me to the bathroom.
- I need a drink.
- Okay.
One, two, three, four...
- Vodka rocks.
- You got it, baby.
Hey, vodka rocks.
What do you say
you and me get nipple to nipple?
I can do that without you.
Get him out of here, now.
Come on, man.
Get your hands off me.
If you're not drinking,
you're out of here.
Hey,
don't let him bother you.
Morgan was born an asshole
and just grew bigger.
I'm Carrie Ann.
If you need anything,
anything,
you just let me know.
You got a name?
Yeah.
Well, what is it?
Dalton.
Oh, my God.
Shit, I heard of you.
Carrie Ann!
What are you waiting for?
Christmas?
Move!
Shut up.
I'm going. Jesus Christ.
Â™ª No discouraging word
could be heard
♪ 'Cause I'm a confidence man
♪ Now, maybe Chicago
is where you're bound
♪ But love is a cheap perfume
It hangs around
♪ You roll the dice
♪ Now let the bet stand
Get him out of here.
Let's go, Sleeping Beauty.
Come on, move.
Come on.
What do you think
this is, a rest home?
Â™ª 'Cause I'm
a confidence man ♪
All right, y'all.
We'll be back in 10.
We got to drain
the main vein, man.
Stick around.
Hey, you're paid to play.
Play!
Thanks, man.
So, you play pretty good
for a blind white boy.
Yeah, and I
thought you'd be bigger.
Dalton, how you doing?
It's good to see you.
Same here, man.
The boys and I heard
you were coming into town.
Man, this toilet is worse than
the one that we worked in Dayton.
Really?
It's a mean scene
around here, man.
Blood on the floor in
this joint every night.
Hey,
Hank, you know who that is?
- Who?
- Dalton.
Â™ª Wanna tell him maybe
about Uncle John
♪ And then he got dizzy
but he had a lot of fun
♪ Oh, baby, yeah
♪ Yeah, baby
That guy at the end of the bar
is fucking Dalton, man.
He killed a guy once.
Ripped his throat right out.
Bullshit.
- What do you need, buddy?
- Coffee, black.
Yeah, all right.
Thanks, Bill.
Ever seen a better
pair of attitudes?
Fine, ain't they?
I'll tell you what.
For 20 bucks
you can kiss them.
Are you kidding?
$10 a kiss. Here and now.
Go ahead. Do it. Go on.
Come on. Come on.
$10 a kiss. Go ahead.
Hey buddy,
what are you doing?
Are you going to
kiss them or not?
I can't.
What do you mean, you can't?
I ain't got $20.
Why, you...
Shit.
Fight!
Break it up!
You son of a bitch!
Bastard!
Â™ª Having us some fun tonight
♪ Something going on
in the city
♪ Saw my baby comin' ♪
Fuck. Anybody got a mirror?
Shit.
Hey, how'd you like to tell us
what the fuck's going on?
Are you gonna
help us out or not?
I'll let you know.
You know,
I heard you had balls
big enough to come
in a dump truck, but
you don't look
like much to me.
Opinions vary.
Cody.
Later.
All right, man.
You take care. See you guys.
So,
what about this song for me?
This Dalton character,
what's his story?
The story is, you fuck with him,
and he'll seal your fate.
Yeah?
So far,
he hasn't shown me shit.
She's a runner.
- These work?
- Sure do.
I'll take it.
Good morning.
You the one who's
got a room to rent?
Come on.
You honest?
Yes, sir.
You expect me
to believe that?
No, sir.
God damn it.
I swear, he does that
just to piss me off.
- Who does?
- Brad Wesley.
You like horses, do you?
If they like me.
You wouldn't
steal them, would you?
No, sir.
Calling me "sir" is like putting
an elevator in an outhouse.
Don't belong.
I'm Emmet.
I'm Dalton.
So, what do you think?
Well, I'll take it.
Must've been 20 people
look at that room this past year.
No phone, no television.
No conditioned air,
no tolerance for the fragrance of nature.
Nobody wanted it.
How come you do?
You're just too
persuasive for me, I guess.
It ain't the money, you understand,
but if I don't charge you something
the Presbyterians around here
are likely to pray for my ruination.
How's $100 a month strike you?
Fine.
You can afford that much?
If it keeps you
in the good graces of the church.
Ain't it peculiar how money
seems to do that very thing?
Now this
is the new Double Deuce.
I put a lot of money
and time into this.
And to protect my investment,
I've hired
the best damn
cooler in the business.
From now on,
he's in charge of all the bar business.
What he says goes.
Dalton.
Morgan, you're out of here.
What the fuck
you talking about?
You don't have the right
temperament for the trade.
You asshole.
What am I supposed to do?
There's always barber college.
You're a dead man.
You're out, too.
We're selling booze here, not drugs.
Well, thank you.
Anybody else here dealing?
I'm telling you straight.
It's my way or the highway.
So anybody who wants
to walk, do it now.
All right.
People who really want to have a good
time won't come to a slaughterhouse.
And we've got entirely
too many troublemakers here.
Too many 40-year-old adolescents,
felons, power drinkers
and trustees of
modern chemistry.
It's going to change.
Man, that sure sounds good.
But a lot of the guys who come
in here, we can't handle one on one.
Even two on one.
Don't worry about it.
All you have to do
is follow three simple rules.
One, never
underestimate your opponent.
Expect the unexpected.
Two, take it outside.
Never start
anything inside the bar
unless it's absolutely necessary.
And three,
be nice.
Come on.
If somebody gets in your face and calls
you a cocksucker, I want you to be nice.
Okay.
Ask him to walk.
Be nice.
If he won't walk, walk him.
But be nice.
If you can't walk him,
one of the others will help you,
and you'll both be nice.
I want you to
remember that it's a job.
It's nothing personal.
Uh-huh.
Being called
a cocksucker isn't personal?
No.
It's two nouns combined
to elicit a prescribed response.
What if somebody calls
my mama a whore?
Is she?
I want you to be nice
until it's time to not be nice.
Well, how are we supposed
to know when that is?
You won't. I'll let you know.
You are the bouncers.
I am the cooler.
All you have to do
is watch my back and each other's
and take out the trash.
One, two, three...
♪ 737 coming out of the sky
♪ Won't you take me down
to Memphis on a midnight ride
♪ I want to move
♪ Yeah, traveling band
♪ Yeah
♪ Well, I'm flying
across the land Trying to get a hand
♪ Playing in a traveling band
This is a Sears credit card.
Beverly, Agnes.
Hi, Steve.
It's okay.
They're friends of mine.
- But Dalton said...
- It's okay. Trust me. Right this way.
Â™ª Well, I'm flying
across the land Trying to get a hand
- Leaded or unleaded?
- Leaded.
Hank!
Come on, darling.
Pal, do me a favor, and get her
down off there. What do you say?
I say, let her dance.
Come on, baby!
Hey,
look, pal, we don't want...
Come on, motherfucker.
Stand back.
Come on.
Come on, motherfucker.
Escort this gentleman to the door.
Did you see that shit?
- That's Dalton.
Â™ª Well, I'm flying
across the land Trying to get a hand
♪ Playing in
a traveling band ♪
Who is that guy?
He's good.
He's real good.
The name is Dalton.
Yeah.
You're gonna be my regular
Saturday-night thing, baby.
Yeah.
I've been thinking about you.
Yo, Steve.
You're history.
But I'm on my break.
Stay on it.
Shit.
You were hot that last set.
Yeah,
we were good, weren't we?
You got quite
a little enterprise going here.
What?
You go through
a bottle every 30 minutes.
You're skimming the till for six
shots a bottle, on drafts, one every ten.
I figure he's costing you
about $150 a night.
So?
So,
consider it severance pay.
Take the train.
I didn't hear you say that.
Well, I'm saying it now.
You sure?
Get out.
Well, it was a good night.
Nobody died.
It'll get worse
before it gets better.
Â™ª Blue Monday
Ah, it's blue Monday
♪ Got to work,
rather sleep all day
♪ Here come Tuesday
Poor hard Tuesday
♪ I'm so tired
Ain't got no time to play
♪ Here come Wednesday
I plead to myself
♪ My gal calls
Gotta tell her that I'm out
♪ 'Cause Thursday is
a hard workin' day
♪ And Friday I get my pay
♪ Saturday morning
Oh, Saturday morning
♪ All my tiredness
has gone away
I love this guy.
- Isn't he cute?
- Darling.
Â™ª ...and my honey
♪ And I'm out
on the street to play ♪
Dalton!
Hey, Dalton!
No.
Dalton!
Morning.
I brought you some breakfast.
Shit.
How'd you find me?
Oh, I, uh... It wasn't too hard.
I mean, you know...
What did you do
there last night?
What do you mean?
You fired the bartender, Pat.
He was skimming.
You should not have
done that, Dalton.
Why is that?
You just shouldn't have,
that's all.
Here you go.
Breakfast.
Thank you.
Oh, my God.
What is the joke?
There's no joke.
I just think
I'm looking at a dead man, though.
It seems everywhere I go,
I hear that same joke.
Something tells me
you bring it on yourself.
Â™ª Oh, life could be a dream
♪ If I could take you up
to paradise up above
♪ If you would tell me
I'm the only one that you love
♪ Life could be a dream,
sweetheart
♪ Now every time I look at you
♪ Something is on my mind
♪ If you do what I want you to
♪ Baby, we'd be so fine
♪ Sh-boom sh-boom
♪ Ya-da-da Da-da-da
Da-da-da Da ♪
♪ Sh-boom ♪
A new windshield's gonna cost you
more than that old beater's worth.
My advice would be scrap her.
Well, I like her,
so order me one, would you?
It'll take a few days.
Aerial I can get you now.
Great.
You the boy from
the Double Deuce?
Yes, sir.
I kind of figured you'd be by.
You want to put in
a standing order now?
No, I'll pay as I go.
- Dalton.
- Red Webster.
How long are you
gonna be in town?
Not very long.
That's what I said 25 years ago.
Really?
What happened?
I got married to an ugly woman.
Don't ever do that.
It just takes
the energy right out of you.
She left me, though.
Found somebody
even uglier than she was.
That's life.
Who can explain it?
Oh, that's $5.
So, uh, why'd you stay on?
Oh, uh, I fell for the place.
Hello, Brad.
Red.
Brad Wesley.
Dalton.
He's working at the Double Deuce.
Oh, terrific. Hope you're
gonna clean that place up.
Bad element over there.
Well,
anything I can do for you...
Thanks, Red.
Well, Red,
beautiful day, isn't it?
Was.
Â™ª People preaching to me
about the life that I lead
♪ Saying it's unhealthy
running around at my speed ♪
Problem?
There's no problem.
Just a little mistake,
that's all.
What's that?
My job.
You don't get it, do you?
Why don't you explain it to me?
I'll explain it to you.
Hey, shut up, shithead.
Mr. Tilghman has changed his mind.
And that's all you
need to know, son.
No, I'm afraid I'm going to have
to know a bit more than that.
Mr. Tilghman may own this bar,
but the liquor he serves
is supplied to him
by Brad Wesley.
Pat McGurn is
in the employ of Mr. Wesley,
his uncle, not Mr. Tilghman.
You see, I'm staying,
and you're going.
- Really?
- That's right.
Sit down.
Come on, Dalton.
You and me right now.
Right now!
What's the matter,
you chicken dick?
What are you afraid of? Me?
Is that it, Dalton?
You scared to fight me?
You big, bad Dalton.
What do you want?
To kiss and make up?
Jesus Christ.
Stand up. Get him up.
Get up.
Get the fuck up.
You're out of here, pal.
- Hi.
Hi, I'm Dr. Clay.
Hi.
How'd this happen?
Natural causes.
Looks like a knife wound.
Like I said.
You're a bouncer.
Mmm-hmm. Double Deuce.
Nice place.
They send a lot of business my way.
I'm hoping to change that.
All by yourself?
Mr. Dalton,
you may add nine staples
to your dossier of 31 broken bones,
two bullet wounds,
nine puncture wounds
and four stainless-steel screws.
That's an estimate, of course.
I'll give you a local.
No, thank you.
Do you enjoy pain?
Pain don't hurt.
Most of my patients
would disagree with you.
Okay.
Do you always carry your
medical records around with you?
It saves time.
Your file says
you've got a degree from NYU.
What in?
Philosophy.
Any particular discipline?
No, not really. Um...
Man's search for faith.
That sort of shit.
Come up with any answers?
Not too many.
How's a guy like you
end up a bouncer?
Just lucky, I guess.
Dr. Golden,
please call the nurse's station in ICU.
Nice work.
Good, clean stitches.
Thank you.
Do you ever win a fight?
Nobody ever wins a fight.
There you go.
Thanks.
Listen, uh,
if, uh, you'd like to stop by
the Double Deuce sometime,
I'd buy you a of coffee,
if you...
Happen to be in the neighborhood?
For that line of work,
I thought you'd be bigger.
Gee, I've never
heard that before.
Did I explain it wrong?
- Is that it?
- No, boss, you didn't.
Pat's got
a weak constitution.
You boys know that.
That's why he's working as a bartender.
He's my only sister's son.
And if he doesn't
have me, who's he got?
And if I'm not there,
you're there.
I should have let you go, Jimmy.
One of you boys
owes me an apology.
Now, I leave it up
to you to decide
which one of you wants
to say, "I'm sorry."
- I'm sorry, boss.
I believe you, Tinker.
But you, O'Connor,
somehow I don't believe you.
You better try it again.
If there's one thing I can't stand,
it's a man who's untruthful.
I'm sorry, boss.
One thing that disgusts me is
a man who can't admit when he's wrong.
I swear to God,
boss, I'm sorry.
You disgust me.
You want to know why?
No, why, boss?
Because you're a bleeder.
You bleed too much.
You are a messy bleeder.
You're weak.
You got no endurance for pain.
Come on. Get up.
You'll be fine. Come on.
Well, help him up!
You're gonna be fine.
And you know why?
Because I like you.
Get this piece of shit
coward out of here.
Work ain't work
when you're having fun.
Life is good.
Jesus.
Red?
- Red?
- Yeah?
What happened?
Did you get robbed?
Every week.
So, what does he take?
- Who?
- Brad Wesley.
Ten percent, to start.
It's all legal like.
He formed the Jasper
Improvement Society.
All the businesses
in town belong to it.
Everybody pay?
Does a hobbyhorse
have a wooden dick?
Pour it on. Squirt it on.
Charge!
Come back here, you jarhead.
Take it easy, Rambo. I know you want
to save the world from the commies,
but you're gonna have to do
it from down here, man.
Squirt him.
- Hose him down.
- Cool him off.
Let's get him.
Garrett!
Yo.
Some guy, name of Dalton.
What's going on, mijo?
Hey. How you doing, buddy?
Shit. Hell, kid.
I'm in hog heaven.
If I was doing any better,
I couldn't live with myself. How 'bout you?
I'm all right.
By God, you ought to be,
all that money you're making, right?
What's going on down in Jasper?
You know.
New town, same story.
Um, listen,
you ever heard of a guy
named Brad Wesley?
No, can't say that I have.
You having trouble?
Nothing I'm not used to.
But it's amazing what
you can get used to.
Tell me about it.
This place has a sign
hanging over the urinal, says,
"Don't eat the big white mint."
Stay cool, kid.
- Right.
- Got to go.
I'll see you later.
Â™ª Ooh, I don't wanna lose
this good thing
♪ That I've got
♪ 'Cause if I did
♪ I would surely
♪ Surely lose a lot
♪ For your love
is better
Why won't you look me
in the eye, Dalton?
I'm shy.
Would you be shocked
if I said, "Let's go
to my place and fuck"?
It ain't gonna kill you.
You know,
you might even like it.
Say good night, Denise.
Let go.
Â™ª Lightning
♪ The way you love me
is frightening
♪ I think I better
knock on wood
I didn't know she could sing.
Right boot.
Got it.
Sorry, we're closed.
Then what are all
these people doing here?
Drinking and
having a good time.
That's why we're here.
You're too stupid
to have a good time.
Go, Dalton. Kick his ass.
All right, yeah.
Son of a bitch!
Give me the biggest
guy in the world,
you smash his knee,
he'll drop like a stone.
Damn good fight.
- Hi.
So, you looking for somebody?
You.
Are you always
better than they are?
Pretty much.
Never been put down?
No.
Not really.
How do you explain that?
The ones who go looking for
trouble are not much of a problem
to someone who's
ready for them.
I suspect it's
always been that way.
Somebody has to do it.
Somebody's got to
pay somebody to do it.
Might as well be you.
I better take you home.
If I keep talking you're going
to go off thinking I'm a nice guy.
I know you're not a nice guy.
Pretty soon I'm gonna have to
start charging that bum rent.
Tonight's rent.
Your fan club?
They are devoted.
You live some
kind of life, Dalton.
Too ugly for you.
I didn't say that.
- See you.
- Bye.
We've been looking
all over for you.
Mr. Wesley wants to see you.
Let's go.
After you.
Â™ª I want to know
just one thing
♪ This is the way I feel
♪ I'm not pretending ♪
Hey, Dalton.
Have a Bloody Mary?
Some breakfast?
No, thank you.
Well, suit yourself.
Will you shut that shit off?
I can't listen to that crap.
It's got no heart.
My grandfather.
Looks like an important man.
He was an asshole.
But you,
you're a smart boy,
aren't you, Dalton?
You're just not too realistic.
Christ, I'm just like you.
I came up the hard way
from the streets of Chicago.
You know, when I came to this
town after Korea, there was nothing.
I brought the mall here.
I got the 7-11,
I got the Photomat here.
Christ, JC Penney is coming
here because of me.
You ask anybody,
they'll tell you.
You've gotten rich
off of the people in this town.
You bet your ass I have.
And I'm gonna get richer.
I believe we all have
a purpose on this earth.
A destiny. I have
a faith in that destiny.
It tells me to gather
unto me what is mine.
But Christ, you get
paid for beating people up.
Tell me you don't love it.
Of course you do.
You wouldn't be
human if you didn't.
I have a cousin in Memphis.
Tells me you
killed a man down there.
Tells me you said it was
self-defense at the trial.
But you and I know
that isn't so, don't we?
Relax.
Tell me,
if I owned a bar and
wanted to clean it up,
how much would it take
to get you to come work for me?
There's no amount of money.
Â™ª Keep your eyes on the road
♪ Your hands upon the wheel
Hey, we're here.
Â™ª The back of the roadhouse
♪ They got some bungalows
♪ Yeah
The back of the roadhouse
♪ They got some bungalows
♪ And that's for the people
who like to get down slow
♪ Let it roll, baby, roll
Thanks.
Â™ª Let it roll
♪ All night long ♪
Good to see you.
Ernie, what's the story?
Whiskey's running low.
I finally get this
place just the way I want it,
and now we're running out of booze.
I've called every supplier I know.
Why won't they deliver?
Wesley.
Ernie, give me the phone.
I'll take care of it.
Hi.
I hear you're
the new marshal in town.
You heard wrong.
Uh-oh.
Dig a hole.
This is your place?
Up there.
It's quiet, and the horses let
me know if anybody comes around.
I love it.
Â™ª ...arms of mine
♪ They are lonely
♪ Lonely and feeling blue
I saw your picture in
Red Webster's place.
He's my uncle.
Nice old guy.
Yeah.
He raised me
after my parents died.
That's why I came back here.
Now we take care of each other.
So, how come you
never got married?
I did.
What happened?
Didn't work.
Why?
Guess I picked the wrong guy.
Â™ª These arms of mine
♪ They are burning
♪ Yearning from wanting you
♪ And if you
♪ Would let them hold you
♪ Oh, how grateful I will be
♪ These arms of mine
♪ They are burning
♪ Burning from wanting you
♪ These arms of mine
♪ They are wanting
♪ Wanting to hold you
♪ And if you
♪ Would let them hold you
♪ Oh, how grateful I will be
♪ Come on, come on baby
♪ Just be my little woman
♪ Just be my lover
♪ I need me somebody
♪ Someone to treat me right
♪ I need
your woman's loving arms
♪ To hold me tight
♪ And I need
your tender lips ♪
Mmm.
Little Rock.
You're going to have a lot of
pain when you get older, Dalton.
You could be crippled
if you don't slow down.
Yeah, that's what they say.
You already know that?
No, I just said,
"That's what they say."
Where are you
going to go from here?
I don't know.
You could stay, Dalton,
if you wanted to.
I don't think so.
Hang on!
You got a woman
up there with you?
That's right.
Don't give me no lip, Lord.
Where'd she get to?
She'll be back.
If you're smart,
you'd pitch your tent.
Sometimes I'm not as smart
as I'd like to be.
You never know, son. Maybe she'll
be smart enough for both of you.
Thanks, Ernie.
- Hi, Dal.
- Hi, honey.
Hey, there he is.
- What's up?
- What do you say?
Hey, Cody.
Hey, bro.
What's going down?
Not too much.
That's not what I hear.
The word is, you've been
spending time with Elizabeth Clay.
So?
You know who had a thing
for Elizabeth Clay?
Brad Wesley.
As I hear it,
she left town and he went nuts.
It's a small town.
And I don't...
Dalton!
The truck's here.
Okay.
Of course,
that's just the word.
- Thanks.
- No problem.
The Double Douche.
Hey!
Put them back.
This bar is closed for business.
It's okay, Jim. Take a break.
Can I buy you guys a drink?
Guess not.
You got a skinny little runt
named Dalton working here?
He's out the back.
I know you.
Pour me a beer, will you?
I'll be back.
How do you like that,
kung fu?
How's it going, mijo?
Mind your own business, dad.
Do you want to fight,
dickless?
I sure ain't gonna
show you my dick.
Shit!
Damn, that hurts, doesn't it?
Hey,
there's a fight out back.
I had it under control.
Yeah, I knew that.
Glad to see you.
Good to see you.
Who is that guy?
Gentlemen, Wade Garrett.
Holy shit.
Exactly right.
Morgan, nice to see you.
Where in the fuck
are we going now?
I got somebody I want you to meet.
Uh-oh.
I thought you said
you were all right.
I'm fine.
I fucking knew it!
Hi.
Hey.
1975, Albuquerque.
Got blindsided by
a bottle of Jack Daniels.
Fucking around somewhere where
I shouldn't have been at the time.
I was very drunk.
The kid here got
his head cracked.
You got the scar.
I'll show you a scar.
I'll show you one I'm real
sentimental about, Doc.
A woman?
Boy, was she.
God, I feel like dancing.
You like to dance, Doc?
Yeah.
What time is it?
Daytime.
Good, then some other place
will be open. Let's get out of here.
Take this lady someplace where
it's a little more romantic. Let's go.
He's serious.
- Come on.
- Well, we'd better go.
There you are.
Â™ª All my ex's
♪ Live in Texas ♪
Yee-haw!
Â™ª And Texas is a place
I'd dearly love to be
God, he's great coming out of
the gate, but not much for stamina.
Â™ª But all my ex's
live in Texas
♪ And that's why I hang my hat
in Tennessee
Is this the part where you tell
me what a great guy your friend is?
Not hardly.
This is the part where I tell you,
I want you for myself.
Uh, yo...
Whatever he's saying,
you can be fairly sure it's a lie.
Â™ª But I'm alive and well
in Tennessee ♪
Don't bet on it.
Thanks, Doc.
Excuse me, gentlemen.
That gal's got entirely too
many brains to have an ass like that.
You've got
your hands full, kid.
What's the matter?
You're still living
in the past, aren't you?
We're a long way from Memphis.
Memphis has nothing to do with it.
Bullshit.
That dog won't hunt.
I can't believe you're still
dragging that shit around with you.
It seems to me, you'd be a
little more philosophical about it
and cut it the fuck loose.
You know, that fucking c...
That girl never told you
she was married.
Did she?
And when a man sticks a gun in
your face, you got two choices.
You can die, or you can
kill the motherfucker.
Don't mean to
bust up the party or anything,
but my shift starts
in a couple of hours.
Yeah.
Thought I'd go home
and get a little sleep.
Aren't you guys tired?
Doc, I'll get all the sleep
I need when I'm dead.
Thanks for the dance.
Bye.
Hey, Dalton,
Red's place is on fire!
Oh, my God!
Come on, stay with me!
With a fire like that,
nothing they could do. Nothing.
Jack Daniels.
Thank you.
It's like a morgue in here.
Play something, Elvis!
Get those firemen in here.
I want to buy them a drink.
They risked their lives
to save a no-good,
faggot draft-dodger
like Red Webster.
Ask for a little contribution
to improve the town,
everybody digs deep,
except for him.
Of course you can dance, honey.
Elvis, play something with balls.
Showtime, guys.
Â™ª Gypsy woman told my mother
♪ 'Fore I was born
♪ She said you got
a boy child comin'
♪ He's goin' to be
a son of a gun
♪ Gonna make pretty women
jump and shout
♪ And the world gonna know
what's it all about
♪ You gotta know I'm here
Move it!
Gimme a little bit.
Â™ª Well, I'm
the hoochie-coochie man
♪ And everybody knows I'm here
♪ I got a black cat bone
♪ I got a mojo too
♪ I got a
John the Conquer root
♪ I'm gonna mess with you
I'm gonna make you
♪ Lead me by my hand
♪ Then the world will know
♪ I'm the hoochie-coochie man
♪ Everybody knows I'm here
♪ Hoochie-coochie man
♪ You better believe I'm here
If you're going to have a pet,
keep it on a leash.
You're right.
Jimmy.
Â™ª On the seventh hour
♪ Of the seventh day
♪ On the seventh month
♪ The seventh doctor said
♪ He said
he's born for good luck
♪ And that you see
♪ I've got $700, baby
♪ And don't you mess with me
♪ Because you know I'm here ♪
Can somebody get
a drink around here?
You!
Come on, old man.
All right, that's enough.
This isn't working out, Dalton.
Let's go, boys.
Your ass is mine, boy.
Same town, new story, pal.
Let's get a beer.
I've talked till I'm blue
in the face, God damn it.
We could salvage the place, Red.
We could build it back up.
I'll help you out.
Nope.
But you got insurance, don't you?
For 20 years,
I watched Wesley get richer,
while everybody around him
got poorer.
Can you prove he started the fire?
Who you going to prove it to?
He has the sheriff and
the police force in his pocket,
for Christ's sake.
I can call a friend in
Springfield who works for the FBI.
Are you going to
take the stand against him?
There's only one person
around here
you've got to prove anything to.
That's Wesley himself.
You scared him last night.
Brad Wesley, he's not afraid
of anything, right?
Last night, that son
of a bitch was afraid.
No, he wasn't.
Dalton, check this out.
Wesley wants to put
a little something down
on a new car.
You lost your faith, Strodenmire.
That's what it is.
It's made you an abuser.
Well, what are you
waiting for, Gary?
Drive through there!
No! No! No!
Hold it. Hold it. Hold it.
Oh, my God.
Yeah!
What the hell is
wrong with you, Brad?
Have you lost your mind?
He's a drifter, you know.
To see you wind up
with someone like that is a shame.
This has nothing to do with him.
Well...
You get him out of here, Elizabeth.
Because if you don't,
he's going down.
And I'm not going to lose
a second's sleep about it.
Strodenmire.
I never thought
you'd turn on me, too.
This is my town.
Don't you forget it.
Let's go, Jimmy.
You got insurance, don't you?
Hey, little amigo.
You're all fucked up,
aren't you?
Let's crank that thing up
and head down the road.
We can be gone by dawn.
Never see this place again.
You can leave anytime you want to.
Shit, kid.
Fuck.
You don't need this.
Don't tell me what I need.
If you want to go, go. Get the
fuck out of here and leave me alone.
Yeah, you're right.
I ought to stop
telling you what to do.
Maybe I ought to kick your ass.
No, we don't want to do this.
And I'll tell you something else.
You taught me as much
as I ever taught you.
I love you, mijo.
I'll see you.
Dalton.
Little late for
a house call, don't you think?
I came to talk to you.
No,
you came to tell me to leave.
I care about you, Dalton.
You don't know him.
Bullshit.
I know exactly
who Brad Wesley is.
I've seen his kind many times.
He keeps taking and taking
until somebody takes him.
It's obvious nobody in this
town can stand up to him.
But you can stop him.
Brad Wesley picked me.
And when he did, he fucked up.
I'm only good at one thing, Doc.
I never lose.
But what are you going to win?
Who's this for anyway?
Are you doing it for them?
I don't think so.
Do you think you're gonna
save these people from Brad Wesley?
Well, who's gonna
save them from you?
Emmet!
It's Dalton.
Are you all right?
I'd be fine if you'd get off of me.
Prepare to die.
You are such an asshole.
I used to fuck guys
like you in prison.
Damn, boy.
I thought you were good.
Go fuck yourself.
I'm gonna kill you
the old-fashioned way.
Wesley!
Fuck you!
Hello.
- Top of the morning to you.
Here's what's on for today.
Wade? Or Elizabeth?
What?
One of them dies.
Now, who will it be?
You are a sick man.
Well, I just have to flip a coin.
Hold on a second.
Wesley?
Dalton,
I'd sure like to tell you
how it turned out.
Wesley.
Garrett. Oh, my God.
Over here.
Are you all right?
There was only three of them.
They said I was lucky.
I got to find Doc.
Let's go.
Sit the fuck down.
Have a beer. I'll be back.
Hey.
Wesley wins, man.
We're out of here.
That a boy, mijo.
Where's Dr. Clay?
She's in X-ray.
Get your things.
We're out of here.
I'm not going anywhere with you.
Yes, you are.
Let's go. Now.
Forget it.
Doc,
the man is crazy.
And you're not?
Now, get out of here.
Yo.
Wake the fuck up.
We're out of here.
I said one beer, senor.
Remember that blonde? Whew.
She could suck-start a Harley.
There he is.
Get out of here!
Find that prick.
O'Connor?
Shit.
Tails again.
I hate this place.
Mr. Wesley!
You're made for each other.
I see you found
my trophy room, Dalton.
The only thing that's missing
is your ass.
What's this all about, anyway?
Your friend Wade?
One old man?
That's what I call
a mercy killing.
I took him out of his misery.
Now, you're not mad at me
about that, are you?
Hell, you took Jimmy.
He was in better shape.
Hell, you took all my boys.
Now, come on out, Dalton.
This town is big enough
for both of us.
Let's talk about this.
I thought it would be fun
to fight you.
I really did.
But now,
I just don't have the time.
No!
It's over!
This is our town,
and don't you forget it.
Brad, where are you?
They're in here, Sheriff.
All right, who's gonna tell
me what the hell happened here?
I didn't see nothing.
You see anything, Pete?
No, I didn't see anything.
You see anything, Red?
I didn't see nothing.
Not a thing.
You see anything, Tinker?
A polar bear fell on me.
Â™ª Look out across the fields
♪ See me returning
♪ Smoke is in your eyes
♪ You draw a smile
♪ From the fireplace where
my letters to you are burning
♪ You've had time to
think about it for a while
♪ Well, I've walked 200 miles
Look me over
♪ It's the end of the chase
and the moon is high
♪ It won't matter
who loves who
♪ You'll love me
or I'll love you
♪ When the night comes falling
♪ From the sky
♪ I can see through your walls
♪ I can tell
that you're hurting
♪ Sorrow covers you up
like a cape
♪ Only yesterday I know
that you've been flirting
♪ With disaster
Somehow managed to escape
♪ Well, I can't provide
for you no easy answers
♪ Who are you that
I should have to lie?
Â™ª You'll know
all about it, love
♪ It'll fit you like a glove
♪ When the night comes falling
♪ From the sky
♪ For all eternity
I think I will remember
♪ That icy wind that's howling
in your eye
♪ You will see me in your time
♪ In the wasteland
of your mind
♪ When the night comes falling
♪ From the sky
♪ From the sky ♪
-== [ www.OpenSubtitles.com ] ==-