[Music]
i told you not to come this far
i just wanted to see i remember a place
if we get stuck out here i'll kill you
would you relax
i know it's out here
do you love me do i love you baby
please do you have to ask
girl likes to hear it since when are you
one of those type of girls
hey look hey i'm just kidding around and
playing you know when you ask me a
question like that
it makes me think that you think
i don't love you so do you
come here
what's wrong nothing
i found it
[Applause]
[Music]
all right
i gotta go to the hey
take this
[Music]
alright
so
ah
[Music]
oh god
you have to do it
do it
dude goddammit right here do it
[Music]
so
i love you
[Music]
so she said baby is that what i think it
is
and i say yeah that is a certifiable
last snickers bar on the face of the
earth
so she says to me what i gotta do to get
some of that snickers bar baby
and i told her i said honey if you want
to get down with some nuts
and some chocolate you're gonna have to
get down with some nuts
some chocolate
hey hey you even listening to me
sorry i'm just i'm tired
i don't even know why we're here ah come
on you know why
man who told you about this [ __ ] a
friend of a friend
a friend of a friend as far as i'm
concerned this is a complete total
[ __ ] waste of time hmm
so you'd rather be back at base camp oh
we're gonna be back out here tonight
might as well get some shut eye
there where
right there
damn yeah see i told
day walker
one shot
you winged him
i said one shot
it must have been a crosswind
[Music]
for the hands king
what are you doing
kill it
what did you say
[ __ ] better call the sin
what's your name what's
your name i don't know you don't know
what you won't say
i don't know well what do you know
i know something's [ __ ] up it's been a
war
or something happened to the government
oh and your men were trying to kill me
mistaken identity and you're lucky they
didn't just what the hell's going on
you really don't know
how far back do you remember
[Music]
uh
get him some food all right some more
water
[Music]
okay
uh
[Music]
she's
foreign
is
[Music]
so it's classic amnesia
i'd appear so what would be the cause of
that
aside from the wounds inflicted upon his
capture that doesn't appear to be any
sign of
trauma or apparent head injury i'm
ruling on a stroke
but i can't rule out viral based
encephalitis or some sort of
disassociate of psychogenic
on the other hand if the cause
is viral then he could be one of those
we heard about
it's possible i i can't say for sure i
don't have the equipment here to confirm
a status
he does have some scarring previous
entries on his hand arm and torso
these all point to a viral cause
thank you
sorry for your loss
we all are kevin was a great man
[Applause]
i wanted to go out on patrol tonight
that's not a good idea all right we need
you strong
i want to kill as many of those [ __ ]
as i can
don't worry you'll get plenty of chances
all right we got enough for two four
days max
depending on the intensity of the attack
if we get another one like last night
maybe even less
i want to thank those of you who are
being careful with your ammo
we owe you a lot now i'm going to ask
you for even more then why would we
leave
we go further out in the desert and away
from all this
who can answer that what do we have here
that we all need
susan
and what else water right
we have a supply of fresh drinking water
we can go further inland we can go all
the way to the mountains
they won't get us there but we'll all
die just the same
y'all i'd be willing to bet that we'd
find water inland
when was the last time you saw ray
how many of you are willing to gamble
that will find
water this is insanity so we make a run
for the ammunition
great some of us die so we've got the
ammo
how much of it can we get back here and
how long is it going to last us i mean
come on
soon we'll be right back here in this
same spot again
it's a tough situation but until we find
something better
we have to stick together it's the only
chance we've got
all right let's move they're at the
perimeter let's move susan
get emily out of here
[Music]
i told you to stay behind
who's at the perimeter welcome to hell
so
here you come
[Music]
ready
lights out
[Music]
so
it's a big budge how many
[Applause]
[Music]
everybody ready everything
on my mind
[Music]
uh
quick get him off her
oh
[Music]
uh
alice what happened to them too many
just kept coming i took them with me
where are they
here drink this you need it
come on try and drink something
[Music]
what are you
is that really necessary yes it is
[ __ ] maybe i'm just not thirsty
drink you know the rules the first sign
of infection is hydrophobia
the virus is like rabies the infected
can't drink water
instead of water they drink blood given
the chance to rip your throat out
i'll tell you that i'll tell you come on
i'm fine
[ __ ] was gonna kill me yeah she does
things like that
whoa slow down sister i'll come with you
the hell you are what do i need to
gimbal you for i thought you might enjoy
the company
anyway you never know i might come in
[Music]
handy
go go
[Music]
god damn it don't you listen to orders
all right this guy's supposed to stay at
camp he probably saved your life
yeah well it's not worth it i don't you
know who he is
what he is you risked our future our
chance at even having a future by
bringing him out here
what are you talking about here what are
you talking about
before the cities fell there was this
rumor
that uh there were some people that were
immune to the virus
i think they got infected they got a
fever
they fell into a coma when they came out
of the coma the virus was gone
so we were trying to find some of those
people you know we thought maybe if we
got some other blood we could like
develop a serum a vaccine
that virus just exploded so fast
that's all we could do to survive
he infected controlled the cities and we
all fled out into the wasteland
so what are you saying you think that
that i might be
one of these immune people i don't know
but what i do know is that
the immune people when they woke up out
of their coma
they had amnesia where were you when you
woke up
i was on a lake i was
in a boat on a lake um small boat
rowboat i had no identification
nothing nothing on me it looked like
i've been said adrift
that there was food there was water
basic rations
they didn't last long and
the sun was unbearable so i swam ashore
and when i got ashore i started walking
and i walked and i walked
and then i ran into him
nice to meet you yeah pleasure's all
yours
emily go back
well back
emily get back
um i'd only be the bearer of bad news
but i think your camp's on fire
we got about 10 hours of daylight the
truck's filled with water but frankly
without more ammunition we're not going
to be able to make it through another
night
we'll get overrun what about hobbs
reservoir by the pass
it's not too far away enough i remember
the pumping stations work yeah we tried
that already the water's contaminated
what about the alabama hills near lone
pine i mean we overran them there before
we got here and we didn't have the
weapons we have now
and i know there's water there yeah
that's good but there might be other
groups there
if you need ammo i might know a place
somewhere i saw about 20 miles away
before i came here
there was a load of military vehicles
just abandoned
they're stripped there was something
else there was it's a processing plant
i think there'd be machine shops there
if we can find a lathe
we can make a bullet mold
but it's a start isn't it
[Music]
so
uh
kevin i know you're in there the new guy
dallas said he may be able to fix you
i'm not gonna give up on you you
understand
grass
[Music]
ah
what the hell is this
i'm sorry i couldn't do it
so you endanger all of our lives to
bring him here what would you do
i'd have pulled the trigger like you
said you did
all right look take emily back to camp
what are you gonna do
i'm gonna deal with it
but dallas don't look
you're going to need a really strong
sedative the strongest one we've got
talk to susan about that
if we get a serum we're going to need a
test subject
if you'll agree to that he can live if
not take your share of the supplies and
go that's the best i can do
good all right get em sedated we're
gonna leave in a half hour
he stays chained up just like that and i
want a muzzle on him
i'm not taking any chances
let's go
nothing
uh
it's all clear for now
all right first priority is get the high
ground all right
get the truck covered up get the solar
panels out but make sure they're not
exposed or they can't be seen by anyone
from a distance
any kind of trouble shoot up a flare if
we're not back by nightfall
don't come looking for us all right just
assume we got stuck
somewhere and we'll be back in the
morning you got it
we should stick together dallas
we've been over this
where we're going there's a much greater
chance of running into trouble
either from night runners or just
flat-out hostiles
we'd run a lower profile by ourselves
and we don't have to risk everybody for
this
just be careful hey
you too if you see somewhere that looks
like a clinic or a medical facility you
know what to get
centrifuge beakers cooler microscope
incubator
maybe they've got an infirmary the mine
or something that we'll keep an eye out
all right good luck thanks
[Music]
those things they're nocturnal them
right
they don't come out during the day
they're photosensitive
when they first get the virus they could
be out in the daylight
but it quickly becomes too painful
vampires
light doesn't kill them
so where do they go during the day
look i know what you get find them kill
them while they're vulnerable
exactly we tried that
[Music]
uh
okay
[Applause]
[Music]
uh
and
when the numbers were in our favor it
worked
but once the infections spread too
[ __ ] many of them
look if we can rearm ourselves
stabilize maybe we can find a place to
hold up
try and develop the serum i know it's a
long shot
it's the best we got
i don't like this i for one would rather
be here than where they're going
dallas knows what he's doing
where are we going they can't come with
us right now sweetie but they'll meet up
with us later
somebody woke up
when i don't know as soon as they can
i want to go with them
if i get sick will you burn me up
you're not going to get sick i'm here to
protect you okay
okay okay
so when you first found me
when you shot me that was because you
thought i was one of them what'd you
call them night runners
the infected yeah
that's right but you found me during the
day
and now you're saying they only come out
at night
maybe i didn't like the way that you
looked
no no it's uh we heard from another
group
that some of them can come out during
the day
day walkers [ __ ] i heard about them
from a guy who went into the city
he said he saw them in broad daylight
hordes of them
and it took all he could just to get out
maybe the virus mutated i don't know
i'm not a pathogen expert but why would
he make something like that up
until we get clear evidence otherwise we
operate based on what we
know stay out of the dark
stick together at night don't get bitten
we deal with what we know
and there's a few of them they're easy
to manage in case of night runners you
get a small number you can fend them off
pretty easy
you see a big bunch run they're like
locus
again a large group their behavior
changes
when they start collecting together they
get more
violent more aggressive it's off the
scale
the more than they are the worse it is
it's like they're different species
instead of an individual they act as one
and i've seen it a wave i've been on
death
and destruction every ounce of energy
used to feed kill
infect
where are they now it depends how recent
this attack was
they stripped the town of victims they
might be long gone
yeah but if it's recent you can bet that
they're still here
hiding in the dark
over there that looks like a mine
gold might have had to guess oh great
but mine you can stay in the car if you
want who's gonna have your back papa
smurf
i think so i'm here to whip some ass
[Applause]
[Music]
so
like that you know how to use that
i think i can figure it out
hey look i'm going to tell you this for
your benefit
when we go in there you got to be so
quiet
you can hear a mouse fart from 50 yards
away noise is not a good thing
um why do we want to be listening for
mouse fox
they sleep during the day after my sleep
during the day no
shh i'm not saying that they're in there
but if they are it's best to let
sleeping dogs lie
all right so there's dogs and mice in
there have you got a list now for the
dog farts as well
hey mary poppins do me a favor
shut the [ __ ] up all right
[Music]
so
shhh
what are we looking for anything that
can be used to make
bullets or be useful all right
there's no light there's a lot of good
scrap now let's take what we can carry
now
maybe we'll come back with the truck
there's tons of raw material here
[Music]
all right let's go
gotta get off this road what what is it
we're not alone we're
about four miles ahead heading this way
two vehicles did they spot us
you can count on that
maybe they didn't see us i love that
you're an optimist
bingo
dallas
perfect how are we going to power up
one step at a time
jerk let's go
we cannot run them but if we make it to
the hills we might be able to lose them
on foot
you mean abandon the vehicle to come
after us they'd have to the same it's
never gonna work
listen any of those yahoos come near us
i'll take them out got it i've dealt
with worse before
what's important right now is stay calm
[Music]
what the hell hey
all right look there's got to be another
way out of here yeah don't panic there
is i've seen one
downstairs ground level all right let's
[Music]
go
[Applause]
[Music]
yes
it's a shotgun it's nine millimeter
they're not gonna be too happy to make
it out of there alive well
you better see about getting this thing
running then yeah
[Music]
she's got a spare tank oh
[ __ ]
she's rigged to blow well can you disarm
it yeah i could if i would bomb squad
they're not going to be driving around
with this thing armed
there's got to be a kill switch trunk
[Music]
they're still coming
oh
man make those bullets put my name
on each and every one of them
i want them to know when you shoot them
that they got shot by jack
we can get you help all right all right
you
you you make us terrible
right
nick you're an owl i'll be right here
i'll be right here wait
wait
[Music]
what are you doing following protocol
he's not a zombie not yet jeez man
guys respect
[Music]
all right okay
we got to focus we still got to deal
with whoever locked us in here
[Music]
um
don't move
thorne how the hell did you get out here
man
you all right for your friends
it'd be nice to have you back at camp
we all thought you was dead
you can put that down now
[Music]
i'm sorry
you're not mad well that all depends
[Music]
hey hey hey
ain't no hard feelings for what happened
in there huh how we supposed to know it
was you
come on we're gonna get you back yeah
bit busy right now yeah
what is it i'm helping them
helping them yeah
you got some strange cargo
he's going of ours so you're gonna make
him a pet
that's not your [ __ ] business
i'm helping them that's all there is to
it hey
you didn't have to explain yourself to
me listen maybe we can help to make up
for this
uh misunderstanding
yeah all right we need am i
sure hey no problem
why don't we get that stuff back at camp
huh river will be happy to see you
it'll be dark soon come on
yeah why don't you just tell where the
camp is i'll drop by later on tonight
it's the same place as always why would
we move
listen i don't think i can let you leave
look why don't we go with you we'll help
your friends get back and then we'll go
see revere how's that
well why don't you just give us the ammo
we can see you back here tomorrow same
place same time
how about that what's wrong with you man
i gave them my word does that mean
anything to you
it's gonna be dark in about an hour all
right now susan and sylvia they'll
hunker down for the night they're good
at that
now look at them they look like good
samaritans do
so we don't want to lead them back to
our people
i say we go with them spend the night
we'll be on our way in the morning
are your people
they're not the ones in that armored
truck heading north on 395 are they
you've seen them no but i've seen the
truck
before we got here it was heading north
into the alabama hills with an entourage
on their tails
now you didn't have anything to do with
that did you
like i said it'll be dark soon
whatever happened to them it's suicide
to go out until morning
we are going after the truck you can
come with us stay here
do what you want we're going you're not
stopping us tell revere i'll see him
tomorrow
okay can't do it now okay
we got the truck
[Music]
look we didn't know they were with you
thorne how the [ __ ] were we supposed to
where are the people i don't know about
them they were gone
they abandoned the vehicle they're in
the hills somewhere
look come back with us and tomorrow
we'll help you look for them
if they keep their heads down overnight
they have a chance it's a small chance
i know but how the night runners cleaned
out this area
i would be surprised if there were too
many of them up there
if i find out you had anything to do
with that you and the bearded lady are
[ __ ] dead
we weren't even there we heard it on the
short wave they caught up to the truck
and it was empty
i swear
[Music]
all right listen up we want our truck
we know you have it we want it back
then you can have your people and we'll
be on our way
got it
you were invited here on good faith but
when someone steps into my house
pulling weapons they're gonna pay for it
thorne you of all people should know
that
it's late i'm tired just give us the
[ __ ] truck
i think we have a friend of yours
we can start with her and move to the
rest of your pals
if necessary
we've got enough c4 right to this thing
to take us all out
your server
that's one thing i like about a
delusional bastard like you
you somehow know how to keep it fun
you can have your people release them
good luck dawn you're gonna need it
there are too many of them i'm gonna
make it to the hills
where's dirk dirk didn't make it
let's get the hell out of here
come on
put it down
[Music]
shhh
you know a snake can only have one egg
i'm gonna [ __ ] it down we'll see you on
the other side
so what's the bare minimum we need to
make a serum we can test
to start basic medical equipment syringe
needles we have those already beyond
that
we need test tubes and a centrifuge with
that we can separate
antibodies from plasma so medical supply
cuff only work if it hasn't been looted
what about a school university
they've got labs haven't they deep
springs
it's in the valley beyond the white
mountains not a soul for a hundred miles
it's a farm and a research facility
we could set up and do the testing there
so
then we take everybody might be the only
place we keep everybody safe
what do they want we're stopping this
needs to end
[Music]
[Applause]
damn it we're never gonna be able to
take all of them on
[Music]
situation like this you got two
you're under your fight we don't run
ah
[Music]
get in
hang on
oh
[ __ ]
ah
oh my god
[Music]
look at me
we're gonna make it
hold on
[Music]
wow
i don't know
but he's going
just gonna find out if they're all right
we need like bolt cutters or saw
something i'm on it
emily
just look at me
ugh
where the bloody hell have you been
i was looking for you you were the only
thing i remembered
i don't see anything
i need to ask you a question
[Music]
have you got any boat cars
now i'm gonna need a new pair of pants
okay i'm going to bring him out of it
now
should be enough time to see if the
serum is effective
the photosensitive response is the first
test
should give us a clear indication if the
virus is active
you can take the gag off
the hell are you people
we are friends i'm nikata
hey he's got a drink first
[Music]
drink
the serum didn't work no it worked
we gave him the antibodies from thorns
blood
what are you saying
phone's not immune he's infected
but this is something different he's
conscious
sentient this is something we haven't
dealt with before
we heard from another group that some of
them can come out during the day
day walkers i heard about them from a
guy who went into the city
he said he saw them in broad daylight
and it took all he could just to get out
we weren't making a cure we're making a
contagion
what are you talking about
we were wrong you're not immune
you're carrying the virus
dirk was right day walker
hold on that son of a [ __ ] killed dirk
he's one of them calm down just hold
on
[Music]
did they bite you were you bitten
no
[Music]
you
ah
[Music]
look at me this was the only way
you have to help him there's nothing i
can do
come with me
what you are changes everything
if you want to make good if you want to
fix this
then you have to eliminate the virus
and that means anyone that's carrying it
either you do it or i will
you're [ __ ] nuts
we're leaving i'm try loverboy he's
coming with us
what are you talking about you're not
thinking of letting them go nobody's
leaving just you try and stop us
[ __ ] you
[Music]
i didn't want to die of old age anyway
can't go around back and head them on
what are you doing this is war
it's either us or them
if it has to be done i'll do it
i need cover
if any of the infected leaves the virus
[Music]
wins
we can go to the city there's people
there like us
survivors we'll be safe yeah it sounds
idyllic
yeah we can run around and scavenge
blood and tear people's throats out
it's not like that then what's it like
babe
tell me what is it like
[Music]
well it must be another way there is
another way status
what i don't want to fight dallas
i'm standing up
don't you
we can work this out dallas
ah
[Music]
hey
we're leaving now
[Music]
believe
stop stop
look
i don't know any people here right
whatever's going on here doesn't concern
me
let me go all right i believe
you will never see me again
he can't do that
why because i love you
[Music]
to change
take me down
[Music]
is
[Applause]
[Music]
pages
is
[Music]
you