Imagine an end to crime...
...an end to poverty.
Imagine 2 million good jobs
waiting to be filled.
Sounds like a dream, doesn't it?
Well, sometimes dreams come true.
Delta City.
For our children.
This is Media Break. You give us
three minutes, we'll give you the world.
Good evening, I'm Casey Wong.
Our top story tonight:
Motor City goes Japanese as the
Omni Consumer Products Corporation...
...ended months of speculation today
by announcing its takeover...
...by the multinational
Kanemitsu Corporation.
Come on, honey, hurry up with your
calculus. It's almost time for bed.
I'm watching Media Break.
- the first private corporation
to completely own and operate a major city.
Company spokesmen
express special interest...
...in the issues of urban resettlement...
...and a crime wave in Detroit that
many citizens are calling a war zone.
But as usual, OCP has an answer.
Meet the Rehabs, Urban
rehabilitation officers.
From the blazing fields
of the Amazon War...
...comes state-of-the-art
urban pacification.
We're here to help the people, augment the
police force and deal with the gang problem.
What about reports you're
actually evicting people...
...to make way for
construction of Delta City?
Nikko, you heard your mom.
Go on.
Oh, man.
- And the homeless?
- What a gyp.
Some buildings have to come down
before Delta can go up.
I won't deny we're serving
an eviction notice or two...
...but most of these people have already
taken their urine tests and placement exams.
They've got new jobs waiting for them.
We're just helping them
make the transition, that's all.
- We're cops, nothing more.
- Nothing more?
Well, we're not robots,
if that's what you mean.
Hey, Dad?
You're supposed to be asleep.
Is it true what the Tv said?
That it's a war zone outside?
Don't listen to what the Tv says.
This is your home, you hear me?
And you're safe here.
I'll buy that for a dollar!
Get out, get out, get out!
This neighborhood is the
property of omni Consumer Products.
- For God's sake, help us!
- That's what we're here for, ma'am.
Just get on the bus.
Where are they taking us, Dad?
What's happening?
Don't believe them! They'll throw us
into the streets to die like rats!
Nazi sons of bitches!
Shoot her if you must,
but get her out of here.
Yes, sir.
Let's go. Come on.
I think it's going rather well,
don't you?
Yes, sir.
Come on, I said, move! Move!
- Manandle an old lady, would you?
- Shut up!
- Move, move!
- Get up there!
I said, get up!
What are you doing down there?
Piece of slime!
Can you hear me?
I said, get up, you drunken cow!
Get back! The crane's gonna blow!
Listen to me, people!
These buses are going nowhere!
Stay here! Fight for your homes!
There is no silver lining!
Only corporate scumbags
who want to line their pockets!
Nikko! Nikko!
Mom! Mom! Dad!
Nikko! No! That's my baby!
Nikko, Nikko!
Mom! Dad! Dad!
Mom, Dad!
Mom!
Dad?!
You! Stay where you are!
Repeat: The rehabilitation
officers are here to assist you.
It's okay, it's okay.
You're with us now.
Is he gone?
Are we clear?
Clear!
Okay, let's do it.
Okay, Moreno.
Cover your ears.
Rock 'r roll.
All clear. Let's go.
Jesus!
- ED 209!
- He wasrt in the recon photo!
Freeze! You are trespassing
on police property.
Please surrender your weapons.
- What the hell?
- Is she crazy?
You have 20 seconds to comply.
- Hey, kid, come back here!
- You're gonna get us all killed!
What the hell is she doing?
You are in direct violation
of penal code 114, section 3.
I am authorized to use physical force.
You now have 10 seconds to comply.
You won't believe this.
He'll be loyal as a puppy.
You have five seconds.
Four seconds.
Three seconds.
You have one second to comply.
I am now authorized to...
...be loyal as a puppy.
Damn!
Will it work?
Stole it off a dead cop.
Holy shit! That's the police armory!
- They deleted the access signature.
- Let's get out of here!
They'll be a few minutes. Let's
figure out how to open that door!
Are you kidding me?
One-stop shopping.
- Let's go! Gotta get out of here!
- He's right. Let's ride.
- What are you, picking out drapes?
- Coming!
- Get that.
- Why?
It looks expensive.
Come on! Come on, let's go!
Drop your weapons now!
Do it! Drop them!
Freeze! You're trespassing
on police property.
Eat lead, suckers!
Nikko, get in! Come on!
What can I do for you?
Nobody move!
Everything in the register!
Now! Do it!
What's it like
being a rocket scientist?
All units, we have a B and E involving
police property, please respond.
Repeat, all units, we have a...
Hey, Donnelly, it's your turn.
- No way. We went last time.
- No, it's Lewis' turn.
Lewis, you're up.
Lewis! Lewis! Lewis!
Isn't anybody gonna arrest me,
or what?!
- Where's your friend Murphy?
- He's not big on doughnuts.
- I knew that.
All units, repeat,
that is a battered yellow van.
No plates.
Tracking shows southbound...
- That's a battered yellow van.
- No shit, Sherlock.
Moreno, company's coming!
Hold on. Here we go.
Unit 477 in pursuit,
eastbound, Esposito.
Watch it!
I'm watching it!
Jesus!
They're still on our tail.
Don't sweat it.
Hey, kid. Watch this.
Hold the champagne.
You stopped in the middle
of the street!
- That was my light!
- You idiot!
- Is everybody okay?
- Okay? What are you, a comedian?
I traded in a brand new SUX
for this classic. Now look at it!
It's garbage. It's going to the junkyard.
What is this, fellas? You give a broad
a badge and she gets delusions of gander.
It's "grandeur," dumbshit.
This new guy is making me nervous.
I don't think this is exactly a guy.
You think it's him?
Unit 477 to dispatch.
This is 477 to dispatch.
Come in, dispatch.
We could use some backup out here.
Hello, dispatch. Come in.
This is 477 to dispatch.
Lewis.
Splatterpunks.
Wait a second, what do you need
the shotgun for?
Shit, we're all gonna die.
- Sit tight, people. Backup's coming.
- Sit tight?
If it wasrt for you, I wouldn't
even be here, you dumb broad.
I'll make you a deal, tough guy.
You want to eat the tie, keep it up.
Take it easy. My brother's a cop.
477 to dispatch, code 3! We're low
on ammo and need immediate backup!
Right now!
Sergeant Reed.
I got Murphy's cruiser on the grid.
- He just turned around.
- He what?!
Murphy, this is Reed.
I have three other vehicles
en route to Lewis.
Murphy, continue pursuit! That is a
direct order! Do I make myself clear?
Murphy, are you listen...?
Police officer. No loitering.
You called for backup?
Thanks for dropping by, Murphy.
Are they gone?
I'm still scanning three.
Make that two.
Block it! Megazone invasion!
Pop a tranq, hypo-head.
Splatterville's ours.
Shoot him in the mouth.
Cyborg eats bullets, Jock.
Not tonight he don't.
Hit him in the mouth!
- Shut up!
- Do it! Do it!
Nice try, creeps.
Give me it!
You have the right to remain silent.
Down there.
Jesus, Murphy, are you okay?
I'm fine, Anne.
Thank you for asking.
Come on, come on!
Let's go! Everything
will be all right.
Get your damn hands off me!
Stupid kid.
- Come here. Come on.
- Would you forget the stupid kid already?!
Kanemitsu-san...
...I realize we've had setbacks...
...but we've done everything possible
to get Delta City back on schedule.
Gentlemen...
...you are now looking at a company...
...in transition.
Needless to say, this has resulted in
the implementation of certain...
...well...
...let's call them...
..."cutbacks."
But who can put a price tag
on a dream?
Our esteemed former chairman
had a dream.
He called it Delta City.
Knock it off, Johnson.
The great city of Detroit represents
an important precedent, gentlemen.
There's only one small problem.
It's turning into a war zone!
It's just a small resistance group.
There's no reason to believe they
pose a significant threat.
I'd consider...
...a deficit of 350 million dollars
a significant threat.
Wouldrt you?
- Fleck!
- Sir.
You're in charge of Security Concepts.
Where's that Robocop
we spent so much money on?
The police had a problem
with the unit. I'm dealing with it personally.
You do that.
Get him to the Rehab Team...
...and maybe we won't have to worry
about a "small resistance group."
Get the hell out of here, all of you!
You take your time.
And for God's sake, Fleck...
...try to get the police on our side.
What if I don't want
a robot on my team?
You've got 4 days, McDaggett.
If Cadillac Heights isn't cleared
for demolition Friday midnight...
...our loans will be called in.
OCP will be ruined.
We made a deal, didn't we, chum.
Oh, by the way...
...if you're just figuring out the
line between big business and war...
...is a little blurry...
...then you're further over the hill
than they say.
This is entrapment! My client was
visiting close friends in that motel.
Hey, buddy. Your client's friends...
...were a non-union video crew
and a German shepherd.
That's prejudicial.
Did the arresting officer
ask to see their union cards?
Come get this crap.
Will someone answer the damn phone?!
Metro West. No, ma'am,
we're not on strike.
You could have fooled me.
I'll deal with those looters myself.
Get me a baseball bat
with some nails in it.
How are you feeling?
I've been better.
To be honest, it looks like you just
made friends with a Mack truck.
I don't have many...
...friends.
Dr. Lazarus.
- You want to tell me what happened?
- Atlanta beat the Pistons last night.
- That's cute. I meant with glory boy.
- Oh, him.
He got shot to hell and set on fire.
You know what I'm talking about.
He disobeyed a direct order. Why?
- My real opinion?
- No, lie. Make up a story.
Well, Mr. Fleck...
...offhand...
...l'd say the only reason
he'd disobey an order is if...
...he didn't agree with it.
Excuse me?
He made a decision.
His friend was in trouble, he made
a judgment call. Cops do that.
Human cops. What do you mean,
"his friend"? It's a machine.
Look, if oCP just wanted a robot, why'd
they put Murphy in there in the first place?
Murphy's dead, sweetheart,
that's on record.
Mr. Fleck, this is Murphy!
What's left of his face,
his cerebrum, his cerebellum.
Human tissue that's still alive.
How can you interface human
and machine...
...then complain
when the human part makes a decision?
So not only did we get Murphy's
years of training...
...and his law-enforcement skills,
we also inerited...
...his memories, his feelings,
his emotional baggage?
Well, I'd call it his humanity,
but I don't think you know that word.
I see.
You talked me into it.
His emotions: Get rid of them.
Find their location and erase them.
If it wipes out his memory, too bad.
We could cut out
the appropriate circuits by...
...implanting a micro-neuro-barrier.
Do it.
I got news for you.
I don't give a shit how smart you are.
OCP owns the cops. That means they
own him, and they own your cute little ass.
Nobody owns me.
Fine.
We want him on the Rehab Team.
That means you make him predictable,
or look for a new job, sweet cheeks.
I think I'm in love.
What's going through your head?
That's his family.
Want me to install
the neuro-barrier, doctor?
No, I can do it.
I think I'd like to be alone with him,
if it's all right.
Alex, I thought
you'd never get home.
Don't let the fact that these people
are homeless sway you.
They're terrorists, pure and simple.
On the screens
are suspected rebel locations.
If these locations appear
on your regular beat, check it out.
Make sure you report
any unusual findings...
Hear what they did to Murphy?
Murphy.
Lewis, you want your body armor?
What? No, I'm off duty.
What's up, anyway?
Do you have family?
Yeah, I have a brother in Pittsburgh,
the one who never calls. You know that.
Robo, are you okay?
I'm fine.
And call me Murphy.
Murphy?
Step out of the building.
Stay right there.
We're police officers.
We don't want you.
We believe there are squatters in there.
Now step away from the door.
They're civilians.
They're just trying to stay warm!
Those people belong
in the nearest rehabilitation center.
Some are terrorists. Step away or you
will be cited for obstructing justice.
I'm not going to ask politely next time.
Step away from the door.
This is your final warning.
You are making a mistake.
- Back off, or there'll be trouble.
- Now you're talking, Murphy.
We're not budging. If you wanna get in,
you'll have to shoot through us.
I don't have a huge problem with that.
Cease fire!
Robocop.
Come on, come on, come on!
Come with us!
Cover me.
Some tough cop I am. Huh, partner?
I'm scared.
Don't be.
It won't hurt long.
Get them for me.
Promise me.
I promise.
Murphy.
Officer down.
Move it!
We don't have much time.
Nikko, let's go.
Come on. Come with us.
Is she crazy?
He's a cop! He's one of them!
He's on our side now.
She's right. You saw what he did.
You'll let a stupid kid
make our decisions?
- We're at war. We can use his help.
- Are you kidding me? Look at him!
He is totaled, man!
People, come on.
We don't have time for this shit.
He's right.
We should go.
Five-meter spread.
Search the perimeter.
Damn.
- We're tracking him, sir. He's moving.
- Impossible. The building is surrounded.
He's gone underground.
Find a manole.
We got a little held up.
Rats?
One or two.
Go on through.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Hey!
You guys!
Oh, man!
I told you it was a mistake to bring him.
I bet he weighs a ton.
Watch your step.
All right.
Clear the way.
- Get out of the way.
- Hold up your side.
He don't look good.
You wouldn't look so good either
if you took a grenade in your chest.
Tracking.
- Beacon.
- Tracking?
He'll lead them right to us!
Shut up, Coontz!
What's he talking about?
- Did he booby-trap the 8th Street entrance?
- Maybe.
Better get mobilized, folks.
They got a little too close
to home that time.
It's not won'th it.
It's not won'th this shit!
You better take
a real deep breath right now, Coontz.
Because if you don't think
it's won'th it...
...then you're nothing but excess baggage.
Do you hear me?!
You get it together, Coontz.
Cadillac Heights may not be much,
but it's our home.
It's all we got.
If you don't think our homes is won'th
it, then tell me what the hell is.
This is Bertha to Base op.
We're coming in.
Set an extra place.
We're bringing in a friend.
Incoming caller.
What do you want?
Nice work, dollface.
What you talking about?
You haven't heard?
You might want to turn on Media Break.
Tv on, channel 378.
Witness to the tragic shooting
was Rehab Commander, Paul McDaggett.
All I can say is it's a terrible loss
of a fine public servant.
It's hard to believe that she was
gunned down by her own partner.
An OCP spokesperson has confirmed...
...that Robocop has joined
the terrorist rebel forces.
He is heavily armed and should be
considered extremely dangerous.
Tv off.
Congratulations, sweet cheeks.
Now listen up. I want your legendary ass...
...and your corporate I.D. Card
in my office...
...by 7:00 a.m. Tomorrow. And maybe
you won't be brought up on charges.
Meantime, you might want to decide
whose side you're on.
Sleep tight.
- He what?
- Shot at Rehabs and went underground.
- There goes our P.R. Budget.
- Company line is he's gone renegade.
- How'd the CEo take it?
- How do you think?
Between me and you,
I think the CEo's losing it.
I mean, take a look around, will you?
It's the Fall of Rome around here.
It's Darwin time,
you know what I'm saying?
Survival of the least expendable.
Remember the old man.
Everyone's expendable.
It can't be that bad.
Honey, can you hear me?
Are you there?
Every corporation
goes through this sort of thing.
Oh, my God, what happened?
What's happening?
Arnott just went out the window.
- That's the fourth one this month.
- Chickenshit.
I'd eat a bullet myself.
Less showy.
The writing was on the wall
the minute we hopped...
...in the sack with that shitty
Kanemitsu corporation.
As I was saying...
...we have a warrant out
for Robocop's arrest.
If we can eliminate him, then we'll
find that the squatters are more...
...let's say, easily persuaded.
Fleck. A word with you, son.
I'm sorry for the intrusion, sir.
Anything Security Concepts can do?
Security Concepts can kiss
my freckled butt. You're fired.
You heard me!
You're fired. Get out of here.
Three days until disaster.
What the hell
will I tell my shareholders?
What about more Rehabs, sir?
We could recruit them
out of the Police Department.
It would be cheaper than mercenaries...
...and we could use the Metro West facility
as a staging area.
Give them a nominal raise
for an incentive.
You're a good man, Johnson.
I knew there was a reason
I made you a vice president.
Thank you, sir.
I really...
Heads up!
Come on, let's go. We're gonna be late!
Well?
Can you fix him?
This isn't a valve job on a Chevy.
I never worked
on a damn Robocop before.
- I can do the body work, but...
- Look...
...we gotta hang on to the Heights
for three more days.
- He can hold out till then, can't he?
- Are you listening to me?!
He's messed up.
We don't have the equipment.
Who the hell does?!
Lazarus.
Find doctor...
...Lazarus.
Who are you?
I'm friends with Robocop.
Well, he's not here. I'm sorry.
You don't believe me.
To tell you the truth,
I don't know what to believe anymore.
He had a message for you.
He said to thank you for not
taking his memories away.
Well, well, well.
Afraid you're a little late, pal.
You must be one of Kanemitsu's boys.
I'm impressed.
Trouble is...
...your boss...
...he kind of owns oCP.
And oCP's kind of on our shitlist
with a bullet!
So you want to know
where the rebels are?
You can tell your bosses
to kiss my ass!
A vehicle is approaching.
How you doing, Murphy?
I've been better.
- Give me a status scan.
- Organics intact.
Systems efficiency: 23 percent.
Looks like a direct hit to the heart.
We have to recalibrate
the pneumatic system.
Is he gonna die?
Not if I can help it.
Let's get everything hooked up
to the generator.
We've got work to do.
I'm going to unplug you
for a little while.
Don't worry,
everything's gonna be okay.
Here you go.
I got that heart you wanted.
I said a Nissan. That's a Kanemitsu.
Zack, we need that sealant! Zack!
Marie! Marie! Look!
Oh, shit.
Bring me that chest plate over here.
You wait, man.
You are gonna be so cherry.
Moreno, watch out for the...
What the hell are you doing?
I didn't know that thing was there!
- Don't yell at me!
- Well, don't do it.
Murphy.
It's you.
Alex, I thought you'd never get home.
Welcome home, Murphy.
I couldn't sleep.
How are you feeling?
My efficiency rate is 93 percent.
Anything above 90
is considered normal.
I heard Marie call you Murphy.
Is that your real name?
It was...
...before...
Before what?
So...
Now that you're better, will you stay?
Will you help us?
You know what Bertha says. If we hold
back the Rehabs for two more days...
...they can't make us move.
And they'll have to let my parents go.
We'll all be together like family again.
Your parents?
Murphy? You okay?
Your parents, you miss them?
Yeah.
But...
...you remember them.
Because...
...if you remember them...
...they're never really gone.
Hey, Murphy...
...l'm glad your new heart works.
I heard voices.
She should be in bed.
Could you leave her...
...just a moment?
Of course.
You gotta pay for that.
What are you, deaf?
Son of a...
That's not what we said.
It's not what we said
we were gonna do!
Bertha, you said
to relocate the weapons...
...but where do you want this thing?
Oh, my God.
How did you get this?
We stole it from the police depot. Why?
This looks like the exhaust
system from an F-27.
No. It's the prototype
for Robo's flight pack.
The funding ran out
before we got a chance to test it.
- How do you know so much about it?
- I designed it.
Well, looks like the odds
on the home team just went up.
What I've done
is programmed the command system...
...to take its cues from your hard drive.
I've also rigged it to work as
an auxiliary power unit.
So if you ever have a power drain
like yesterday...
...just interface with the flight pack
and recharge whether you fly or not.
Nikko, see those resistors over there?
Get them for me, will you?
Get them for me.
Promise me.
What's going on?
Excuse me.
Hey, where you going?
Unfinished business.
It's okay. He'll be back.
He needs us too.
Where's he going?
To keep a promise.
You got a Robocop.
You got an alien cop?
- Got a ghost cop?
- I don't have time for...
You got a vampire cop?
- Murphy.
- Good evening, Sergeant Reed.
Do you know there's a warrant
out for your arrest?
Yes.
I was just checking.
What can I do for you?
Please direct me
to the Rehab Staging Area.
It's down the hall.
You can't miss it.
Thank you.
You may want to call
the fire department.
- You got a light?
- Sure, man.
Allow me, scum.
Oh, shit.
Where's McDaggett?
That does not look like
a police station.
You're damn right
I'm not at the station.
If my spy hadrt warned me,
I'd be dead now.
I thought your damn ninja was
supposed to take care of Robocop.
That's the deal. I clear the area,
he keeps the robot off my back.
You have the device I sent you?
It hasn't come to that yet.
And it won't. Relax.
It is difficult for me to continue
our business relationship...
...when I don't know your methods.
You don't need to know my methods.
I said I'll clear the area
and I'll clear it.
Just get the robot cop off my back.
I understand you're willing to pay good
money to know where the rebel base is.
Yes, well...
...the money's good...
...if the tip's good.
The last tip saved your ass,
didn't it?
What do we have here?
You don't like men in uniform?
My dad lost his job.
I just need some money.
- We've got lots of money, honey.
- Don't.
- No!
- She said, "No."
Maybe you have a hearing problem?
Go home, young lady.
You are in violation of curfew.
Where's McDaggett?
Room 212.
Thank you.
I hope you are insured.
Elevator door sticks!
Don't.
I have a message from officer Lewis.
Stop!
Drive!
I said, drive, goddamn it, drive!
My time, my money. I told you
and won't tell you again, understand?
I must commandeer your vehicle
for police use.
What is your problem, sucker?
I mean, officer.
Cover me.
Commander!
What's the deal?
Where the hell is Robocop?
We could drive around
and listen for explosions.
Are you doing that?
I got tired of splicing wires,
so I put in a pulse tach decoder.
- Telemetric?
- No.
- Smart ass.
- I know you are, but what am I?
Here, let me try.
Thanks for the heart attack.
I believe I will go
and send out a recon team.
I got a better idea.
Why don't we just all have a seat.
And relax.
It'll all be over in a few minutes.
You son of a bitch.
Watch the language,
there's children present.
Drop it, Coontz.
I'm not going to ask twice.
What do you mean, "it'll all be over
in a few minutes"?
Get the kids out of here! Now!
Bertha!
Go.
- Got to get her.
- Go!
Come on, let's go! Come on!
Come on.
Come on! Get in! Come on!
Come on!
Okay, now go!
- Go on!
- No, it's happening again!
Don't let them take you away.
I said, go! Get out of here!
Where is he?
Go to hell.
Take her to headquarters.
I promise my men won't leave
a mark on you.
Sir. What about our friend Coontz?
If we'd let him live,
we'd have to have paid him.
We're talking about hundreds
of thousands of dollars in damage.
- Murphy can be rough on properties.
- Yeah. Well...
...every cent of it will be coming out
of your salaries.
Hey! You built him!
We're taking Cadillac Heights.
I'll need 50 of your men armed and in full
body armor in one hour. Johnson...
...tell the CEo the demolition crews will
have access at 0600 hours tomorrow.
Hey, we don't do that kind of work.
That was a direct order, sergeant.
Driving people out of their homes
is no work for a cop!
Now, sergeant.
Fifteen years on the force
is quite an investment.
Your job, your pension.
Maybe instead of worrying about these
squatters, think about your own family.
I am.
I'm thinking I have to go home
and face them.
You can't do this.
You are employees of oCP!
Now remember that.
You're jeopardizing
your retirement benefits!
Stop that man.
How would you and your friends
like to make some money?
- It's...
- Johnny...
- Rehab!
- Hurray!
Johnny Rehab action figures, parts
and accessories all sold separately.
Three nuns and five clergy are dead...
...in what is believed to be the latest
atrocity by the killer cyborg, Robocop.
The OCP claim the former police unit...
...is responsible for a spree
of terrorism...
...in the Cadillac Heights section
of Old Detroit.
I'm sorry, I can't even read this.
This is bullshit!
Are you buying this?
Are you kidding me? Robocop?
Marie.
Lousy sons of bitches!
- OCP bastards!
- Nobody is listening to you, sweetheart.
We are in position.
This is Big Stick. You have a green.
Arm and proceed to strike zone.
All teams, we have a green.
Hey, take it easy.
- So what now?
- What now?
- Game's over, Moreno. Just shut up.
- What about Bertha's plan?
Damn it! Bertha's dead!
I'm sorry.
Folks, in about 45 minutes...
...the Rehabs are coming
to blow you out of your neighborhood.
I want you to take your kids...
...and anybody who shouldn't be fighting
to the basement!
The rest of you are hereby deputized
by the Detroit Police Department.
It's time to show
how real cops kick ass.
Detroit Police! Identify yourself.
You are under arrest
for assaulting an officer.
And destruction of police property.
Quiet!
Hold your fire
until absolutely necessary.
Commander...
...Detroit Police are out there, sir.
They're fighting against us.
So? We have a schedule to keep.
We don't fire on police officers!
You're out of line, McDaggett.
I'm in charge here. I'm pulling the plug.
Sit down.
Have you gone war-wacky?
I said, sit down.
Good idea.
How are we getting out of here anyway?
How'd you get...? Never mind.
Is there a transmission dish outside?
Yeah, and I was just watching
the Media Break guy pick his nose.
Do you have your computer with you?
People of Detroit...
...this is an illegal broadcast.
It may be cut off at any time.
So listen to me.
OCP is lying to you.
They're destroying people's lives
for big business.
Those Rehabs you see on TV...
...they're mercenaries hired by OCP
to throw people out of their homes.
You've got to believe me.
I'm speaking for all the homeless
and jobless citizens of this city...
...and every city like it run by
heartless capitalist scumbags...
OCP doesn't care about people.
OCP cares about...
Your neighborhood is next
unless you fight back now.
Time's running out. OCP's the enemy.
I repeat. Time is running out.
OCP is the enemy.
Help us. Innocent people are dying.
- More ammo!
Zack's hit!
They're winning, aren't they, sergeant?
What in the name...?
Sir?
Splatter that, you sons of bitches!
Come in, Big Stick.
All right, Mr. Robocop.
Come and get me.
Get away from the door.
Think it over.
Oh, my God, Johnson,
our stock has dropped to nothing.
We're ruined.
How may I help you, officer?
By resisting arrest.
Don't count on it, chum.
Anyway, what's the charge?
The murder of Anne Lewis.
Dead or alive, you're coming with me.
McDaggett, you can have oCP.
It's all yours. Sayonara.
Where're you going?
You're gonna miss all the fun.
No flashy bravery, tin man.
Or the two cuties say, "Bye-bye."
What are you doing?
Stop them! Stop them!
Stupid fools!
Don't you know what you've done to us?!
Those androids are programmed
with a thermal fail-safe device.
You mean to self-destruct?
In 15 seconds,
everything within 20 yards...
...of where we're standing
will be atomized.
We're dead, you stupid slag.
Don't count on it, chum.
Hang on.
- Come on.
- Let me give you a hand.
Kanemitsu-san...
...I realize that it looks bad...
...but maybe our plans were
over-ambitious.
Let's start a skoshy bit smaller.
Let's gentrify this neighborhood.
Build strip malls.
Fast-food chains. Lots of popular
entertainment. What do you think?
- What did he say?
- You're fired.
I got to hand it to you.
What do they call you?
Murphy, is it?
My friends call me Murphy.
You call me...
...Robocop.