ANNOUNCER 1:
Ladies and gentlemen...
ANNOUNCER 2: We're in
Moscow in the Soviet Union,
and this promises to be the most
watched event in boxing history.
I must break you.
Throw your right!
ANNOUNCER 2: He just will not
let him out of that corner.
Rocky!
Rocky Balboa is
in serious trouble.
He's getting
killed out there.
Drago continuing to
punish Rocky Balboa.
TONY: No pain!
ROCKY: No pain.
No pain!
No pain.
ANNOUNCER 2: Rocky's
been hit with bombs.
Rocky's hurt!
Right hand from Drago sends Rocky
Balboa 15 feet across the ring.
And his head's down.
Come on, get up!
It's been
a one-sided fight so far.
And Drago throws a hard right
hand that stuns Rocky Balboa.
They might have to stop this
one before somebody gets killed.
Rocky taking punishment.
He is completely exhausted.
And Balboa goes down again
from a right hand.
Taking punch after punch.
Amazing willpower.
Rocky Balboa's taking Ivan
Drago's best punches so far.
He's cut
and he's bleeding.
PAULIE: All right,
what's happening out there?
I see three of him
out there.
Hit the one in the middle.
Right!
ANNOUNCER 2:
The Russian's cut!
Hit him!
Whoa! Get him! Yeah!
Go!
Hits the ground
like a wrestler.
It's a gutter war!
No holds barred in Moscow.
All your strength, all your
power, everything you've got!
Now, this is your
whole life here.
And a big right hand
by Rocky Balboa!
Rocky Balboa has
done the impossible!
Yeah!
ALL:
Rocky! Rocky! Rocky!
TONY: Man. I never saw nothing like it!
Came through like
the champ you are.
You did yourself and everybody
proud, especially Apollo.
ROCKY: Yo, Tony.
Yeah, what is it, baby?
What do you need?
Get Adrian.
Rocky?
How's everybody
doing out there?
Everybody...
Everything's okay.
What's wrong?
Remember when Mick said
when he was fighting,
sometimes he'd fight so hard
that he was thinking that
he broke something inside,
and he was gonna die,
and that's what he said, that's
when the angels was pulling on him.
Rocky, you're scaring me.
I don't know...
What's wrong?
Adrian, I can't...
Can't what?
I can't stop my
hands from shaking.
I never felt this thing.
You gotta see a doctor.
No, I...
Right away. Yeah!
No, I just wanna go home.
No.
You can see a doctor.
I'm just tired.
I just wanna go home, Mick.
And I'm just tired.
I just...
Okay.
I just... I just wanna go home, okay?
Adrian, where's the kid?
ADRIAN: I don't know.
I don't see the kid. Where's
the kid? Ain't he here?
Dad! Dad!
There he is! There he is!
Hey, slugger, how you doing?
Say hi to your mom over there. Hi, Mom!
Then I'm forgotten now?
Hi, Uncle Paulie.
Dad, how you feeling?
Well, I got a few new dents.
How you doing in school?
I made the honor roll.
You're beautiful! Home team!
Hi, I'm Sheila Downes,
airport security. Hi.
Welcome home.
If you'll follow me
there's a press
reception inside.
Rocky, how did you feel about
the Russian people in general?
You know, it was very
good. They was great people.
I mean, I didn't understand what
they was speaking all the time,
but I think I understood what
they was meaning, you know?
Mrs. Balboa, did you learn any Russian?
Did I learn...
Yeah, yeah,
she got fluent in vodka.
Hey, yo, Paulie...
Paulie.
Rocky, there are rumors of physical
complications after the fight.
Complications?
No, no,
those were rumors.
He's in perfect
physical condition.
Rocky. Rocky,
a question.
Recently the American Medical
Association recommended
that boxing be banned.
Yeah?
REPORTER: Do you agree
with the doctors?
Yeah, you know, absolutely.
I think that doctors
should never fight. No.
DUKE: That was a beautiful
answer, champ. That's right.
Doctors should
stay out of the ring.
Doctors should never fight.
They should stay out
of the ring forever.
Rocky Balboa,
the funniest champion ever.
America's own Rocky Balboa.
How are ya? How are ya?
George Washington Duke here,
promoter extraordinaire,
welcoming back Rocky Balboa,
champion of all the Americans
and all of the Russians.
Now, I would like to digress
from the questions a bit
and pose an interesting
proposition to the media.
Everyone in this city,
certainly in the world of sports,
knows my reputation
for promoting
some of
the finest extravaganzas...
I... What...
...in this country.
Well now,
with the press present,
I'd like to ask you,
Rocky Balboa...
Yeah?
...to be the flamboyant, rambunctious
sportsman we know you can be,
and give this man
here, Union Cane,
a chance to challenge you for the
heavyweight championship of the world.
Balboa, I want the opportunity
to take what you got.
Isn't this bad timing to
present a challenger, Duke?
The man just
got off the plane.
Timing is the essence of
life, gentlemen and ladies.
Now, what I have on this
paper is the largest guarantee
ever offered to
a champion on this planet!
I'm talking about a fantastic
international extravaganza,
to be held in Japan, called
"Letting It Go in Tokyo. "
People, ain't it incredible
that only in America
could people like us
rise from oppression,
rise from poverty, to join hands
in this international event?
Only in America!
Excuse me!
Excuse me.
My husband is retired.
He has nothing... He has
nothing more to prove.
Hey, wait a minute!
Wait a minute!
Hey, Rocky, don't you consider
this a public responsibility
to respond now
rather than later?
Respond to the people.
I mean, isn't this a
question of professionalism?
To talk about it now,
not later.
Mind if I heal first?
The whipping you got ain't nothing
like what I got here for you.
So, what in the hell
does this all mean?
No, that isn't enough.
We gotta hear about this now.
Gotta think about that.
So, anyway,
I wanna tell everybody that
the flight over was really nice.
Come on, guys.
We need more!
Adrian, you know,
if you weren't with me,
I never would
have done as good.
You're my Adrian... You're
always there, you know?
And my kid, having you is
like being born all over again.
Come on, what do you say?
Are you gonna retire or not?
Anyway, I'd like... Excuse
me. I'd like to go home now.
Are you gonna give us
something to write?
Thank you very much. I appreciate
it. REPORTER: What do you say?
No.
Don't worry. You'll
get him. You'll get him.
I know.
Really, it's great.
Yo, look at this place.
I swear, I ain't never
leaving this place again,
you know that?
I swear... Hey, would you like to dance?
How about a homecoming
dance with your old man?
No, don't be silly.
It's cold.
Come on. I'll warm you up, young lady.
Come on, have a dance. Hurry
up, the music's almost over.
Do you like the song?
ADRIAN: You should rest.
Yeah, I know.
I'm tired. Come on.
Yeah? Well, maybe I'll take you upstairs
and violate you
like a parking meter.
It'll cost you
a quarter.
Yo, Adrian!
Where'd you learn to
talk dirty like that?
Hey, Uncle Paulie, you notice
something strange about Dad?
He just took
a few hard shots.
I think you tell better
jokes than me, Adrian.
Yo, did I hear somebody
call for their old man?
Did you do this?
Hey, it's sleep time,
kid, okay?
Dad, did you know that your
bones grow three times as fast
during the night?
No, I didn't know that, but I
heard something like that once.
Is that me?
Excellent!
ROCKY JR.: Yeah,
that's you.
Now, is that me?
Yeah.
When we was fishing, right?
Yeah, that's when...
That's beautiful.
Look at the tent.
You know, the fish was a
lot bigger, if I recall.
Well, actually, that was a lot smaller.
Now, anyway, come on.
Hit the bed.
It's time for you to get
healthy and everything.
This is great,
how you do this.
I don't know where
you learned this.
It is something, how this
thing comes out of your fingers.
Oh, my God.
Who's this?
That's Madame Dupont,
my French teacher.
Really?
Yeah, she looks French, sure.
I wouldn't show this
to your mother,
'cause she don't
understand French too good.
God. Better cover
that one up.
Well, champ,
it's bedtime.
Hey, you know what?
I know some French talk.
Knock, knock.
Who's there?
Madame.
Madame who?
My damn foot's
caught in the door.
That's an old joke.
What do you want from me?
I'm trying. You know?
I don't know all the
good things, you know?
Hey, what's this?
What?
Look what I
found in your ear.
Russian money.
Money ears!
All right. Anyway, listen,
kid, you gotta get some sleep.
Dad?
Yeah?
Today when you said having me
was like being born again...
Yeah?
What did you mean?
Well, you know, when you come
up like I did, and you got like
three square meals of zero
a day, you know what I mean?
You got the A side of life
and the B side of life.
I'm, like, on the B side, but
you, you got all the breaks.
So, when I see you having all
these things that I didn't have,
I, like,
live through your eyes.
I enjoy it a little bit.
It's like having
it all over again.
That's nice.
Hey, look at my face.
Do I look like a raccoon?
A little bit.
Yeah, like Rocky Raccoon?
Yeah, a little bit.
No!
Yeah, you do a little.
Really?
Hey, if you think I look bad, you
ought to see the other guy's knuckles.
Anyway, yo, good night.
Okay, kid?
Night.
Dad?
Yo.
Glad you're home.
Thanks. I appreciate it.
And we'll play tomorrow,
okay?
Maybe you can show me
your English teacher.
She's pretty hot, too.
Nah!
Yeah.
Good night, kid.
ADRIAN: You deserve the
worst for what you did.
Paulie, it wasn't your
money. It was Rocky's money.
You gonna be hysterical?
You cost us everything.
That's what I need.
It was a mistake.
You think I thought this
all was gonna happen?
Don't you walk
away from me.
You just gave up
our life!
And you think it's
like some stupid thing?
Paulie! Paulie, do
you know what you did?
Do you know the
seriousness of what you did?
I understand it!
Do you?
Then answer me!
I understand
the whole freaking thing!
I understand it! Your
accountant's the crook, not me!
I did what I
thought was right.
So, now, don't blame me for nothing.
I want to murder the bum
worse than anybody.
Hey, Adrian,
what's wrong?
Look what you done now.
She's dumping
everything on me.
Come on, Paulie. Don't
turn this around on me.
Come on, what'd you do, Paulie?
He gave power...
Power of attorney to
our accountant. What?
Gave... I just didn't gave
anything to nobody, huh?
He sent a letter!
He says we're gonna be in Russia
a couple of months. He says,
"And I need Rocky
to sign a tax extension!"
Not an extension! That was
a power of attorney, Paulie!
He's the thief!
I need alcohol.
Rocky, on my eyes, I never
stole a freaking dime.
Adrian,
what's happening here?
It's gone.
What's gone?
The money.
Everything.
It's all gone.
LAWYER: The piece of paper
Paulie had you sign
wasn't a request for an
extension on your tax returns.
It was a blanket power of attorney
in favor of the accountant,
who was involved in some very
high-priced commercial real estate.
He thought he could flip
it quick, take his profit,
have your money back
before you knew it was gone.
And unfortunately for you
and everybody in this room,
his deals fell through
because the market dried up.
And you lost millions.
So, what are you saying? There
ain't nothing I can do about it?
I'm doing plenty. I've filed
eight criminal acts against him,
but you've got tremendous debt
payment on this property, Rocky.
You didn't pay your tax
returns in six years,
and the mortgage on your house
hasn't been paid in months.
Wait, we didn't have a mortgage.
Our house was fully paid for.
Don't take it from me.
Ask him.
Apparently not. There's nearly
$400,000 still outstanding.
The only thing you have
that's not encumbered
is a gymnasium that was
willed to your son
by a Mickey Goldmill
in 1982.
You can sell some things.
Remember those commercials you did?
You know, Paulie, I ain't
no commercial kind of guy.
I'm a fighter.
It's what I do for a living.
LAWYER: Nah, it's just as well.
We couldn't get any sponsors.
With the investigation
of the accountant,
out pops a criminal record
of Rocky's for assault
in connection
with loan sharking.
But that was a long time
ago. He didn't know what...
Why not a couple more fights?
With your
popularity right now,
you could be out of
this thing in no time.
No, he's retiring.
Rocko, fighting's the ticket.
I said he's retired!
Paulie, we're here
because of you!
I'm not taking
the heat for all this.
I thought I was
doing smart business.
You thought you
did smart business?
Hey, you...
Me?
What are you talking about me?
The accountant was your choice!
My choice? You should
have known he was a thief,
but you're never awake
because you live in this fairy-tale
world where the air don't move.
Paulie... You're like a
season that don't change!
Hey, you don't
talk to her like this.
I'm not no tomato
can you kick around!
Paulie, no!
Yeah!
You call Duke. You tell
him I'll fight Cane.
I don't care,
anywhere, anytime.
No, Rocky. LAWYER: If
that's what you want,
I'll get on it right away.
No. No.
Rocky, Rocky, please.
We can't go down like this. A couple
of fights, we're out of trouble, Adrian.
Yeah, but you said you wouldn't.
No, I didn't say anything.
Look, did we come
this far to lose it?
Well, you know, you
have to see a doctor.
Adrian, I don't need to see no doctor.
I need to get
a promoter.
Hey, you know, you gotta see a doctor.
If he says it's all right, I'll
support anything you wanna do.
I gotta fight, okay?
I got problems.
I gotta fight.
Will you do it for me?
All right, for you.
DOCTOR: Because of the continuous
violent blows to the head,
you've developed a condition
particular to boxers
called cavum
septum pellucidum,
which is a hole in the membrane
separating the ventricles.
The brain's surface neurons in this
area have also been traumatized.
Excuse me, Doctor.
Simply stated, Mr. Balboa,
it means that you've suffered
some damage to the brain.
ADRIAN:
How long until he recovers?
The effects
are irreversible.
I... Rocky,
you have to retire.
Adrian,
I don't want to retire.
You know, this ain't
the time to retire.
No, not in here,
not in no office.
I just fought the best fight of
my life. I just did that, you know,
and all I need
is a couple more.
No, Rocky, you suffered
severe brain trauma.
Well, he could be wrong.
Anybody could be wrong.
I don't think he is.
He ain't God. Look, Adrian,
only God ain't wrong.
Hey, Rocky,
this is what's good for you.
All I need is
a couple easy ones, right?
Not with the way it is. You
can't get licensed in any state.
He can't get
licensed anyway, Doctor?
That is correct.
Rocky,
do you love me?
Yeah, I love you.
Why you ask that?
Because if you
love somebody,
you live with them,
you live for them.
You don't gamble
with a life.
Rocky, I don't care
about the money. It's you.
That's all that matters.
Please. We'll be okay. We'll be fine.
No one's gotta know...
ADRIAN: Uh...
No one has to know,
doctor, right?
It'll be
strictly confidential.
Thank you.
AUCTIONEER: May we hear
our next bid, please?
Are you done?
Sold.
Moving along, ladies and
gentlemen, item number 46.
Hey, kid.
Bike's been sold.
Hey, bike's been sold.
Get off the bike. Come on.
We have an opening bid.
$25,000 is the bid.
Don't worry about it.
We've been down before.
I'll get it all back.
We just gotta stick together,
all right?
Home team.
Yeah, right.
AUCTIONEER: Sold.
Come on, you know,
Mickey used to say
a fight ain't over
till you heard the bell.
We ain't heard
a bell yet, have we?
Rocky Balboa's boxing gloves
from his first heavyweight fight.
Rocky?
Hey, it still fits.
Why you wearing
those clothes?
I was just going through some of
the stuff up there, and I found 'em,
and they feel kind of
comfortable, you know?
Well, I was looking all
over for you downstairs.
It's kind of
depressing.
Yeah, I know
what you mean.
What's this
doing in your ear?
What? Oh, God.
Remember these?
I... Yeah.
Go ahead.
You...
I remember when
you took them off.
That's right.
First time I ever
kissed you, remember?
Kiss me.
Adrian, I want to go out
for a little bit, you know?
Just take a little walk.
I just wanna
feel better, but...
Hey, could you talk to
the kid? 'Cause he's...
He's really taking
this hard, you know?
Sure.
Okay?
Where you going?
I thought I'd go to Andy's.
How you doing, Mick?
Slip the jab.
MICKEY: Slip the jab,
will ya?
Slip the jab!
That's right.
That's it.
Hey, I didn't
hear no bell!
ROCKY: Okay.
MICKEY:
All right. That's right.
Slip the jab.
That's it. Mentalize.
See that bum
in front of you.
You see yourself doing right,
and you do right.
That's pretty.
That's very pretty.
Time!
Come here, Rock. My God,
you're ready, ain't you?
And Apollo won't
know what hit him.
You're gonna roll over him like
a bulldozer, an Italian bulldozer.
You know, kid,
I know how you feel
about this fight
that's coming up.
Because
I was young once, too.
And I tell you something.
Well, if you wasn't here, I
probably wouldn't be alive today.
The fact that you're here
and doing as well
as you're doing gives me,
what do you call it, a
motivization to stay alive?
'Cause I think that
people die sometimes
when they don't
wanna live no more.
"Nature's smarter
than people think. "
And nature is smarter
than people think.
Little by little, we lose our
friends, we lose everything.
We keep losing and
losing till we say,
you know, "What the hell
am I living around here for?
"I got no reason to go on. "
But with you, kid, boy,
I got a reason to go on,
and I'm gonna stay alive, and
I will watch you make good.
"And I'll never leave you. "
And I'll never leave you
until that happens.
'Cause when I leave you, you'll
not only know how to fight,
you'll be able to take care of
yourself outside the ring, too.
Is that okay?
ROCKY: It's okay.
MICKEY: Okay.
Now, I got
a little gift for you.
Mick, you... Now, wait a
minute. Wait a minute now.
Wait a minute.
Really, I don't
need nothing.
Look at this. See that?
This is the favorite thing
that I have on this Earth,
and Rocky Marciano
give me that.
You know what it was?
His cufflink.
And now I'm
giving it to you.
And it is gonna be
like a...
Like an angel on
your shoulder, see?
If you ever get hurt, and you
feel that you're going down,
this little angel is
gonna whisper in your ear.
He's gonna say, "Get
up, you son of a bitch,
"'cause Mickey loves you. "
Okay?
Thanks, Mick.
All right.
I love you, too.
Go after 'em, kid.
Go after 'em.
Thanks.
You was the angel.
MICKEY: There it is.
What happened to
his other cufflink?
I don't know.
He only give me one.
He gave it to some bum.
Take you back Take
you back Take you back
Take you back
From the streets
Cometh a man
A fighter
Doin' the best that I can
To survive Yes, and it's
survival of the fittest
Strive for what is mine
The Lord is my witness
Many believe
in what they see
And I wonder
What do they see in me?
For a man,
he must walk alone
To grow
And to bring
his knowledge home
School of hard knocks
is my alma mater
Lady luck,
you know that I got her
Fame and fortune
never a concern
Don't worry about these.
All right.
Let's go, Paulie.
I really can't believe it.
This kid's taking this too good.
MAN: Need a hand, champ?
No, I got it.
Hey, Rock. It's good I
kept the place, right?
How you doing?
It saves money.
Yeah.
Hey, get back.
Right?
A little aluminum on the
front, hey, it's a winner.
Thank you.
WOMAN: Welcome back, Rocky!
We missed ya!
It's only... It's only
temporary, you know?
Come on inside.
Thanks.
Hello?
DUKE: Mrs. Balboa?
George Washington Duke here.
Yes?
Mrs. Balboa, can you hear it?
Listen close,
you must be able to hear it.
Hear what?
The sound of
the parade going by,
of opportunity knocking.
I mean, what's it gonna take
to get you people to realize
I'm giving you a chance to
pull yourselves together again?
Let me handle your husband's
career and the money will pour in.
You can start living
like human beings again.
Listen, Mr. Duke, we're
living like human beings.
You ought to
try it sometime.
You leave my husband alone.
Women.
When'd you
start that?
I don't know. It's like a
bad habit that comes back.
But, hey, listen.
We ain't talking about me,
we're talking about you, right?
MAN: Hey, Rocky,
how you doing, man?
Yo. How you doing?
Good to see you back
in the neighborhood.
Yeah. Thank you.
It's great to be back.
You know, you're
real smart in school,
but you gotta be smart
on the street, too, see?
How do you mean?
Well, you gotta know
who the players are
and, like, who you're
talking to around here.
Watch out for the scammers.
Everybody's gonna try to scam.
What's a scam?
Ask your father.
Well, a scam is
like a hustle.
PAULIE: He don't get it.
ROCKY: Well, you know, like
a hustle's related to...
WOMAN: Rocky?
Yeah?
Rocky, remember me?
I'm Bubba's mother.
Yeah.
You used to use his
head for a punching bag.
Yeah, he had
a nice head.
Welcome back.
So, anyway, like a hustle's
related to a con, you know?
PAULIE: He don't get it.
ROCKY JR.: A deception.
Excuse me?
You're saying
beware of deceptions.
Yeah, that's good.
Absolutely.
You're very smart,
you know?
ROCKY: Hey, ain't this where the
Atomic Hoagie shop used to be?
I'm new here,
Dad.
This neighborhood's coming
down with tooth decay.
It's called
urban blight.
Yeah?
I'll tell you something, this
place is blight new, you know?
I think a little aluminum
siding and some paint,
this place could be okay
again. What do you think?
I don't know. Anyway, we're
gonna be late for school. Come on.
Hey, Paulie, I wanna talk to
the kid private, like, you know,
man to smaller man,
all right?
Right.
Like I got no feelings.
Come on, Paulie.
That's how wars start.
Relax, would you?
So, anyway, you know, everybody's
got an angle, you know?
Yo, tough break, Rock.
Yeah.
Everybody's got
a hustle, you know?
See, like these kids around here,
they got street brains,
you see?
That's how they live.
These kids ain't like...
Listen to me.
They ain't like no personalities
that you growed up with.
So you gotta stay very,
very sharp around here.
I intend to.
"Intend. " You know, sometimes
you make me feel very stupid.
Why?
'Cause you're smarter
than me, and that's a fact.
No, I'm not.
Yeah, you are.
It's like every day
you learn something new,
and every day I
forget something new,
but listen.
Listen to me.
We're in this thing together,
so if you can figure out any way
on how to fix things up,
don't be afraid to tell me,
'cause we gotta stick
together, 'cause what are we?
What?
What are we?
Oh, oh...
Home team.
Home team! You know, you got that right.
You know, I used to go to
this school when I was a kid.
You know. Nice bricks.
Used to have good milk
at lunch and everything.
It was real tough then,
but I think you can
handle it, don't you think?
BOY: No way, you don't even
know what you're talking about.
If you went here,
I can go here.
I'm not scared, really.
Really?
Well, I guess
I'm a little scared.
But that's normal,
don't you think?
Yeah. You know,
I had 72 fights coming up,
and every one of 'em
I was scared.
So, yeah, you know,
that's real, real normal.
I'll see ya later.
Okay, kid.
Here's the front door.
Okay. Hey, wait!
What's this?
What's...
Goodness gracious.
Where'd this come from?
It's a strange place to stash
your lunch money, don't you think?
It's just a lunch joke, you know?
Thanks, Dad.
Okay, listen.
I'll see you later.
Remember, Daddy loves you.
You're number one.
Home team!
Just be nice, right?
You'll be okay.
And don't mess with
nobody's girlfriend.
They don't like
that around here.
ROCKY: You know, Paulie, I'm
really worried about the kid.
You know, he ain't
used to living like this.
He don't know
the streets or nothing.
And that school, I know
exactly what's gonna happen.
Some wise guy's gonna come
up to him 'cause he's my kid.
He's just gonna come out
and try to bang him out,
give him a cheap shot,
you know? I mean... Jeez.
Mr. Balboa?
Yeah?
How you doing?
My name's Tommy Gunn.
Yeah, how
you doing?
Well, with a name like that,
you better be tough.
Yeah, very true.
It ain't easy.
Anyway, I come
from Oklahoma.
Welcome.
I have an amateur's
record of 45-to-one.
And I turned pro at 18,
and I had eight fights.
You're a fighter?
Yeah, I'm a fighter.
And now that I'm 20, I'd just
like to show you what I got.
Well, I... I mean, I've
saved up about 400 bucks.
Mr. Rocky Balboa. I could
pay you for training.
Yeah... What?
Excuse me, young man,
I have some business here.
What, is he lost or what?
Thank you.
Good to see you again,
friend. How you doing?
Yeah. How you doing?
DUKE: My health is fine.
What more could a man ask for?
PAULIE: Money and hair.
Listen, I gotta
go to work now.
What? Where? Here? In a sweatbox?
Yeah.
Can't be good
for the image.
Urban light.
What are you gonna do?
Hey, Rocky, Rocky...
What'd you say?
Urban light. It's
"blight. " Urban blight.
Rock, George would
like you to consider
putting on those
damn gloves again.
It's a hell of
a payday.
Well, you know,
I'm officially expired.
No, you do have
marquee value.
You put butts in the
buckets, asses in the seats.
A businessman with
any sort of brain
don't retire when he can
still pull in the bread, baby.
'Cause only in America do we
get these kind of opportunities.
Union Cane's going for
the title on the 14th.
Yeah, here's some
tickets. Be our guests.
We have a strong
feeling about this one.
Think he's gonna take it.
That's the time
to challenge.
Because people
love comebacks,
and there's nothing in the
boxing business more commercial
than a long-shot comeback
of a down-on-his-luck,
pure snow-white underdog.
Now, like your
Mark Twain once said,
"Virtue has never been
as respectable as money. "
Who's Twain?
He was a painter.
Look, simply put,
you're the great white hope.
You mean great white dope.
No, forget it.
No, no,
Rock, Rock...
I ain't emotionally
involved in boxing...
Hey, hold it.
Hold the bullshit.
I know what the problem is.
You think I was born yesterday?
Merlin, show him
the paper.
What paper? Now, this
is your medical report.
It's not so good, but
we can work around it.
Where'd you get this?
It really doesn't matter,
does it, Rock?
You agree to fight Cane,
and George here can guarantee
you get licensed in any
country around the world.
Guaranteed.
You can do this?
No problem.
His comeback's in the bag
and worth millions.
The time is hot, the
deal is hot. Caliente!
We could use one more payday. I agree!
Adrian, where'd
you come from?
What do you
think you're going?
Mrs. Balboa just appeared.
This woman is magic.
Look, I don't think
you're very funny.
Are you trying to talk my
husband into fighting again?
We're talking business,
now, darling.
Do you like feeling hard up?
Do you like reaching in your
pocket and only feeling your leg?
Well, do you?
I didn't think so.
I'm offering you your
last golden opportunity
to dump this loser image.
Who you talking to?
Hey, Adrian, you
weren't working across...
Hey, what the hell are you
two people talking about?
This is
a tremendous opportunity.
Opportunity for who?
For you to make money?
For him to be disabled?
What would you do if the
choices were reversed?
You have to
think about that.
Rocky, they don't
care about you.
You want to get serious?
Let's get serious.
You represent the dreams of the
long shots, the little people.
The never-wills
identify with you,
and identification is
the key to public success.
You're a true champion, a true
product of the people. Now sell it.
Sell it while
there are still buyers.
They ain't
gonna last forever.
You say you're a fighter?
Then fight!
You say you want a
champion's do, then do it
and I'll make you so much
money you could swim in it!
You can swim,
can't you, darling?
What do you say?
Come on. Put it there.
It's time to put some hustle
behind this muscle.
He's done!
He's done fighting!
You're a damn fool.
Maybe we ought to sign Mrs.
Balboa to fight Cane, huh?
Looks like she's the one with
the cojones in the family.
Yo, you don't talk like that
in front of my wife, you know?
That ain't no
park bench, boy.
I'll get him.
Rocky, I'm really sorry.
I didn't wanna...
Hey, you guys
want privacy now?
I'll be upstairs.
Rocky...
Rocky, I'm sorry.
I... I...
But, you know, it just takes one
bad hit, and you could be an invalid.
Well, I feel like
an invalid already, Adrian.
Why'd you gotta
come back here?
You're too smart
for this place here.
I got nothing to do.
Gloria. I called Gloria.
She said, you know, she
could use some part-time help.
Yeah, but why do you
wanna do this, Adrian?
Why do you wanna go back to
the same place you started from?
I gotta do it,
but you don't gotta do it!
I wanted to be there so
I could be close to you.
All right. Yeah.
You know, it's getting a
little cold out here. Maybe...
Okay. Maybe you
better get inside, okay?
I understand.
Are you all right?
What?
Yeah, I'm all right.
I'm fine.
Hey, it's getting cold, okay?
Yo, Adrian!
Did we ever leave this place?
I don't know!
Hey, mind if I
talk to you now?
My head's
a little busy right now.
George, I don't know
if you're gonna get him.
This guy, Balboa, he don't
think straight anymore.
None of these bums think straight,
but all I need is an angle.
I'll fight Balboa right now. Hey...
I'm better than
Balboa ever was.
Hey, hey!
I own the paper on you, boy.
You will fight who I tell you,
where I tell you, and how
I tell you, you got that?
Don't aggravate the
hand that feeds you, huh?
All right?
None of these bums
think straight.
All I need is a hook.
Hey, ain't you Rocky's kid?
Yeah, you're
Rocky's kid.
You're Rocky's
kid, right?
Yeah, how you doing?
Yeah, I seen your
picture in the paper.
And you know what?
Your old man's a punk.
What?
Get off me!
And what are you
wearing my coat for?
Just leave him alone!
You want a beating too?
Give me my coat! I'm not
kidding around anymore!
JEWEL: You better let
him have it. No way!
BOY: Don't get sick now!
Hope you don't
catch cold, rich boy!
Keep it high.
Slipping and sliding.
Slip the jab.
That's it. Come on.
That don't interest you?
This cup?
Rocky drinks out of it
around the house. Ten bucks.
Well, hey, man. How I
know it's the real thing?
Look at the
lip marks, huh?
All right, five bucks.
Five bucks. No more.
You got a deal.
Okay.
Excuse me.
Tommy Gunn!
Is there
someplace I can change?
In there.
Give me the money.
Time! Hey, Richard, Richard,
good friend, listen to me.
If you wanna survive, you gotta
learn to slip the jab, you know?
Keep it high, and hit
and not get hit, you know?
Okay, take off.
Rocko?
Yeah?
Remember Tommy Gunn?
Yeah, yeah.
He says he wants to fight.
I told him to get married.
Why?
That's gym humor, Rocko.
That... Okay.
Hey, let's see what
you got there, kid.
Get married, eh?
TRAINER: Benson,
wanna move a little?
Yeah, all right.
ROCKY: Hey, Paulie,
what's a cojones?
Cojones? Cojones is
Latin for Spanish nuts.
TRAINER: Yo, Rock.
We're ready.
ROCKY: Wonderful.
Hey kid,
you got the headgear?
Nah, I don't
need one. Nah.
He's gonna get his
cojones knocked out.
Okay. Ready, guy?
Benson, go easy, all right?
BENSON: Sure. Okay, Rock.
Time.
All right.
Just go easy now.
Slip the jab now.
TRAINER: Go easy.
Hey, kid.
What's his name again?
Tommy Gunn.
Tommy. Whoa!
It ain't no law to duck.
TRAINER: That's it.
Go side to side.
That's it.
Whoa! All right,
that's enough.
Hey, man!
Take it easy, man!
Hey, come on,
you guys, lighten up.
It's called sparring.
Now, go on easy.
Whoa! Hey, hey!
Okay, okay.
Hey, lighten up!
That's it. Tie him up.
That's it.
You smell that, Rocko?
What's that? That's
the odor of opportunity.
TRAINER: Hey, that's it.
What'd I tell you?
Hey, hey! Time!
Hey, that's it! Time!
TRAINER: Chill out, man!
PAULIE: Call time!
Time!
Hey! Hey, back off!
Hey, that's enough!
What's the matter with you?
Tommy, are you crazy
or something?
Hey, what's
the matter with you, man?
TRAINER: Get out of the ring.
I'm sorry.
Get out of the ring.
Cool off, kid.
All right.
I'm sorry about this.
He stinks of opportunity,
Rocko.
Hey, look.
Going easy don't mean
breaking bones, kid.
Man, I'm sorry.
But what do you think?
What do I think? I don't
think you listen too good.
But you, you fight, you brawl
like you was a street fighter,
and I know
something about that.
But this is called boxing.
This ain't no mugging, you know?
I'm sorry. But I know I can do it all.
Yeah? Well, not
on this date, okay?
That's it?
Hey, yo, I gotta work
with these kids here.
You guys get ready.
Come on, one more.
How about you
try to manage me?
Manage?
Yeah, unless you think
I ain't got nothing going.
Man, got nothing going?
Yeah, all right, you got a lot
going. You got a lot of tools.
But I ain't no manager.
I ain't never been...
You know, the gentleman
that owned this place,
that was a manager.
But, me,
I was always the managed guy.
Hey, look.
Good luck, all right?
All right, guys.
Let's go.
Come on,
move around.
That's it. Nice.
All right, you guys, come on.
No cheap shots.
Move it around.
How you doing?
Cold? You look cold.
I guess it has something
to do with the weather.
Here, take my coat.
No, thanks.
Where's your boyfriend?
Him. Forget it. He ain't got no manners.
I'm Jewel,
if you wanna know.
I'm Robert.
Hi.
Well, I been living here
about six years now.
It ain't Disneyland.
You been to Disneyland?
Sure.
You make it sound
like everybody has.
I know you can't tell
by the way I look,
but I ain't like the
other kids around here.
Why? I mean, what
makes you so different?
I don't know.
I guess it's
'cause I wanna get out.
You know how it is.
You know, for an Italian kid,
you ain't got a bad butt.
BOY: Shut up, man.
Let's go. Come on.
PAULIE: First money I get,
I'm going to Miami.
Why Miami?
Miami needs
new gigolos.
Yeah, I read
something like that.
Ow.
My back is getting bad.
How come you
don't have arthritis?
Yo, ain't I got enough?
MAN 1: Hey,
watch where you're going.
Adrian's too good for this.
This place is really depressing,
Paulie, you know? It's...
MAN 2: Yo, Rock,
come inside.
Everybody's been asking
for you. You too, Paulie.
ROCKY: Hey, no, thanks.
I'm a little beat.
I'm a little thirsty.
Hey, you go if you want to, Paulie.
Mr. Balboa?
Look at this.
Tommy Gunn.
Yo, why you still
hanging around, kid?
Is there something
I can do for you?
Yeah. I'd like
to try again.
Hey, kid, you know,
I'd like to help you out,
but I really don't know
nothing about no managing.
All I'm asking
for is a chance.
Man, if I screw up or do
something you don't like,
man, you don't have to throw
me out. Hell, I'll leave.
What have you
got to lose?
Me? Nothing. I ain't
got nothing to lose.
It's what you got to lose.
And I got nothing to lose.
Maybe you do. Like, look,
what if I don't
do good, right?
You know,
and you don't make it?
I don't want you blaming me
for this, kid, you know?
You know, here's what
I would do if I was you.
No, listen to me.
If I was you,
here's what I would do.
I would go home, and I'd
talk to your family people.
Maybe you could come up with
something better, you know?
I got no family people.
Man, all I got is
what you see here.
Man, I know everything about you
from back when you had your
first fight with Apollo Creed.
Yeah. I read how nobody cared about you,
how no one ever
gave you a chance.
And I realize I don't come
from the same streets as you do,
but I'm hungry
like you were.
And ever since
I put on gloves,
I've been
waiting to meet you,
'cause I knew that if anybody
could make me a winner, it was you.
Winner. Hey, Paulie, you
see a winner standing here?
Yes! Man,
you beat the best!
Nobody could ever
say any different.
Look, Rock,
you don't know me,
but anything you want me to do, I'll do.
And if I can't,
I'll bust my butt trying.
Man, I'm not
hustling you, man.
All I'm asking
for is a chance.
Man, just one shot.
Are you hungry?
Yeah.
Yeah?
Come on.
You're really gonna like the
way Adrian cooks, you know.
She does, like, amazing
things with macaroni,
especially tomatoes.
But I gotta warn you.
She can be a little
vicious with the garlic.
So, why'd this kid
smack your face for?
It really doesn't matter, Dad. Sorry.
Hell, sure, it matters.
It does matter.
They took his coat.
No. They... Look, I don't want the coat.
They took the one
with the collar?
ADRIAN: I'm gonna go to your
school tomorrow and just...
Yeah, you should. You'll only
make things worse if you go.
Can't I do what
I think is right?
Well, you know, what
do you think is right?
A baseball bat across
the face would be nice.
Paulie, what are
you telling this kid?
Adrian, can I have
the plate?
I'm sorry, yes, Rocky.
You know, I had trouble one
time when I was in school.
It seemed like every day
I got chased by this one kid,
till one day my mother
said to me, she said,
"Just pretend
the guy's like a balloon. "
Balloon?
She said if you pop him hard,
these guys just go away.
Tommy, we're trying to raise our son
so he can handle
his problems with his mind,
not his muscles.
Sorry.
That's why I'm
gonna get mangled.
No, you ain't gonna
get mangled.
Dad, will you
teach me how to fight?
PAULIE: A baseball bat
would be nice.
Come on. Do you want to grow
up and just use your fists?
You know, Adrian, I don't
think it would be so bad
if I taught him how to throw
a few deadly punches, you know.
Tommy, did your Dad
teach you how to fight?
No. Not exactly.
I had to...
What?
Come on, sweetheart,
don't get personal.
No, it's okay.
See, my old man, he used
to drink a lot, seriously.
He'd go out with his
friends and tie one on,
then he'd come home
and look to punch on me.
You know, he'd punch on my mother, too.
He did that
a lot of times.
You know, so, growing up, I never
really thought about fighting anybody
but my father.
You know, when I was 13,
I got in trouble at school.
He tied me down
and he whipped me so bad
I couldn't walk for a week.
Just couldn't do anything.
But, I tell you, the first guy
I ever knocked out was my father.
And now when I get in the ring,
it's like all I see is him.
That's kind of sick, huh?
Hey, yo, Tommy.
At least you had
an old man to
knock out, you know.
Yeah.
Some of us didn't even
have that, you know?
Yeah, someday you could
punch out your pop.
Hey, yo, Paulie, what are you
telling the kid things like this?
Hey, it's fittest
of the survival.
Hey, Tommy,
where you staying tonight?
You got a place?
I'll find someplace to stay.
I mean...
No, I tell you, we got
room down in the basement.
It's not...
It's nice, I don't know.
What about me?
Wait, now, sweetheart. Your
son is sleeping down there.
No, well, he can stay
with his uncle, right?
What the hell am I?
A pit stop?
ROCKY: No... Hey, I don't
want to cause any problems.
I mean, I can find someplace to stay.
No, it's okay.
You know, it's just
for a little while,
you know, right?
No problem at all. You
know, it'll be all right.
Hey, kid, I appreciate it. Is
that all right? It's cold outside.
Hey, I'm not
changing no sheets.
Hey, since when
have you ever?
Hey, Tommy, why don't
you come on down
and we'll show
you the whole place?
Sweetheart, why don't you go downstairs,
show your Father
what you did today?
Come on. Come on.
Hey, junior, your plumbing
don't leak, do it?
You know this guy?
Yeah. He hits hard.
TOMMY: You know, Adrian,
man, she can really cook.
ROCKY: Yeah,
she's okay.
Listen, Tommy,
we ain't had a chance
to get this place
too nice, so...
I'll get it together in
a little while, you know.
Wow, man! This is what it's all about!
Holy mackerel...
Well, I...
Why do you keep
this stuff down here?
When did you get
a chance to do this?
He took
everything out of a box
and fixed this up like this.
It's beautiful!
And you painted! When'd you
get a chance to do this, kid?
After school.
It's no big deal.
If you don't mind me asking,
where'd you get the glove?
This?
Yeah.
Thanks. This is one
of my favorite objects.
You know, like, Mickey give
me this before he departed.
It was Rocky Marciano's
cufflink that we had fixed.
Really? The real Rocky Marciano? Yeah.
Yeah. You know, you got me
thinking about Mick.
I wanna show you something.
Come on.
He told me a long time ago.
He says that,
fightin' is like,
90% in the skull
and 10% in the body.
This is what
he says to me.
Hey, Dad, I met this really
nice girl today. She's great.
Yeah? Really?
That's wonderful.
Yeah, she's a lot
better than Sarah.
Hey,
don't change the station.
I'll be right back with you.
I just wanna tell Tommy
a few things, you know? Hey.
Who was your best
friend back in Orlando?
That's...
That's Oklahoma.
Right, well, yeah.
Eric Elder.
No, no, no. No, your best friend
is a guy named Frankie Fear.
You see, fear is
a fighter's best friend.
You know, but it ain't
nothing to be ashamed of.
See, fear keeps you sharp,
it keeps you awake,
you know, it makes you want to
survive. You know what I mean?
But the thing is, you gotta learn
how to control it. All right?
'Cause fear is like
this fire, all right?
And it's burning deep inside.
Now, if you control it,
Tommy, it's gonna make you hot.
But, you see, if this
thing here, it controls you,
it's gonna burn you and
everything else around you up.
That's right, you know?
Anyway, these are the
things that was taught to me,
and if you want,
I'd like to teach to you.
So, this... This mean
you're gonna manage me?
Absolutely.
Hey, home team! Okay!
All right! Yeah!
Let's go for it.
TOMMY: Hey, Rock,
as long as we're down here, do
you mind showing me a few things?
Sure, Tommy. I'm gonna
show you a lot of things.
Hey, rich boy, how much you
got in your pocket today?
Nothing.
Come on, let's have it.
Nothing. I got nothing.
Come on. Give me the money.
Come on!
Hey, I gotta eat.
He's hungry. He's gotta
eat. Well, eat this!
I got it. I got it. Go.
Father Carmine! Yo!
Father Carmine!
You know,
maybe he's not home.
No, priests is always home.
Rocky!
Yo!
Well, I didn't want to
disturb you that much, Father.
Excellent.
Everything is perfect.
You know...
Father, this is my
new friend, Tommy Gunn.
Well, I was wondering... You
know, Tommy here is a fighter,
and I'm supposed to be
his manager, you know?
So I was wondering if
you could do me a favor,
you know,
if you ain't that busy.
If you could throw us down
a couple blessings, you know?
One, that I don't
mess up being a manager,
and B, that Tommy does as
good as I think he can do.
You know, great, and don't get
hurt none. Could you do that?
I love when he does that.
Hey, thanks, Father.
I really appreciate this.
Anytime.
Okay. Hey, I'll see you
in church!
Okay.
Hey, man, what'd you do this for?
Hey, it don't hurt having an
angel in your corner, you know?
Come on!
Hey, Rock,
how's it going?
ROCKY: Doing great, guys!
Better slow down, we're
gonna give you a ticket.
This is Tommy Gunn.
He's gonna be champ, guys.
How you doing, Tom?
Break it up. Break! Break! Break it!
Get off the ropes.
Just go easy, all right?
Man, I need more work.
No, no, no, you're ready.
No, I need more work.
This guy's killing me.
Now, listen to me. You're
ready now. He's killing me.
No, you're perfect,
you understanding me?
Man, I feel weak. I feel
weak. No, no, no. Listen to me.
Shut up! Listen to me.
Mick used to say
the only difference
between a hero and a coward is
the hero's willing to go for it.
All right? He's willing
to take the shot, okay?
Now, this guy over
here is scared, too.
You're scared. He's
scared. You're both scared.
Remember, in the basement,
when we was talking about fear
and how it's
like this fire, huh?
And you gotta control it 'cause
it's like, it'll, like, burn you up
or it's gonna burn him up.
All right?
Now, you gotta make it
work for you, Tommy, okay?
I would never do nothing
that would hurt you.
You gotta understand
what I'm saying.
Now, fear is like
this fire, okay?
Now, let it burn and burn until
it becomes like this volcano,
and when the time is right,
and you see the opening,
explode all over
this guy, okay?
Now, you can take him, okay?
It's all heart, you
understand? Okay. Got it.
It ain't all muscle, it's
all heart. Heart and fire.
Heart and fire! Okay.
Now you do it.
Remember, I'm like this angel
sitting on your shoulder, okay?
I ain't gonna let nothing
happen to you, okay?
Go!
Got it.
Go for it
Come on, Tommy, jab!
Explode! Left, right!
The body! The body!
Hook!
All right!
Are you gonna stop
or keep on rushin'
Farther, faster,
quicker than the next man
To be the best
is the master plan
Go on with all you got
Give it your best shot
Don't ever think
about trying to stop
Keep reaching, pushing
hoping for perfection
Make up the direction
Don't ever stop for a moment
If you got it, flaunt it
And get up on it
Go for yours not for a
minute but all the time
You better do it
'cause I'm going for mine
Yeah!
Go for it
Go, go, go
I see it in your eyes
Time!
You've got to go
for the feelin'
It's time for the rhyme
of the bold and the gifted
Listen closely
and you'll get lifted
Like you've never
been before
Get more than
you bargained for, for sure
Life can be a trip
full of trouble
But you gotta stand up
and fight back double
Don't let nothin'
hold you back, yo
When life says stop
you say go, go
Go to the body, Tommy.
Come on.
That's it,
that's it!
Sam, you okay?
Hey, Tommy Gunn.
You got some guns,
don't you? Paulie!
'Cause I know
you got the knack
To go farther than
you've ever been before
Rocky!
REFEREE: It's over.
PAULIE: 18, 19.
I see it in your eyes
ROCKY: Drive through it.
85. Go on, now.
You got to go
for the feeling
And 10. Come on,
you can do it. That's it.
You got it.
Come on, bring it up.
Yeah!
TOMMY: I got you.
I got you this time.
Damn!
Yeah.
ROCKY: Tommy, you know, these trunks,
is, like, very special to me, you know?
Dig, dig, dig!
Hook!
Yeah!
Way to go, kid! That was
great! That was great!
CROWD: Tommy, Tommy!
Go for it, yeah
Go, go, go
I see it in your eyes
Go for it
All right, kid.
You got to go
for the feeling
Yeah! Whoo!
I beat the man!
I don't believe it!
You sure did.
You're very swift,
Tommy Gunn.
To be or not to be dope
That's the question
Are you gonna stop
or keep on rushin'
Farther, faster
Quicker than the next man
To be the best
is the master plan
Yeah, Merlin, listen.
Got an idea.
I think we can
finally nail Balboa.
Go for it
They're waiting again.
Yeah.
If you don't got enough
money, I got almost a dollar.
Save it.
Slumming again, bimbo?
Hey, barefoot,
what you got in the bag?
Shut up.
Hey, squaw, what?
You're not talking to me?
Take two more steps and I'm
gonna pound your teeth out.
Go for it!
What'd he say?
The punk's losing his mind.
What'd you say?
Go for it!
JEWEL: Do it!
BOY: Kill him!
Come on! Put up your hands! Come on!
No way!
I didn't like him anyway!
I think that belongs to me.
KIDS:
Robert! Robert! Robert!
If you wanna end this,
let's end it now.
Yeah, I got no problems with that.
See you later.
All right.
I can't believe it.
Well, are you gonna tell your dad?
Yeah.
Come on, let's go.
Good, that's it.
One more time.
Yeah, yeah, look...
Hey, Tommy, Tommy,
you're doing
great combinations,
but you gotta learn to move side
to side, like a windshield wiper,
so you ain't getting kicked
in the face with his jabs.
Dad!
Back and forth, you know...
I got my coat back!
Look, I got my coat!
That's great, kid.
That's beautiful.
I trashed this guy. Everybody in
the school went crazy. Everybody!
Hey, Rock, man, I'm
cooling down over here.
Hey, listen,
I gotta get back with Tommy
'cause we gotta work out. He's
cooling down and everything, but...
Listen, go tell your mom. She'd
like to hear things like that.
That's beautiful, you know.
Okay, let's go, Tommy.
Looking good!
Come on, lay it on me.
Look at Tommy go!
ANNOUNCER ON TV: Union Cane, the new
heavyweight champion of the world...
You think I have
a chance at that?
Absolutely. You kidding?
Hey, Tommy, anybody's got two
fists, right, and a good heartbeat,
they got a chance, right?
Like a monsoon, typhoon,
stormin' in the worst way
Here to stay, no play
hear what I say
Not goin' out 'cause I
got it goin' on intense
You're out!
Strong renegade
cannot be slayed
You wanna rate me
A is my grade
Move and groove till
you're lookin' like a pro, yo
Takin' 'em out
with a rock-hard body blow
Go!
ROCKY: Come on, kid, 49.
Heads up!
Yeah!
Quick on the draw
Shoot for the jaw
Stone to the bone
Rebels stand tall
Ask for nothing
Boy, you got hands of gold.
I want to introduce
you to somebody.
Ring the bell
Feel the vibration
Straight to the kill
For best stimulation
Calculation for
the situation at the end
It's total ovation
Keep it up
Go, Tommy!
Don't you stop now
Keep it up
Yeah!
Don't you stop now
Keep it up, keep it up
Keep it up, yeah
Keep it up, ooh
Make 'em sweat
wet like a hot dog
Turns on your mind
like you were an android
I'm on, I said it
You know it, I meant it
I control your souls
hold the contract
Adrenaline feels good
like a climax
TOMMY: Yeah!
REFEREE: That's it. It's over!
Tommy, back him up!
That's it!
Yeah!
There's your boat, Rock.
What boat?
The one that's sinking.
DUKE: Tommy Gunn at the top.
You come with the Duke,
you can get
the kind of payday fights
Balboa could
only dream about.
To the victor
goes the spoils.
Slip the jab, Tommy!
Yes!
You're out!
Yeah!
Great, kid.
You did it, man!
You did it! You did it!
Hey, man, now am I gonna
get a shot at the title?
Yeah, you're gonna get one real
soon. WOMAN: Tommy, over here!
Hey, baby,
how are you?
ANNOUNCER: The winner, at
two minutes and 10 seconds...
So, Rocky, when's Tommy
going up against Union Cane?
We gotta talk about that.
How does it feel to be a
manager? Get lost, will you?
Rocko, he ain't
worth it, buddy.
He fought a great fight,
you know, Paulie?
Your ship is sunk, Rocko.
It sunk, huh?
He probably got hung
up in traffic, Adrian.
He should have
been here by now.
Why? Why? It's Christmas time.
He should be here
with his family.
Well, maybe he doesn't
think this is his family.
Sure it is.
Yo, Adrian, look.
Look at this.
What?
I wanna give
this to him.
What do you think?
I think you've given enough.
Hey, come on, Adrian.
He's given us some
things too, you know?
He's given us, like,
a second shot, right?
Come on, it's Christmas.
DUKE: That's right.
Only in America.
Having the best,
wearing the best.
But to keep it up,
you gotta stay on top.
Nobody remembers
number two, kiddo.
I sure don't.
Now, Tommy, I've checked
with the boxing commission.
It seems there's no formal
contract between you and Balboa.
No, nothing. Just a... Just a handshake.
Tommy, this is a complex business
and you got to stay sharp.
But I don't have to
tell you that, do I?
'Cause it gotta be damn difficult,
you living in Rocky's shadow,
people calling
you his puppet.
I don't know anybody who could
have done it as long as you have.
Tommy, I'm afraid.
I'm afraid that if you keep
going the way you're going,
you're gonna be watching
the parade go by.
Exactly.
Tommy, you haven't had
the big payday yet,
and you won't until you
fight those top contenders.
And those top contenders,
Tommy boy, I do surely own.
I got the contracts.
It's a complex business.
But if you want the best,
then go with the best.
Man, what about Rocky?
I mean...
Rocky can still train you.
My God,
he's done a wonderful job.
Now look here,
here's $20,000.
Take it as an advance.
Time to put some hustle
behind this muscle.
Merry Christmas.
ROCKY: Whoa,
stop the presses!
Yo, Adrian, I can't believe
who just come up on the roof.
You know, hey, you know, he
just landed there and crashed.
And who do you
think it is?
Do I hear
reindeer on my roof?
You know...
Rantlers.
Unbelievable.
It's like a billion...
Whoa! Come on.
Look who's here!
You know this guy.
You got a weird family.
Don't I know.
It's gonna be next Christmas
before he gets down.
Hey, let's put it
together for Santa! Hey!
Merry X-mas. Yo, yo, yo.
Hey, I don't think
you got it right, Santa.
No, no, no.
It's, "Ho, ho, ho. "
What's
the freaking difference?
Where I come from,
it's, "Yo, yo, yo. "
Looks like we got
a 90-proof Santa.
Hey, Santa,
tell all the kids what
you got in the bag for them
that you brought
from the North.
Yeah, I got my laundry.
No, you got the wrong bag.
Come on, chubby, get out
of the way. Yo, watch it.
Let Santa take a seat.
Come here, little boy.
You been nice?
Uncle Paulie! Come over
here. Sit down here.
Hey, kid, why don't you tell
Santa what you need? What you...
He's stretching
the clothes, man.
I don't need nothing.
Hey, kid, tell Santa what
you really want. Come on.
That ain't Santa. It's
Uncle Paulie. Let's get real.
ROCKY: What do you mean,
"Get real"?
You know,
why you talking like that?
We're just trying
to have a good time,
and Santa's here
and everything and...
It's stupid!
Yo, you know, come on. It ain't stupid.
We're just trying
to pretend here.
But you see, you're
supposed to be pretending.
It's like this game,
right? You know?
I don't like pretending. Why
don't you guys talk to Santa?
Hey, yo, kid, you know,
I ain't talking to them.
I'm talking with you,
here, you know.
See, it's very important that
you spend time with the family,
you know,
and have a good time and
just getting the spirit
going, you know...
It's good, right?
Good for what?
Come on, let's go.
Look, his friends are here.
Maybe he doesn't want to.
Adrian, I know
what he wants.
How do you know
what I want?
'Cause I know you.
You know me?
He thinks he knows me.
Look, I ain't
celebrating nothing, okay?
Hey, wait a minute.
Hey, yo, come here.
What's the matter
with you?
You know? We always done this before.
We always had a good time,
Adrian, you know?
We don't have to
change nothing, never.
I mean, do you
remember last year
when we had fun,
when we had a good time?
It ain't last year, and
you ain't the same either.
What?
Adrian, what...
What did I do?
Go talk to him.
Even I could've saw
this thing happening.
I should have went to Miami
when I had the chance.
You wanna talk,
let's talk.
You know, I thought we was
supposed to be, like, like,
you know, be very close.
Hey, come on, kid.
I love you.
No, you don't.
Sure I do, you know? Do you
remember what the deal was?
We were supposed to be, like,
tight, like crossed fingers.
No, no, what you want is
you and Tommy to be tight.
That's who you're
really talking about.
Don't say that.
Why can't I say it?
Since he's been here, it's
been "Tommy this, Tommy that. "
You don't have no time for
nobody, so I got no time for you.
Hey, what are you
saying to me, kid?
You're like another person.
You're the other person!
You said I would be
number one to you!
You said that and you lied!
You lied to me
and you lied to Mom!
I never lied to you.
Tommy needed my help.
So did I.
And remember when you said to
watch out for scams and deceptions?
Yeah?
You're the one that
should have watched out.
Where you going?
Out.
When are you coming back?
Later.
Later? When?
ROCKY JR.: Later.
DUKE: Season's greetings,
Mrs. Balboa.
You take care
of these people.
Behold,
a Santa for all seasons!
What, are you guys lost?
Au contraire,
mon ami.
I know exactly where I am.
Yo, Rocko!
Guess what's
coming to dinner?
Tommy Gunn's
got new friends.
DUKE: New friends
for a new year.
Please. Paulie.
Nice tree. Charming.
Hey, Tommy, how you doing?
Merry Christmas, my lord.
Greetings!
Yeah, how you doing?
Listen, I don't wanna
take up too much time.
I just wanted to come by and
give a little season's greetings.
I don't need no presents.
Give them to the neighbors.
Look, you've done a hell of a
job with the man. Facts are facts.
I'd have to be blind if I didn't
say a title shot isn't in the cards.
Title shot?
DUKE: That's right, title shot. Now,
we're gonna work beautifully together.
No problems.
No friction.
Only harmony, huh?
It's time to put some
hustle behind this muscle.
Why, our Tommy boy here's got
a little something personal
to discuss with you.
So I'm gonna be
saying good night.
Merry Christmas.
KAREN: Merry Christmas to you.
See you soon, huh?
Bye.
Sorry I'm late.
I ended up having dinner.
Let's go.
Hey, that's okay,
Tommy, you know,
Adrian cooked something, but
it's probably all cold now.
What we can do is make
sandwiches. It's no big...
Rocky, I don't
wanna make sandwiches.
I don't wanna make... No. Tommy,
why did you bring him here?
He just wanted to come by.
Tommy... Rocky, do you mind
if I talk to you outside
about a few things?
Yeah, sure.
It's getting late.
We have to be
there by 10:00.
Rocky.
No, it's okay.
Hey, Tommy, what did you
wanna talk to me about?
Isn't it a long drive?
Yeah.
So, what do
you think?
Well, where'd you
get this from?
Duke gave it
to me.
Tommy!
Hey, you know,
maybe you ought to
give this thing back,
you know, Tom.
And I knew it. I knew
you were gonna say that.
Give it back? Why?
I mean, the guy
likes the way I fight.
It's almost 10:00.
All right. We'll make it.
I know, but, you know, you see
what he's doing here, Tommy?
Hey, don't let him put
nothing between us, okay?
We got something
good going here.
TOMMY: Put? Like what?
I mean, the guy was just
talking about getting a shot...
But we don't need him,
you know what I mean?
I mean,
you're gonna get a shot.
You're gonna be able to buy
10 of these things here.
Rock, when you
gonna wake up, man?
We're watching
the parade go by.
What parade?
What are you talking about?
TOMMY: The big time.
Man, the way I'm going,
I'm not gonna get
a shot at the title
for a long time.
Now, listen, Tommy... TOMMY:
And I've got a perfect record.
I'm 22 and 0.
Where's the money? Where?
Man, we haven't made
any serious money yet.
And we won't
without the man.
I ain't talking
about the money.
Look, the money is
gonna be there, but...
I'm talking about
your rep, Tommy.
Look, don't sell out. Don't.
We don't need this guy.
Listen, Duke is a wonderful
man. Put the top up.
Hey, forget about
the top, would you?
I'm signing papers
with the man tomorrow.
No, listen to me, Tommy,
you sign them papers,
you're like his property.
You see, you got no control. You
know, this is a dirty business.
It's full of these thieves
and gangsters, you know,
and they promise every good
young fighter who comes along...
They promise them the world,
and then they suck them dry.
And they leave them when
they ain't worth nothing.
They leave them in the
gutter, broke, Tommy!
That's the way
this business is run.
Look, guys like Duke,
you know what he is?
He's a vampire.
He's living off
your blood, Tommy.
You know, the thing I'm trying
to do is what Mick done for me.
He tried to keep me away from
the dirty part of the business,
the way I'm trying to
do for you.
Man, I ain't you!
And you ain't Mick!
Man, when are you gonna
understand that?
When are you gonna understand
that this is a business?
In a business you need...
What, brains?
You said that, not me.
Is that what you're saying?
You're saying I got no brains?
Look, Rocky, you took me
as far as you could.
But Duke gave me my
title shot, you didn't.
And if you wanna keep
training me, then do it.
But if you don't, don't!
But it's my way or
it's the highway!
Tommy!
Rocky,
put on your coat.
Just put on your coat.
Come on.
It's not worth it.
Adrian, it is worth it.
He's just confused.
You don't see what's
happening under your eyes.
Yeah, I do see!
What... Yeah, he's...
He's twisted around by Duke.
I see what's happening.
No, come on, it's you, it's not
him. You can't live backwards.
Come on, you can't
turn back the clocks.
We live now,
we live here.
Hey, Adrian,
I know where we live.
What, do you think
I'm stupid?
I'm not as dumb
as you think I am!
Look, you don't think
I can smell it?
I see where we are.
Adrian, I don't want
this no more.
I want something
good for the family.
I don't want this.
I don't want this!
I mean, did I come
back here and get my
brains beat out for
these guys to say,
"Hey, there goes Balboa"?
I'm just another bum
in the neighborhood!
I didn't want this!
No, come on.
Nobody says that!
I'm saying it, Adrian.
I'm saying this.
When that kid was in the ring,
you know what I was doing?
I was winning.
When he was winning,
You were winning?
Yeah. It was...
It was like...
It was my last chance
at getting some
respect for us.
Do you know that?
Come on, I respect you.
I respect you. Yes, I do. It's
gone! You can't respect me.
I don't respect myself.
No, you can't do it!
I do!
Don't tell me that.
All those beatings
you took in the ring.
I took them with you.
I know how you feel.
I know when somebody like Tommy
comes along, you feel alive.
But he's not you. He
doesn't have your heart.
All those fighters you beat, you
beat 'em with heart, not muscle.
That's what Mickey knew.
That's why you and
Mickey were special.
But Mickey's dead!
If there's something you want to
pass on, pass it on to your son.
For God's sakes,
your son is lost.
He needs you!
I know Tommy
makes you feel great.
He makes you feel
like you're winning again.
But you're losing us!
Rocky, you're losing
your family!
I'm sorry.
You know it was
always you and me.
It was always you and me.
I'm sorry, Adrian.
I don't know
about you guys,
but I gotta get
out of here.
Hey, what do you say
we go to the shore?
Yeah, let's go.
Yeah, great. How are we gonna get there?
What do you mean
how we gonna get there?
We throw our thumbs in
the air. We'll hitchhike.
Yo.
What's he want?
You want me to
stay with you?
No.
Yeah, right. I got enough
problems with my old man. Come on.
You ain't gonna
hit him, are you?
No, I ain't gonna
hit him. No.
Yo, kid,
when you start smoking?
I don't know.
Didn't you ever smoke?
Yeah, I done a lot of
bad things, you know?
So?
So, I...
You know, I wised up.
Okay, so maybe I'll
wise up someday, too.
Maybe tonight's
a good night for
both of us to start
this wising-up thing.
Hey, don't worry about it.
I gotta worry about it.
I mean, the deal was we were
supposed to be tight, right?
What about Tommy?
You tight with him too, huh?
Tommy.
Yeah, well.
That was yesterday,
you know?
You know, kid,
you remember you were
telling me a long time ago
about deceptions,
and I was talking to you
about scams and...
I should have listened to
you. I was trying to teach you.
All right? But you, you were
teaching me and I didn't wise up.
And I didn't know, and I made
mistakes, and I do things, you know.
It bothers me, you know?
I forget a lot of things.
I... Just...
You know, I...
Hey, kid.
I know I made a few mistakes,
you know? It's...
But I would love to
hang out with you again.
Just you and me.
I swear to God, it's just
gonna be you and me this time.
Home team?
Yeah, home team.
ROCKY: Hey, kid,
you wanna hear a joke?
ROCKY JR.:
Yeah, sure. Why not?
Knock, knock.
Who's there?
Tuna fish.
Tuna fish who?
You can tune a piano,
but you cannot tune a fish.
Well,
you're getting better.
Yeah,
that's a good one.
All right, folks. Lock
the door and hide the kids.
It's time to wage war!
ANNOUNCER ON TV:
Tommy Gunn has been said
to be such a student
of Rocky Balboa's style,
he's been nicknamed by
the press the Clone Ranger.
DUKE ON TV:
In the red corner...
Relax, Rocko. He ain't worth the stress.
It ain't him, Paulie.
It ain't him.
Turbo-charged.
Tommy "The Machine" Gunn!
Tommy Gunn.
ANNOUNCER ON TV: Boy, looks like
the fans are unhappy with Tommy Gunn
for leaving
Rocky Balboa behind.
Yeah, of course. He's
nobody's sweetheart, that kid.
DUKE: Weighing in at 242
very impressive pounds,
the present world heavyweight
champion, Union Cane!
Looks like he's in great
shape, don't he, Paulie?
Yeah.
ANNOUNCER ON TV: And the
referee, Capaccito, calling
both fighters to
the center of the ring.
Whoa, Tommy, you're
looking... He's a little tight.
He's nervous, you know?
Like the way I felt when I was
fighting with Apollo, you know?
Rocko, he ain't you.
Hardly ever was, that kid.
Hey, come on. Give
him a break, would you?
All right, come on, Tommy.
Do what you was told.
In and out, side to side.
Don't eat the jab.
Get off the ropes!
What are you, blind?
Well, he's getting hit with
everything but the ring posts.
Come on, Cane. Let's
rumble. Go for it, Cane.
ROCKY: Come on, Tommy, what's
the matter with you? That's it!
That's it!
Slip the jab, move.
Move that, side to side.
Back and forth,
like a metronome.
Slip, slide, glide.
That's it!
Jab!
You see what...
He remembers everything.
All right.
Come on, Tommy.
I'm in there, man.
Do what I'm doing.
Do what I'm doing. Back and
forth, side to side, that's it!
Come on! Come on!
Come on, kid! Don't let
him up! Don't let him up!
Roll, roll, roll!
Dig, dig!
Got him! He's down!
The heavyweight champion
Union Cane is down!
REFEREE: One, two, three,
four.
Five.
REFEREE: Six, seven.
What are you doing?
Eight.
Nine!
Ten! You're out!
Yeah!
Yo! Yo!
The heavyweight champion,
Tommy...
Yeah!
Ladies and gentlemen,
by way of a knockout,
we have a new champion,
Tommy "The Machine" Gunn.
REPORTER ON TV: Congratulations.
A sensational upset victory.
And you're now the champion
of the world. How do you feel?
Never better.
I mean, I don't know
what's wrong with
these people, but...
Because you're not a champion.
You're a crumb bug dirtbag.
ROCKY: Hey, come on,
Paul, give him a break.
He did something wonderful.
Long live the king!
Yes!
I'd like to say thank you.
I'd like to thank the
man that made this happen,
and I'd like to thank the
man who made me believe
that all this
could happen,
the man who's been like
an angel on my shoulder,
Mr. George Washington Duke!
Yeah!
ANNOUNCER:
And there you have it.
A new champion of the world,
Tommy "The Machine" Gunn.
Boy, I'll tell you, a big
surprise, at least to me,
that the new champion
thanked Duke
instead of the guy
that got him here.
Yeah.
This crowd is unhappy.
CROWD:
Rocky! Rocky! Rocky! Rocky!
Rocko, too much TV
is bad for the eyes.
No, my eyes are okay,
Paulie. Sit.
Well, too much TV
is bad for my ears.
Yeah.
Hey, hi, slugger.
Good fight, huh?
It's okay, dad.
You're the real champ around
here. I made this for you.
Yeah?
Beautiful.
Rocko, let's put our teeth
around a few brews, okay?
I could use the company.
ADRIAN: Sure.
Yeah, good idea.
Think I should go out
with your uncle Paulie?
If I can watch TV.
Yeah, hey, okay,
listen.
Yeah, you can
watch TV, okay?
But don't stay up too late.
You gotta get
them bones growing.
All right.
Okay.
Wow, what a fight.
That was something.
Yeah, something.
Jeez.
I told you you could
give him everything
but you can't
give him your heart.
It's okay, Adrian,
really.
Yeah?
Yeah, it's all right.
It's... Hey, kid, don't
you stay up too late, okay?
That was some fight.
Are you okay?
Sure.
I won't be out too late.
Okay.
See you, champ.
Yeah, yeah. Have a good
time with Uncle Paulie.
Yeah, sure.
Ladies and gentlemen, let
me present to you the newest,
the youngest heavyweight
champion of all time,
Tommy "The Machine" Gunn!
Yeah!
Do you think
the fight was too easy?
He hit me a few good shots.
But I was never hurt.
I mean, I'm just glad
to be the champ. Yeah!
Tommy, don't you think
that this looked more like
a Philadelphia
sparring session at times
instead of
a championship match?
It didn't look like
you broke a sweat.
DUKE: Yeah,
you're very observant.
Union Cane wasn't
feeling that good.
But Tommy Gunn would
have done the same thing
if Union was 100%.
Next.
100%? He fought like he didn't
have a heartbeat. Come on!
Everybody knows that Cane
is just a paper champion.
What does he mean
by "paper champion"?
It means Cane's title
was manufactured.
He never won it from Balboa.
Gentlemen, give the boy a
break. Union Cane is for real.
Tommy, you ever think
you're gonna get out
from underneath
Rocky Balboa's shadow?
Man, I won the title.
What more do I have to do?
REPORTER: I'll tell you
what you have to do,
you've gotta fight some
real opponents, right?
Balboa fought them all.
But I beat the best tonight.
The best? The best?
This guy's a bum.
He doesn't even deserve
a shot at the title.
Gentlemen,
whoa, whoa, whoa.
We're getting carried away.
Now, Union Cane was the
recognized champ. Next question.
We know the rating system
can be manipulated.
The bottom line is Tommy Gunn
beat a second-rate fighter
with so much glass in his jaw,
he ought to be a chandelier.
DUKE: Say what you want,
but this man will prove
to be a great champion.
He might win a few fights, but
a Rocky Balboa he'll never be.
No, no, no.
He's no Rocky Balboa.
Let's face it.
There is only one Balboa.
Now, Balboa was
a true people's champion.
But in time,
Tommy Gunn may be
able to fill his shoes.
Next question.
REPORTER: Not by fighting
stiffs like Cane, he won't.
Man, I'll fight anybody anywhere!
Who? When? When are you
gonna fight a real fighter?
Gentlemen, gentlemen,
gentlemen, come on.
We want to thank you for coming
tonight, and we'll look forward...
Hey, Tommy,
I got something for you.
For your next fight, why don't you
fight the redhead in the front row?
I hear she comes
real cheap.
We look forward to seeing you
at Tommy Gunn's next fight.
Why the hell did you say
Balboa was better, man?
Do you believe he's better?
Of course not.
But we can't
talk in here, huh?
You the champ.
REPORTER: Who are you gonna
fight for the next fight, Tommy?
TOMMY: Man, what the hell
happened in there?
I won the damn title, and
these people think I'm a bum!
Man, why didn't you
take up for me in there?
Listen to me, when the press
is right, they're right.
Right? Man, I'm as good
as Balboa ever was.
I don't give a damn
about what they say.
And I'm tired of being
called a damn robot, too!
Listen to me, Tommy Gunn.
You can't fight the press.
I can't fight the press.
Oh, God!
As long as they got Balboa on
the brain, he'll always be champ.
The man fought
wars in the ring.
Tommy, face facts.
You're in his shadow. I don't
know if there's any way out.
This is your own man talking!
No, no, no!
Listen to me.
There's a way for you to
get the respect you deserve,
but what you've got to do is
challenge Balboa to fight man-to-man.
That's right. George here
could set this fight up abroad
in a matter of weeks.
Yeah, it'd be the greatest fight ever.
Teacher against student.
Old lion against young lion.
And it's the only way you're
ever gonna get peace of mind,
'cause believe me
when I tell you
that press is gonna hound you
with that man's legend
for as long as you dare
to wear boxing gloves.
You've got to get him
into that ring, Tommy Gunn,
or you're gonna be hearing
questions like you heard tonight
for the rest of your life.
Then you're gonna start to ask
yourself, "Could I really take him?
"Am I really good enough?
"Do people really think
I'm a cheap carbon copy
"or a second-rate
pretender who only
"got a shot
because of my skin tone?"
You've got to challenge that
man to fight, Tommy Gunn.
And if he refuses,
then you gotta insult him!
You gotta dog him.
You gotta humiliate him.
You gotta do whatever you got
to do to get him into that ring,
but that's what
you got to do.
ROCKY: Okay, blast off.
Rolling silver.
And down. Yo, Andy! Andy,
flippers ain't flipping. Yo, Andy.
ANDY: Hey, that machine
cost me a fortune.
Yeah, well, it's costing me
a fortune, too, you know?
DUKE: Rocky Balboa.
What the hell
was that?
Rocky Balboa, there's a man out
here wishing to speak with you.
Rocky Balboa!
Rocko, you know who that is?
MAN: Ain't that the Duke?
Yeah, I know who that is.
Rocky, you need
some help?
No, guys, it ain't
no pie-eating contest.
PAULIE: Look what's
in the street.
Yo, Tommy,
what are you doing here?
You ought to be out there
celebrating, right?
No, I'm challenging you
to a fight.
Anytime, anyplace,
anywhere.
Fight?
TOMMY: That's right.
You're coming down here
with these people,
asking me if I wanna
throw hands with you?
Is that what this is about?
TOMMY: Yeah,
that's what it's about.
And I ain't nobody's
robot! Nobody's boy!
Now, are you accepting the
challenge, or are you yellow?
He has no class.
Come on, Rock.
Hey. He has no class. Come on.
MAN: Let's go inside.
Come on.
You know, Paulie,
it ain't him, you know?
You wanna shoot some
eight-ball or something?
Hey! Man, I ain't through
talking with you yet.
Hey, look, Tommy, I ain't got
no more to say to you, okay?
Look, I just wanted good
things for you, all right?
Hell you did. Man, you were
only in this for the money.
Money?
Yeah, I'm tired of walking
around in your shadow, man,
people calling me
your robot.
You thought I was in this
for the money, Tommy?
You know, we were supposed
to be like brothers, you know?
You don't remember that?
You don't know this, but you
got a deception going here.
This guy here. He was
using you for the bait.
He wants to get you
and me in the ring.
That's what he wants, us to
fight each other, you know?
To make the money, right?
He don't care
about you, Tommy.
He don't care about me
neither, right?
Come on, come on. Enough of
the fantasy. Let's talk reality.
Rocky Balboa, are you prepared
to accept Tommy Gunn's challenge?
Tommy.
DUKE: All right.
Hey!
Hey, man, I would've taken you
any time. Come on. Let's go.
Hey, Tommy, you're a piece
of garbage, you know that?
TOMMY: This ain't
none of your business!
Ain't none of my business?
Hey, come on, Paulie.
Paulie, forget about it.
The man spit blood for you,
put you ahead of
his own family,
and you bring these rat bums
around here and kill his dignity?
Rocko made you your shot, you
know that? He's the real champ.
You're just a goddamn joke.
Now, just get out of here
before I break your face.
DUKE: Tommy! Tommy,
come on!
Paulie!
What?
Break your hand on this bum,
and what are you worth then?
Paulie, are you okay?
You should have left him on
the street where you found him.
TOMMY: Get off me, man!
DUKE: Right.
Get him out of here.
Merlin, Merlin,
get him out of here!
Merlin!
TOMMY: Get off me!
DUKE: Get him out of here!
Get him out of here! Merlin!
MERLIN: Tommy!
Get off me!
Now you knocked him down. Why
don't you try knocking me down now?
No, no, in the ring,
in the ring.
Tommy Gunn only
fights in the ring.
Come on,
let's get out of here.
My ring's outside.
Yeah? Let's do it.
Come on!
Tommy! Tommy!
Let's go live!
Go live!
MAN: Come on, Rocky. Kill
this here punk. He's nothing.
Tear him down.
You gotta take him down.
Just take him right down.
He's a bum, Rocky, I'm telling you.
Balboa is
a street fighter.
You a prize fighter.
Don't be a damn fool!
Hey, you don't own me!
Take it easy, Tommy!
You don't own me!
What the hell is wrong
with you? Take it easy!
Nobody does.
I want my respect.
Tommy.
Well, come and get it.
Come on, Tommy.
Come on, Rocky.
I loved you, man.
Do you know that?
You and me were supposed
to be like this, Tommy.
You blew it!
You...
MAN:
You're always champ, Rocky.
Lucky punch. Lucky punch!
But he's a street fighter.
And I told you never to fight
a street-fighting fight.
Come on, let's get out
of here. Come on, come on.
You're always the champ,
Rocky. Great.
MAN: Hey! Rock, watch out!
Somebody...
MAN: Rocky! Come on,
Rock! Rocky, come on!
Get out of it, Rocky!
Come on!
Get him, Rocky!
Come on, Rocky!
Rocky, get out of it!
I got it!
MAN: Rocky!
Come on, Rocky!
Rock! Get up, Rocky!
This is great stuff!
This is beautiful!
Mom! Mom! It's Dad.
He's on television.
He's fighting.
What?
Come on, man! Come on!
Ready to fight me? Come on!
Come on, Balboa.
Who's your puppet now?
Come on!
MAN: Get out of it, Rocky!
Get him, Rock!
Come on! Come on!
Come on!
Rocky,
you gotta get up.
TOMMY: Come on! Get up!
Come on.
What's the matter, Rock?
ADRIAN: Rocky!
You're out!
And if he dies, he dies.
You're the champ!
Now get up! One more round.
Come on, Balboa!
Get up! Don't lay down!
Fight this guy hard!
Come on! Come on!
He's no machine.
I didn't hear no bell!
Get up, you son of a bitch,
'cause Mickey loves ya.
Come on, boy. It's all
right. You the champ.
Yo, Tommy!
I didn't hear no bell.
Tommy. One more round.
Tommy, come on. Get back. Get back, boy!
Tommy,
you don't need this.
Tommy, you lose,
you're finished!
I got one more round.
Come on!
I'm not gonna knock
you out this time.
I'm gonna put you
through the street.
One more round.
Come on, Rocky!
Come on, Rock!
Come on, Tommy.
DUKE: Come on, get up.
Come on! Get it!
Come on, Tommy!
Come on! Come on!
Touch me and I'll sue.
All right, Rocky.
You've done it.
What in
the hell are you doing?
Get up! What in the hell?
Rocko!
Let's get home.
MAN: That's it, Rocky!
Come on, knock the bum out!
He took my room!
PAULIE: Your right.
Throw your right!
Jab, jab, come on!
You're losing everything!
Come on!
Come on, Dad!
You can beat him!
Fight back, you bum!
Fight back!
Stop!
Rocky!
Come on, get that...
Come on, Dad!
Go for it!
CROWD:
Rocky! Rocky! Rocky!
Hit him, Dad, come on!
CROWD: Rocky! Rocky! Rocky!
Go for it!
Dad!
CROWD:
Rocky! Rocky! Rocky! Rocky!
Hey, Adrian, you were right.
You were right.
God damn.
Only in America.
Hey, Rock, you outclassed the bum, huh?
Yeah. Yeah.
Rocky, come on.
Don't.
Duke.
Touch me and I'll sue.
Come on, punk.
Sue me for what?
Rocky! Rocky!
Hey, yo, father.
I love it
when he does that.
CROWD:
Rocky! Rocky! Rocky! Rocky!
ROCKY JR.: Come on, Dad.
We're gonna be late.
ROCKY: Come on, Speedy
Gonzales! Come on!
Come on, Dad. You can
do better than that.
No way.
I don't know.
It's like these steps
keep growing
taller every year.
My goodness!
Look at this thing, kid.
As long as this
thing is here,
pigeons is always gonna
have a place to sit, right?
I can't believe it,
you know?
And this is where it
all started for me, kid.
Running up and down
these steps, you know?
Dad.
Yeah?
Dad, we're gonna be late.
Yeah, okay.
Hey, wait a minute.
What's wrong with your ear?
What's wrong with it?
You got something growing in
your ear. You got like a bump.
What bump?
This bump.
Thanks, Dad.
Hey, you deserve it.
Thank you for being born.
Thank you, thank you, thank you.
What do you think?
The new me?
Well,
you look like the daughter
that I always wanted.
What are you talking about?
Yo, yo.
Hey, now, don't punch me.
I'm getting brittle as it is.
Look at this, you know.
I've been running up and
down these steps for 20 years,
and I never knew
there was valuable pictures
in this building,
you know?
Well, you're never too
old to learn something new.
Yeah.
You're gonna love Picasso.
Yeah?
Yeah, well,
I love almost everybody.
These battered hands
are all you own
This broken heart
has turned to stone
Go hang your
glory on the wall
There comes a time
when castles fall
And all that's left
is shifting in the sand
You're out of time,
you're out of place
Look at your face
That's the measure
of a man
This coat that fits you
like a glove
These dirty streets
you learned to love
So welcome back
my long-lost friend
You've been to hell
and back again
And God alone knows
how you've crossed that span
Back on the beat,
back to the start
Trusting your heart
That's the measure
of a man
It's the fire in the eyes,
the lines on the hand
It's the things
you understand
Permanent ties
from which you once ran
That's the measure
of a man
You've come full circle
and now you're home
Without the gold,
without the chrome
And this is the way
you've always been
You had to lose
so you could win
Rise above your troubles
while you can
Now you can love,
now you can lose
Now you can choose
That's the measure
of a man
It's the fire in the eyes,
the lines on the hand
It's the things
you understand
The permanent ties
from which you once ran
That's the measure
of a man
You've come full circle,
now you're home
Without the gold
without the chrome
And this is where
you've always been
You had to lose
so you could win
And rise above your troubles
while you can
Now you can love,
now you can lose
Now you can choose
That's the measure
of a man