Encoded by Deceit @ YIFY Torrents.
What The Hell! I didn't tell you to
go! God Damn! What's wrong with you?
Aw Man!... Ain't nobody listenin' to me?
Ladies! You can visit here at any time for free.
I need to see your license and registration.
Brother, you okay? You cool?
10 minutes, doors open on my signal.
I'm glad you're here, Lee! I always
feel better with you watching my back
I'm just doing my job, Mr. Ambassador
Stay close to me today
Lee, we're making history.
This is bullshit! You know who I am?
My family owns half of Rodeo drive!
Do you know who I am?
Detective James Carter. L.A.P.D.
My family owns half of Crenshaw Blvd.
I want a lawyer
You need a personal trainer, it's like you're a
180 Ibs. you weigh more then the damn car, girl.
I have a Tyroid condition,
What's that mean Tyroid's?
Look... can't you just like
give us a warning or something?
That depends... you girls like Chinese?
Excuse me.
Carter?
Lee, we're on for tonight, I just
picked up 2 girls, who wanna play hot...
with an Asian Policeman
I can't talk now, I'm in
the car with Ambassador Han.
Trust me. These girls are
sushi great, we gotta hit these!
I have to go, I'm sorry.
You're still mad at me aren't you?
You're mad because of what
happened when we was in New York.
I don't want to talk about that.
That was 3 years ago,
when you gonna let it go?
Let it go? Isabelle was my girlfriend.
Lee, we're friends man, just come
over here one night, the Wushu's on me.
Lee?
My mom says hi.
The Chinese Triads now
has a 1/2 million members,
In over one 100 countrys, and...
...these are not street kids,
shaking down local merchants.
These are buisness men, who build a $50 billion
empire on extortion, drugs, sex and slavery.
We must cut off the head... of this
snake, before it swallows us whole.
As Chairman of the World Criminal Court, I
have intrusted my good friend, Ambassador Han...
to lead the Fight, against the largest
criminal organization in the world.
Ladies and Gentlemen.
The Triads society is build on secrecy
Nobody knows who these men are
who control them, who leads them.
Nobody has known for 500 years.
But today I stand before
you with a secret of my own.
Today I will disclose information
that effects everyone in this room.
After years of searching,
I believe I finally
located the Sha Xing.
Mr. Ambassador, Sha Xing is not exist.
Excuse me, who is this Sha Xing?
With all due respect, Sir. I like...
Everybody down!
- Call an ambulance!
- Someone get a doctor!
- Ambassador down!
- The Ambassador is down!
Stay with him!
Na... ah, ah, I'm keeping
these, 'till I see you tonight,
World authority, World Criminal Court
Bldg. The Chinese Ambassador has been shot!
Chinese Ambassador? - Move
your ass girl, move over! - Shit
Lee!
What the Hell is he doin'?
- L.A.P.D. get out of my way!
- Give us a brake.
Hey Lee, I'll get you when I come back,
Lee, I'm coming!
Don't move!
Hello, Lee.
Put your hands up, Kenji!
Lee, what're you waiting for? Shoot me.
Maybe this will help.
Drop the gun or I'll shoot!
I think we both know,
that's not gonna happen.
Kenji!
You see?
I know you too well.
Lee, you okay?
Lee, I all-most killed your
ass, why didn't you move?
I like you to meet our dates for
this evening, Marsha and Dora.
The Fat one's yours!
How many times you want
me to say it, I'm sorry...
I'm sorry I ran you over, man, damn.
Not now all right... not now
All right, hold it right there.
Don't say a word Carter.
Capt. O'Neal, I had
nothing to do with this.
All I did was borrow a
car and backed up Lee.
Tell him partner.
I need to see Ambassador Han.
The Ambassador is just out of surgery.
The bullet missed his
heart. He's gonna be okay.
Capt'n, you have to give me back
my shield and put me on this case.
I made one little mistake,
take a brother of the bench.
One little mistake? You handcuffed
2 woman, and stole their car.
Isn't that why we have insurance?
Anyone has an off day Capt'n.
Last month you arrested 6 Iranians
and put them in jail for a week.
You and I both know them
Iranians was terrorist.
They were scientist at UCLA.
Big deal... 'cause they
cure cancer in rats...
that doesn't mean
they dont blow shit up!
Sir, let me find the person
who shot Ambassador Han.
Relax Carter, the L.A.P.D. will
be heading this investigation.
The Ambassador is my responsibility.
Then maybe you can tell me
exactly how the shooter got away.
Also... the Ambassador's daughter is
coming here to see her father right now.
Make sure nothing happends to her!
Don't worry, Capt'n,
we gonna make you proud.
And try not to think about
your wife leaving you.
She'll come back.
Soo Yung's here? I haven't seen
her since she was 10 years old.
She lives here in Los Angelos now.
Let's go to the gift shop and
get her a little teddy bear,
In a bra...
Lee, I'm so glad you're here.
Detective Carter.
- It's been so long.
- So long... Soo Yung, so long.
- How is he?
- He is out of surgery.
They said he will be okay.
Soo Yung, I'm sorry.
It was my fault. I didn't
get to him fast enough.
I want you both... to
promise me something.
I want you to find the
man who did this to him.
I want you to find him because...
I don't think he'll stop
untill my father is dead.
Soo Yung.
I need to hear you say it.
Okay, I promise.
And so do I.
Thank you.
Soo Yung, your father was addressing
the court before he was shot.
2 weeks ago, my father
mailed me an envelope...
he said, if anything ever happend
to him, I should give it to you
Where is it?
I put it in my locker...
at the Kung Fu studio, where I teach,
It's at 8347 First Street... China Town.
Go home, Carter, this has
nothing to do with you,
I made Soo Yung a
promise the same as you.
This is a business of China,
Well for your information
I'm part Chinese now,
That's right Lee, for the last 3 year,
I studied at the Institute of the Budah...
Earning 2 black belts
in Wushu Martial arts
And spending every afternoon at
the Hong Kong Massage Parlor...
I'm half Chinese, baby!
If you're half Chinese,
I'm half black...
I'm your brother, and I'm fly,
you're done with this, Snoopy?
That's dope, ain'it?
Sorry Lee, you can't be black!
There's a height requirement. I'm
still with you, no matter what,
Go home, Carter!
I can't leave you, Lee,
now you're my "Peng You"
I can't leave my brother!
All right, listen up!
I need everyone's attention!
I'm Detective Carter,
this is Inspector Lee
We need see Soo Yung's locker right now!
No one is allowed in the back,
without the master's permission,
Maybe you didn't hear me,
we need to see that locker
I'm sorry
Wait, Carter!
Lee, I got this!
Hey!
Kids listen, Knife's will solve nothing,
As the Chinese say, all great
battles are won without fighting,
Sorry!
- Ok?
I don't know him!
Look!
Let's try again from the top!
None of the Wushu formality,
You ain't gonna see it coming...
you ain't gonna see it coming!
Stop!
Run for your lives!
It's about time, I get some
respect around here!
Carter, wait for the master!
Whoa, damn!
Sorry, man, I thought
this was the bathroom, sorry!
Lee, I got a big problem, man!
This boy's on steroid's,
he's got a head like King Kong.
Oh no!
Carter? You're okay?
Lee, Lee...
Awww... my bunion.
Come on, man, let me go,
I love Chinese people.
Wait!
How you say surrender in Chinese?
Okay, I'm gonna slice you up
like a Giant California Roll
I'm sorry!
May I help you?
We'll be asking you questions, old man
Who are you?
Yu!
Not me, you!
Yes, I'm Yu
Just answer the damn
question, who are you?
I've told you!
Are you deaf?
- No, Yu is blind,
I'm not blind, you're blind,
That's what I just say,
You just say what?
- I did not say what, I say Yu,
That why I ask you,
And you're not answering...
- Shut up!
You!
- Yes?
Not you, him! What's your name?
Mi
- Yes, you!
I am Mi
- He's Mi! And I'm Yu
And I'm gonna whoop your ass
old man, sick of playing this game...
you, me, and everybodys
ass around here, you...
Carter!
- Lee, no, no,
- Carter,
Teacher, My name is Inspector Lee.
We have a key to Soo Yung's locker,
Some men came here this morning,
they had guns. They emptied...
her locker, I could not stop them,
You must go to her at once,
Why?
They said, she would end up
like her father.
Let's go! Thank you.
I don't know what the hell you feeding him, but he's too damn big.
- Carter, let's go!
Where's everyone?
Where's all the damn cops?
Lee?
Where's the security?
They were called away.
What's wrong?
Carter!
They're coming for him!
What do we do?
No!
Don't move or I'll blow your ass' Jigsaw
Get back!
Who send you?
Oh!
Don't move!
Lee, throw me a gun!
Throw me a gun!
Damn, Lee!
Lee, I thought you watched my back!
Soo Yung, one more!
Lee, I'm in trouble, need assistance!
- Empty!
- What?
You see, I always guard your back,
Why the hell you give me
an empty gun?
I didn't know,
You almost got me killed, Lee!
Who send you?
What the hell is that?
I think he's speaking French,
French? What kind of Chinese speaks French?
Tell me something and dont play around,
Ok, I tell him, I don't speak French!
No!
No! Stop humiliating yourself!
Find someone here, who
speaks French, please,
Speak English!
This is Sister Agnes,
from the chapel upstair...
she speaks fluent French, and she's
pleased to intrubite for you,
Sister, we appreciate
you're doing this
My Pleasure!
Sister Agnes, please ask who send him!
He said, you both making a big mistake
That one day, you'll beg him
for mercy, he also said...
What?
Please, Sister, we have to know!
There's lifes at stake.
Well, he used the "N" word
What, the "N" word?
- You tell this little mother...
- Carter!
She's a nun,
Sister, you tell this piece of "S" word,
that I will personally "F" word him up!
Did he say Nigger?
He use the "N" word again, but this
time he mention your grandmother
You tell him, that his mama is a "H",
Carter!
I believe Whore is spelled with a "W"
Right, "W", and his sister's a "W",
and his grandmama is 2 big "W's"...
who makes 2 double that's got no "T's"!
You tell I'm said that!
Did he say it again?
No, this time, he called this Gentleman
a word that means cat and another word
that rhymes with matt,
What?
Would you tell him, his an "AW"
Lee, hole is spelled with "H",
I have a dictionary upstair.
Just call him an asshole!
He said you both are marked for
death, like Han the girl,
Sister, turn your back, you
don't want to see this!
Who is Sha Xing, and how do we find him?
Tell me right now, or I'll cut
your beets off, and shove'm in your mouth
His beets?
His beets, Sister He's carreing
stinkin' beets!
Tell me something now!
Lee, give me the gun,
give me the gun, Lee!
Who is Sha Xing?
What he say Sister?
He said shoot me!
Lee, there's no bullets in here.
Sorry!
I'm trying to kill somebody, man!
Damn!
Ok!
You better tell me somethin' right now,
or I'll send you right to heaven!
- Carter, stop!
- Tell me now, I ain't got nothin' to loose,
That's right sister, tell the lord he's
gonna have some company.
- Carter, stop!
- Tell me somethin'!
- Carter Enough!
- She's almost done, just give me father fire.
Just wait!
What did he say?
50 Franklin D. Roosevelt, Jon Piere,
Thank you!
Nice working with you, Sister!
Anytime, brother!
- 50 F.D.R.
- It's an address
It's a wild goose chase, every city in
America has a street named after Roosevelt,
- Who's Jon Piere?
- I don't know!
Soo Yung, we're getting you out of here!
Why?
Is not safe here!
I won't leave him!
We have no choice!
- Soo Yung?
- Mr. Reynard.
I'm glad your father is ok.
My people won't leave his side,
you have my word.
Thank you!
So, let's go!
Where am I going?
We're getting out from this
Area, it's not safe for us!
Just for a few days, Soo Yung, I promise
You're coming with me, and
my family to Paris!
Ok!
Wait!
You made me a promise!
Don't forget!
My God!
We got an Assasin in custody that
only speaks French,
A limo blows up at the French Counsulat, and the next meeting of the world court is in Paris 2 days from now
Are you thinking what I am thinking?
Yeah!
We go to Fiji, we head out there for a year, we
change our names, get jobs and I'll call you Kiko!
We have to find Sha Xing,
before he finds us!
- We're going to Paris, ha?
- Yes, tonight!
Did you know, the average french
women is naked 34% at a time?
We not going there for the women!
You have to forget about her,
and let me hook you up!
Hook me up?
After what you did to Isabella?
It was an accident!
Besides, you never even slept with her,
Thanks to you, but it was going to happen!
- But you had to ruin it,
- What did I do, that was so terrible?
You shot my girlfriend, in the neck.
- There's nothing else to say,
- Now that she died...
So she had a cute li'll ass,
so she worked at air boco loco,
That was temporarily, as soon as she
complaint the secret service took her back.
You know what your problem is,
you need to relax, have some fun...
you have to much rice in your diet
and you're constipated,
I never should have brought you!
Listen, you need me, brother,
I don't need anyone, and
please don't call me brother
What's this?
Underground they have in Paris
Forget it!
Check out the address!
50 Franklin D. Roosevelt,
Like I said, you need me.
Excuse me, can we have one bag
Potato chips and some Exlax's.
Where're the bag's at?
Excuse me, Gentleman.
Would you please come with me?
Why?
Just need to ask you a few questions.
Ouch! Oh my god! Damn!
That's one of the worst
airports I've ever been to,
Now that I have your attention,
Why don't you tell me what you cops are
looking for here in Paris?
I told you, man, we're on vacation.
Just taking in the sites.
Gentleman, this is my city, and
I must force away two stupid cops...
come here and get their heads
blown off by the Triads.
Now I can't force you to leave
but I can make a suggestion.
After all, I found this dirty
little gun inside your jacket.
Which means you could both
do 20 years in my jail.
Do we understand each other?
Excellent
It was wonderful meeting you both.
So we can go now?
This will just take a moment.
Welcome to Paris.
Oh shit
Where're you go?
50 Franklin D. Roosevelt
No, get out!
What?
I don't drive his kind.
My kind?
Americans, I don't drive Americans.
But I'm Chinese.
Yeah, but you're with him, and
they're the most violent people I know.
Always starting war,
always killing people.
Americans make me sick.
Look, man, we're not
in the mood for this.
Me and my partner just got
violated by a small Frenchman.
Wearing a very large ring.
You're a pathetic bunch of criminals
Always resorting to violence.
Always pushing around the little guy.
That is not true,
Americans are not violent.
Our man in America is a joke.
You lost in Vietnam, you lost in Iraq
You can't even beat the
Europeans in basketball anymore.
The dream team is death.
I didn't hear you, man
Talking about the NBA,
I dare you, I double dare you,
Even with you're skinny woman
like Halle Berry.
Oh, now you're going to far.
You want violence frenchman, realy?
Do you want violence? Well, you got it
Put the gun down
Say I love America!
I love America,
Please don't kill me,
Sing the national anthem,
Not that one, man, sing the American one,
I don't know it.
Wait right here George,
Hulala! Lee,
Carter, stay focust! We're
looking for Jon Pierre,
Let's split up, I'll take the woman.
Carter, James Carter
I know you probably dont
understand a word I'm saying...
but I gotta tell you, you're the most
beautiful woman I ever seen in my life.
And I like to strip you down and butter
you like a slice of wonder bread,
And shave your arm pits, and put
honey all over your naked body,
And for the next two or three weeks
I wouldn't get hungry there,
Well, James Carter, I happend
to speak 6 lauguages.
Is one of'm english?
Are you in or not?
Money plays,
Sir, it's a 1000 Euros minimum.
How much I'm short?
930 Euros,
It's okay, let him play.
Thank you,
I'm looking for Jon Pierre,
Maybe I can help you.
Do you know what I hate about cops?
Even when they're with a woman...
they can't stop thinking
about getting their man
Who is Sai Xing?
See what I mean.
Come upstairs, cop I'll
give you what you want.
- Hit Me!
- Mister, this is Baccarat!
I know that,
You think I don't know
baccarat when i play it?
When I was a kid, my friends and I used to
hang out at a place called magic Johnson...
and we played baccarat all night long.
Now hit me.
Three kings... read'm and weep,
Three kings is a zero, you have the
worst possible hand, you lose
What?
Ahh... Madam has a seven, she wins
100,000 Euros, Bravo...
Mr. Carter, it's a pleasure,
you brought me luck,
I'm not here for some game,
Excuse me,
Way to go Lee!
Today my boy becomes a man.
Why are you helping me?
Maybe I'm helping myself,
How do I find Jon Piere?
I see you like to get right to it,
Do you know Shi Xing?
Would you like to know a secret, cop?
Yes, please.
Someone's gonna die here tonight
And it's you!
Come on buster, you don't hide
Do it, Lee,
Tear that ass up!
- You are a super freak!
- Carter!
Sorry!
- You got a boy friend?
- Carter!
Start that truck!
Go on!
Drive, fast!
Carter, look!
George, we need you to go faster, man.
No, forget it,
You want to kill me
then go ahead, kill me,
Drive faster!
Please, I'm scared
- George, you watch American movies?
- Yeah
Okay, man, alright,
listen, you're a superspy,
A superspy!
- Now drive this can, come on.
- Okay.
I'm a superspy.
Oh, George, go!
George, when I tell you to,
hit the breaks!
NOW!
Oh my god! Lee!
Back up!
Way to go, George!
It's okay.
I got this one!
Oh my leg!
Lee, help!
Hold him down!
Lee!
This is not my fight!
This is not...
Lee, my... my whole
life flashed in front of me.
In 3 years i've been married to
this American Chinese woman,
we had 3 kids, they just looked like you.
only they're adopted...
- Carter!
- What?
- Put your hands up,
- What're talking about!
Whou!
Some people say the modern wall was
invented when the French built these sewers,
10 million gallons pumped
through every hour,
A marvel that no one ever sees,
Welcome to Paris, Lee.
Lee, you know this guy?
Go on, Lee, tell him who I am...
Don't be shy...
Introduce him to your Xiong Di,
Xiong Di? Your brother!
He doesn't talk about me much...
In fact, he's spend his
whole life trying to forget me,
How would it look if Hong Kong's
great Inspector Lee...
had a brother on the
wrong side of the law?
You're not my brother anymore,
Are you forgetting about Chenzhou?
Yes, i forgot,
You spared my life in Los Angeles,
You could have shot me in that
alley. But you didn't pull the trigger.
because you can't escape your past.
I didn't kill you because
I'm not an assasin.
Let me repay the favor, Lee,
I allow you to live...
if you promise to leave Paris tonight.
You got yourself a deal...
thank you for showing us the sewer,
...listen, that's a bad ass suit,
let's get the hell out of here
What about Han and his daughter?
There's nothing i can do for them.
I have no choice.
Then I have no choice.
I guess he's staying, who wants
to take me to the airport?
We're always be brothers, Lee,
In this life and the next.
Tell me, Kenji, who is Shi Xing?
Some secrets are worth dying for,
Hold it, alright, okay,
Lee, what the hell is going on?
Shit, man, it's locked!
Over here,
We've got to jump!
Oh, it's a sewer, man, hell no Lee
- No choice
- I rather die
Come on!
I'm gonna kill you, Lee!
Welcome to the Patacy Inn,
how may I help you?
- Its great to see you again, its been to long.
- Yes, far to long Sir.
Listen, I need a big suite, two beds,
two showers...
a massage therepist, some new clothes,
and a case of Old Spice.
That's all your fault, how come
you didn't tell me about Kenji?
It was none of your business.
In case you missed it man,
he was trying to kill me.
I'm covered in shit, and some french cops
whooped my ass with yellow pages, man.
So don't tell me it's none of my business.
You're lucky,we're not in Hong Kong,
phonebook is twice as big.
Why didn't you tell me
you had a brother man?
Oh, hell, no... lady, your
damn dog just pissed on me.
Good girl.
Do you know what I think?
I think you feel sorry for this guy.
Maybe Kenji didn't get away in LA
Maybe you let him go.
The Aqusa killed his family in Tokyo.
He was send to China when he was seven.
He was put in Ching Zhou at the orphanage
where I was.
We kept each other alive.
You protected each other,
and you still protect him.
I called him Xiong Di,
he was like my brother.
- And then, I left him.
- You was adopted, what choice did you have?
He headed out on the streets.
You could never understand.
I understand man, I got a brother,
My little Brother Perry, we used to be
best friends, now we don't speak.
He thinks I took the cops out by
his chicken fights in his garage?
Do you believe that? My own
brother thinks I'm a snitch.
Just because my chicken lost, in the semi finals, I'm even a kid...
- Carter!
I had it fixed, we can find the
chicken and still make it's way.
And it still went the distance, it had
a lot'a heart, and it was delicious.
It's best if I do this on my own.
This fight is personal.
Let me help you, man, I'm telling you, what
ever the kid's telling you, it ain't true,
- He ain't your brother.
- And you're not my brother.
Fine, I'm not your brother.
Yes... I would like to order some fried chicken
please, oh, and some sweet potato pie, Merci.
Enjoy your Mushu Sir.
- Thank you. - Good bye.
- Oh...
- Hello Inspector.
- Hi, Mr. Raynard.
- They want to kill me, may I come in?
A dozend agent from the French secret
police have already been murdered...
only this last month, we're at war with
the Triads, right here in my own city.
Who is Shi Xing?
Ah, Sha Xing, Sha Xing is not a person, it's a list.
- A list?
Yes, every five years, the Triad bosses
come togather for an election.
And during that ceremony, they'll
choose the man who will lead the Triads.
Dragon Heads.
Yes,
13 Dragon Heads who control the largest criminal organization in the world. And the 13 names, are...
inscribe on the list known as Sha Xing, a secret that's
been handed down from generation to generation.
If the names from that
list, will ever to get out.
The secret society wouldn't
be so secret anymore.
They would all be ending up in jail or dead.
And the list is some where in Paris?
A young lady named Generieve,
made contact with Ambassador Han,
And we belief she know where it is.
I'm asking for your help, Inspector.
Finish what Ambassador Han started. Get to the
girl, before the Triads do, and you get (?).
- I don't know such, who are you?
- Who am I? I'm Bubbles, your new costume designer.
- Has anyone seen Goldie Hayes?
- She's has her own dressing room.
Wait... Bubbles, do we look ok?
No, no, no, these costumes are terrible.
Ladies please, we have work to do.
1st, I would dress the Blonde's...
and then the Brunnett's...
and finaly the highritz...
the Lord has truely blessed you all...
Would I mean this... trust me...
and some of you have what I like
to call... silver dollar potential.
- Lee, what're you doing here?
- What are you doing here?
- I found Generieve.
- So did I, they're trying to kill her.
- What?
- Look.
- Lee, you get the lights, I get the girl.
- Go.
- Your life is in danger!
- What the hell is going on?
You step into that spot light, it's the
last step you ever gonna take,
- They're gonna kill you right now!
- Who are you?
James Carter, L.A.P.D.
Sorry James, It's time for my solo
Get your hands off of me!
- Taxi! Taxi!
- Get in,
Go, go, go!
I've been looking for you all
day, my friend, we need to talk,
Forget it George, we're not paying
for any damages
Oh, no, no, no,
I don't want you to pay...
I want to ask, if I can drive for
you full time, no charge,
Why you want to drive for us?
Today was amazing,
The guns, the shooting, now I understand
what it is to be an American,
Please, I'm begging you,
let me be your driver!
Let me kill someone tonight!
- You never be American ok?
- I'll drink this shit all day if I have to
Just give me a chance,
Alright, fine, get us to the plaza fast
You got it, boss
Hold on!
So you think, she stole the
Sha Xing list from the Triad?
Only one way to find out!
You think what I'm thinking?
We need her to talk! Get her relaxed!
We can get some
wine from the mini bar
Maybe we should put on a dirty movie,
Lee!
Only 9.95!
This is our chance to find Sha Xing!
I'm going in!
What's wrong with you?
- Wait, let me go with you!
- Something's a man has do on his own,
You ok?
Can't mister, figure out what I have done?
I'm as good as dead!
You stole the list didn't you
you tryed to sell it to Han?
You don't get it!
I'm one of them!
And If I'm dead, you're dead!
Hey!
We're safe, no one know
we're here, just relax!
No one is safe,
I'm marked!
Trust me!
Why should I trust you?
As the Chinese say...
What does that mean?
A donkeys lips will not fit on a horses mouth,
I'm not sure I can relax,
Well, I was, thinking!
You have nice lips, that's all,
You safed my life today,
thank you, Carter!
Oh, please, call me james,
No one safed me in a long time!
How can I repay you!
You have 20 Bucks?
How about ten?
What?
I'm bad too - I'm a
bad girl - Haleluya
Don't you want to?
My nipples are sensitive be careful.
- I've never been with an American man before,
- Neither have I,
I feel so safe with you,
Do you want me?
- Once or twice and once in the shower,
- Oh yeah?
I'm going to bathroom,
make myself more comfortable,
Don't move, I'll be right back!
Hello, room service?
Get me a bottle of Honey and some RedBull,
Do you like it?
No wonderland is all soked and
all the way here to ride a bike...
Thank you,
Wait, baby, wait!
Oh yeah!
Freeze, don't move!
Damn!
- I'm sorry
- It's ok...
I'm ok!
So, we're even now, huh? Is that it?
I shoot your girl You shoot my girl
I tryed to save your life,
Couldn't you wait 5 minutes, we started
makeing love, man, and you ruined it
They will be coming for us, we
have to get out of here, now!
You see that?
We got to get out of here now, damn!
Lee, damn you!
Next time, I'll get my own damn room!
They have a problem! Get them out!
George! These people are dangeres,
There is something you should know
I'm not what you think I am!
Are you telling me, you're gay?
I'm try to tell you, I'm American spy
You're a spy?
Yeah, I'm working undercover with the
police we're about to break a big case!
Shut your mouth, George, you're nothing more then
a cab driver, just like your father was a cab driver,
What Kind of case could you crack,
Can't talk about it!
From this moment on!
Don't ever ask me, about my business!
Come with me, shmuck!
Now!
We need to get out of the city
We're not going anywhere,
untill you tell us exactly...
what's going on? Did you steal
that list from the Triats?
Generieve... we can not help you,
until you tell us the truth...
where is Sha Xing?
It's right here!
Holly mother Jesus! She's a Man!
I went to second base, with a damn
Frenchmen, It's a crying game
I broke my par!
I'm not the man, it's just a wig,
You sure about that?
Lee, go on check out her hardware
If she's got anything in her bag, bigger
then a 3 iron, I'm gonna beat his ass,
I'm a women, James, a women who needs
a way out... you have to help me,
You have Sha Xing?
No!
I'm Sha Xing!
In the ancient time, when
the Triads selected new leaders,
They would secretly tatoo the
names on to a women...
A women, who can carry the list of
Sha Xing, to the 35 borders of China
When the journey ended, and
the new leader was found...
the women would be beheaded,
and burried forever,
No records, no witness...
What the hell kind of tradition is that?
Have these guys never heard
of a goddamn fax machine?
Kenji told me do it, he
said it was a great honor.
I wanted to do it for him.
For the brotherhood.
Then why did you send
the names to Hun?
Because I thought the world
court could protect me.
But now I see.
Nobody can.
You're mixed up in some weird shit, lady.
I mean, man, whatever the hell you are.
I'm a woman.
And they will send an army to
kill me. To protect their way.
You know what? We can't
fight no army, Lee.
Who can protect me? I mean us.
I know a place.
I won't be here when
you come out. I'm sorry.
My wife says I can't be a spy.
And I have to be home for dinner.
Truth is I'm a cab driver. Nothing more.
This is my destiny.
I will never know what
it's like to be an American.
Never know what it feels
like to kill for no reason.
George, it's okay.
Thank you.
- And good luck.
- Good luck.
Mr. Raynard.
We have it.
The Sha Xing list, it's incredible.
Some people said it was a myth.
No, it's no myth, I've seen it, felt it,
kissed it, but I didn't french kiss it.
You do understand how dangerous this is.
We could always use some protection.
Can we go to the police?
The Triads control to many of them.
We have to get you out of the country.
Now my dear.
Would you mind taking off that wig...
and showing us Sha Xing.
We never told him that she was the list.
Look at that.
13 names and things, through
centuries of tradition.
The only real proof that
a secret world exists.
Shut her up
Get their guns.
I told you he was
bad, didn't I tell you?
Well, I was thinking it,
the explosion at the embassy.
As head of the world criminal court,
it would make sense
for me to be a target.
Why did you come to my room?
Geneviere was going to be killed.
Having you die in the crossfire
would put an end to the investigation.
Now, it will end another way.
It's over, Reynard.
You know what it's like
to be an old man in prison?
They call you pops.
They make you work in the library.
Your best friend, s'gonna be a mouse.
I'm not going to prison.
You have a phone call, Inspector.
Hello, brother.
I'd like to make a trade.
Some friends of mine came across
something in the Los Angeles.
Something very valuable.
Lee.
Help me please.
Do we understand each other?
What do you want?
Sha Xing.
You and Geneviere will
meet me alone tonight.
If I see you with any other cops...
the girl dies.
Where?
Jules Vaugh Restaurant.
Midnight.
Don't be late.
He brought the girl.
Send the elevator down.
Welcome to the party, Lee.
Tonight we celebrate
the return of Sha Xing...
and the return of my brother.
Where is Soo Yung.
This sword has a past.
Unlike our world, it has
seen much pain, much blood.
Hundreds of years ago, the
Triads would kill their enemies...
with 100 cuts to the body.
They would be very careful
to avoid any major arteries...
so that the victim would stay
alive for as long as possible.
You have just experience
to your first cut.
If anything happens to Soo Yung...
You can never kill me, Lee.
We both know that.
You know nothing about me.
I know you have no wife.
No children. No family.
Your life ended when you
were a kid back in Chenjo.
You have nothing... just like me.
I wouldn't say nothing.
He has me.
His brother from another mother.
Where is she?
Enjoy the view.
Soo Yung.
Help me.
Let her go.
What the hell is wrong with you?
Do you wanna die, Kenji?
Get her in here,
Carter, drop the gun,
Get off that damn brother, or I'll
shoot you and the damn temptations
Right now!
- Do it!
- Put her down, I'm serious
I'm not playing, you ain't my damn brother
Kenji - Drop
the gun. - No!
Drop it, Carter!
Shit
Tonight I lose a brother.
Get'm, man!
I'm gonna kick your ass, Kenji,
Come on, kill him already!
He might be your brother,
but turned out to be your sister,
Give me your hand,
Lee... Lee!
Jesus!
Hold on, I'm coming!
Lee!
Enough, Kenji!
Everybody comes for kungfu fighting.
Soo Yung?
What're you waiting for? Do it!
- Let go! We're both gonna die
- No, I can save you
- Good bye, Lee
- No, Kenji
Nooo...!
I'm coming Soo Yung!
My God,
Stay cool lady!
It doesn't have to end this way,
Don't do it... don't do it lady,
Don't you do it
Think about what you're doing?
Hey... Hey!
Would you like to know a secret?
No...
No!
- Lee, So Yung is up here,
- Soo Yung,
I'm ok.
Shit!
Yeah!
Lee, Reel me in,
Black people don't fly,
Pull... Pull it,
Lee! Get me out of here,
Thank you, Lee,
God...
Lee I'll kill you, when we get down...
Hang on!
I'm drowning
Hang on! Lee!
Carter! - What?
- I'm not constepated anymore,
Put your hand ups!
Genvieve!... Hey man you're the head of
the world court,
What you gonna do shoot us
down like animals?
We're police officer
- Yes, and you two, just killed this girl
Blew her brains out,
Carter!
- Don't do it,
Put the gun down,
- I follow'd you, Case Closed,
Good job man, come on!
Hey man, you touch me again
you gonna be dead in the movie,
Congratulation, it appears we finally
broke down the Traits,
We?
- You didn't do shit!
The Americans and the French need to work
together in the spirit of brotherhood...
together we can do anything,
Anything!
Yeah he's right, Lee,
together we can do anything,
You go this way and I go that way,
That right Lee, last 3 years I
study the Ancient teaching of Boody...
Cheese!
What? Oh Freeze!
As soon as she could
bring, the seafood secret
The seafood secret
I know seafood, I know secret, secret
see but when everything together