Help!
Anyone?
Hello, Michael.
I want to play a game.
So far,
in what could loosely be called your life,
you've made a living watching others.
Society would call you an informant,
a rat, a snitch.
I call you unworthy
of the body you possess,
of the life that you've been given.
Now we will see
if you are willing to look inward
rather than outward,
to give up the one thing you rely on
in order to go on living.
The device around your neck
is a death mask.
The mask is on a spring timer.
If you do not locate the key in time,
the mask will close.
Think of it like a Venus flytrap.
What you are looking at right now
is your own body
- not more than two hours ago.
- Oh, fuck.
Don't worry.
You're sound asleep and can't feel a thing.
Taking into account
that you are at a great disadvantage here,
I am going to give you a hint
as to where I've hidden the key.
So listen carefully.
The hint is this.
It's right before your eyes.
How much blood will you shed
to stay alive, Michael?
Live or die.
Make your choice.
Who the fuck are you?
Fuck! No!
No!
Someone help me!
Oh, fuck!
Do it.
Help me!
Help me! Please!
Fuck! What the fuck?
Please!
No, no, no, no, no, no!
- Excuse me.
- Help you?
I'm here for Daniel Matthews.
Sign these.
Thanks. Let's go, Daniel.
Took you long enough.
I'm sorry I didn't have it penciled in
on my schedule.
- They're gonna press charges, you know.
- Yeah. They're assholes.
Of course they are. You stole from them.
This works out great for me, though.
Your mother gets to keep custody.
I get to take you into custody.
What is it with you?
What, are you a tough guy
'cause you steal now?
Please, save me the after-school special.
- Why are you such a cop 24/7?
- Hey, it's called being a father.
Trust me, you're better at being a cop.
I just think
I should go back to Mom's early.
- What did you say?
- What, can you not hear me?
No, I can't hear you. Say it again.
- I think I should go back to Mom's...
- Well, then, go!
Jesus.
Hey, it's Daniel. Leave a message.
It's Dad. Sorry about yesterday.
Look, I haven't heard from you.
Would you give me a call, please?
Daniel.
Oh, sorry, Sarge.
I thought you were my son.
Yeah. I'll be right there.
What do you got?
County asbestos cleaners
were working on a deadline.
One of them finds a body, calls it in.
Says that this whole section's
been abandoned for two years.
We've spotted people down here, though.
- Who?
- Well, homeless, mostly.
Bunch of kids held a rave
in the boiler room about two months back.
- Get an estimate on the time of death?
- Forensics just got here.
But it was the arriving officer
who called it in as your buddy.
He wasn't my buddy. He was an informant.
This officer IDed him
just by looking at him?
Well, he wasn't positive.
- That's why I wanted you here.
- All right.
Well, let me get a look at his face.
I'll tell you in two seconds if it's him or not.
Therein lies the problem.
Yeah, it's Mike.
When were you gonna tell me about that?
Thought you'd wanna see it for yourself.
Okay. Well, I saw it.
All right, look. I mean, it's a little early,
but so far
everything matches Jigsaw's pattern.
I can see that. What do you want with me?
All right, let's just pretend for a second
that this is new to us, all right?
Can you think of anyone
that would wanna do this to your guy?
Well, he's an informant, Kerry.
You want a list of possible suspects?
Grab a phone book.
Crackhead county punks
don't have engineering degrees.
Now, I'd say that our cause of death here
narrows that list down just a little bit,
wouldn't you?
Sure. And you're the expert.
Look closer, Detective Matthews.
At what?
Ask whoever wrote it.
Hello, Michael.
I want to play a game.
So far,
in what could loosely be called your life,
you've made a living watching others.
You know, you and that guy
have a lot in common, Kerry.
- Oh, yeah?
- Yeah.
- You both like playing games with people.
- Excuse me?
Don't ever pull some shit like that again
on me at a crime scene.
- Look, I'm not the one taunting you. He is.
- Doesn't mean I have to take the bait.
- Besides, I got a full caseload as it is.
- A bunch of desk errands and shit work.
Yeah, well, between that,
IA breathing down my neck,
my son's budding criminal career
and my wife's fucking divorce lawyers,
I'd say my hands are pretty full,
wouldn't you?
Yeah. Look, I'm sorry.
I was hoping, maybe,
that I could bring you in on this one.
We're not partners anymore, Kerry.
Hey, forget that we're not partners.
What about the fact that this guy wrote
your fucking name on the wall, huh?
He asked for you.
It's not the first time
some psychopath called me out.
All right.
What about the fact that I'm asking?
Can't help you.
- Wow.
- You're the Jigsaw expert.
When did you stop being a cop?
Look closer, Detective Matthews.
This guy wrote your fucking name
on the wall.
Look closer, Detective Matthews.
He asked for you.
All right, fellas. Listen up.
These are the best entry points.
They're the ones with direct street frontage,
vehicle access and good cover.
Now, remember,
we're doing this in broad daylight.
We don't wanna scare any civilians.
Look, I've been there before.
I know the location.
Let's just bust in there
and scare the shit out of anyone
who happens to be inside, okay?
We're going in teams of three.
I'll go with Team Alpha.
Just like the good old days, huh?
I thought your caseload
was big enough as it is.
I'm just tagging along for the ride.
Go, go, go, go, go.
Check the back. Secure the back.
- Go around.
- I got it, I got it.
Alpha Team, I want you in front.
Baker, flank the side.
All right, let's do this.
Go, go, go.
Keep moving, keep moving.
Freeze!
What the fuck?
Officer down! Officer down!
The fucking place is wired!
Fuck this! Baker Team, get in here now!
- All right, go, go! Go!
- Baker Team, get in now!
Guys.
Talk to me, guys.
Go. Go.
Officer down. Okay.
Stand back.
Move him out. Move him out.
Clear. Clear.
Stand back.
Move out!
Repeat.
Freeze! Don't move!
Let me see your hands.
I'm not gonna ask again.
Put your hands where I can see them.
Down on your knees!
- Down on your knees!
- I'm afraid I can't do that.
Get him in restraints now.
You have the right to remain silent.
You have the right to an attorney.
If you can't afford one,
one will be appointed to you by the City.
He's clean.
Hey.
Is this close enough?
Get his ass out of here.
Actually, I will need to remain here
while you deal with your problem,
Detective Matthews.
- What problem?
- The problem in that room.
You keep him secure.
Clear.
Shit.
- What?
- I don't know.
Shit.
I think that's my son.
Fuck.
He's got my son.
What the fuck is that?
Hey! Hey! What the fuck is that?
It's your son, Daniel.
You remember him, don't you?
I know who he is, you piece of shit.
What is he doing on that fucking monitor?
Well, I haven't looked at the monitors
for some time,
so it would be hard for me to say,
but I would imagine
that he's cowering in a corner
with a look on his face...
- You motherfucker!
- No, Eric. Wait.
You motherfucker!
Where is he? Where is he?
Where is he?
That's a problem you're gonna
have to solve before it's too late.
He has about two hours
before the gas
creeping into his nervous system
begins to break down his body tissue
and he begins to bleed
from every orifice he has.
Oh, yes. There will be blood.
Tell me where he is.
He's in a safe place.
- Eric.
- I need a phone.
- Eric, just listen to me for a second.
- Just give me a phone!
- Look, everything about this fits his profile.
- I need to be sure.
You've reached Daniel's phone.
He's not in right now, but if you'd leave...
I'm sorry.
We have something
counting down over here.
Get me bomb squad, now.
Hey.
Hey, wake up.
Can you hear me?
She's still breathing.
What is this, house arrest?
- Are we in jail?
- No.
- This ain't jail, man.
- Oh, yeah? You done a lot of time?
Yeah. Too much.
- Somebody open the fucking door!
- I don't think anybody's listening.
Damn. What the fuck is this?
Somebody's listening.
No.
Those types of cameras don't have sound.
Fuck!
How do you just wake up in a room
and have no idea where you are?
I guess you never been drunk before.
I've been drunk.
I spent three years at college drunk.
This isn't drunk. This is kidnapping.
Look, I saw this movie on TV last week.
This guy, he was a reporter,
and he goes into this war zone, right?
He goes in to sleep in his hotel room
the first night.
Bam! He wakes up the next morning,
he's in a cell with no windows and no light.
And he spent nine years in that room.
Nine years?
Man, that's nothing. Get over it.
What do you mean, "get over it"?
I mean, stop bitching about it
and let's do something.
- I think we should all just calm down.
- Shut up! Shut up!
I hear something.
What is it?
It's ticking. I hear ticking.
Hey, hey, hey. Calm down. Calm down.
What's your name?
Amanda.
- Where am I?
- I don't know.
Nobody knows.
We all just woke up here like you.
No!
- No!
- No, it's okay.
No!
- What?
- Fuck!
What?
What are you looking for?
What is this?
Everything you need to know is on this.
Greetings and welcome.
I trust that you are all wondering
where you are.
I can assure you
that while your location is not important,
what these walls offer for you is important.
Salvation, if you earn it.
Three hours from now,
the door to this house will open.
Unfortunately,
you only have two hours to live.
Right now,
you are breathing in a deadly nerve agent.
You've been breathing it
since you arrived here.
Those of you
familiar with the Tokyo subway attacks
will know its devastating effects
on the human body.
The only way to overcome it
and walk out that door
is to find an antidote.
Several are hidden around this house.
One is inside the safe in front of you.
You all possess
the combination to the safe.
Think hard.
The numbers are in the back of your mind.
The clue to their order can be found
over the rainbow.
Once you realize
what you all have in common,
you will gain a better understanding
of why you're here.
"X" marks the spot for that clue,
so look carefully.
Let the game begin.
- Who is this?
- What does he mean, gas?
- And how did you know where to find this?
- This is bullshit.
"Do not attempt to use this key
on the door to this room. "
Fuck this, man.
- Yeah, fuck this. That's a good idea.
- No, no.
- That's not a good idea.
- So what are we gonna do, huh?
- Sit here?
- The note said not to use the key.
Who gives a shit about the note, all right?
This is all a fucking big goddamn joke,
and I'm about to end it.
You better start talking right now.
- What is this?
- It's a game.
It ain't no fucking game!
My man just got his head blown off.
- He's testing us.
- Who's testing us?
Jigsaw.
- Who the hell is Jigsaw?
- You don't watch the fucking news?
- No. Who is he?
- He's a serial killer.
No, he's not.
He's testing us. He wants us to survive this.
But you have to play by the fucking rules!
I'm gonna ask you again.
How do you know all this?
Because I've played before.
I want a tech team in here now.
Find out where that feed is coming from.
What do you want with me?
- A little of your time, Detective.
- I don't have any time.
You asked me what I wanted,
and I told you.
Believe me when I tell you
your son is in a lot of trouble.
And what if I give you
a little bit of my time? What then?
I only wanna talk to you.
Everyone else must leave.
- Those are my conditions.
- No. It's a crime scene. Nobody leaves.
They don't have to leave the building.
They just have to leave this area
long enough for me to talk to you.
If you agree to that,
then you will see your son again.
If I don't see my son again, I swear to God
I'll rip your fucking head off.
I don't intend to mock you, Officer,
but I'm a cancer patient.
How could you possibly put me
in any more pain than I'm already in?
Just get them here now.
All right, tech team's on the way.
Should have your signal traced
within an hour, maybe two.
He said he wants to talk to me alone.
- Well, maybe you should talk to him.
- Well, fuck that.
Five minutes, old-school method.
He's not gonna respond to
the phone-book treatment. You know that.
Don't underestimate
a tried and true method here.
I am the one who has been working
on this case from day one.
I have been spending every waking moment
piecing it together.
Maybe that's why
you ain't got a goddamn family for yourself
and you can't understand
what this man is going through.
- Don't.
- Look...
I don't wanna talk to him.
Listen, you already lost your son
one time before
because you got involved with me.
It's not gonna happen again.
This is bullshit.
What are we gonna do?
Just humor him. Buy us a little more time.
You can win this, Eric. You can beat him.
- Come on.
- All right.
...find an antidote.
Several are hidden around this house.
One is inside the safe in front of you.
You all possess
the combination to the safe.
Think hard.
The numbers are in the back of your mind.
The clue to their order can be found...
Shit.
Hey, wait a minute. Where you going?
I'm gonna find an antidote,
and I'm gonna get out of here.
What? Antidote? You been in the joint.
You talked to the guards
that run the chambers.
You know there ain't no antidote
for this shit.
Look at this. The doors are locked.
You hear that? It's wood.
Plaster. It's not a fortress.
It's a fucking house.
All I'm saying is let's just take our time
and come up with a game plan.
Well, you come up with the game plan.
All right? I'm getting out of here.
Look.
- You okay?
- Yeah, I'm fine.
I wouldn't do that if I was you.
You don't know
what's behind that fucking door.
Fuck.
Shit.
Clear the room.
Okay. Let's talk.
Sit down, Eric.
I want to play a game.
The rules are simple.
All you have to do is sit here
and talk to me,
listen to me.
If you do that long enough,
then you will find your son
in a safe and secure state.
We haven't been properly introduced.
My name's John.
- I thought you liked to be called Jigsaw.
- No, no.
It was the police and the press
who coined the nickname Jigsaw.
I never encouraged or claimed that.
The jigsaw piece I cut from my subjects
was only ever meant to be a symbol
that that subject was missing something.
A vital piece of the human puzzle.
The survival instinct.
This is all really, really interesting, John,
but right now
I'd really like for you to talk to me...
I am talking to you.
You're not listening.
- Don't forget the rules.
- I'm listening to you,
but all I'm hearing
is the same sick fucking bullshit
that comes about two seconds
into every interview I've ever done
with one of you fucking people.
Well, that's an interesting approach
to police work, isn't it?
Aren't you supposed to be convincing me
that I'm your friend,
lulling me into a false sense of security
so that I'll confide in you?
It's a little hard to follow the manual
when you've got my son, John.
The manual?
What do you really wanna do to me
right now, huh?
What would you have done
five years ago, huh?
Would you have followed the manual then?
Would you have broken my jaw
with a flashlight?
You seem to know a whole lot about me.
I know you were once considered
a fearless police officer.
Do you feel a whole lot safer
now that you only sit behind a desk?
I feel a whole lot of things right now.
But you feel alive. That's what you feel.
And that's the point.
Would you
kindly get me a glass of water?
I would very much appreciate that.
Fuck!
Well, we've established
that the macho-bullshit approach
isn't opening the door.
- Any other suggestions?
- Look who's talking.
The only door you know how to open
is between your legs.
- Why don't you shut the hell up, all right?
- Come on, man.
- Why don't you shut the hell up?
- I'm sick of your bullshit.
- That's right, back up, bitch!
- You little dickhead.
- Asshole!
- Hey!
What you gonna do?
Yeah, yeah, that's right, back up!
Okay, man. All right.
Nobody take shit from nobody.
We've established that.
- Did you find anything?
- No. Nothing.
So, that ink on your arm,
that's Joliet, right?
Yeah. So?
- Well, I did a stretch there myself.
- I'm proud of you.
And you,
what is your correctional facility of choice?
What's your point?
My point is, you didn't get that way
by teaching grade school, right?
That makes three of us that's done time.
I think we should be concentrating
on that tape,
'cause that tape said
we have more in common than we know.
I say the three of us doing stretches...
Hey! I found a door over here.
I need the flashlight.
Over there.
What the fuck?
Oh, shit!
Hey!
- Damn, kid.
- Sorry.
- "Obi. "
- What the fuck is a Obi?
Obi. It's my name.
Hello, Obi. I want to play a game.
For years,
you have burned those around you
with your lies, cons and deceits.
Now you'll have a chance
to redeem yourself
for the games you've played with others
by playing one of mine.
Inside the device in front of you
are two antidotes
for the poison
coursing through your veins.
One is my gift to you
for helping me kidnap the others.
The second is yours to donate.
However,
one of them will come with a price.
Remember, Obi,
once you are in hell,
only the devil can help you out.
Wait a minute.
What does that mean, "kidnap the others"?
- How would I know?
- Because you put us here.
The car.
It was...
I knew I knew him.
You're the last person I saw
before I woke up here.
You did this.
Are you sure it's him? You better be sure.
I'm sure.
You would have done the same.
I did what I had to do.
I'll give you a choice.
- You got five seconds to get us out of here.
- I don't know the way out.
Bullshit! You put us in here.
You can get us out of here.
No, I can't.
- Then you're a dead man.
- So are you.
He's not gonna... Wait, wait, wait, wait!
Wait, listen to me.
Okay, we got two antidotes
at the back of that oven.
- We're wasting time here.
- Wasting time? Are you kidding me?
He kidnapped me in the middle of the night.
We don't even know
what's in those syringes.
You willing to stick yourself in the arm
to find out?
Okay, wait. So who gets them?
I mean, there's two.
So which two people get the antidote?
We'll work that out later!
Right now you're going in there
or I'll kill you where you stand.
Shit.
If you're gonna threaten me with a knife,
you may as well cut me a little.
I guess I'm going in there
to get those needles.
But I get one.
- One for me.
- Hurry up.
Come on, baby.
You guys can fight over this one.
Thank you, Obi.
Come on.
- Oh, shit. The fucking door closed!
- Open the door!
Open the door!
It's locked. I can't open it.
Open the fucking door! Not funny!
Come on! Get him out of there!
The door!
The nail!
I can't get it open!
- Get him out of there!
- Not funny!
Use your coat! Use your fucking coat!
- Come on! He's burning up!
- Stop it!
- Come on!
- Turn! Turn!
Stop it.
- You gotta put your weight on it.
- Stop it.
My man's dying!
Guys, there's a window over here.
- He's got the antidote.
- Stop it!
Get him out.
- Hurry!
- Get it open.
- Fuck!
... glass or something.
- Stop it!
- Hang on, man. We're gonna get you out.
Shit.
Stop it! Stop it! Stop it! Stop it! Stop it!
Get out of the fucking way!
Go on, move! Move!
Here. Shit! Come on!
The needles!
He ain't got the fucking needles!
It's fucking in there!
I want the fucking needles!
Calm down.
- Fuck!
- The needles are fucking melted.
They're gone.
He had a choice.
Another one down, Kerry.
How much more time are we gonna waste
on this bastard?
We're not wasting time.
We're doing exactly what we should be
doing until the tech team gets here.
It's not what it looks like to me.
You see, Detective,
Darwin's theory of evolution
and survival of the fittest,
based on his little trip to the Galápagos,
no longer applies on this planet.
We have a human race
that doesn't have the edge
or the will to survive.
- What the fuck do you want?
- It's hard to remain calm, isn't it,
when your son is walking around
on those monitors?
I can't give you what you want
if you don't tell me what the fuck it is.
I told you what it is.
- Just remember the rules.
- No, you said you wanted to talk.
Then you said you wanted to play a game.
You're talking, but it means nothing!
What do you think
the cure for cancer is, Eric?
- What?
- The cure for cancer.
- What is it?
- I don't know what it is,
but I know
it's not killing and torturing people
for your own sick fucking pleasure.
I've never murdered anyone in my life.
The decisions are up to them.
Yeah, well,
putting a gun to someone's head
and forcing them to pull the trigger
is still murder.
Since when is force a problem for you?
Why are you so desperate
to get your son back?
'Cause he's my son.
What's the last thing you said to him
before you left him?
Well, then, go!
Seems to me that the knowledge
of your son's impending death
is causing you to act.
Forgive all his sins,
to wipe the slate clean...
Why is it that we're only willing to do that
when a life is at stake?
I've always loved my son.
That's never changed.
No, no. It's changed now.
You see, the knowledge of death
changes everything.
If I were to tell you the exact date
and time of your own death,
it would shatter your world completely.
I know.
Can you imagine what it feels like
to have someone sit you down...
John Kramer.
...and tell you that you're dying?
The gravity of that?
That the clock's ticking for you.
In a split second,
your world is cracked open.
You look at things differently.
You smell things differently.
You savor everything, be it a glass of water
or a walk in the park.
The clock is ticking, John.
But most people have the luxury
of not knowing
when that clock's gonna go off,
and the irony of it is that
that keeps them from really living their life.
It keeps them sleepwalking.
It keeps them drinking that glass of water,
but never really tasting it.
You can still fix this, John.
Yeah, but can we fix you?
Me?
I'm not fixable.
I've got cancer.
You're using cancer as an excuse
for what you do?
No.
The cancer isn't what started me
in my work.
It was the moment I decided to end my life
that started me in my work
and brought meaning to it.
Fuck!
I had literally driven myself to suicide,
and I had failed.
My body had not been strong enough
to repel cancer cells,
yet I had lived through a plunge off a cliff.
But, to my amazement, I was alive.
And I was determined
to spend the rest of my days
testing the fabric of human nature.
Do you understand, Eric?
You got a chance to do something.
Do it right now, John.
Just tell me where my son is.
I'll help you.
I don't need your help,
and I can tell you still don't understand.
Those who don't appreciate life
do not deserve life.
My son appreciates his life.
But do you appreciate yours?
Do you appreciate your son's?
Oh, this is shit!
Don't forget the rules
if you wanna find your son.
Where are you?
No. No, we don't have 15 minutes.
We need that location to the video feed.
Hey. I don't think we should stop, okay?
Laura, can you hear me?
That's the second time
I've had to wake up in this shithole.
Think you can stand up?
Yeah, but I don't really want to.
There's so much left to do.
So many people left to talk to.
This can't be it.
It's not.
- Amanda, you said you survived this, right?
- I what?
This guy, whoever's doing it,
you said that you've played before
and you survived.
Yeah.
So that means we could survive.
Wait. Amanda, why did he pick you?
Because I was a fucking junkie.
And the funny thing is,
I passed his little test.
If you passed his test,
then why are you back here?
I wasn't being very good to myself.
- How long have you...
- I started in jail.
- What were you arrested for?
- Possession.
But I thought you said that...
Maybe you should talk
to the cop who arrested me.
I'm guessing
you've never been arrested before.
No.
I mean, I've been in trouble a few times,
you know, in and out of stuff.
My dad's a...
He's a real hardass.
You know, he's probably got half the city
right now looking for me
just so he can kick my ass
for disappearing on him.
Yeah.
Probably.
We found a door. Come on.
Come on. We have to go.
It's the only one without a lock,
but we can't get it open.
- How's it going?
- It's stuck on something.
Oh, shit.
- Here, let me try. Move, move! Come on.
- Will you take it easy? Jesus!
Just back up, all right?
If it's stuck, it's a trap.
Lady, this whole house is a trap.
Obviously someone didn't want us
to get into this room.
- Now what?
- I'm gonna be right back, okay?
Whatever we do,
we got four minutes to get it done.
Hello, Xavier. I want to play a game.
The game I want to play is very similar
to the one that you've been playing
as a drug dealer.
The game of offering hope to the desperate
for a price.
I think we can agree
that your situation is desperate.
So I offer you hope.
The price you pay is that you must crawl
into the same pit of squalor
you force your customers into.
- By entering this room...
- Oh, my God.
...a timer has been started.
When the timer expires, the door
in front of you will be locked forever.
- Only in finding the key...
- Guys? Guys.
- What?
- Look.
...before the timer runs out
can you unlock it
- and retrieve the antidote inside.
- Oh, my God.
I will give you just one hint
as to where that key is.
It will be like finding a needle
in a haystack.
Let the game begin.
Somebody's going in there.
Now, look,
somebody's fucking going in there, man.
No! No! No!
- Oh, shit.
- What the fuck are you doing?
- Stop.
- What are you doing?
- No! No!
- What the fuck are you doing?
- No! No! Please!
- Let her go now.
No!
Shit!
My God.
Come on!
- We don't have time!
- Oh, shit.
What the fuck's wrong with you?
What are you doing?
- You're out of your fucking mind.
- Hurry up.
Oh, shit!
Come on!
We don't have time.
Keep fucking looking.
- Come on! Come on!
- Fuck you!
What the fuck?
Somebody's gotta help her.
What the fuck, guys?
Fuck!
No. No. No. No.
No!
No. No!
Come on.
No, no, no.
- You fucking bitch!
- All right. That's enough.
That's not nearly enough, man.
Stop this bullshit.
Did you hear that tape?
He knows about us. Our names.
There's something that we're not seeing.
Jail.
You said you three had been there.
Make it four.
- For what?
- Doesn't matter.
Anybody else wanna own up?
What about you?
You got juvie written all over you.
No, never been.
All right.
- Let's talk this out.
- No.
No more talking.
The only thing you people have in common
is holding me back.
I'm gone.
- Where is this goddamn tech team?
- They'll be here any second.
I'm not listening to this anymore.
- Another second is too fucking long.
- Look, I know how this guy works, okay?
He's playing a game.
Eric just needs to stay in it
a little bit longer.
Take a look at the clock.
You need to start thinking outside the box,
or his son is gonna end up in one.
His work.
You wanna get to him, that's how you do it.
I mean, he's relishing this.
It's an opportunity to be heard,
to be studied.
Threaten to destroy his work.
How will you get your conviction
without all this evidence, Eric?
I don't need this shit to convict you.
So go ahead. Destroy it.
- I will.
- Destroy it all.
Just know it will not save your son
if you do.
You kill my son, I kill you.
Go ahead.
Why wait? We both know
the sort of person you are, sir.
- Get out of here.
- The sort of person
who guns down an unarmed suspect.
In fact,
the sort of person who plants evidence
in order to obtain a conviction.
The sort of person whose wife leaves him
and whose son hates him.
Shut the fuck up!
- Okay, set up all the traces to the satellite.
- Let's go.
Your tech team's arrived.
Just in time.
You better hope
they find the source of that feed.
There's something I haven't told you, Eric.
I'm done listening to you.
Maybe I can just show it to you.
But, unfortunately, it's going to be difficult
for me to get it myself,
so perhaps you could ask the people
who are listening on that walkie in there
if they could get it for me, all right?
Brown desk.
Second drawer down.
You may not remember all those people,
but I'm sure they remember you.
You were the arresting officer
in all of their cases,
and you were the one
who planted all the evidence
used to obtain their convictions.
You were the one who put them away.
Your son is playing a game
with a lot of people
who don't like you very much, Detective.
It would be a shame
if they discovered who he was.
You all possess
the combination to the safe.
Think hard.
The numbers are in the back of your mind.
The clue to their order can be found
over the rainbow.
Son of a bitch.
- What are you doing?
- I haven't decided yet.
You know, the others,
they're scared of you.
Good.
You and me,
we can keep going at each other
like we're back in the yard,
or we can come together
and figure out who's doing this to us.
You and the others can do what you want.
I already found what I'm looking for.
You remind me of me.
No matter
what kind of fucked-up situation you're in,
you always gotta find yourself an enemy.
You know what? I got enemies, man.
Outside these fucking walls, bro.
And they're looking for me.
And if they don't find me,
they're going after the ones closest to me.
My family.
You understand?
No.
I don't understand.
It's just me, and that's the way I like it.
Now, turn around.
- What?
- Turn around.
Oh, shit.
- No. We can't stop.
- Shit.
Oh, my God.
We've been here for two hours.
If what that tape says is true,
then in one hour, the front door will open.
We're not gonna make it that long.
That's a real winning attitude.
She knows what she's talking about.
Oh, yeah?
"X" marks the spot.
What?
"X" marks...
Marks the spot.
There's the answer.
What are you doing with him?
This is your father?
- What? You know him?
- Yeah.
He's the guy who put me away.
He set me up.
Tell me that's not your father.
It's okay. It's okay.
I can't trust any of you.
You two are on your own.
Now we know what we have in common.
Amanda, please. I didn't know.
Hey, kid! Amanda!
Where are you?
Please don't leave me.
We gotta move.
Hey, kid!
Amanda!
I found a way out.
Eight.
Hey, kid!
Do not run.
Eric. Eric.
No! Stop!
Get off of me!
We tried it your way.
You motherfucker! Where is he?
Eric.
Damn it.
I'd like to go now
until your son is pissing blood.
Now, that's the Eric Matthews
they gave medals to.
Help!
Help me!
Oh, my God.
Jonas.
Help me! Help me!
Help!
Please.
It's okay.
- Help me.
- It's okay.
No. No.
No!
Fucker!
Amanda.
Nobody's listening anymore, asshole.
Open your mouth. Open your mouth!
Come on.
There you go.
You gonna tell me where he is now, huh?
What?
Say it again.
Game over.
I'll take you to the house.
You're gonna take me right now.
Right now.
I will only take you.
No one else.
All right. Just me and you.
- How do we get out of here?
- There's a button on the wall.
You'd better hurry.
There's not much time left.
- The elevator!
- Come on!
Fuck!
Secure the warehouse now!
- All right, let's go! Go! Go, go, go!
- Damn it.
We've got a lock.
This is Kerry. They're both gone.
If I don't find my son, I swear to God...
Kerry, they're gone.
Fucking gone.
Yes! Kerry. We got a lock.
We got a lock on the house.
- Rigg, we got it.
- What?
237 North Hyde Crescent.
- That's North Hyde Crescent.
- 237 North Hyde Crescent. Got it.
Where to now?
Straight ahead.
Come on, come on. Where are you?
Make a right on Alfred.
Open the fucking door!
Open the door!
There's nowhere to go.
All I want is the number
on the back of your head.
There's nowhere to go! Come on, Amanda!
I can't hold it.
Come on! Let me in!
Let me in!
Open the door! Come on!
What do we do?
Take a left at the next street.
It's the last house on the left.
Oh, shit.
Shit!
Come on!
Come on, Amanda!
- Amanda, what is it?
- It's a door.
It's a fucking door.
You have nowhere to go!
Come on!
Help me move this thing.
I'm not gonna hurt you.
Come on, Amanda!
Shit, it's locked!
Let me in!
Come on, open the door!
Come on!
The key.
The one we found with the tape recorder.
Where is it? Where is it?
Fuck!
Jonas. Jonas had it last.
- Come on, Amanda!
- Find it! Hurry!
Come on!
Come on, open the door!
Let me in!
Eric, you're gonna need this key
when you get inside the house.
Where the hell are we?
Run! Run!
Daniel?
Daniel!
Daniel, we gotta go!
- We gotta go! Come on!
- Run.
All right, come on.
Let's go. Let's go. Let's go.
Let's go, let's go, let's go!
Go, go, go!
- Hallway's clear.
- We're in.
Daniel!
- The ground floor is secure.
- Moving up. Moving up.
Kerry, we're in the house.
I repeat, we're in the house.
Cannot see you, Sergeant.
Repeat, cannot see you.
Repeat. I cannot see you.
- Where the hell is everybody?
- What is your 20?
Rigg, do you copy?
Hello, Mr. Hindle.
Follow your heart.
I really wish I had checked in there first.
What the fuck is this?
My name is very fucking confused.
What's your name?
I'm gonna kill your husband now,
Mrs. Gordon.
He doesn't want us
to cut through our chains.
What are you doing to me? No!
He wants us to cut through our feet.
No! Oh, my God!
It hurts!
No!
Daniel!
Daniel, no. Don't leave me.
Please.
He's gone.
Doesn't matter.
All I want is the number
on the back of his neck.
And then yours.
You still don't know your own number.
How are you gonna get it if I don't tell you?
Daniel!
Shit.
Run!
Fuck.
Daniel?
I still cannot see you, Sergeant.
Rigg, do you copy?
- Left side clear.
- Right side clear.
All clear.
I still can't see you, Sergeant.
I repeat, cannot see you.
It's not live.
Kerry, we're in the wrong fucking house!
They've been dead this whole fucking time.
- Get your team out of there.
- Let's go.
Daniel?
Daniel.
Hello, Eric.
You probably don't even remember me,
but you changed my life once.
You sent me to prison.
I was guilty of a lot of things,
but not the drug charge you framed me for.
You wouldn't know the things you lose
when you're locked away.
The second time
somebody changed my life, I was guilty.
Hello, Amanda.
But my life was saved that day.
- You said you survived this, right?
- Yeah.
I found myself a father, a leader, a teacher.
You must meet death
in order to be reborn.
He helped me.
What is the cure for cancer, Eric?
Those who don't appreciate life
do not deserve life.
The cure for death itself?
The answer is immortality.
Daniel!
By creating a legacy,
by living a life worth remembering,
you become immortal.
So now you find the tables are turned.
He asked for you.
- What the fuck do you want?
- I told you.
He wants us to survive this.
I want to play a game.
You have to play by the fucking rules!
The rules are simple.
All you have to do is sit here
and talk to me.
What?
If you can do that long enough,
you will find your son
in a safe and secure state.
What the fuck is that?
It's your son, Daniel.
You remember him, don't you?
My dad's a...
He's a real hardass.
I call you unworthy
of the life that you've been given.
The knowledge
of your son's impending death
has caused you to forgive all his sins.
Why is that we're only willing to do that
when a life is at stake?
Daniel!
I'm done listening to you.
Don't forget the rules.
Shut the fuck up!
He's playing a game.
I don't wanna talk to him.
You're not saying shit.
We both know the sort of person you are.
I'd like to go now
until your son is pissing...
I'll take you to the house.
Daniel?
There's something I haven't told you, Eric.
It is I who will carry on John's work
after he dies.
Daniel!
So go ahead. Destroy it.
And you...
Daniel!
...are my first test subject.
Now you are locked away,
helpless and alone.
- You fucking bitch.
- Game over.
I'll fucking kill you!
You fucking bitch!
No!