Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org
Welcome to WWE City.
Take the next exit because
it's just that good.
I'm The Miz, and I'm awesome.
Who's awesome? I'm awesome.
Who's awesome? I am... uhh!
Kane, you're back.
I thought we'd never see you again
after you lost that last match.
Not that I agreed with the decision.
Not the face. Not the face.
Not the face.
Welcome to WWE City.
Take the next exit because
it's just that good.
Whoa!
Oof!
Yeah, that's what I'm talking about.
You keep on going, Kane.
You're lucky! You got
off easy this time.
Who's awesome? I'm awesome.
Who's awesome...
Who's in there?
Is that you, Kane?
Come on. Come on out and get some.
Uhh!
That all you got, Yogi?
Uhh! Uhh!
My... my face!
Welcome to WWE City.
Take the next exit because
it's just that good.
Good.
Really?
Ahh! No! No!
Unnecessary roughness.
Captioning made possible by Warner bros.
Animation
Look out. John Cena is the
doctor of Thundernomics.
Ha ha ha.
He can't see me.
You can't see me at all.
Like, no one can touch John Cena.
Sin Cara can.
Scooby Dooby-doo!
1, 2, 3.
Sin Cara wins it.
Way to go, Scooby-Doo, old buddy.
Booyah. Dooby-doo.
Congratulations.
You just beat the game on
the hardest level ever...
double triple beatdown extreme.
But can you complete
the victory dance?
Oh, yeah.
It's all yours, pal. You earned it.
Perfect score!
Whoo-hoo!
Hello there. I'm Vince McMahon,
chairman and CEO of WWE.
Mr. McMahon.
We're not worthy.
Because you beat the
game on this level
and executed a perfect score on the
victory dance, you win a special prize.
We did?
You've won an all-expense
paid trip to WWE City.
Come revel in a place
dedicated to everything WWE.
It'll be a week of
fun and excitement,
culminating in ringside seats
at Wrestlemania. Don't miss it.
Report to training camp in WWE City
as soon as possible with this game disc
as proof of your win to claim your prize.
Like, Wrestlemania.
Ha ha ha!
You gotta be kidding me.
Think of it.
The fun.
The fans.
The food!
We gotta go, old pal.
Like, we just gotta go.
We gotta go.
It's the ultimate slamtastic
life-affirming experience of a lifetime.
It's Wrestlemania.
Yeah. Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Uh, I don't know, guys. It's not
something we're really into.
And I have a lot of
reading to catch up on.
Uh, no, thank you.
Like, come on, guys.
Scoob and I never ask for anything.
Like, I can't count how many times
the two of us were bait to catch
some crazy mask-wearing villain.
Yeah.
I got the photos to prove it.
Take a good look, people.
Exhibit "A." Like, here's the time
you guys made us dress like giant tools
to catch the monstrous mechanic.
Or as ducks to catch
the horrific huntsman.
Or when we had to be the cow to catch the
crazed cowgirl from beyond the grave.
Scooby-Doo almost got milked.
It was so humiliating.
And the Piéce De Résistance,
the time we posed
as señor Pepe Jose
and the dancing hairless
Chihuahua Don Pero
to catch the ghastly
Gordito of Guadalajara.
Yeah, the hair didn't even
grow back in some places.
Scooby was naked.
Look at him.
Just look at him!
No, no. Ok.
We get it.
You win, Shaggy.
Win? Wait, what?
I was actually thinking
about taking a trip anyway
to try out my new allodium
Q-36 digital SLR camera
and optical stabilizer zoom lens.
Maybe I can snap some
action-packed pictures.
And this will give
me an opportunity
to explore the parallels between
the modern world of WWE
vs. Ancient warrior customs.
Besides, it beats another
weekend with grandpa Dinkley
and his mysterious odor problem.
Scooby-Doo almost got milked.
The hair didn't even grow back
in some places.
Ok, we'll go to Wrestlemania.
Whoo-hoo!
WWE City, here we come.
Oh, boy.
Hee hee hee!
Here comes the flying huna
caruna off the top ropes.
Ha ha ha!
And it's countered by Scooby's
patented corkscrew counter crunch.
Um, exactly how many more
play-by-play Scooby snack attacks
will we have to endure
before WWE City?
Like, we brought everything we had.
Scooby and I need to
keep our energy up
so we can cheer like
crazy at the main event.
There's so many boxes
I can't even see the luggage.
Luggage?
You didn't pack the luggage?
Ruh-roh.
Of all the food-induced,
insane things
you two have done, this
absolutely takes the cake.
Mmm. Cake.
I mean it.
Like, what's the big deal?
We all wear the same outfits
every single day anyway.
Well, you gotta admit it,
he does have a point.
Hmph.
Hey, look.
Like, WWE City, next exit.
Hold the phone!
Looks like we're stuck.
There's a car coming.
Maybe they can help.
Well, now, this ain't a
good place for a breakdown.
Can we help you kids out?
John Cena.
Whoa.
Ok. Looks like you kids
ran into some trouble.
This ain't safe, champ.
We gotta keep moving.
Calm down, cookie.
I'm just saying that it's
dangerous out here at night,
what with the bear trouble and all.
That's why Ruben,
my nephew here,
and I have been following the
superstars on their jogs.
Hi.
Well, these kids aren't going
anywhere while their van is stuck.
This shouldn't take long.
Uh, what's he gonna do,
lift the van out of the ditch?
Scooby! Shaggy!
Cool.
I didn't know WWE
superstars were so hot.
Strong! I mean strong.
Grr!
Scooby, no!
Come back!
Scooby! Scooby!
Scoob, stop!
Aah!
Scooby-Doo, where are you?
Zoinks!
A mo... a mo... monster!
Monster? Where?
Where?
Oh, scoob!
Ha ha ha!
You had me worried, pal.
It's me.
It's you.
Yikes!
What are you two doing in my woods?
Um, leaving.
Cool down a bit, Bayard.
The dog and the long haired
fella didn't mean to trespass.
They're just fans come for the WWE.
They all come for that.
And the more they come, the
hungrier they make the beast.
The beast?
The beast called WWE City.
Every day it eats up more
and more of our land.
But not for long,
'cause there's a storm a-coming,
and we're gonna watch it
blow you all out of here
like dead leaves.
Now, get off my property.
Oh, don't let old Bayard spook you.
He's not what you
call a people person.
Still, it's not right.
Can I make it up to you by offering you
some VIP seats at our live event tonight?
Would you be interested?
Would we?
Ladies and gentlemen,
welcome to WWE.
Uhh!
Ahh!
Like, pinch me,
I think I'm dreaming.
Ow!
I'm not dreaming.
Boy, what an exciting tag team
match we have here tonight.
The big show and Alberto del Rio
are up against sin
Cara and John Cena.
And Cena wastes no time
delivering an elbow to big show.
Whoo-hoo! Yes!
Big show with a chop.
And del Rio blindsides Cena.
That was a dirty move.
And I think the ref agrees.
Oh, my goodness, Sin Cara's up.
And he delivers high-flying
justice to del Rio.
Whoo-hoo!
Heh heh heh!
And it looks like the end for Cena.
But somehow Cena reverses.
He's got big show up.
Oh, no!
Look out!
That was my favorite table.
Del Rio's up.
But he walks right into
Cena's sidewalk slam.
And the crowd goes wild.
But wait, big show's back.
With a picnic table?
Where did he get a picnic table?
Oh, the humanity.
I don't see anything in the rules
about the use of furniture.
It's a show, Velma.
It's Sin Cara to the rescue
with a tilt-a-whirl.
And it's a takedown
of the big show.
Oh!
Whoo-hoo!
W!
Best move ever.
Cena gathers his...
Well, I can't say I'm bored.
And here it comes.
You can't see me.
Cena's vintage 5 knuckle shuffle.
Let's go, Cena!
Whoo! Whoo-hoo! Yay!
With incredible strength, Cena
takes big show to the top ropes.
An avalanche.
Attitude adjustment.
Into the cover.
1, 2, 3!
It's over!
Cena for the win.
Yeah! Yeah, man!
Amazing, dude!
Tonight's tag team winners,
John Cena and Sin Cara.
Oh, Cena! My gosh,
you're wonderful.
Welcome, fans.
You should be excited because
I'm about to lay on you
something very heavy...
our very own WWE championship belt.
Ahh.
Yes, it's solid gold,
encrusted with priceless
gems and jewels,
but any WWE superstar will tell
you it's not about the glitter.
The championship belt
represents honor, respect,
hard work, dedication,
the very soul of WWE.
As you know, ever since Kane's WWE
championship match was overturned,
this championship belt
has been held vacant.
And so it shall remain until
a true champion rises up
and proves themself worthy
this weekend in the main
event at Wrestlemania.
Did you know that a
golden ceremonial prize
was customary at ancient games
for thousands of years?
No, Velma.
Thank you.
Oh, it's a text from John Cena, thanking
me personally for all the cheering.
That's a keeper.
When did you give Cena
your phone number?
Oh, when I gave him my email, my
home address, and my scarf size.
Hey, why don't you crazy kids join
us at the training camp tonight?
It's something to see.
WWE training camp?
How'd you like sin
Cara's convertible?
Like, it's a real muscle machine.
Here we are, guys.
WWE's rock yard,
where the pros train for greatness.
Ahh!
Uhh!
Look!
It's sergeant slaughter.
Like, Zowie!
There's Jerry "The King" Lawler.
And Jimmy hart.
Here at camp, we even have
our own 24-hour restaurant.
It's like home.
More like paradise.
Ha ha ha!
Is that the championship belt?
That's right, carved
into the Mountain.
A prize set in stone and the
dream of every superstar.
Mr. Sin Cara, could
we stop for a second?
Uhh!
Sweet.
Way to go, Ruben.
That was a nice job.
Yeah, nice move, Ruby.
Yeah, funktastic, baby.
Like, wow, I didn't know your
nephew dude was a superstar.
That's what he'd like to think.
I'd better get you all
settled into your cabins.
Up ahead on the left, Sin Cara.
I can't believe Shaggy and Scooby
left all our luggage behind.
Now all I have are
these two scarves.
Which do you think John
would like better?
Seriously?
Seriously.
Be honest.
The one on the right.
My thoughts exactly.
I don't understand, Uncle cookie.
It's just not fair.
You know I'm good.
I know you know I'm good.
Why won't you help me get into WWE?
Somebody's got to put
some sense into you.
Do you think I built this brace
because it looks good?
All it takes is one accident
to put you out of contention.
Maybe I'll be luckier. Maybe not.
You have to be practical.
You should keep going to
your computer classes.
Computers, that's the ticket, Ruby.
Poor Ruben.
I feel sorry for him.
It's understandable.
Ruben represents the heroic male aspiring
to the stature of decorated warrior.
His journey is relatable, and therefore
appealing to a wide audience.
Velma, has it ever occurred to you
that maybe WWE isn't something
you can scientifically explain?
Don't be silly, Daphne.
Science and logic
explain everything.
Hey, like, the most
awesome thing about WWE?
You get all the food you can eat.
Yeah. All the food.
Big day tomorrow.
Cookie said we get to see
some superstars training.
I want to grab some
wicked action shots.
Come on, lights out, you two.
Okie doke, Fred.
Sweet dreams, Scoob.
You, too, "Raggy".
All the food.
Food.
Food, food, food, food,
food, food, food, food.
Huh?
Ladies and gentlemen,
let's get ready to Scooby-Doo!
You want to take me on?
Bring it.
Ahh!
Uhh.
Oh, yeah?
Prepare to become a Scooby snack.
Scoob.
Scooby-Doo.
Hmm?
Like, dude, what are you
doing with that bear?
Hmm?
Aah!
Zoinks!
Really?
Aah!
Uhh!
Ooh!
Aah!
Back off, ugly.
Time to call your mama.
Aah! Ooh!
Aah!
Uhh!
Not funky.
Shaggy! Scooby!
Are you ok?
Ghost... Ghost bear.
Then it's true.
What's true, cookie?
The legend.
The monster has returned
from the grave.
Vicious, the ghost bear has
come to challenge us all.
Oh.
Well, gang, sounds like we have
another mystery on our hands?
Assault, battery, property damage.
Ghost bear!
What the heck is going on?
And what are you kids
doing in WWE City anyway?
We won a contest.
Don't look at me, Richards.
You sent out that memo.
The victory dance contest.
Oh, that's right.
That wasn't my idea.
Boys over in marketing
or game development.
One of those.
Who can keep things straight with
all these bear attacks going on?
There have been others?
Indeed. Several.
All of them inside our buildings.
The creature trashed the kitchen and
totally obliterated our video game studio.
And as quickly as it
appears, it disappears.
I'm telling you, it's the ghost.
An evil from beyond the grave.
Let's try to remain calm here.
We don't want to jump to
any crazy conclusions.
Mr. McMahon.
Like, in the flesh.
I can't believe I'm actually
face to face with Vinnie Mac.
The boss.
The higher power.
The Mac attack.
The Mac daddy.
Daddy Mac.
Yes. Ahem. Thanks for that
trip down memory Lane.
Let me cut to the chase.
I've been doing a little
research on you kids.
You're some kind of
mystery solvers.
We could really use your help here.
Gee, Mr. McMahon, we'd be glad to.
My main concern is the
championship belt.
Not only is it worth a fortune,
but Wrestlemania wouldn't
be the same without it.
Excuse me, sir, but we don't need these
kids meddling in security matters.
I promise the championship
belt is well guarded 24/7
with a state-of-the-art electronic
laser trip wire alarm system.
There's no way the
bear could get to it
without tripping a beam
and setting off an alarm
that would bring in half my
security men within seconds.
I understand, Richards, but it couldn't
hurt to have these kids lend a hand.
It's what we do.
You mind if I help?
Um... great idea, John.
Awesome. Because I think there's
someone you should talk to.
Sin Cara?
He knows the legend of the
bear better than anyone.
Like, why is he hanging
out on the roof?
Sin Cara has a flair for drama.
Ahh.
But does he even talk?
He doesn't have to.
Luckily, I speak masked luchador.
I'll translate as best I can.
The legend of the ghost
bear begins 100 years ago
when a monstrous bear was
part of a traveling show.
They named him vicious.
And for good reason.
The creature had a mean streak
a mile wide and twice as ugly.
It'd never been beaten, ever.
Till it met...
Sin Cara Grande,
Sin Cara's great great
great grandfather.
He challenged the bear
on this very spot
long before there was
ever a WWE City.
The battle between man
and bear was epic.
The bear was a horrible,
unstoppable beast.
But when the match was over, it
was the man standing victorious.
The bear could not
contain its anger.
He unleashed his rage on the town.
Many lives would have
been lost that day
had it not been for the brave
luchador Sin Cara Grande.
While saving those innocent
townfolk, he was injured.
Sin Cara Grande would
never wrestle again.
And the bear?
It escaped into the woods, disappearing
into a cave north of town,
never to be seen again.
Until now.
Sin Cara believes the
spirit of the beast
has been stirred by
Wrestlemania itself,
which is why the monster has risen
from the grave to have its revenge.
But fear not.
It is now Sin Cara's honor and duty
to continue his great great
great grandfather's legacy
and protect WWE City at any cost.
Wow.
That's amazing, dude.
I have half a mind to
go out in the woods,
find that bear, and
rip its head off.
I don't know, Triple H,
he's awfully tough.
I think we should stick together.
What do you think, Miz?
Stick together.
I can't believe you two are still
hungry after the meal we had.
This is just a late night snack.
Right, Scoob?
Right. Helps us sleep.
Man, if you guys' muscles were
as big as your appetites,
you'd both be superstars.
Like, Fredster, don't you want
to join the Pizzapalooza?
Eh, no, thanks.
I thought I'd patrol with the guards,
maybe get a picture of the ghost bear.
I'll lock the door after me.
Like, to keep the bear out?
To keep Scooby in.
Good idea.
Like, don't worry, Freddy, the faster
we eat... the faster we fall asleep.
Ahh!
Yah!
Like, is something wrong,
Ms. Richards?
Indeed, there is.
The WWE championship
belt has been stolen.
And we know who did it.
Your dog.
Uh, but that's ridiculous.
Scooby-Doo's been in
here with me all night.
Isn't that right, old pal?
That's right.
Oh?
I saw that.
Uh-uh, nothing to see here.
Just me in bed.
You, sir... uh, dog, are a thief.
But, Ms. Richards, Scooby
couldn't have taken the belt.
He's never stolen anything
in his whole life.
Yeah, never.
I have proof right here.
Last night's security footage.
Take a look.
Ooh. Uhh.
I... I... I did steal it.
Say it ain't true, Scooby-Doo.
Hold on a second.
Is there something
strange about Scooby?
You really want us to answer that?
Yep, this is the
championship belt all right.
I'd know it anywhere.
Take it.
And we'll be taking the
thief with us as well.
No! Don't let them take me, "Raggy".
No!
I won't, pal.
Hang on.
Don't let them take me, Raggy.
I'm innocent.
Jinkies! That's it.
Come on, we've got to work fast
if we're going to save Scooby.
All right, kids.
What's going on here?
Thanks for coming, Mr. McMahon.
We've asked you all
here to show you
that our Scooby isn't a thief.
He's just a pawn.
Allow me.
Here's the security video of
Scooby as he was taking the belt.
And here's the video file of Scooby
doing his winning victory dance
from the memory card of
Shaggy's video game.
Yeah, that's a funkadactal move.
Is there a point to any of this?
Watch as we slow down
the victory dance.
It's the same movement.
Scooby was programmed with
a post-hypnotic suggestion
to steal the championship belt.
Like, that's why he's been sleep
walking since he got here.
Ohh. Yeah.
And just how did the dog get
this post-hypnotic programming?
My guess is from the
video game itself.
May I?
I'm connecting Shaggy's
WWE video game file
to the tron screen.
See, someone highlighted
every move with light flashes.
Flashes which could have planted
a post-hypnotic suggestion
in Scooby's brain.
Yeah, there's a plant in my brain.
Nice hacks, Ruben.
That's my nephew.
He's a computer genius.
Listen, kids, as compelling
as this theory might be,
I'm still a guy that likes
to look at the facts.
And the fact is, he stole it.
And he's going to jail for it.
Jail?
And it was your video game, so you're
going with him... as his accomplice.
Accomplice? I'm no accomplice!
I'm not even sure
I know what that means!
Miss Richards, isn't there something
we can do to prevent that?
No!
Actually, yes there is.
Whatever it is...
We'll do it.
WWE City law states that
anyone accused of a crime
can compete in the ring for a
chance to win their freedom.
I have the power to
give you that chance.
But I have only one competitor
left who is looking for a match.
Kane!
I want another shot at the title.
Looks like I'll have to go
through you two to get it.
I accept the challenge.
Like, you know, Scoob, I hear
prison food isn't that bad.
No!
You want a chance to prove
your innocence in the ring.
They accept the challenge,
Mr. McMahon.
Miss Richards, release these
two so they can prepare.
Unless they can prove
their innocence,
their match with Kane will
kick off Wrestlemania
tomorrow night.
Like, Velma, are you crazy?!
Yeah! We can't fight Kane.
Look, guys,
pull yourselves together.
I need you to buy us some time if
we're going to solve this mystery,
and clear Scooby's name.
I don't know, Velma,
we only have until tomorrow
before Shaggy and
Scooby get slaughtered.
Hello! Thanks, Fred.
They're going to need a
whole lot longer than a day
to learn how to
compete in the ring.
Could you help them, cookie?
Please?
Yeah, yeah, please, please, please!
Oh-ho-ho, please, cookie!
Eh, well, maybe I can
train 'em enough
so they might survive...
Ooh!
For a few minutes.
Aj, you want to help me here?
Sure, cookie.
Hi, boys.
I heard you could use
some practice sessions.
Wouldn't want those itty
bitty whiskers to get bent.
Like, Scooby-Doo,
you know, this may not
be so bad after all.
Aahh!
Never underestimate a diva.
You ok, Ruben?
No, I'm not ok.
I don't understand why my
Uncle is willing to train
Shaggy and Scooby and not me.
Just because he never won a
championship doesn't mean I can't.
Sorry.
See, it's just because all my life,
I've dreamed of being
a WWE superstar.
I've even come up with my own name...
The Bone Bender.
I got an outfit I made out
of spandex and bones.
Real bones I ordered
off the Internet.
Want to see?
Well, maybe later.
Daphne?
You got to hide us!
Aj's like Kane, with lipstick!
Hey, gang, we got maps
of the whole area.
And I found the perfect place to start
looking for clues about the ghost bear.
Scooby, Shaggy.
Where you boys hiding?
Like, what are we waiting for?
Let's go, let's go, let's go!
Like, wouldn't it be
better to clear our names
than to go, you know, bear hunting?
That's just it, Shaggy.
I can't help thinking
that whoever framed Scooby is somehow
connected to the ghost bear.
Keep it down.
We don't want to attract Bayard.
You mean the hillbilly
with the thieving raccoon?
Yeah. Their cave is
right on his property.
Can't say I didn't warn 'em.
Zoinks!
Aroo?
Run!
Scoob!
Aah!
Whoo-hoo-hoo-ah!
Oh! Ooh, hoo, whoa-ho!
Aah!
Huh?!
Like, that was amazing!
Cen-amazing!
How'd you know where we were?
Daphne texted me.
Mmm.
Naturally.
What's going on?
Hillbilly hospitality.
We should keep moving.
Come on, I'll explain on the way.
This is it, guys.
Bear cave.
Come on, follow me.
Now, that's rich.
Those dummies just
walked into a trap
that's better than
any I could make.
Bet you that was the original bear.
He doesn't look so vicious now.
How long do you think
he's been there?
Who cares, as long
as he stays there.
Yeah!
Like, man, what is
this crazy place?
My guess? The lair
of the ghost bear.
Like, he has a lot of junk
for a ghost... or a bear.
Not junk.
Clues!
What are those?
Books on hypnotism.
Hypnotic techniques and
subliminal hypnosis.
Jackpot!
Ohh!
I think we just found our
first piece of evidence
to get you guys off
the hook with Kane.
Evidence! Whoo-hoo-hoo!
We love evidence.
Mwah!
Hey, gang.
Check this out.
Schematics for EMP.
What's an EMP?
What's a schematic?
An EMP is an electromagnetic pulse.
It's a device that can destroy
electronics within its range.
Urghh!
Look what I found.
This calendar has the date for
Wrestlemania circled in red.
R.I.P. WWE.
Fred!
Evidence photos, Velma.
Can't have an investigation
without evidence photos.
So someone thinks they're going to
knock the lights out on Wrestlemania?
Not on my watch!
John!
Gh-gh-ghost bear!
Run!
Yikes!
Ohh!
Whoa!
Ohhh!
Ah-ah-aaah!
Huh?!
We're right back where we started!
Jinkies!
And so's the ghost bear!
Where are the boys?!
We got to get the evidence!
Don't worry, Shaggy.
I still have the photos.
Yeah!
No!
Yoinks!
Ahh!
Guys, hold on to something.
Aah... ohh?
Ohh!
Ah. Huh?
Boom!
Epic!
Ah, enough already!
Hey! Over there!
Huh?
Hey! What do you know?
The caves are connected directly to
the storm drains under WWE City.
Giving that ghost bear
full access at any time.
So you see, Richards,
that's how the ghost bear
gets in and out of so
many places so quickly.
And we have reason to believe that
whoever's behind these bear attacks,
has planted an EMP device
right here in the stadium.
He could shut down the whole place
right in the middle of Wrestlemania.
We shouldn't take any risks.
We'll have to cancel the show.
We can't cancel Wrestlemania!
That's like canceling Christmas.
Not to mention my career.
Besides, what could anyone gain
but shutting off the lights?
Not only the lights,
but the TV cameras, too.
There'd be no show.
People would panic
in the pitch black.
They'd get hurt!
You're right, Sin Cara.
It would tarnish the
entire legacy of WWE.
Listen. I'll have my men
guard the stadium's
generators 24/7.
They'll check every square inch of
the building right before the show.
No one's going to get away
with anything under my watch.
One way or another,
Wrestlemania goes on.
If the object of the EMP
is to create chaos,
you can bet that ghost bear is not
going to be far away when it happens.
I think we all know
what we need to do.
Run away?
Nope. We've got to turn
Wrestlemania into a trap.
A big bear trap.
Whatever you plan,
Fred, count me in.
Come on, then.
We don't have much time.
Ladies and gentlemen,
announcing a new match
for tonight's event.
Kane vs. Skinny man and dead meat.
Like, do you think maybe the
gang has solved the mystery yet?
Because there's no mysteries
to where we're going.
Yeah. To the hospital.
No. The morgue!
Come on, guys, you got
to have confidence.
You have to get up there
and give it your all!
If you don't hold back; If you
battle with your heart and soul,
if you give everything you've got,
then you'll not only survive
this, you could win!
Nice knowin' ya.
Hey, uh...
Break a leg, you two.
Ooh! If we're lucky.
Whoo-hoo!
Let the games begin!
Bring on the pain train!
Whoo!
This is going to be great!
Yeah!
So awesome!
Everybody in position?
Check.
Sin Cara's ready.
And so am I.
Triple H?
Ready out here.
Welcome to Wrestlemania!
Allow me to show you
why we're all here...
Bring it up.
The WWE championship belt.
The superstar who wins
tonight's main event
will be the new WWE champion.
Jinkies! That's it. Fred,
I know where the electromagnetic
pulse device is.
Tonight's first match
is a big one, folks.
We have the newcomers,
skinny man and dead meat.
Ohh!
They'll be facing the
meanest competitor
in and out of the ring.
Back for revenge, determined
to destroy anyone
between him and the title.
I give you the big, red monster.
Kane!
This is a last man standing match.
The superstar who's unable
to answer a ten count
after being knocked down
is declared the loser.
Come on, Scoob, we got...
we got to keep it together!
Oh... oh... k!
After Kane is finished with
skinny man and dead meat,
we'll be scraping them off
the mat with a spatula.
And there's the bell.
Kane explodes across the ring.
Oh! There goes any
chance for a fair match.
Skinny man and dead meat...
slam into the big red monster.
Certainly that blow can
only increase Kane's fury.
Ohh!
Miss Richards, you have to open the
safe and check the championship belt!
Are you crazy? Look, I checked the entire
stadium for your electro-whatumacalit.
It's not here!
It's right there.
Impossible.
If only I had a magnet to prove it.
Wow! Where did you get that?
Luchadores... always
ready for anything.
Ok. Miss Richards,
this magnet will prove
that your championship
belt isn't gold.
Because if it sticks...
Then it's made of
iron and it's a fake.
Caught in the clenches of Kane,
the newcomers are done for.
Whoa!
The bounce out of the ring
offers skinny man and dead meat
a chance for escape...
but look at this!
Kane has just taken the
match under the ring.
It's bedlam down below!
Huh?!
Ahh!
Not again!
Somebody get me another
desk out here, please.
Ha ha!
Jinkies! The EMP is
about to go off.
We'll never get it far enough away.
The arena power generator
is right below us.
I've got to warn everyone.
I have an idea.
Hold this and let go when I say.
Right... Ok.
Now!
Eeh!
That wasn't supposed to happen.
Huh? Whoa!
Huh? What's going on?
What happened?
What happened to the TV?!
Oh, man, this is awful!
Who turned out the lights?
Ok, guys, it's here.
The fans are starting to panic.
Plan B. Here we go.
Whoo-hoo! Nice throw!
We can see!
Let there be light!
Funkadelic.
Part of the show?
That was just part of the show!
I was worried.
I'm fine now.
I'm ok!
Scooby! You can do it.
You know all the right moves.
I do?
Yeah!
From the video game.
I trust the massive power
of your superstar-tastic
dance moves.
Just pretend you're playing
the video game.
I can do this.
I can do this!
That a boy, Scoob!
Huh?!
Ghost bear sighted.
Good. He's here.
Just like we thought he'd be.
The lights are starting to go.
Don't worry... Fred's on it.
Triple H.
Ok, guys,
hit the generators.
Huh?
After a mysterious blackout,
we're somehow back on the air.
Hey! Dead meat's not dead yet.
Wow, look at that doggy move.
Go, dead meat!
Freddy, go!
Plan C.
Hey, smokey!
Where's the fire?
Prepare to face the wrath
of the bone bender!
Is that a bear?!
Like, zoinks!
Is that Ruben?
Ruben, no!
Whoa-oh-oh!
Ohhh!
I don't believe it, folks.
Kane has been flattened, and a new
competitor has entered the ring.
But wait! Someone has
activated the cage.
Sin Cara and John Cena
are leaping into the ring.
It's a cage match!
Like, we're all doomed!
Don't worry, Shaggy.
I'll protect you.
The mysterious new competitor
attacks the bear from behind,
creating a distraction
for Cena to make a move.
But this powerful creature
turns the tables on them both.
Now Sin Cara stands alone.
The fearless luchador attacks.
He glides around the
bear like lightning.
The bear can't even touch Sin Cara.
Ladies and gentlemen, I haven't seen
moves like this in the ring before.
Sin Cara delivers a
stunning blow to the bear
while John Cena
recovers on the mat.
He's going after the bear.
Cena is lifting the bear
over his head.
And the bear is down.
Yeah!
Yay!
Yes!
What's that, bear, what's that?
You can't see me!
Ladies and gentlemen, here it is.
Cena's vintage five
knuckle shuffle.
It's lights out for
this big, bad bear.
This match is over.
Yay! Yay!
Cena and Sin Cara going
for a tandem pin.
Impossible!
Huh?
Ooh-hoo-hoo!
Scooby-Doo, where are you?!
This looks bad for skinny man.
But wait, what is dead meat up to?
Dead meat has revived Kane.
The big, red monster has risen.
Never before have we seen
a stand-off like this.
It's monster vs. Monster inside
the cage at Wrestlemania.
Who will survive this
supernatural match-up?
Who will be victorious in
this paranormal pandemonium?
Kane drives the bear back
with a stunning blow.
The bear hits the mat.
Kane pins down its leg.
A new competitor,
John Cena and Sin Cara
pile onto the powerful creature,
but they can barely hold it down.
Scooby-Doo, it's up to you!
Only dead meat can
tip the balance now.
Can he do it?
Can dead meat save the day?
Scooby Doobie Doo!
Dead meat just delivered a
gut-wrenching belly bomb
and flattened the ring
and exploded the cage!
The dust is clearing now.
The bear is out cold.
Dead meat wins it!
Whoo!
Dead meat!
That bear is toast!
You ok, Velm?
This... Is... Awesome!
Whoo-hoo!
Now let's see who this
ghost bear really is.
Cookie?!
Uncle cookie!
Why?
WWE is your life.
WWE was his life,
but sadly, your Uncle cookie
never got the glory...
And his injury put him
out of the spotlight.
Permanently.
He started to truly resent WWE
because he knew he could never be the
champion he always dreamed of being.
That resentment grew into
hatred over the years,
as he trained others to
be what he could not.
That's when he developed
his plan for revenge.
But that wouldn't be enough.
He needed a pawn to steal
the championship belt.
That's when he devised the idea
of hacking into a video game
and placing post-hypnotic
suggestions into it.
That game would become
part of a contest,
which cookie set up with fake
emails he sent throughout WWE.
That's why he used the bear to
attack your video game studio.
To cover his tracks.
The contest assured that
only the most skilled pawn
would arrive at WWE City
to aid in the theft.
Cookie then used flashing lights to activate
Scooby's post-hypnotic programming.
When cookie identified the belt in
Scooby's bed as the championship belt,
he was lying.
He'd already switched them.
With Scooby taking the blame, cookie was
free to carry out his ultimate plan.
Which was to turn out the lights,
and with the help of the bear,
create so much panic and injury...
That Wrestlemania would be completely
ruined and WWE would never recover.
But thanks to Fred here, we got
the lights back on pretty quick.
Good work!
Ah, um, thanks.
And the real championship
belt, where is it now?
Elementary, my dear Mr. McMahon.
Cookie's wearing it.
Sorry, cookie.
But the championship belt isn't
for cheaters, it's for champions.
Good call, hiring these kids, sir.
I thought they might come in handy.
Just get cookie out of here!
Yes, sir, will do, sir, you bet.
A championship belt was the
icing on the cake, Mr. McMahon.
Cookie could live off its golden
jewels for the rest of his life.
Boo!
And I would have gotten
away with it, too,
if it weren't for you meddling kids
and your giant, crazy dog!
I guess after what my Uncle's done,
you won't be wanting
me around anymore.
Not so, Ruby.
You're one of us now.
You got the funk, son!
That's right, Ruben. You've shown
a superstar spirit in the ring,
and at the computer.
You've earned a place with us
in whatever you want to do.
The choice is yours.
Thanks, Mr. McMahon.
Now that we have the
real championship belt,
it needs to be awarded
to true champions.
And after what I've seen
tonight, they're right here.
Skinny man and dead meat!
Really?
Huh?
Well done.
Scooby-Doo!
Scooby-Doo! Scooby-Doo!
Scooby Doobie doo!
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today