(ENGINE STARTING)
Oh, I'm so nervous.
-Don't sweat it, Daph.
You'll do great.
-SCOOBY-DOO: Mmm-mmm.
You think so?
Yeah, driving tests are easy.
Even I passed mine.
Yeah, me too!
Daphne, you're gonna be great.
I believe in you.
-We all do!
-ALL: Yeah.
If you put your mind to it,
you can do anything, Daphne.
ALL: Yeah! Right on!
-You've got what it takes.
Right, guys?
-ALL: Yeah.
-Yeah?
-ALL: Yeah!
All right!
(TIRES SCREECHING)
-Oh...
-(CRASHING)
VELMA: Oh, no.
(MAN GROANING)
So, did I pass?
-== [ www.OpenSubtitles.org ] ==-
Hi! Clark Sparkman here,
welcoming you all
to Sly Base Earth,
an airport where the flights
are out of this world.
And  Celebrity Heat
is blasting off!
Three years ago,
rash billionaire daredevil,
Sly Baron,
vowed to make space tourism
a reality.
Today, his lucky passengers
are boldly going where
none of them have gone before.
No, not Delaware!
Space!
A trip around the Moon!
And they'll travel in style
on Sly Star One,
the first space cruise ship.
The passengers
are pure A-list.
Celebrated Astronaut,
Shannon Lucas.
Retired legends, Zip Elvin
and Colt Steelcase.
And football star,
Uvinious Botango,
a.k.a. U-Boat.
Superstars going to the stars!
But wait, what about
the average guy or gal?
Didn't Sly promise to make
space available to anyone?
Yeah, what about us?
Hold on
to your boosters, folks,
'cause this super cute
reporter is about
to blow your mind.
(PEOPLE CHEERING)
Sly created a sensation today
when he revealed
that he reserved
five seats for five
lucky lottery winners.
Wow!
Who could they be?
(DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING)
Four teen sleuths
and their dog
won the "Sly Me To Space"
sweepstakes.
Luckily, they'll be
in the company
of space greatness,
including me, Clark Sparkman.
In T-minus zero, the
Celebrity Heat's  exclusive
intergalactic coverage
of the greatest party
on Earth.
(CROWD CHEERING)
How great
are these custom flight suits?
I never want to take mine off.
I know.
The colors are perfect.
And the colors are perfect.
And, like, there's pockets
for snacks.
Ooh, big pockets!
State-of-the-art technology.
I'm Shannon Lucas.
You must be the lucky winners.
Hi! You can't imagine
how surprised we were
to find out we were
actually going into space!
Oh, I think I can.
It was a surprise to me too.
The Baron kept it a secret
until the very last second.
But I guess
he's a man of mystery.
(LAUGHING)
Well, we sure love mysteries.
Right, and love solving them
even more.
(ALL LAUGHING)
-What?
-It's too bad we have to wear
these helmets.
Talk about hat head.
(LAUGHING) I know! Awful.
What? I haven't worn mine yet.
Oh, sorry.
Well, Daphne,
your hair is so great,
I'd consider not going.
Oh, jeepers, thanks!
I use a special conditioner,
extra bounce.
-(HAIR WHIPPING)
-(GRUNTING)
Well, here we are,
about to go into space
and we're talking about hair.
Hey, what are
these lights for?
Indicators.
Each suit is fitted
with every convenience
you have here on Earth.
(LAUGHING) There's no
little boys' room
on the ship, Shaggy.
You go in the suit.
Wow. I really don't have
to take this suit off, ever?
-Not even for...
-Right.
I'm guessing that
the red light might means
you should think about
changing out
your payload though.
Like, dude, we're wearing
atomic diapers.
The Baron spared no expense.
Well, I'm sure
Sly can afford it.
Besides, all he cares about is
over-the-top publicity stunts.
I wouldn't be surprised
if he made some grand entrance
wearing a suit
made out of money.
(PEOPLE CHEERING)
Wow! A suit made out of money.
Yes, yes. Cheering for me.
You're welcome.
Ladies and gentlemen,
thanks to me,
you're about to experience
a life-changing event
you'll never forget.
A safe and easy way for anyone
and everyone to go to space.
It will thrill you,
especially if you pick up
some souvenirs
in the Sly Star gift shop.
Now, let's blast off!
(CROWD CHEERING)
(CAMERA SHUTTERS CLICKING)
Wow, there's Zip Elvin
and Colt Steelcase!
Let's go say hi.
Hi, Zip.
Hi, Colt.
(CLEARS THROAT) Fred Jones,
reporting for duty.
Oh. Hi, Fred.
I'm a huge fan!
(STAMMERS)
A huge fan.
Even though you guys
landed on the moon
years before I was born,
you've always been
an inspiration to me.
-Well, we're not that old.
-He can't hear you.
-Fred, you need to push
the com button on your...
-I can't hear you!
So, you're probably wearing
those diaper things, right?
Probably used to them
by now, though.
I know how it must
kind of itch and stuff but...
-I think it's so cool.
-(GROANING)
So, Shannon, do you have
our training test scores, yet?
Just curious.
I'm not obsessed
with test scores or anything.
I was actually
just looking at them.
-Wanna know how you did?
-Yes!
I mean, sure.
Why not?
You all passed.
But one of you
scored high enough
to enter the NASA
Astronaut Candidate Program.
-Nice work...
-Thanks.
-...Daphne.
-Really? Me?
Wow! That is so cool!
-Have you ever considered
being an astronaut?
-No, never.
I have,
ever since I was a kid.
Well, you should.
We'll talk later, girlfriend.
Okay, sounds great,
girlfriend.
And maybe you can give me
some hair tips. (GIGGLES)
Oh, my gosh, I would love to!
I'll see you in a bit.
Yeah, we'll all talk
later then.
She is so nice.
This is going to be
the best trip ever.
-What are you doing?
-(GROANING)
(CROWD CHEERING)
MAN: U-Boat! U-Boat! U-Boat...
Scoob, it's him!
(LAUGHING)
Uvinious Botango, the U-Boat.
Like, the best
football player alive!
Okay, everyone needs
to calm down.
SLY:  All passengers
please board
and prepare for takeoff.
Oh, my gosh!
I've been waiting
my whole life for this moment.
I can hardly breathe!
Okay, let's get going.
WOMAN: (ON PA)  T-minus
five minutes to launch.
(SEATBELT SIGN PINGS)
I can't believe
Shaggy and Scooby are so calm.
They get jumpy on elevators.
They have U-Boat fever.
-Why do they call him that?
-Because he sinks everybody.
He's a tackling machine.
And he has a line
of snack foods.
U-Boat Bites!
I'll be surprised
if Shaggy and Scooby
even notice we're in space.
Hey, would you like to join us
on the bridge for lift-off?
Would I? Oh, you have...
What do you say, Daphne?
Really? Well, sure. Thanks!
(VELMA STRAINING)
Boy, she sure left in a hurry.
Well, at least I have
you here, Fred.
Hey, Zip, Colt.
You guys going to the bridge?
-Yeah, but this really...
-Great! I'll join you.
Wait, I'll come too.
Just need to undo
these stupid belts.
I'd keep those on
if you want to live.
Ridley,
alien resistance fighter.
Wait, really?
That's a job?
It will be,
when the aliens invade.
Velma Dinkley, right?
You're one of the teen
detectives, Mystery Inc.
Clark Sparkman,
Celebrity Heat.
Mind if I ask you
a few questions?
You can if you like,
but I won't answer.
Good call.
TV is a factory of deceit.
BOTH: U-Boat!
(SCOOBY-DOO GROANS)
WOMAN: (ON PA)  T-minus
20 seconds to launch.
SLY:  Here we go, folks!
We're heading to the stars,
thanks to me, Sly Baron.
MAN: Sly Star One,
this is ground control,
you are clear to go.
WOMAN: (ON PA)  Five, four,
three, two. We have ignition.
And one. Lift-off.
(PEOPLE CHEERING)
SLY:  Welcome to space.
We did it!
High five, guys.
SLY:  Ladies and gentlemen,
we have reached
our cruising altitude
of one million meters.
(SEATBELT SIGN PINGS)
Sly Co.'s latest
Host Android Marvel,
or H.A.M.,
is moving through the cabin
with refreshments
and observational comedy,
courtesy of me.
You're welcome!
You know why moon restaurants
always go out of business?
No atmosphere.
Am I right, people?
(VELMA STRAINING)
(H.A.M PLAYING
STUDIO LAUGHTER)
If you need any more
buttons pressed,
(WHISPERS) I'm your man.
Ew. And this sort of stuff
works for you?
Still not gonna do
an interview.
I don't watch  Celebrity Heat.
-No offense.
-None taken.
It's my job, not my life.
So, want to check out
the ship?
I'm in.
Strength in numbers.
-Look, I think we made
a good impression.
-(BOTH LAUGHING)
-Care for a wet towel, sir?
-Out of my way, robot!
No peanuts for him.
Come on, pal.
All this hero talk
has made me hungry.
Let's go find the snack bar.
(BOTH STRAINING)
Oh, look at that view!
-Been there.
-Done that.
I never get tired
of it, though.
How could you?
It's... It's...
Exactly.
What's next?
For us, safety check.
We got to make sure
this billion dollar yacht
stays in one piece.
Sounds important, I'm in.
(GROANING)
Aren't you going with them?
I have to run diagnostics on
the navigation system first.
But you go ahead,
I'll catch up with you.
Shannon, thanks for making me
feel like I belong up here.
You do!
Space needs
a lot more Daphnes.
I'm just speeding up
the process a bit, girlfriend.
(GIGGLING)
Okay, thanks, girlfriend.
(GROWLS)
Like, did you see something
funny in the window, Scoob?
Funny? No.
-Me neither.
-Phew. Must be
our imagination.
Like, I once saw a show
about a guy that saw gremlins
on the outside of his plane.
-What happened?
-I turned off the TV.
Good idea.
(CLATTERING)
-What was that?
-Probably space junk.
Since the space age began,
we've dumped millions
of pieces of trash into orbit.
Some weigh more
than 6,000 tones.
-How do you know all that?
-I visited NASA last month.
-Research.
-Research?
You work for  Celebrity Heat.
Space junk.
That's exactly what
the aliens want us to think.
Or it's really
just space junk.
I know what you're thinking.
"Ridley. She's just some
whacked out alien freak
"who's seen one too many
sci-fi movies."
-Yes, that's exactly
what I'm thinking.
-Me, too.
We are not alone.
(LAUGHING)
"We are not alone." Oh...
But I've dedicated my life
to alien combat training
for one simple reason.
(GRUNTING)
Breakdancing?
Combat training.
They're out there.
And how do you know that?
Do you have
any firsthand experience?
Yeah, have you ever
seen an alien?
Have I ever seen an alien?
Ha!
No, I haven't.
-But I do have video evidence.
-(DEVICE BEEPS)
We've been in contact
with aliens for decades.
Uh... That's a kitten.
Oh, sorry, that's not it.
Here. Look!
Did you see it?
It was right there!
-(GROWLING)
-(STATIC)
That's just
the tip of the iceberg.
There's more footage.
Lots more.
And I'll show it to you.
Wait here!
-And that's our cue to hide.
-Way ahead of you.
Like, dude,
they have U-Boat Bites.
That's U-Boat Nacho Bites!
Come on, open up. (PANTING)
We're having a snack attack.
H.A.M.:  Do you know what
my favorite snack is?
I don't have one because
I cannot digest food.
Am I right, people?
(H.A.M PLAYING
STUDIO LAUGHTER)
I don't get it.
Are you challenging me,
canine life form?
Uh, no, I... I...
I'm kidding. Ha, ha.
I'm a robot. Ha, ha.
I'll destroy you
with one blow.
Ha. Am I right, people?
(H.A.M PLAYING
STUDIO LAUGHTER)
That comedy robot
has a dark side.
Like, that is not uncommon.
Humor is often inspired
by the same darkness
from which it endeavors
to provide an escape.
Huh?
Wow, I'm so hungry,
my brain ain't workin' right.
-(HEAVY FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING)
-SCOOBY-DOO: Huh?
SHAGGY: Yikes!
(WHIMPERING)
(GRUNTING)
-(TEETH CHATTERING)
-(WHIMPERING)
CLARK: I guess an alien
wouldn't shock you.
You've seen all kinds
of weird stuff.
You researched me?
Why? You're here
to do a piece on the Baron.
I'm not sure he's the most
interesting person on board.
(CLICKING TONGUE)
Know what I mean?
Ew!
-(FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING)
-(WHIMPERING)
Phew! Like, it's you,
Mr. U-Boat.
We're huge fans.
You're like the best player
on the field every Sunday
and Monday and Thursday
and some Saturdays.
You're the best
off the field too.
We love U-Boat Bites.
Like, man,
we'd be eating them right now,
if the snack bar was open.
(GRUNTS)
Space is delicious.
(GROWLING)
DAPHNE: Whoa.
Did you hear that?
Thermal contraction caused
by temperature differential.
It's normal.
Right. It's normal, Daph.
It didn't sound normal.
It sounded like
there's something outside.
Something outside?
You mean in the vacuum
of space?
-Like what?
-(SCOFFS) Yeah, like what?
In the vacuum of space?
You think
there's an alien out there?
A creature with an oversized
head and big black eyes?
Hold the phone.
You've seen it?
No, because it doesn't exist!
If aliens exist, they never
introduce themselves to us.
And we've spent a lot of time
in their neighborhood.
Not that it matters.
Space is dangerous enough
without little green men.
Maybe they were cloaked
from human sight.
I saw a movie
where the aliens did that.
-Here, I'll show you a clip.
-No, no, no.
You kids watch so much junk on
screens, you think it's real.
When I was your age,
we watched less
and lived more.
Makes sense. There was
a lot of less stuff to watch
when you were our age.
(CLANGING)
-I mean... Well, of course
there was... Oh.
-(BEEP)
(INAUDIBLE)
Colt, let's get out of here.
(BEEP)
Uh, maybe you should just
give them some space, Fred.
(LAUGHING) Get it? Space!
That's so funny.
I... I don't get it.
(ALARM BLARING)
-COLT: What did you touch,
hotshot?
-Nothing.
ZIP: Come on. Let's go see
what all this fuss is about.
He called me a hotshot.
SLY:  Nothing
to worry about, folks,
just working out
some first flight bugs.
Be sure to capture
my perfect physique
and spirit, hmm?
I've said it a thousand times,
civilians do not belong
in space.
You're right, Colt.
You've said it a thousand
times, at least.
Man! (HOWLING)
We're doomed.
SCOOBY-DOO: How do we
get off this thing?
-ZIP: What's going on?
-It's the air supply.
We're venting oxygen.
Something must have damaged
the external tank.
(SNAPS FINGERS)
Like the alien we saw.
We saw an alien outside,
or we didn't.
I like "we didn't" better.
Did it have black, hollow eyes
and slimy looking skin?
Like, yeah. (LAUGHS NERVOUSLY)
How did you know?
Jinkies.
(RATTLING)
Man, that doesn't sound good.
(ALARMS BEEPING)
It's not good.
We're nearly out of oxygen.
-How long do we have? Hours?
-More like minutes.
-Minutes?
-(BOTH PANTING)
We need to find air, fast!
-(GASPING)
-There's a lot of air
on Earth.
And, like, no aliens.
We'll never make it back
to Earth in time.
Never make it? But there's
nowhere else to go.
That's not entirely true.
There is one place.
(CLEARS THROAT)
Shouldn't you be
filming me being dramatic?
Oh, right.
That's not entirely true.
There is one place.
SLY:  You don't need air
when something
takes your breath away.
SHANNON: The Baron has been
secretly building
on the dark side of the moon
for over 10 years.
It's quite an achievement,
don't you think?
Furthering his dream
of making space travel
available for anyone.
You're welcome,
average people.
I guess he really is
a man of mystery.
You are the first
to experience the very finest
space has to offer.
(GIGGLING)
Welcome to Sly Moon Prime,
the moon's first
luxury resort.
It's not quite finished yet,
but the air generators
are on line
and producing more air
than we could ever breathe.
(BREATHES DEEPLY)
-Your helmet?
-What?
Oh, forget it.
Anything you want or need,
just ask a Sly Bot.
-That's why we made them.
-MAN: We?
Forgive me.
(CHUCKLES)
I had little to do
with actually building them.
Nothing but the money
to make all of this possible.
This is Hudson,
my right hand space man
and my twin brother.
He made them.
(H.A.M. PLAYING
DRAMATIC MUSIC)
Sorry.
He's been here since day one.
11 years, two months,
12 days, most of it alone.
It's great
to see friendly faces.
Or any faces at all.
(FORCED LAUGH)
(WHIMPERING)
Mmm?
This isn't all happening
in my head, is it?
It's all real, right?
Yes, it is, brother.
People, people, people!
(LAUGHING)
People, people, people.
You're really here.
You're all real.
(LAUGHING)
It's been so long.
I love him,
but he's a little odd.
Hudson, why don't you
make the introduction?
Yes, yes, yes. Introductions.
This is Frank.
He keeps us all honest.
This is Linda,
our ray of sunshine.
Here's Reggie,
the comedian of the group.
(LAUGHING)
Good one, Reggie.
(CONTINUES LAUGHING)
Oh... Oh, that's funny.
(CLEARS THROAT)
And finally, there's Twiggy.
She's not happy with me
at the moment.
We're having a disagreement,
isn't that right?
Oh, is that so?
Well, we'll talk
about this later.
So, what can we do for you?
We need to patch and seal
our air tanks.
Gonna need
two welding rigs.
-Make it three.
-Like I said, two.
Yes, yes, of course!
I'll put my best bot on it.
(GASPING)
That's Caroline Prime!
(BEEPING)
(GULPS)
Caroline, we have guests!
(WHEELS SQUEAKING)
Stop. Stay.
She was just
stocking supplies.
She can move thousands
of food crates in a matter
of minutes. (CHUCKLES)
Food crates! (LAUGHS)
Like, I think I found
my favorite robot, Scoob.
Yeah, me too.
(H.A.M PLAYING
STUDIO RECORDING)
Aw!
I don't trust anything
that's not human.
Maybe you shouldn't get
too close, U-Boat.
She's perfectly safe.
Wouldn't hurt a fly.
I checked her protocol myself.
She'll do anything we ask.
Watch. Sit!
Oh. (GIGGLING)
Not you. Caroline.
Caroline, sit.
It'll take some time
to get the rigs prepped.
And of course,
you'll be needing
cryogen down the mag coils
and synthenix first, right?
He said the engines
will need to cool.
That's right.
Oh!
(VELMA CLEARS THROAT)
-I speak nerd.
-Of course, you do.
-Watch it, four eyes!
-You wear glasses too.
(SCOFFS) Whatever.
Okay, good, good.
Let's get to work.
-Might take a day or so.
-DAPHNE: Great.
That will give us
a chance to find the alien.
-Alien?
-(H.A.M. PLAYING
DRAMATIC MUSIC)
Uh, you're not helping.
Sorry.
That's what ripped the oxygen
lines on the  Sly Star One.
It could still be on board.
Or around here somewhere.
Who knows what you saw?
It was probably nothing
but space junk.
Come on, Zip,
let's get to work.
Right, let's get to work.
I'm afraid
I have to excuse myself
for a satellite interview,
probably about
some award the world
needs to bestow upon me.
Um, feel free to take
the Sly Moon buggy ride.
It's fun out there.
Now, watch me leave!
Like, dude,
if the alien might be inside,
maybe we should go
where it isn't.
Like, outside.
What do you say, old pal?
Yeah, yeah, outside.
I'm right behind you, buddy.
So, where should we start?
I have to recalibrate
the oxygen levels
for the station.
More people,
more air to breathe.
Shouldn't take too long.
I'll see you in a bit.
(GIGGLING)
So, Clark, didn't you mention
that you wanted to do
an exclusive expose
on someone
in the mystery solving game?
That someone being me!
Hmph!
Oh, yeah. Well...
Whoa!
Knock, knock.
I'm not home,
but these guys are.
(H.A.M. PLAYING
STUDIO RECORDING)
Aw!
Yeah! Whoo-hoo!
Yeah! Scooby-Dooby-Doo!
(GIGGLING)
That Colt guy
was right, Scoob.
Maybe it wasn't
an alien after all.
Maybe it was just
space junk.
I mean, look at this place.
It's a regular junkyard.
(ECHOING)
Junkyard. Junkyard. Junkyard.
Yeah. Yeah. Space junkyard.
(GIGGLING)
(EXCLAIMS)
(CLASSICAL MUSIC PLAYING)
One small step for a dog...
And one giant leap for me!
-Yeah.
-(BOTH LAUGHING)
That's weird.
I thought we left
the dark side of the moon.
(GROWLING)
(BEEPING)
(SCREAMING)
(GROWLING)
Zoinks!
-Catch me!
-Okay, dude!
-Scoob!
-(ENGINE STARTING)
Shaggy!
(SHAGGY SHOUTING)
(BOTH WHIMPERING)
(SCREAMING)
(HISSING)
(SHAGGY GASPS)
Hmm.
I think we lost it, Scoob.
(BEEP)
(EXCLAIMS)
(BOTH WHIMPERING)
Like, we're totally sorry,
Mr. U-Boat,
but that alien was chasing us.
Really?
You must have been scared.
Scared? (STAMMERING)
Like, why would you
think that?
That's okay, I get scared too.
Like, you get scared?
(GASPING) Of what?
Of what?
Sharks, dentists,
public speaking,
aliens, mines, the IRS,
being in space,
lots of things!
Sometimes it's all
in your head, though.
The trick is finding something
that helps you deal with it.
-Like food.
-Or music.
-BOTH: Or food.
-Or exercise.
BOTH: Or food.
-Hey, or maybe even...
-Food!
-...Singing.
-BOTH: Or food.
Singing... (LAUGHING)
-Like, you sing?
That's funny.
-(BOTH LAUGHING)
(SOFT MUSIC STARTS)
¶ Fear is just a word
a four letter word
¶ Like love and meek
and made
¶ Only just a word
a silly little word
¶ So it doesn't
make me afraid ¶
Wow! That is...
¶ F la la la la
¶ E la la la la
¶ A la la la la R
¶ Spells nothing
you need to fear
¶ Fear is just a word
¶ A silly little word
¶ So it doesn't
make me afraid ¶
Huh.
(DOOR OPENING)
Wow!
Look at all this cool stuff.
I don't even know
what half of it does.
(TOOLS CLATTERING)
Check this out.
Maybe you shouldn't
touch that.
(WHIRRING)
It's a coolant gel used
to extinguish fires by...
Ah!
...totally immersing it
in gel.
-Fred!
-Sorry, Daph. Let me...
(GASPING) Wow!
Look at this thing.
I wouldn't touch that, Fred.
It's oxygen
and butyl liquid nitrogen.
If that goes off...
Zip, what are you doing?
-I'm going to get him
out of there.
-Really?
You think that's a good idea?
You hear that?
It's really quiet, peaceful,
-no Fred talking.
-Oh, right. (CHUCKLING)
How long can someone
survive in that?
Well, it depends.
How long you want to enjoy
the blissful sound
of not hearing his voice?
Uh, half hour?
Yeah, sounds about right.
Now, hand me those calipers.
(DAPHNE STRAINING)
(BEEPING)
(SIZZLING)
Interesting.
I thought you didn't trust
anything that's not human.
A microwave isn't human,
yet you let it make your food.
You'll be needing this,
I suppose?
Another machine.
See?
Machines are useful.
-Machines are...
-(GROWLING)
(H.A.M. PLAYING
SOUNDTRACK RECORDING)
Ooh...
Jinkies! You really
don't like robots, do you?
I guess you don't take
to progress very well.
Progress?
You mean the sort of progress
that put automated machines
in the car factories?
The sort of progress that put
my father and hundreds
of others like him
out of work when I was a kid?
That sort of progress?
Boy, if he had his way,
we wouldn't have planes,
let alone the technology
to fly to the moon.
Hmm.
SHAGGY: Maybe U-Boat's right.
Maybe that alien was only
in our heads.
Hmm?
Yeah, just like that alien.
(GROWLING)
Yep, that alien's
not really there.
-(GROWLING)
-Neither is that one.
-Or that one!
-(BOTH SCREAMING)
Yikes!
Have we lost him?
-I think we're okay, Scoob.
-Yeah, more than okay.
(EXCLAIMS JOYFULLY)
There's no alien. Yup!
No alien at all.
We're just hungry, that's all.
Yeah, we need to eat
that alien away.
(BOTH LAUGHING)
I feel better already.
Me too, Scoob.
This spread is, uh... Huh?
(GROWLING)
(BOTH WHIMPERING)
I am so scared!
Me, too!
(SNARLS)
Sorry, Mr. Alien.
Like this table's for two.
Plus, he can't reach it,
unless aliens can
jump really high.
Can aliens jump really high?
(GROWLING))
(SCREAMING)
(BOTH WHIMPERING)
(GROWLING)
(ELEVATOR BELL DINGS)
(PANTING) So, you
guys were on
the very first mission, right?
That's so cool.
You probably have a huge
following on the Internet.
Have your own blog?
But it wasn't around
back then.
Heck, I don't think there were
even computers back then.
(LAUGHING)
Aw! We should have
left him in the ice.
I still can't feel my fingers.
Ew! What's that?
Condensation. Probably
from the air vents.
Looks like alien juice to me.
And you've seen
alien juice before?
No, not exactly.
But if I were to take a guess
at what it looked like,
I would say it would
look a lot like that.
Could this day get any worse?
-(BOTH SCREAMING)
-(CRASHING)
What the blazes is going on?
Alien! Big!
(WHIMPERING) Chasing us!
Yeah! It hates food
and likes melting brains.
-Maybe it's lost.
-Or maybe it doesn't exist!
Wait, where did
you see an alien?
Dude, restaurant!
And you left before
you were done eating?
BOTH: Uh-huh.
Shaggy and Scooby
would never leave food behind.
Something was
in that restaurant.
And that's the truth!
-So help me hot dogs.
-Okay!
Let's go take a look.
Oh, sure. Why not?
I could use a good laugh.
(H.A.M PLAYING
STUDIO LAUGHTER)
That's not funny.
Look at this.
It's lucky no one's hurt.
Tell that to
the poor spring rolls.
Or to anybody replaced
by an alien imposter.
Because they do that.
Better the food than the ship.
-Watch your mouth, Hollywood.
-(GROWLING)
Shaggy is very sensitive
when it comes to food.
Well, it could
have been worse.
Exactly. Good point, Daphne.
Yes, Daphne, well done.
It's lucky we have
a space expert like you here.
What's that about?
I have an idea.
Talked to the chef Sly bot.
He didn't say anything,
maybe because he's scared.
Or maybe because
Sly bots can't talk.
Uh, right.
So we have two witnesses.
Right, who are eating
raw fish off the floor.
Come on, Zip.
This is a joke!
There's no alien
and we've got work to do.
-(LOUD THUDDING)
-(SCREAMING)
It's back!
SLY: Looks like I missed
one heck of a party.
Well, look who shows up
right after
all the excitement.
Perfect timing, I'd say.
I was about to give
a satellite interview,
about me, of course.
But it appears
someone or something
put it out of commission.
The satellite is out?
We're cut off from Earth.
No way of communicating
to anyone.
(GASPING)
(WHIMPERING)
-It must have
happened right before...
-The alien attack!
Don't worry, folks.
I'll be fine.
-Besides, Hudson is on it.
-Mmm-hmm.
And the Sly bots are preparing
more food as we speak.
Wow! Awesome boots!
Yes, they are awesome,
because they're on me.
They're my brother's latest
magna-boot prototype.
It creates a pressure
sensitive electromagnetic
field for attraction.
I think you might know
a thing or two about
electromagnetic attraction.
-Am I right?
-You can't be serious.
I think I may throw up.
Really, are you serious?
Sorry.
And repulsion.
That's more accurate, I'd say.
Very handy in space.
Handy for creating
a spectacle too.
No one creates
a spectacle quite like you.
(LAUGHING)
What, a spectacle?
Right you are, Velma Dinkley.
And an alien attack is the
greatest spectacle of all, no?
Are you suggesting
I had something to do
with this alien situation?
Well, if the boot fits...
(LAUGHING)
I get it...
(GUFFAWS)
I wish I had thought of it.
And I probably would have,
if I wasn't too busy
doing interviews
about how awesome I am.
An alien encounter is
a publicity gold mine.
There's only one thing
that would top it.
An alien space battle.
-Well...
-DAPHNE: Or an alien wedding.
-No...
-How about an alien cook off?
No!
An alien in captivity!
Too bad for you
there's no alien to capture.
-You can't say
for certain that...
-Oh, yes, I can!
Last count, I'm pretty sure
Colt and I have been to space
a whole lot more times than...
Gentlemen, ladies, please!
It's been a long day.
We're all tired.
And maybe it's making us
a little uneasy.
Why don't we all
get some sleep?
Excellent suggestion, Shannon.
I'm glad I thought of it.
A few hours' sleep
will do us all good.
The  Sly Star should be ready
by then too. Right, brother?
Yes. Uh-huh.
(ELEVATOR BELL DINGS)
Like, man, I don't know
about you guys,
but I won't be getting
much sleep with that
alien still out there.
Yeah, me neither.
Guys, there is no alien.
But Velma, we all saw it.
Oh, I forgot.
You're the expert now.
Are you still mad
at me because I scored
higher than you on the test?
And have better hair?
Guys, I need you to take
a break from arguing.
We're a team.
There's only one way
to find out if this alien
is real or not.
We've got to catch it!
(ELEVATOR BELL DINGS)
Did someone say,
"Catch an alien"?
(H.A.M PLAYING DRAMATIC MUSIC)
(ELEVATOR BELL DINGS)
This is going to be
the greatest alien trap ever.
Isn't this technically
the first alien trap ever?
It is also an act of war.
All the more reason
to make it perfect.
Plus, I want to impress
Zip and Colt.
Kind of tough to impress them
if they aren't here.
Have you considered that
they may not warm up to you?
-No matter what you do?
-No. Why?
(SIGHS) No reason.
Aliens would laugh
at this trap if they
had a sense of humor.
-But they don't.
-(SIGHS)
Okay, for fun,
let's say aliens are real.
What do you think
is gonna happen?
This is phase one. Contact.
RIDLEY:  A single alien
from a race advanced
light years beyond ours
stealthily boards
a human ship with ease.
The alien makes contact.
It seems hostile
but it's not after blood.
It's gathering intel from us.
The alien pinpoints
our weaknesses and transmits
his findings home.
So begins phase two. Invasion.
An alien fleet enters
our solar system,
an armada
of infinite size and power.
It surrounds
its target, Earth!
And attacks.
Our meager defenses
are no match for its
vast and superior might.
The world's greatest cities
are devastated by the siege.
New York, Tokyo,
Paris, Dublin...
Which leads to phase three.
Rock Bottom.
The aliens enslave humanity,
forcing us to mine Earth's
natural resources until we
and the planet are bled dry.
In short, not so good.
Not until...
Human rebels rise up against
their alien oppressors.
FRED:  They fight from
the shadows turning alien
technology against its makers.
Wait, what?
No, no, no, no, no.
As I was saying...
Humans stick together when
facing a monumental challenge.
DAPHNE:  They fight with,
instead of against each other,
when confronting
a common threat.
(GIGGLING)
I could use my superior
video game skills.
(PINGING)
This is my thing.
I get to say what...
It takes more than
teamwork and video games
to defeat the aliens.
VELMA:  It takes a particularly
clever human,
whose skills are
sometimes overlooked
by her fellow humans.
Great.
-Nothing left for me to say...
-Or maybe...
Oh, this is ridiculous!
I'm leaving.
(ELEVATOR BELL DINGS)
(ELECTRICITY FLICKERING)
It's starting.
They're here.
Places, everyone!
Shaggy, Scooby,
I just spotted the alien
in the observation deck.
Head up there and lure him
down to Hudson's work area.
Daphne, Velma, and I
will cover the rest.
It's almost too easy.
Any questions?
Uh, yeah.
Could we not do this?
Guys, relax.
It's just an alien.
It can't hurt you if
it doesn't catch you.
Yes, it can.
It tried to melt our brains.
Man, I don't know about this.
(BOTH GASP)
BOTH: Sticky buns?
FRED:  I figured you might
have second thoughts.
I thought I'd give you two
some added incentives.
Like, yeah.
Incentives with frosting.
(CHUCKLING)
Yeah. Yeah. Yummy.
VELMA: You're probably
going to tell me I'm doing
this all wrong, aren't you?
(SCOFFS) You can't stand
that I did better than you on
the astronaut training tests.
What do I care?
Those tests must be flawed.
(GASPS) Because I did well?
No, because you
did better than me.
Ugh, I knew it!
After all this time, is it so
hard for you to accept
that I might be something
more than a pretty face?
No...
(SIGHS)
What's hard to accept is that
you get to have it all.
If you're prettier,
and more stylish and smarter
and a better astronaut,
what's left for me?
If you're a better me
than I am,
then who am I?
I...
-(ELECTRICITY FLICKERING)
-(GASPS)
Huh?
(ELECTRICITY CRACKLING)
Dang it!
Tripped the breakers again.
(GASPS)
Something's wrong
with the gravity!
You think?
What makes you say that?
SLY:  Hi, folks. Slight glitch
with our artificial gravity.
We'll have it back on shortly.
Until then, enjoy the float.
Like, dude, a glitch. Oh, boy!
That doesn't sound good.
Scoob, what are you doing?
Enjoying the float.
You can swim
without getting wet.
(LAUGHING)
Hey, you're right.
And you can eat
without getting sticky.
It's all good.
Just relax and have a...
(GASPS) Huh?
(BOTH SCREAMING)
Like, what do you say, pal?
Maybe we should try some
of U-Boat's singing.
¶ F la la la la
¶ E la la la la
¶ A la la la la R
-(GROWLS)
-(SINGING CONTINUES)
I don't think the singing's
working very well, Shag.
Guess there's only one
thing left to do.
Run!
(BOTH SCREAMING)
(SNARLING)
FRED:  Don't eat
the sticky buns.
Use them to stick.
Man. A great idea, Fred.
It's working.
(GROWLING)
(SCREAMING)
Rogue One, this
is Rogue Leader.
The package is
heading your way. Over.
-Am I Rogue One or Rogue Two?
-It doesn't matter.
We're ready, Fred.
Oh, come on.
Use your call sign, Velma...
I mean... (CLEARS THROAT)
Rogue Two. Over.
(BOTH SCREAMING)
Sting darts away!
Oh, they missed.
No problem. My turn. Over.
Like, now what?
(GROWLING)
Gotcha! Gravity gel.
That should hold him.
(BOTH EXCLAIMING)
(EXCLAIMS)
Oh, dude, I guess
the gravity's fixed.
But now my head's broken.
(GROWLING)
(GASPS)
You caught it!
(ELEVATOR BELL DINGS)
-The alien!
-You caught the alien!
-Yes...
-(ELEVATOR BELL DINGS)
The alien!
You caught the alien!
-Yes, we...
-(ELEVATOR BELL DINGS)
The alien!
You caught the alien!
-Yes...
-(ELEVATOR BELL DINGS)
The alien!
You caught the alien!
-Yes...
-(ELEVATOR BELL DINGS)
Does anyone have a spare
hair dryer? I seem to...
The alien!
You caught the alien!
Yes, we caught it!
-How many elevators
are in this building?
-It is real.
I wouldn't be so sure.
(STRAINING)
ALL: Shannon Lucas!
-But how?
-Why?
Who?
Oh, right. It's Shannon.
That's right. It was Shannon.
Being an astronaut made her
the perfect alien.
FRED:  She knew how to adjust
the frequency of
a micro radar transmitter
to turn it into a devastating
sonic weapon.
Like, that explains
the alien's mind beams.
She used Sly's
magna-boots to defy gravity.
VELMA:  And she knew
how to use holograms,
videos and audio recordings
to mask her whereabouts
at any moment.
FRED:  And she knew the ship
and the resort, so she
could come and go at will.
It was a plan
years in the making
by a highly trained expert.
Yes, an expert.
Someone who has sacrificed
everything to get here.
Not some regular nobody
that Sly had decided
could simply go to space
because it was easy
and safe for everyone, anyone.
I decided to change that.
The original plan was
to sabotage the ship,
stage an alien attack
and make the world see that
space travel is dangerous
and only a place for experts.
And you had the perfect guests
to help you with your plan.
Two veteran astronauts to make
the trip seem credible.
And you had U-Boat,
a superstar athlete
that would ensure
the whole world was watching.
And Ridley, the one person you
knew would confirm to the
world that aliens were real.
Don't forget Clark.
Celebrity Heat would
give you all the exposure
you could ever need,
by ignoring the actual facts
to get you
a sensational story.
-Sorry, Clark.
-It's a living.
You had it all figured out.
Except I didn't count
on the greatest mystery
team being on board.
That was just plain old luck.
Bad luck.
I knew your snooping
would ruin my plans.
I even tried to convince
you not to go.
Well, Daphne,
your hair is so great,
I'd consider not going.
Then, I switched your
scores, hoping it would
break up your happy team.
And I guess
it did for a while.
Wait, so I didn't get
the highest score?
(CHUCKLES WRYLY)
No, Daphne. Shaggy did!
-What?
-ALL: Shaggy?
Like, dude, me? (CHUCKLES)
I had to prevent you from
figuring out my plans so I
came up with a different one.
A plan that meant
leaving you here.
So we would never be able to
return to tell the real story.
It was you that
sabotaged the satellite!
Boy! Everything that happened
was perfectly calculated.
And expertly executed.
And you would have got
away with it too, if it
hadn't have been for me.
You?
Oh, right.
I meant and you would have
gotten away with it too,
if it wasn't for me
and these meddling kids.
(CHUCKLES) "Would have"?
Oh, I'm getting away with it.
(DEVICE BEEPS)
It's some sort of
invisible force field.
Uh, it's called glass, Fred.
An invisible force field
made out of glass!
-Genius.
-(GROANS)
-You're just going
to leave me here?
-And us.
Oh, right. You're just
going to leave me
here with these people?
Oh, yeah.
And just to be certain
you never leave,
I've planted thermal
charges like this one
throughout the complex.
How many can there be?
(BEEPING)
So that's what that alien was
doing when Scoob and I went
outside for the drive.
Shannon, name your price!
Anything!
A weekend in Paris with me!
A signed portrait of me!
(ALL EXCLAIM)
You can't put a price
on this sort of fame.
Besides, returning as a hero
will bring me all the money
I could ever want.
Please don't hate me,
especially you, Daphne.
(CLICKS TONGUE) Great hair.
(LAUGHING)
(BEEPING)
-We've got to get out of here.
-How?
-She just left
on the only ship!
-No.
It's not the only ship.
RIDLEY:  I got to hand
it to you. It looks just
like Sly Star One.
But something feels different.
I just can't put
my finger on it.
ZIP:  You can't, 'cause
I'd say that pretty
much is the difference.
I can put my finger on it.
Oh, right.
It's really small.
How are we all
going to fit in there?
This isn't the ship.
It's just the model.
(DOOR OPENING)
Oh, well, that's more like it.
You built this?
I did, with a little help
from the Sly bots.
Well, why did
you keep it a secret?
Well, actually you see, living
up here in the darkness,
all alone, it's been hard.
I built this ship
so I could leave.
But I couldn't.
I knew how much
this place meant to you,
how much you
needed me to stay here.
But there were times
I thought about leaving.
-About being...
-In the spotlight, like me?
No...
About being with my brother.
I'm sorry, Hudson.
I'm sorry for not
being here for you.
Be sure to get
a close shot of my face.
Sly!
Sorry, it's a habit.
(EXPLOSION)
Shannon's explosives are
starting to go off!
We better get going.
Does your ship work?
There's still some glitches
but with some quick work,
she should be up
and running in no time.
(GRUNTING)
There's too many.
This could take days.
We don't have days!
Gee, Daph, you think?
Did you just do all that math
on your own or did your pal
Shannon help you?
Oh, I'm sorry, Velma.
So Shannon wasn't perfect.
Perfect? Daphne, she's
a homicidal lunatic that's
about to blow up the moon!
Oh, Velma, she's not going to
blow up the whole moon.
Just, you know, part of it.
And that's
supposed to be okay?
Stop that!
Stop! Stop! Stop!
Stop it! Stop it! Stop it!
For goodness sake,
we're all going to die
and all you can think about
is arguing over who liked who!
You're crazy!
You're not a robot, are you?
Nope.
I'm an actor playing a robot.
And if it wasn't for you
meddling kids...
ALL: You would have
gotten away with it too.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Blah, blah, blupity...
(STRAINING)
(PANTING)
It's no good.
They're too heavy.
What the heck is in them?
Wow! (LAUGHING)
U-Boat snacks!
A year's supply.
-How in the world are we going
to get through all that?
-(MUNCHING)
Well, yeah.
Like, time for the experts
to take over.
-Right, Scooby-Doo?
-Uh-huh.
(CHUCKLING)
Caroline, about time.
Help us move the last
of these boxes.
That's not Caroline.
She's different.
Oh, for Pete's sake, Ridley,
she's not different.
She's the same old... Oh!
(SCREAMS)
That is different.
Run!
(INAUDIBLE)
RIDLEY: She's going
to kill us.
U-Boat, come on!
No, if she makes it through,
she'll crush the ship.
I'll hold her off
while you guys fix
whatever needs fixing.
Go!
Oh, she's been
idle for too long.
-We're going to have to jump
her from the energy cell.
-We're on it.
(BONES CRACKING)
(YELLS) My back!
My knees aren't
what they used to be.
(BONES CRACKING)
-Maybe we're getting
too old for this.
-No! You're not!
Don't you get it?
You guys are the reasons
why thousands, millions even,
want to become astronauts.
Why I wanted to become one.
You're the inspiration
for dreams
and that sort of stuff
can never get old or obsolete.
You're Zip Elvin and
Colt Steelcase, astronauts.
You'll always be astronauts.
And how great is that?
It's a three-man job.
We'll need someone
to come with us.
-Daphne...
-No, no, Fred. We meant you!
Oh. Me?
Oh!
Ugh! Dirty robot!
(GROANS)
Thanks, but aren't you scared?
(CHUCKLING) Yeah,
like really scared.
But like we said,
when we get scared,
we resort to food.
That's how we deal with it.
Right, Scooby-Doo?
Yeah, and if there's
one thing we love to do
besides eating food...
It's playing with it.
Food fight!
It worked.
The engines are primed.
Hudson, ready when you are.
Well done, guys.
Now get back here.
Hudson, we have a problem.
-What's wrong?
-What is it, Zip?
-The fuel valve is broken.
-(ALARM BLARING)
We gotta hold it on to keep
the power supply running.
We'll have to ride it out of
the engine compartment.
-Okay, I'll fly the...
-(THUDDING)
He's out cold.
Who's going
to fly the ship now?
I've got this...
-Not to worry, I'll...
-(THUDDING)
You can't be serious.
Okay, looks like all that food
has made her sleepy.
Let's get to the ship.
-What happened?
-They got knocked out.
Then who's gonna
fly this thing?
-Don't worry, I...
-BOTH: No!
Oh!
(GROANS)
(BOTH GASP)
Don't worry. I got this.
(GRUNTING)
But they're
all wearing helmets.
-COLT:  What's the hold up?
-Uh...
Everybody's been knocked out.
There's nobody
to fly the ship!
Yes, there is. Stand by.
No! No way, Velma.
I can't. You heard Shannon.
She faked the scores.
Velma, I can't even drive
Fred's van.
I just don't
have the right stuff.
Yes, you do!
You were on the bridge
with Shannon.
You're the only one
that saw how
she flew this thing.
Right now, you know
more than I do about this.
Sure, Shannon might
have faked your score, but
it doesn't matter, Daphne.
It's just a piece of paper.
I don't need
a piece of paper to tell me
what I already know.
That I believe in you.
And that you can do anything
you put your mind to, Daphne.
Wow! Looks like
a billion dollars
going up in smoke.
Yeah, but think
of the publicity.
Everyone, hold
on to something.
This is going to get bumpy.
Fred, we couldn't have had
a better team lead than you.
Thanks.
It was a real honor
working with you.
We're about
to enter the atmosphere.
(ALL SCREAMING)
MALE REPORTER:
Miss Lucas! Miss Lucas!
And it was this terrible alien
that destroyed the station
and my friends.
(SOBBING)
Space is no place
for the average person.
It's for trained astronauts,
like me.
-FRED: That's a great story.
-(GASPS)
If it were true.
And just to be certain
you never leave,
I've planted thermal charges
like this one
throughout the complex.
You can't put a price
on this sort of fame.
Besides, returning as a hero
will bring me all the money
I could ever want.
(CROWD GASPS)
(CAMERA SHUTTERS CLICKING)
She was the alien!
A fake alien!
Sly was right.
Space travel is for everyone!
Sure, it takes training,
but maybe it all starts
with an adventurous spirit,
an imaginative mind,
a brave heart,
-and good old-fashioned...
-Money, tons of the stuff!
-Sly, please!
-Sorry.
And good
old-fashioned curiosity.
Who knows what's out there?
But isn't that
the very reason to go?
(CROWD CHEERING)
(CROWD JEERING)
Like, dude,
it was real swell
meeting you, U-Boat.
Yeah! Yeah! Swell!
Shaggy, Scooby,
it was a real blast!
Come here.
(CHOKING)
Velma, I'm sorry.
I should have seen
that Shannon
wasn't really a true friend,
and that you were always
my best friend.
-Aw. Thanks, Daphne!
Maybe you and...
-(CAMERA SHUTTERS CLICKING)
REPORTER: Tell us
about your trip, Daphne.
REPORTER 2:
How do you keep your hair...
PHOTOGRAPHER: Daphne,
over here! I need some shots
of the hair. It's beautiful!
My hair?
There are far more
important things
to talk about than hair.
Like friendship and support.
Now that's worth a story.
(REPORTERS CLAMORING)
So, I guess there are
no aliens after all.
Oh, I wouldn't say that,
Ridley.
Space is too big.
Who knows what's out there?
You must have been
lonely up there.
No less lonely than someone
who believes in something
when nobody else does.
(EXPLOSION)
Uh, looks like
your ship is ruined.
Yes, but it wouldn't
take me long
to have her back in shape.
And maybe if, uh,
somebody would come with me,
I wouldn't mind
going back up there.
See what we might find.
You mean a copasetic
prime directive involving
a dual core system drive
with a high probability
of some elementary binary
codex and interface time?
I couldn't have
said it better myself.
-(ENGINE STARTING)
-FRED: Easy, just let
the clutch out, easy!
-(GRUNTS)
-DAPHNE: Jeepers!
I'm trying, Fred.
Something must be wrong
with the pedal.
-Okay, calm down.
-I am calm!
-Daph, why don't you try...
-Velma, why don't you try
not being a back seat driver!
I flew a spaceship
for goodness sake!
I think I can handle
the Mystery Machine.
Okay, okay.
Just trying to help.
Go ahead.
FRED: Easy. Easy!
VELMA: Whoa!
ALL: Whoa!
SCOOBY-DOO: Scooby-Dooby-Doo!
(WHIMPERING)
Please rate this subtitle at www.osdb.link/qgr4
Help other users to choose the best subtitles