---
SCREAM 2
I hate scary movies. I should
be studying. You know I got a bio due.
Baby, did I mention that
these tickets were free ?
Sandra Bullock is playing
right down the street.
Nobody wanna pay $7.50 see some Sandra
Bullock shit... unless she's naked.
Oh, but you will sit through
a movie called Stab ?
It's adrenaline, Maureen.
It's good to be scared.
It's primal.
You know what I'm sayin' ?
No, I'm gonna tell you
what it is, okay ?
It's a dumb-ass white movie
about some dumb-ass white girls...
gettin' their white asses
cut the fuck up, okay ?
Yeah. I suppose Sandra Bullock
is Miss Ethnicity, right ?
Well, no, all I'm saying is that
the horror genre is historical...
for excluding
the African-American element.
When the hell you get your Ph.D.
in Black Cinema, Sister Souljah ?
Listen, I read my Entertainment Weekly,
okay ? I know my shit.
Yeah, Maureen. I read my
Black Beat, too, homey.
Tonight we're going to have an
all-black movie, all-black cast,
all-black wardrobe, black eyes-
Everything.
Black-eyed peas. Black cats-
- Crazy.
- Thank you.
- Hi. Here you go.
- What's this ?
Stab souvenirs.
The studio send them.
Hah !
And it's white.
- Thanks.
Thank you.
Kill ! Kill ! Kill !
Very romantic.
Whoa !
Whoo ! Take it off !
Now, why has she got
to be naked ?
What does that have to do with the plot
of the story, her being butt-ass naked ?
I don't know about the plot,
but I got a stiff one.
You better loosen up
that wrist.
Hello ?
Hello.
- Who is this ?
- Guess.
- No, really. Who is this ?
- Were you expecting somebody ?
- No.
Bitch, hang the phone up
and Star-69 his ass ! Damn !
- Shh !
- Who is this ?
- Who would you like it to be ?
I don't like games.
Who is this ?
Look out back.
You see your boyfriend
anywhere ?
I don't even have
a boyfriend right now.
Would you like one ?
Damn it all. Can l- Give me some money.
I need to get some popcorn.
- You got money.
- I asked for your money.
What do you say ?
Cheap ass.
- Thank you.
- Come on.
Cat got your tongue ?
You know, I don't even know you,
and I dislike you already.
Come on !
- Hey, we're sold out.
- Oh, cool !
Hello.
Hi. Um, can I have a medium popcorn,
no butter, and a small diet Pepsi ?
- You got it.
- Thanks.
That's it. I am not
going back in there.
Come on, you chickenshit.
It's just a movie.
No, it's not just a movie.
It's a true story.
All these kids got killed
a couple years ago in California.
- Here's the popcorn.
- Thanks.
I was so scared,
I almost had a heart attack.
Hah !
Stab you, man !
- Whoa !
- You ass !
- I'm sorry. I had to, baby.
- What are you playing ?
- Would you relax ?
God ! What's wrong with you ?
I don't like being scared.
I don't like that.
Baby, it's just
a movie.
Besides, scary movies
are great foreplay.
Excuse me ?
Let's go see
Sandra Bullock.
Oh, no. Sandra started already.
We can stay.
Just stop playin' so much.
All right. I gotta go
to the bathroom.
See ya inside.
Sorry.
Hello ?
No, no, no, no, no, no !
Don't do that !
Move ! Move !
Go !
All right, go !
Baby, give it up.
You came back just in time.
It looks like she's about to get it.
Want some popcorn ?
Uh-uh. See, if that was me,
I would be out of there.
Oh !
Here it comes !
- Here it comes !
Oh, my God !
Whoa, oh, oh
This could be
your lucky day
In hell
- Never know who it might be
At your doorbell
This could be
your lucky day
In hell
Hello ?
- Hello ?
- Hello, Sidney.
- Yes ?
- What's your favorite scary movie ?
- Who is this ?
- You tell me.
Cory Gillis,
555-0176.
- Oh, shit !
- Hot flash, Cory-
- Shit !
- Crank calls are a criminal offense...
prosecuted under
penal code 653-M.
Hope you enjoyed
the movie.
Time to change
numbers again ?
No. It'll die off.
It's opening weekend.
We'll see how it goes.
Okay.
You know, Ron, uh,
it's not an easy thing to be accused
of a crime you didn't commit,
particularly one
as heinous as murder.
But how do people treat you
now that they know the truth...
- about your innocence ?
- Most people are cool.
There's some who still keep
a safe distance, which is odd for me,
'cause I've always been
sort of a people person.
But you were
wrongly accused !
You were fully exonerated.
Yeah, well, that and a nickel
will get you a cup of coffee.
- Even that's not true anymore.
Well, certainly, with Gale Weathers'
book- and now the movie-
- it's set the record straight
for Cotton Weary.
- One would think.
But, uh, Gale's-
Gale's been terrific.
Hey ! Move your ass, okay ?
You're late.
Don't forget about the martini mixer
tonight at the Delta Lambda Zetas.
- I don't think I'm going
to be able to make it, Hal.
- What ?
Don't even try to bag, okay ?
'Cause you promised me.
- A vague promise at best.
- Nobody's asking you to join, okay ?
It's a party.
Free beer, meet the girls.
Hallie, you know me
and organized religion.
- It's a sorority.
- Worse.
Look, Sid, just lower the walls
for the next few days.
This self-induced isolation
you got goin' is not healthy.
- I'm fine.
- "I'm fine."
Yes, I know. "I'm fine" is stretched
tightly across your face.
Check out the news.
The two Windsor College
students were murdered...
last night during a sneak preview
of the new movie Stab.
Police haven't released any information
except for the victims' names,
but a press conference is scheduled
for later today.
The victims, Maureen Evans
and Phil Stevens,
were both Windsor seniors.
- Where's Randy ?
- He's got Film Theory this morning.
...ended with the brutal murders
of two promising-
Sidney ! Sidney !
Sidney, did you know
the victims ?
-Do you feel threatened by the murders ?
-No comment.
-Do you think there'll be more murders ?
-Sidney ! Sidney !
-What can you tell us about the victims?
-How about the police?
- We just need one statement.
- Please talk to us !
You could say what happened in that
theater is a result of the movie itself.
That is so Moral Majority. You can't
blame real violence on entertainment.
What ? Wait a second. Yes, you can.
Don't you even watch the news ?
Yeah. Hello ! The murderer was wearing
a ghost mask, okay ?
Just like in the movie.
It's directly responsible.
No, it's not. Movies are not responsible
for our actions.
It's a classic case of life
imitating art imitating life.
This is not a hypothetical.
It's not about art.
I had Biology with that girl.
This is reality.
Thank you. I agree with you.
Let me tell you about reality, Mickey.
I lived through this.
Okay ?
Life is life.
It doesn't imitate anything.
Come on, Randy,
with all due respect,
the killer obviously patterned himself
after two serial killers...
- who have been immortalized on film.
- Thank you.
Are you suggesting that someone's trying
to make a real-life sequel ?
Stab 2 ? Who'd want to do that ?
Sequels suck.
- Oh, please. Please !
- By definition alone,
they're inferior films.
- Bullshit generalization.
Many sequels have
surpassed their original.
- Oh, yeah ?
- Name one.
Aliens. Far better
than the first.
Yeah, well, there's
no accounting for taste.
Thank you. Ridley Scott rules.
Name another.
No. Aliens is a classic, okay ?
"Get away from her, you bitch !"
Believe the line is "Stay away from her,
you bitch." It's film class, right ?
- Whatever. You know what I mean.
- Another.
- T2.
- Mmm.
You've got a hard-on
for Cameron.
- Big one.
- Wait a second.
- The first Terminator is historical.
- Yeah.
"Sarah Connor ?"
"Yes."
- All right. All right, okay.
House II:
The Second Story.
- What ?
- The entire horror genre
was destroyed by sequels.
Hey, I got it, by the way.
I got it.
The Godfather, Part ll.
Very good.
That's the Oscar-winning exception.
- All right, that's enough.
That'll be a wrap. The sequel discussion
to be continued.
So, Mr. Originality, how would
you make it different ?
I'd let the geek
get the girl.
Three hundred people watched.
Nobody did anything.
They thought it was a publicity stunt,
for Christ's sakes.
And it would have been a good one too.
- It's starting again, Randy.
- It's not.
Shit happens at the movies. People
get robbed, shot, maimed, murdered.
Multiplex is just a very dangerous place
to be these days.
Yeah, and you are
in extreme denial.
And you should be too.
This has nothing to do with us.
Randy, a guy in a ghost mask
hacked up two people...
in a movie theater
telling our life story.
- Coincidence ?
- You know what happened at Woodsboro.
- You can't ignore it.
- I know, Sid, but I don't
want to go back there again.
Can't we just go back to our
pseudo-quasi-happy existence ?
- Hello, Derek. How ya doin' ?
- Hey, Sid.
- I heard. You weren't in class.
- Yeah, I know.
I skipped. I couldn't take all
the "that's her" looks.
Is there anything
I can do ?
Well, you got any tricks
for getting me back...
to a pseudo-quasi-
happy existence ?
- I might just have one for that.
- Yeah ?
Oh, yeah ?
What is it ?
That was pretty good.
Get a room.
They're threatening to what ?
Are you kidding me ?
They'd be stupid
to pull this movie.
With all this free press, they're
gonna have huge numbers this weekend.
It'll break
box office records.
- Consider it done.
Uh, Miss Weathers ?
Hi. I'm Joel.
The affiliate sent me.
I'm your new cameraman.
- Yeah. You got experience ?
- Huh ? Uh, yeah.
I mean, I'm local,
but I shot the bingo finals.
- Great. Great.
- I almost got an award for that.
All right, listen, Joel.
This is how it works.
I point, you shoot.
You stay focussed and fast on your feet,
and we'll get along fine.
You're playing with the big boys now,
you got it ?
Got it ! Got you covered.
I'm all over it.
Don't worry about a thing.
How hard can it be ?
You point and I shoot.
I'm there !
Excuse me, Miss Weathers ?
Uh, could I have a minute ?
- No.
- Just one second.
I-l know you probably
get this all the time,
but I just wanted to say
I am such a big fan of your work.
I just finished you book.
I-l couldn't put it down.
Insightful, probing-
I just really, really loved your book.
- Thank you. Thanks.
- Sure.
I'm a writer myself.
I write for the local paper,
for the Post Telegram.
I'm Debbie Salt. I took your seminar
in Chicago last year.
I was the one in the front row asking
all the questions.
- Right. I thought you looked familiar.
- Oh, thank you.
Um, can't wait
to see the movie.
You know, you must be getting
quite a lot of flak on that, right ?
I mean, with all the
violence-in-cinema issues.
What is your position
going to be ?
- No comment.
- Miss Weathers, please- I would-
It would be an honor for me if I could
just get a quote from you for my story.
Okay. Begin quote:
- Great.
- "Your flattering remarks are
both desperate and obvious."
- Ouch !
- End quote.
Gale, what are you doing here ?
Do you think these murders are
connected to Sidney Prescott ?
Miss Weathers, what's your theory
on these murders ?
What's your feeling
about this ?
May I have your attention.
- My name is Chief Louis Hartley-
- Chief Hartley.
Hi. Gale Weathers,
author of The Woodsboro Murders.
Do you think the killer
will strike again ?
We have no evidence
that this is a serial killer.
- I'd like to read from a prepared-
- Can you tell us of any...
precautions
that you're taking ?
Well, first of all, we think it's just
an isolated incident,
- and we will be-
- Ladies.
Oh, my God.
This is huge.
Do you have
any suspects ?
- Sidney, look. It's Gale Weathers.
- What ?
Star of the Gale Weathers
press conference,
based on the book
by Gale Weathers.
Soon to be a major motion picture
starring Gale Weathers.
- Be kind. She saved our lives.
- She had calf implants.
Chief Hartley, do you plan
on giving the town a curfew ?
I'm gonna get closer.
- So that's her ?
- Yeah.
Hello, girls.
Enjoying yourselves ?
- Hello, Sister Lois, Sister Murphy.
- Hello, pledge. Hi, Sidney.
- Hey.
- This must be flat-out hell for you.
- How are you holding up ?
- I manage.
It's really weird, isn't it ? To think
this fuss is all because of you !
I mean, not directly, but in some
six-degrees-of-Kevin Bacon way.
Hallie, are you gonna bring your friend
to our little martini mixer tonight ?
- I have a lot of work to do.
- We'll be there.
Oh, good. Because Sid,
we have our eyes on you.
You hang in there, and if there's
anything we can do-
The Delta Lambdas are very sensitive
to your plight.
- Yeah. Bye !
- Bye !
- You gonna start to dress
like that once you get in ?
- That's not gonna happen.
The Delta Lambdas are the biggest
bunch of fuckin'-
Hey ! I'm pledging
Delta Lambda, thank you.
Oh, my God.
Who's that ?
Dewey ?
Hey !
- What are you doing here ?
- Ah !
- Oh, I was worried about you.
- Yeah ?
I heard about what happened
and I was on the next plane.
- Oh.
- Can we talk ?
Yeah. Yeah.
Are you okay ?
I'm fine, Dewey,
or I was.
I mean, things were okay
until now.
But, uh,
theater's going great.
I got my first starring role.
We open in two days.
- That is great.
- Yeah. I'm loving it.
You know, and I've got
some great friends,
and, uh,
I'm seeing someone.
Nice guy. Premed,
no apparent psychotic tendencies.
I was just worried.
Look, Sid, if there is some
freaked-out psycho trying to follow...
in Billy Loomis's footsteps,
you probably already know him.
Or her, or them.
They're probably
already in your life.
They get off on that.
I just want you
to be careful, Sid.
Oh, you- You think I don't
know that, Dewey ?
But what am I
supposed to do ?
Just cut everybody off ?
Crawl under a rock ? What ?
Just watch out.
Keep an eye out.
I'm gonna talk to Chief Hartley
and the local police.
I'm gonna
just hang around.
I wanna make sure you're safe,
if that's all right with you.
Yeah.
I'd be honored.
All right, Sid.
Hey.
- You okay ?
- Uh-huh.
- Who was that guy ?
- An old friend.
Deputy Dewey, Woodsboro's finest.
What's he doing here ?
He's worried.
Our surrogate big brother.
Nothing like a funeral to bring
the family together.
I'm gonna go say hi.
- Chief Hartley said the girl
was stabbed seven-
- Drop it.
Hello, Sidney.
- How are you ?
- Hi. What do you want, Gale ?
Well, I was hoping I might get
just a few words with you.
- Cotton.
- Hi, Sidney.
Here we are at Windsor College,
where Sidney Prescott...
has just been reunited with Cotton Weary
for the first time...
since she wrongly accused
him of murdering her mother.
- What the hell are you doing ?
- We want to know how you feel.
Tell us everything that's happened,
looking back on the last two years.
Sidney, I'd just like to say
that I forgive and forget,
and just like you, I'd like to get
back on with my own life.
- Do you have any comments ?
- You bitch !
- Ah-ah.
- Deep breaths. Lot of deep breaths.
Oh, Sidney,
share with us, please !
- I'll share with you !
- Okay, okay, okay.
Did you get that
on film ?
Yes, I got that
on film.
Sid ? Wait, wait, wait,
wait, wait.
Where's she going, Gale ?
Sidney ?
Where's she going ?
Gale, l-l thought we had
an official interview.
What's going on ?
She didn't know ?
- Man, that was cold.
- Hey, you need to check your
conscience at the door, sweetie.
I'm not here
to be loved.
Gale, you promised me ten minutes
of national coverage.
You'll get
your ten minutes...
when I get
my goddamn interview.
Don't walk away from me, Gale.
I'm still-
Gale, I did my part !
Joel !
Dewey.
What are you
doing here ?
Why don't you just
leave her alone ?
Hasn't she been
through enough ?
And my name is Dwight.
I was just doing my job,
Dwight.
-No matter who gets hurt in the process?
-Hey!
Who got punched here-
again ?
Well, I don't condone violence,
but maybe you deserved it.
Page 32: "Deputy Dewey
filled the room...
with his Barney Fife-ish
presence."
You read my book.
Oh, yes, I do read,
Miss Weathers.
Oh, Dewey, don't take it so seriously.
It's a character in a book.
Page 41:
"Deputy Dewey oozed
with inexperience."
Don't you think you're overreacting
just a little bit ?
No. What I think is that you're
a money-hungry, fame-seeking-
and forgive me for saying-
mediocre writer who's got a cold storage
shed where her heart should be.
No offense intended.
Dewey, I never meant
to imply-
How do you know that my
dimwitted inexperience isn't...
merely a subtle form of manipulation
used to lower people's expectations,
enhancing my ability to effectively
maneuver within any given situation ?
I'm sorry.
I don't know
what else to say...
except I'm sorry.
No. I'm the one
that's sorry.
I misjudged you.
Now, if you'll
excuse me,
I have some oozing to do.
One more thing.
Nice streaks.
Well.
Hey, I am not
a sorority pusher.
I just think,
despite its trivialities,
it is a life-affirming, mentally stable,
healthy environment for you.
I mean,
look at this place.
I think you're taking your psych major
a little too seriously, Hallie.
I'm fine.
Yeah ? That's beginning
to become your theme song.
"I'm fine." Yeah- Fucked up,
insecure, neurotic and emotional.
Sidney, you made it !
Hi !
No, I really mean that.
- Hi.
Do you girls
want a drink ?
Uh, well, actually, yeah, but
you know what ? We'll get it ourselves.
I love those guys.
Are they still together ?
I haven't seen it
in, like, three weeks.
- No, they broke up again.
- Really ?
Mm-hmm. Sarah found out
that Bailey slept with Gwen.
She dumped him, like,
two episodes ago.
I wish she'd get
her shit together.
- Hold on. Someone's calling.
Omega Beta Zeta.
Hello ?
- Yes ?
- Who is this ?
- Cici. Who's this ?
- Who do you think ?
Ted ?
Where are you ?
Are you drinking ?
Hold on.
Ted's on the other line.
He sounds drunk. I'll call you back.
That shit only calls you
when he's drunk.
- Don't go over there, Cici.
- All right. I'll call you back.
Okay, Ted. You sound loaded.
What's up ?
Who's Ted ?
Oh, I'm sorry.
My bad.
I thought you were
someone else.
That's okay.
I am.
Who are you calling for ?
Nobody's here.
Where is everybody ?
We're cosponsoring the acid rain mixer
at Phi Gamma Alpha tonight.
- Why aren't you there ?
- I'm "sober sister."
I need to be here in case
a drunk sister calls and needs a ride.
- That's too bad.
- "Drink with your brain."
That's our motto.
- Who are you calling for ?
- What if I said you ?
What if I said good-bye ?
Why would you
want to do that ?
- Why do you always answer
a question with a question ?
- I'm inquisitive.
Yeah, and I'm impatient. Do you want
to leave a message for someone ?
Do you want to die
tonight, Cici ?
Omega Beta Zeta.
So, was it Teddy ?
No. It was some creep asshole
trying to scare me.
That movie Stab is
bringing out the crazies.
- Shit.
- What is it ?
- I heard a noise.
- Where ?
Upstairs.
- Shit !
- Hello ? Hello ?
- Kill, kill, kill, kill, kill, kill.
- Die, die, die, die, die. - Stop it !
I can't believe you're alone
in that house.
- I don't think I'm alone.
I'm out of here.
You're breaking up.
Where are you ?
- Outside.
- Don't panic, Cici.
- Call campus security.
- Okay.
Campus Security.
- Hi. I'm calling from the Omega Beta-
- I can't hear you. Hello ?
Hello ?
- Can you hear me now ?
- Hello ?
- Hello ? Shit !
- Campus Security.
- Yes. I'm calling from-
I can't hear you.
Hello ?
-I'm calling from Omega Beta Zeta house.
Look, someone
is harassing me.
- Hello ? Shit !
- Hey !
- Jesus, Dawnie, you scared me.
- I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Did anyone call for me ?
- What are you doing here ?
- I live here, remember ?
I just thought you were
going to the mixer.
Yeah, I am. I had to change,
so I'll be out of here now.
Omega Beta Zeta.
- Is Cici there ?
- Mm-hmm. Who's calling ?
- It's Ted.
- It's your ill-conceived boyfriend.
Okay, so, I'll
see you later.
And don't forget
to set the alarm.
Bye.
Hello, Ted.
Wish it was Ted. Don't forget
to set the alarm.
Hello ?
No ! Please, no !
- No !
Never said I was innocent
I will burn in hell
for the things I've done to you
Never said
I was anything good
Everyone thinks that sororities
are just about blow jobs,
- but it's not true.
- We only promote safe, condomed sex.
See, we're about love,
respect and responsibility.
Harmonica style
is okay, right ?
- Oh, yeah.
- Cocktail ?
What took you so long ?
And you know, Derek is
a Delta Lambda big brother.
And we like to keep it
all in the family.
Wow. You know, you girls have
really given me a lot to think about.
Thanks.
It's working.
- Hey, babe. You wanna dance ?
- Oh, I'd love to...
with that tall, wide-shouldered
fraternity boy.
- Think you can arrange that ?
- That hurts.
The Empire Strikes Back. It
was a better story, improved effects.
Not a sequel. It was part of a trilogy.
Completely planned.
I like those
little furry things.
They're Ewoks.
They blow.
Hey.
- How ya doin' ?
- Good.
- Twits being nice to you ?
- Painfully nice.
I take it you will not be pledging
Delta Lambda Zeta.
I think not.
- I'm crushed.
- Hey, guys.
Something is up
at Omega Beta Zeta.
- Police are everywhere.
- Hurry !
Come on, let's go !
- Way to break up the party !
- Shit !
I should have brought
my drink.
Death by blunt trauma,
and there's a double stabbing.
So it's definitely
not suicide.
Okay.
Thank you.
Gale, hi. You're just getting here.
It's not good.
It's a single victim:
sorority girl.
So- I gotta go.
I've got a deadline.
- Joel, let's go.
- In-In a minute.
It's happening again,
isn't it ?
You'd love that,
wouldn't you ?
- Please, stay back.
Better hurry, Gale.
Might get scooped.
Come on, I'm just trying
to get close enough...
- to get a shot.
- Move it, Joel.
Gale, I have to be honest with you.
I'm not cut out for this.
I mean, I was brought here to do
an interview, not Faces of Death 14.
Do not fuck with me.
Come on.
Get your jacket.
Let's get you home.
Yeah.
- You about ready ?
Almost.
- Hello ?
- Hello, Sidney.
Remember me ?
- What do you want ?
- I want you. It's show time.
Then why don't you show your face,
you fucking coward.
- My pleasure.
Derek !
- Sid ? Sid ?
- Sid ?
Sid !
- It's me. It's me.
- You okay ? You okay ?
- Yeah. Yeah.
No, Derek !
Don't !
Sid !
Dewey !
- The killer's in there. And Derek.
- You all right ?
- He went that way.
Sidney, he's in here !
Is everything okay ?
He got me. He got me.
- Now, apply pressure to it.
- Don't do that-
The police are on their way.
Thanks for your cooperation.
Hallie, I'll be with you
in a few minutes, okay ?
Uh, no problem.
That's the easiest interrogation
of my crime-filled life.
I'm gonna go get a quick cup of coffee.
You want ?
No.
You want some, Sid ?
How you doin' ?
You all right ?
Not at all.
You know, I knew
this was coming.
- I knew this wasn't over.
- You are not alone, Sid.
Okay ?
We are all here for you.
All right ?
Whatever you need.
- That poor girl.
- I know.
It's crazy, but-
- Derek could've been killed, you know.
- But he wasn't.
He's fine.
He just needs to realize...
the '90s is no time
to play hero.
Why would anyone go back
in that house anyway ?
I went around to the back of the house
and ran into Sid there.
That's when she told me the killer
was inside, so I went in to see.
- You're lucky there's no nerve damage.
You're gonna have
to take it easy though.
- So then
you went back inside the house ?
- Yeah.
No struggle ? He just cut you
and ran away ?
- You're lucky he didn't kill you.
- Yeah, it's awfully convenient.
- Say what ?
- Nothing.
It's just a shame
he got away so easily.
you got there too late,
right after he disappeared.
Yeah, it is.
We got three victims.
Maureen Evans,
Phil Stevens...
and Cici Cooper.
- Is Cici the girl's real name ?
- Oh, uh, no.
It's, uh, Casey.
Casey Cooper.
As in Casey Becker ?
- Excuse me ?
- She was a young victim in Woodsboro.
As well as her boyfriend,
Steven Orth.
As in Phil Stevens.
Maureen Evans- Maureen Prescott.
That's Sidney's mother.
Do you think someone's
trying to duplicate Woodsboro ?
It looks like it.
I think you have a copycat
on your hands, Chief.
Jesus Christ !
What are you doing
to keep Sidney safe ?
I got my two best
detectives guarding her.
Do these guys have to follow
you around everywhere ?
Oh. We're attached
at the hip.
- How am I ever gonna get you alone ?
- You know, to be honest, Derek,
I think it would probably be
in your best interest to...
stay as far away
from me as possible.
I hope that was an
off-the-cuff remark...
that holds no
subtext whatsoever.
No, actually.
I mean it.
I mean, look at you.
You already got hurt.
I don't want to see
that happen again.
I'll take my chances.
Derek, I'm serious.
This is serious.
You are concerned with my
personal well-being and...
not with trusting me
or anything, right ?
Like I said, I just don't want
to see you get hurt.
And I don't want
Okay, Sid ?
- Take care, Miss Weathers.
- All right.
- Dewey.
- Chief.
Hi.
So, I'm heading over to admissions
to do some leg work. You game ?
I'm not here to write
a book, Miss Weathers.
I'm here to help Sid.
I want to help her, too.
And help myself,
of course.
Come on, Dewey. Smile just once.
Please ?
I'll smile when
I catch the killer.
Gale, hi. So who
do you think did it ?
What about Sidney's father ?
Has he been ruled out as a suspect ?
Well, he's supposedly out of the country
on business,
but that sounds a little fishy,
don't you think ?
-I'm not here to do your job, Miss Salt.
-What about this ex-cop, Dewey ?
-It's kind of strange that he showed up.
-Yeah, what's he doing here ?
Dewey's a good guy,
unlike some of us.
Really ?
Well, it just seems to me that
if the killer is repeating...
what happened in Woodsboro,
it's quite possible that the killer...
could be from Woodsboro.
That's all.
Derek, you think Sid will let me
interview her for my documentary ?
Oh, yeah. You know, she turned down
Primetime Live, 20/20 and Dateline.
- But for you, yeah.
- Drop it.
I've been thinking about
this whole murder thing.
- Have they checked out Randy ?
- What ?
I know he's an innocent victim the first
time around, but he's a little off.
- You know what I'm saying ?
- Come on. Randy ? The guy's harmless.
- That's what they said about Dahmer.
- Guys, keep it down.
Come on.
What's up, Sid ?
- Hey, Sid.
- How's it goin' ?
Where are
the Secret Service guys ?
Uh, over there.
And which one
is Kevin Costner ?
The one on the right
is Officer Richards.
He is a Capricorn.
Divorced. Father of two.
And the one on the left
is Officer Andrews. He is a Gemini.
He's single,
but I think he's gay.
- Really ?
- Mm-hmm.
Derek ?
Penny for your thoughts.
"This morning, I woke up
with this feeling...
I didn't know
how to deal with."
And so I just
decided to myself
I'd hide it to myself
- What is he doing ?
Uh, Tom Cruise,
Top Gun, 1986.
- Derek, don't.
- When you walked into the room
- I think I love you
- Don't do this.
I think I love you
Isn't that what life is made of
And though
it worries me to say
- I've never felt this way, hey
I think I love you
So what am I so afraid of
I'm afraid that I'm not sure of
A love there is no cure for
I think I love you
Isn't that what life is made of
- And though it worries me to say
- I've never felt this way
Believe me
You really don't have to worry
I only wanna
make you happy
And if you say
"Hey, go away"
I will
But I think better still
I better stick around
and love you
Do you think I have a case
Let me ask you to your face
Do you really love me
'Cause I think
I love you
Let's show
a little love, huh ?
Come on.
Come here, come here.
Don't worry, Sid.
I know things are a little crazy.
Isn't that a big
frat faux pas ?
Oh, yeah.
That is a big no-no.
See, you're not supposed to give
your Greek letters to your girl...
no shape, way or form.
The brothers are gonna kick his ass,
but it's tradition.
- It's tradition.
- It's good luck.
It'll protect you.
So, tell us about this part
you're getting rave reviews for.
Well, I play this young girl,
Sidney Prescott,
who discovers that her boyfriend
is this crazy serial killer...
who also killed her mother
the year before that.
So what kind of research
did you do for the part ?
I don't get it. They get
Tori Spelling to play Sid,
and they cast Joe Blow Nobody
to play me.
- At least you get David Schwimmer.
I get the guy who drove
Jane Seymore's stagecoach...
for one episode
of Doctor Quinn.
This is Tori Spelling
starring in the new film Stab.
Billy, you scared me.
- What are you doing here ?
- They let me go, Sid. I didn't do it.
- I'm innocent.
- I know.
- Please.
- Why won't you let me touch you ?
Look, I've been going through a lot
lately, Billy. And with my mom-
Sid, I think you need
to just deal with that and move on.
I mean, when my mom
left my dad, I accepted it.
That's the way
the cookie crumbles. Moms leave.
Yeah, your mom left town. She's not
buried in the cemetery somewhere.
My mom's dead, and she's
never coming back. Ever.
- Stupid.
- Ooh, I love scary movies.
I'll wait for video. Okay,
let's get down to business.
The way I see it,
someone's out to make a sequel.
You know, cash in on all
the movie murder hoopla.
So it's our job to observe
the rules of the sequel.
Number one: the body count
is always bigger.
Two: the death scenes are always much
more elaborate; more blood, more gore.
Carnage candy. Your core audience
just expects it.
And three: if you want your sequel
to become a franchise, never ever-
How do we find the killer, Randy ?
That's what I wanna know.
Oh. Let's look
at the suspects.
There's Derek, the obvious boyfriend.
Hello, Billy Loomis.
The guy's premed, and his
pity-me surface wound...
conveniently missed every major vein
and artery.
- So you think it's Derek ?
- Not so fast.
Let's assume the killer,
or 'ers, has a half a brain.
He's not a Nick At Night
rerun type of guy.
He wants to break
some new ground.
- Right ? So forget the boyfriend.
- Right.
- It's tired. Who else do we got ?
- There's-
Mickey, the freaky
Tarantino film student.
But if he's a suspect, so am l.
So, let's move on.
Whoa, wait a-
Let's not move on.
Maybe you are a suspect.
Well, if I'm a suspect,
you're a suspect.
You have a point.
Okay, let's move on to-
- Hallie.
- Sid's roommate ?
- Uh-huh.
- Serial killers
are typically white males.
That's why it's perfect. It's sort of
against the rules, but not really.
Mrs. Voorhees was
a terrific serial killer.
And there's always room
for Candyman's daughter.
She's sweet. She's deadly.
She's bad for your teeth.
Come on, Randy.
These kids are your friends.
Who do you think's
the killer ?
- How about Gale Weathers ?
- Gale ? A killer ?
- Why not ?
- Well, she is vicious enough.
- She's an opportunist.
- Yeah.
Isn't it conceivable
she's planning her next book ?
That's what reporters do, Dewey.
They stage the news.
No. Gale's a lot of things,
but Gale's not a killer.
- Just because you're sweet on her-
- No, I'm not.
Please, this is me talking.
Randy,
the unrequited love-slave
of Sidney Prescott.
I know all
about obsession...
and pain.
- You've got your love scar to prove it.
- And so do you.
And what's with that limp anyway,
'cause you were stabbed in the back.
Severed nerve.
Look, Gale's no killer.
Okay, okay.
Whatever you say.
But if she's not a killer,
she's a target.
Joel, let's get
some establishing shots.
Um, Gale,
can we talk for a sec ?
- What is it ?
- Look, I'm a little confused here.
I mean, with your
given track record,
why would you wanna be here
when the killer strikes again ?
I mean, granted, I should've read
your book before I took this job.
But I'm reading it now,
and- Whoo !
I read what happened
to your last cameraman.
The guy got gutted.
Now, me,
I'm gonna do what any
rational human being would do,
which is get the fuck
out of here.
First of all, he wasn't gutted.
I made that up.
His throat was slashed.
What are you-
Gale, gutted, slashed,
the guy ain't in
the union no more.
It's a job, Joel.
And like every job,
there's a few drawbacks.
But you're a professional cameraman.
You've got to act like one.
Yeah, but I wanna report the news.
I don't wanna be the news.
Besides, brothers don't last long
in situations like this.
This is national television.
Think about it.
This is a big chance
for you.
The story is monumental.
Don't you wanna be a part of that ?
Come on.
I need you.
I cannot do this without you.
Good.
Come on.
- Let's get some work done.
- Yeah, let's go get killed.
We've been through this before.
You know what I think about
your potential as an actress.
I know.
It-It's just that with,
um, the murders...
and the movie
and my life-
I do know how difficult
it is for you.
Gus, l-l just-
I don't think I can do it.
The battle for the soul is
fought in the forum of art.
You're a fighter, Sid. That's why you're
here. That's why this is your major.
- Yeah, I'm a fighter.
- I didn't hear that.
- I'm a fighter.
- I don't believe you.
I don't.
I'm a fighter.
Okay.
So, at the risk of sounding
like a college drama teacher,
if you've got pain around
this kind of material, use it.
This is your role, Sid.
Cassandra is one of the great tragic
visionaries of literature.
She saw it all coming.
The wars,
the murder,
the madness.
She knew
she was cursed.
It was her fate,
and she embraced it.
None of us can avoid our fate,
but as an artist...
you can honestly face it...
and fight it.
- You're good.
- There's no understudy. I'm desperate.
You can do this.
Okay, everybody. Gather around.
Third Act, one last time.
Cue the music.
All behold the dreaded
fate of Troy...
that once stood proud and light
upon the hills of Sparta !
Now shrouded in
the deathly smoke of ruin,
her royal children
pitched from her walls,
her people driven
through her ruins.
And now alone in
fate's cruel isolation...
stands Cassandra,
her kingdom,
family and friends...
driven to the wind.
- No crime against gods or man...
have I committed,
saith to speak
the truth.
And each hideous vision
born from my mind...
has come to pass.
Troy has fallen,
not by my hand
or wish,
but as I foresaw.
So now,
fate's vengeful eye...
is fixed...
on me.
Tell us, O Cassandra,
where has the sweetness...
of life gone ?
What stays fate's hand
from striking now at thee ?
from thee ?
What stays fate's hand
All right, hold it.
Hold it !
Everyone, take five.
Sidney ?
Sid.
Your escort has arrived.
- Derek, how long have you been here ?
- I just got here.
- Is everything okay ? What's goin' on ?
- What happened to Mickey ?
We swapped. He had to edit.
You get me instead. What happened ?
Derek, don't.
Don't. I-l just need to be alone
right now, okay ?
Being alone is not
the answer, Sid.
Yeah, well,
I think it is.
I need some distance.
Well, do I
get a say in this ?
No.
I guess I'm supposed
to be... understanding.
Yeah.
You got it.
All right. Let's just assume the killer
is repeating Woodsboro-
- Yes ?
- I have Bob calling.
- I'll have to call you back.
That doesn't
explain Sidney's attack.
Sidney wasn't killed
in Woodsboro.
Wasn't for
a lack of trying.
The killer's trying
to finish what was started.
- Sid's under protection, right ?
- Yeah.
- What ?
- Bob really needs to talk to you-
- Tell Bob I'll call him back.
- When'd she start smoking ?
- Ever since
those nude pictures on the internet.
It was just my head.
It was Jennifer Aniston's body.
Anyway, you're
forgetting something.
In Woodsboro, there were more victims
before the homestretch-
Tatum, my cameraman,
Himbry-
Time out ! I don't need to be hearing
about no dead cameramen, all right ?
Now, I'm warning you guys. I am a verb
away from vacatin' these premises.
I'm gonna get me some coffee,
donuts, Prozac,
see if I can find some crack,
Special K- "X," not Malcolm-
and I'll be back when you guys
start talking about something...
a little more Saved By The Bell-ish,
all right ?
- He seems a little shaky.
- Don't worry about him.
If the killer is following a pattern,
maybe we can figure out who's next.
I wouldn't follow
a killer's pattern.
We were all involved in Woodsboro.
Could be any one of us.
So what do you wanna do, bonehead ? Sit
here and wait and see who drops next ?
- Well, I don't know. "Phonehead."
- Gale's not here !
I'm not interrupting anything, am I ?
You three
look deep in thought.
Have you ever felt a knife
cut through human flesh...
- and scrape the bone beneath ?
- It's him.
- Who ?
- The killer.
He can see us.
- Just keep him on the phone.
- What do you want me to say ?
I-l don't know. Just keep him talking.
Come on, Gale.
- Uh- Hi.
- What are we doing ?
Look for somebody
with a cell phone.
- So what's your favorite scary movie ?
- You'll never find me.
What do you care ?
Let 'em have their fun.
So, uh-
What's up ?
What's your
favorite scary movie ?
Showgirls. Absolutely frightening.
What's yours ?
- What's your problem ?
- Sorry.
Wait. Let me guess.
The House On Sorority Row ?
Dorm That Dripped Blood ?
Splatter University ?
Graduation Day ?
Final Exam ?
- Am I close ?
- Closer than you think.
Too slow, geek.
Do you want to die ?
Is that the best you can do ? Because
Billy and Stu were much more original.
Hey !
- Who's this ?
- Gale Weathers, author of
The Woodsboro Murders.
- Who ?
Come on.
Okay.
He's gotta be
around here someplace.
He's just playing with us.
White male suspect-
nine o'clock.
- My clock or your clock ?
- Your clock.
I'll go
around the back.
Why are you even here,
Randy ?
You'll never be
the leading man.
Fuck you !
No matter how hard you try,
you'll never be the hero,
and you'll never, ever
get the girl.
- Shit !
- Shit ! Sorry.
- Hey, man-
- Wrong guy, dead boy.
Oh, yeah ? Well, let's redirect
a moment, Mr. I'm-So-Original.
- What's she doing ?
- I don't know.
Hey ! Ah !
- What just happened ?
-What the hell are you doing ?
- A citizen's arrest-
- Can I help you ?
- Hello ? Hello ?
- Sorry. Beg your pardon.
Where's your innovation ? Why copycat
two high school loser-ass dickheads ?
Stu was a pussy-ass
wet rag.
And Billy Loomis- Billy Loomis !
What the fuck !
Jesus ! What a rat-lookin',
homo-repressed mama's boy !
Why not set
your goals higher, huh ?
You wanna be one
of the big boys ? Huh ?
Manson, Bundy, O.J.,
Son-
-Where's Randy ?
-I don't know. This guy just grabbed me.
- I'm okay, Mom.
- I don't see him.
Randy !
Ah !
What's goin' on ?
Yo, man.
Who broke my window ?
Did your computer
just freeze ?
You have an instant message,
that's all. Just hit "alt-M."
Yeah, but I'm
not signed on.
Someone here in the library.
All the terminals are connected.
- He's here.
- Shit.
Get here away from the computer.
Sid, it's probably just a sick joke.
- May I see your screen, please.
- Wait right here.
Yeah.
- Psst ! Sid, you okay ?
- Cotton.
- Can we talk for a sec ?
Um, this, this isn't
a good time.
Come on, Sid.
You sent me to prison.
I did over a year for you.
You can give me two minutes.
Cotton, I'm sorry. Every day I'm sorry.
I don't know how to apologize anymore.
Sorry-schmarry, Sid. I have the solution
to all of our problems.
What are you
talking about ?
First of all,
forget Gale Weathers.
She doesn't get it. She doesn't
see the story. Between you and me,
she wouldn't see the story if
it smacked her in the side of the head.
I mean, have you read that book ?
Which brings me to my point.
Who calls me out of the blue,
but Diane Sawyer.
Believe me, I was
as shocked as you are.
She tells me that if you and I
go on the air together,
- she will give us the entire hour.
- What ?
We're talking prime time, Sid.
You, me and Diane Sawyer.
- Cotton, I can't.
- No, no. Look, Sidney.
If this is about money,
it's not like we're not getting paid.
There's $10,000 each,
not to mention what I've got going
on the side with the 900 number.
- Cotton-
- I know. You don't like the press.
I know that,
and I respect it.
But-But, Sidney-
It's Diane Sawyer. Hello ?
She's a class act. Sidney, this could
be some very, very heavy exposure.
I'm sorry.
Look, between the movie
and the book...
people know the truth.
Let's get on with our lives.
There's been enough exposure.
Why would you want any more ?
Why ? I don't know,
Sidney. I don't know.
Uh, maybe because I fucking
deserve a little exposure ?
I mean, come on, Sidney.
You dragged my name through the mud,
everybody thinks I'm
some kind of psycho killer,
and all I'm asking for is one fucking
Diane Sawyer interview...
to maybe get my side
of the story straight.
Now, I don't think I'm being
unreasonable in that request.
Do you ?
Honestly ?
I'm... sorry, Cotton,
but no.
You're sorry.
Yeah, I bet you're
real sorry, Sidney.
Such a good angle, Sidney.
Loveable and fucked up Sidney Prescott !
Everybody's favorite
little victim !
- Ow ! What are you doing ?
- Relax !
- Put your hands on top of your head !
- Shut the fuck up !
Jesus ! I'm not Billy Loomis !
You killed him ! He's dead ! Remember ?
Run it by me one more time,
will ya ?
- Why did you attack Sidney Prescott ?
- I didn't- There was no attack.
We were talking
very heatedly.
Miss Prescott and l...
have a very
complicated past.
I didn't think
that was a crime.
- No, but homicide is.
- Okay then, book me. Book me.
Okay ? Look.
I don't know about homicide,
but you've definitely...
got me for raising my voice
in a public library.
We're dealing with four murders
here. You watch your mouth.
That shouldn't have been Randy.
- It should have been me.
- No.
I should call his mother.
Sid, I already made
that phone call.
Are you okay ?
Stop treating me like glass,
Dewey, I'm not gonna break.
It's okay to break.
It's not gonna happen.
You better hope
your alibi's airtight.
Could I please remind everyone here
that I'm an innocent man.
Don't you watch TV ? Current Edition ?
That was a very insightful program...
on which it was made abundantly clear
that I'm an innocent man.
So until you find me standing over
a dead body with a knife in my hand,
I think you better treat me
with the rights and privileges...
accorded to every innocent citizen
in this country.
I don't- Is there- Is there
some problem with the word "innocent" ?
I know. It's a big one.
Chief ?
- What's going on ?
- I have to let him go.
- Why ?
- We don't have anything on him.
Sign here.
Gale.
Enjoying the show ?
- Cops are funny.
- What do you think you're doing ?
Waiting for
my 15 minutes of fame.
You can understand that,
can't you, Gale ?
Don't do anything stupid,
Cotton.
Gale, you were so
instrumental in my freedom.
You're not having
character doubts now, are you ?
- Sidney, if you change your mind-
- Come on. Take a hike.
Sorry about that.
What a creep.
They're gonna take you
somewhere safe, Sid.
Yeah ?
Where's that.
I don't know, but I'll
be there with you.
We should get going.
We'll take you by the dorm,
and you can pack some things.
We've issued
a campus lock-in this evening.
-No one's allowed out after dark, okay ?
-Yeah.
Who's doing this, Dewey ?
I mean,
if not Cotton,
then who ?
I don't know, Sid,
but I'll find him.
Any leads, Gale ? Do you think
the killer will come after you ?
How does it feel to be
on the other side of the news ?
There's Cotton.
Cotton ! Hey !
- Are you still a suspect ?
- It's all been a huge misunderstanding.
- Have you been officially released ?
- Gale ! Hang on one second.
How about a photo ?
No ? You look great.
How're you
holding up, Gale ?
Must be scary knowing somebody's
out there waiting, watching,
enjoying all this.
- How does that make you feel ?
- Look, local woman !
I know that you hold me up
as your career template...
and it gives you some sort of...
charge to challenge me.
But give it a rest !
You're right. I'm sorry.
It's my-
It was the wrong time.
I'm sorry.
- What's going on ?
- Whoo, let's see. For starters,
they impounded my van.
It's now an official
crime scene, thanks to you.
Here's your footage.
Enjoy.
See ya.
Wouldn't wanna be ya.
Joel, I need you !
No. No, you need to
have your head examined.
- I feel bad, Dewey.
I feel really bad.
I never say that
because...
I never feel bad
about anything.
But I feel bad now.
Is this
just another...
brilliant Gale Weathers
performance ?
There are no cameras here.
I just wanna find this fucker !
I- I really do.
Me too.
Could I
give you a hand ?
What's in here ?
Just some crowd footage
that Joel shot.
Hey, wait a minute.
If the killer really is
watching and relishing every minute,
then he'd be here
on these tapes, right ?
- At each crime scene.
- It's worth a look.
It's definitely
worth a look.
This way.
Dubbing room.
Editorial.
Video archive.
- It's locked.
- Can you pick it ?
- That would be breaking and entering.
- No shit.
There's gotta be a VCR
around here somewhere.
What's in there ?
- Now we're gettin' somewhere.
- Perfect !
- Let's start with this one.
- Sorry. Oh !
- Oh !
- Ow.
- I'm sorry.
- Did I hurt you ?
- No.
You're a money-hungry,
fame-seeking-
forgive me for saying-
mediocre writer...
who's got a cold storage shed
where her heart should be.
- I didn't mean to imply-
- Listen.
- You're cute when you're angry.
- I was rude.
I was being rude.
Dewey, I'm sorry.
I never meant
to hurt you. Hey.
Really.
I should be studying.
You know I got a Bio-
Dewey.
Dewey !
- Sorry.
- That's not my footage.
Outside.
- Fuck you !
- No matter how hard you try,
you'll never be the hero,
and you'll never, ever
get the girl.
- Sorry.
- Wrong guy, dead boy.
- Stay here.
- Dewey, don't !
Dewey !
There's no one there.
Fuck !
Gale !
Gale ?
No !
So.
Listen, Sid.
Hey, wait up !
- She's- She's fine.
- I'm her therapist.
Bye, Derek.
Bye.
We better get going.
When this is all over,
I'll still be here.
You ! Prepare to die.
- You gave up your letters.
- Oh, man.
I'm not-
Uh, guys-
- To Troy ! We march !
- Whoo !
This is so romantic.
- And so Greek !
I was in the wrong place
But it must have been the right time
I was in the right place
But it must have been the wrong song
I was in the right vein
But it seemed like the wrong arm
I was in the right world
But it seemed like wrong, wrong, wrong
- Wrong song
- Who do you love, baby ?
- Sidney.
- Did you say
"my Omega Kappa Beta brothers" ?
No, I said Sidney !
So, where are you
taking us, anyway ?
If we tell you,
we'll have to kill you.
Don't ask; don't tell.
Help me !
Oh, my God !
Outta the car,
you fucker !
Get down back there !
Come on, you son-of-a-bitch !
I'll blow your
fuckin' head-
- Is he dead ?
- I don't think so.
- He's still breathing.
- Oh !
Oh, is he dead ?
Oh, God.
I think so.
- How are you
supposed to get outta here ?
- We're not. It's a cop car.
Hallie, it's the only way out.
Help me out.
Come on.
We're jammed up against
a pole.
Oh, my God.
Oh. Oh, my God.
Come on, Sid.
Don't ! Sid !
God, I hate this shit.
Oh, my God.
Don't do that again.
Try the window.
- Shit !
- Get me the fuck outta here, Sid.
I can't. The door's jammed.
You have to go through the front.
- Oh, no fuckin' way.
- Hallie, do it.
Go on.
Hallie, go.
Okay.
Okay, that's right.
Shh.
Okay.
Okay, that's good.
Oh, right
through his eye.
Come on.
That's good. Easy. Easy.
He's not gonna hurt you.
Come on. Let's go.
Let's go.
- Hallie.
- What ?
I wanna know
who it is.
- Oh, no. Come on, Sid.
Please ? Let's just go.
- I'm going back.
Look, look.
Stupid people go back.
Smart people run. We're smart people, so
we should just get the fuck outta here.
Hallie, I'm sick
of running.
- If we know who it is, then it's over.
- No, we can just get the police.
And when we come back, he'll be gone.
It'll only take a minute.
- I have to do this.
- Sid. No, Sid. Come back !
Sid, come back.
Shit.
- Oh, shit.
- What ?
- He's gone !
- No !
- Gale.
- No, no, no, no.
This isn't what it looks like.
- Get away from me.
I found Dewey. I tried to help him.
I- No, no. Gale, wait.
Gale ! Gale, wait !
Gale !
Shit.
- You can't miss the street-
- Help me !
- ...curfew in full effect.
- Give me the goddamn phone !
- Gale. I was right
in the middle of a story.
- I've got your goddamn story !
- What's the matter ?
- Operator, this is an emergency !
Get me the police !
- What's happening ?
- The killer !
It's Cotton-fucking-Weary !
Cotton Weary ?
Hello ?
Gus ?
Derek ?
Derek !
Oh, God.
Thank you. Thank God, Sid. Thought I was
gonna be up there till opening night.
- Shit ! Who tied these ?
We gotta get outta here.
- The brothers got me, Sid.
- He's out there. He killed Hallie.
- What are you talking about ?
- The killer ! He's here.
- Where ?
Right here.
- You're fast, Sid.
- Get me down. Hurry !
I wouldn't do that if I were you.
You really wanna trust your boyfriend ?
Don't you know history repeats itself ?
Hmm, Sid ?
Mickey.
Surprise, Sidney.
- What the fuck ?
- Since Derek, here,
disappeared on my ass,
I been on my own
all fuckin' night.
- Thanks a lot, partner.
- You motherfucker !
Sid, he's crazy.
You know me better than that.
Come on, Sid.
I gotta have a partner.
I couldn't have possibly
done this alone.
- God, Derek.
- Sid.
Oh, no, Sid. Sid.
No, no, no, no.
It's okay, Derek.
We got her.
You-
Sid, he's lying !
Sid ! Sid !
Untie me.
- Sid, untie me.
- Hmm ?
Boyfriend. Killer.
Sid, the man is lying !
Untie me. Sid.
Untie me.
What do you think, Derek ?
Sidney experiencing some deja vu ?
No. No. I am gonna
fuckin' kill you !
Fuckin' kill you !
You are dead ! Dead !
- Derek.
- Sid. - Derek.
I'm sorry.
I never...
would've...
hurt you.
Never.
You should really deal with
your trust issues, Sid.
I mean, poor Derek. He's completely
innocent. And such a nice boy too.
He's bright and funny and
handsome. Decent singing voice.
And he was gonna be a doctor.
This was just the kind of boy
you'd like to take home to Mom.
- If you had a mom.
- Fuck you !
Oh ! So vulgar. Did Billy
let you talk to him this way ?
Billy was a sick fuck,
just like you.
No. Billy was a sick fuck
who tried to get away with it.
Mickey is a sick fuck
who wants to get caught. Yeah !
See, I've got my whole defense
planned out.
I'm gonna blame
the movies.
Pretty cool, huh ?
It hasn't been done before.
You see, this is just the beginning,
a prelude to the trial.
That's where the real fun is 'cause
these days it's all about the trial.
Can't you see it ? The effects
of cinema violence on society.
I'll get Dershovitz
or Cochran to represent me.
Bob Dole on the witness stand
in my defense.
Hell, the Christian Coalition'll
pay my legal fees.
It's airtight, Sid.
I'm an innocent victim.
- You're a psychotic.
- Yeah, well. Shh.
That'll be our little secret.
'Cause people love a good trial.
It's like theater. They're dyin' for it.
And I've worked hard
to give the audience what they want.
That's what Billy was good at.
He knew... it's all about...
- execution.
- Yeah ?
Well, you're forgetting
one thing about Billy Loomis.
What's that ?
I fucking killed him.
You piece of shit !
Sid.
You got a Linda Hamilton
thing going.
No, no. It's nice.
I like it.
Now, who's doin' that ?
Could that be... the mystery guest
waiting in the wings ?
Told ya I had a partner.
Surprise cameo
just for you.
Gale.
Mrs. Loomis ?
- What ?
- Billy's mother !
Nice twist, huh ?
Didn't see it comin', did ya ?
Jesus.
It can't be. I've-
I've seen pictures of you.
This is 60 pounds
and a lot of work later.
It's called a make-over.
You should try it.
Look a little tired
yourself there, Gale.
- So you two are in this together ?
- Yeah, well.
Had to have financing.
Tuition's expensive.
Deb, there- my backer. We met on the
Internet. Psycho Web site. Classifieds.
There's only an estimated
97 active serial killers in the country.
So Mickey, here, was quite a find.
Definitely one on the way up.
- All he needed was a little
guidance and nurturing.
- As only a mother can do.
Told you it was gonna work.
Wait till the trial !
It is gonna rock !
Oh, Mickey.
There's not gonna be a trial.
- Gale !
Two birds, one stone.
Oh, Mickey was a good boy, but, my God,
that whole blame the movies motive.
Did you buy that
for one second ?
Poor boy was completely
out of his mind.
- And you're not ?
- No. I'm very sane.
My motive isn't
as '90s as Mickey's.
Mine is just
good old fashioned revenge.
You killed my son !
And now I kill you. And I can't think
of anything more rational.
You're never gonna
get away with this.
Of course I will.
Everything's traceable
back to Mickey.
Including the cop gun he used
to kill everybody.
But let's just suppose
that you...
had gotten hold
of the other cop's gun.
And you chased Mickey. And there was
a big shoot-out and a big scuffle.
And you shot Mickey,
killed Mickey dead.
But not before he got off
one shot at you.
Okay. So, have I
covered everything ?
Are there any questions, any comments ?
You know what, though ?
Who give a flyin' fuck
anyway ?
Let 'em try and track down
the second possible killer.
Debbie Salt doesn't exist.
You're as crazy
as your son was.
What did you just say ?
Was that a negative, disparaging
remark about my son ? About my Billy ?
No, Billy was a good boy.
Billy was perfect.
You did a bang up job, Mrs. Loomis.
It's not wise to patronize
a woman with a gun, Sidney.
Randy spoke poorly of Billy,
and I got a little knife happy.
I was a good mother.
You know what
makes me sick ?
I'm sick to death of people saying
that it's all the parent's fault.
That it all starts with the family.
You wanna blame someone ?
Why don't you blame
your mother ?
She's the one who stole my husband
and broke up my family.
And then you took my son !
You don't know what it is
to be a mother.
To raise a child and teach him...
and guide him-
And abandon him.
Isn't Mickey
supposed to be dead ?
Don't you fuckin' move !
- Goddammit !
- Cotton.
Okay, okay, okay.
Everybody slow down.
I have had
a very, very bad day,
and I would like to know exactly
what the fuck is going on here ?
- Sidney ?
- Cotton, meet Billy Loomis' mother.
She's the killer.
What ?
- Then who's that ?
- The other killer.
- Mickey.
- Okay.
- Look, Cotton-
- Shut up.
So. Hi.
You're, uh,
not Debbie Salt, are you ?
You're not with
the Post Telegraph.
No, but I can still
help you, Cotton.
Ah-ah-ah !
You don't need her.
Let me kill her !
As long as she's alive,
you're never gonna be the lead story.
That's what you really want,
isn't it, Cotton ?
If you really wanna be
in the spotlight,
just let me kill her...
right now.
Then you're the only survivor.
You're the star !
She sent you to prison
for a year !
Personally, I think
it's rather poetic.
No. No, Cotton,
don't you listen to her.
Well- Well-
It's, uh, quite a predicament
you're in, Sid.
- Cotton-
- I mean, she makes a good point.
Let me think about this.
Maybe you should too.
Betcha that Diane Sawyer interview's
lookin' real good right about now.
Huh ?
Consider it done.
Wow.
That... was intense.
Hey, Sidney, uh-
Look, I want you to know that I would
never, ever do anything to hurt you.
Cotton, give me the gun.
Yeah. Okay. Sure.
Take it.
Hey, Sid, we should talk about
exactly what happened here.
You know- I mean, get our stories
straight for the press statement.
- Oh, shit !
- Cotton.
- Could somebody get me outta here ?
Gale !
Are you all right ?
I been shot.
Of course not.
- Help !
- Give me your hand, Gale.
Jesus, Gale,
you scared the crap outta me.
- Isn't anybody else
down there, is there ?
- No.
So much for reporting
from the trenches, huh ?
- Shut up, Cotton.
- How bad is it ?
Just bounced off my ribs.
Geez, Gale, you got
more lives than a cat.
Give me one of those.
Is she dead ?
I don't know.
They always come back.
Whoa !
Just in case.
- That about wraps it up, Chief.
- Okay, Frank.
Take it easy.
You got a couple broken ribs.
- Greg, I'm okay.
- Sure.
Hey, Gale.
Are you all right ?
- Joel.
- I'm- I'm back.
You know, I was thinking maybe we could
get the scoop like in the old days.
You're Gale Weathers...
at Windsor College.
We got a live one here !
- Move it !
- Where's Gale ?
- There room in that one over there ?
- Yeah ! Watch your back !
- Dewey !
- Let's go !
- Oh, God.
I can't believe
you're alive.
- Are you okay ?
- Gale.
You hang in there.
- Knife went into some old scar tissue.
Saved his life.
Bye-bye.
- I'm coming with you.
- Can you tell us what you saw ?
- What happened in there ?
Can you tell us how it feels
to be a hero ?
Talk to Cotton. He's the man
you want to interview.
He's the hero.
- Cotton !
- What went on in there ?
- Is it true you're a hero ?
- Details, please !
- Look, guys,
no one wants to give you
the story more than I do.
Unfortunately, there is
a time and a place,
and indeed, a price for everything,
so feel free to call me.
Come on, Cotton.
Tell us something.
Well, uh,
I'll tell you one thing.
It'll make a hell of a movie.
Thank you.
Life's river shall rise
She said
And only the strong
shall survive, she said
But I'm feeling quite weak
she said
Will you comfort
and forgive me, she said
She said
she's still searching
For salvation's light
Yet she wishes all day
And then she prays all night
She said she won't
speak of love
'Cause love
she's never known
Well, it's
moments like these
When she hates to be alone
Forgive me
She said
I'm sleepin' and right in
the middle of a good dream
When all at once I wake up
from something that keeps
knocking at my brain
Before I go insane I hold
my pillow to my head
And spring up in my bed screaming out
the words I dread
I think I love you
So what am I so afraid of
I'm afraid that I'm not sure of
a love there is no cure for
I think I love you
Isn't that what life is made of
Though it worries me to say
that I never felt this way, yeah
Believe me, you really
don't have to worry
I only wanna make you happy
And if you say hey, go away, I will
But I think better still
I'd better stay around and love you
Do you think I have a case
Let me ask you to your face
I think I love you
Yeah, I think I love you
So what am I so afraid of
Afraid that I'm not sure of
a love there is no cure for
I think I love you
Isn't that what life is made of
Though it worries me to say
that I never felt this way, yeah
I don't know what I'm up against,
I don't know what it's all about
I got so much to think about
Yeah
Yeah, I think I love you
So what am I so afraid of
I'm afraid that I'm not sure of
A love there is no cure for
Do you think you love me
I think I love you
Pain goes away
I dig a hole
When it goes away
I'll dig a hole
Runnin', goin' out at night
Friends they
push and pull you
Burned out ground
Poor flowers
Spinning, falling outta time
When it goes away
I'll dig a hole
La-la-la-la, ooh
When it goes away
I'm reminded
Someone thought they knew me
That I hadn't changed at all
Wrapped up in a
picture perfect package
That just stands up
way too tall
Because they see my world
Ooh, through
the eyes of sand
You walk in desert,
Baby, you're a polished stone
Ooh, oh
You don't know my world
Ah-ah
You walk in the desert
And I walk in the desert
Yeah, I walk in the desert
Scream !
Could be your best friend.
Could be your enemy.
Scream
I hear him coming
I see him coming
I hear him coming, Peace
Y'all be trippin'
Man, the ghetto got me I know it
I be like eyes open, turnin'
With both of my toys on him
These daydreams sometimes
turn to nightmares
I be trying to shake it
but it seem to be like right there
I know some homies who made
deals for a short time to live good
But when its all over you should see
the data that'll put 'em out the hood
One, two
I'm comin' for you
Three, four
I'm kickin' up in your door
This whole life
it seem to be a bad dream
Scream as loud as you want but
ain't nobody gonna hear your scream
Scream
I hear him coming
I see him coming