Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org
That is the ugliest thing I've
ever seen in my whole life!
It certainly is.
Who sent it?
Oh! That's strange.
It doesn't say.
Where could it
have come from?
I don't like it.
It's staring at me.
Oh, it's probably one of
Uncle Arthur's little jokes.
Well, I don't think
it's funny at all.
Darling, I'm
just going to have a shower.
Be there in a minute.
Claudia, I told you not to
leave your toys lying about.
Good God! You are hideous.
Claudia.
What?
I have a bone to pick
you with you, young lady.
We had an agreement,
didn't we?
Didn't we?
But, Daddy, I
didn't leave it there.
In a civilized society,
our word is our bond.
I don't know what
you're talking about.
Just because
it's your birthday,
that doesn't mean
that you can relinquish all...
Richard?
Richard, what was that?
You killed
my mommy and daddy.
And now
you're pissing your pants!
You're pissing your pants!
Wake up!
And now, ladies and gentlemen,
what you've all
been waiting for
Shitface!
And the greatest ventriloquist
in all of England:
the psychotic Psychs!
This grotesque abomination...
He ain't even
anatomically correct.
Don't laugh.
It's a serious condition.
Six years ago, I found it in
a cemetery back in the States.
Little fucker
tried to rip me throat out.
I was trying
to give you a hug.
I don't know much about myself.
I know I'm an orphan.
I know I'm a freak.
And, of course,
I know that I'm Japanese.
But why do I have
such terrible nightmares?
Filled with hate
and blood and guts.
I'm not like that at all.
I wouldn't even hurt a fly.
Oh, there he goes,
back to his family.
Oh, I envy him.
Sometimes I wonder
about my own parents.
Were they Zen masters?
Did they serve the emperor?
Oh, sometimes I wonder what my
mom and dad were really like.
So, you don't
believe in Santa Claus?
Well, trust me, honey, tonight
I'm going to make you believe.
You wait and see what Santa is
bringing you, you naughty girl.
No, I can hear you fine.
You're not breakin' up.
Sheila, I just said
you're not breakin' up.
Oh.
You're breaking up with me?
Wait, you're breakin' up
with me on Christmas Eve?
Sheila, you have got to be
fuckin' kidding me!
Sheila!
Well, that's just great.
God!
I knew it!
You're not real.
You were never real.
You know what
that kind of disappointment
can do to somebody?
Do you have any idea
how that can
fuck with your mind?
Fuck with your mind!
Fuck with your
mind! Fuck with your mind!
Fuck with your mind!
Chucky is broke again.
This is bloody ridiculous.
Cut! Cut! Cut!
Kill the snow.
Get off me.
Tony, what was that?
I'm sorry,
it's... it's...
This is unprofessional,
and I can't work like this!
No, Jason, I'm sorry.
No, Jason. Please wait.
We're here in Hollywood,
where production is underway
on the new horror flick,
Chucky Goes Psycho.
The film tells the urban
legend of Chucky and Tiffany,
two dolls supposedly possessed
by serial killers.
The dolls were
found at the scene
of a string
of real-life murders
which remain unsolved
to this day.
Hey, you guys, I think, uh,
Tiffany's left arm is loose again.
Yeah, uh,
I'm looking for Jennifer.
Does anyone have
a 20 on Jennifer?
Check the catering truck.
Mmm.
Jennifer.
I got you a Skinny Quick.
Oh, uh...
Miss Tilly,
we're ready for you on set.
Jennifer, I am so proud of you.
For what?
For sticking to your diet.
Oh, thank you.
What's going on
in the world today?
Julia Roberts is getting $25
million for her next film.
Julia Roberts.
I'm so tired of hearing
about Julia Roberts.
You know, I should have
played Erin Brockovich.
I could have done it
without a Wonderbra.
Julia stole that part
right out from under me.
And you know
how she did it?
She slept
with the director.
That's what I think.
Jennifer,
you know that's not true.
How come I don't ever get
any of the good roles anymore?
How come nobody
takes me seriously?
Nice tits.
Thank you.
Look at me. I'm an Oscar
nominee, for Christ's sake.
Now I'm fucking
a puppet.
I've got no fan mail,
no paparazzi, no stalkers.
Well, there must be something
I'm right for?
Let's see.
Uh... Oh.
Hip-hop superstar
turned director, Redman,
is still looking
for the right actress
to take the female lead
in his upcoming Bible epic.
Well, that sounds good.
What's the role?
The Virgin Mary.
What's so funny?
Nothing.
It's perfect.
It's just what I need
to reinvent myself.
The Virgin Mary.
I always loved
the way she wore robes
and her hair off her face,
kind of like this.
Joan, Joan,
get Morty on the phone
and tell him I need to take
a meeting with this Redman.
Right away.
Okay.
That's a wrap for
Access Hollywood.
Reporting from Hollywood,
where, as you can see,
Chucky and Tiffany
are alive and well.
You can catch their movie
in theaters next Halloween.
Thank you, Chucky.
Fuck you very much.
I'm no orphan after all!
Well,
you were shit last night.
You are going to have
to be more scary.
Scary?
Uh-huh.
Let's rehearse,
shall we, all right?
Oh.
Hello.
Look, you got to learn
to tap into
your killer instincts, mate,
give in to
your natural impulses.
Or else I'm going to
have to, uh,
fire you.
Hey!
Come here!
"Mary, you are truly a
vision of unsullied innocence,
"unique among all women,
"as pure as the virgin snow.
"But I ask,
what is troubling you?"
"Joseph, husband,
there has been a miracle.
"As I stand before you,
I must tell you
"I am with child. "
"But, Mary,
how could this be?
"In accordance
with God's wishes,
"we have never lain together
as man and wife. "
"Yes, it is true.
"And I beg you that you
believe me when I tell you
"I have never lain
with any man at all.
"Do you believe me, Joseph?
Do you?"
Do you?
Yes. Yes, I do.
Uh, you were great.
You were super.
Thank you,
thank you, Mr. Man.
Oh, can I call you Red?
Listen, there's a whole lot of
different ways I could do it.
Not just the way you saw.
I could do it faster,
I could do it slower.
I could...
I could do it as a rap.
Uh, no, no,
no, no.
You already showed me
a side of the character
that, uh,
I've never seen before.
Oh, thank you.
But I think I'm going to have
to go with my first choice.
Thanks for
comin' by anyway.
I mean, really,
I'm a huge, huge fan.
I really want to work with
you one day. We should call...
Um, excuse me, I hope
you don't mind my asking,
but who is your first choice?
Julia Roberts.
But thanks for
comin' by, anyway.
Um, listen, listen, Red.
Um, I've been giving a lot
of thought to this project,
and I have a lot
of interesting ideas
about the character.
And I was thinkin' maybe
you would like to discuss it
in a more intimate setting.
Just the two of us.
Oh. Oh, well,
I didn't know you were that
passionate about the role.
Oh, yes,
I'm very passionate.
Mmm.
So, shall we say my place?
8:00?
Pardon me, sir.
Oh. Oh.
Uh, sorry.
Sorry, sir.
Don't mind me.
Excuse me.
Oh, dear.
Oh, dear. Oh, dear.
Mom?
Dad?
I've dreamed of this moment
all my life.
I know this must come
as quite a shock.
It's going to be
an adjustment for all of us.
Look, I still have the
necklace you left me.
I've always wanted to know,
what do these words mean?
Is it our family motto?
Please say something.
It's because of
the way I look, isn't it?
For pity's sake,
please wake up.
"Wake up"?
"Awake. "
Tiff?
Chucky?
Who the hell are you?
Shitface.
Now, what kind
of a name is that?
Where are your
mother and father?
Judging from that face,
my guess is they're hidin'.
Shut up,
you asshole.
Well, come on. It looks like
the kid fell off the ugly tree
and hit every branch
on the way down.
I mean, you got to feel bad
for the parents.
I wonder what
they must look like.
Whoa.
Oh, my God.
What? No.
We, uh...
You didn't... We didn't...
Sweetface, come to Mommy.
What's... What's going on?
Where are we?
In Hollywood.
I saw you on the telly.
Chucky, Chucky, wake up.
Look at us.
We've had makeovers.
We're movie stars.
Shit. Barbie mode.
No, they're puppets.
They don't walk and talk
by themselves.
Listen,
if you want them to work,
I'm going to have to
take them apart.
Is Mommy ill?
The courts thought so.
Heads up!
They're stark raving mad!
Hey, you're pissin'
your pants.
Chucky,
she just had an accident.
You mean,
"he" had an accident.
Don't look at me.
See, what did I tell you?
A beautiful little girl.
What? Are you blind?
That's my boy.
Yeah.
He just hasn't had
his growth spurt, yet.
Don't worry
about it, Son.
You're a late bloomer,
that's all.
And it's high time
that you had a real name.
Let's see.
I think
I'm going to call you
Glen.
Glen?
What kind of a name is that
for a girl?
Don't listen to him, honey.
From now on, your name is
Glenda.
Run, Glenda.
Jeez, what a mess.
Ugh.
There you are,
Mr. Goodbar.
Jennifer Tilly.
Hello.
Hey.
Oh, my God.
You look so real.
You are cuter
than my last boyfriend.
I think we make
a lovely couple.
Jennifer. Miss Tilly, were
you having an affair with him?
I don't know
what you're talking about.
Pete Peters,
Celebrities Revealed.
Jennifer,
what did you see?
What, you want me
to draw you a picture?
Would you?
Somebody give her
a piece of paper.
Look, I'm not gonna
draw you a picture, okay?
Oh, don't feel bad.
You're an actress
not an artist.
What were you doin'
when you saw the body?
No comment.
Jennifer, I love you.
I...
Is it true that you and Redman
are in talks
about you starring
in his new movie?
Yes. As a matter of
fact, that is true. I have...
Can I have your autograph?
Okay, sure.
Hey, hold on,
you forgot the head.
Excuse me. Excuse me.
Excuse me.
Jennifer,
how old are you really?
Paparazzi scumbag!
What year were you born?
Give us the exact date.
I want to sit up
front with you.
Sure.
What are you hiding?
Hey, you okay?
Yeah, I am now.
We're on the boulevard
We're cruisin' in my car
See all the fellows turn
to look and see
So, are you a pair
of ninja assassins?
Huh?
Are you hit men
for the yakuza?
We're not from Japan.
We're from Jersey.
Just think, Jennifer Tilly
is playing me in a movie.
It's absolutely
perfect casting.
But that voice!
I know, she sounds just
like an angel.
Now, I've got it all
figured out.
I'm going to transfer my soul
into Jennifer
and you're going to transfer
your soul into Redman.
I'm down with that.
We'll ditch these plastic
bodies once and for all,
and we'll be
Hollywood's hottest couple.
What about me?
Don't worry, Glenda.
I've got that
figured out, too.
You're going to be
a real live girl.
Boy.
How?
Well, I'm not getting pregnant
again, I'll tell you that much.
My mother always told me,
"Once is a blessing.
Twice is a curse. "
Well, that would explain
your sister.
The only sensible option
is a surrogate mother.
Hey.
Jennifer, I have
something important...
Yeah, hold on a second,
sweetheart.
Hello?
What are you doing?
I'm busy.
I do have a life,
you know.
Turn on the news.
Were you
having an affair?
The actress
discovered the victim's body.
As of yet, there is
no official confirmation
as to whether or not
Miss Tilly is a suspect.
Jesus!
Can you believe this?
Are you okay?
I've had better days.
Um, listen, Joan, I need you
to do something for me.
I need you to get me
a bottle of champagne
and bring it by my house.
What for?
Well,
I've got a big night tonight.
Tonight?
With who?
Redman.
Jennifer, what are you up to?
Thank you, Joan.
Oh, come on, Stan,
it's just business.
He'll be out of there
by midnight.
Oh, my God,
she's a complete slut.
Nighty-night, Glenda.
Sleep tight.
Leave it on.
Oh, sweetie, there's nothing
to be scared of.
Your daddy and I
will be right here.
Why do you kill people?
Excuse me?
Why do you kill?
It's a hobby, really.
It helps us relax.
Am I going to be a killer?
Of course. It's been a family
tradition for generations.
But violence is bad,
isn't it?
They said so on TV.
Not "violence. "
"Violins. "
Violins are bad.
That screeching music's gonna
ruin the goddamn country.
Chucky, Glenda's right.
It's time
we owned up to it.
We have a problem
with killing.
I don't have "a problem"
I like a little killing
now and then.
What's wrong with that?
Killing is an addiction,
like any other drug.
But we're parents now.
We have to set
a good example.
Oh, let's quit, Chucky,
right now.
Cold turkey.
You have got to be kidding.
Promise me, Chucky,
no more killing.
No.
Chucky?
No, no.
No more killing.
We can't do it anymore.
No, no.
A thousand times no.
We have the future to
think of. We have a child!
Fine!
All right, already.
I promise.
Thank you, doll baby.
You're
a sweetheart.
Now we really will be
the perfect family.
Did you hear that?
Maybe you should
forget the director
and fuck
the exterminator instead.
So, how do I look?
Never mind.
Jennifer,
this is beneath you.
Think about what you're doing.
What are people gonna say?
Who cares what people say?
But don't you see
how evil this is?
I don't wanna hear it.
You're prostituting yourself
so you can play
the Virgin Mary.
Joan, I don't
wanna hear it.
Oh, this is so evil.
You're going to hell.
No.
Hell would be ending up
on Celebrity Fear Factor
in a worm-eating contest
with Anna Nicole Smith.
Which you'd win.
He's here.
Let yourself out the back.
And while you're at it,
why don't you leave
your key on the counter?
What are you saying?
Well, you think
I'm so disgusting.
You think
I'm going to hell.
I'm only trying
to survive here, Joan.
God knows I wouldn't want to
drag you down with me.
I'm saying you're fired.
Cut 'em up
I'm gonna hit that ass
Now, in artificial insemination,
timing is everything.
So you'll have to hurry.
That shouldn't be
a problem for you.
Yeah, yeah, just don't let
that player get into her pants.
I don't want him
touching my woman
till I'm him
and you're her.
Right.
Hey.
Aren't you going to give me
a hand here?
Mmm.
Too tall.
Hey, lezbos.
Done her.
Here we go.
Come to papa.
Cheers.
You know, I wasn't bullshittin'
when I told you I was a fan.
Oh, That's so sweet,
Redman.
Which of my films
is your favorite?
That movie when you and
that chick was makin' out.
Oh, Bound.
Everybody likes that one.
You still in
touch with homegirl?
Gina?
Yeah.
Oh, yeah,
sure, we're friends.
Wow.
Close friends.
Whoa.
Very close friends.
Maybe, the three of us
could hang out
together some time.
You know, I would really
like that a lot.
Okay. I'll see
if I can make it happen.
Bottoms up, baby.
Skol.
Redman, um,
I was wondering
what's it gonna take
to make you see me
as a virgin.
Well, you tell me.
A masturbating midget?
Get it, mini-meat.
Whoa.
Oh, sweet Jesus,
God bless the little people.
I don't know
if I can do this.
Why not?
What will people say?
Man, fuck what people say.
Know what I'm saying? This was
meant to be, baby, for real.
Know how I know?
Because the man upstairs
told me so.
Really?
Hell, yeah.
Look,
Mel Gibson ain't the only one
God's been talkin' to
in Hollywood.
And He personally told me
that you was my Virgin.
Well, I guess...
What the hell?
Pig.
And you...
You should be
ashamed of yourself.
Where's your self-respect?
You know what my mother used
to say about dirty girls?
She said,
"You can always smell it
"on girls who sell it. "
Um, by the way, Miss Tilly,
can I have your autograph?
I'm a big fan.
What am I
supposed to do with this?
Now, Miss Tilly,
I know you're frightened.
You're probably
even wondering
if you've gone
completely insane.
But I promise you, tomorrow
you're going to wake up,
and this will all seem
just like a bad dream.
In the meantime,
we can do this the easy way
or the hard way.
It's really up to you.
No wonder
her career's in trouble.
Check it out, Tiff.
Look at the size
of his feet.
You know what they say.
Fuck, she's fat.
I can't believe it.
She's not even pregnant yet.
Paparazzi scumbag.
Uh, looks like you've got
everything under control.
I'll just leave you to it.
Motherhood is so beautiful.
No.
Sorry, just messin'
with you.
What time is it?
Time to get dressed.
We are going to have our own
boys' night out, just you and me.
How does that sound?
Where are we going?
Hunting.
I can't see anything.
Maybe we should slow down?
No! You're doing great.
Son of a bitch!
Up yours, asshole!
What?
Not you, Son.
Come on, floor it!
Oops! I did it again.
Jesus Christ!
No!
Attaboy!
No, I didn't.
And I thought
you weren't ready.
Kid, you're
a fuckin' natural!
But he... he
hit the shelf.
And don't worry
about your mother.
It will be
our little secret.
Say "cheese. "
Good morning.
Oh. Hi.
We must have really
got wired last night.
Yeah.
Redman, did we...
You don't...
You don't remember?
No. It's all a blur.
What about you?
I kind of remember
you screamin' a lot.
Oh, yeah,
I seem to remember that, too.
You know, I tend to have
that effect on women.
Really?
Yeah.
Wait, I do remember
I had the strangest dream.
I dreamt my guardian angel
came to me.
She had the sweetest voice
I have ever heard.
She told me to
respect myself.
And then she asked
for my autograph.
Let's see.
"Step Number One:
Admit I have an addiction. "
Okay, check.
"Step Number Two:
"Give myself over
to a higher power. "
Whatever.
Oh. Here we go.
"Step Number Nine:
"The recovering addict
must make amends
"to anyone he or she
has harmed. "
Hmm.
Hello?
Good morning.
Is this Ruth Bailey?
Speaking.
The widow of Robert Bailey?
Yes. Who is this?
Mrs. Bailey,
my name is Tiffany Ray.
Um, you don't know me,
but a few years ago,
I killed your husband.
And I am
so very, very sorry.
What is this,
some kind of sick joke?
Oh, no,
I'm completely serious.
But I want you to know
I'm in recovery now
and I have put all of that
behind me.
I don't know
who you are...
Thank you, Mrs. Bailey.
Have a nice day.
I feel better already.
Morning, Stan.
Hey, wasn't there
something important
you wanted to tell me?
Well, uh,
the thing is, Jennifer...
I'm sorry.
I don't know
what's gotten into me.
Um, so you were saying...
Forget it.
Okay.
Now, let's see.
What should we
do today?
I'm pregnant.
Redman, I said
Congratulations.
Who is the baby's daddy?
Don't even look at me.
Well, I haven't slept
with anyone else
to advance
my career lately.
Who are you kidding?
It's true, Redman.
Look,
I know I come off
all slutty,
but that's... that's
for my image. It's just...
Do you think
anyone would cast me
in these sexpot roles
if they knew I hadn't
been laid in a year?
I haven't even slept
with my driver yet
and I think
he really likes me.
Hey, that's all very
touchin' and shit.
But I'm telling you,
it can't be me.
Why not?
I had a vasectomy
as soon as I got to Hollywood.
I ain't no idiot.
Well, then,
that's impossible. I...
Hey, Jennifer,
I hate to break it to you.
But I can't hire you
if you're pregnant.
That is ridiculous.
The character is pregnant.
Yeah, I know,
but I have a very specific
vision of Mary.
And what can I say?
She gots to be hot.
That pig!
Recovery Hotline.
Yes, I'm in recovery.
And I'm afraid
I'm going to have a slip.
Can you
get to a meeting?
No, it's really
not an option.
I just freak everybody out.
Don't be
so hard on yourself.
We're not here
to judge you.
What's your name?
Tiffany.
Listen to me, Tiffany.
I know exactly what
you are going through.
You do?
Yes, I... I do.
In fact, I'm gonna let you in
on a little secret.
Just last week,
I had a slip.
Really?
Yes.
And believe you me,
it was not pretty.
It never is, is it?
In fact, it took me 3 hours
just to clean up the mess.
Oh, God, don't remind me.
But I'm not beating myself up
over it.
You know why, Tiffany?
Why?
Because Rome
wasn't built in a day.
You're right.
You are absolutely right.
Hello? Speaking.
Well, who's this?
All right, I know.
I understand who you are.
I just don't know
how you got my phone number.
Because it is a private,
unlisted phone number.
Pete Peters?
Yeah, I saw him yesterday.
No, I don't have
any relationship with him.
He is a firking
paparazzi
that is trying to
get pictures of me
in compromising positions.
Yeah, I'm with Redman.
Redman, he's a director.
Oh, yeah.
Well, he's a rapper, too.
He is a rapper-director,
okay?
He's a hyphenate.
Bye-bye.
Jennifer...
Do you mind?
I'm on the phone.
There's been another murder.
What?
No, I told you where I was.
I was right here all night
with Redman.
What? I don't...
You're not telling me
I'm a suspect.
All right, I'll be fine.
I'm on my way.
I'm leaving.
You can let yourself out.
By the way,
Redman, drop dead.
Oh, Glenda.
Glenda, honey.
Everything is okay.
It was just a little slip.
There's no need
to tell your daddy.
It will be our
little secret, okay?
Okay? Shh.
It's
D- day here at San Quentin.
Who would have thought
it would ever come to this?
They're executing
Martha Stewart this morning.
I don't think I can take
nine months of this shit.
Silly Chucky.
It is
a voodoo pregnancy.
It's accelerated.
How accelerated?
It is 102.7, KllSFM,
LA's number one
hit music station.
Ryan Seacrest in the morning.
Ellen K., I don't know
if I can take it.
What's on the way?
We have bad
weather on the way in LA, Hollywood,
and surrounding area.
Now, we're
not used to bad weather.
No, we're not.
I'm not quite sure how that's
going to affect my whole vibe.
Oh.
This is Joan.
Joan. Joan, I'm...
I'm... I'm fat.
You're not fat.
No, I am fat.
I'm... I'm huge!
For the love of Mary,
I'm pregnant.
Oh, my God.
No, I should have
listened to you, Joan.
You said it was evil
and I was going to hell.
You're right,
and now God is punishing me.
Oh, God.
Is it Redman's?
No, it's definitely
not Redman's.
What?
It's definitely
not Redman's.
What an asshole.
W- What makes you
say that?
Say what?
That Redman is
an asshole.
I didn't say it,
you did.
No, I didn't.
So he's not
an asshole?
Yes, he is.
Joan, will you please
stop doing that?
Doing what?
Imitating me.
I do not sound like that.
Oh, yes, you do.
I do.
Joan, will you shut up?
There's something
really wrong with me!
I'm pregnant. I don't...
Jennifer, what's wrong?
Nothing.
Nothing, I'm fine.
I heard you scream.
I can still
hear you screaming!
Oh. Oh, I mean, it's just...
Well, Bound is on cable.
Gina Gershon
is fingering me.
I love this movie. Don't you?
Jennifer.
Yeah, uh-huh,
that's really interesting,
but I've got to go. Bye.
Jennifer.
Too tight?
Yes.
Ain't no such thing.
What are you doing?
Stop it.
What the hell is
going on in here?
She, um,
came on to me.
Help me!
Somebody help me!
Shut her up,
asshole.
Help me! Somebody help me!
Somebody help me!
What the hell
is this?
We had an agreement,
Chucky.
We decided,
for the sake of our child
we weren't going
to do this shit anymore!
No, you decided.
Just like you decided
our son was a girl.
He is a girl!
He is a boy, God damn it!
And he is
the most promising killer
I have ever seen.
You should have
been there, Tiff.
You would have been
so proud of him.
I want a girl!
I want a boy!
You are tearing me apart!
What about what I want?
What?
Doesn't what I want
mean anything at all?
Oh.
Okay, interesting.
Tell us.
What do you want,
Sweetface?
I think
I want to be a boy.
Yes!
In your face, lady!
But being a girl
would be nice, too.
Hmm.
Well, which is it?
I'm not sure.
Sometimes I feel
like a boy.
like a girl.
Can't I be both?
Well, some people...
Uh-uh!
No way.
But one thing
I do know for sure.
I don't want
to be a killer.
Glenda.
Glen. Whatever.
I'm so proud of you.
No matter what happens,
we'll deal with it together,
as a family.
Okay, Okasan.
Wait a minute.
I'm not going to let you
poison our son's mind
with your touchy-feely,
12-step bullshit.
If you two don't want
to kill anymore,
that's your loss.
But don't look
down your noses at me.
I'm not ashamed
to be a killer.
I'm proud of it.
It is not an addiction.
It is a choice.
And it is not something
that you should have to
hide in a closet!
Whoa!
Oh.
Oh, dear.
Oh, God.
Well, well, well.
Looks like
Miss High and Mighty
ain't so perfect
after all.
It was just
a little slip.
Rome wasn't built in a day,
you know.
Besides, the fucker
really had it coming.
Well, what about
my body?
I'll take care of it.
Jennifer, I love you.
I love you.
This is Stan.
Hello, it's Jennifer.
Stan, baby, I need your body.
I'll be right there.
Jennifer,
if anything happens to me,
I want you to know...
They really
do make a cute couple,
don't you think?
It's like my
mother always said...
Christ!
Enough with your mother,
already.
I killed that bitch
20 years ago
and she still won't shut up.
There, there.
It won't be long now.
Jennifer!
Who is it?
Jennifer.
It's that nosy bitch, Joan.
I'll take care of her.
I wouldn't want you
to violate
your delicate sensibilities.
Jennifer!
Jennifer.
Oh, my God.
Look out behind you!
Joan!
No!
Dang!
Look, I'm not going to
give you crap.
Nobody is perfect, Tiff.
I got a few skeletons
in the closet myself.
See?
Well, come on, Tiff.
How long did it take
to build Rome, anyway?
Tiff.
Glen?
Guess again, Daddy.
Glenda?
That's my name.
Don't you wear it out.
Oh, shit.
What did I miss?
Oh, nothing much.
I just fired Joan.
Looks like you
win after all, Tiff.
Congratulations.
Oh, you both win.
I'm a real lady-killer
if you catch my drift.
I'm a bona fide bonus baby.
Jesus Christ, Chucky,
what did you do to him?
What did I do?
Hmm.
At least I spent time
with the kid.
Glen, wake up.
Stop it, Mommy.
You'll wrinkle
my dress.
Oh, and how
do you like it?
I made it meself.
Like mother,
like daughter, right?
like daughter.
Get it?
"Mother and daughter. "
I said, wake up! Right now.
Mom? Dad?
What am I?
Push, Miss Tilly. Push.
I am pushing,
you little star-fucker!
Pay no attention
to little Miss Potty Mouth.
She's hormonal.
My God. It's coming.
I can see its little head.
What is it?
It's a boy.
A boy.
Oh, thank God.
Give me my baby.
I want my baby.
Chucky, Chucky, uh,
well, we're not done here yet.
What?
Jennifer isn't done.
We've got another one here!
Push, Jennifer!
Push! Push, push.
Push it out! Push!
What's this one?
It's a girl.
Groovy.
Ai, yai, yai, yai, yai.
Chucky, it's time.
Give me the power,
I beg of you.
Chucky, first
he has to choose.
I beg your pardon.
I'm sorry.
She has to choose.
We don't have time
for this shit!
Wait, Chucky.
We have a son
and a daughter.
Glen and Glenda.
Don't you get it?
Maybe they don't
have to choose.
Help!
Hurry, Chucky!
Do the chant.
Chucky, do it now!
Help us!
Chucky, what are you
standing there for?
Do the chant!
What are you waiting for?
Do it!
Do the chant!
Everybody just shut up!
I have had it! That's it!
There is a limit
to how much I can take.
What are you
talking about?
Look around you, Tiff.
This is nuts.
And I have a very high
tolerance for nuts.
If this is what it takes
to be human,
then I would
rather take my chances
as a supernaturally
possessed doll.
It's less complicated.
You can't be serious?
As a heart attack.
Think about it.
What is so great
about being human, anyway?
You get sick. You get old.
You can't get it up anymore.
I'm not lookin'
forward to that.
But I want to be
Jennifer Tilly.
I want to be a star.
And I don't want to be
your chauffeur.
As a doll,
I'm fucking infamous.
I'm one of the most notorious
slashers in history.
And I don't want
to give that up.
I am Chucky, the killer doll!
And I dig it!
I have everything I want:
a beautiful wife,
a multi-talented kid.
This is who I am, Tiff.
This is me.
Chucky, I don't know
what the fuck
you're talking about.
I don't know
who the fuck you are anymore.
But it's not enough for me.
I want more.
What are you sayin'?
It's over.
You've got to
get out of here, Sweetface.
I'm leaving you, Chucky,
and I'm taking the kid.
Nobody leaves me.
Nobody!
No!
Jennifer,
I love...
Stan, tell me. Tell me.
What?
Jesus.
Oh, my God.
My babies.
Give me my babies.
I just want to know
where they are.
They're fine, Jennifer.
They're in
the maternity ward.
All right,
was that so hard?
The important thing to think
about now is getting well
so you can get on with
your life and your career.
I don't care
about my career.
I want my babies.
I'm working on it, Jennifer,
but you're not making it easy.
I already talked
to the cops.
They cleared me.
They know
you're not a killer.
They didn't say
you were mentally competent.
Now what do you expect,
after the story you told them?
It's true.
Yeah, well, I suggest from now
on you keep that to yourself.
Hmm?
We'll talk later.
Try to get some sleep.
Wish me luck, Sweetface.
Mommy is going to be a star.
I can't think
of a thing to say.
Fuck it!
Give me the power,
I beg of you.
Switch! Switch!
Switch! Switch! Switch!
Nobody leaves me. Nobody.
Okasan.
I want you
to be a good girl
or boy. Whatever.
Don't make the same mistakes
your mom and dad made.
Especially your dad.
Let's go.
Glenda?
No, Dad! It's me!
Your boy!
Your chip
off the old block!
Are you proud
of me now, Daddy?
Are you?
Attaboy, kid. Attaboy.
There, there.
It's all right.
It's going to be
all right.
There, there.
It's all right.
Yesterday, she gave Dana
Shelton a bloody nose
and took pictures of it
for Show and Tell.
She called
the cat the "C" word.
And I'm pretty sure she's been
taking money from my purse.
That's ridiculous.
Glen, he is an angel.
An absolute dream.
But Glenda,
she's a bad girl,
Miss Tilly.
A very bad girl.
I'm not listening to this.
Oh, I hate that thing.
Some of the kids
really want to see her.
Miss Tilly.
What?
I'm afraid of her.
Oh, Fulvia,
it's only a doll.
I was talking about Glenda.
Fulvia,
just exactly
what are you trying to say?
I can't work here
anymore.
What?
I'm sorry,
I just can't.
If you only saw the way
she looks at me,
with such hate.
All right, Fulvia,
if that's what you want.
We'll miss you.
Thank you, Miss Tilly.
God bless.
Hmm.
Mom got her wish.
She's a bright shining star.
Now we're the perfect family.
I've learned
a lot about myself.
I know I'm not alone.
I know I'm not a freak.
And even though
we had our differences,
I know my dad
really loved me.
Oh, Glen.
Glen, sweetheart,
come over here.
Here, sweetheart,
look.
Here's another one.
Who is it from, Mommy?
I don't know.
Hmm, let's see.
Oh, it doesn't say.
Strange.
It doesn't say who it is.
Bye, sweetheart.
Don't run so fast.
You're going to trip.
So anyway, he determined
that he was going to go off...
One way or another,
I'm gonna find ya
I'm gonna get ya, get ya,
get ya, get ya
One way or another,
I'm gonna win ya
I'm gonna get ya, get ya,
get ya, get ya
One way or another
I'm gonna see ya
I'm gonna meet ya,
meet ya, meet ya, meet ya
One day maybe next week,
I'm gonna meet ya
I'm gonna meet ya,
I'll meet ya
I will drive past
your house
And if the lights
are all down
I'll see who's around
One way or another,
I'm gonna find ya
I'm gonna get ya, get ya,
get ya, get ya
One way or another,
I'm gonna win ya
I'm gonna get ya, get ya,
get ya, get ya
And if the lights
are all down
I'll see who's around
One way or another,
I'm gonna lose ya
I'm gonna give you
the slip
I'll slip out of here for
another I'm gonna lose ya
I'm gonna trick ya,
I'll trick ya
One way or another,
I'm gonna lose ya
I'm gonna trick ya, trick
ya, trick ya, trick ya
One way or another,
I'm gonna lose ya
I'm gonna give you
the slip
I'll walk down the mall,
stand over by the wall
Where I can see it all,
find out who you call
Lead you
to the supermarket checkout
Some specials and rat food
Get lost in the crowd
One way or another
Where I can see it all,
find out who ya call
One way or another
Some specials and rat food
get lost in the crowd
One way or another
Where I can see it all,
find out who you call
Some specials and rat food
get lost in the crowd
I just love
this movie. Don't you?
Let's hit the street tonight
we got a brand new ride
We got a beat that's tight
me and my boy inside
Let's ride
till the wheels fall off
All the ladies
scream and shout
All the fellas ball
'Cause we're going
to the club tonight
Man, I'm buyin' up the bar
once I get inside
East coast west coast
Show love from
the north to the south
Everybody,
cut it up, cut it up
Cut it up, cut it up
Cut it up, yeah
Cut it up, cut it up,
cut it up
Cut it up, cut it up
Cut 'em up
Ooh, look at
the big-time stunner
Cruising down Mulholland
in the new Hummer
You know it was stolen
you know I stay rollin'
Me and my boy-boy
we ride like soldiers
Big Chucky
ooh, I'm so lucky
I'm a murdering psychopath
that's why they can't touch me
I'm iller than M.J.'s Thriller
see the scar on my face
Like Pacino I'm a killer
Cut it up, cut it up
Cut it up, yeah,
cut it up
Cut it up, cut it up
Cut 'em up
Whoever thought that I was
a joke I slit their throat
Then drink a rum and coke
I get movies and I'm iller
than ever tougher than leather
And way more clever
Everybody in the club
feelin' this, Big Chucky
with his son and
of course his missus
So beware if you've got a flat
tire, I swear Jason, Freddy Kreuger
and even Michael Myer
cut it up
Cut it up, cut it up
Cut it up, yeah
Cut it up, cut it up,
cut it up
Cut it up, cut it up
Cut 'em up
I can't think of a thing to say.
Fuck it!
Oh, God!
Please rate this subtitle at www.osdb.link/36976
Help other users to choose the best subtitles