Downloaded from
YTS.MX
Official YIFY movies site:
The legend of the ten rings
has been told for thousands of years.
Every generation,
the story grows.
But at its centre,
there is always one man.
Some say he found the rings in a crater
or stole them from a tomb.
They gave him the strength of a god,
and the gift of eternal life.
He could have used them for good.
But all he wanted...
was power.
He called his army The Ten Rings.
Over the centuries,
they spread into
every corner of the world.
They moved in the shadows...
Toppled governments...
And changed the course of history.
He chased money and power
for a thousand years.
But he still wanted more.
Have you heard the legend of Ta Lo?
A hidden village with mythical creatures
and ancient magic.
Where people practise a
martial arts style from the gods.
I want to find it.
Of course. I'll send a scout
to explore the area,
and come back
with more information.
I want to go now.
The forest...
...is moving.
He had nothing left on Earth to conquer.
That's when he came
for my home.
Where's the entrance
to Ta Lo?
You're not welcome
in our village.
You don't know who
you're talking to.
I don't care who you are.
Turn around now,
and I won't have to hurt you.
Is that all?
That was the first time
I met your father.
He was the last person
I thought I'd fall for.
But love had other plans.
Shang-Chi,
there's much more to know
about the legend of the rings,
but you'll learn about that
when you're older.
If Dad's rings were so powerful,
how did you beat him?
Where I'm from, we are empowered
by the magic of the Great Protector.
When you have the heart of our dragon,
you can do some amazing things.
Can you still do those things?
I left those powers in Ta Lo
with our dragon,
but what I got in return
is so much better.
I want you to have this.
Whenever you feel lost,
this will help you
find your way home.
Can you remember that?
That seat's for Waigong.
He's getting all his favourite things
this year for the Day of the Dead.
He can take anything.
Last year I put a bottle of whisky
on his grave...
And it was gone the next morning.
I know you kids think it's silly.
When are you two going
to get married?
Waipo, we're just friends.
All right. Go, go, go.
Give me the pendant,
and no one gets hurt.
I don't want any trouble.
Then give us the pendant!
Sign here to get in.
I'm looking for my sister,
Xu Xialing.
Have you heard of her?
This is the address she gave me.
Two million views
in three days, bro!
And you're the driver!
Thanks!
Sister.
What are you doing?
I know you're upset.
But can you hear me out?
We don't have time for this.
Can you please stop hitting me?
Stop it! I'm trying to help you!
Dad's coming for you.
I'm not fighting you.
You shouldn't have come back.
Sometimes when I'm doing my forms...
I close my eyes,
and it's like I can feel her.
Do you ever feel like that?
No.
Please don't leave me here.
I'll be back in three days.
You run this place?
I own it.
You left us for dead!
Now you know how it feels.
I've missed you, my son.
That's enough.
You know who's in there?
Say, "Hello, little sister!"
When will you stop pretending?
It's okay, my dear.
We're all going to be
together soon.
Hi there!
I am Xu Shang-Chi.
This is my sister, Xu Xialing.
We're Ying Li's children.
This is my friend, Katy.
Get in your car and go home!
Please. You don't understand.
Guang Bo!
What are you doing?
Put down your weapons!
Shang-Chi.
Xialing.
I'm your aunty, Nan.
I've waited so long to meet you.
You look like your mother.
To the range.
Guang Bo.
Let her shoot.
If you aim at nothing,
you hit nothing.
You're not in your
father's house any more.
In Ta Lo, we train as equals.
You've been in the shadows
long enough, my child.
We'll be together soon.
Lead with your breath.
Look into your heart,
the light and the dark.
To know yourself,
you must face them both.
Your husband tried to destroy us.
The Iron Gang is here
to repay that debt.
My husband is not the man
he used to be.
It doesn't matter.
Your business with him has nothing
to do with my children.
They can go,
but someone has to pay.
Xialing. Shang-Chi.
Go inside.
I'm going to talk to our guests.
But you don't have your powers.
Shang-Chi, you have nothing to fear.
She told me I could change.
That I could leave my past behind.
But she was wrong.
If I hadn't taken them off,
those men wouldn't have dared
to do this.
And now they will pay for it.
Where's your boss?
I don't know!
I swear I don't!
Okay.
A blood debt has to be
paid by blood.
Will you help me?
A blood debt has to be
paid by blood.
No!
You're not ready.
She stays here.
You fool. We turned you away.
The sins of your past would have
destroyed this place.
Be careful how you speak to me,
young man.
I've lived ten of your lifetimes.
Save me.
Save me, my dear.
I'm coming, my love.
It's too dangerous.
Don't die.
Everyone to the water now!
Save me.
Aim at the sky,
to win or die!
Deep breath.
Shang-Chi, you have nothing to fear.
You have the heart
of our dragon.
I will always be a part of you.
And your dad will too.
Take everything we've given you
and make it your own.
I'm so proud of you.
Our family needs you.
Go.
Draw.
Fire!
Let me out!
If it gets our dragon's soul,
it will be unstoppable!
Aim for the throat!
You have to let me go.
Let go!
Go.
Farewell, Dad.
Mum, we'll be okay.