Hi, everybody,
and welcome to the Shrek in the Swamp
karaoke dance party!
I'm gonna take things down a little bit
with one of my personal favourites.
Don't go changin'
To try and please me
You've never let me down before
I made it through the wilderness
You know I made it through
Didn't know how lost I was
Until I found you
Yeah!
I like big butts and I cannot lie
You other brothers can't deny
When a girl walks in
with an itty-bitty waist
And a round thing in your face you get...
Feelings
It's fun to stay at the
YMCA
Do you really want to hurt me?
Do you really want to make me cry?
Staying alive! Staying alive!
Who let the dogs out?
Who? Who? Who? Who? Who?
Say, get up and dance to the music!
Come on, everybody now!
Dance to the music
Oh, yeah!
Yeah, yeah!
AIl we need is a drummer
For people who only need a beat! Yeah!
Break it down, green girl!
Thelonious, my man!
I'm gonna add some bottom
So that the dancers just won't hide
Yo, take it, Shrek.
You might like to hear my organ
I said, ride, Sally, ride!
I can't see me lovin ' nobody but you
For all my life
Dance to the music
Shrek, you ain't dancin' yet!
Oh, yeah!
Dance to the music
That's how I like it!
Everybody!
Dance to the music
So happy together
Hey, Pinocchio,
you wanna watch that nose, man?