You cannot defeat me.
Do not go to Silent Hill.
Honey, it's okay.
I'm here.
Dad?
i was burning.
Hey, come on, kiddo.
it was just a dream.
it's always like
this when we move.
This feels different.
Hey, look.
Once we've unpacked,
and given this
place a lick of paint,
it'll be our home, yeah?
The dreams will fade.
They're calling me.
Don't listen.
Do you hear?
i want you to promise me
that whatever happens,
you'll never go there.
Okay.
Shit.
Rough night?
Yeah.
Dad, l don't want
to do this again.
L know, honey.
Yeah. Spoons.
"Heather." Why Heather?
it was my grandmother's name.
You can change it
if you don't like it.
No, no.
Heather's fine.
i was Sharon,
then Mary, then Cathy.
Now Heather.
You were Christopher
and now you're Harry.
Names don't matter.
i'm still me.
Happy birthday, you.
Dad, thank you!
But you're early.
Just a little.
Can't a dad indulge
his soon-to-be
1 8-year-old daughter?
What's wrong?
Nothing. l love it.
L love it. Yeah.
Yeah?
Lt is the one l saw you
looking at in the mall.
Yeah, yes.
Thank you. l love it.
l love it so much.
You're welcome, honey.
You're getting
a little bit gray there, Dad.
Your fault.
Your roots are showing.
Yeah, l know. l'll fix it.
i think this place is
gonna be good for us,
you know? What do you think?
Yeah.
Hey, come on.
Once l've unpacked,
given this place
a lick of paint,
you know, it will...
Don't, Dad.
What?
it's just what you
said in my dream.
Just, don't.
L got to go.
Don't want to be late
for the first day of school.
Hey, remember the rules.
New town, new school.
Yeah, yeah.
i've done this before.
i know you have, l'm just...
You know l worry.
Don't worry.
i'm careful.
i'll be fine.
i love you.
i love you too, honey.
Hey, Rose.
L wish you were still here.
it's been so hard
since you brought
Sharon back to me.
Christopher, my love.
Rose.
i tried to find you.
i searched for so long.
My love, l don't have
a lot of time.
i'm trapped here.
There's nothing
you can do for me,
protect her.
She's the one that matters now.
Why can't you come back?
i found a seal.
Part of it is missing.
Only one of us
could come through.
i made a choice.
Where's our daughter?
They'll come looking for her.
They'll come looking
because they need her.
Never let them take her.
No matter what happens,
no matter
what you have to do,
swear to me.
Swear to me you will
never let them take her.
i swear.
i brought her back to you.
She is yours to care for now.
Don't go.
Goodbye, my love.
Rose.
Daddy.
Sharon?
My God, Sharon.
You're here.
Daddy!
it's okay.
You're safe now.
What happened?
L don't remember anything.
it's okay. lt's okay.
You...
You were in an accident.
Where's Mommy?
Mommy saved you.
She's gone, honey.
Sorry. l didn't mean
to scare you.
Sorry, what?
Are you okay?
Yes. Yes, l'm fine.
it's just that you
don't wanna be messing
with the vagrants, miss.
i was just seeing if
he needed some help.
Some people are
beyond our help.
Have we met?
No, no, l don't think so.
No?
L'm sure we have.
What's your name?
i have to catch my bus.
Welcome back,
everyone. l hope you had
a good Christmas vacation.
i would like to
welcome some new students
who will be joining us
this semester.
Heather Mason.
Could you say hello
to the class, Heather?
Hi. l'm Heather. l'm new.
i just moved to town, so...
Come on, Heather,
share a little
bit of yourself.
Everyone has a story.
Tell us yours.
What is this, third grade?
What do you wanna know?
Do you get all of your
clothes from Goodwill?
Okay, you know what?
Let me make this
easier for you.
This is the fifth school
l've been to since l was 1 1.
Me and my dad, we move around.
So l do this a lot.
So don't bother
trying to remember my name
because l'm sure as hell
not gonna remember yours.
Don't talk to me.
We won't be friends.
L won't lM you or facebook you
or tweet you, read your blog.
And whatever you're
thinking of saying or doing,
don't bother,
because l've seen it before,
and l'm just
guessing here, but...
l don't think there
are too many original
thinkers in this room.
And by the time any
of you have found out
anything about me
that's worth knowing...
l'll have moved on.
How's that?
Very impressive.
Now the next
addition to our class,
Vincent Cooper.
Are you kidding me?
L can't follow that.
Shit!
Burn the witch!
No.
i'm not a witch!
Please!
Leave me alone.
Burn the witch!
Please! Come on!
Whoa.
Are you all right?
What?
Are you okay?
What are you
doing out of class?
You know what? l'm lost.
i can't find Math.
Any ideas?
No, no.
i... l'm lost too.
Hey look,
you wanna get a coffee?
No, we have class.
i mean, later.
No.
Why not?
We're both new.
We don't know anyone else.
That speech
l gave in class,
l gave it for a reason.
i really don't want
to know anyone here.
Hey, honey.
How was your day?
i think there's
someone following me.
What do l do?
Okay.
Don't come back here. Not yet.
L'll meet you somewhere.
Central Square Mall.
Then we can be sure.
Okay, l'll meet you
at the Happy Burger place.
i'll be there as soon as l can.
Do you think someone knows?
No.
No one knows.
L'll see you soon.
i love you, Dad.
i love you, too.
Happy birthday, Heather!
Make a wish!
Sharon.
Sharon!
Please, sir.
Sharon, wait!
Dad! Dad, l...
Sharon. Sharon, wait.
Sharon!
Keep away from me!
it's okay.
No, it's not okay.
Nothing is okay.
Who are you?
My name is Douglas Cartland.
L'm a private investigator.
What do you want from me?
i'm paid to find people.
Someone wanted
you found, Sharon.
That's not my name!
You're Sharon Da Silva.
Or at least you think you are.
Tracked you down
after you left Portland.
You and Harry got away
from the police,
but l found you.
What my dad did there...
That was self-defense.
i don't care who Harry killed.
i'm trying to help you.
Get back! Why?
Because l didn't know who
l was working for then,
but l do now.
They call themselves
the Order of Valtiel.
And they want you.
You're lying.
You don't understand.
They know where you are.
i told them where you are.
They're coming.
You've gotta get away.
Don't worry, l will.
Keep away from me!
Everything your dad
ever told you was a lie.
Fuck you!
He told me the truth.
You know why you don't
remember anything
from your childhood?
i was in a car crash.
My mother died.
l lost my memory.
No! There was never
any accident.
You were trapped in
a place called Silent Hill.
But your mother saved you.
She got you out.
But they want you back.
Ask your dad.
He knows that...
Tell me who l am.
Please, tell me.
it's gone. lt's gone.
i'll help you. Come on.
You two, move back now.
Hey, miss!
You can't be back here.
Back behind the tape, please.
Come on, folks.
L need you back.
Everybody,
get back behind the line.
Come on, move back.
Whoa, one second,
there's a wallet
in his pocket.
Douglas Cartland.
Some Pl from out of town.
What you got, Cable?
The boys found this
jacket down there.
There's blood on it.
Okay.
Hand it over to forensics.
Let's find out
whose blood it is.
Heather Mason.
Sharon Da Silva.
This girl? Maybe this is hers.
Let's find her and ask her.
See what we got
on this Cartland.
Pull the security tapes.
l wanna see what
happened here tonight.
Hey.
Vincent.
They found a guy dead
in there. Did you see?
Yeah.
Hey!
What's wrong?
i can't tell you.
it's okay, you can tell me.
No, l can't.
Because l have no idea
what's going on
in my head right now.
It's me.
Leave a message.
Dad, call me when
you get this, please.
You're cold.
Where's your coat?
Come here.
Thanks.
What's the matter?
Do you see them?
They who? The runner?
No.
Never mind.
Just another thing
to prove that
l'm going crazy.
So... Where's home?
A couple of blocks away.
No, l mean, before.
Where do you come from?
Nowhere, really.
l traveled a lot
with my dad.
Do you think there's
a difference between
dreams and reality?
What happened
to the small talk?
No "What's your
favorite band?"
"Do you facebook?"
Nothing like that.
Fuck Facebook. Do you?
L never think about it.
Everybody thinks about it.
Not me. My life is
complicated enough.
You should talk
to my grandfather.
lt's all he ever thinks about.
Drove him crazy.
it's driving me crazy.
No, l mean, he's insane.
Bat-shit nuts.
Back in my sweet
little home town,
old man Leonard
drools in a padded cell.
He'll tell you
there are no such
things as dreams,
just endless realities
all piled on
top of each other.
Some people see monsters,
other people just see people.
And they locked
him up for that?
My mother had him committed.
Jesus!
Yeah.
She's kind of intimidating,
my mother.
No difference between
fantasy and reality...
l don't think
l like my reality.
Do you think anyone does?
At least l'm real.
Well, l think l am.
And you?
Yep. Pretty real.
Or just pretty.
That was
a lousy pick-up line.
Does it ever work?
i never tried it before.
How'd it go down?
As a crime
against pick-up lines.
You're kind of funny, Heather.
You're pretty fucked up,
but l don't know,
l think you're
goofy fun inside.
Goofy fun?
That'd be nice for a change.
Anyway, this is my street.
Thanks for walking me back.
L'd like to do
it again sometime.
Vincent, you're nice,
but l don't think
you want to know me.
i do.
No, you don't.
i'm gonna call you later.
i didn't give you my number.
i'll see you around!
Dad?
Dad!
Dad! Dad!
Heather, it's Vincent.
l heard you yell.
ls everything all right?
i need your help.
Look.
is that blood?
Have you called
the police?
l can't.
Why not?
They can help.
l just can't!
Okay?
Okay.
Do you know where
this Silent Hill is?
No, it's...
lt's something that
l've dreamt about.
My dad, he...
He warned me never to go there.
But l know that symbol.
This is it.
He kept it all in here.
is this your mom?
My adoptive mom, Rose.
You were adopted?
Yeah, l never knew
my real parents.
Did you write all of these?
Yeah.
Do you know what that is?
No.
Looks like
there's another side
that fits in here.
- A gun?
- Why do you need a gun?
Miss Mason, it's the police.
i thought you said
you didn't call them.
i didn't.
Then why are they here?
What is going on, Heather?
i have to go.
if they catch me,
l'll never find my dad.
Catch you?
Why would they catch you?
What have you done?
Nothing! l haven't
done anything, l swear.
Help me.
What do you want me to do?
Can you drive?
What?
i can't drive. Can you?
Santini, come here.
You wanted probable cause?
This is it.
What the hell happened here?
That look like
a gang tag to you?
i don't think so.
But l've never
seen anything like it.
Call Crime Scene,
get them down here.
What about the girl?
She's a murder suspect.
"My dearest Sharon,
"lf you are reading this,
then something
has happened to me.
"You're on your own now.
"Don't try to find me.
"And whatever you do,
don't go to Silent Hill.
"l promised your mother
l'd keep you safe,
but l failed.
"l know you think
we're running from the police,
"because of the man l killed
in Portland two years ago."
You can't protect her forever!
Dad!
"But the truth is,
he wasn't just
a random thief."
Get your things, we're leaving.
"He was sent to take
you back to Silent Hill.
"He was a member of the Order.
These people want you,
they need you.
"l don't know why,
"but they will do
everything in their power
to draw you back.
"You must resist it.
"l tried to keep you safe.
"And l never meant to
lie to you, but l had to.
"You'll find
the truth in my notebooks.
As much as l could find out.
"l hope that when you
read what l've learned,
"you can finally
begin to understand
who you really are.
"Please forgive me
for not telling you the truth.
"l did it to protect you.
"l love you, Sharon."
Are you okay?
Do you wanna stop?
No.
What does it say?
So much.
i knew he was frightened,
but this is crazy.
it says, "Silent Hill was
originally a prison colony,
"built on ground
taken from
the native lndians.
"They called it
'The Place of
the Silent Spirits."'
Never build
on ancient lndian
burial grounds.
i thought everyone knew that.
it says here,
"Religious zealots
called the Order of Valtiel
"secretly ran the town
for the last 1 00 years.
"They were waiting
for a child to be born
to be a vessel for their god,
"who would then be resurrected
and make the world anew."
lt sounds like one of those
crazy doomsday cults.
Yeah. Sounds like it.
There is a newspaper article.
Fire in the coal
mines got out of control.
The whole place
is still burning,
deep underground.
Everyone had to leave.
My dad doesn't
believe that, though.
No?
He says the town
was cursed by the power
of a demon child.
Her name's Alessa.
This Order tried to
cleanse her with fire,
but they failed.
And Alessa's revenge
was to summon
a world of darkness,
filled with
terrifying creatures.
This one, it says,
is her "guardian
and executioner."
We should stop.
No, l want to keep going.
i'm tired.
i need rest, you need rest.
Do you think they'll find us?
Someone will, eventually.
You think we're far?
No.
No, l think we're really close.
And l don't think
you should go...
What?
L think your dad is right.
i don't think you
should go to Silent Hill.
i need to find him.
You read his notebooks.
He wants you to run.
Vincent...
No, listen to me.
The Order, they want you.
i think that's
why they took Harry.
To make you come back.
i don't have a choice.
Don't you understand that?
i understand.
i just...
l just don't want
anything to happen to you.
You didn't sleep?
No.
We can't go any further.
We already talked about this.
L have to.
Why can't you just trust me?
it's for my dad.
You don't understand.
i do.
No, you don't.
How could you?
Because l am
a child of the Order.
What?
i was born and raised
in Silent Hill.
i was chosen to
come into this world
to make sure you return.
No...
No, that's not possible.
The Order are
trapped in Silent Hill.
The notebook said so.
it is possible
for a few to escape
just for a while,
but it requires...
lt requires
sacrifice and suffering.
You have been chosen for this!
How could you do this to me?
My whole life,
all l've been taught...
All that any of us are taught
is that Alessa is
the great evil of the world.
She trapped us,
she brings the darkness,
and you...
You are part of that evil.
But l know that's not true.
After seeing you,
after spending
this time with you,
l know you're not evil, l...
lf you are part of Alessa,
you're the innocent part.
Every step of the way,
you lied.
l had to.
They were watching, projecting
their spirits into the world.
You saw them.
You took my dad.
Please believe me,
l had nothing
to do with that,
l'm sorry.
Why take him,
why not just take me?
Because you have to return
of your own free will.
Taking him,
they knew you'd follow.
Why do l matter so much?
Because the Order
can't be free until
Alessa is gone.
Her power keeps them trapped,
and she can't be destroyed
until she's whole again.
You will make that happen.
What about my dad?
is he still alive?
Yes, but not for long.
My mother, Claudia,
won't keep him alive after
she has what she wants.
Where is he?
in the sanctuary
beneath the town.
Wait, Heather, stop!
No!
You need this.
You have to find
the other half.
it's the only way
you'll be able
to save your dad.
My grandfather has it.
The one in the asylum?
Yes, Leonard Wolf.
He's dangerous.
Let me help you.
No! Get off of me!
Please! Please,
listen to me.
Don't!
What is happening?
The Darkness is coming.
it's coming.
What's going on?
Stop! Make it stop!
You did this.
No.
it's not me.
How could it be me?
Because you are part of Alessa.
We're so close,
you allowed the darkness
to break through.
Vincent, what is going on?
i don't know.
Vincent!
Burn the witch!
You should not be here.
They will use you.
We will all suffer now.
i know who you are.
You're her mother.
Alessa's mother.
How could you
let them burn her?
No, l loved her.
it's all right, sweetheart.
it's okay. lt's all right
I was deceived.
Come along, child.
i never wanted this for her.
Where are you taking me?
Mommy! Mommy!
But Alessa was special.
She was the only one
who could survive the fire,
that's why she was chosen.
No! Stop!
No! No!
But it only led
to our damnation.
You all got what you deserved.
Yes, and l became
the mother of the demon.
But you are her daughter.
What are you talking about?
Alessa didn't die in the fire,
but she suffered so much.
Her pain was only
matched by her rage.
And with that rage,
her powers grew
beyond all comprehension.
Alessa knew there
was a part of her
that could still
be free from pain.
So she took that last,
innocent part of her soul
and placed it into
a newborn, orphan child.
You.
You were secretly
taken from here,
to be raised by loving,
but unaware parents.
You're the only part of
Alessa that feels love.
You balance her hate,
but you should
never have come back.
Because now you have
given the Order what
they could never have...
A way to destroy
Alessa and you.
Where is my father?
There is nothing you can
do to save him without
damning yourself.
i don't care.
Just tell me what you know.
i know the darkness is coming.
it's safer to be inside.
Run.
Run!
No!
What?
Help me.
No...
Run.
i'm here!
i'm gonna help you!
What happened?
Fast! lt's coming!
What's coming?
Come on! Run!
Where did you come from?
i took a wrong turn.
Got lost in the fog.
There! Come on!
No!
This way.
Run!
My own son...
Mother, please...
betrayed us.
She is not evil.
Your mind is corrupted
by her darkness.
You were young to
be given this task.
i understand.
You created Alessa.
The darkness is your evil
reflected back at us.
She is innocent.
She is innocent?
You are insane,
just as your
grandfather is insane.
Burn him! Make him suffer!
Let the God judge him!
No!
You succeeded.
Even in your madness,
you guided her back to us.
What my sister, Christabella,
could not achieve, l shall.
Salvation is at hand.
And a broken mind
can be mended.
No.
Mother, please, don't.
Take him to the asylum.
Cure him.
No.
No. No!
Leonard.
Do you think someone knows?
No.
No one knows.
L'll see you soon.
i love you, Dad.
i love you, too.
Leonard Wolf.
Okay.
S-1 2.
Leonard.
Hello, child.
Please, come closer,
so l can touch you.
i don't think so.
Did Claudia send you?
Claudia?
Yeah.
No. She put you here.
My own daughter says
l'm corrupted by the darkness.
She says that l'm a monster.
She's far worse than l am.
She is also corrupted
by the same darkness.
i am looking
for my father.
ls he lost?
He's in Silent Hill.
There are many Silent Hills.
Are you sure it's this one?
Vincent said you'd
know how to help me.
Vincent, that little traitor...
My own flesh and blood
turned against me!
Listen.
You may be able to hear
the cries of his torment.
He's here?
Where else would you go
to mend your mind?
Like yours is?
i'm...
l'm just an ongoing project.
i have half of this.
Will it help me?
Please...
l'm blind, child.
i cannot see
what you have there.
Place it in my hand,
and l will try to help you.
Don't be afraid.
Come on.
You know what it is.
i was the Master of the Order.
How could l not know
the Seal of Metatron?
it was stolen from me
and used by her
to escape with the child.
Without it,
we cannot summon the god.
it is a key.
What does it unlock?
The true nature of things.
i need to find the other half.
- But you've already found it.
- The other half is in me!
What are you doing? No!
Stop!
Now l see the truth of you.
You're a demon!
You must be destroyed!
Not today.
Two halves coming together.
it's complete.
- Alessa?
Can you feel me?
You know l'm here, don't you?
You know l've got
the Seal of Metatron.
Somebody help me.
No.
Get back! Get back!
And you!
Get back!
Look out!
Do it! Do it!
How can l find my dad?
Heather, help me.
Tell me where he is.
in the sanctuary,
beneath the amusement park.
i can help you.
Fine.
Hurry!
L am hurrying!
Shit!
Stuck! Heather, it's stuck!
Okay, we need a knife.
How can you live like this?
This darkness, those creatures?
it's all l've ever known.
My reality.
Darkness should
have faded by now.
Why hasn't it?
You're so close to Alessa,
two halves
coming together again,
it's changing the world.
What's gonna happen?
That's up to you.
Lakeside Amusement Park
is over there.
And the entrance
to the sanctuary.
Do you think you can save him?
i have to try.
My dad gave up his
life to protect me.
Then l think he'd
want you to leave.
You don't know that.
if he loved you,
he wouldn't want you
to be in any danger.
And if you loved someone,
you'd know that you
would never give up.
No, wait!
Get down.
Look.
Are they soldiers?
Not really.
We call them The Brethren.
The most devout
servants of the Order.
See the masks?
They won't breathe
the air of the darkness.
They think it corrupts them.
i hope you find him.
i hope you live
free and happy,
it's more than l ever did.
What are you talking about?
Vincent, no!
Alessa?
Daughter.
Sister.
Self.
No.
i gave you life so
you could live my dream.
You're the part of me
that could be
free of this pain,
could live and feel love.
Do you feel nothing?
Nothing but hate.
They say you are a demon.
They are right.
You created this nightmare.
Everyone has
a different nightmare
in Silent Hill.
i am theirs.
i have to save my father.
He's not my father or yours.
And sacrifices have to be made.
Go to hell!
Can't you see?
We're already here.
And you are not welcome!
Do you think l
won't destroy you?
How can you?
i am you.
Time to take back
what l gave you!
Stop!
We are one, Heather.
Dad!
Sharon!
Sharon.
You don't hurt her!
What do you want from me?
Look around you.
This was our sanctuary.
A last, safe place
from the darkness.
And now, even here
has fallen to her evil.
But we praise the god
that you are here, finally.
You have delivered us.
i have done nothing for you.
You have done everything.
Defeated Alessa.
Rejoined the seal.
You are the savior.
if l've done so much,
then let my father go.
He cannot go.
His blood will
feed the newborn god.
Just as your body
will be its incubator.
Why?
Why me?
it is your destiny.
You have been chosen
many years ago
to be the vessel.
The god can only be
born through your flesh.
And then we will be
free from this prison
to cleanse
the world of its sins.
And all we need
is your body.
No!
You leave her alone!
You have the Seal of Metatron.
With it, l can summon the god.
Give it to me.
Take it,
l want to see the truth
of what you are.
Dad!
Sharon.
The ash.
it's stopped!
Because of you?
No, it's not me.
i think things are gonna
be different around
here from now on.
The Order's power is broken.
Alessa's nightmare is over.
She's gone.
Another one will come.
This is the place
of lost souls.
What's wrong?
i can't leave.
What? Why?
i'm going to stay here.
But, Dad, we're free.
We're safe.
For the first time.
i'm gonna find your mother.
You saved my life.
And l can never repay you.
Rose is still
trapped here somewhere.
i'm gonna find her.
Let me help you find her.
No.
i promised her,
once you were safe,
l'd come back.
This is my task.
You've done
what you had to do.
Now, l want you to
be free, finally.
Do you understand
why l have to do this?
You are everything
l could've ever wished for.
i love you, baby.
i love you too, Dad.
Vincent, look after my
little girl, do you hear?
i don't think
she needs me for that.
Come on.
Yeah.
Come on in.
Watch your step.
Thanks.
No problem.
You're lucky l came by.
l haven't been this
way in a long time.
Travis Grady.
Vincent.
Sharon.
Nice to meet you.
So where're you
two lovebirds headed?
Just take us as
far away from here
as you can.
Amen to that!
Got it.