Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
Hey Sinbad, do you have
any idea where we're going?
Nope. Why should
I start that now?
Hold up, Hold up,
Hold up, Hold up.
Is my treasure hunting
interfering with your online
dating?
As a matter a
fact, it is.
I want to see what kind
of women are available here.
You know, you mind
shutting that thing that's below
your nose?
It's making a lot of noise.
I'm trying to focus here, man.
What is this?
You can't die yet.
You still owe me a
thousand bucks.
Leave it. A
millennia from now maybe
two guys will find it, convince
somebody it's a historic relic
and make a big pile of money.
But what if--
No. Nothing.
Come on. I found it.
Man.
This is where he hide.
Wait. So Perseus hid his
treasure in Mexico?
This place wasn't called
Mexico back then.
Perseus was just staring at a
big black map looking for a
place to hide his fortune.
You see, when the kid who killed
medusa be came an old man,
he went crazy with Dementia.
He was convinced Zeus was
after his fortune.
So he packed up his ship and
spent 10 years searching for the
perfect place to hide it.
Eventually, he hoarded all his
wealth up in a cave.
This cave.
Wait, so Perseus discovered
the New World?
Yeah. It's all in my book.
At least what should be my book.
Sinbad, not now.
How did we even get
in this place?
Same way Perseus killed Medusa.
Through the neck.
Open sesame.
The treasure of Perseus.
Whoo.
What? Oh yeah.
Someone's been here.
Recently.
Why didn't they take nothing?
Probably some academic moron who
wants to preserve this place.
How do you even know that?
Because I use to be one of those
academic morons.
Let's hurry.
Oh yeah. That's nice.
That's nice.
That's nasty, man. Look,
just leave it, alright?
Let's just go.
No, no, no.
This bitch made it personal.
I'm going to sell this thing and
buy a yacht the size of a
football field.
Hi.
We were just browsing.
What kind of return policy do
you guys have?
Who are you?
- We were just leaving.
RUN!
Want that?
Ha Ha!
Get him!
Go! Go! Go!
Oh, come on.
Whoo!
That kid just stole the next
atom bomb.
I want it back.
Find him immediately.
Understood?
-Yeah.
Left this though.
Oh.
You should log into his
Facebook. Say something stupid.
-Ssh! Don't talk.
Ten thousand dollar.
My final offer.
The gold alone
is worth that.
Fine. The new price is nine
thousand.
-Nine? What happened to ten?
You annoy me.
Service charge.
Wait, have you actually sucked
the life right out of a man?
Because right now I feel like I
w ant a divorce and we're not
even married.
So go sell it somewhere
else. But I doubt they'll
give you cash today.
Come on. Throw in some
hazard pay? I almost go
shot getting this.
Who did you try to
kill for this?
They tried to kill me.
Were they government?
No. Fortune hunters like me.
Big guy had an eye patch.
The other was wearing
a thingy. Like--
-The other one...
Was he a bit of a...dandy?
Do you interrupt everybody's
conversations?
I was going to introduce you
after our deal. Sinbad, meet
Ace Adar.
I'm an aficionado of you,
young man.
Well that sound a little
bit dirty.
-No.
Half of my collections at home
are pieces you've found and sold
to Lyta here.
Anything of interest?
No artifacts this time.
Just gems.
"Just gems." Lyta, give me what
I need for my boat so I can
leave town
and end our torrid love affair.
Ooh!
-Ooh! You hurt so good.
Careful. That gave me a
chemical burn when I
touched it.
Oh.
Fascinating.
Do you know what this is?
Oh, Oh yes.
I believe you found the
Heart of Medusa.
Legend says that while her eyes
could turn a man to stone,
her heart could turn the
world to stone.
Sounds like a premium
price to me.
Wow.
I'll give you twenty five
thousand for the stone.
Ooh, and double for the
scimitar.
This isn't for sale.
No?
No.
Some things can't be bought.
Blasphemy!
My Dad gave this to me.
He said it was handed down by
Old SIndibad himself.
Wait. Seven Seas-Arabian
Knights Sindibad?
Maybe. All I know for sure is
that it's a great way to open up
champagne bottles.
Ah. Oof.
If that's the true Scimitar
Sindibad,
they opened up throats of
both men and demigods.
I don't believe in any of that.
My Dad did.
He even said I look like him.
You do.
Look.
See. Here.
You must forgive me. I forget
that trinkets I collect are
family heirlooms.
I have more of your history at
my home in Los Angeles.
That's okay.
You keep it.
No, no. I insist.
It hasn't brought me luck. Maybe
it'll make your wish come true.
See, already working.
Hey!
I'm the buyer.
You're the seller.
You keep talking dirty to me,
Lyta. You're turning me on.
And if you're serious about
buying a boat,
may I suggest you do so
and lay low.
The men who I met at the cave.
The "dandy." You know them?
Yes, I do.
He sounds like Manta.
Another collector of rare
antiquities. Except for one
difference.
Not as weird?
To me, artifacts are a
taste of history.
But to Manta, they are weapons
of magical destruction.
Weapons? Come on,
you believe that?
No, no, no.
But Manta does.
Rumors are he slaughtered
an entire Amazon tribe with
the amulet of
Silverado in an attempt
to look eternally young.
Trust me. It didn't work.
Why didn't he just use
photoshop?
You joke now. But Manta is
deadly serious about his
tactics.
Well then let's get together
and kick this guy's ass.
- I ain't afraid of him.
- You should be.
I'm leaving for California
tonight. I'm curious to find out
more why Manta wants this stone.
Please join me.
My estate is secluded
and off the grid.
You'll be safe if Manta
chooses to look for you.
I'm not hiding from this guy.
Especially not in LA.
If Manta messes with me,
I'll mess back.
Besides, this time tomorrow
I'll be half-way to Chile.
Well if you reconsider,
you always have an ally and
a confidant in me.
Like you I keep a low profile,
but you can always find my
consignment shop in
the city's Tehrangeles market.
That's my card.
Lyta, always a pleasure.
Good luck to you.
I already took out my
twenty percent.
Why are you giving me more?
Consider it my donation to the
"Snarky Bitch Club."
So how we make out?
- We got enough for the boat.
The good one.
Aye, aye, captain.
So we'll set sail tomorrow.
Or we could go north?
I'm never going back to
the United States.
What?
-Hey.
Do you think I look
like this guy?
Nah. He's actually
good looking.
Really?
Pack up. We're leaving in
the morning.
Why so soon?
You want to be around if eye
patch and that Russian guy track
us back here?
Good point.
Weapons of magical destruction.
WMDs.
Hola.
Jax?
What are you trying
to do kill me?
Why are you sneaking
in here?
I didn't think you'd be home.
Oh God.
Here, I'll get you some ice.
How did you find me?
Who did you think I was-
The cops?
Yes. I mean, no.
Ow!
There.
Does that feel better?
You're making it worse.
Oh, you big baby.
Just hold it on there
for a minute.
-There's no bag.
Jax.
What are you doing here?
Well I'm spending the
summer here studying old
missionary customs.
And then when I saw
you were also here--
-No one knows I'm here.
You have a
snapchat account.
With pictures of yourself
in San Lucas.
- I like they way the
filters make me look.
Yeah.
Well, I hope that you're not
that upset that I brought it.
I thought it might help
patch things up.
Patch things up?
Okay. Maybe patch is
the wrong word.
Pants can be patched.
Tires can be patched.
You can find pumpkins in a
patch. But my reputation--
I'm sorry! Look, how many times
do I have to say that I'm sorry.
I'm sorry that your father
ruined my reputation.
You can't blame him forever.
He stole my work and then blames
me for what he stole.
Okay. You know what,
you're right.
It was a stupid
thing to do.
He was afraid he'd
lose tenure.
Well I lost my degree
and now spend my time
hiding from the law.
That was your choice, Sinbad.
-Was it?
Sinbad, you stole the
university's collection
of Egyptian dynasty
gems and then you sold
them online.
- Because I was very,
very upset.
Are you trying to
decapitate me?
Jealous of my skills?
Oh yeah. I am just heartbroken
over you skills.
Seriously, Sinbad.
You could have been the
greatest archeological
professor in the world.
Now you're just a
lousy thief.
I prefer the term
undercover entrepreneur.
Oh really?
Then how come you can't do
any better than selling
buried treasure to old
crone Lyta downtown, huh?
At least I'm honest
about who I am.
- Well.
He did put you
in the book.
See.
"Special thanks to
Sinbad Siridad."
Really?
I want to help you start over.
Why?
Because if you really wanted to
be a criminal,
then I wouldn't still be
in love with you.
Okay.
Here's my "special thanks."
And then out of nowhere, this
cyclops comes running--
-He wasn't a cyclops.
It was a bloody cyclops.
Just because a guy
wears an eye patch
doesn't make him a "cyclops."
-I bet he was born with one eye.
Well, you only
have one ball.
Sinbad and his bad jokes.
Remember buddy, I own half the
deed on this mine.
- I know.
- So we set sail tomorrow.
Alright, well we have a 90 foot
schooner.
It's a traditional Turkish motor
sailer with a transform stern.
Technically, it's a 35 foot
fishing boat with an off
board motor.
Do we have a crew?
-Are we just gonna go with those
dudes you found on Craigslist?
You know they
work cheap.
Sebastian?
As long as you're on board,
I'm fine.
Wait. So you're going to
trust a deaf guy over me?
Any day. No one's more
trustworthy than a man
who can't hear anything.
Was that even sign language?
-Nah.
Sebastian reads lips.
I was just trying to
look smart.
-Hmm.
See you tomorrow.
The rest of you, godspeed
and wadaeaan.
Wadaeaan?
I'm embracing my culture.
So now you're embracing
your culture?
Help me pack up the rest of this
stuff. Just the essentials.
Hmm.
See you on the boat,
baby.
Really?
What?
I thought we were gonna,
explore the women of the world
and screw the seven seas.
Yeah, yeah, yeah. I mean,
still gonna do that.
With your girlfriend
around?
Nah. Well, you know, she--
she's like--
You bought her a flower.
You're in love.
I'm- I'm not in love.
You are hopelessly devoted.
No. I'm just...
yeah. Yeah.
I'm in love.
But she's coming with us,
alright?
It's my boat, too. So do you
have a problem with that?
No.
Very chivalrous
of you.
- I'm going to take
a shower.
She's a lucky lady,
Nicky boy!
Yeah. Yeah.
May we come in?
Nick!
Get out of the shower.
Now.
The Heart of Medusa.
We know you stole it.
What?
Remember Cyclops and the
Russian guy we met at the cave?
Yeah?
I think they sent Charlie's
pissed off angels to get their
stuff back.
What? Dude, there's
nothing right there?
Let me ask one more time.
Or do you prefer a
different language.
- Where is the Heart of Medusa?
I don't have what you want.
I still smell her
heart on you.
The stone's residue
sours the skin.
I didn't hold anyone's heart.
How can you lie when the proof
is branded on your skin?
If you're talking about the
emerald, I sold it.
Who did you give it to?
This one's a fighter.
Manipulate the coward instead.
Tell us where the heart is. Or
rip your friend's out instead.
Why just his heart?
When he has such other
such delicate intimacies
we can rip open.
I sold the damn thing.
To who?
- To a woman who I thought was
the world's biggest bitch.
Until you walked in
the door.
Ow!
Man, come one, Sinbad. Man,
Stop pissing them off!
Look, it was Lyta.
Lyta!
How do we know you're
not lying?
Because this one is crying.
Who the hell are you guys?
You're a man. You don't get
to ask me questions.
You're Arabian?
You know him?
You ladies want this, too?
What do you think this place is-
QVC?
When I get that stone back,
I'm coming back here to break
open your head
the same way it broke mine.
-And mine!
Sinbad?
It's Lyta.
- It's still there.
- Huh?
What a nightmare.
I know who did this.
They think it was an
animal attack.
I had no idea they'd
kill her.
Who?
Three women.
They knocked me out before I
could her they were coming for
the emerald they sold.
Why didn't they
come back for me?
I should tell them.
-No, wait.
You're on probation.
They'll probably just blame
you so they have an easy
case to close.
I can't stand back
and do nothing.
Okay. Well, why don't
you try telling them
what's going on?
The I can see
if I can help.
So what's so special about
this amulet that you had?
Someone told me it's the
Heart of Medusa.
The Heart of Medusa?
Oh my God.
Who all knows that
you have this?
I was chased down
by a Russian guy.
Manta?
Manta Marquis?
How do you know
about him?
I was the one who told him where
to find the Heart of Medusa in
the first place.
You told someone else of my
theory of Perseus burying his
treasure out here?
Okay. I's not just
your theory.
Look, we shouldn't talk here.
It's not safe.
Let's go to my office.
That's them.
Who are they?
The Furies.
The living manifestations
if vengeance,
Jealousy,
and unresting rage.
So Manta hired three look
a-likes to scare me into
giving back the
Heart of Medusa?
That guy is sick.
And you led them to me.
Or maybe she
led you to me.
What the hell are
you doing here?
I came to render additional
services from the doctor,
but instead I find her
keeping interesting company.
What's going on?
You two know each other?
We had a deal.
Or so I thought.
Manta hired me to map out
a potential location of
Medusa's heart.
And when Dad's book was
published--
A book based on my theories.
A lot of people came out
looking for treasure.
Fortune hunters like Manta
hire me all the time to help
them map out spots.
I had no idea he'd
actually find it.
But I did.
And now I find you coercing
with the man who stole it. Why?
No. You tell me why you killed
Lyta to get it back.
Or maybe you know?
How dare you accuse me of
being involved in that. I
don't even know this guy.
Once he paid me for the map,
I was done with him.
I've spilled no blood.
Yet.
You just have your
women do it for you.
I don't associate with
the newer sex.
They're devious, as the
good doctor proves.
Where is the stone?
Lyta sold it. Ask her.
Oh, wait. You can't,
because she's kind
of dead now.
Its too bad. I thought
you might know.
Kill them.
Starting with her.
You okay?
I am the great Manta.
Wow.
He's so strong, AHH!
So we're getting a boat and
leaving tonight, right?
In this storm? No way.
We have to wait
till morning.
But what if Manta
find us here?
Trust me. If Manta finds us in
here we are more than prepared.
What's wrong?
What is it?
-That guy threw one
hell of a punch.
Here. Let me see it.
Does that hurt?
A little bit.
-Yeah.
Yeah. It's a
little blue.
No. Doesn't hurt.
So who did you sell the
Heart of Medusa to?
Never you mind who I
sold that heart to.
Sinbad, I'm serious.
What's to stop Manta from
going after that guy?
We made a deal under
the table.
Lyta doesn't keep records.
There's no way Manta can
find out who it is.
Don't you think you should
warn the buyer?
This buyers isn't
afraid of Manta.
And I don't want you
to be either.
I am. I feel responsible for
getting you into this mess.
Well make it up to me.
What?
You afraid of remembering how
much you like kissing me?
No. I just don't want to
lose you again.
I'm not gonna let
anyone hurt you.
It's not me that I'm
worried about.
It's you.
Why?
Someone has to
worry about you.
Right?
Jax.
Damn girl. I missed you
so much.
Hello, lover.
You lied.
One more time.
We want the heart.
I told you, I don't have it.
If you won't tell us,
We'll have to pull it out of
his whore instead.
Is it in there?
Enough!
What was that?
Alright.
Everyone on the boat.
We're leaving right now.
Shouldn't we call the cops?
Yeah. I'd love to see how
they'd handle this.
Everyone wants this stone so
bad and I want to find out why.
If anyone knows,
it's this Ace dude.
Voicemail.
-Shoot.
Ace, this is Sinbad.
I'm taking you up on that
offer you made me.
Hide that stone I sold you.
Manta is after it.
And the Furies.
It's going to take me about two
days to get to your shop.
You said if I ever got in
trouble I'd be safe with you.
I hope you meant it.
You in?
Well I'm not sticking
around here.
Plus, I'd like to see the
Heart of Medusa for myself.
Yeah. I'm coming with
you. Me and the fellas,
we got your back.
And me.
-Baby, no.
You're leaving me
here by myself?
I will not put the woman that I
want to propose to in danger.
This is how you propose?
-I will propose
when I get back, baby.
I promise.
I hope you're worth it.
You and me both.
Let's get our asses to
Los Angeles.
Hey. Keep an eye
on those RPMs.
We lose this engine we'll
be sitting ducks.
You know if you didn't have
such a criminal records,
we could have flown there.
And miss all this
aquatic comradery?
Yeah. Yeah, you're right.
We're about an hour ahead of
schedule. If you can keep
this up all day and night,
we should be in Los Angeles
about dawn.
Hey. It's going to be okay.
You're not alone in this.
Not with me around.
Yeah, I know.
Look. Dolphins.
They're a good omen.
How so?
When pirates attacked Dionysus,
she turned them into Dolphins.
And then she charged them
with helping sailors,
instead of harming them.
Sweet story.
Too bad it's not true.
I think that what we saw last
night, it can all be true.
What you call magic,
I call science.
Okay, then how do you explain
what those women turned into?
I mean, they flew away.
Biotechnological weaponry.
Manta's Russian after all.
That is paranoid and
delusional thinking. What are
you, an American?
And you believing in gods and
goddesses and
magic dolphins isn't paranoid
and delusional thinking?
As always, logic wins
the debate.
You want science?
Fine.
Come on.
Come on!
You ever study
numerology?
That's on my list of
things never to do.
Well when they showed up at
your door that first night,
you know what time
it was?
I don't know. Late.
Real late.
Was it after 3:30?
Sure.
When those two women
grabbed me last night, I
happened to look at the clock.
It was exactly 3:33.
Now there's 3 women.
That's one Roma numeral
for each woman.
Now, 3+3+3 is 9.
-Hold on.
9. Yep.
Good work.
A group of 9 is called an
ennead.
Multiple enneads is
called Erineys.
Which is a Greek term for--
-Furies.
Exactly.
We live in a
mathematical universe.
Somehow the time of 3:33
unlocks a dimension between
our world and theirs.
Is that central or
mountain time?
I just can't figure out why they
can't stay in our world?
What keeps sending them
back each time?
Maybe they have part-time
jobs as telemarketers.
That would explain why they're
so pissed off all the time.
-Sinbad, come on.
Be serious. I'm trying to
save your life here.
And my life. Nick's life.
I appreciate it.
I really do.
-I'm scared
that your sword isn't gonna
save you this time.
-I'm not.
This isn't paranoid or
delusional.
-Oh my gosh.
What is it gonna take to
convince you that these women
maybe supernatural?
- Sinbad?
SINBAD! SINBAD!
Oh my God!
Sinbad!
Ooh!
-It finally happened.
David Duchovny turned me
into a dolphin.
It's Dionysus, you idiot!
And quit making fun of me!
I'm okay.
Thanks for asking.
How you ever been with
a Merman, girl?
You want to go to Atlantis?
Right under the sea.
Are we gonna
celebrate this ship's
inaugural trip or what?
And may I point out how long
this trip is since some of us
can't fly?
Sinbad.
What kinda of adventure do
you got me going on?
Your last one.
Before you settle down and
become and old man.
- And you will get back to
Mexico,
give Daphne a proper proposal,
and become and old man.
I promise.
That ain't for you.
Nick wasn't kidding.
He really does love that girl.
Do you want to get married?
Are you proposing?
No.
Eww. I'm asking in general.
It's not really my style.
Yeah. I didn't think I
liked tradition either.
I think I'm staring to
change my mind.
About a lot of thing actually.
Like the Furies.
Even though they scare me, I
feel strangely comforted by
the fact that magic and
myth could be real.
Why?
The Ancient World was a
madhouse.
And you prefer that over
the mindless chaos of the
modern world?
I mean, at least back then, you
could appease a god by making a
sacrifice to it.
Sinbad! Come
join the party!
It would be rude to not go up
and have a couple brewskis.
Cheers.
"Party on!"
"Excellent!"
Maybe they overslept.
Did you get any sleep at all?
Nope.
Man.
I thought for sure I'd
figured it out.
Maybe they can't
manifest in water?
And can only crawl out of the
earth from where their blood was
first spilt?
So you do believe!
No. But you do.
It's cute.
I'm sorry they're just
regular assassins.
I'm so embarrassed.
Don't be. I used to stay up all
night waiting for Santa
Claus to show up. So what?
You stayed up all night
waiting for the brides of Satan
to show up.
It is a little weird. I guess,
I can see how you'd be a
little embarrassed.
Why are you up so early?
We're half hour from port.
Oh really?
Thirty minutes.
That was fast.
Hey, can I see those
binoculars?
Thanks.
I gotta go help up top.
Go pack up your books.
I want to be ready to rock
as soon as we dock.
Wait. Wait, do you see
that over there?
On that cliff.
- Where?
- Here.
Trees?
Go back up.
Everybody up!
Approaching land!
I never thought I'd
be back here.
What? The United States
or with Jax?
Hey! We're not like official.
Keep it straight!
I can't control it.
I'm getting pulled
towards the rocks!
I'm going to go
shut off the engine.
- Alright.
Hurry!
We're in trouble!
Sebastian,
grab the wheel!
Mikey! Eyes up top!
Special K is out of
the plates.
- It's the Furies!
- Not now Jax!
Ah! Stop! Stop!
Stop! Please!
Help! Sebastian!
Sebastian!
Sebastian! Help me
hold him down!
Sebastian!
Are you okay?
Okay. Help the other crew!
Hurry!
What happened?
Furies! Come on!
Hurry!
You want him?
Nick!
Come and get him!
No!
Finally Arabian.
Your payment for my
vengeance is long overdue.
Nick!
Looking for Ace Adar.
You heard of him?
He wasn't very nice.
Let's try that guy.
Hello.
Oh, no thanks.
Don't look now but that guy
back there has been following us
for a while now.
You're about as subtle
as a drunken goat in a
convalescent home.
No thank you.
It's pretty.
Come on. Let's go around.
Gotta find this Ace guy.
That's too expensive.
Thank you though.
Not to worry, Dr. Kree.
- Compliments of Manta Marquis.
Let's get out of here!
Stop! Thief! Thief!
In there!
All clear.
What about these?
You're not gonna like this.
I must be crazy.
You...
-Oh my God.
- are welcome.
Thank you.
Mr. Siridad!
Who are you?
I want to help you.
Why have you been
following us all day?
I wasn't sure if it was you.
You an assassin, too?
I'm your driver.
Ace Adar sent me.
He wanted you to
arrive in style.
Welcome to Los Angeles.
Come. This way.
Mr. Siridad, we have arrived.
Sinbad!
Welcome!
-Hey you!
Oh!
How fragrant you are.
You didn't pick up your phone.
I lost the damn thing again.
Me and modern day
don't mingle well.
Ace, I'd like you to meet--
-Shh!
Ooh.
Let me guess your name.
Okay. Mm-hmm.
-Please come closer.
I want to read your palm.
Sure.
Hmm.
Somebody's been a naughty girl.
Intelligent.
Yet naive in some matters.
Excuse me?
It's okay. I'm a raving idiot
about mechanics,
but I know every
constellation by heart.
Hmm.
You have a secret dream.
You're scared to tell the
other about.
Don't me all?
Now, as enchanting as this is,
we really do have to--
Ah. Ah.
Here it is.
You have your aunt's name.
Jacqueline.
Boom!
Oh my God!
That's incredible.
Try him next.
Oh no, no, no, no. Sorry.
My skills only work on women.
Please, come inside.
Come inside.
Thank you.
Thanks.
-Thanks.
Come.
Ah.
Come in my friends.
Welcome to my home.
The Babylonaica?
But these volumes were lost
when the Library of Alexandria
burned down, right?
You have a good eye.
Actually, those are only
reproductions.
The originals are stored
safely in my vaults.
But don't tell. Every armchair
archeologist with a blog will be
flying in to check it out.
Please. Come and sit down.
Oh my gosh.
Do you still have the
Heart of Medusa?
Of course. Along with the liver
of Prometheus, the loins of
Adonis--
Keep your loins to yourself.
Manta knows we're in
Los Angeles.
His men attached us by
your shop.
Ooh. That's awfully
bold of him.
Like the other artifacts
he recovered,
he must believe the heart can
be used as a weapon as well.
Is this stone a weapon?
Hard to say.
Anything can be mutated into a
device of destruction.
Just look at what we've done
with the atoms in the air.
Three women are also after us.
Jax believes they're the Furies.
I know they're the Furies.
Wait.
You're on the hit list for both
the Russians and the Greek gods?
Popular boy.
Give me the heart and
let's all get out of here.
And who's going to
reimburse me?
Where would you take us that's
safer than here?
Not every problem can be solved
by running away, Sinbad.
Fine.
What's your solution?
What do you think we
should do with the heart?
Destroy it.
If the stone no longer exists,
there's nothing for Manta or
these Furies to take.
No. That stone is an
invaluable artifact.
To be studied and learned from.
Not to be destroyed.
My past experience ditching the
evidence only pisses of the
people you owe even more.
Ace, what is the deal
with this stone?
I'm not sure but I believe there
is someone that can tell us what
we're dealing with.
But...
But you rather give
me a migraine while I
try to figure out
what you're thinking
outside your head?
The heart isn't the only
treasure I own with
mystical appeal.
You have a skill with these
artifacts. I would like to
take advantage of.
If you want me to do magic
tricks, there's a two
drink minimum.
But first,
you need to take a
bath and change.
To look at some artifacts?
Let's just say it's best to make
a good impression on her.
"Her?"
"Her."
No. "Her."
Okay. Alright you guy.
Well I think a shower
sounds wonderful.
But unfortunately, We
don't have ant clothes that
we can change into.
Not to worry. I have ample
wardrobe selection for you both.
I hope you don't mind a more
traditional style.
Show our guests to their rooms.
And lay out the clothes
I prepared.
We are running for our lives and
you're planning a dinner party?
Who's supposed to jump in and
save the day, Martha Stewart?
Oh, she' much better
than Martha.
Who is this lady you want
me to impress?
I've never met her myself,
But I believe you can
draw her out.
Come my friends.
Go.
So where's Sinbad?
This is going to make
and impression.
Was he an Arabian
Chippendale?
Very nice.
I just can't do the turban.
Not to worry. I wouldn't
wear it either.
But you look
magnificent.
A spitting image if I may
say so myself.
You know, we may
just fool her.
Who else is
here besides us?
Ace, instead of
playing dress up,
we should be figuring
what this stone can do
and how to stop Manta and those
women from getting it.
-Mmhm. Yeah. Yeah. Sure.
Does it feel heavy?
Yeah.  I should feel overly
exposed, odd weight to it.
-Like,
aura of armor, yes?
Where did you get this?
The desert's too hot for
heavy armor,
so old Sindibad had it woven
from the silk of the Calypso
Spider to give him an
advantage in war.
I want to live
here forever.
I love this!
Sinbad, isn't this
awesome?
Fits me perfectly.
Yeah. It is perfect. For a five
year old birthday party.
Guys, enough games.
Ace, where's the heart?
Upstairs. That's the best place
for us to try this.
Just in case things get
a little boisterous.
You know, if the Furies
do come tonight,
and it's safe to
assume they will,
we're going to need a magical
bodyguard ourselves.
Please, come on.
Yes.
This way.
Jax?
Oh, I'm good I'll stay here.
I found some reading.
-You sure?
Yeah.
-Okay.
How do these furies
keep finding me?
And if they're so magically
powerful and all-knowing,
why don't they know you
have the heart?
Maybe it's not all
they want.
What aren't you telling me?
I wonder if the Furies
really want the Heart of
the Medusa back.
I'm beginning to believe that
they could be after you instead.
Watch your step.
Oh! Oof!
Is this where you keep
the dead bodies?
I know.
It's the heart.
Where is it?
In that basket.
I tried covering it up
to contain the smell,
but it just gets
stronger.
Ah!
Sorry. That's
Cleopatra's asp.
What a great ass she had.
Some say it's Cesar.
Dude. get a new hobby.
Try the other.
Careful.
There's definitely a chemical
breakdown in that jewel like
nothing I've encountered before.
Wha is all this stuff?
Ah. This...
is my more
eclectic treasures.
Aladdin's carpets.
Here, the tears of Allah.
This is a perfect atmosphere
for us to try using this.
It never worked for me.
Not even as a traditional lamp.
But perhaps if a descendant
of the original Old
Sindibad lights it,
maybe it will bring her our
of her slumber.
Okay. Come on.
What do you have to lose?
Try it.
I've tried all kinds of oils.
It's not a lamp.
It's a puzzle box.
-Really?
How do we open it?
Simple.
Solve the riddle.
My lord.
I had no idea it had
such a shine.
It's like brand new.
What's it saying?
It's some kind of Ancient
Genie dialect. I'm a bit rusty
but let me try.
She said she can manifest
reality three times
if you're too lazy to do it
yourself. Oh! She's witty.
Manifest reality, like...
Anything?
She said, you can limit
yourself if you like.
Millions do it everyday.
Ask her what the Heart of
Medusa is and why Manta
and those rejects from
Lita Ford School of Rock
want it so bad.
That's a mouth full.
Let me try.
She's getting angry. She said
she can't read minds and the
stone can't do anything,
It's just matter
without consciousness.
But you just said she could.
Let me try.
She's getting really mad.
She says, "Make a wish.
Any wish. Get a life!"
Bring my friend Nick
back to life.
You said you can do anything.
She can turn time forward, but
she can't turn time back.
Okay. What else
can't you do?
She won't intentionally harm
anyone and she won't give you
money.
That would involve taking it
away from someone.
So you can't kill the Furies?
I am a Genie, not a machine gun.
Wait a minute, you
speak english now?
What is this? Some weird
elaborate hoax?
I had no idea.
I don't have time
for this.
You are different than
the other Sinbad.
You have an air of arrogance.
And yet you are actually humble.
A valiant hero trying
to be a thief.
You're wishes don't work because
you're actually pretending to be
something else.
A rogue.
If you think I'm a joke,
say it to my face.
I don't need some industrial
Light and Magic rip-off
making fun of me.
I came here for one reason.
To get the stone. Now that I
have it--
Hey! That's got the snake in it.
Which you should get rid of
because it's illegal to keep
exotic pets in California.
Look at the thief
peaching the law.
The Jinn was right. Deep down,
you are a hero at heart.
Sebastian, we're
out of here.
Sinbad, wait.
Get your stuff.
We're out of here.
This guy has done nothing but
waste our time and play games.
Sinbad, I'm sorry.
I never meant to offend you.
Offended I can handle.
But lied to?
I never miss let you.
And you told me you were
going to share the magical
mysteries of my family.
And I have!
If my heritage involves playing
footsie with some second-rate
Barbara Eden wanna-be you keep
locked up on the attic, I pray
to God I'm adopted.
Young man, that lamp hasn't
worked for anyone for
hundreds of years.
Who knows what you're
capable of if you just embraced
your legacy!
I don't care about my heritage.
I don't want the lamp. I
don't want the heart. I wish
I'd never even found it.
I'd rethink that if I were you.
Why? What's so special about it?
Well it says here that the Heart
of Medusa has the power of
twenty gods.
Big deal.
And it can transform the
shape of continents.
Oh yeah? I think Global Warming
has dibs on that one.
Okay. Well I think with
these ancient texts backing
up these claims,
that gem it could easily
be worth over one hundred
million dollars.
I will fight to the death
to keep that stone away
from anyone who tries to take
it or wishes us harm.
How do you know that anyway?
Easy.
I found the instruction manual.
I forgot I owned that book.
These texts are endless
allegories about the
Heart of Medusa
is a warning that revenge and
anger just trap a person
in some kind of prison of rage
so that they can't move on with
their life.
Sound like wise words to me.
Cardinal, bring another
bottle of wine.
The Domaine Jean-Louise Rhone
2005.
Not the 2003?
You common Peasant!
Oh, I'm impressed.
Fetch the good vintage. I must
live up to Sinbad's standards.
You seem pretty calm on the
eve of Armageddon.
Well, I learned long ago to let
fate have her way with me.
All I can control is whether
I face her sober.
This is useless.
Ah. Let me see your finds.
I'm not even sure if the Heart
of Medusa is a weapon anymore.
Then we stick with what
we know works.
Yeah.
I picked these up at the
market yesterday.
These work.
I highly recommend them.
Instead of striking back
at the Furies,
perhaps there's another way to
quell their anger towards you.
Why do they hate me so much?
What's this grievance they
have against me?
Hmm. The "useless" wisdom our
dear doctor discarded
is actually the instructions
we're looking for.
Here it is.
You ancestor, Old Sindibad,
sailed seven voyages.
Most with passion
and glory,
but it says here his fourth
voyage, i'm sad to say,
brought out the worst in him.
He shipwrecked on an
island and married the
kingdom's princess.
Not long after the wedding,
she fell ill and died.
It was then he learned the
land's dastardly custom.
If one spouse died, the
living spouse was buried
alive with them.
You know what, they use to
do that in India.
Except it was only the wives
that had to be buried alive with
their dead husbands.
No the other way around.
Which is sexist.
Why did you look at me when
you said that?
Sinbad was thrown into the
communal tomb with just a little
bit of water
and a small loaf of bread.
Weeks passed. Just when he
was about to die, the tomb
opened and another couple-
this time the husband dead,
but the wife was alive.
She was thrown into the cavern.
Only thinking about
himself, Sindibad killed
the woman and took her
rations to stay alive.
He did this two more times
with two other women
thrown into the tomb.
Eventually he had enough
rations to regain his
strength and escape.
Those three women he killed
became the Furies.
The stone he used to beat
them dead was the actual
hardened heart of
the slain Medusa,
discarded in the cave,
but given new life  by the anger
of the three murdered women.
Resurrected by mad magic
as the Furies,
they swore to one day use the
stone to punish all men
for Old Sindibad for Old
Sindibad's crimes.
The stone keeps them
confined to this earth in an
infinite cycle.
As long as their rage is
eternal, their lifeline will
have no end.
So is the stone a life
force for them?
Would explain the desire
and need for it.
And why they never stay dead.
Each night they're born anew.
Old Sindibad's eighth voyage was
meant to be one of redemption.
To use his wrath to
break their rage.
He died before completing it.
But perhaps that for you to do.
Cardinal?
Ace, wait.
Get back pretty boy.
Get your hand off the
butter knife.
Hello, treasure hunter.
I'd like my property back, hmm?
Where is the Heart of Medusa?
How dare you enter my home!
You are a terrible host.
We came all this way
just to see you.
Cy, find the stone. I want to
test my theory of it.
Right here.
Right now.
Oh yeah, you got a
theory?
What "theory" is that?
Unlike you, this stone has
untapped potential.
Cy, find the stone.
Where is the stone?
Sebastian,
tell him where he can find it.
Yes, Sebastian.
Really?
Drop it!
Hey, hey! Stab her
neck.
I will filet your neck
right now if you don't
tell him to let her go.
Oh you won't
dare, Big boy.
Snap her neck,
Let her go!
-He's going to snap her neck.
It's easy. She's going to die.
Don't snap her neck. Tell
him not to snap her neck.
Let go of me first and
I'll let her live.
Oh? Hmm? Then you'll get a
little on the side? Huh?
Huh?
Eh?
Alright.
-You like that?
Yeah,
Wow.
You. Little rich man.
You're going to tell me where
the Heart of Medusa is?
Because you know and I don't.
I want to find it so badly. Hmm?
Right on time.
Who's that?
Sure as hell ain't the
Avon lady.
We better get the hell
out of here.
-No. No.
We don't have to
do anything. Hmm?
Cy, go check the door.
Fine, you stay here watch them.
me and my new friend will go
check the door, okay?
Manta.
I would listen to Sinbad.
Cy, you're my bodyguard.
I pay you to guard my body.
You're going to go first.
Then we're going to
come in after you.
And you, my man,
you're doing great.
You keep your gun on them.
If he sneezes you shoot him in
the kneecap, okay?
What are you doing? Go.
-He punched me in the throat.
I will punch you in the
clavicle. Go! Now!
Promotions for you.
Who wants to play?
Did you order strippers?
What's wrong with you?
Hand over.
Ta-ta-ta-ta. Who are you?
What do you want?
Rage shouldn't be wasted on
those we have no quarrel with.
So let's not disappoint them.
What is this, hmm?
Some kind of parlor fit for you
try to seduce me? No, no. no.
-I want you. Do you want me?
Ehh! No, you're woman--
She's got no penis for
me to play with.
What is wrong with you and
your stupid lady brain.
Always--
Bob, get in here!
Take care of these women.
Trust me. You do not want
to hear what these women
have to say.
Come on.
We can get out
through here!
Too high. We need a rope
or something.
They're going to bust
their way in.
Not if we barricade the door.
Come on.
Take that.
This should buy us some time.
Oh God.
is it some kind of acid or
something?
I don't know. It look magical.
I'm taking it.
Okay. Come on.
Books.
Come on.
Swords.
What the heck is this?
Sword. Big flower thing.
Jax, are you serious?
Everything else Ace's shown us
in here has worked.
Why not this?
How?
-I think it's a good idea.
Ask.
-The Genie is a jerk.
Do it! Hurry!
- I don't have time to take a Rosetta Stone class.
-  Speak English!
That's a demand.
Not a wish.
What?
How do I use that?
You really want to know?
-Yes!
-I'll tell you.
Are you ready?
-Yes.
Oh my god! They're breaking in.
Wake up!
I know how to fly carpets!
Come on.
Get on.
Steering.
Breaking systems.
- Ready?
- -Start the thing!
Are you okay?
I didn't need my spleen anyway.
Oh no!
The stone is okay.
It's still in tact.
Don't look directly into it,
Jax.
Oh God.
Ace was right.
It does hurt to look at it.
Aww, is it beautiful.
Come on. We have to get Ace and
bring Manta to the authorities.
Authorities?
Sinbad, you're a wanted
man. They're just going to
arrest you.
Then I'll do my time.
I'm tired of hiding.
No more running away.
You're going legit?
I guess I am.
I knew you were a lousy thief.
I suck at it.
You know, I have to admit,
this whole time I secretly
blamed you for what your
father did to me.
Taking credit for my work.
Stealing everything I ever had.
You're nothing like your father.
I wish that were true.
Why didn't you take the
stone and run?
- Yeah, with those things
running every night?
I don't think so.
And I did wait for you,
didn't I?
You wanted to cut me out and
take the stone all for yourself.
Don't tell me that my act was
so convincing that I fooled the
great Manta.
Don't try to out bitch a bitch.
Thank God you're alive.
I was worried you'd been
knocked into a coma.
Why are you doing this, Jax?
Mr. Siridad! Just in time.
You two are in this together.
I found the location of the
stone and Manta brought the
man power to get it.
And you almost ruined everything
with your big man muscles.
Yeah.
Of all the caves you could have
explored, Sinbad. Why that one?
Huh?
All through I'm still not sure
why I still let you convince me
I should leave the stone
where I found it.
I was right about it being
guarded, wasn't I?
Jax, why are you doing this?
I have my reasons.
One hundred million to be exact.
One hundred million split
between us. Hmm?
Of course.
You said the stone couldn't be
used as a weapon.
What mystical powers it has,
I still don't know.
But it does have a
practical use.
It is after all, it's
still a mineral.
The Heart of Medusa is actually
a complex emerald made up of
chromium and vanadium.
Chromium helps regulate your
blood sugar and vanadium is
a very rare chemical capable
of binding steel together.
The gun chips off a bit of
the gem here,
the it oxides in
this chamber,
and when the particles are
combined and projected into
someone--
It turns them to stone.
In a way.
The overdose of chromium
ruptures your blood vessels,
carrying the vanadium throughout
your body, hardening all your
organic tissue
before you finally combust.
-We call it the Medusa 2.0.
All through I wanted to call it
the gore gun, but Jax here
thought--
Isn't it fascinating?
Bravo.
Why do you have Ace
and I tied up?
Huh?
To give you and audience?
No, silly.
So we can test it out.
On you.
Rock hard Sinbad right
in front of me.
An new age is dawning.
One where technology and
magic are combined.
Unlike our ancestors, we won't
bow down and worship the gods.
Yeah.
This time around,
we are the gods.
May I do the honors?
Better have Cy. Just in case it
vaporizes whoever is holding it.
We still have some of the kinks
to work out.
Good idea.
Cy, will you do the honors?
You know I can hear you.
-What?
Ace, I'm so sorry.
No, you've inspired me.
Just as I will inspire you.
My friend, don't waste
your journey.
Fire!
It's still calibrating!
Get'em you stupid idiot!
- Where they go?
- That way!
How do I stop this?
Be more specific with your
intention to get what you want.
I can't do this alone.
Can you--
It is impossible for me--
-Kill anyone. I know.
What should I do?
I suggest using your enemy
to fight your enemy.
The Furies?
Man, they want to kill me.
And you think I can get them
in my side?
If that is your wish.
Shall I bring them forward to
follow your will.
How?
It's daylight.
Is it?
Why did you summons us, Arabian?
I don't mean to hurt you.
I mean to serve you.
I mean, if you're willing
to serve me.
You can give is the weapon that
can also annihilate us?
-It's a trick.
Look, we're on the same
side now, okay?
We're not adversaries anymore.
The enemy of my
enemy is also my friend.
There's people up there
that have done some really
messed up stuff.
I don't think you guys would
appreciate either. I think if
we--
-What you stole from us
other have perverted and
desecrated.
Help me fight them to
get it back.
This is a limited alliance.
You're too much like the
one who cured us.
If you think we'll
befriend you--
-I don't exactly want to
have a picnic with
you guys either, okay?
Could you stop blabbing and
start screaming?
Protect yourself.
Did you guys here that scream?
Do you think those women
are coming back?
If they so they're going have
to deal with me.
The money is in the account.
We fly to Russia tonight.
First I need to fix the
calibration on this thing.
So there's no delay
between shots.
No, you will do as I say.
Must I?
Yes, dearest doctor.
You will.
I am so sick of you talking
down to me.
Too bad.
Indeed.
The queen is dead.
Long live the queen.
Damn right.
Hand over the weapon, Jax!
Run!
You get Sinbad.
I'll get the last one.
You moron.
Sinbad, come out. I'm
not playing hide and seek,
especially not with my ex.
She's picking us off one by one.
We can't hide from here forever.
So let her find me.
Jax?
I'm coming out.
So we can talk.
I've been thinking.
Maybe it's not too late for us.
Jax?
It's not too late.
We can still take that magic
carpet and fly to Cabo.
Wait, wait, wait.
Answer me one question.
Do you believe in soul mate?
No.
Me neither.
Aah!
Give it to me! I've earned it!
Please. We had a bargain.
This has to end.
I'm free.
Unlock your heart.
Stop your sufferings.
Set free your rage.
Right now this rage is
all I got.
Everyone I ever loved is dead.
Every dream I have gone.
Go to your ship, Sinbad.
See why the
Jinn couldn't grant your
deepest wish.
How could she? You can't
resurrect the living.
Nick!
You're alive!
Dude! Dude!
I've been working all hard all
day to get the army to find you.
The fact that I had no idea
where you were hindered
those plans a bit.
Bro, I saw you drown.
Yeah. A lifeboat pulled me out
the water that's to Daphne.
I few up and didn't let the
Coast Guard sleep until they
found him.
I got a bit of a bump on my head
but at least I got the boat
fixed up and running.
What'd I miss?
Nothing important.
Everything all good
with the heart?
Yeah. Yeah.
Everything's just fine.
Should I call off the troops?
Yeah. Call them off right now.
They find out who we are, we're
all gonna be in trouble.
Most definitely.
Right. Right.
So, can we go to Chile now?
We can go...
where ever we want.
Ripped and synced by explosiveskull
www.addic7ed.com
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org