Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org
Nice, easy mile now, warm it up!
- Take your time.
- Hurry up!
Aww.
It'd be so much cuter
if you were wearing little shoes.
It'd be cuter if he exploded at the end.
- Excuse me.
- Bless you.
- You know...
- Black lung.
Did you know that
pilgrims used to think sneezing
meant you were expelling demons?
- What?
- That's why I never sneeze.
I want to keep them all
- in my soul.
- Your soul.
If I had one.
Twitter poll.
If you could stay one age forever,
what would it be?
- Easy. 21.
- No way. I'd be 10.
Oh, no, 10 was the worst, man.
I say, 30. It's like
the height of sophistication.
- You?
- What about the age we are right now?
I'd like to stay like this forever.
Seriously? I mean,
what's wrong with you?
Okay, fine. The age we are right now,
but we could all live
in a house together.
Okay, fine. But without Wren, though?
Yeah, obviously,
that goes without saying.
Super funny. Like, whoa.
Guys,
the dudebros in their natural habitat.
Let's observe, shall we?
Hey, Tom! So, what's the plan tonight?
- Big plans...
- Hey.
- It's top secret.
- Oh, I see. A circle jerk?
- Hey, Chloe.
- Hey, Kyle.
So, what's the big secret?
I mean, I could tell you,
but then, I'd have to kill you.
- Okay, buddy.
- Yeah.
Yeah. It's very intriguing.
You guys, I got to go get my sister,
but I love you. Bye.
See you later.
I'll pick you up tonight.
- I'm sorry.
- Bye. It's okay.
Bumped into Coach Sanders today.
Said your 1,600-meter time
is really improving.
All that training's paying off.
Nice work, sweetheart.
Did you tell them Delores Constantino
quit the team'?
Why?
She's pregnant.
What is she planning to do, now?
She's gonna drop out, and keep the baby.
I assume Wren is gonna be
at Katie's tonight?
Yeah. So?
So, what are you guys gonna do?
You know, drink a lot of vodka,
and meet guys online.
Funny. Very funny.
- Can I come?
- Not a chance.
- You said I could come next time.
- I lied.
- Hey.
Do you think
I could hang out with you guys?
Uh, yeah, not tonight, grasshopper.
Sorry. Maybe next time.
Oh, I wore the shirt
you gave me to school.
Got sent to the principal's office.
- Well done, man. Yes.
- Hey.
- Goodbye.
Bye.
Love me.
Bye, Lizzie.
- Hey.
Don't make any noise.
It's dormant.
Just another exciting Friday
night at the Jensen's.
No? On?
Yeah, it's girl gaze porn.
You know how they have POV porn?
- Yeah.
- This one's from our perspective.
- I don't want to see that.
- For sure.
Oh, my God.
Do you think she likes that?
- Oh, my God
- No!
Oh, God! Once you see it,
you just can't unsee it.
What the hell is he doing?
He's probably just
looking for another bottle.
- Sometimes, I wish I could just leave.
- I know.
Why don't we just all leave?
Get out of this stupid town together.
Where would we go?
I have friends in Paris.
We could totally stay with them.
What friends?
You've never been to Paris.
- My mom has friends there, idiot.
- Don't I wish.
I'll just be stuck here forever,
in this shithole.
Seriously! No, I think you
and Carl would make an adorable couple.
It's "Kyle," and I don't like him.
Yeah, yeah, yeah. Whatever, you know.
But we all know that you wish you were
at their little secret sausage fest
right now.
No.
But I do know what their secret is.
Oh, yeah? Do tell.
So, they're getting together
tonight at Tom's house
in his garage, to summon Slender Man.
- Creepy.
- Who's Slender Man?
Yeah, he's the guy
who makes all those kids disappear.
Why have I not heard of this?
That's a much longer conversation.
- Listen.
- Troll...
"Slender Man can manifest
in a variety of forms.
"Certain accounts speak
of a hypnotic power
"that renders his victims helpless
to stop themselves
"from walking into waiting arms.
"While his origins and motives
are completely unknown,
"he preys upon innocent youth.
"Once you see him, you're his.
"Some he takes, some he doesn't.
"Nobody knows why he takes who he takes,
or why he leaves who he leaves.
"But the ones he leaves behind
are messed up forever."
All right, here it is.
"How to summon Slender Man."
- Guys, we so have to do this.
- We actually don't.
Actually.
If they're doing it, we're doing it.
This feels wrong. This feels like
Russian malware-y virus-type shit.
Come on, don't be such a wuss.
"Those who hear the three bells toll
"accept his invitation.
"When you hear the first,
you must close your eyes,
"keeping words unspoken.
"If one wants to hear,
you must listen closely,
"for they are soft and distant.
"With eyes still closed
and mind wide open,
"clear your thoughts
and await the second,
"opening your eyes
only once you've heard the third."
Hmm.
Are you serious? This is...
Shh!
What a stupid video. Honestly.
Can we do something else?
- Let's watch a movie.
- Yeah.
This burial ground dates back
all the way to the Revolutionary War,
which was 1775 to 1783.
In 2004, it was put on the
National Registry of Historical Sites,
which was very exciting.
Initially, all of this land
belonged to Thomas Clifton,
who left it to the town of Winsford
in his will in 1674.
You guys, I threw up twice
this morning, before I got on the bus.
Is it Carl's?
Ha. That's hilarious,
and also, scientifically impossible.
Have you been having nightmares?
Mmm-mmm.
Have you?
Uh...
About what?
It's nothing, really.
It's just that video.
Stronger and more
durable, which is also...
Hey, Katie?
Katie, are you okay?
Yes.
Katie? Cut this shit out, man.
All right, we're all prisoners
because of you.
So, none of you saw where she went?
- No.
- Really?
- Damn it.
- I mean, where is she?
Yeah, she still hasn't answered
any of my texts.
Why are the police here?
Oh, shit.
You see her'?
Mmm-mmm.
Teenager
Katie Jensen was last seen on Wednesday,
during a school field trip
to the historic Clifton Cemetery.
As of now, local police have no leads,
but are questioning friends
and family members
in hopes of gaining insight
into the reason for her disappearance.
Citizens with any information are being
urged to contact local authorities.
You should tell me
what really happened to Katie.
We never keep secrets from each other.
How would you know'?
You don't know that. Do your homework.
Come on, I don't want to talk about it.
It was a boy, right'?
You think I'll tell? I'd never tell.
You'd totally tell.
Not Mom and Dad.
Totally Mom and Dad.
Maybe.
Definitely,
but you get points for honesty.
So, tell me.
You don't know. Do you?
Just do your work, Lizzie.
- Hallie.
- Lizzie.
Fine.
I could stay home alone, you know.
I'm old enough.
Physical age, maybe.
Did you hear that?
Hey, Morn? Dad!
Hey, Mom?
Hallie, someone's in here.
Stay here. Okay? Don't move.
Hallie? Hallie, what is it? Hallie...
We called the police!
Katie? Katie?
Police emergency.
Can I help you?
Katie.
Katie, you here?
Mr. Jensen?
Where's my daughter?
I don't know.
- Is Katie here? Are you hiding her?
- No.
I don't know where she is.
It's all your fault.
She was never into this stuff.
- All this occult stuff.
- Hallie?
Lizzie, stay back.
- Where is she?
- I don't know.
- No! Don't! Hallie!
- Where is my daughter?
- Hallie!
- Lizzie!
- Where is she?
Let's go.
- Stay the hell away from my family!
- Hey, hey, hey!
You hear me, Jensen?
Did you guys really try
and summon Slender Man?
Why?
We chickened out.
You chickened out.
- I chickened out?
- You chickened out.
- I remember you being the one...
- He chickened out.
That chickened out.
Katie's father
broke into my house last night.
- What?
He said something about Katie
being into the occult,
and then he blamed us
for getting her into it.
Wait, what did he mean about
Katie being into the occult?
I don't know. He was so wasted.
This could be
the next wrinkle in the story.
I don't want to play this game.
It's not a game. Katie's missing.
Yeah, and we know things
that nobody else knows.
What do we know?
We know that she watched that video.
Look, we all watched that video.
It didn't do anything.
When are we gonna admit
that Katie was kidnapped?
Somebody has her.
Yeah, but when we watched that video,
it affected all of us.
Something happened. I felt it.
- I didn't see anything.
- I didn't see anything, either.
Didn't say I saw it. I said I felt it.
And I think you did, too.
And I'm damn sure that Katie felt it,
and that's why she disappeared!
This is a bad idea.
It's just a quick look around, okay?
Plus, you know what,
he's probably totally passed out by now.
I don't know, I just feel like
there's got to be something.
- You know, like a clue, maybe, or...
- You're crazy.
You don't realize how he was last night.
The back door is always unlocked
for when Katie gets home late.
Just saying.
Great. Then let's go.
Told ya.
Wren?
Hi. Hi, Mr. Jensen.
What are you doing here?
Well, I just wanted to come down
and see if there was anything
that I could do, if I could help
in any way?
Anything I could do.
I miss her.
People just don't disappear.
You want to come in?
Thaw be great.
She's really gone.
The police must have taken her laptop.
What is all this?
She used to keep
cigarettes and stuff in here.
Let's just take it.
Okay.
Here's the last site she visited.
What am I looking at?
Here, click it.
Okay.
Oh, shit.
All these, like, town names,
and dates and stuff.
Click another one.
Okay, guys. Let's go.
I am Slender Man.
- Dude.
- Guys, guys.
Whoa, whoa.
What is that? What is that?
I'm so scared. I'm so...
Go, go, go!
- Oh, God!
- Dude, he's there!
I can't...
- It's him.
- I don't like this.
- Wait, look.
- What?
AleeyKat93.
Jeez.
They went back and forth,
like, a gazillion times.
"I knew he was there
before I saw him."
It's like they're comparing experiences.
Wait, look. Katie posted a video.
Look, it's from the night
before she disappeared.
- What was that?
- What did you see?
What did you see?
- I don't know, I...
- I don't know, either.
- I talked to her.
- Who?
AleeyKat93.
It was that girl that Katie was
talking to on that website.
I messaged her, and she replied.
You went back on that website?
She told me everything.
He gets in your head like a virus.
What kind of virus?
Like a computer virus
that infects your hard drive,
but instead of your hard drive,
it's your brain.
- Wren, you're gonna need to slow down...
- No, listen to me.
Once the virus takes hold,
he's got you. It's done.
Some he haunts, some he drives mad.
- And others, he takes, like".
- Like what?
Katie.
Listen, I know that this...
This is gonna sound crazy,
but AleeyKat said we can
"unveil ourselves."
Okay, if we just surrender
something to him
that has personal meaning,
something that we truly love.
What the hell does that mean?
We can contact Slender Man.
Why would we do that?
To get Katie back. Hello?
Katie did it, and the next day,
she was just gone.
Okay, Katie asked Slender Man
- to take her?
- Yes.
Why would she do that?
I don't know. You know,
maybe she had an alcoholic father,
and maybe she hated her life,
and maybe she talked about
running away all the time, you know?
Guys, the police have no leads.
Right? Right?
So, even if the odds
are a million-to-one
that any of this is real, or that...
That he has anything to do
with Katie's disappearance,
we owe it to her to try.
This should work.
I guess that I'll...
Go first, then.
I...
I made this in pottery class,
when I was five.
This is a picture of me and my dad.
It's the only one I have
where we're together.
It was taken a few months
before he died.
My grandma made this
when Lizzie was born.
She died eight years ago.
Surprised you didn't bring
one of your trophies, or medals.
You said it had to be something
I cared about, so...
I brought this.
Lights out.
Okay, so...
Listen, once we ask for Katie's return,
we have to keep
these blindfolds on, all right?
AleeyKat said not to look in his face.
If you do,
you're messed up forever.
It's different for everyone,
but it only ends in insanity, or death.
Okay.
Okay, hold my hand, hold my hand.
You hold her hand, too, okay"?
We all have to hold hands.
How long do you think
we're gonna give this?
As long as it takes.
Keep your blindfolds on.
Do you hear that?
Guys, we shouldn't be doing this.
- She's right.
- It's too late.
- Chloe! Chloe!
- Chloe, come back!
- Come on! Chloe!
- Come back, Chloe!
Chloe?
Hallie!
Oh, my God! Hallie.
- Where's Chloe?
- I don't know!
I told her to keep
her freaking blindfold on.
- She...
- Chloe!
- Oh, my God, Chloe!
Jesus, Chloe, you scared us to death!
Where did you go?
I lost my shoe.
It's okay.
What happened?
- You saw him.
- Wren.
Chloe, I told you
not to take your blindfold off.
- Did you see him?
- Nothing happened.
I just got scared. Okay?
Something happened, and she knows it.
Something happened back there!
You're right. We didn't get Katie back.
That's what happened.
Come on.
Wait, guys. Wait for me.
Hal?
Go away.
Are you okay?
I'm fine!
I'm fine! Just...
I'll see you later, okay?
Just go to sleep.
We'll hang tomorrow, okay?
Hey.
What's up with Chloe?
It's been a few days.
She's fine. Just a cold.
Hey, Hallie! Wait up.
- Hey.
How you holding up?
I mean, with Katie and everything.
Um...
Well, I'm okay. I...
Hey, tomorrows Friday.
We got the weekend coming up.
I was thinking,
maybe we should do something.
Yeah, sure.
You want to come over tomorrow night?
To my place?
Hallie.
Hallie?
- What?
- Are you okay?
Yeah, that's cool. Your place?
Sure.
I'll see you later?
Okay.
Hallie. Hallie, can you...
Can you hear me? I...
Hello?
Oh, God.
Please! Please help!
No! No, no!
No!
Please!
No, no!
Miss, are you all right?
- Are you okay?
- Oh, God.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Hey. Are you not
getting my texts, or something?
- Look, Wren, I don't...
- No, no, no.
Look at me. I found proof.
I found the proof. Right?
Look, look, look, I understand.
I understand now,
what AleeyKat was trying to tell me.
It's proof. Read this.
Read this with me.
Okay, it says, "paranormal contact
with bioelectric systems
"often results
in a symbiotic relationship.
"The effects on host organisms
have been well documented and manifest
"in various forms, such as..."
- Wren. Wren. Calm down.
- No, no, no.
Shh. Listen to me. "Personality
change, bizarre behavior,
"mental illness, psychosis,
loss of contact with reality,
"self-mutilation, and suicide.
"And nonspecific dissolution."
They just disappear.
Has...
Has anything weird happened
to you lately, or strange, or...
Do not hold out on me.
- Okay, so, I was talking with Tom...
- Tom?
- What's wrong with Tom?
- What? Who gives a shit about Tom, Hal?
- Just tell me what happened.
- Okay.
I thought I saw something in the trees.
It was him.
And, what about Chloe?
Have you talked to her'?
I don't know. I've called her house,
and her mom keeps telling me she's sick.
Last time I called, she pretty much
flat out told me to stay away.
We need to go there right now.
Wren, there's nothing we can do,
and I have track.
- I can't just leave.
- Track?
I thought you didn't care
about track anymore.
I thought you cared about Chloe.
Chloe.
Chloe. Wake up.
What the hell was that'?
I don't know, but I told...
I knew that she saw his face
in the woods, you know?
I knew that she was lying, too.
I knew that.
I don't want to do this anymore.
Yeah, I don't, either.
But I'm stuck in it.
And you are, too.
You just don't realize it yet.
Don't look at me like that.
I'm not doing a "thing."
All right.
"All right"?
Yeah, don't say "All right."
We only watched the website video.
But Chloe, she saw him in the woods.
- Wren, I can't keep...
- Read the book that I showed you.
You will see the body count, okay?
Thousands of disappearances.
Search parties, faces on milk cartons.
I'm not making this shit up.
And it all happened
exactly like AleeyKat said.
It's probably some 50-year-old dude
living in his parents' basement,
getting off on e-mailing
teenage girls every day.
Did you ever think of that? Did you?
So, you think that you can
just go back to real life?
Yeah, I do.
In fact, I have a real-life date
with real-life Tom tonight.
In real life.
He's not gonna stop!
And going on a date
with fucking Abercrombie Tom
is not gonna change anything!
You know I'm right!
You know I'm right.
- Hey.
Sorry I'm late.
- No worries. Come on in.
- Thanks.
I thought I had the wrong house
because there weren't any cars
in the driveway.
Yeah, my dad's at this business thing,
and Mom's at her book club, so...
So, nobody' s home'?
No, it's just us. Is that okay?
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
I didn't know you were
such a music geek.
Hmm.
So, this is my dad's, but I like it.
Cool.
Do you want me to put
something else on, or...
- No. This is great.
- Okay. Cool.
- What?
- Do you hear that?
Yeah. It's good, right?
Hey.
Hey, come here.
What the hell?
Hallie, I didn't do anything.
I know. Oh, God.
Are you okay?
Here.
Have you told anyone else about this?
If Katie was on some weird
Slender Man website, then
who knows who she met? I mean...
Probably some weird guy
in a van, you know?
I hate to say it.
Is this it?
- No, don't.
- Come on.
Tom, please. You can't go on that site.
- It's just a video.
- It's not just a video.
Promise me
you won't ever watch that video.
Tom, I'm serious. Please promise.
Okay. Okay, I promise.
Really.
I need to go.
All right, first,
let's all take a moment to observe...
- Tom. Hey.
- The exterior anatomy here.
Tom? Tom.
Hey. Are you okay?
Now, you'll notice that the cornea
looks a little cloudy and bluish.
That happens naturally because
of the preservation process.
So, very carefully, with your scalpels,
I want you to make a slice right through
the sclera as evenly as you can.
That's gonna separate
the anterior features of the eye.
Hallie.
- Katie?
- Hallie.
Hallie.
Katie?
Hallie!
- Help me, Hallie.
- Katie'?
Katie?
Hallie.
Katie!
Katie, come back!
Hallie, help me.
Come on, breathe.
You're gonna be okay.
- Breathe...
- How long did they say?
- I don't know. Come on. Come on.
- It's gonna be okay.
- Just breathe, sweetheart.
Breathe, breathe.
Come on. We got you.
We got you. Stay up.
That's right, deep breath.
- Just breathe. Deep breaths.
- Lizzie, what's going on?
Oh, my God. Lizzie!
- The ambulance is on its way.
- Lizzie.
Lizzie, it's okay. Just look at me.
- We got you.
- It's okay, baby, ifs okay.
Okay, the ambulance
is on its way, honey.
No. No, Lizzie!
- Lizzie, wake up! Lizzie!
- We're all here, Lizzie.
- Dad, do something!
- Where is that ambulance?
- I'm doing my best. Come on, Lizzie!
- Lizzie, wake up!
- Come on, Lizzie, just breathe.
Blood tests are negative.
She's gonna be fine.
They think it was just
some kind of panic attack.
They want to keep her to monitor her
for at least another day.
No. No.
Lizzie? Lizzie?
Lizzie! Lizzie!
Lizzie!
Lizzie, please.
Lizzie?
Hallie?
Hallie, are you okay?
What's the matter?
Sweetheart, what's going on?
Hey. She's okay. She's okay.
It's all right. She's gonna be fine.
Dr. Barnes, 4721.
- BP 80/40.
- Let's get her moving.
- Lizzie!
- Get her moving.
- Let's get her moving.
- Where are they taking her?
- I've got to get her to the ICU.
- Lizzie!
- He had no face.
He had no face! He had no face!
He had no face!
Lizzie!
Okay. So, now, what do I do?
Just sacrifice something you love.
Wren!
Damn it, Wren! I know you're in there!
Open up!
Wren!
Wren, what are you doing?
Wren, take my hand. Come on.
Wren, you're gonna fall! Wren.
Wren!
I'm sorry.
You're sorry? That's it'?
That's my sister! Why would you do that?
She came to me.
- Wren, she's in the hospital!
- She came to me.
It was before I knew.
To get Lizzie back, to make him stop,
you can't just
give him something you love.
It's not enough.
He wants us!
Hello?
No.
That's here. That's here.
Wait, wait, Hallie!
No.
Wren! Wren!
To get Lizzie back...
He had no face!
To make him stop...
Hallie, are you okay?
You can't just give him
something you love.
He wants us!
Take me.
Lizzie!
Hallie! No!
Hallie! Hallie! No!
- Honey! It's okay!
- Hallie! No! No!
It's okay.
- Nurse! Somebody help us!
- Hallie! Hallie!
- Hallie!
- Can we get a nurse in here?
No! No! No!
Right here.
Hallie! No!
Hallie, Katie, Chloe, Wren.
There's almost always a pattern.
He only shows himself
just enough to infect us.
The more fear he creates,
the more fascinated we get.
We talk and write about him,
share pictures, dick on finks,
Photoshop images.
That's how a virus works.
That's how it spreads.
And some people cross the line
and actually seek him out,
like my sister and her friends did.
And those messed-up people
go out and do messed-up things
that become more stories
for people to tell.
Ifs all spreading his word. You know?
We know he abducts people.
I started getting
a ringing in my ears.
It's the thing that we fear.
There?! been reports
of strange lights coming from the woods.
Viral nature of his
ever-expanding reach and influence.
I keep having nightmares
about his pale face.
Pictures include variations
of a thin man with a blanked-out face.
He seduces them.
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org