Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org
What does this say?
Does it say, "i grabbed it
outta my suitcase
"and went to the beach"
or "girl who overplans
for vacation outfits"?
There's just a picture
of a bird on it.
It doesn't
say anything.
No, I mean, like,
its vibe, you know?
Like, what's its vibe?
Oh.
It's perfect for Ecuador.
Yeah. And, like,
why Ecuador?
Because we didn't
want to go
somewhere touristy.
We're not just, like,
a couple of white assholes.
No offense.
I really need it.
I just want to, like,
sip a mai tai
and smoke a j,
and then just
kinda, like
start having red wine
at night.
And then scotch.
And if somebody's like,
"have you ever done
ayahuasca?"
I'll be like,
"no, is it safe?"
And then I'll try it.
I don't care.
And are things ideal,
financially, right now?
No. The answer is no.
But will
things pick up?
One thousand percent.
Did I tell you
Michael's band is
blowing up right now?
Yeah.
you know, money won't be
an "ish" much longer.
This is a good color
for me, right?
So, did you guys have this
in my size?
Yeah, no.
Sorry.
Okay.
Thanks, anyway.
Have fun on your trip.
Nice meeting you.
I hope you
find your keys.
Oh, my keys. Fuck!
This would be
cute on me if...
Are you serious?
You are supposed to be
selling clothes
to the customers.
And what are you even doing
on the floor?
I'm re-racking
clothes
you know what?
You're fired!
What?
I need this job.
Can you just
think about this?
Like, what about this bitch?
I've never seen her do shit.
You don't do shit here!
She doesn't work here.
Oh, okay.
Hi. Thank you so much
for coming in.
Look, can we just
talk about this
when I get back from
my vacation to Ecuador?
Vacation?
You never even asked
for time off.
And I'm realizing that
right now, okay?
And it's because
i forgot.
God! You know what?
I don't need this job.
I'm gonna go have
a sick time in Ecuador.
with all your shirts
and your hours.
Because I don't need it.
I'm about to
kick your ass.
Takin' this.
Put the damn hat down!
I looked her
right in the eye,
and I went
"i wouldn't work here
if you paid me."
And I just stormed out.
Just like, for real.
Like, "bye."
Another one will come.
You know what? I'm not gonna
talk about that anymore.
I wanna focus
on you and me
on the beach.
Are you with me?
I can't go
to south America.
What are you talking about?
I can't go
to Ecuador.
You know it's
a non-refundable trip,
right?
I don't want to make it
about money
but I don't have any more
coming right now, so
I'm breaking up
with you.
When?
Like, right now. This is it.
You're in the middle of it.
Is it because
you're afraid
because things are going
so great between us?
That's what this is!
No.
You're terrified, because
you've never felt this way
about somebody before.
I know what's happening.
I'll tell you what it is.
Okay.
The band is
really blowing up
right now, you know?
And I'm going like this.
I'm taking off, all right?
Okay.
And this is you.
Just on the ground.
I'm up here, too.
No, you're not up there.
Why can't I go up there?
No, stop.
I'm going this way.
I'm with you.
Well, I'm going
that way now.
Now, I'm over there.
I'm going.
You can't reach.
My hand's over there.
Look.
This is the thing.
Where I'm going,
there's gonna be
a ton of...
Inspiration.
...Pussy.
Inspiration?
No, pussy.
I keep talking
over you,
but it's sounding like
you're saying...
Pussy.
I heard it that time.
You heard it?
You always say
music inspires you.
Pussy inspires me.
I have a pussy.
You have one pussy.
But there's gonna be, like,
hundreds of other pussies.
What about just my pussy,
hundreds of times?
That's not as inspiring.
You don't want to lose us.
You don't want to lose this.
No. Just no.
All right,
this is the thing.
You don't have
any direction in life.
What does that mean?
It means you're not
going anywhere.
You're not
doing anything.
You know what?
I am so sorry,
honestly
I'm sorry,
but I want to see
other people.
Excuse me?
You're great
but I have
a lot going on
right now.
Yeah, I'm heartbroken.
You're gonna meet
someone so special.
Okay, I'm gonna go.
Bye.
I want you to leave!
You get out of here.
Okay, one more for you.
Yeah, not for you, Andrew.
You blew it.
Hey, it's Emily.
Leave a message.
Ah, em! Listen, honey,
I want you to be
really careful
because there was some kind
of heist in Delaware.
Yeah, and I know you're in
New York and everything
but you can never be
too safe, honey.
Okay. All right.
Okay, guys.
Let's go to bed.
What?
What? No!
Thank you. There you go.
Oh!
Poor thing!
You look awful.
Thank you.
Who the hell
does he think he is?
How do you know
i didn't break up
with him?
Did you?
No.
Of course not.
All right,
this is a long hug.
L know.
One more minute.
I haven't seen you in,
like, forever.
Can we just
move this hug along?
Hello, Philip.
Okay, honey.
So you can stay here
for as long as you want.
Carte blanche, okay?
I definitely have
to go back tonight.
Oh, tonight, right?
Tonight, I'm going back.
All right.
Well, do what you want.
Thank you.
We're in the kitchen.
Oh, Jeffrey's home?
What a shock.
Okay, don't start!
What?
Agoraphobia is
not a joke.
Mama, mama, mama... oh.
Hey, em.
'cause you guys have, like,
the exact same voice.
Okay.
No, we don't.
You have the exact same
haircut, too.
You know who you have
the haircut of?
Who's that?
Harry Potter.
Harry Potter is
the greatest
of all the wizards.
He's a hero
and a great role model.
So, I'll take it
as a compliment.
Mom, can I have
a chocolate milk?
Oh, god, mama! Mama!
Yeah?
Very cold!
I didn't heat it up.
Maybe three to four minutes
and get it nice and toasty?
We could toasty-toasty!
Don't ask mom
to toast your bread
for you!
What? Is something wrong
with your legs?
They're in
a seated position.
She's already up.
I'll put the butter
on myself.
Thank you, mama.
Wow, you're gonna
butter it yourself?
Does mom feed you
like a baby bird
when I'm not here?
I eat plenty. Don't worry
about my diet. Don't!
Mama! She's showing me
her food in her mouth.
No, I'm not, mom.
I'm chewing
like a person.
Then she opened her mouth
and showed it to me.
He's lying again.
Hey, guys!
This is supposed
to be fun.
I know what's going on
with you, man.
You got shot
through the heart.
Okay, Michael's gone.
Because you know what?
He was the best
you'll ever do.
Mom, can I eat upstairs?
No!
I would like to eat
right here with you, mom.
Mama.
You're so gay for mom.
I'm not gay for mom.
You're gay for mom!
She's a woman.
She has a vagina.
You suck mom's dick.
Guys! Cool it!
If you keep this up,
I'm not cooking anymore
and I'm not feeding you.
Stop it.
Truce.
Arthur!
Here, kitty, kitty.
Honey, have you
seen Arthur?
Did he get out?
He's right there.
Oh, good.
Hi, okay.
Does he ever move?
Sweetie,
want to watch a movie?
I don't care, mom.
Oh, honey,
i know you feel so sad.
But everything is going
to get better, honey.
I'll tell you,
when dad left
I thought I would
never have sex again.
And I was right.
But I tell you,
i am really, really relieved
that you are not going
on that trip.
Who said I'm not going
on that trip?
I'm definitely going
on that trip.
I'm just trying to pick
which friend
to bring with me
right now
because, like,
everybody wants to go.
I can't deal with
you evaluating my life
right now.
Can we just
take the night off?
I'm not in a place.
I get it.
Enough.
Don't do that.
Okay, shadee,
how about instead of rent
this month,
hear me out
you cash in on a free trip
to Ecuador?
Come on!
Aren't you, like,
from there?
Uh, no, you're the one
who sounds racist, actually.
Wow, you jumped
to the c-word
pretty fast!
How rude is that?
Oh, shit.
Mom!
Can I borrow a shirt?
Sure, honey.
Go into the hall closet.
Pack your bags.
You're going with me
to Ecuador.
Absolutely not.
Not with my knees.
Not going.
Yes, you are.
No!
Mom! Look what
i just found.
Look at how fun
you were.
Look at that!
I can't even believe
that's you.
Mmm-hmm.
Look at this.
Oh!
That was a long time ago,
honey.
Ma
this would be
so great for you.
Oh, everybody knows you need
two years to plan a vacation.
No!
What are you
talking about?
You don't do
anything fun anymore.
I go to the y twice a week,
and I take sculpting class.
I mean, look! Voila!
Mom! I told you
i would not
acknowledge that.
That is not right. Okay?
It's your home.
You put it where
you want it,
but it's an
upsetting image.
Okay.
Mom, look,
i didn't want
to do this
but here it goes.
What?
My trip...
Yeah?
...is non-refundable.
Oh, my god!
You always book refundable,
Emily! Everybody knows that!
I know, but...
Look, it's done,
and no one else
will go with me.
No one.
But I booked a journey.
And I refuse
I refuse to let
Michael's decision
dictate whether or not I,
as a woman
go on this trip.
I will embrace
this challenge
in the intrepid spirit
of all the independent
women
who have come
before me.
'Cause it's
upon their shoulders
that I'm standing.
No, I won't back down!
No!
So I stand before you
right now, Linda
and I ask you
will you
Linda, my mother,
middleton
join me
on this pilgrimage?
No.
Non-refundable!
Mom!
I can't.
Help me put the "fun"
in non-refundable.
I actually kinda caught
a piece of you, mom.
Could you lean out
a little bit?
That's cute.
Here, put this on.
What is this? What?
That is a rape whistle.
That's a rape whistle.
What?
This is
a dog whistle, mom.
Are you afraid these dogs
are gonna rape me?
Is that the main concern?
Can I just see that?
I didn't look
at the dogs.
Do they look like
rapists to you?
Why don't you just say,
"thank you, mom"?
Thank you.
"I'm being raped by a dog."
Oh, my god!
It works.
Wow! Mmm-hmm.
Huh?
Welcome.
Oh, thank you. Um
that's check-in, right?
Welcome.
No, no! Thank you so much.
No. Thank you.
This is me.
Thank you.
Oh, thank you
very much.
What's this?
Welcome!
Ma'am!
"Whale" what?
"Welcome."
Oh!
I'm sorry. Honey!
They're not serving up
whale semen.
I'm so sorry.
I've got it, thank you.
I know,
but that was not good.
Okay.
And I have you down
for a king.
Oh. Nope,
that's not right.
I was supposed to
be a king
but one thing
led to another,
and I changed it.
So, it's two queens now.
Are you sure
you changed it?
Yeah, I called ahead.
I do see that note here.
Okay, well, can you look
at that note
and make that
note happen?
I'm sorry, I cannot.
So I'm just
gonna share
a king-size bed
in a romantic locale
with my mother?
You can sleep
head-to-toe.
Like we're 69-ing.
Great.
I know what that means,
you know. "69-ing."
Really, mom?
What does it mean?
Don't test me.
Hey.
Hi.
You ate lunch
without me.
Oh, yeah. Sorry.
And you got a drink.
At 2:00 P.M.
Mmm-hmm. Sure do.
Hey, honey, you're gonna
break your toes in these.
These flip-flops are bad
for your feet.
Okay, all right.
I know.
I'm a grown woman,
so I'm fine.
But thank you.
Why are you dressed
like powder?
You look like a beekeeper.
Just get some sun,
is what I'm saying.
The sun
is very dangerous.
Mom!
Okay, please.
I just want to fix this.
I don't want you
to get melanoma
in front of my eyes.
Please.
Here. Here.
Mom!
So
I'm just gonna
read my magazine.
Oh, that's nice.
I didn't know they had
a day care program
at the hotel.
So, I don't get it.
It's gross.
It is gross.
Oh, god!
Have you talked
to your dad lately?
Mmm-mmm. I think he's still
in Florida with Susan.
Let's go out tonight.
What? No, I can't.
Yeah, you and me.
We're going out.
No, no, no.
Why?
Hair, make-up, boobs.
We're going out.
Come on.
Don't do this.
Emily, I am not going
strolling in Ecuador
at night.
You're such
a scaredy-cat.
This is what
I'm talking about.
You're gonna miss
this whole trip.
Everything shouldn't be
so scary.
Oh, it damn well
should.
Okay, thank you.
Name's Ruth. Traveling with
my best friend, Barb.
We usually go to
the Arizona gem show
every year.
But this year,
Barb got a deal
on this resort.
Well, enjoy it.
Ecuador's a pretty place.
No arguing that.
But you can't
let your guard down.
That is right.
That is exactly right.
A lot of terrible things
happen outside
these little gates.
Exactly. See?
The world's a scary place.
One in four tourists in
south America are kidnapped.
What? Incredible!
Not true.
Totally true.
One, two, three,
somebody's missing.
It's false.
Anyway, Barb retired
last year. Oh, look!
That's her over there.
Finally getting some peace.
You know,
she was in special ops.
And she's seen some shit.
Hi, Barb!
Special ops!
Wow, that's
very interesting.
Oh, don't bother
waiting for a response.
Barb cut her own tongue out
when she left the service.
Precautionary measures
to prevent from
being interrogated
for top secret information.
Couldn't they just
torture her
into writing down
the information?
Well, anyway,
i best get going.
Here's my number,
in case you guys want
to grab dinner
or lunch, or breakfast,
or a snack.
Okay.
Or just kinda sit,
you know?
Just sittin'.
Thank you, Ruth.
Thank you so much.
See you at dinner.
- Wow.
- Well
I'm going to be having
a lovely evening
here tonight
reading my novellas.
Well, I'm going to get ready
and have a drink.
What a shock.
Hey, do you mind
if I join you?
Hey, that dude...
Oh, no. Uh, sorry.
You.
Mind if I join you?
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, come over.
Please.
Uh, not you. It was me.
Excuse me?
Could you kind of beat it?
'Cause you're a distraction.
Hey, how are you?
I'm James.
Emily.
Hi, Emily.
Nice to meet you.
What happened
to your arm?
Did you try to kill yourself
'cause you're so ugly?
No, I, um
I've just spent the past
few weeks in koh phangan.
And my last day there I kept
thinking about that quote
"man cannot discover
new oceans
"unless he has the courage
to lose sight of the shore."
Wow, I love that
you don't
care about sounding
like a weirdo.
Well, you know,
I wanted a tattoo
to symbolize that
but I'm pretty sure
i must have been wasted
because I don't know
what borat has to do
with any of that.
That is brutal.
Yeah, it is.
But, actually,
i can beat that.
Look at this.
Okay.
I got this.
I was 18, okay?
Look at that.
It's raised.
Touch it, it's raised.
That is horrible.
I got it
at the worst place.
And my skirt's
over my head.
I mean,
people have certainly
finished on it.
I'm sorry.
I'm trying to, like,
be funny for you.
So, here you are.
How come you're here?
I'm a model.
I'm here, modeling.
So you're not here
with your boyfriend?
Is he a model, too?
Uh, no, I'm just here
with, um
my
my mom.
Hey, that's so crazy
you're here with your mom
because I'm here
with my mom.
Really?
No, absolutely not.
That would be so sad,
because I'm an adult.
It's pronounced "adult."
You've been to Egypt?
What were you saying?
No, yeah,
i went to Egypt.
I know it's kind of
dangerous right now.
But, I've hiked up
mountains in Iran.
I've run with the bulls
in Spain.
I've eaten poisonous
blowfish in Japan.
To me, those are the moments
that make life worth living.
I love everything
you're saying.
Your instagram
must be insane.
Oh, well, no. I'm not really
on any of those things.
How can anybody
see what you do?
Well, they don't.
But I get to live it.
Do you wanna do
something tonight?
Like, something crazy,
or can we do
something amazing?
I'm sure we can rustle up
some adventure tonight.
Yes!
Yeah.
Everything okay
over here, Emily?
I met them at the pool.
Oh, you guys.
Remember, never have more
drinks than you have tits.
Two tits, two drinks.
I know how many tits
i have.
Please, go away.
Did you just give me
danger eyes?
I don't even know what
"danger eyes" is.
I gave you
get-the-fuck-outta here eyes.
Go away.
It was like this.
That's kind of a thing.
I didn't make that face.
I think you...
That's danger eyes.
Go.
Go away.
Ride or die.
Barb, you're wilin' out
right now.
Thank you, Barb. Okay.
Hey.
That was not
what it looked like.
I was just washing my vagina
in case we hooked up.
That is what
it looked like.
Oh, okay.
Yeah.
'Cause when I drink sometimes
it smells like soup.
Hey, do you know what?
Shall we?
Yeah?
Hey, what kind of soup?
Um, that is none
of your business.
Really? What? What?
Slow down. You're like...
Here we go.
What is this?
Check it out.
No.
Oh, my god!
What do you think?
I can't believe this.
I know.
They just sort of pop up.
Is this like a tree
or something?
It is a tree.
You're gonna know all these
people by the end of it.
Yes.
Hola!
Just two of those.
That's Capoeira.
Oh, shit!
Uh, I'm really sorry.
She's never done that before.
I think you might have
killed the guy.
Holy shit.
I'm sorry.
Oh, this is nice.
Right?
That's made of glass.
Yeah, it is.
And the elevator there
is made of steel.
And you are okay
finding your room?
Oh. Yeah.
No, I had a buzz earlier.
But it's gone now.
Uh...
Your tit's out.
Your tit's out, too.
No, your tit
is actually
emerged.
I thought
i felt a breeze.
Will you excuse me?
Oh, no.
Yeah, absolutely.
God, I wish
i could invite you up.
But I can't.
I have to 69 my mom.
Well, how about,
then
you set your alarm
for 9:00 a.M
and we will go
on another adventure?
Yeah! I would love it.
Oh, shit.
I got my mom.
No, bring her.
It'll be fun.
Oh, my god! James!
That's all right.
The pleasure's
gonna be mine.
So, you get off to bed
and I will see you
tomorrow.
I'll see you
tomorrow, too.
Oh!
Sorry.
Mom,
i had the best night.
I learned the capoa.
You do that.
And I danced with a lady.
I'm okay.
And we twerked.
Did you ever twerk, ma?
No.
It's easy.
You just loosen
your lower back,
and you kind of jump.
Are you getting it?
Yeah.
I was doing it
better before.
What is this haunted swan
doing here?
Scram, swan!
Mom
I met a man.
Yeah?
I met a real man.
Well, drinking with a man
in a foreign country...
You know? It's a smart,
responsible thing to do.
I know that
that is Sincere,
and I thank you.
You missed
a maleficent night.
Well, I'm sorry.
Go to sleep.
I can't get in.
It's too tight, mom.
Just, here...
Just put your feet
under there.
It's so tight.
It's tight,
but it will untighten.
What are they
trying to prove?
Just go to sleep, honey.
I know, I'm sure.
Yeah, whatever.
Wait till tomorrow.
He's gonna take us
on a day trip.
No, I'm not.
I'm gonna read my book,
is what I'm gonna do.
I've got ten pages left.
Now that I'm awake.
And hopefully you won't start
drunk-snoring till I'm done.
Do you wanna know
how this book ends?
I do. Absolutely.
Then the only way
you're gonna find out
This is my book now.
This is not your book.
Yes, it is.
This is my book.
Oh, really?
Well, you're too old
to be acting like this.
Now, give me my book!
No!
You're coming!
You wanna know
how this ends, Linda?
Yeah, I do.
You will come tomorrow.
What did you do?
I've got 'em right here
in my chi-chas.
Chi-cha?
I'll see you
and James tomorrow.
God, Emily,
this isn't fun.
Good night.
Oh!
Emily, please.
It was the swan.
Ah!
Ma!
Is he looking at me?
Is James looking?
No, he's not.
Here he comes.
Here we go.
Yes!
Here you go.
Thank you!
Thanks.
Hey, cheers!
Ooh, cheers!
Cheers.
What's in it?
He said it was
a secret family recipe
or something.
Oh, really?
It's good.
'Cause I was thinking
maybe we could take
the scenic route.
We're gonna
go past waterfalls.
I always see about
12 rainbows.
It's insane.
Or, if you want
we could just take the old,
boring, dusty highway.
I'll take the old,
dusty highway.
What? Do you
hear yourself?
Why are you
a life-ruiner?
Do you know what?
She is kind of right
'cause I think we'd save
probably a whole
five minutes.
So...
Okay.
Waterfalls and rainbows.
Where the hell are we?
Oh, we're just coming up
on a really beautiful view.
Do you guys have any service?
I have, like, no bars.
It's not letting me
post anything.
All right. That's it.
Let's just get us
on the main road, please.
Are you sure?
I mean,
this really is the way
to experience the culture,
you know.
No, thank you.
Mom, it's fine.
I'm sure.
No, it's absolutely not!
Just get us out, you know,
back, okay? And now!
I want you to
do it right now.
That's okay. Listen,
I'm really sorry, guys.
Listen, I'm just gonna have
to turn around up here
and then we'll get back
to the road.
What was the name
of that dance
that we were doing
the other night?
Mom, you should have seen it.
Oh, my god!
Capoeira!
Are you okay?
Oh, my god!
Where are we?
Why would they take us?
Oh, my god!
Oh, fuck! Ew. Ew.
Mom, why aren't
you talking?
Because I'm trying
to remain calm.
And when I think about
where we are
and what's happening,
i start to panic.
And I don't
want to panic.
So I have chosen
to believe
that I am reading
a very compelling article
on local farming practices.
What the fuck is that?
Is that porn?
Because
when I think
about all this...
I get upset!
Oh, my god.
So I'm moving on
to another article
about this woman's asshole.
Because I just don't know
what else to do.
Oh, my god!
Do you think they're
holding him here?
Oh, Emily, don't you know
that James is part
of all this, honey?
How can my daughter
be so foolish?
How could she
just not know this?
I am sorry
that this happened.
But I will get us
out of here, okay?
I'm gonna call...
Oh, my god.
They took my phone.
Oh, my god,
they took my phone!
It's fine.
That's fine.
We just gather
raw materials.
Okay, we...
And we make a shiv.
I saw this.
No.
I saw it. Yes!
No. We fight, we lose.
Holy shit!
What are you
holy-shitting about?
Oh, the blood on the wall?
Oh, well, that's there.
Hey, how about the scorpion,
over there in the corner?
What? Oh, my god!
It's a fucking scorpion!
Mom, you have to kill it.
I'm not gonna kill it.
Kill it!
I can't kill it.
Oh, my god! Oh, my god!
Where have you taken us?
I have a few questions.
We have a very
high-up family,
and you're in
a lot of trouble.
What the fuck is this?
That is heat-activated
birth control, sir,
so please
keep that refrigerated.
This was a day.
This was a day trip.
I know, but I like to be
prepared. It's important.
What's your pin number?
One
two
three
four.
Oh, god.
I was gonna change it.
Do you have husband?
I am divorced.
I also don't have
a husband yet.
What about Jeffrey?
My son, Jeffrey.
Oh, my god.
Our lives depend
on Jeffrey.
Shit.
What you're doing is shit.
It sucks.
Okay,
just think about
how to be better.
You got Jeffrey.
Hello, Jeffrey.
We have your mother
and your sister.
And you will now
pay ransom.
Pardon?
$100,000.
Wired by noon tomorrow.
Okay, I don't know
who this is,
but if you keep
pranking me,
I will report it
to the police.
It will become
a police matter,
and you will go to jail.
Okay?
I'm with Jacob right now.
It's his piano lesson.
So fuck off.
Unfortunately,
for Linda and Emily
it is very real.
Await further instructions.
Mama? Hello! Hello!
Oh, my god.
Not too bad.
However, I have to move you,
and that is annoying to me.
Fortunately,
you have not
made me angry.
Should you ever
make me angry
I will skin you alive
while your mother watches.
What does that mean?
Oh, god.
Oh, my god. No! No!
Fight, mom. Fight!
Fight, mom!
Go limp. Go limp!
No!
Go limp.
I have a real phobia
about this.
Of what?
Being locked in
a car trunk?
Yeah, I think everybody's
got that one, mom.
Oh, my god!
I feel like I can get this.
It's loosening.
Hold on.
Wait, I think I got it.
Oh! Okay.
Do me! Do me!
No. I don't care.
Okay.
Okay. It's off.
Oh, my god.
We're stopped.
Okay, he's out.
What do we do?
These people were trapped
in a trunk,
Wait, wires?
I feel some wires.
Just grab it?
Yeah.
Should I pull it?
Yes.
Oh!
Oh, we're out! Okay.
Okay.
Okay, this way, come on.
Mom, what are you doing?
My knees.
Keep up!
Oh, shit!
I told you not to wear
your flip-flops!
It wasn't
flip-flop related, mother.
Oh, my god!
Oh, shit!
Go, mom!
Go!
Ola!
Oh, my god!
Mom! Come on!
I'm trying!
Come on!
I'm coming.
Watch out, mom!
He's right behind you!
Emily!
Come on!
Oh, my god.
He's got my leg!
This is the end of the line,
whatever that means.
Come on, honey.
Ma, do you think there's
any way that, like,
maybe that guy's okay?
I saw his brains.
Why can't you just
make me feel better?
Oh, my god.
Thank you so much.
You are such a sweetie.
What? Hector morgado?
This is...
Honey, he's nervous.
Wait,
where are you going?
Where are you going?
Should we get
back in here?
What are we
supposed to do?
Okay, we gotta get
out of here. Let's go.
What we need to focus
on is that we got out.
I don't know
why I let you talk me
into this
in the first place.
I should have stayed
at the hotel.
I can't fight with you
right now. I'm starving.
Do you hear
my stomach?
It's, like, crazy.
I'm so hungry.
- Oh, my god.
- A phone!
A Turkey leg!
Mmm-hmm,
hold on one second.
State department,
this is Morgan.
Please listen
very carefully to me, sir.
My mother and i
have been kidnapped.
Mmm, okay,
where are you guys now?
Puerto Matias.
That's in Southern Colombia.
Let me pull that up.
Will you hold on
for one second?
They took us to Colombia.
It's fine, it's fine.
It's just a different...
Zip code.
It's so far.
Okay, go ahead and get out
a pencil and paper for me.
And write down "calle..."
Is this a tall building
that we need to get to
so you can pick us up
on the top of it?
That's the address
of the nearest
us consulate in Bogota.
Okay, but you have
to actually come get us
because we are Americans
in peril. So...
but any time you
travel internationally,
Most of Colombia
is beautiful and
very safe now.
With the exception
of puerto Matias,
which is very much not.
So trust no one.
And thanks for calling
the us state department.
You talked to him.
What'd he say?
I think we're gonna need
to make another phone call.
We're gonna get you
out of this.
I don't know if you remember
me telling you this
but Barb was
in the special ops.
So she's highly trained
for this type of situation.
Let me tell you a story
about Barb.
We're on a limited time card.
We really need...
1991, Kuwait.
Hot as fuck...
Hello?
Oh, my god.
This place seems okay.
Hi.
Hi. When does
the next bus leave?
Bus doesn't leave
for about 36 hours.
Oh, my god.
But I know a man
who can take care of you.
Oh, yeah,
I'm sure he could.
Mmm-hmm.
This is how sex slavery
starts, honey.
Listen, no.
You don't have to
worry about that.
Those kinds of people want
young, beautiful females.
You're safe.
Oh, well, yeah.
That's good.
Okay, how dare you!
Like, that is so rude.
That's crazy.
Well, honey.
No. Like, how dare you.
That's my mother.
Okay, fine.
But if you think
it would be safer
for me to kind of,
like
go hide and then
she meets your friend
who knows
how to get us to the...
No, I don't want you
to do that.
No, you're both safe.
How do you mean?
Your poofy face
will protect you.
But, over there,
that man is who I mean.
Can I help you, ma'ams?
He's American.
America!
Oh, my god.
We're Americans. Hi.
I'm Emily and this is Linda.
Hi, I'm Linda.
You don't even understand
the ordeal
that we have just
been through.
We really need to
get to the us consulate in
Bogota?
Right.
As soon as possible,
kind of.
So, if you know
the easiest way.
The easy way?
They were laughing
at something else.
You're not going to find
that in Colombia.
Ah, you've got
mountain ranges
to the north.
Mom, come on.
Jungles to
the east and west.
And, well, the mighty one,
the river,
she's to the south.
There is no easy trek.
There's a reason
they call Colombia
"the sack of the Jaguar."
I never heard of that before.
I'll tell you what.
I've got a slow boat,
headed down river.
I can take you east
along the Amazon
We should be able to
drop you off close enough
that you can
make it to Bogota without
too much trouble.
Name's Roger Simmons.
The boat's docked
just out back.
Crew's getting her seaworthy
as we speak. So...
I'll check in with them
then come back for you.
Thank you.
Senor!
Chicken wings
for the ladies.
You're safe with me.
Thank you.
Yeah!
Slow boat!
Slow boat.
You wanna
get the chicken wings?
That'd be great.
Ma, stop.
Don't, like, caress me.
You look just like you did
when you were three.
Okay. You need to start
dating again.
What?
Yeah, you do.
Oh, please.
Don't start with
this again.
Why?
I've been there,
done that.
All right,
I'm gonna pee.
Don't let them
take the wings away.
Okay, honey.
Oh, my god. Help!
Mom! Oh, my god! Ow!
Oh, my god.
That's him.
That's the guy.
Oh, god.
Hi, sir.
Remember us?
Shut the fuck up.
Why did you come
to south America?
I didn't want to come.
I never wanted to come.
For the cultural
experience
and the red cross.
You come down here
you stay
at your fancy resort
clutching your pearls.
Look at my people
like you are at the zoo.
What the fuck?
You offer nothing
here to them.
And you take everything.
And then
you kill my only nephew.
Oh!
Oh, my god.
Oh, no. No.
- We had no idea.
- We didn't know.
- We're new in town.
- We're very new.
He was cute.
You should have seen him
in those last moments.
I'm sorry.
But listen,
you kidnapped us.
And that's what
motivated that.
So, like
that is on you.
Okay. What?
Wait a minute.
She's really
such a good kid.
She is garbage.
No.
Yeah. Yes.
Yes, I am.
Yes, you are.
I am garbage.
I have never voted.
I don't know any Spanish.
I only know one word.
What they called me at my job
at the restaurant. Puta!
Which I don't know
what it means.
"Princess" or
"pretty" or...
It means "whore."
That checks out.
You took someone
from my family.
I must take someone
from yours.
That is the way it is.
I didn't make the rules.
Not this one.
Mom.
Okay. Okay.
Hold on. Look!
A spear gun.
and I want you
to threaten him with it.
Okay, I'm gonna
distract them.
Where are you going?
I'm gonna distract them!
You're distracting them?
My son!
My son! My only son!
What?
Kill them!
I told you
to threaten him.
Someone order a boat
with a side of adventure?
Shut the fuck up, Roger!
My son! My only son!
- Go!
- Let's go!
Manuel! Quickly, the boat!
Come on, mom!
This is Morgan Russell.
Yes! Morgan Russell!
I'm the one
that's been calling
and their situation
down in south America.
Let's go get 'em.
What's the plan?
Right, so, I told her
to contact me
There's not much more
i can do,
unfortunately, sir.
Okay, I imagine that
you have some kind of
Maybe, like,
four underground
criminals
who were tried for a crime
they didn't commit.
And they've been living
in the underground
kinda helping people
along the way, almost
sir, were you born
in the '70s?
That sounds like the a-team.
It is the a-team.
Do you have an a-team?
We actually disbanded that
program in 1994, sir.
Fuck! Shit!
Pull out a pen
and a piece of paper.
And write down, "if you feel
the urge to call again
"resist it."
Wait. That's the advice?
That's what
you're giving me?
Yep.
I don't remember
the last time
i had a drink.
Mom, you need to relax.
All right?
You're stressing me out.
The most terrifying man
i ever saw in my life
was going to cut us up
in little pieces
with his machete.
And that was before
you murdered his son.
Accidentally murdered.
But, mom.
What?
Can we focus on the positive?
Because we are safe now.
We're safe?
You think we're safe?
Yeah, we're safe.
We're on a boat.
Look how fast
they found us!
I mean, I'm going to be
looking over my shoulder
for the rest of my life.
And then
when I go to sleep
at night,
of that spear going
into that man's throat.
Ugh!
Why would you
bring that up, mom?
Can't you just
comfort me?
Can you just please
be my parent
and make me feel better?
Do you want me
to make you feel better?
Yes.
You are
a very gifted murderer.
Okay.
just because you
can't control
this exact situation
does not mean
you have to
lash out at me.
I can't stop my hands
from shaking, honey.
Maybe you need to chill out
with the drinking,
just a little bit, mom.
Look, Roger is gonna
get us home.
Let's focus on that.
Roger's going to
get us home
just like James
was taking you out
on a date.
Get it?
Judgment.
Linda, Emily.
Luis, here, just got word
that there's a boat
50 klicks back
looking for two
American women.
Oh, god.
Oh, my god.
Now, see? What'd I tell you?
Okay, okay.
We have no choice but
to slip off now onto a canoe.
I'll guide you through
the sack of the Jaguar.
Oh uh...
You know, it's funny.
I've been looking
for adventure
ever since I got to this
godforsaken land.
And now, well, now
it looks like
adventure's found me.
Yeah.
Yeah, it has.
Oh, I'm weak, honey.
You should eat something.
Hey, Roger.
Is this fruit okay?
Sure.
Okay.
Oh, wait, do you mean, like,
is it poisonous?
I don't know. Probably.
Oh, my god!
There's always a risk if you
want to feast on the sack.
At some point, you're gonna
have to pick your poison.
Starvation
or poison.
Mmm.
Vatmonos.
Oh!
Ow!
how soggy the wood was
when I tried to light it?
So weird.
Linda, thanks
for stepping up.
You really did a great job.
Yeah. It's awesome, mom.
Thanks, honey.
Roger, why don't you
tell us a story?
You've been an expedition
guide for forever, right?
Expedition guide?
Oh, that's flattering.
I haven't heard
that one before.
Yeah, my story.
Uh, I've been here
three long weeks now.
First time on a plane.
'Til recently, I was a gm
at a trader Joe's
up in Rochester.
Although,
one could say that
the way that store
was managed,
that was the real jungle.
And then, well,
my doctor said I was sick.
So, I said to myself,
"Roger! What the heck?"
"Go on down
to south America."
Oh, god. Are you ill?
Hmm? Yes, ma'am.
Caught the travel bug.
Oh, the travel bug.
I thought
he was saying...
And cancer.
Doc gave me, oh,
a month to live,
which gives me about
a week now, so, yeah.
I mean, because you're
not just gonna
walk on in
to the Amazon
if you're expecting
to walk on out.
And so, yeah.
No.
Sure.
We got a big day
tomorrow, huh?
So I think we need to catch
a little shut-eye.
Someone needs
to stand watch.
Why don't you guys
take the first shift?
Wake me up in ten hours.
Oh, boy!
I don't know if
I'll ever even be able
to get to sleep.
God. Ugh!
Why are we still
following him?
He's a cashier.
He's a manager, mom.
Just stay positive.
Feel free to drink
from any puddle you see.
All water in the jungle
is safe.
You have no information.
Wait.
And just over this Ridge
that's the quickest way
to Bogota.
We're going to swing over
to the other side.
One at a time.
I'll go first
'cause I'm the man.
Ha-ha!
Oh!
Fuck! Shit!
Okay, okay.
Oh, my god!
This is bullshit!
Okay.
Oh, my god!
Maybe he's okay.
Okay, okay, okay.
Okay.
Okay? Okay?
Okay. Okay.
Okay.
Russell.
Hello, Morgan.
Sir, you've called
12 times today.
I've been in touch with
the us consulate in Bogota.
They put out an alert
with the Colombian military
and police.
All we can do is wait
until we hear from them.
And I wonder what
joanne would think
about this.
Wait, did you say "joanne"
like, my wife, joanne?
Is this some kind
of a threat?
No,
i didn't say joanne.
I said "yo, Anne."
No, you said "joanne"
like you've been on
my Facebook page
or something.
You called an officer
of the us government
and threatened his wife
over the phone.
so I want you to get
real quiet, okay?
If you call this number
one more
motherfucking time
I'm gonna show up
at your house,
handcuff you
to the bumper of your car
and drag you
to federal prison,
where you will
be skull raped
to within an inch
of your life,
every single
fucking night!
I don't think
you're gonna enjoy that.
Oh, yeah?
I'll come to your house,
and I'll fuck your dick.
You know what? Hold up.
Yo, yo, yo!
"Yo, yo, yo"?
That's racist, Jeffrey.
That's fucked up.
"Yo, yo, yo"?
Yo, this is
this is Derrick.
What's your last name,
Derrick?
Black.
Now let me
tell you something.
That threat you made
is all fucked up.
I'm gonna come to your house.
I got your address right here.
Okay,
where do we go now?
Roger said
it's just across the Ridge.
Roger is dead.
I realize that.
Yeah, and he didn't know
anything.
Just use the map, mom.
Oh, my god.
This is a placemat
from a restaurant.
Everything will be fine.
Everything is not fine,
Emily Louise.
Look where we are.
In the middle
of the Amazon!
Oh, my god!
That's how desperate I am
to spend time with you.
I see you
all the time.
You see me
when you
need something.
That's not true.
When I just say anything
just remotely critical...
Wait!
"Remotely critical"?
Mom, you flat-out
insult me.
All the time.
What?
It's not a good way
to raise kids.
What do you know
about raising kids?
about anything?
Except posting
pictures of yourself?
Okay, well, I only post
so many pictures of myself
because I want
people to witness me
having an interesting,
full life
and give me compliments
in the comments.
You can do that without
posting pictures. I do.
You have a full,
interesting life?
You just check the locks
all day.
And change
the kitty litter.
You hide in your home
with your adult son.
Are you saying that
I've wasted my life?
I didn't say that.
You know what?
You're wrong!
Because I had you.
And I had your brother.
So don't you dare say
i wasted my life.
I gave you
everything I had.
Everything!
And I did it alone!
What the hell have you
ever done for anybody?
For 18 years
your mother is the most
important person
to you in your
entire life.
And then...
One day, poof!
You're gone.
And then what are you
supposed to do?
Like, just adjust?
Just like that?
It's not possible, Emily.
You were mine.
And now, you're not.
And I...
I miss you.
Mom, I'm right here.
I'm the one who
invited you on this trip.
I'm on this trip, Emily,
because you didn't want
to drink mai tais alone.
No! You are
the mergle fur!
What the hell
is mergle fur?
Oh, Emily!
Oh!
Thank god!
Honey, we're so lucky
because I had to drag you
all the way through
the jungle, looking for help.
And I ran into Dr. Armando
and his friend.
who I've been teaching
a little English.
No big deal.
Go ahead.
Hello.
Ah!
Good.
That's great.
He's been assisting me
as I search local plants
for a compound
that could potentially...
Are you ready?
Cure cancer.
That is amazing!
I think so.
Yes, thank you.
All right.
Well, thank you, guys.
- Thanks, macho.
- You ready?
Yeah, we're gonna
head out of here.
Oh, you can't go
just yet.
Um, you have
a parasite in you.
What?
What's that?
Here's the thing.
Your mother told us
that you've been, like,
extremely hungry lately.
And thankfully,
when you passed out
you shat yourself.
Thank god.
Never seen so much shit.
Like a human, almost.
Yeah.
Okay, we understand.
It was a lot of shit.
Lots of shit. Yes.
But through that, we could
take a stool sample
and determine that
you have a tapeworm.
A tapeworm?
Tapeworm.
What?
Can I look at that?
Yes, please.
A second opinion is...
Yes.
Please, please, please.
Go ahead.
So what's the treatment?
Like a z-pack?
If it's already affecting
your appetite,
I think it's probably...
It's pretty significant.
Listen.
We're out of praziquantel
to substract it
from you manually.
What? Manually? What?
With my manuals.
That's fuckin' gross.
Good news! Right now,
the tapeworm
is really hungry, right?
So what we're gonna do
is we're gonna lodge open
your throat
and dangle a piece of meat
in front of your throat.
Try to coax it out.
It'll feel safe,
but it's not safe
because I'm gonna pull it.
No!
Slowly!
Slowly! Slowly!
Then, slap it down.
Slap it down. Kill it.
It's a two-man job, ma'am.
It's a two-man job, I'm sorry.
I've got a worm, mom.
I know.
Mom!
I'm here.
Get the worm out, mom.
I'm your pillar.
Hello.
Oh, hello.
When will we know
when it's working?
When we look into
the worm's eyes, Linda.
Come outside and face me.
Yes. Show me your face.
Oh, here it comes. Okay.
Okay.
Oh. What?
Oh, it's coming.
It's making its way.
Okay, relax, I got this. Move.
Knock me out!
What are you doing?
Okay! Okay!
Help me. Help me!
It's not like at home.
I bet.
Oh, there she comes.
Oh, look!
Hi.
Baby.
Do you feel better?
I feel great.
- Oh, good.
- Yeah.
You did good.
Hi, maco. Thank you.
Emily, this is
a traditional gift
that the village
made for you.
It's for protection
while you're here.
For me?
Yes, for you.
Oh, my god.
That's so nice.
It's heavy. It's thick.
It's, like, hurting.
Thank you.
It's tight.
Something kanye
would design.
That's great.
Do they just kind of
do that all day?
Oh, yes.
When we got here,
we provided a lift.
They used to have to walk
miles up the hill.
But, much easier now.
That's very
thoughtful of you.
They just kind of straight
chill, or...
Culturally,
the women do the work
and the men, they provide
the protection, you know?
Yeah.
That's fucked up.
Not for the men. Yeah.
That's so cool.
This is what
you guys are up to.
Oh, I'm like in this now.
Okay.
Ooh!
Emily! The doctor said
he could get us to Bogota.
That is amazing.
Oh, my god!
Okay. Do I have
a couple minutes?
'Cause I'm
kinda helping...
Helping out the ladies.
Thank you.
Come here,
you know i
got you, girl.
Look at you helping.
Yeah, I am helpful.
Honey, you know, when
i said that, I didn't mean...
That I'm selfish
or that I'm worthless?
Which part of our fight?
Emily, come on.
I didn't mean that.
It's fine.
I know how you see me.
Yeah? Okay.
Oh, god.
Shit, shit, shit, shit.
Shit, shit, shit!
There's some very bad men
looking for you.
They've blocked the main
entrance. It's really bad.
No, nobody's being fucked,
okay? I got an idea.
I got an idea.
Go, I'll stall them.
Go, go, go.
Yeah?
Honey, get in here!
This won't hold both of us.
I'm too heavy.
No, you're perfect.
You're just perfect.
Okay, hold on tight.
And, remember,
when you get down there,
get to the embassy.
No, mom!
I want to stay with you!
Mom!
Everything's gonna be okay.
I love you!
Oh.
Hello.
Emily.
Hi.
We were able to get
your items sent over
from the hotel.
Any updates on my mom?
Oh, I'm sorry.
There's nothing yet.
But we are
gonna get you
an escort
to the airfield base...
And then someone will
get you home from there.
I'm not doing that.
I'm not going anywhere
without my mother.
Can I be candid with you?
Yeah. What?
It's my third day.
And I guess everybody
takes off on Fridays,
but they didn't tell me
because it's my third day.
So if you could just
take your box and go.
I don't know
what you're talking about.
I just need to
find my mother.
That's why I'm here.
The only reason my mother
even came on this trip
is because I made her.
Because I am selfish.
And I need help
finding her right now,
and I need you to be the guy
that helps me.
Come on, man.
Be that guy.
Who's the guy?
Not me!
It isn't.
It's never been.
I'd love to be the guy who
sweeps you off your feet
and is your hero
and can save your mother
and take care of you
and maybe we hook up.
I don't know.
Wait, what?
But I'm just saying
that I am not that dude.
So I need you
to be that girl
who just takes your box
and walks outta this office
before you draw
any more attention
to the fact that
i don't know
what I'm doing.
Can I just use your phone?
Can you be the guy
that lets me use his phone?
Yes. See? That I can do.
Come on.
I haven't been trained
on the phone system.
Oh, my god!
Hello, Morgan.
Choose your next move
carefully, brother.
Wait! No, no, no!
Don't touch me.
Security!
Purell! Put on purell!
Fucking shit!
Let me have
my day in court.
All right,
wait, wait, wait!
Morgan, I'm a middle-aged man
who never leaves the house.
All I have in this world
is my mama and my sister.
And if something
happens to them
then all I'll have
is you.
And I'm telling you
right now
I'm fucking annoying.
I've read all
the game of thrones books.
I'll text you spoilers.
I don't
want to go to an orphanage.
I can't be an orphan.
I need my mama!
Help me find my mama!
Thank you so much
for answering.
I didn't know
who else to call.
The guy I dealt with
at the embassy was insane.
Emily, we're gonna
get you through this.
But Barb wants me
to let you know one thing.
She refuses to use
sexual humiliation
as an interrogation
technique.
What are you
talking about?
I don't care what she does.
Just can you help me?
Meet us at
the presidente apartments
We're trying to use
her cell signal
Colombian military is
setting up
a couple stingrays
We can have a unit ready
to go in by tomorrow.
Well,
we got a big problem
'cause that unit
needed to be
there yesterday.
I told you
to shut the fuck up!
Okay.
We've got reports
coming in that puts them
about 50 miles
outside of Bogota.
Yeah, that's
morgado territory all right.
Who's morgado?
Let's just say he's none
of your goddamn business.
- Let me come with you.
- No!
Please!
Absolutely not!
I'll translate.
You speak Spanish?
I speak dothraki.
I speak klingon.
You speak klingon?
I'm coming with.
You're not going anywhere.
I think I see them
right there.
Is that them?
Little specks there?
You know,
why don't you
wait outside.
Go, go in the hallway.
Fuck!
Nerd. He's a nerd.
We have someone here I think
you're gonna want to see.
James?
Thank fuck. Emily. Listen,
you've gotta help me, please.
We found him
sitting at the bar,
chatting up another
pretty young girl.
It's a scam, Emily.
Yeah, so Barb waited
for him outside
smacked him in
the back of the head,
threw him in the car
and here we are.
It's not a scam.
These women are crazy.
This whole fucking thing
is insane.
Crazy?
Oh, you wanna
know crazy?
You remember
my platonic friend, Barb?
Oh, Barb!
We were supposed to go
to the Arizona gem show
but instead, I'm here,
fucking with you.
You should know that Barb
spent her life in special ops.
Not that bullshit
regular ops.
She's retired now
so she doesn't
have her toolkit.
But she was
able to improvise
a few things.
Which, I'm pretty sure,
will all be applied
to your dick hole area.
Esmeraldas!
She's in esmeraldas.
It's, like,
an hour's drive from here.
We got a real
chatty Cathy here.
Give me a map. I can mark it
on the map for you.
Write it down.
You want to start here...
Barb is really upset
about this. She had plans.
Now this doesn't always
show up on waze
but you be sure
to take that one
because it's
the quickest route
if you want to
avoid traffic.
Okay.
Okay, let's go.
Listen, Emily.
Be sure you check
all the rooms.
She'll probably be held
on the third floor.
Do you have any loyalty
to the people who hired you?
Hey, Emily,
can I just say,
as well, you...
Fuck, you look great.
Thank you.
I got a tapeworm.
Well, it's working
for you.
Hey, listen!
Are we, uh...
Am I ever going to
see you again?
Well, I don't know.
I guess if you're, like,
in New York,
we could get a drink.
In your wet dreams,
motherfucker.
Be super quiet.
You have
arrived at your destination.
Fix it!
Let's go get your mom.
Just walk.
Huh?
Ow!
We're all
gonna jump down there,
sneak past those guys
and get your mom.
Okay.
Fuck, fuck, fuck
oh, honey!
I made a shiv.
You're alive.
Oh, my god, mom.
I'm so sorry
i got you into all of this.
I should have just
listened to you.
I should have
You're always there.
If I'm sad or lonely.
And it's 3:00
in the morning,
i call
and you answer.
You always answer.
I know, I know.
You're that person
for me, mom.
Okay, honey.
I'm so sorry.
I love you.
Honey, this is
a really long hug.
Can we have just
one more second?
I really thought
you were dead.
but we really got
to get the fuck
out of here.
Okay, okay.
Okay.
The car's over here.
- Oh, my god.
- Are you okay?
No.
Oh, my god!
Do you have some cyanide
we could take, or something?
Oh, my god!
Hurry up! Hurry up!
It doesn't hurt too much,
but roll it down.
No.
Roll it down, pendeja.
No!
Push the fucking button.
I can't, pendeja.
It's broken.
It's broken?
Yeah, sorry. Goodbye.
Hi!
No! No! No!
No! No!
No!
Now, I'm gonna kill you.
Don't touch my daughter!
Don't move!
Now what?
Do you wanna dance?
Yes!
Nice kick, malparida.
Nice kick.
Now
let me show you my dance.
Oh, my god.
Ugh! Okay.
I beg you.
Don't shoot me.
You fucked with
the wrong bitches.
Yeah, you did.
Kill him, mom.
No. I can't.
This is a mom thing.
No, this isn't a mom thing.
You got this.
- It's not what I do well.
- I don't do it well.
You did it before.
Those were accidental.
I can't hold it anymore.
Okay, here I go.
Go!
I'm gonna count down,
I'm gonna do it.
Please. Please.
100...
99...
Oh, fuck!
Oh, thank god!
Come on. Kill me.
Now I'm getting
the confidence.
Give me that thing.
Oh, okay.
No, I can't do that.
I just got excited.
Don't move!
I will kill you.
Very rude!
Here we go.
Moving in hot.
This is what we trained for.
You, on the roof.
You, also on the roof.
Everyone on the roof.
I know you're scared...
Again,
shut the fuck up, man!
Okay?
Okay.
Jeffrey.
What?
Jeffrey!
Mama...
Mama! Mama!
Mama!
I missed you.
Oh, my god!
I'm so happy to see you.
I left the house.
You left the house.
I made all these
men come...
What?
Oh!
Here! I made them come here
to get you.
I missed you!
I missed you, too!
Hey. Agent Russell.
Let me take
that from you.
Good job with morgado.
We've been looking for him
for a while.
Oh, my god.
He's so mean.
Anyway, your brother
really cares about you.
Mama!
He's a real bummer.
Oh, yeah. The worst.
Yep. Awful.
Full agreement.
Morgan. Morgan!
What?
Thank you.
You're the best!
Thank you for your help.
I wanna go home
so fucking bad.
I'm so hungry.
Let's get the fuck
out of here!
Can I have just whatever
everyone is drinking?
Just, like,
your signature thing.
Yeah.
Hi.
Hey.
What brings you
down here?
Oh, uh...
I'm actually
volunteering.
That's awesome.
Yeah, it's really fun.
Can I get you a drink?
Uh...
I'm kind of here
with somebody.
Oh.
Honey!
Hi, mom!
Oh, god,
this is so fun!
Okay, so anyway, I met this
fascinating woman over there.
And she's gonna take us
to her home
and she's gonna teach us
how to make murtabak.
What is that?
It's a stuffed pancake.
I'm gonna go make a request
because I want to dance.
Oh, I love you.
I love you.
You're here
with your mother.
Yeah.
Why?
Um...
She's fucking awesome.
That's really sweet.
Her tit is out.
Wait, what?
Oh, mom!
Mama!
Captioned by deluxe
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today