Aah! The armenians
Know about the money train!
Diro green-Lit your family.
- If we just work together On this thing
- We don't work together On shit anymore.
You had me arrested. You make the case go away. As
long as I'm locked up In here, everything's at risk.
Shane is neck-Deep In armenian
shit. We got to keep him close.
Corrine: vic's had this ex-Cop Watching us all
day long, And I don't know what's going on Between
I do. He didn't know about
The bogus armenian threat.
Shane was acting out On some bullshit
tip From some banger in county.
I guess one of us Is being lied to.
This is cruz pezuela. This
city Needs cops like you.
I have larger interests
I'd like to protect.
Found out the name Of one of your former employees Who was stealing secrets
- Luis aramboles.
Pezuela doesn't know You lost
their blackmail files. No.
What about the files? He sold them to rezian. The
armenians are making a hard Play for your barrio sandbox.
Looks like I'm gonna need you To
get my family Clear of this thing.
Make rezian Believe the mexicans
Are the armenians' Worst problem.
Vendrell: This is I.A., baby. It's latino land,
And I know every mexican gang From here to sinaloa,
Which means that nothing happens To vic's family Or
you lose the only guy who can Stop your mexican threat.
I got the mexicans thinking That the armenians
are making A power play for the barrio.
So, what now? We can just
sit back, Watch the gang war.
Subtitles downloaded from www.OpenSubtitles.org
Bring back memories?
On a clear night, you can See guardo's house from
here. Don't worry. I haven't seen his ghost around.
Come on. Who's the amigo? Luis
aramboles. Intel operative For the mexis.
He came up here To start some shit.
I told your boss you sold his Box of sins to the
armenians, Which means you're breathing On borrowed time.
He won't believe that. They're
already out Looking for you.
Price on your head
- I could retire. It's time to disappear...
Unless you want me
To just turn you over.
Who's he? Someone who wants to help
you With your travel arrangements.
He would never want to see An...
innocent man get killed. Hey. Hey!
You want to give me a clue
What all this is about?
He's the key to defusing The armenian
time bomb You laid At my family's doorstep.
He's the keeper of the intel The mexis are
using To blackmail Their way to the top.
Orwas, Till I helped myself.
And you made it look like this
Prick sold out to the armos.
Which lit the fuse for The blood feud we're
stirring up Between rezian And the mexicans.
Nicely done.
Aramboles is the only one Who
can put my face to the grab.
So he's got to go away.
I need you to hook him up With the coyotes we
were using To get lem set up Down in mexico.
Who's he working for? I want
him gone By tomorrow night.
Getting him out of the
country's Not a problem.
Setting him up on a goat farm With money and contacts,
It would be nice to know who And what I'm dealing with.
Working with you to protect My family
- I'm down with that.
Trusting you? Not there yet.
No, that's a mistake. You
should have Come to me first.
This piece of shit Rezian He's
taken something That belongs tome.
So drop a couple of low-Level
Armenian bodies on the street.
Scare them into getting Your blackmail box back,
But trying to whack rezian now Goes too far too fast.
It's already in motion. Be prepared
To help me control the blowback.
When's this going down? Today. We have
some people In county jail where he's at.
Look, when all hell breaks loose
Out on the street Because of this...
It's gonna Hurt your business.
And it's gonna hurt my
ability To protect you.
I'm confident you'll be able
To handle the job adequately.
Any other questions?
Not at the moment.
Hey, tina, Have you seen shane?
No, haven't had The pleasure today.
What the hell is this?
The mayor just released a list Of the top-10 most
wanted gangs To a press conference This morning.
Hey, are we making celebrities
Of these douche bags now?
It's the latest initiative
In the city's war on gangs.
It's just gonna get sets
Competing to move up the ladder.
Gang crime's up 14% Citywide this year.
While farmington's numbers Are down.
I guess I can't be everywhere.
I weighed in against this With phillips.
I was told that the mayor Wants to be proactive In
identifying gang problems To reassure the public.
Well, it made the
front page, So hang on.
Well, fortunately, most of
these Bangers can't read.
Still, I got the over/under On one of these crews Doing
the first whack To move up the list In three hours.
I'll take the under. Rumor has it that
you're Scheduled for a new hearing.
Four weeks from today.
Well, if you would like to spend That time with
your lawyer, Your pba rep organizing Your case...
As long as I got this, I'm
gonna use it. Nice try, though.
Vendrell: arrangements Have been
made. Have aramboles Ready at 10:00.
This war we started is already
Spinning out of control.
Mexicans have overreacted.
Rezian's been green-Lit.
They're gonna make a
move Against him tonight.
Protecting rezian Is the only thing
That's keeping Your family alive.
I'm not the one behind this. We need
to get rezian In protective custody.
It's too late for that. He'll be
dead Before the request is processed.
Jesus.
Okay.
Okay, maybe... Maybe my
armenian problem Goes away.
With rezian dead, Maybe he's the only armo
Who knows enough about me To hold a grudge.
Or maybe armenian number 2 Knows what rezian
knows And blames us For getting the boss whacked.
You have to warn him.
Yeah, so he can get himself In the
right frame of mind To take a shiv?
No, I'll figure out How to head that off. Meanwhile,
you get cred By giving him a heads-Up, And he'll owe you.
How you holding up?
Oatmeal and bologna. I
haven't had a woman In weeks.
Well, oatmeal's good For the
colon. You think this is funny?
The d. A.'S Squeezing the accountant
Who did my books at the port.
He agreed to turn evidence. He's
being deposed This afternoon.
I'll see what I can do.
Meantime, you got A much bigger problem.
I got word That you're hard candy.
You've been green-Lit By the mexicans.
The mexicans? Why?
Look, you just need To watch yourself Until
I can get you Moved into protective custody.
I am going to protect you.
You better.
You know why?
Anything happens to me, I've already given
the order to Go after your friend's family.
And yours, too.
If I wanted you dead,
I wouldn't warn you.
Then let's just call it Incentive.
I guess some of these bangers Canread.
Asher: this is john layton, Pasadena
address, No priors, no witnesses,
At least none Of the sharing kind.
What's mr. Layton from pasadena With no priors
doing Walking around This stretch of misery?
Gardocki: gang turf, Upscale victim
- Drugs?
This is not Where
whitey scores his powder.
Century boulevard caters more To the pale
- Face group.
He's got over $100
in cash In his wallet.
It's no robbery. Maybe trying to pick up
a trick? The stroll's Six blocks that way.
These tags - Los mags, one
niners - This is gang central.
We all know what this is.
Only difference is, you're the
One who has to call the mayor And tell
him that his list Got a white guy popped.
We don't know It's top-10 related.
Drive-By?
Vic: look, this list is like the
Standings in the sports section,
And every gang Is making a playoff push.
Find the shooter.
Okay, vic and I Will take the one niners
- No, no, no, no. Shane comes with me.
I
- I'll bring him up to speed. You and julien Go press the los mags.
How'd rezian Take the bad news?
He's a big believer In life insurance.
He gets whacked, they come
after Your familyandmine.
We got to figure out how many
Rungs on the armenian ladder
Know about Our
money-Train rip-Off.
Jesus christ!
How'd we lose control Of this?
Rezian's accountant's
About to give him up.
He expects me To hose him down.
If we don't, That screws us up, too.
The accountant - Later.
Keeping rezian alive - Now.
Vic: moses.
Just crashing by To say, "what up?"
Vendrell: redecorating?
Moses: This is all your boys. Pigs
blew through here Like a damn hurricane.
Tossed My breezie's crib, too.
Shut down my weed spot Around
the way, And I ain't done no harm.
You waking up in the morning Does harm.
Dead bodies on your turf
- Not a good look, moses.
Like I told po-Po, Don't
know nothing about it.
Didn't stop them From
messing up my place.
I guess you don't know nothing About
the top-10 list In the paper, either.
I know we reppin' at number
5. I'm good with that.
Blow a hole in a white man, You
get respect, Shot at number 1.
I'm a businessman. And merking white
folk Is a no-Go for my commerce.
What about one of your baby
Bangers trying to earn cred?
One of my g's wildin'
out, I'd have heard.
There's plenty of nigs out there
Perpetrating felonious bullshit.
Why don't you swarm on
them? Stay out of my grill.
Who else would pull
a jack move Like this?
Athens, piru, spook street. Spook
street Didn't even make the list.
What I'm saying. They need to
step they game up Or they out.
You got any soldiers In county, moses?
Do I got soldiers in county? We straight
claiming county As one nine turf.
Got a deal for you. We have
an associate Locked up there.
Needs protecting.
I ain't doing jack for you Till this shooter's
gaffled up. Keep the cops out of my shit.
You do this, I'll make
sure Our guys back off.
You got till 4:00 to make The streets
smooth So I can be about my paper.
Then I'll see about your boy In county.
Deal.
Sofer: please get these
people Behind the yellow tape.
Victim's lana boyle.
Looks like a cinder
block Fell and killed her.
Wagenbach: Death from above.
This is doug obermyer.
Victim's his girlfriend.
I'm detective wagenbach. This is
detective billings. I'm really sorry.
Dude, one of those
assholes Murdered her!
You think This wasn't an accident?
Those goddamned beaners Have been hassling
us Ever since We rented this space.
Um, this is a commercial Building?
It's a rehearsal space.
Lana was our lead singer.
Yeah, rent's cheap In this neighborhood.
The tenants next door
Didn't like the music?
It was one of them,
man. They killed her.
You're gonna Arrest somebody, right?
We're gonna talk to people,
Try and determine what happened.
I was out here When it happened!
They was yelling out of the
Window, bitching at us to move!
And
- And you didn't?
If they don't like our smoke, They can go
back to mexico city And choke on the smog!
Okay, doug, doug, Don't go away. I
may need To talk to you again, okay?
I wonder if rock-Star boy Is more upset
about losing His girl or his lead singer.
Somebody did drop That cinder block
intentionally, Probably a resident.
Maybe still in the crowd.
Oh, right. I'll, uh, get a
read. Don't want to put you out.
I interviewed The boys in the band.
They were all out here When it happened,
But nobody was looking up When the
cinder block Came tumbling down.
The band was just here
Taking a smoke break.
I need you to track down
The building manager.
I want every tenant With a window
view of the street Brought down here.
Policia. We need everyone Outside now.
Policia!
Man: Qué carajo estás pensando?
Hey! Come on out! We
can hear you in there!
Great. We respond to a
murder. We get a domestic.
Luna puta! Labre la puerta ahora!
What?! Hey! A little more respect!
And didn't you Hear us knocking?!
Listen up. A girl was killed outside.
We need everyone Downstairs now.
Nothing to do with us.
Icierra la pinche puerta!
Step aside. And you shut up.
Tell your woman To put some clothes on And
get downstairs For questioning right now.
Hey! Put your hands
Where I can see them now!
He was getting a shirt To cover
her up Like you asked him to.
Total news blackout On anything
gang-Related Until further notice.
Wouldn't have anything to do With the
businessman Being shot this morning?
Whatever the reason, Something
like this happens, It's a tragedy.
And the timing Couldn't be worse.
And because the mayor doesn't
Want to fuel speculation
That his gangbanger hall
of fame Is the cause.
Who's working the case? Strike team.
Mackey in the mix?
Front and center. Good.
Oh, don't tell me you're
Drinking his kool-Aid now, too.
Am I the only one Who will rember
The trail His tornado left behind If
and when he's finally Thrown out of here?
I'm under no illusions, But a day
like this one? I can live with him.
Who's that guy?
Jamal Just replaced trinitron
As the number-One shot-Caller
For spook street, Although he claims
to be just Another downtrodden black man
In the struggle. Join the club.
You know what the street's
Saying about your set?
Calling you the clown posse, As
in laughingatyou, Not with you.
Hauling me out of bed without
Letting me take my calm pills.
Spook street's a joke.
They in my pocket. Forget
to take them Yesterday, too.
And y'all are making me On edge.
Hey, my wife
- She takes these When she's on the rag.
Maybe I should Get you a tampon, too.
You gave the order To
merk that white guy,
Let people know that Spook
street's still around.
Maybe you can get spook
street On that top-10 list.
Hell, they could put
together A top-100 list.
Your piece-Of-Shit
crew Wouldn't be on it.
How am I trying to beef with
Some white dude I never seen?
Maybe you were just
trying to Lay down the law,
Trying to get your
soldiers To come correct,
Pasadena square biz Walks
into your line of fire...
Look, If this was accidental,
Maybe one of the guys in your
Crew has an itchy finger, We can help.
All you got to do Is tell us the truth.
Man, I got kids to feed... Another
one on the way. My moms is dying.
I ain't a clown. I ain't a bitch.
Just trying to look out
For my own, make my way.
A man of peace.
With the most high As my
witness, I didn't shoot no man.
Don't know about no shooting.
Now, please, Can I have my pills?
Any gang presence In the building -
Young men, tattoos, Baggy t-Shirts?
Yeah, I know what
gang members Look like.
Nah, it's mostly families. They pay their
rents on time, And they keep to themselves.
Complaints about the noise
And the smoking next door -
Anybody Particularly more upset?
Nobody's complained to
me, And I can't think
Of anybody here Who would
do anything Like this.
Where were you When it happened?
At the hardware store To get a
pipe fixture For a broken toilet.
Um, thanks. I'm gonna need
that tenant list. Sure.
Can I, uh... Steal him for a minute?
I'll be back.
You get Any good information?
If you mean her phone
number, No, thanks to you.
Um... If this is the billings level
Of effort I can look forward
to, You may as well just go home.
No, me interviewing A witness
Is just as good As you doing the same.
I'm the only one working
At maximum capacity.
Really? What did you
Come up with so far?
Sofer: hey, dutch, I
talked to every tenant
With an apartment On
this side of the street,
And every single one of them
Says they didn't see anything.
Hanlon: Same here. Looks
like they'd rather be
Watching theirnovelas
Than help I. D. A killer.
Yeah, don't worry. Dutch is on the case.
Young woman Got her head bashed in.
You're not disturbed By the apathy?
Why don't you Take a look around you?
We've been standing In the
hot sun for how long now,
And we are Right where we started.
So if you've got Some magic beans
In your Detective bag of tricks
That'll make these people Give a shit,
Why don't you start Planting them?
You know what, steve? You're
right. We have been here a while.
Excuse me! Could I have your attention?
I'm pleased to announce That, today,
you're all Gonna have the pleasure
Of seeing your local tax dollars
At work up close and personal.
Since none of you Want to
do the right thing here,
You're all coming down To the farmington
station For continued questioning.
And until someone comes
forward Who saw what happened,
I'm gonna make all of your lives As
inconvenient And unpleasant as possible.
Have a nice day.
Better get a bus down here.
What's up? Colorado plates.
Visiting usc for graduation.
And they thought tuition Was a bitch.
Same neighborhood,
m. O., Victim profile.
Hey, claudette...
You need to be back At the office
on spin control. We got this.
You're not Used to a
short leash? I'm fine.
Woman: I saw what happened!
I was right over
there, And I saw it all.
Woman #2: you need To
stop snitchin', bitch!
Why you helping one time?!
You need to mind your mouth
And get back to your mama!
You a straight rat, You
old fool! Stop snitchin'!
I lived in that building For 40 years,
And I seen these young folks Turn
these streets Into living hell!
Woman #2: No snitchin'!
Why don't you let us Take
you back to the station,
Where you can make a statement
Someplace quiet? For safety?
I'm not scared. I'm too old for scared.
My sons are in jail. My lesbian
daughter Won't give me grandchildren.
They want to kill me?
I can't wait To see my Jesus.
Did you get a look At the shooter?
There were two, And they
were in gray do-Rags.
Spook street.
You just told me You ruled them out.
Jamal lied his ass off, And I bought it.
Can you give us a physical
Description of these men?
Age, height, tattoos?
They wasn't no men.
They were like 13 or 14...
Maybe. They were babies -
Babies on bicycles.
Vic: hey, moses!
Yo!
The shooters are spook
street. Case closed.
Now, call up your boys In county.
They need to be on the lookout For
this armenian dude. His name is rezian.
Byz lats is looking To put him down.
Only you're not Gonna let that happen.
So get off the weed And get on
the phone With your boys in county.
You have a window that faces the street.
You didn't see What happened?
I always Keep my blinds closed.
Even on a hot day Like today?
When I'm in my apartment,
I like to be naked.
Thanks. Excuse me.
Where'd you get those?
From that man.
Oh, come on.
Hey, asher, take this lying
Piece of shit jamal upstairs.
Hey, guys. What a surprise.
Busy day. What's going on?
Why do you have somebody
Watching us and following us?
You didn't get a tip From
some banger in county.
Mara told me About the whole armenian
thing You and shane Are mixed up with.
Now, what's the truth?
Hey, calm down. Let's not
do this here, okay? Come on.
Cass, don't move.
What the hell is going on?
I'm handling it.
Oh, handling it is by tying
up Mara and gagging her?
That's a gross exaggeration.
Look, shane got Both of
our families in a jam,
Which I am currently
Getting us all out of.
I need you -
Trust you, right?
We were working An undercover job.
Believe me, you don't
want To know the details.
Now, Shane used bad judgment.
That's why you have
some ex-Cop Following me?
He's just there to -
He's just there to make
sure You're all right.
Look
The truth is, Something
might be going down.
I want to move you guys To a hotel.
I don't believe this.
I'm done. I'm going to connecticut
- My cousin's.
I need you to stay in town Where
me and my guys Can look out for you.
If you think I would let
anyone Hurt you or my children,
You don't know me.
Do you work here?
Eight hours a day, Minus
half-Hour for lunch.
You need some change
For the vending machine?
I want someone arrested For a crime.
Yeah? Who's that, sweetheart?
My father.
Wyms: got a call claiming
Responsibility for the murders.
We already know It's spook street.
Caller confirms it's spook
Street working with al-Qaeda.
Al-Qaeda in the hood? This is serious.
Knock yourself out. But it's bullshit.
I've seen the fbi report.
There's internet chatter.
Terrorist groups Are trying to get
in business With local street gangs.
We're rolling On internet rumors now?
Hell, on the internet, dutch boy Is still a
13-Year-Old girl Looking For her first training bra.
Terrorists Funding their operations
By selling drugs and weapons
To gang members Who deal drugs and weapons
- How is that a stretch?
Look, we spend all day, Every day, in the
barrio. That's just not What's going on.
How does it look If we do nothing And,
God forbid, The unthinkable happens?
It's the world We're living in now.
All right. We'll work the
international Terrorist angle.
We've already notified Homeland security.
They'll be taking over From here.
When the men from u. N.C. I.E. Are
cruising alvarado Looking for osama,
I'll be sweating some good, Old-Fashioned,
trash-Talking American dipshit.
Jamal...
Lying to me Is unacceptable.
Man, I told you the truth
And nothing but the truth.
Yeah, with the most high As your witness.
I know. Only I got a witness, too,
Saw the shooters In spook street colors.
Then there's some niggas
Out there false flaggin'.
Listen, shithead! The feds
are gonna be here In a minute.
Once they get here, I can't help you.
Oh, white people get shot,
And it's a federal case now?
Oh, we're way past Black and white.
Your boys Used the al-Qaeda card,
Which means you got a rainbow Coalition of
law enforcement Shitting Multicultural bricks.
Look, I gots no love
For them sand niggas.
I claim black man south
central East side rider.
Well, you're gonna be The only cat in
guantanamo Praying in that direction.
The rest of your homies For life,
They'll have Their asses in the air,
Noses in the carpet, Facing mecca,
And there ain't no calm pills In gitmo.
I gave no order. Some "g," unaffiliated,
Outside my set, does a deed -
How's that on me?
The shooters were baby
g's. They were kids.
What? We was watching
cnn. I made a joke.
You know, You want to stir shit
up, Say you riding With al-Qaeda,
Taking flight on a white man. Bad shit
happens to him Or one of his blonde breezies,
That's all anybody talks About
- Period, point blank.
You're the boss. Someone took
your joke As an order. Who?
Some kid called my phone From the
barbershop, Talking crazy shit.
I didn't pay it no mind.
I need a name. Who?
Psh! I don't know, man. Some
little shorty Always underfoot.
Step out of the room, Detective.
What time Did you get this call?
About 2:30.
Hey. I need to look At jamal
tillman's property. Tillman.
Hey! Cut the shit!
Here you go.
Great. Thank you.
Hi. I'm detective vendrell.
I need to speak To mr. Grubman.
No visits.
I'm the arresting officer. I just need
to speak with him Before his deposition.
Sorry. I'm not supposed
to Allowanyonein that room.
Look, we have reason to believe
He may have been threatened.
He recants his previous Statements to us
under duress, An armenian mob boss Goes free.
Now, you want that On
your résumé, rookie?
Look, you're just Trying to do your job.
Why don't you Come in
with me? Hi, mr. Grubman.
U're the cop Who arrested rezian.
Vendrell: yes, I was.
They have you down here today, too?
I'm always working.
I, uh... I came to
thank you for testifying.
We're very confident in
our case against mr. Rezian.
Just trying to do the right thing.
Is there anything else that we can
get you To make you more comfortable?
No, I'm fine.
And we'd all like for
it to stay that way.
Okay.
We don't want you to have
any fears about testifying.
We're not gonna let any harm come to
you Or your daughter down in anaheim.
My daughter?
Well, when we heard
about the death threat,
We took every precaution to
guarantee katrona's safety.
You have my word.
Now, is there any part
of your testimony...
That you would like to go
over so that we're clear?
No.
I'm perfectly clear
on what I need to say.
Great.
Vic: uh...
I might be able to help I. C.E. Think
locally and act globally. You interested?
I'm a big-Picture gal.
Of course I'm interested.
Look, I got the name and address Of
an illegal alien Who's running weapons.
He's a fired Mexican intel op Who's a
possible connection To a local power player.
Now, this goes international,
Be better for you than me.
What's his name?
Aramboles?
Don't know him.
You're about to.
I'd get there now
Before someone else does.
Grubman's got a bad case Of amnesia.
What about rezian in jail?
Well, he's still
alive, As far as I know.
Can't really call him up And ask
And hour later, He takes a knife.
Yeah, well, just have to trust That
moses' guys Are gonna keep him breathing.
Sofer: Claudette needs to see you.
In a sec.
Not you. Shane.
Uh, you beckoned?
I got a call from the d. A., Said you just
visited the Witness, rezian's bookkeeper?
Yeah.
Yeah, my jailhouse chats With
rezian, He didn't seem too worried
About grubman as a witness, Which
didn't give me A good feeling.
You didn't talk to grubman
About his testimony, did you?
Just to make sure he wasn't
Being pressured in any way.
Sheriff's deputy Was
present the whole time.
I know. I just spoke with her.
Grubman's changed his story.
He's recanted everything.
Shit. Rezian got to him.
D. A. Wants to talk to you, Make
sure You didn't have a hand in it.
How does it benefit me to lose a
High-Profile collar like rezian?
I haven't Figured that out yet.
Well, tell the d. A. I'm
available To talk to him anytime.
Hanlon: dutch.
Look, I've spoken To
my people twice now.
Is there a chance That
nobody saw anything?
No, see, some people
Would rather stay cowards,
Keep their mouths shut, and
not Put themselves on the line.
You got a problem with me? Because if
you do, why don't you Just let it out now?
You tell me. Or you gonna Keep your
mouth shut Like the rest Of these people?
Right. Right. Unis are
saying That you blame me
Because the guy cut out the
back At the army-Surplus bust.
Is that what all this
Roundabout shit is?
Where there's smoke, There's fire.
You didn't clear a room, and
A cop could have gotten hurt.
I cleared the rooms I
was supposed to clear.
You want to think it was me
Because you don't like me?
Fine.
But it was you Who
pulled out a gun today
Because you didn't think
That I can handle the job.
Or were you just scared?
Guess we should all,
uh... Get back at it.
You lil b. K?
Who "axing"?
Jamal "axing" From the joint.
Mal ain't trying to put my name
In his mouth, Talking to no police.
You called his cell Right
before he was arrested.
I ain't make no call.
Gardocki: your number's On
his phone, little asshole.
Look, a number Ain't
nothing but a number.
You want stripes With these 187s,
You got to name them And claim them.
No one steps up, spook street
Doesn't make the top 10.
Maybe one niners start
Whispering they're the ones
With bowling balls
swinging Between their legs.
Or you go down in hood lore
As the punk who earned jamal
A 20-Year stretch As an accessory
for something He knew nothing about...
Since the phone call
ties him To the shootings.
Yeah, it was me and my boys Who blasted
them fools! Jamal wasn't knowing.
It was myowningenuity shit. Myshit!
So, what we gonna do now, Slow man?
Man...
Reppin'
That spook street, my
nig! That's what's up!
S- P-To the double-O-K!
Yo, take my picture!
I merked them slobs straight up!
Spook street!
Meet al-Qaeda's
Number two and three.
Want me to call juvie, Or
you want to waterboard them?
Hey, vic, You got a minute?
Not really.
It's about your daughter.
Cassidy wanted to file
charges Against you today.
She made Some pretty crazy claims.
I just thought You should know.
Said that you assaulted Vendrell's wife?
You don't buy your kids
A cellphone these days,
They want you dead. Who
else did she talk to?
Just me. I didn't write it up.
I figured it was just a kid Acting out.
Hey, thanks For the heads-Up.
You know, I got girls of
my own. It's a living hell.
You should take the
time... Talk to her, though.
Wyms: you're not really
thinking Of keeping these people
In the barn overnight, Are you?
I'm allowed 24 hours. As fatigue
sets in, Someone will crack.
You sure This isn't about someone else?
Billings may have gotten
to me A little today.
He's selling them food
From his vending machines.
He hasn't done anything
To help solve this,
And he's making a profit.
You deal with it.
If he sees his lawsuit
through To the bitter end,
He's not going anywhere Any time soon.
And send these people home.
If you made one move that
Even approached competence,
This would look A lot different.
You think I don't know How you and
missus feel, That you want me to quit?
Well, I'm getting my pension
- Every penny of it.
God! Is that Allyou want?
Billings: that and The
tiniest bit of respect.
For what, steve?
You give that To a man - Respect -
You earn his hard work And loyalty.
That's what management
here Doesn't understand.
You show a little
R- E- S- P- E-C-T,
And people will do Almost anything to...
Nacio. The building manager.
Wagenbach: nacio?
You assume people Are indifferent, lazy.
Maybe they just found
someone Worth protecting.
Man: Knock it off!
I'm sorry to have kept
All of you here so long.
It's important to find out
What happened to that girl.
I meant to ask you earlier, How long have
you been the Manager of the building, nacio?
This august, It'll be one year.
Apartment managers Aren't usually
well-Liked. Seems like you are.
Well, I made a lot of
changes Around the building.
Get things fixed right away, Even if
it means fighting With the landlord.
It's the little things That matter.
Why do you think Nobody's come forward?
They don't know anything.
They're worried about The
trouble it could bring.
A lot of them Don't have papers.
Any other reason?
Well, they're mad...
About the noise, the smoke.
They complained to the
police Over and over,
But in that neighborhood,
It's tough to get a response.
You told me today You didn't know
anything About the complaints.
Well, I-I've been Talking to, uh...
The people down here,
Since we were waiting.
Where were you When it happened again?
At the hardware store.
Right.
Broken toilet.
And then you came back Afterthe murder.
And you put the bag With the
pipe down, Came out to talk to us.
Yeah.
So if we drove you back
To the apartment right now,
You could show That bag to us.
If I can rember Where I put
it. It's been a crazy day.
There's an old saying, Nacio
If you never lie, you never
Have to remember anything.
I don't think You meant to kill lana.
Look, it was your building.
You worked hard to keep it nice.
Probably asked those rockers Politely.
But they didn't listen, Did they?
What were you trying to do with
The cinder block, scare them?
You killed someone, nacio.
You didn't intend to...
But you did.
And all those people out there
Aren't talking for one reason.
Because you're the only guy that
Makes their lives any better.
Isn't it time To send those people home?
Where's the boy's mother?
Suckingyourman's dick
'Cause you won't, bitch.
Man: I've advised my client
Not to answer any questions.
Shit, nigga, I got something to say.
We smoked them fools All
day long, All three of them.
Why?
Just paying the white devil His due.
No more talk.
You working My last nerve, nigga.
We was bringing the ghetto
Heisman back to spook street.
Like back in the day.
You realize That killing innocent people
Because of the color Of
their skin is a hate crime?
You say it Like I give a shit, nigga.
Haters taught hate.
That's why I bang it.
This word You're so fond of using -
You're one of them "n-Word"
Type of bitches, huh?
You use that word, You
turn a person into a thing.
Makes it easier for you to
Rob them, hate them, kill them.
Do I got to listen To this church
up in here From this nigga bitch?!
Do you realize how many Black
folks have fought and died
To give us the opportunity
They never had?!
Mm, four? Five?
Not only Have you taken innocent lives,
But you turned yourself Into athing.
You can't Even say the word, bitch.
White man even got you
talking By his rules now.
Straight up.
I wouldn't Waste the word "nigger"
On someone As empty and godless as you.
Too many of our people Have died
Being treated like niggers...
For me to belittle Their suffering.
Yo, just make sure The streets know
Spook street nigs Merkedthem devils!
Againstme?
They're alleging that you used A racist
epithet To intimidate And harass the suspect.
It didn't happen.
The lawyer Said he witnessed it.
Oh, he's taking what I said
Completely out of context.
So, youdiduse the word.
Some crack-Baby tweener Does a triple homicide,
And I'm the one Being held over a barrel?
You let him get to you.
Listen, all that's gonna Come of this
Is a rainforest worth Of
paperwork And some chest-Thumping.
At my expense.
I'll look at it for you.
You ever feel like you're being
Pulled right back into something
That you have worked so
hard for For so long -
Don't even go there. I
got to work out a plea.
The defendant dumped
Boiling water on her baby
Because the father came home
With a hickey on his neck.
Tell mackey and his guys Good collar.
Hey.
That had to hurt.
Everything hurts.
New meds doing anything?
Beside the fact they make you
Want to jump out of your skin.
I heard your guy confessed.
Yeah.
Brass have to be pleased To get
these killer kids Off the street.
No, no, They're too busy
Trying to plot how to hang me
Out to dry for being a racist.
Deflect attention from their
Al-Qaeda thing not panning out.
So, uh, You're a racist now?
How's that Working out for you?
Vic: Those are federal agents
Finding your arsenal Of illegal weapons.
With enhancements, that ought
To earn you 18 to 25 years.
On another front, Your boss thinks
You sold his blackmail
intel To the armenians.
That's the definition Of a bad day.
Coyote's waiting To take you across.
Even found you a casa With
a little mountain view.
You like goat's milk?
I got your boss so worked up,
His orders were for me
To shoot you on sight.
You ever Try to come back
here, It'll be a race between
The feds, the cartel,
and me To catch your ass.
The feds and the cartel catch
You first, you'll be lucky.
Vendrell: Hasta la vista, shithead.
Now we just need moses to come
Through on the rezian front.
You and me
- We're on the road To being cool, right?
Look, I handled aramboles For you.
I saved your wife and
kid From an assassin.
I'm not your whipping boy For life, man.
That's what you got Ronnie for.
Mara ran her mouth To corrine,
Got her all revved up
About this armenian crap.
I don't need her Starting trouble
When I'm dealing with shit
Coming out of both of my ears.
Handle your wife.
And as far as you Making it
sound like I oweyoufor anything -
County jail. Yeah. Okay.
I hold you responsible For this.
Who do you think made sure the
Mexicans didn't finish the job?
I warned you About the threat.
I put those bangers on
The payroll to protect you.
'Cause those brothers Sure
as hell Didn't pull that
Shiv-Wieldingeseoff your ass To fulfill
some Community-Service requirement.
I want the mexican Who did this to me.
I don't even know That
the orderwasmexican.
The latino crime bosses
Need you out of the way
So that they can get on
With their brown revolution.
But diro is my first choice,
As previously discussed.
And I wouldn't rule
somebody out In yourowncircle
Looking to spread Their wings.
I want who did this to me.
Well, I'll get right on that.
But the one thing That
we did learn tonight -
I may be the only friend
That you can trust now.
Vic: aramboles vanished.
Where?
It looks like he took the
money From selling your intel
And booked himself A sea cruise.
Been a bad 24 hours for you.
You lost aramboles. Your
hit on rezian failed.
He's walking. He's one
pissed-Off Eastern euro peon.
He'll be harder To get to now.
I can help. But this
30-Day-Trial bullshit Is over.
I want tenure.
You owe me for your badge.
You got my hearing delayed.
I found out who aramboles
Was flipping your intel to. Even steven.
Anything else Is subject to my
availability And new negotiations.
10 grand a week.
Any attacks on the armos
Go through me first.
And no civilians get killed.
Wars are messy.
I like a buck As much as the next guy.
Can't feel good About spending it
When some schoolgirl's
Collateral damage in a drive-By.
Because you've got morals.
A few.
$10,000 is a lot...
Especially if someone's
morals Might get in the way.
A call girl gets a fraction of
That to leave hers at the door.
Then get your answers From a hooker.
I don't like being told
How to conduct my business.
Only two things I know
About how you make a living -
Employees get well paid To get their
hands dirty So you don't have to.
And before you raise up A new building,
The old one has to get torn down.
So?
So, 10 grand buys you a
one-Man demolition crew.
I'll need your answer in the morning.