DISPATCHER: (FAINTLY) Dark Star November,
this is Gator 6. Return to base.
Dark Star November, this is Gator 6.
Return to base.
(EXPLOSIONS ECHOING)
I took your advice.
It was good advice. Thank you.
You look pale. Everything okay?
Sean?
Hey.
Anyway, listen. I wanted to tell you.
- God damn it!
- The only reason why I canceled...
(CELL PHONE RINGING)
He's calling me three times a day.
I hear more from him now than I did
when we were together.
What is it with guys?
I gave notice.
- CONDUCTOR: Ticket?
- Notice?
May I see your ticket?
I, uh...
Hey. Hey.
You're acting a little strange this morning.
You okay?
- Ticket?
- Are we gonna make up the 10 minutes?
We're gonna try, sir.
Hey, Grandpa,
what the heck was the delay back there?
I just punch the tickets, sir.
(MUTTERING) I should punch your face.
Sean? Did I do something?
Look, I can see that you think you know me,
but I don't know who you are.
My name is Captain Colter Stevens.
I fly helicopters for the U.S. Army
in Afghanistan.
(LAUGHS)
ANNOUNCER: Now approaching
Glenbrook Station.
Sean, that's...
- Sean?
- Glenbrook Station, next stop.
I feel sick.
WOMAN: Damn it!
MAN: I'm sorry.
- Let me help you with that.
- No, it's okay.
Glenbrook Station.
MAN: Hey, mister!
- Hey!
- Glenbrook Station.
Hey!
You dropped this.
Thanks.
What is that?
Chicago.
All aboard.
Doors are closing.
This is a Chicago-bound train.
You okay there, Captain?
Next stop, Chicago.
Union Station.
Did you see that?
You're kind of freaking me out.
No.
No, no, no, no.
Are you all right?
I don't know what's going on.
Talk to me, Sean.
Look, I don't know who Sean is.
And I don't know who you are.
Okay. We'll get off at the next stop.
We'll figure out
whatever's going on here, okay?
This doesn't belong to me.
Look at me. Everything's gonna be okay.
GOODWIN ON SPEAKER: Captain
Colter Stevens, this is Beleaguered Castle.
Captain Colter Stevens,
this is Beleaguered Castle.
Acknowledge transmission.
Captain Stevens, do you copy?
Where am I?
You're with Beleaguered Castle.
Are you functional?
I'm dizzy. Did I just A-lock?
Adjusting your rotation.
Can you report at this time?
What is this? What is this?
Where...
Who am I talking to?
Captain, report what you saw.
What? I don't understand.
Where were you
before you were talking to me?
There was an explosion.
Coming from where?
(SIGHS)
Some confusion is perfectly normal
at this stage, Captain.
Do you have a visual signal?
Who are you?
You already have that information, Captain.
- I do?
- Recall my name.
We'll rebuild the pattern. Try to focus.
I...
I was on a mission.
I was flying,
and then I woke up on a train.
And now I'm here.
I need to be briefed.
What unit is this?
You're with Beleaguered Castle.
Who?
Stand by for thread one
of alpha memory pattern.
What is Beleaguered Castle?
The exercises will assist you.
Memory thread one.
Listen to the following passage.
"Lilly awoke in an evening dress
and opera cloak.
"In her hand were five playing cards."
- Is this a joke?
- "They were,
"the queen of spades, four of clubs,
"nine of clubs,
- "three of hearts, nine of hearts. "
- (GRUNTING)
- Is this a Red Flag exercise?
- End of thread one.
Thread two. The following is a recording
of a Western Screech Owl.
End of thread two.
End of pattern. Acknowledge.
Acknowledge end of pattern.
Stand by to initiate pattern recall.
Go for pattern recall.
Arrange the five playing cards
in order of descending value,
irrespective of suit.
- Queen, two nines, four and a three.
- That is correct.
The passage I read contained mention
of a woman's name.
What was that name?
- Her name was Lilly.
- That is correct.
Recall my name.
Goodwin. Your name's Goodwin.
That is correct. Welcome back, Captain.
(CLACKING KEYS)
Ma'am, I need to talk to my father.
Has anybody been notified
that I'm stateside?
Who bombed the train, Captain?
What?
Who bombed the train?
A woman kept calling me Sean.
That is incidental.
Think, Captain. Remember back.
Who bombed the train?
I don't know who bombed
the goddamn train.
- Then go back and try again.
- Back where?
You will have eight minutes,
same as last time.
No, no, no, no.
No more bullshit sim tests, okay?
I need to know where I am.
What is the location
and condition of my crew?
Does anybody know that I'm stateside?
You are obligated
to give me this information.
Start with the bomb.
Where is it? What does it look like?
What kind of explosive?
How is it detonated?
- Right.
- Find the bomb,
and you will find the bomber.
Find the bomb. Wait, no, I...
I took your advice.
It was good advice. Thank you.
Okay. That's good.
And I signed up for an LSAT course.
Next thing you know,
I'll be moving to India to find myself.
LSAT.
Know any good gurus?
(CAN OPENING)
She got your shoe.
So, what do you think?
Am I on the right track?
It's the same train, but it's different.
Deep.
I hope it's different. I feel the same way.
(CHUCKLES)
What?
(CELL PHONE RINGING)
- COLTER: Do I have...
- Bryan.
What is it with guys?
Everything's more beautiful in retrospect.
COLTER: What is...
This looks so real.
I think it's gonna be really good for me
to get as far away from him as possible.
Unbelievable detail.
Ticket? May I see your ticket?
They wouldn't put the doer in front of me.
- The doer?
- You're the pretty girl.
- CONDUCTOR: Ticket?
- The distraction.
- Distraction?
- Every sim has one.
Are we gonna make up the 10 minutes?
- We are gonna try, sir.
- Are you talking about Bryan?
Hey, Grandpa,
what the hell was the delay back there?
- What are you late for?
- What?
You seem concerned about the time.
What are you late for?
I'm on my way to an asshole festival.
I hear you're headlining.
That's funny. What are you, a comedian?
Yeah.
He is a comedian.
Sit down.
Freak.
Fans.
That's the guy.
He came in third on America's Got Talent.
Got cited twice for a DUI.
- (ANNOUNCER CHATTERING)
- We talked about him.
- Thank you, ma'am. Thank you.
- You're welcome.
Glenbrook Station.
Yeah, but by 1:00
the bridge is gonna be jammed.
WOMAN: Damn it!
MAN: I'm sorry.
WOMAN: Just let me get it, okay?
Hey, mister!
Hey!
Hey! You dropped this.
Thanks.
ANNOUNCER: All aboard.
Doors are closing.
This is a Chicago-bound train.
The explosion came from behind me.
- What's with you?
- I don't have time to talk to you right now.
MAX: I got time for you.
Next stop, Chicago.
Union Station.
Holy shit.
(BEEPS)
Goodwin?
You gonna tell me how to disarm this?
Uh...
Should I...
Unplug it?
Or do you want me to just leave it? Or...
Okay, um...
(EXHALES)
I'm just gonna leave it.
Okay?
I'll be late.
Ladies and gentlemen, transit security.
- No, you're not.
- Due to a classified security breach,
I need all of you to turn off
any personal electronic devices
until we pull into the station, okay?
That means laptops, cell phones.
Cell phone, sir? Cell phone, sir.
Thank you very much.
Pagers, anything electronic.
Thank you. It's just a precautionary
measure. Nothing to worry about.
So which is it?
Security breach or precautionary measure?
Sir? Sir.
Is there a problem here, sir?
- I'm in the middle of a very big deal.
- Sean?
- I need you to turn that off.
- Why don't you show me that ID again?
- Sean?
- Turn it off.
- What's your problem, asshole?
Hey!
Sean! What are you doing?
Hey, not a good idea, ma'am.
Not a good idea.
That's not a good idea.
- I think you broke his jaw.
- It's okay.
He's not any more real than you are.
I'm not real?
How about next time you drive to work?
Not gonna be a next time.
(GASPING)
Stabilize.
Lower your pulse.
Did you find the bomb?
Yes.
There's hydraulic fluid all over the floor.
It's not a concern, Captain.
- What is...
- Tell me about the bomb.
Where's that man?
I saw a guy with a crutch on the monitor.
He looks like he's in charge.
I want to talk to him.
That's irrelevant, Captain.
I want to talk to your commanding officer!
You can talk to him upon completion
of your mission.
My mission is in Afghanistan,
where my unit is.
I flew two goddamn sorties yesterday!
You've been with us for two months.
Did you ID the bomber?
No. Where's my unit?
And under whose jurisdiction
is this simulation?
Captain, this is not a simulation.
Lives are depending on you.
What lives?
What do you remember about the bomb?
Tell me about the detonator.
No, no, no. What lives?
What are you talking about?
I need to be briefed.
Sir, I need to give him something.
That's fine. Go ahead.
Okay.
Get ready to send him back in.
MAN: We're still waiting. Justin is trying to do
all the profiles right now.
At 7:48 this morning,
Central Standard Time,
a bomb exploded on a commuter train
outside of Chicago,
killing everyone on board.
And that's the train that you've been on.
No, no, no. I'm right here.
You're talking to me right now.
A man named Sean Fentress
was on that train.
He, for all intents and purposes, is now you.
Every second spent explaining things
puts more innocent civilians at risk.
- This makes no sense.
- The train explosion
was the first attack of a series.
There are going to be more.
Now, did you find the bomb?
In the restroom.
Ventilation panel above the sink.
Cell phone detonator.
Are we done?
No, no. But that's good.
That's very, very good, Captain.
Good.
Our records show that 1,812 calls ended
at the moment of the explosion.
Fifty-two of those calls were tethered
to the cell tower nearest the train.
So, one of those calls was made
by our bomber.
Do you remember a freight train passing by
just before the explosion?
- Yes.
- The explosion was timed
to engulf the passing freight train,
which means the bomber had to be watching
both trains when the call was made.
Fifty-two callers.
One of those is our bomber.
I want you to concentrate on the passengers
in your car. Get to know them.
Narrow the suspect pool.
Look for ones who seem
quiet or withdrawn.
Who seem nervous.
As always, you will have eight minutes.
Eight minutes and then I blow up again?
Yes.
I need you to discipline yourself
on this next pass.
Perform only the tasks that we assign you.
Everything else is irrelevant.
Charge the drivers.
Okay. Has my father even...
I took your advice.
It was very good advice.
MAN: Watch it.
- CHRISTINA: You're kind of quiet today.
- (CAN OPENING)
Just got a lot on my mind.
Careful.
CHRISTINA: Yikes.
- So sorry.
- Don't worry about it.
Ticket?
That was very kind of you.
You're very decent.
Thank you.
You're real.
Ticket?
- COLTER: How's everything today?
- It's good.
- Anything out of the ordinary?
- No.
- (CELL PHONE RINGING)
- I meant behavior on the train.
Does anything, anybody
seem strange to you?
You're a little strange.
How about you?
Does anybody look suspicious?
Are you drunk or something?
Come here.
Come here for a second.
Come on.
Think of it as a game.
A game?
Wow.
They're all so utterly normal, Sean.
That's what's so terrifying about them.
Maybe there's a team at work.
The sleeping giant in cahoots
with the minister and Denoff there.
Don't forget the sullen college kid.
He's the expendable one.
I bet they're all controlled by the conductor.
Standing there all dictatorial.
Demanding tickets.
You're funny.
Damn it.
What about that guy?
CHRISTINA: Deposition.
COLTER: What about the woman
who's sitting across from him?
Hair appointment. Every Monday.
You know this.
You talk to these people more than I do.
Right, right. And the guy behind her,
he's late for an audition, right?
That or a court appearance.
- That's the guy that was cited twice for DUI.
- For DUI. I know.
- Hey, how's the signal in here?
- It's good.
ANNOUNCER: Now approaching
Glenbrook Station.
Is teaching not stimulating enough for you
anymore, Sherlock?
Uh-oh.
Now we've slipped into racial profiling land.
Did anyone else come out
of that bathroom today?
CHRISTINA: Well,
I saw you coming out of there.
- Me?
- Yes.
- No.
- Glenbrook Station, next stop.
Me?
MAN: Hey, mister!
- Hey.
- Hold on.
Hold on a second. Just hold on a second.
There's gotta be something in here.
- MAN: You dropped this.
- Gotta be something in here.
A broken phone? What is this?
Glenbrook Station.
Christina?
Yeah.
Excuse me.
Glenbrook Station.
Hey. Hey, come with me.
- This isn't our stop.
- No, come on. Let's take a walk.
- We don't get off here.
- I know. We'll just be spontaneous.
You're kind of freaking me out.
I know this is gonna sound really weird,
but I have a really bad feeling
about this train,
and I think that we should get off. Okay?
- Just get your stuff.
- All aboard. Doors are closing.
COLTER: Come on. Come with me.
So, what now?
Wait for me, right here. I'll be right back.
ANNOUNCER: Your attention, please.
Train 7140 to Skokie
will be leaving in 15 minutes from track two.
(COUGHING)
Your attention, please.
Train 7140 to Skokie will be leaving in...
(EXHALES)
(DRYER WHIRRING)
CHRISTINA: Hey.
You ready to get that coffee now?
Sorry, yeah. Just one more second, okay?
Oh, for God's sake.
Feeling sick?
It's motion sickness. I get it all the time.
- Excuse me.
- Excuse me?
- Are you following me?
- Can I borrow your phone?
No. I don't have one.
Sure?
Yeah, I'm sure.
Look, why don't you leave me alone, please.
Or I'll call the police.
With what?
I thought you said you didn't have a phone.
You know, you have no right.
What are you doing? Give me my bag back!
Are you crazy?
- COLTER: Where are they?
- Sean?
Get back!
Sean, what are you doing?
Sean, what's going on?
- Sean!
- Where is the phone?
- Sean! Sean!
- (EXPLOSION)
It wasn't you.
What the hell's wrong with you?
- No!
- Are you insane?
No! No! No!
- Where is the phone?
- CHRISTINA: Stop it!
- Get away from me!
- Where is it?
Get away from me, please!
(EXCLAIMS)
(TRAIN WHISTLE APPROACHING)
CHRISTINA: Sean. Sean! Get up! Sean?
- Shit.
- Sean, listen to me! Get up!
- Sean! Sean!
- MAN: Give me your hand! Get off the track!
- Mister, come on!
- Sean, Sean, get up!
Sean! Sean!
(GASPING)
Cold.
Goodwin?
Goodwin, come in. Do you read me?
Captain Stevens, this is Beleaguered Castle.
Do you copy? Please respond.
It's freezing in here. What's going on?
(EQUIPMENT POWERING DOWN)
What was that?
(BEEPING)
He's in trouble.
I think the oxygen just went out.
Goodwin?
(METALLIC CREAKING)
Goodwin!
Find a way to get through to him.
(GRUNTS)
What is it?
What's going on?
It's not the tertiary cooling, either.
Just keep sending strings out.
See if he hooks onto something.
It's hard to say exactly
what he's going through.
(BANGING)
(GRUNTING)
- Sir?
- Please!
There's not a whole lot
we can do from here.
If nothing changes,
how much time does he have?
Some.
But not a lot.
(EQUIPMENT POWERING UP)
(WHIRRING)
GOODWIN: (DISTORTED)
There are four principal dialects of Arabic.
Egyptian, Gulf, Syrian-Lebanese
and North African.
We will now play you portions of each,
discussing their differences.
(CLACKING KEYS)
(UNDISTORTED) Lilly awoke
in an evening dress and opera cloak.
In her hand were five playing cards.
They were the queen of spades,
the four of clubs...
Goodwin, you out there?
(BEEPS)
Goodwin? Where's Goodwin?
This is Captain Stevens. Do you copy?
RUTLEDGE: Captain Stevens?
The capsule lost power.
The capsule?
Is that where you are right now, Captain?
In a capsule?
You should know. Who are you?
Let me get Captain Goodwin. Get Goodwin.
You invented this thing, right?
- I did.
- Wait. Are you in command here?
I am. Were you able to locate the information
we need, Captain?
That's a negative, sir.
I was unable to find the bomber,
but I did save a passenger on the train.
I got her off safely. A woman.
Captain? It's gonna be counterproductive
for you to try to save anyone on that train.
They are outside the mission.
But she survived.
And maybe the rest could, too.
She survived,
but only inside the source code.
None of them can be saved.
What is the source code?
It's quantum mechanics. Parabolic calculus.
- It's very complicated.
- Try me.
Fine.
When a light bulb is turned off,
there's an after-glow,
a lingering, halo-like effect.
Have you seen it?
- Yes.
- Of course.
The brain is like that.
Its electromagnetic field remains charged,
just briefly, even after death.
Circuits remain open.
Now, there's another peculiarity
about the brain.
It contains a short-term memory track
that's approximately eight minutes long.
Like a convenience store security camera
that only records the last portion
of the day's activity on its hard drive.
Now, in combining these two phenomena,
circuitry that remains viable post-mortem
and a memory bank
that goes back eight minutes,
source code enables us to capitalize
on the overlap.
Sean Fentress died on that train.
Of all the passengers aboard,
he was your best link.
You two share compatibility
in terms of gender, body-size,
and your synaptic maps.
What happens after the eight minutes?
After? Nothing.
You cease to exist on the train.
You cannot exist inside the source code
beyond Fentress's eight minutes.
Source code is not time travel.
Rather, source code is time reassignment.
It gives us access to a parallel reality.
Now, the deaths on that train were a tragedy,
but source code empowers us...
No, but I saved one person.
That girl that's always sitting
across from me.
I pulled her off the train.
Give me her name.
Christina. I don't remember her last name.
Her name was Christina Warren.
- Yes.
- She was 28.
- That's her.
- Born in Wilmette, Illinois.
Died this morning on the train.
No, no. I pulled her off. She's fine.
No, she isn't.
Believe me. She is.
Believe me!
She saw me get hit by the express train.
- This isn't getting us anywhere.
- No, no, no, wait.
Sir, we have to send him in.
A second attack is imminent, Dr. Rutledge.
What second attack?
The train was just the beginning,
a letter of intent.
(STAMMERING)
What aren't you telling me here?
We have information
that downtown Chicago is the next target,
and they're planning to detonate
a dirty bomb.
Do you have any idea
how many people would die
if an explosion of that magnitude
were to occur in the city?
We're evacuating as we speak.
We have to stop it before it happens.
Do you understand?
GOODWIN: If you find the bomber,
his second attack,
the real attack, we think, can be prevented.
We have very little time left. Out here,
the clocks only move in one direction.
Charge the drivers.
GOODWIN: On the upper deck of the next
carriage, there's a conductor's compartment.
It's a small office containing a strongbox.
Inside is a loaded handgun.
Get to it. You are authorized to use
whatever force necessary.
CHRISTINA: (ECHOING) I took your advice.
It was very good advice.
You're still here.
Of course I am.
Guess what?
You quit your job
and you enrolled in an LSAT course.
Good guess.
Soda can.
- Coffee spill.
- (TRICKLING)
Listen to me.
Don't answer this.
(CELL PHONE RINGING)
You deserve better than that guy.
Everything looks more beautiful
in retrospect, doesn't it?
- CONDUCTOR: Ticket?
- How did you know that was...
- Are we going to make up the 10 minutes?
- We are going to try, sir.
- How well do you know me?
- MAX: Hey, Grandpa...
Not that well, apparently.
Do you know me well enough
that if I did something that looked
a little strange
and was maybe even a little bit dangerous,
but I told you to trust me anyway,
that you could do that?
No.
Wow. That was honest.
You're beautiful. You're kind.
And you're painfully honest.
Who are you?
And what did you do with Sean Fentress?
It's the new me.
ANNOUNCER: Now approaching
Glenbrook Station.
Glenbrook Station, next stop.
CONDUCTOR: Ticket?
Glenbrook Station.
All right, I don't wanna hurt you.
(GROANING)
CHRISTINA: No, I'm not gonna sit in my seat,
all right? He's bleeding.
He needs medical attention.
Is it true that you tried to steal a gun
out of the train's security box?
Careful, ma'am.
- Damn it!
- What were you thinking?
- Can I borrow your phone?
- No! You need to go to the hospital, Sean.
- Please, please, let me borrow your phone.
- No! Why do you want my phone?
What would you do
if you only had a minute left to live?
I don't know.
I would call my dad.
I would hear his voice,
and I'd tell him I was sorry.
(TRAIN PASSING)
Tell me everything's gonna be okay.
Everything's gonna be okay.
Oh, yeah, the gun in the strongbox,
that was a really great idea. Thanks for that.
Did you make any progress?
Can I get access to a phone?
I need to talk to my father.
I will try to work on that soon.
Yes. I will try.
Goodwin, how am I doing?
I'm just trying
to measure my performance here.
Have you ever gone back in?
Am I doing better than you did?
We are wasting valuable time here.
No, no.
I have never been on the other side
of a source code mission.
- I wouldn't be a viable candidate.
- Why not?
(MUTTERING) CAOC-N. What is that?
Because the specifications
are extremely narrow.
What are they?
Captain, you should have found a suspect
by now.
This tactical advantage,
this tremendous tool that we've given you,
don't squander it thinking. Do.
Please contact my father for me.
This will stop at some point, Captain.
As soon as you finish the mission.
And you're doing really great.
And this will end.
Now, whoever planted the bomb
had to have equipment of some kind.
Some gloves, a screwdriver to get
into the overhead vent,
flashlight, something.
Check bags and backpacks,
briefcases, anything.
So, I took your advice.
- It was very good advice.
- Hey, Grandpa...
- What are you doing?
- I'm just trying to remember something.
- What is that?
- It's a military patch.
Were you in the military?
A friend of mine was.
He was in Afghanistan and he disappeared,
and no one's heard from him since.
Do you have the Internet on your phone?
No.
It's just connected to the office
by a really long piece of string.
Do you think you can see
what you could find on this guy?
- Sure.
- He's just been on my mind a lot lately.
His name is Captain Colter Stevens.
He's in the 17th Airborne.
Okay. You owe me.
I'll buy you a cup of coffee.
Why don't I get one for you now?
Okay. Christina?
Um...
I've been having these dreams lately.
Really vivid.
And you've been in them.
Really?
What? Oh. No. Not like that.
Not that I wouldn't. I...
It's just...
Um...
I'll call you back in a minute, all right? Yeah.
- Cramming?
- Uh, yeah.
For what?
Psych. And I got a big test this morning,
so I should get back to it.
Can I borrow a pen?
Yeah, sure.
Whoa! Hey, that's not cool, man!
Hey, your bag is a mess.
What are you doing, man?
Never find what I'm looking for.
It's just like my bag. It's just like my bag.
How about you let the guy
have his bag back?
Finish your deal.
Stay out of this, tough guy.
It doesn't end well for you.
This guy.
Don't do that.
Nothing. What am I doing?
Jesus.
Dick.
CAOC-N.
- WOMAN: Can you believe that?
- Asshole.
Excuse me, ma'am?
Hey, how are you doing? Good morning.
- Do you work at Walter Reed?
- Yeah, I used to.
- I'm in the military.
- You're in the military?
Yeah. Yeah, I am. I was wondering...
Then what was going on down there?
Oh, you know, uh...
We were just having a little bit
of an argument, actually, about this patch.
Is that what they train you to do?
Assault civilians?
No, ma'am, please. Do any of these letters,
they look familiar to you?
Do you know what the "N" stands for?
It's Air Force, and the "N" stands for Nellis.
Now approaching Glenbrook Station.
Thank you. Can I borrow your phone?
You know what?
Actually, I can pay you for it.
I don't even need to borrow it.
I can pay you for it. I have $100.
- Just for a couple minutes...
- I don't want your money. Just bring it back.
All right. Thank you so much.
This is a Chicago-bound train.
Next stop, Chicago,
Union Station.
Come on, come on, come on, come on.
Post Operator.
- Rutledge, please.
- Please hold.
Name, please?
You tell him
Captain Colter Stevens is calling.
- Hold the line.
- ANNOUNCER: All aboard.
Doors are closing.
OPERATOR: Dr. Rutledge
will be on in a moment.
I have to tell you something.
- I know. I found him.
- Your friend?
- I got him. Nellis Air Force Base. Las Vegas.
- No, he's not...
He's dead, Sean.
What?
I'm sorry. Your friend was killed
in action two months ago.
No, you must've gotten the name wrong.
Colter Stevens.
17th Airborne helicopter pilot.
It was on the first site I tried.
His father's name is Donald, right?
This is from last week.
"Donald Stevens will join host,
Leonard Watt, to discuss
"the death of his son,
Army Captain Colter Stevens,
"who died in Afghanistan in February,
"and was honored posthumously
with a silver star.
"Also on the broadcast
will be Army Sergeant Robert Alvarez,
"whose life was saved by Captain Stevens
"in a fire fight just outside of Kandahar."
I'm sorry.
GOODWIN: (ECHOING) Captain?
Sean? Talk to me.
Captain?
Captain Stevens,
my name is Captain Colleen Goodwin.
You're with Operation Beleaguered Castle.
You're safe.
Hey, this guy's crashing!
(RAPID BEEPING)
GOODWIN: Captain, just tell me what you see.
Just look and speak.
COLTER: I see a card.
GOODWIN: That's good.
COLTER: Do you copy?
We are taking a lot of RPG fire here.
GOODWIN: That's very good.
Am I dead?
A radio listing is saying that I died
in a helicopter crash, in country,
and my father received a medal for me.
Your condition's not the issue here.
You need to focus on preventing
any subsequent attack.
Everything else is irrelevant.
A news report saying that I'm dead
is irrelevant?
Until the person or persons
who blew up that train are in custody, yes.
Goodwin,
one soldier to another, am I dead?
Part of your brain remains activated.
What about the rest of me?
I can see my hands and my feet.
They still move.
They are a manifestation.
They're just your way of making sense
of all this.
So, what are you saying?
Are you saying that I'm imagining this?
I'm imagining that I'm still alive,
that I'm in this capsule?
MAN: We have core temp dropping.
(RUMBLING)
Captain, what just happened?
I asked you a question.
(SIGHS)
The capsule is a manifestation as well.
Where am I?
That's classified.
Fuck you!
Captain, I cannot imagine
what you must be feeling right now.
But if we're to prevent a second attack,
we need to send you back immediately.
And, Captain,
you cannot deviate from the mission
while inside the source code,
even to investigate your...
Even to investigate what happened to you.
There's only one continuum on this end
and it can't be unsettled.
Well, you know what? I did unsettle it.
I called you from the train.
Just before the explosion,
so at 7:46 this morning,
- they paged you with a call from me.
- You may have made that call from the train,
but I would never receive it here.
It's a different reality, Captain.
If the call even went through,
it would be received
by a different me entirely.
This may be difficult for you to hear,
but you are a hand on a clock, understand?
We set you, you move forward.
We reset you, you move again.
And that represents the entirety
of your function here.
You know what?
Next time I'll send you a pizza!
I'll see if that makes an impression!
You cannot alter the continuum
of this reality from within the source code.
This can't be legal, what you're doing.
In fact, your acquisition by this program
as well as the program itself
has been reviewed and sanctioned
by military court.
Many soldiers would find this
preferable to death.
The opportunity to continue
serving their country.
(STAMMERS)
Have you spent much time in battle, sir? Huh?
That's immaterial.
Any soldier I've ever served with would say
that one death is service enough.
Fine. You can have that in return
for completing this mission.
- Have what?
- I'll give you what you want.
Terminate your service. Let you die.
This is taking too long.
You've been too easy on him.
No more rest periods.
I am certain we can find other servicemen
with wounds similar to yours
who would consider
being a part of this program an honor.
What? No, wait, what?
Send him back.
Charge the drivers.
And Captain Stevens,
I'd like you to remember
that it's not only about you,
but it's also about
two million real-world Americans.
Now, you may not value your own life,
I do, however, ask that you value theirs.
CHRISTINA: Your advice.
Hey, Grandpa.
(GASPING)
Calm yourself. You're back.
Did you find the bomber?
There are hundreds of people on that train.
Well, then check them out one by one.
It doesn't matter what you do to them.
They're already dead.
Get to that gun,
and shoot someone if you have to.
But get us some usable intel.
(GRUNTS) No, wait!
We have to keep doing this
until you find the bomber.
Please. I'm trying. I'm trying.
Who is the bomber?
I'm trying.
I'm sorry, Captain. I know you're exhausted,
and we're all frustrated,
but we cannot fail. You can do this.
I can't. I can't.
Yes, you can.
You're a born hero, son.
Even your father thinks so.
Saving people is what you do best.
DONALD: It was about his third tour.
-I didn't want him to go back.
-Dad?
I just started feeling like
he didn't want to come home anymore.
-Dad?
-Like somehow, he couldn't come home.
And he wouldn't talk to me,
wouldn't hear me.
Finally he said he just couldn't leave
his unit out there without him,
and that was that.
Those guys were his family.
I said some things I shouldn't have.
I don't know,
I never fully understood him.
And I can't believe he's gone.
Send me back in.
Please don't blow me up again.
(EXHALES)
Hello?
I know it's you.
ANNOUNCER: Now approaching
Glenbrook Station.
I'm gonna find you. Turn around.
- Hey, there.
- Me?
Why do you look so surprised?
Don't.
Move. I said move. Move.
Put your bag over there.
- Okay.
- Move over.
- Put the bag over there and move over.
- Okay, okay.
Move over. Move over.
Now hand me your phone.
- You're done. You're done.
- What?
You can't kill anybody anymore.
What? I don't understand.
You were going to trigger the bomb
with your phone.
What? Dude, I swear I don't know
what you're talking about.
Listen, my name's George Troxel.
I'm a software engineer, okay?
- Right.
- I was talking to my wife.
Try it again.
Your call. Dial it again.
Okay. I'm gonna press redial.
Your phone is gonna ring,
and then I'm gonna shoot you.
(CELL PHONE RINGING DISTANTLY)
Shit. I'm sorry. Sorry.
MAN: Hey!
You dropped this.
Wow. Thanks.
WOMAN: Hey!
All aboard. Doors are closing.
Shit! No! No!
No!
Wait!
(ALARM SOUNDING)
No! Come on!
Stop the train!
(GROANING)
Hey!
- Derek Frost.
- Yes?
- See this?
- Yes.
- You recognize it?
- No.
Jesus.
How about you give me your wallet?
Okay.
(EXCLAIMS)
You left it on the train deliberately.
I must have dropped it.
No.
You planted it there,
so everybody would think you were dead.
(SCOFFS)
I know it's you.
How do you know so much?
What the hell is that thing?
Whoa, whoa, whoa! Slow down! Slow down!
Do you wanna see it?
Very patriotic.
Slowly, slowly!
All right, all right!
Back up! Back up! Back up!
(DEVICE CRACKLING)
Not many people could build that.
All right. Where is your next target?
Sean?
(GUN FIRING)
Oh, my God!
Sean Fentress?
Teacher.
History.
(BELL CLANGING)
I don't know you.
I think I killed your girlfriend.
(TRAIN APPROACHING)
Why?
You messed up my timing.
- Why?
- Oh.
You mean "Why this?"
Because the world is hell.
But we have a chance to start over
in the rubble.
But first there has to be rubble.
You're a teacher, you understand.
Christina.
Stay with me. Stay with me.
Everything's gonna be okay.
This isn't the end.
Check through there. I'll go check this way.
(CELL PHONE BUZZING)
(EXPLOSION)
(GRUNTING)
- Okay.
- GOODWIN: This is Beleaguered Castle.
Captain, this is Beleaguered Castle.
Acknowledge transmission.
Captain Stevens, this is Beleaguered Castle.
I have your bomber. I have his name.
You have the bomber's name?
Derek Frost.
He got into a rented white van
in the Glenbrook Station parking lot.
Illinois plates, five, Charlie,
Golf, Yankee, eight, four, seven.
Illinois plates, 5CGY847.
All right, let's move.
And Goodwin, there is
a radioactive device in the van.
Some kind of bomb.
Thank you, Captain.
Yes, ma'am.
You are now off the clock.
About our deal?
I had hoped that you might reconsider that,
for the sake of the program.
I have. I want something else now.
Good.
I still wanna die.
But I want to go back in
and I wanna save all those people
on that train first.
It doesn't work that way. It can't.
No, I know. I know, I know.
I'm not really asking you to believe me, sir.
I'm just...
I'm asking you
to have the decency to let me try.
MAN 1 ON RADIO: CPD-2, this is AU SWAT-1.
Van is approaching fence gate
to the quarry. Over.
MAN 2: Roger that, AU SWAT-1.
Allow the vehicle to enter the quarry road.
We'll stop him about halfway down. Over.
AU SWAT-2, this is CPD-2.
Block the east end of the road. Over.
WOMAN: AU SWAT-2, roger that.
REPORTER 1 ON TV: We're going to switch
now to a live feed from our Chicago affiliate.
REPORTER 2: The SWAT team
is approaching the white van.
The Illinois man has been sought
since early this morning.
The door is open
and the man is on the ground.
It appears he has surrendered.
REPORTER 3: Earlier today,
the police discovered...
MAN: Congratulations, Captain.
In recent months, Frost started posting
anti-government statements on his website.
Yes, sir, it's a real validation
of the program.
A clear window into
just how revolutionary source code can be.
We finally have a powerful weapon now
in the war on terror.
Congratulations, Captain. A job well done.
He's not gonna send me back in,
is he, Goodwin?
(SIGHS) I'm still waiting on an answer.
Are you married, Captain?
Um...
Joe?
Why don't you go take a break?
-You deserve to celebrate.
-Sure.
Can I get you something?
No, I'm fine.
Why? Are you asking me on a date?
Sorry. Poor taste.
- Are you married?
- Hmm?
No.
I am divorced.
Do you think
there's an alternate version of you?
A Goodwin who made different choices?
What do you mean?
Like, a you who didn't get married
and get divorced.
Or just married someone else.
A woman who took
a different fork in the road.
No, I don't, Captain.
What you experienced was a shadow.
It was an afterimage of a victim on a train.
This is real life. Here.
The one where you're talking to
a dead helicopter pilot?
The program wasn't designed
to alter the past.
It was designed to affect the future.
And you've done that.
I missed something, Captain.
That train shouldn't have blown up.
There must have been a second detonator,
something I couldn't see. A fail-safe.
It's a computer program, Captain.
The girl on the train, all the others,
they're lost.
I'm sorry about that.
I get it. I get it.
I know.
Quantum physics, parabolic calculus.
You're wrong, Goodwin.
You're just plain wrong.
Captain, Christina is dead.
She doesn't have to be, ma'am.
Okay. I'll ask Rutledge.
I'm asking you,
I'm asking you. Just...
Send me...
(BEEPS)
Captain.
It's your choice.
At the end of this source code,
I will terminate your life support.
(MOVING TRAIN ECHOING)
There will be no coming back.
I'm gonna save her, Goodwin.
It was an honor, Captain.
And I thank you for your service.
Good luck.
I took your advice.
You're gonna move to India,
and become a guru.
- (CAN OPENING)
- Careful, ma'am.
Yeah, I'm gonna go
find myself in the mountains.
Well, maybe you'll have a cup of coffee
with me before you go.
Yeah. I'd like to do that. Put it to the test.
Good.
Let's do it today.
Let's just skip work.
Bryan can find someone else to assist him.
(CELL PHONE RINGING)
- You know what?
- What?
I feel really good.
Why?
Because I've been waiting for weeks
for you to ask me for coffee.
Ticket?
Okay.
Just give me a couple minutes, okay?
And I'll be right back.
Gotta go save the world.
I knew he was a keeper.
Excuse me!
Beautiful day.
Now approaching Glenbrook Station.
Ticket?
Oh, I'm sorry. Sorry.
Glenbrook Station, next stop.
- You trust the DOD?
- WOMAN: They've got the finances.
Yeah, well, sure.
Look, if we can get the funding,
I guarantee we can have at least...
Eight source code projects up and running
by the end of the year.
- Really? That many?
- Maybe more.
You're a real hero, Dr. Rutledge.
Well, thank you.
We did save lives today.
Yes, a true victory for the program.
A great victory for us all.
We'll talk soon.
So? Exciting times.
Let's initialize the memory wipe on SC-1,
start crunching the data.
Sir,
we told Captain Stevens
that we were gonna let him die.
Let him die?
He just saved millions of lives today.
How many other disasters
might he avert down the line?
For all we know, he may be
the only candidate
with which the system works.
So,
let's clear his memory
and reinitialize source code.
Shall we?
Yes, sir.
Sorry, I just dropped...
Hey, Derek! This isn't your stop.
MAN: Hey, mister!
You dropped this.
Come on back here.
Oops.
Derek,
it's over.
You understand?
Hey. My name is Derek Frost.
I planted a nuclear device in a white van
parked in the Glenbrook Station CCR
parking lot.
Right now I'm handcuffed to a pole
on the 944 CCR train
headed to Chicago Union Station.
I am a sick and pathetic human being.
And I need to be locked away
for a very long time.
Okay.
Derek,
there's no more
burying the world in rubble today.
You mind if I borrow this?
Captain, some of the guys and I
are gonna go celebrate.
And...
Do you want me to initiate
the memory wipe, Captain?
Hello, Captain.
(PHONE LINE RINGING)
- Hello?
- Donald Stevens?
Yes?
My name is Sean Fentress.
DONALD: Who?
COLTER: I served with your son, Colter.
- Oh, boy.
- It's...
I'm sorry it's taken me so long to call you.
Sometimes it just takes a while to figure out
what you want to say. You know?
Don't be too hard on yourself.
I imagine it's not an easy call to make.
How are you doing, sir?
Well, all that came back was some ash.
It's hard to believe that it was him.
How well did you know him?
I was there when he died, sir.
He said
that the last time
that you guys talked was tough,
and
he wanted to say that he was sorry.
I just want him back.
I loved him so much.
I wish you could have told him that.
He knows it.
You take care, Mr. Stevens.
You okay?
Yeah.
Save the world?
Sort of.
So, where were we?
Getting some coffee.
(PHONE RINGING)
Dr. Rutledge.
What?
Shit.
MAN: What's so damn hard about it?
I run a business, okay?
Everything moves on time
or people get fired.
That's the way it works in the real world.
- (SCOFFS) Ten minutes.
- Hey, buddy?
Don't sweat the small stuff. You'll drown.
Thank you for that moment of Zen,
but nobody was talking to you.
What, are you selling self-help CDs today?
Why don't you just mind your own business.
Security? Get me a detachment of MPs here
this instant!
Why are you always so bitter, Max?
It's a bitter world we live in, my friend.
What do you want from me?
It doesn't have to be.
I will bet you $100 you can't make
all these people on this train laugh.
-(BEEPING)
-Oh. Right.
Actually, you know what? 126 bucks.
Is that your way of making fun of me?
I guess you have a better gig. Never mind.
No, no. I'm good.
Easiest money ever.
COLTER: Come on.
MAX: Excuse me, people.
(CLEARS THROAT)
One of our fellow passengers has decided to
offer me some money to...
What has gotten into you today?
You're like a different person.
- It's the new me.
- I like it.
I am going to prosecute you
to the full extent of the law.
(BEEPING)
Women always mess up my last name.
I was with a girl the other night
and she kept calling me "Getoff."
She was like, "Getoff! Getoff!"
I'm like, "No, Denoff, Denoff."
She says,
"No, you're fat and you're heavy. Get off!"
(ALL LAUGHING)
Good?
Twenty seconds.
Make it ten.
Goodwin?
-Look at all this.
-(PEOPLE LAUGHING)
MAX: It's good to see you, ladies,
up this early in the morning.
- What?
- Michelle. Barack.
All this life.
Goodwin. Open this door.
MAX: Put those headphones on.
I wanna see them stretch.
-Why do you keep looking at your watch?
-Christina,
what would you do
if you knew you had
less than a minute to live?
I'd make those seconds count.
I'd kiss you again.
Again? Mmm.
Goodwin, open this goddamn door!
He's done enough, Doctor.
(MONITOR FLATLINING)
MAX: And, I'm on the train...
Everything's gonna be okay.
MAN ON RADIO: It is a beautiful Monday
in Chicago today.
Temperatures expected to
reach the lower 60s.
Right now 55 at the lakefront, 54 at Midway,
53 at O'Hare.
And now, up in the sky, we've got...
(CHRISTINA LAUGHING)
He earned that money.
-Yeah, he did.
-He was funny.
- Speaking of which, I have no cash.
- (LAUGHS) Great.
Come here. I wanna show you something.
- Such a beautiful day, isn't it?
- Yeah.
It is a really perfect day.
Do you believe in fate?
Not really.
I'm more of a dumb luck kind of gal.
-Come here.
-Wow.
CHRISTINA: So what do you wanna do today?
I think we should stay here for a while.
This feels like exactly where
we're supposed to be, doesn't it?
WOMAN ON RADIO: Las Vegas' number one
morning news follows.
It's 72 degrees
on a cloudy Monday morning.
MAN: This is News Radio 840KX
in North Las Vegas.
- Good morning, Joe.
- Good morning, Captain.
(CELL PHONE BUZZING)
COLTER: Lilly awoke in an evening dress
and an opera cloak.
In her hand were five playing cards.
At some point today,
you're gonna hear about
a failed terrorist attack
on a commuter train near Chicago.
You and I kept that bomb from going off.
(KNOCKING)
MAN: An attempted bombing on a CCR train
outside Chicago.
But it was thwarted,
and the suspect was found on board,
- named Derek Frost.
- Derek Frost.
Captain Goodwin,
anything I can help you with?
No, that's fine. I'll come back later.
Keep an eye out.
One of these days the right crisis
is going to rear its head
and source code is going to
have its moment in the sun.
Yes, sir.
COLTER: If you're reading this e-mail,
then source code works even better
than you and Dr. Rutledge imagined.
You thought you were creating
eight minutes of a past event,
but you're not.
You've created a whole new world.
Goodwin, if I'm right,
somewhere at the source code facility
you have a Captain Colter Stevens
waiting to send on a mission.
Promise me you'll help him.
And when you do, do me a favor.
Tell him everything is gonna be okay.