Watch Movies, TV Series and Live Sports
Signup Here -> WWW.ADMITME.APP
Fuck this shit.
Let's go home.
Regret and remorse. Amends and atonement.
That's life, right?
Well, this next one is for you,
all you lost souls racing down
that long road to redemption,
and all you sinners running from your past
but heading straight
into that pit of darkness up ahead.
We're all on the same endless highway,
the one with no name, no exits, looking
for a way out of tonight and into tomorrow.
Well, they're gonna try to stop you,
but you gotta say, "Fuck it,"
and keep moving,
because this is your highway,
and tonight might just be
the night you finally outrun
those wicked demons once and for all.
And I'll be right here with you
making sure you get where you're going.
What's up?
Nothing.
Don't worry. We're fine.
It's customers only.
Hey!
Read the sign.
Twenty on the truck.
Rough night?
Yeah.
Have a nice day.
Fuck.
Mitch! Let's get the fuck outta here.
Come on!
Come again soon.
Fuck!
What the fuck?
Rough night?
There's gotta be a way out.
What if there's not?
Pull over.
- What?
- Pull over.
Are you crazy?
What are you gonna do?
I'm not running.
Mitch! Mitch!
Hey!
I know we've had a pretty fucked up day,
but if you could keep it together for
a little bit longer, that would be great.
Why? What are we running to?
What?
So we get out of here, we go home,
and then what?
And then nothing! Then we're home!
That's the point!
- Back to normal!
- Exactly.
Mitch, you wanted this.
We did this for you.
We did this for Kathryn.
So get in the fucking truck.
I'm not asking you to stay.
You've lost it, man.
You want to stay here and get killed?
- I'll see you around.
- Jack.
Come on.
What do you want?
Haven't you figured it out?
They've come to collect.
There's no way out. We fucked up.
You know what, Mitch? Fuck you.
I'm going home.
No!
Jack!
Dad?
Kathryn?
Dad! Why won't you help me?
Kathryn!
Dad, help me!
Dad, I need help!
Help!
Fuck!
Dad!
Dad, I need your help! Help me!
- Kathryn!
- Dad!
Fuck! Kathryn! Fuck!
Fuck!
Why?
It's piercing my brain.
My God. It's 1:00.
Guys, we gotta go. Ava, get up.
Come on.
I've never been so hungover in my life.
You guys got everything?
Now, maybe you're out there
next to that special someone,
that one who's going away.
But you're still here...
It's too early for this!
Baby.
...gettin' on down that road, and this time,
hold on and don't ever let go.
Kim! Kim!
Shit!
Man, this thing is fucked!
Of course, on the one day
we can't afford to stop and get a flat.
We'd be fine if your drum kit
didn't take up so much space.
It wasn't my idea
to take out the spare tire, Kimberly.
Whatever. Let's just call AAA.
Can you hand me my bag?
Well, do we even know where we are?
GPS can't even find us on my phone.
No, we're not on a private road,
we're in the middle
of a state highway right now.
Why is it so hot?
We can't help you.
Well, yeah, thanks for nothing.
Best of luck.
The closest place is four hours from here.
And it's closed.
Why? It's so early.
The chick on the phone
sounded like she was at a bar.
Which reminds me.
Wait, you're not serious, Kim.
What? It's not like we're going anywhere.
Warm beer.
Guys! Car!
Great. I was seriously thinking
who I'd have to eat first.
It was you, by the way.
Youngest!
Can we offer you a ride?
Is there a town close by?
AAA said that there's nothing for miles.
Yeah, we're pretty far out.
Actually, the closest town's
quite a way south.
You're gonna want to go
to Pete's Auto Body.
- Okay.
- Talk to Pete.
Yeah, but he's not going to be there
until tomorrow, though.
Why don't you come to our place?
Just until we can get a hold of Pete.
Thanks, a lot, really, but we're good.
We're used to sleeping in the van.
You know, Betty...
I wonder if the camper over
at the Kensington's
has the same size tire as that van?
I'm sure they have a spare.
Bet the boys could fix you right up.
Yeah. I guess. I mean, we could...
No. No, no, no, we're good, we're good.
Thank you, though. Really.
Well...
Suit yourselves.
Goodbye.
- Wait!
- What? What are you doing?
We don't know where we are,
we haven't seen another car in an hour...
Am I the only one who thinks it's not
a good idea to go with a couple of weirdos?
Look at us. Look at them.
We're the weirdos.
I'd way rather go with them
than a bunch of rape-y dudes.
So are you girls students?
No, we're not. We are in a band.
Fun! A rock and roll group!
Yeah.
We play jazz.
Smooth jazz.
I do love jazz.
So, how long have you guys lived out here?
I don't know.
Since the war.
Is that a trap or something?
It probably was
but broken now.
Coyotes.
This is your fault.
All right.
You don't have to worry about locking it up.
There's no one around for miles.
Come on.
Here we are. The bathroom is right there.
Nap, shower...
Anything that you need to do.
The Kensington's
are going to be coming over for supper.
It's just so wonderful
to have some company!
I'm sorry about Alex...
What did you say?
It's just so wonderful
to have some company!
No, before that.
I will whip up some supper for us.
Thank you.
What the fuck?
They aren't old, right?
But they act like they're 80,
and from the '50s.
I bet they have the nastiest sex!
Wait. Did you guys hear that?
What are you talking about?
Kim, this totally looks like you!
You're, like, a hot milkmaid.
They definitely have the nastiest sex.
My cousin's a Sunday school teacher
and she loves anal.
I really don't think I'm hearing things.
You're so gross.
You started it.
This bed is like a freaking cloud.
I don't think it's a good idea for us
to take a nap here, Ava.
Hey, you totally had sex with that old guy
just 'cause he had, like,
a Tempur-Pedic mattress.
Okay, he wasn't old.
- Old.
- He was pretty old.
He was 49. That is not old.
- That's so old.
- It's old even for me.
Stop talking to me.
She's done it again.
This is beautiful.
Just beautiful!
How lucky we are that you have access
to these old family recipes, Betty.
So, you guys have a tire?
For the van! Yes, sure.
The boys will fix that up for you.
Won't you, boys?
Sorry, are these your sons?
You look so young.
You just made Bunny's year with that one.
Actually, we adopted the boys.
It's a long, sad story.
Let's give thanks.
O Divine One,
we offer our gratitude for this beast,
for this blood,
for these vessels of anew.
We bow to you, for You are all-knowing.
We offer ourselves to you,
for You are the Master.
Amen?
What exactly is in this dish?
It's a Sunday roast.
I probably should have mentioned before
that I don't eat meat.
I see.
You know, there are some who just
don't have the luxury to not eat meat.
Only the strong survive! Right, boys?
- So, are you guys Russian or something?
- Russian?
That is a good one!
No, Raymond and Bunny, they're just,
very traditional,
set in their ways, as are we!
But it is no matter. Everything's fine.
You don't have to eat the meat.
- No.
- It's actually really good.
It is!
I thought there was four of you.
Enough!
This place feels like a bad acid trip.
Those twins?
What the fuck was that prayer all about?
Why do you have to be so negative?
Seriously?
Yeah.
- So we got a flat.
- What the fuck.
We're here. We got a roof over our head.
We got free dinner.
What's the big deal?
Why can't you just make the best of things?
I don't know,
because we have a show to play tomorrow?
And we're stuck in some house
in the middle of nowhere
on some road that doesn't seem to exist?
Sorry if I'm being a bummer by pointing
this out, but this isn't exactly normal.
Nothing's ever your fault.
- What?
- Nothing.
Just...
Miss Alex, that's all.
If she were here,
everything would be different.
Yeah, so do I. Obviously.
Then why did you let her leave?
What did you say?
You let her leave that night.
You wanted to fuck some nobody asshole
in some shithole club.
I hope it was good.
I hope it was really good.
Why are you doing this right now?
You know that I loved her more than any...
It's not funny, Kim!
You should see your face right now!
What the fuck, man? That's so messed up!
All right, I didn't make her
leave that night.
It's not my... My God! My God!
Okay, I'm gonna get you a towel!
Jesus.
Hey! They're really sick!
Ava and Kim can't stop throwing up this,
like, black stuff all over the place.
We have to do something.
Dear. It's probably the meat.
Newcomers!
Well, the first time is the worst time.
What is in that meat? What is going on?
I've got just the thing.
They'll be fine as soon
as they get some medicine.
Nice play!
Thank you so much.
This medicine's wonderful.
Of course, darling.
See? All better now.
Are you sure you don't want to change
into something more comfortable?
Yeah, I'm sure, thank you.
- Shouldn't we be calling a doctor, though?
- Don't you worry.
Dale knows what he's doing.
Old family recipe.
Yeah, from the Old World?
Yes, young lady, from the Old World.
But I swear,
if I could market this, I'd be rich.
Sleep tight.
Guys, we have got to go!
You need to calm down.
Let's just get some sleep, then Pete
or the boys can come fix our van.
What? No. No, no, no. We go take their tire
and we get on the road. I will pay for a hotel.
I'm not going anywhere.
How would we even get to the van tonight?
I'm going to bed.
I'm so, so sleepy.
How are you guys acting
like nothing is wrong right now?
I wish Alex was here.
I know. Me, too.
But she's dead.
I wish Sadie was a better friend to Alex.
I had more faith in you than that.
Why'd you leave me?
My God!
Let us rejoice!
Hear now this creed!
Contentment thou shall find
through suffering
and through long years in it.
For the damned do not grow old.
Their minds are nourished by living
in the dark waters of the gods.
Knowest thou.
Thou has begun thy transition.
The damned do not grow old.
Sadie.
Hi, Sadie.
Don't be a baby.
Sadie.
You left me there to die.
Now we can all be together.
Hey!
Black.
Black. Pink, black.
I like pink. Go with pink.
Of course you do.
Well, you look great in it.
- You want to wear the black, I know.
- Of course I want to wear the black!
I...
Now, where were we?
Lucas, what just happened?
Seems I lost my train of thought.
Well, folks, the mind is a tricky demon.
Lucas?
I'd say all you...
Lucas, are you okay?
I gotta call you back.
...keep on moving forward.
Try not to linger
on the things you left behind.
Because you cannot undo
what's been done...
And ain't nobody gonna...
Hello? Hey! Are you okay?
Miss, I...
Hi, hey.
Lucas, are you okay?
Yeah.
God damn it, don't do that to me.
All I heard was this god-awful
screeching sound.
I thought you were, like,
getting attacked or something.
When are you coming home already?
When are you coming home?
Baby? Talk to me.
Lucas? Babe, what's up?
Honey, I gotta call you back, okay?
I'm sorry. I love you.
- 9-1-1. What's your emergency?
- Yeah, I just hit a woman with my car.
You just hit a woman with your car...
With your car. Was she on foot?
Yes. She's in the road right now,
and she's very badly hurt.
- Okay.
- She's very badly hurt.
Okay, we got it. Where are you right now?
I'm on...
I'm on... I don't know where I am.
You know what,
I'm in the middle of nowhere.
Sir, I'm sorry, sir, you're breaking up.
I said I'm in the middle of nowhere.
What do I do?
Okay, sir, I can't send an ambulance
if I don't know where you are.
Is there a cross street?
No. There's some lights up ahead.
I think there's a town
a few miles ahead? I'm...
So there's a town. Can you tell me
anything about where that...
I can't find it on my GPS. I'm sorry.
Okay, I'm patching you through
to Emergency Medical. One moment.
Okay.
Hello? Can you hurry up, please?
Sir? Sir, it's okay. Are you there?
Yes! Yeah, yeah, I'm here.
I'm a certified EMT. Are you with her now?
Yeah.
Great. Can you describe
her condition to me?
She's...
She's got a head trauma,
and some broken bones,
multiple broken bones, I think.
Okay. Anything else?
She's got a compound fracture of her knee.
I think.
- Is she breathing?
- Yeah.
- Okay. Is she conscious?
- God damn it, Claire.
- All right, sir, you're doing fine. Sir?
- Yeah.
Lucas? Lucas?
How do you know my name?
We have your cell.
- Right. Of course. Yeah.
- You need to trust us, okay?
Okay.
Sir, she's in critical condition
and we can't seem to locate you,
so we'd like you to try and move her.
You want me to move her?
You said there's a town up ahead, right?
Okay.
All right. Okay. You're okay.
Okay. I've got her in the backseat.
We are driving.
I am heading south. Are you still with me?
- Can you hear me?
- Yeah, we're here. Just stay with us, okay?
You're doing just great, Lucas.
There's a lot of cracks in the windshield.
I cannot see very well.
- What am I looking for when I get there?
- We're gonna talk you through it.
All right, good.
We're doing about 80 right now.
I think I can go faster.
I'm gonna go faster.
- Lucas?
- Yeah?
Can you say something to her?
You know, in case she can hear you.
I'll do everything I can.
Lucas, tell us when you're close.
- Okay, just got into town.
- Okay.
Okay, there's shops.
I see a barber shop,
I see there's a tattoo parlor, a church...
Do you see any people?
Anyone on the side of the road?
- Anyone that you can ask for help?
- No.
No, I don't see anyone.
There's nobody. Not yet.
What about the oncoming traffic?
Can you flash your lights
at the oncoming traffic?
No, no, I don't see anyone.
There's no oncoming traffic,
or there's no people?
- Okay, wait a minute.
- Okay. Lucas, you need...
Wait, there's a sign up here.
Okay, it's a hospital sign.
I think I'm pulling up
into a local hospital.
Dispatch to Regional, he's located
a medical facility of some sort.
Be advised, no contact local PD.
Lucas, we'll stay with you
till you've made contact.
Just make sure you stay with us until then.
Help! I need some help!
Hello? Hello, I have an emergency!
Is there anybody here?
Is there some sort of problem?
Did he run into a problem?
Hello?
Sir, is there a problem?
Lucas, can you...
...no one seems to know.
But that experience must have been
a serious emotional shock.
You think I imagined all of it, don't you?
You think I'm insane?
I didn't say that. I don't mean that.
What the fuck? Hey!
...I'm not given to imagining...
Sir, what's the problem here?
We need you to talk to us.
Lucas, we can help.
Okay, okay, okay.
Sir?
Sir, we need you on the line
telling us what you see.
We need you to keep talking to us. Sir?
- There's no one here. It's...
- Okay.
- It's abandoned or something.
- Okay. Calm down, sir.
There's no one fucking here!
Sir, I need you to calm down.
I'm sure there's someone nearby.
I'm going to need you to find the nearest
surgeon, nurse, whoever you can find.
- There's no one here. Do you understand?
- I need you to find the closest person.
Okay, sir.
I'm looking. I do not see anyone.
Okay, how is the victim? How is the victim?
I don't know what's happening.
Lucas! What about the girl?
How's she doing?
Shit! Fuck!
Lucas, how's she doing?
Not good!
- Not good. Okay, what's happening?
- What?
Her leg is... It's broken. It's...
Okay.
- She's bleeding really, really bad.
- All right.
All right. Focus.
You need to stop the bleeding.
I need you to look
for anything you can use.
- Like a tourniquet?
- Yes.
All right. I got it,
I got it, I got it. I got it.
Now, wrap it around the leg.
All right.
Okay, how tight do I make it?
- As tight as you can.
- Okay.
Something's happening! All right.
She's moving, she's moving!
- I don't know what to do!
- Sir, you need to focus.
Well, then, tell what I'm supposed to do!
Okay, Lucas, is she responsive?
To what exactly?
I don't know what that means!
How is her breathing?
It's upsetting. She's...
There's blood bubbling out of her mouth.
He's losing her. He's losing her.
I need to hear it!
- Can you hear it?
- Yes!
Okay, now listen carefully.
You're going to have to intubate her.
Do you know what that means?
Stick a tube in her throat.
Exactly. Now, you want to find
a specific kit for that.
It's pretty standard stuff,
but it's specific.
- Lucas?
- Okay, what am I looking for?
A package or a pack or a bag.
Probably has an indicator on the front,
but it can vary in shape or size.
What am I looking for?
Okay, it's best just to look
for the word "intubation,"
or "tracheal," "endotracheal,"
"tracheal intubation. " Any of those.
Or "airway," "airway intubation,"
"airway management kit,"
"EMS airway." That's the one we use.
Anything that has those words on it.
Just tell me what you find.
Lucas, tell me what you find.
Have you seen any?
- Can you see anything that looks like that?
- Okay, I got it.
Okay, good. First, open the kit,
look for the curved laryngoscope blade.
It's a metal hand tool.
No, there's no blade. It's just the tube.
- It's just the tube.
- That's right.
You're going to have to do it manually.
First, identify the glottis. It's a little
fleshy valve at the back of her throat.
Feel for the breath.
You want me to stick my fingers
in her throat?
Yes. You have to. It's the intubation.
And have it ready.
You need to hurry, you need to do it now.
Okay. Okay.
All right. Okay. Okay.
You must go farther, Lucas.
All the way to the back of the tongue.
- Now do it.
- Okay.
Insert the tube. Don't hesitate.
Keep going. Keep going.
- Fuck! She's biting me! She's biting me!
- What happened?
She's...
- What's happening?
- Something's wrong.
She's close to death.
Who is this?
Hello? Who is this?
I'm a surgeon, Lucas.
I've been listening since you arrived.
- Okay.
- He's here to help.
Do you want to save her life?
Yes.
Then whatever you do,
do not remove your hand from her throat.
Trust me, the tube is not set
and it's the only thing giving her oxygen,
the only thing keeping her alive.
But it's also killing her.
She's got several broken ribs
on her right side
and the diaphragm is unable
to compress the lung. She can't breathe.
You must compress the lung.
- How do you know that?
- You must compress the lung.
I didn't tell you that.
You must compress the lung.
No, no, no, look, I need a minute here.
I'm not really sure what I...
Compress the lung.
I must compress the lung! I must...
Fine, what the fuck does that mean?
First, use your free hand
to expose the rib cage.
Okay. Okay.
- Okay. Now what?
- Slowly. Carefully.
- You can do this, Lucas.
- Now what?
Make an incision.
- An incision?
- Make an incision.
You have to.
All right.
Okay. Okay.
You have the blade.
Five to seven inches.
Just below the rib cage.
Slowly.
Okay.
- Find the lung.
- Okay.
I got it.
Compress the lung.
Fuck!
What the fuck?
Fuck! Fuck!
Claire?
- Claire's not here.
- We're still on.
We're going to have
to talk about this, Lucas.
I don't deserve this.
Really?
Why don't you elaborate?
Elaborate.
She was out in the middle of the road,
in the middle of the fucking night,
in the middle of nowhere.
How am I supposed to be expect...
I mean it's...
It's an extraordinary circumstance, okay?
How am I supposed to be...
Lucas, it's okay.
Absolutely okay.
Right. Right.
- You had no way of knowing.
- No way of knowing.
She was in the middle of the road,
in the middle of the fucking night...
- In the middle of nowhere.
- At night.
It doesn't have to be your fault, Lucas.
Go be with your wife.
I can just walk out of here?
- Yes.
I can leave?
Yes.
And you aren't tricking me again?
- No.
- No, Lucas.
Find the locker room.
You'll see.
Do I need to worry about what's back there?
- No.
Absolutely not.
You were never here.
Okay.
I'm hanging up now.
That's good, Lucas.
Good night.
I'll take a beer and a shot of whiskey.
You forgot to shut the door.
No, I didn't.
It didn't latch.
Come on, Al.
I been on my feet for hours.
Give me a beer.
First the door.
Seriously? It's shut. It's fine.
Sounds pretty sure of herself, Al.
At the same time, being sure is sort of
a fancy way of being lazy.
You want to go check the door?
I mean...
You can see from here
it's not shut all the way.
I'll buy you a beer.
Well, when you put it like that...
All right, everybody,
put your hands on the tables!
Cooperate and we'll get this over with
real fuckin' quick!
- You! Sit the fuck down!
- Hang on, buddy.
Put your hands on the table.
What the fuck part
of "put your hands on the table"
is so hard for you to understand?
Maybe before we all get carried away here,
we stop and think for a minute.
- How's that sound?
- That sounds great.
Now, I know that one shitty bar
might look just like any other.
But here's some free advice.
Get back on whatever road it was
that brought you here and keep moving.
'Cause I guarantee you
that robbin' this place
is way more trouble than it's worth.
This is not a robbery!
This is my sister.
Her name is Jesse,
and I know that she's in this town.
Now, I don't want to hurt anybody.
But I'm telling you right the fuck now,
I'll do anything to find her.
Put your fucking hands on the bar!
Thank you.
Anyone.
Anybody seen her?
Where'd you get that tattoo?
Did you get that around here?
Fuck!
I don't know if I can kill you,
but I bet that it hurts like a motherfucker!
One more step! One more fucking step!
Last time. Have you seen her?
Yeah.
Yeah? Where?
Nowhere you can go, big shot.
You'll fucking take me!
Move, motherfucker!
Get in. Get in. And drive.
Fuckin' go, man!
Where are my road warriors at,
my veteran road hogs out there
tearing up the pavement
where the rubber meets the road?
You may be an old dog,
but you can still learn some new tricks.
So what's stopping you?
You don't owe the world shit.
It's time to live your own life,
and if someone's dumb enough to stand...
You don't got a lot of time
before the whole valley finds out,
but you know that, don't ya?
Yeah. Yeah. If I need you to,
I'm gonna have you drive off the road.
You don't want to do that.
It looks like the desert,
but if you go out there,
you might not come back.
What the fuck are we doin' here?
It's around back.
- In there.
- In where? What?
How do we get in?
Through the door.
Quit being so fuckin' mysterious!
Sorry.
That's okay, Danny.
How did you know my name?
You're fucked, Danny!
And you don't even know it yet.
Don't you want to see her?
Yeah.
Jesse!
- Jesse, it's me, Danny.
- Danny?
Danny, what...
Are you really here?
I'm really here.
My God! You're hurt.
It's nothing. It's nothing.
I can't believe I found you.
How did you even get here?
Man, Danny, you got old.
I've been searchin' for you for 13 years.
You look absolutely incredible.
- Danny, wait...
- Yeah, what?
- How did you get here?
- |...
- No. Danny, don't!
- What the hell are you doing?
What the hell are you doing?
I'm savin' you!
I came to get you the hell outta here!
Danny, I don't want to leave.
You don't mean that, Jesse.
Now get outta the fuckin' way.
- She does mean it, Danny.
- Shut up!
She's here because she wants to be.
Come on, Danny.
Okay? It's time for you to leave.
- Danny!
- Come on.
Get your fucking hands off of me!
Turn us around.
God damn it!
You're such an asshole.
I'm okay with that.
Just let me be an asshole
and get you the hell out of here.
Fuck.
Danny, you're not supposed to go out there.
If you do this, it's for you,
it's not for me.
I don't have a choice.
I can't see anything!
There's nothing to see!
The fuckin' car's gonna fall apart.
Don't slow down.
You're not supposed to be here.
You can't stay here,
and you can't take me with you.
I'm not leaving you behind.
You'll need your gun.
What?
You have the gun, Danny?
You might have to blow my brains out, too.
Stop it!
No, you can't stop!
You can't stop, Danny, it's too late!
Fucking stop!
- Fuck!
- Danny...
This place is made for people like me.
You shouldn't be here.
I mean, this whole time growing up,
didn't you ever think about Mom and Dad?
What do you mean?
Come on, Danny, tell the truth.
You've really never thought
it was my fault?
You can't
blame yourself for what happened.
No, you're not listening
to what I'm saying.
- You were a kid. We were... You were...
- I killed them, Danny.
I killed them because I wanted to.
All right? And now I'm here
because I want to be.
This place found me and I love it here.
Jesse, help me! Jesse!
You should've let me go.
I just wanted to save you.
Jesse!
What are you lookin' at?
How I'm looking forward to that.
- Yeah.
- Hey.
You can leave your stuff everywhere.
- Hey, sweetie.
- Hey, honey.
I'm so glad that we got to do this
before you start school.
- Me, too.
- Well, let's not get ahead of ourselves, okay?
We still have this one last weekend
to have fun.
Play games and puzzles, make s'mores,
with our little girl.
It's just exciting, sweetie.
Well, we all know the past
can be a piece of shit sometimes,
but when it catches up to you,
you'd better be ready.
Keep your eyes on the road
and let that engine roar so loud
that you can't hear those demons
screamin' in your ear.
Lock your doors and make those tires burn.
Tell your family you love them
and kiss the past goodbye
once and for all,
because every road
has got to end somewhere.
Am I right?
All right.
Sure looks better in the pictures.
Got some charm.
Listen, why don't you go unpack
and we'll have dinner ready in an hour.
Cool.
I'm gonna open some wine.
Do you think she's ready?
Of course not. Is anyone ever?
At a certain point we're just going
to have to trust in the future, right?
I just hope that she'll learn
to believe in herself.
And that she'll stand up for herself.
She will.
Question is, are you ready?
I'll be fine.
I did not say that.
- That's a good idea though.
- Hey, honey.
Hey.
Hold on, honey, let your dad get it.
This next one might be familiar
to some of you...
Who is it?
...who don't want the night to end.
So go ahead...
Hello?
Make some mistakes.
You can always get it right the next time.
No one's there.
What is it?
- Honey, call the cops.
- What?
Call the cops, now! Go!
Okay.
Dad, what is it?
9-1-1, what's your emergency?
- Someone's trying to break into the house.
- What's the address?
It's 6-2-5-5 Bethel Lane.
Okay, just take a deep breath.
We're going to be there in about 30 minutes.
- What?
- You are gonna be fine.
- Dad?
- Daryl?
Dad?
- It's gonna take 30 minutes.
- What?
What?
Dad, what's going on?
We gotta get out of here. Come here.
What do you want?
Jem! Jem!
Why are they doing this?
What do they want from us?
What about Jem?
What the fuck do you want from us?
Please! What?
No. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
What are you talking about, baby?
What are you talking about?
Listen, I'll give you anything you want,
anything you want, just please,
let me know what I can do
to make this right, please.
My God!
You told...
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
No, no! I will not... No!
No! Cait! No!
Cait!
No! No! No!
God! No, no!
No!
She was innocent.
She was innocent!
Just kill me!
Jem! Go!
Go! Go!
Go!
Bitch!
What do you want from us?
Go.
Go!
Thank you.
Thank you. I'm so sorry...
Okay. I'm sorry.
Shane. Get up.
A little help?
Fuck!
We let you go!
Fuck! You!
What've we done?
What the fuck?
Holy shit! Run!
Mitch! Mitch!
What the fuck?
Un-fucking-believable.
Fuck.
- What about Shane?
- Fuck Shane. Shane was an ass...
Fuck!
What the fuck is that thing?
Holy shit.
Fuck this shit!
Let's go home.
Regret and remorse. Amends and atonement.
Well, that's life, right?
This next one is for you,
for all you lost souls racing down
that long road to redemption,
and all you sinners running from your past
but heading straight
into that pit of darkness up ahead.
We're all on the same endless highway,
The one with no name, no exits
looking for a way out of tonight,
and into tomorrow.
Well, they're gonna try to stop you,
but you gotta say, "Fuck it,"
and keep moving
because this is your highway.
And today might just be the day you
finally outrun those wicked demons
once and for all.
And I'll be right here with you
making sure you get where you're going.
Because in the end, we're all
just trying to find our way home.
Right?
Rough night?
Yeah.
Someone needs to stop Clearway Law.
Public shouldn't leave reviews for lawyers.