Someone needs to stop Clearway Law.
Public shouldn't leave reviews for lawyers.
There's a bunch of birds in the sky
And some deers just went running by
Oh, the snow's pure and white
On the earth, rich and brown
Just another Sunday morning
In my quiet mountain town
The sun is shining
and the grass is green
Under the three feet of snow, I mean
This is the day
when it's hard to wear a frown
All the happy people stop to say hello
Get out of my way!
Even though the temperature's low
It's a perfect Sunday morning
in my quiet little mountain town
Well, good morning, Stan.
- Mom, can I have $8 to see a movie?
- A movie?
Yeah, it's gonna be the best movie ever!
It's a foreign film from Canada!
All right, here you go.
- But be back for supper.
- Thanks, Mom.
Oh, what a picture-perfect child
Just like Jesus, he's tender and mild
He'd wear a smile
while he wore a thorny crown
What an angel
with a heart so sweet and sure
And a mind so open and pure
Thank God we live in this quiet
redneck mountain town
Dude! Dude, wake up!
Kenny, come on!
Kenny, the Terrance and Phillip
movie is out. You wanna come?
Where do you think you're going?
You can't! You have to go to church!
Well, fine,
you go ahead and miss church!
And then when you die and go to hell,
you can answer to Satan!
You can see your breath
hanging in the air
You see homeless people
but you just don't care
It's a sea of smiles
in which we'd be glad to drown
That's right
It's Sunday morning
In our quiet little white-bread
redneck mountain town
- Ready, Ike? Kick the baby!
- Don't kick the baby.
Kick the baby.
Ike, you broke another window!
That's a bad baby! Bad baby!
Kyle, we're going to
the Terrance and Phillip movie!
Oh, my God, dude!
- Kyle, where are you going?
- We're going ice skating.
Well, take your little brother
out with you.
Oh, Mom. He's not even my real brother.
He's adopted!
Do as I say, Kyle!
Okay! Okay! I'm sorry!
Look at those frail and fragile boys
It really gets me down
The world is such a rotten place
and city life's a complete disgrace
That's why I moved
to this redneck, meshugana
Quiet mountain town
Ike! Bad baby!
This program is brought to you
by Snacky Smores,
the creamy fun of smores
in a delightful cookie crunch.
Mom! Somebody's at the door!
- Coming, hon.
- I can't see the TV!
It's been six weeks since
Saddam Hussein was killed
by a pack of wild boars
and the world is still glad
to be rid of him.
- Look, Eric, it's your little friends.
- Spider-Man!
What are you guys doing here?
Sweet, dude! Yes! Yes!
Off to the movies we shall go
Where we learn everything
that we know
'Cause the movies teach us
what our parents don't have time to say
And this movie's gonna make
our lives complete
'Cause Terrance and Phillip
are sweet
Super sweet.
Thank God we live in the quiet
little redneck, Podunk, white-trash
U.S.A.
Can I have five tickets to
Terrance and Phillip Asses of Fire?
No.
What do you mean, no?
Terrance and Phillip Asses of Fire
has been rated R
by the Motion Picture
Association ofAmerica.
You have to be accompanied
by a parent or guardian.
- But why?
- Because this movie
has naughty language!
Next, please.
- This can't be happening!
- We have to see this movie, dude!
Screw it!
It probably isn't all that good anyway.
Cartman, what are you talking about?
You love Terrance and Phillip!
Yeah, but the animations all crappy.
Wait, I've got an idea!
Hi, I want six tickets to Asses of Fire.
This movie might not be
appropriate for your little ones.
Hey, he says this movie
isn't appropriate for you.
Look, Mr. Homeless Guy,
if you don't wanna buy us tickets
and not get your 10 bucks and
not go buy yourself a bottle of vodka,
then be my guest.
Six tickets, please.
- Let me have some candy, Cartman.
- Let's see.
Nope, I don't have any Jewish candy.
Like you really need all that
chocolate, fat boy!
The movie's starting.
Hooray!
Say, Terrance,
what did the Spanish priest
say to the Iranian gynecologist?
I don't know, Phillip. What?
Where do they come up with this stuff?
You're such a pig fucker, Phillip!
What did he say?
Terrance,
why would you call me a pig fucker?
Let's see. First of all, you fuck pigs.
Oh, yeah!
Yeah. Fuck my ass and call me a bitch!
- You shit-faced cockmaster!
- Wow!
"Shit-faced cockmaster."
Listen, you donkey-raping shit-eater!
"Donkey-raping shit-eater."
- You'd fuck your uncle.
- You'd fuck your uncle!
Shut your fucking face, uncle fucka
You're a cock-sucking, ass-licking
uncle fucka
You're an uncle fucka, yes, it's true
Nobody fucks uncles quite like you
Shut your fucking face, uncle fucka
You're the one that fucked your uncle
Uncle fucka
You don't eat or sleep or mow the lawn
You just fuck your uncle all day long
What's going on here?
What garbage.
Well, what do you expect?
They're Canadian.
Uncle fucka! Uncle fucka!
Uncle fucka!
Shut your fucking face, uncle fucka
You're a boner-biting bastard
Uncle fucka
You're an uncle fucka, I must say
You fucked your uncle yesterday
Uncle fucka
That's U-N-C-L-E
Fuck you, uncle fucka!
Suck my balls.
Dude, that movie was fucking sweet!
You bet your fucking ass it was!
Fuck, dude, I wanna be
just like Terrance and Phillip.
Hey, wait a minute!
Where's your guardian?
I knew it! You paid a homeless guy
to get you in, didn't you?
- Fuck off, you donkey-raping shit-eater!
- Yeah!
Shut your fucking face, uncle fucka
You're an ass-licking, ball-sucking
uncle fucka
Hey, where have you guys been all day?
Nowhere. We just went to go see
the Terrance and Phillip movie.
- You saw it?
- How'd you get in?
Hey, stop crowding us,
you shit-faced cockmasters!
Wow.
Yeah. You're all a bunch of
ass-ramming uncle fuckers.
We have got to see this movie, dude.
Terrance and Phillip are Canadian,
just like my brother.
There's the girl that I like
Hey, Stan, tell them about
when Terrance called Phillip
a testicle-shitting rectal wart.
Now more than ever
she gives me butterfiies
It makes my stomach queasy
every time she walks by
Asshole, I'm talking to you.
I know I can be cool if I try
Hi, Stan.
Gross!
Come, Wendy.
Let us try to jump the hilly brush.
- Who are you, kid?
- My name is Gregory.
I just transferred from Yardale,
where I had a 4.0 grade point average.
Wanna skate with us?
We've been skating all morning
and laughing
and talking of memories past.
We saw the Terrance and Phillip movie.
Try and catch me, Wendy.
Bye, Stan.
Yes, yes,
I saw the Terrance and Phillip movie.
Who wants to touch me?
I said who wants to fucking touch me?
Come on, gang! We've gotta see
the Terrance and Phillip movie, too!
I hate you, Kenny.
Shut your fucking face, uncle fucka
You're a boner-biting bastard
Uncle fucka...
Okay, children, let's take our seats.
We have a lot to learn today.
We sure do, Mr. Hat.
Okay, children. Let's start the day
with a few new math problems.
What is five times two?
Come on, children. Don't be shy.
Just give it your best shot.
- Yes, Clyde?
- Twelve?
Okay. Now let's try to get an answer
from someone
who's not a complete retard.
Anyone? Come on, don't be shy.
I think I know the answer, Mr. Garrison.
- Shut up, fat boy!
- Hey! Don't call me fat, you fucking Jew!
Eric, did you just say the "F" word?
- Jew?
- No. He's talking about "fuck."
You can't say "fuck" in school,
you fucking fat-ass!
- Kyle!
- Why the fuck not?
- Eric!
- Dude, you just said "fuck" again!
Stanley!
- Kenny!
- What's the big deal?
It doesn't hurt anybody.
Fuck, fuckity, fuck, fuck, fuck.
How would you like to go
see the school counselor?
How would you like to suck my balls?
What did you say?
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Actually, what I said was...
How would you like to suck my balls,
Mr. Garrison?
Holy shit, dude.
Well, I must say, I'm very disappointed
in you boys, m'kay?
You should be ashamed of yourselves.
And I've already called in
your mothers...
- You called my mom?
- That's right.
- Oh, no, dude!
- Mr. Mackey, can I ask a question?
M'kay. What?
- What's the big fucking deal, bitch?
- Yeah.
Now I wanna know where you heard
these horrific obscenities, m'kay?
Nowhere.
We heard them from Mr. Garrison
a few times before.
- Yeah.
- Boys, I seriously doubt
that Mr. Garrison ever said,
"Eat penguin shit, you ass spelunker."
Sweet.
Thank you all for coming
on such short notice.
This just isn't like you, Stanley.
What did my son say, Mr. Mackey?
Did he say the "S" word?
- No, it was worse than that.
- The "F" word?
Well, here's a short list of the things
they've been saying, m'kay?
- Dear God!
- What the heck is a rim job?
Why that's when you put your legs
behind your head
and have someone lick your ass.
Young man, you will tell
Mr. Mackey this instant
where you heard
all these horrible phrases!
I... I...
We can't tell you.
We all took a sacred oath
and swore ourselves to secrecy.
- It was the Terrance and Phillip movie.
- Dude!
What? Fuck you guys!
I wanna get out of here!
Terrance and Phillip?
Those Canadians?
Excuse me,
what the heck is Terrance and Phillip?
Terrance and Phillip are two very
untalented actors from Canada.
Nothing but foul language
and toilet humor.
Well, I guess I'll have to send
a warning letter out to parents
before more children
see Terrance and Phillip.
- Everybody's fucking seen it!
- Eric!
I'm sorry, I can't help myself.
That movie has warped
my fragile little mind.
There's the girl that I like
Over there laughing
with that smart new...
You're holding up
the goddamn lunch line!
- Hello there, children.
- Hey, Chef.
- How's it going?
- Bad.
- Why bad?
- We got busted for swearing.
Our moms say we can't ever see
the Terrance and Phillip movie again!
That's too bad.
You should've seen Kyle
when his mom showed up.
He was scared out of his mind.
- Shut up, Cartman!
- No, dude. I'd be scared, too.
Your mom's a fucking bitch.
Don't call my mom a bitch, you fat fuck!
Don't call me fat,
you butt-fucking son of a bitch!
Whoa, children,
where did you learn to talk like that?
It's pretty fucking sweet, huh?
Chef, how do you make a woman
like you more than any other guy?
That's easy.
- You just gotta find the clitoris.
- Huh?
What does that mean,
"Find the clitoris"?
Forget I said anything.
Move along, children,
you're holding up the line.
You guys, do you know
where I can find the clitoris?
The what?
What, is that like finding Jesus
or something?
Attention, students.
We are now enforcing a new dress code
at South Park Elementary.
Terrance and Phillip shirts
are no longer allowed in school.
Anyone wearing
a Terrance and Phillip shirt
is to be sent home immediately.
- Hooray!
The R-rated Canadian film
Asses of Fire
is number one at the box office.
But is the film
destroying American youth?
Here with a special report
is a midget in a bikini.
Thanks, Tom. It appears that the effects
of the Canadian comedy
are far-reaching indeed.
All over America,
children seem to be influenced,
like at this spelling bee in Washington.
All right. This is for the silver medal.
Spell "forensics."
Fuck that! Why should I fucking
have to spell "forensics"?
- Yeah.
Here you go. S-U-C-K-M-Y-A-S-S.
Forensics.
Tom, the devastating impact
of the Canadian duo
can also be seen with their new hit song
Shut Your Fucking Face, Uncle Fucka.
Shut your fucking face, uncle fucka
You're a boner-biting bastard
Uncle fucka
Thought I told you that
we won't stop
- Back to you, Tom.
- Thanks, midget.
Shocking report.
The controversy began in the small
mountain town of South Park
where the local PTA
is trying to ban the movie.
With us tonight is the head of the PTA,
Sheila Broflovski.
- Hello, Tom.
- And the Canadian Minister of Movies.
Thanks for having me, buddy.
Minister, parents are concerned
about your country's entertainment.
Your thoughts?
Well, the film is R-rated
and is not intended for children.
But of course children are gonna see it!
Can I finish?
The fact is that we Canadians
are quite surprised by your outrage.
- You just don't care!
- Can I finish? Hello? Can I finish?
The United States has graphic violence
on television all the time.
We can't believe that a movie
with some foul language
would piss you off so much.
- Because it's evil!
- Can I finish? Please! Can I finish?
Okay, I'm finished.
But, Mr. Minister, it isn't like this film
is the first troublesome thing
to come out of Canada.
Let us not forget Bryan Adams.
Now, now. The Canadian government
has apologized
for Bryan Adams on several occasions.
You Canadians are all the same,
with your beady little eyes
and fiapping heads!
- You're trash.
- I resent that! I find that racist!
Our children are now addicted
to your filth!
You are a racist, ma'am.
You are a racist.
It is going to take us weeks
to erase the damage
this film has done to our children!
Kids, I wanna welcome you
to rehabilitation, m'kay?
Your mothers insisted that you be taken
from your normal schoolwork
and placed into rehab
to learn not to swear.
I must say, I don't think I belong
with these rogues.
I attended school at Yardale
and had a 4.0 grade point average.
You're a fucking faggot, dude.
M'kay. You see, children?
This is exactly what I'm talking about.
We have to get you off of foul language.
- How are we gonna do that?
- Well, listen here.
There are times
when you get suckered in
By drugs and alcohol
and sex with women, m'kay?
But it's when you do these things
too much
That you've become an addict
and must get back in touch
You can do it
It's all up to you, m'kay?
With a little plan
you can change your life today
You don't have to spend your life
addicted to smack
Homeless on the streets
giving hand-jobs for crack
Follow my plan
and very soon you will say
"It's easy, m'kay?"
Step one, instead of "ass" say "buns"
Like "Kiss my buns"
or "You're a buns-hole"
Step two, instead of "shit" say "poo"
As in "bull-poo," "poo-head"
and "This poo is cold"
Step three, with "bitch" drop the "T"
'Cause"bich' is Latin for "generosity"
Step four, don't say "fuck" anymore
'Cause "fuck" is the worst word
that you can say
So just use the word "m'kay"
We can do it
It's all up to us, m'kay?
M'kay
With a little plan
we can change our lives today
You can change it today
You don't have to spend your life
shooting up in the trash
Homeless on the streets
giving hand-jobs for cash
Follow this plan
and very soon you will say
"It's easy, m'kay?"
- Step one
- Instead of "ass" say "buns"
- Like "Kiss my buns"
- Or "You're a buns-hole"
- Step two
- Instead of "shit" say "poo"
- As in "bull-poo"
- "Poo-head"
And "This poo is cold"
- Step three
- With "bitch" drop the "T"
'Cause"bich' is Latin for "generosity"
- Step four
- Don't say "fuck" anymore
'Cause "fuck" is the worse word
that you can say
"Fuck" is the worse word
we shouldn't say "fuck"
No, we shouldn't say "fuck," fuck, no!
You're cured, you can go
You don't have to spend your life
shooting up in the trash
Homeless on the streets
giving hand-jobs for cash
Follow this plan
and very soon you will say
"It's easy, m'kay?"
It's easy, m'kay?
- It's easy, m'kay?
- It's easy
It's easy
It's easy, m'kay?
M'kay. M'kay.
Now you're cured.
You can take the rest of the afternoon
off for personal reflection, m'kay?
Find your own constructive way
to better yourself, m'kay?
Well, Phillip,
I hope you've learned something
through this whole experience.
I did, Terrance. I learned that you are
a boner-biting dick-fart fuck-face.
Want to see the northern lights?
You burned yourself to death
by lighting your fart!
I sure did, Phillip.
Uncle fucker! Too tight!
Man, that movie gets better
every time I see it.
- Hey!
- Yeah, but you know what?
That whole part about
lighting farts is bullshit.
You can't do that.
No way!
Okay, Kenny, I'll bet you $100
you can't light a fart on fire!
- Holy shit, dude!
- Oh, my God!
Oh, shit! Oh, shit!
- Somebody do something!
- This stick is on fire!
- Oh, my God, you killed Kenny!
- You bastard!
Well, I guess you can light
a fart on fire, huh?
Load that IV with 70 cc's of
sodium pentothal!
- We just called the parents.
- Oh, shit, dude!
Now our moms
are gonna find out we went
to the Terrance and Phillip movie again!
Vacuum!
Try to untangle his trachea
and esophagus.
- Dude!
- No, that doesn't go there!
- Gross, Stan!
- That's sick.
- Watch his liver.
- I'll get it.
We have precious little time left,
people.
We're gonna lose him soon.
- Doctor, his heart stopped!
- Let's get it out of there.
We need to zap this quick!
- Who's making a potato?
- My bad, sir. I missed lunch.
Damn it! I'm not gonna lose this kid!
Close him up. We've done all we can.
The rest is up to God.
Kenny? Kenny, can you hear me?
How are you feeling, son?
Great. Son, I have some bad news.
We accidentally replaced your heart
with a baked potato.
You have about three seconds to live.
Fucking weak, dude!
- Oh, my God, they killed Kenny!
- You bastards!
Damn it! It never gets any easier!
I bet him he couldn't do it.
I bet him $100.
Come on, Cartman, it's not your fault.
No, I know. I'm just fucking stoked
I don't have to pay him.
That's real nice!
He was your friend, you fat fuck!
So, boys, you saw that movie again?
- Yes.
- Well, Kyle, I have had it!
You are grounded for
the next two weeks!
- Grounded?
- And you, Stan. Come on.
And you're grounded
for three weeks, Eric.
Why am I grounded more?
That's fucking bullshit!
What? What? What?
What was that word, young man?
Little boy at peace
What is this place beyond the stars?
Open up your eyes
What are these things
you're moving toward?
Head so full of wonder
worries in the past
Could it be that you are free at last?
No!
Little boy, you're going to hell!
You said bad words
Threw rocks at the birds
And now this is your hotel
You ain't going back
This ain't Disneyland, it's hell!
Little boy, it's time for you to pay
For hurting that bird
and not going to church
And staring at boobs every day
Thought you were in bed
Instead, you're in hell!
Hell isn't good, hell isn't good
Hell!
Hey, fuck-face, have you seen Gracie?
There is orderliness in the universe.
Hell isn't good, hell isn't good
No!
Parents, our children are out of control!
This is what happens when toilet humor
is allowed to run rampant!
That's right. Kenny set himself on fire
because he saw Terrance and Phillip
do it in that dirty movie!
We must stop dirty language
from getting to our childrers ears!
We must go fight the source of it!
But what is the source?
That's easy.
Times have changed
Our kids are getting worse
They won't obey their parents
They just want to fart and curse
Should we blame the government?
Or blame society?
Or should we blame the images on TV?
No! Blame Canada!
Blame Canada!
With all their beady little eyes
and fiapping heads so full of lies
Blame Canada! Blame Canada!
We need to form a full assault
It's Canada's fault!
Don't blame me for my son Stan
He saw the darn cartoon
and now he's off to join the Klan
And my boy Eric once
had my picture on his shelf
But now when I see him
he tells me to fuck myself
Well, Blame Canada! Blame Canada!
It seems that everything's gone wrong
since Canada came along
Blame Canada! Blame Canada!
They're not even a real country anyway
My son could've been a doctor
or a lawyer rich and true
Instead, he burned up like a piggy
on a barbecue
Should we blame the matches?
Should we blame the fire?
Or the doctors who allowed him
to expire?
Heck, no!
Blame Canada! Blame Canada!
With all their hockey hullabaloo
And that bitch Anne Murray, too
Blame Canada! Shame on Canada!
For
The smut we must stop
The trash we must bash
The laughter and fun must all be undone
We must blame them and cause a fuss
Before somebody thinks of blaming us!
All right, you turds, listen up!
Your moms are away at a meeting
and they put me in charge of you!
But you're still grounded,
so you're not allowed to have any fun!
- Any questions?
- Shelly, where's the clitoris?
Now you all just sit there
and keep your mouths shut
while I go listen
to my Britney Spears records.
Okay, it's clear.
Our next guests have the number one
movie in the world right now.
Please welcome Terrance and Phillip!
Hooray!
- Hello, Conan.
- Hello, Brooke Shields.
Now, guys, some people claim
that your Canadian humor
is nothing but immature fart jokes.
That's not true. Take this classic
Canadian joke, for instance.
- Excuse me, Terrance.
- Yes, Phillip?
Gosh darn it!
- Good one, Phillip. Cheers.
- Cheers, fuck-face.
Guys, you can't say that on TV.
Now Terrance smells like my ass!
I farted once on the set of Blue Lagoon.
So, guys, does it make you nervous
to be in America?
There are a lot of organizations here
that want you arrested for
destroying children.
- They'd have to find us first.
- You're right.
Now!
Terrance and Phillip,
Mothers Against Canada
is placing you under citizens arrest!
- Mom?
- Dude, what the hell is going on?
We have a court order for your arrest!
Phillip, we've been ambushed!
Here you go, Conan.
This little scrotum sucker deceived us!
- You are a bad man!
- Don't listen to them, Conan!
You loved our movie, Conan!
We watched it together!
- Remember? You laughed!
- What have I done?
Holy crap! Did you see that?
They arrested Terrance and Phillip!
As the Canadian Ambassador,
I hereby condemn the actions
taken by America
in apprehending Terrance and Phillip.
As you can see from this graph,
the entire economy of Canada
relies on Terrance and Phillip!
Without them,
we are doomed to recession.
What say you,
Mr. American Ambassador?
- Fuck Canada!
- Hey, fuck you, buddy!
Terrance and Phillip
will not be released!
They're going to be put on trial for
corrupting America's youth.
We don't know
what all the fuss is about.
The fuss is aboot taking our citizens!
It's aboot not censoring our art!
It's aboot... It's aboot...
What's so goddamn funny?
Nothing, nothing.
Could you tell us again what your
argument is all about?
This is not aboot diplomacy,
this is aboot dignity!
This is aboot respect!
This is aboot realizing that humor...
You guys are dicks!
Release Terrance and Phillip
or we'll give you something
to cry aboot!
Pilot to bombardier. Pilot to bombardier.
We're nearing the target.
The bomb's ready, buddy.
Baldwin residence.
No, this is Billy Baldwin.
If you want Daniel Baldwin,
call his extension, stupid!
Hey, Alec, do you know
what sucks about being a Baldwin?
- No, what?
- Nothing! Yeah!
You missed me!
All right, children,
your mothers are all making me
throw away my lesson plan
and teach theirs.
Mr. Garrison, how come our moms
arrested Terrance and Phillip?
- Yeah!
- That's gay.
Well, your moms are just upset.
They're probably all on their
periods or something.
Mr. Garrison, Wendy and I think
that was a sexist statement.
Well, I'm sorry, Wendy,
but I just don't trust anything that
bleeds for five days and doesn't die.
Anyway, children,
let's start off with some vocabulary.
- Attention, students!
- What now?
Come to the gymnasium immediately
for a special announcement, m'kay?
- What's going on, Chef?
- Something big, children.
Chef, I can't find the clitoris.
You have to help me.
Stan, the clitoris...
Please take your seats, everyone.
They're about to announce it, m'kay?
This is a state of emergency.
We go now to the White House
for an announcement
from the President of the United States.
My fellowAmericans,
at 5:00 a.m. Today,
a day which will live in infamy,
the Canadians have bombed
the Baldwins.
In response to this,
the U.S. has declared war on Canada.
- Oh, no!
- War?
- No, Gregory! No!
- This is bad, Wendy. Hold on to me.
All the Baldwins are dead?
Now it is the time for us to send
a message to Canadians.
In two days time,
the war criminals Terrance and Phillip
will be executed.
They're gonna kill them?
And now I'd like to bring up my newly
appointed Secretary of Offense,
Ms. Sheila Broflovski.
Holy shit, dude!
My fellow Americans,
our neighbor to the north
has abused us for the last time!
- I have a plan...
- The Canadians want to fight us
because we won't tolerate
their potty mouths!
Well, if it is war they want,
then war they shall have!
- Dude, this is fucking weak.
- How could things be any worse?
Fallen one, I am Satan.
I am your god now.
There is no escape.
Now, feel the delightful pain.
Hey, Satan, did you hear the news?
A war just broke out up on Earth.
Meet Saddam Hussein,
my new partner in evil.
Move over, Satan,
you're hogging all the fun.
Yeah! Yeah!
Man, this is getting me so hot!
Saddam, would you let me
do my job, please?
Come on, rub my nipples
while I torture this little piggy!
Saddam, could I talk to you
over here for a second?
I don't see why you have to belittle me
in front of people like that.
Relax, guy!
Well, sometimes I think you don't have
any respect for me.
Hey, come here, guy.
- Who's my cream puff?
- I am.
That's right, buddy.
- Dude, I don't want to be at war.
- You don't think they're really
gonna kill Terrance and Phillip,
do you?
Kyle, you need to stop
being such a chicken shit
and stand up to your mother.
You need to smack her
in the face and say,
"That's enough of your shit,
you fucking bitch!"
Don't call my mom a bitch, Cartman!
You guys stop it! This isn't helping!
We've gotta think here!
Now, let's see,
what would Brian Boitano do?
Yeah, what would Brian Boitano do?
Hey, what's going on over there?
The American government thinks
it has the right to police the world.
Your government is going
to kill two Canadian citizens,
an action condemned by the U.N.
Home of the free, indeed.
- Let's play tetherball.
- Yeah.
This is about freedom of speech!
About censorship!
Can't you guys be more political
like Gregory?
There's the girl that I like
Now it appears
that she likes another guy
It must be because
he's political and stuff
I bet I could be political, too
What do you think, Stan?
- Damn it!
- You guys, this is all Kyle's mom's fault!
Shut up, Cartman!
Kyle's mom is the one
that started that damn club,
and all because
she's a big, fat, stupid...
Don't say it, Cartman!
Well...
Don't do it, Cartman!
- I'm warning you!
- Okay. Okay.
I'm getting pretty sick of
him calling my mom...
well, Kyle's mom's a bitch
She's a big fat witch
She's the biggest bitch
in the whole wide world
She's a stupid bitch
if there ever was a bitch
She's a bitch to all the boys and girls
Shut your fucking mouth, Cartman!
On Monday she's a bitch
On Tuesday she's a bitch
And wednesday through Saturday
she's a bitch
Then on Sunday, just to be different
She's a super
King Kamehameha bitch!
Come on, you all know the words!
Have you ever met
my friend Kyle's mom?
She's the biggest bitch
in the whole wide world
She's a mean old bitch
and she has stupid hair
She's a bitch, bitch, bitch, bitch
Bitch, bitch, bitch, bitch
She's a stupid bitch
Kyle's mom's a bitch
and she's just a dirty bitch
Talk to kids around the world
It might go a little bit
something like this
Have you ever met
my friend Kyle's mom?
She's the biggest bitch
in the whole wide world
She's a mean old bitch
and she has stupid hair
She's a bitch, bitch, bitch, bitch
Bitch, bitch, bitch, bitch, bitch
She's a stupid bitch
Cartman...
Kyle's mom's a bitch
and she's just a dirty bitch
I really mean it
Kyle's mom
She's a big fat fucking bitch
Big, old, fat fucking bitch, Kyle's mom
Yeah!
What?
Fuck.
Okay, everyone settle down.
As we continue to send troops
into Canada,
M.A.C. is also fighting the war
against potty mouths here at home!
Here to present the V-Chip
is Dr. Vosknocker.
The machinery of the V-Chip
is very simple.
It is placed under the child's skin
where it emits a small shock
of electricity
whenever an obscenity is uttered.
Now, wait a minute.
This chip somehow knows
if the child is swearing?
It's just like a lie detector.
You see, certain things happen to you
when you swear,
just like when you lie.
The chip picks up on this
and gives the subject a little prick.
Patient B5,
would you step out here, please?
Patient B5 here has been fitted
with the new V-Chip.
- My head hurts.
- Don't worry about that.
Now I want you to say "doggy."
- Doggy.
- Notice that nothing happens.
- Now say "Montana."
- Montana.
Good! Now, "pillow."
- Pillow.
- All right.
Now I want you to say "horse fucker."
Go ahead, Eric. It's all right.
Horse...
That hurt, goddamn... Fuck!
Now I'd like you to say
"big floppy donkey dick."
- No!
- Success!
The child doesn't want to swear!
This isn't fair, you sons of bitches!
We will start putting V-Chips
in all our children next week!
Snacky Smores presents
The March of War.
Let's hear it for our boys in blue.
President Clinton
has called them to action
to fight the evil Canadian scourge.
A full-scale attack
has been launched on Toronto
after the Canadians' last bombing
which took a horrible toll
on the Arquette family.
For security measures,
our great American government
is rounding up all citizens
that have any Canadian blood
and putting them into camps.
All Canadian-American
citizens are to report
to one of these death camps right away.
Did I say death camps?
I meant happy camps,
where you will eat the finest meals,
have access to fabulous doctors
and be able to exercise regularly.
Meanwhile,
the war criminals Terrance and Phillip
are prepped for their execution.
Their execution will take place
during a fabulous USO show!
With special guests celebrities,
including Big Gay Al and winona Ryder!
Of course,
the only way to see the USO show
is to sign up for the army!
So join the army
and kill some Canadian scum
as we continue the march of war!
We must rid ourselves
of anything Canadian!
Bomb them!
Dude, don't you like
Terrance and Phillip anymore?
Course not! My mommy says
I hate Canadians now 'cause they
made me have a dirty mouth!
Burn it all!
- Hey, dudes.
- What's the matter, Cartman?
It's this V-Chip. I hate it.
I can't say any dirty words.
- Really? So you can't say "fuck"?
- No.
- And you can't say "shit"?
So you can't say, "I'm Eric Cartman,
"the fattest fucking piece of shit
in the world"?
- Fuck you...
- Sweet.
Come on, you guys.
This has gone far enough.
It's time we talked to our moms.
We're supposed to be grounded
in our rooms.
Come on, Kyle,
it's time for us to get political.
Canada will no longer corrupt
our children!
- Mom, can I talk to you for a second?
- Kyle, what are you doing here?
You are grounded!
Now get back to the house
and stay there!
You too, Stanley!
Mom, we think you're going too far.
You can't kill Terrance and Phillip.
We must fight for
our children's futures...
You started a war! You have to stop it!
...to make them safe again!
- Hello?
- Our children are precious!
- Hello!
- We must make a stand now!
Stop at nothing!
I told you my mom wouldn't listen.
Well, then we're just gonna have to
save Terrance and Phillip ourselves!
- What?
- Think about it, you guys.
What would Brian Boitano do?
He'd figure out a way
to rescue Terrance and Phillip
before they're executed.
We can't do anything.
Our moms' organization is too strong.
Well, then, we'll round up
all the grounded kids in town
and start our own organization.
An organization to help save
Terrance and Phillip.
Hey, yeah, our own secret club!
- I guess that could work.
- We have to try.
What would Brian Boitano do
if he was here right now?
He'd make a plan
and he'd follow through
That's what Brian Boitano would do
when Brian Boitano was in
the Olympics skating for the gold
He did two salchows and a triple Lutz
while wearing a blindfold
When Brian Boitano was in the Alps
fighting grizzly bears
He used his magical fire breath
and saved the maidens fair
So what would Brian Boitano do
if he were here today?
I'm sure he'd kick and ass or two
That's what Brian Boitano would do
I want this V-Chip out of me
It has stunted my vocabulary
And I just want my mom
to stop fighting everyone
For wendy I'll be an activist, too
'Cause that's what Brian Boitano
would do
what would Brian Boitano do?
He'd call all the kids in town
And tell them to unite for truth
That's what Brian Boitano would do
- Did someone say my name?
- Who are you?
- I'm Brian Dennehy.
- What?
- No, not fucking Brian Dennehy!
- Yeah. Get the fuck out of here!
Bye.
When Brian Boitano
traveled through time
To the year 3010
He fought the evil robot king
and saved the human race again
And when Brian Boitano
built the pyramids
He beat up Kublai Khan
'Cause Brian Boitano doesn't take shit
from anybody
So let's call all the kids together
and unite to stop our moms
And we'll save Terrance and Phillip, too
'Cause that's what Brian Boitano
would do
And we'll save Terrance and Phillip, too
'Cause that's what Brian Boitano
would do
Hey, relax, guy.
There's nothing on.
You just get cranky when you're tired,
that's all.
I'm not cranky.
What started as a spat between
the United States and Canada
is quickly turning into world War III!
World War III?
Terrance and Phillip
are going to be put to death
for crimes against humanity.
The time of execution...
It has come to be.
The four horsemen are drawing nigh!
The time of prophecy is upon us!
I love when you get all biblical, Satan.
You know exactly how to turn my crank.
No, I'm being serious.
It is the seventh sign.
- What?
- Behold.
The first signs of my reign
have all come true.
The fall of an empire,
the coming of a comet,
and now, when the blood of these
Canadians touches American soil,
it will be our time to rise.
Yeah. Yeah, man! I'm getting so hot!
Let's fuck!
Do you always think about sex?
I'm talking about
very important stuff here!
I'm just excited about
taking over the world! Come on!
Is sex the only thing that matters to you?
I love you.
I want to believe that.
So what do you say we shut off that light
and get close, huh?
Yeah, you like that, don't you, bitch?
Okay. We can use my dad's computer
to call all the kids together.
Wait. Before we put a message out,
do a search on the word "clitoris."
Okay.
Found eight million pages
with the word "clitoris."
Wow!
I'll just try the first one.
"You must be 18 to enter this website."
Okay.
"Welcome to German sick fetish video."
"If you are under 18 do not..." Okay.
Dude, it's a lady getting pooed on!
- Whoa! Is it Cartman's mom?
- Very funny.
Hey! It is Cartman's mom!
All righty then.
Son of a bitch...
Get out of here, Ike.
You're too young for this stuff.
Bullshit.
What's she doing now?
Okey-dokey.
Click it off, dude! Click it off!
Dude, what the fuck is wrong
with German people?
All right. All right.
Let's just do what we came here to do
and put a message out to kids!
Okay. Let's see. I've gotta put out
an all-access e-mail.
Goddamn, your mom sucks, Cartman.
Just get to the message board!
I'm trying. I can't find a Canadian server.
I've got to break into the mainframe.
Damn it, they've got an access code!
I'll try to reroute the encryptions.
Okay. Here we go.
"Want to help Terrance and Phillip?"
- Tell them we'll have punch and pie.
- We're not gonna have punch and pie!
More people will come
if they think we have punch and pie!
"This is top secret. The password is..."
La Résistance.
And so the draft will begin tomorrow
as more and more troops are needed
to invade the Canadian border.
The Canadian government pleads
for a peaceful resolution,
but naturally we're not listening.
Good night, hon.
Mom, when is the war gonna be over?
I don't know, hon. Soon, we hope.
You want it to end quickly, huh?
- Mom?
- Yes, hon?
If you were in a German Scheiße video,
you'd tell me, right?
Sure, hon. Good night.
There's a ghost!
Kenny, is that you?
Satan! Satan is coming here?
Saddam Hussein?
That doesn't make sense, Kenny!
- Eric, what is it?
- I saw him! I saw Kenny!
You poor dear.
You've been through so much.
I bet him he couldn't light a fart on fire
and now he's all pissed off!
I can't say "pissed off"?
The execution of Terrance and Phillip
is imminent.
Soon, Saddam and I will rule the world.
Hi, Satan. I got some new luggage
for our trip up to Earth.
Let's fuck to celebrate.
What's it like up on Earth, Saddam?
Tell me about it again.
Let's not talk. Let's get busy.
Do you remember
when you first got here?
We used to talk all night long
until the sun came up.
We would just lie in bed and talk.
Well, yeah, 'cause I was still waiting
to get you in bed, dummy!
How come you always wanna
make love to me from behind?
Is it because you want to pretend
I'm somebody else?
Satan, your ass is gigantic and red.
Who am I gonna pretend you are,
Liza Minnelli?
Don't get all pissy!
Sometimes I think
When I look up real high
That there's such a big world up there
I'd like to give it a try
But then I sink
'Cause it's here I'm supposed to stay
But I get so lonely down here
Tell me why's it have to be that way
Up there, there is so much room
Where babies burp and fiowers bloom
Everyone dreams
I can dream, too
Up there
Up where the skies are ocean blue
I could be safe and live without a care
Up there
They say I don't belong
I must stay below alone
Because of my beliefs I'm supposed to
stay where evil is sown
But what is evil anyway?
Is there reason to the rhyme?
Without evil there could be no good
So it must be good
to be evil sometimes
Up there, there is so much room
Where babies burp and fiowers bloom
Everyone dreams
I can dream, too
Up there
Up where the skies are ocean blue
I could be safe and live without a care
Live without a care
If only I could live up there
I wanna live
I want to live up there!
- You're late, Cartman!
- I had to ride my bike here.
- My behind is killing me!
- Your behind?
I have to say "behind"
'cause I get shocked if I say "ass"...
- Did you bring the punch and pie?
- No, you guys, something happened.
- I don't think Kenny's dead.
- What?
I saw him in my room.
I know, Cartman, I know.
I see Kenny every day.
- You do?
- Sure, dude, on the face of every child.
On the smile of every baby.
Hey, I'm telling you, this was Kenny!
He said that if Terrance and Phillip die,
Saddam Hussein and Satan
are gonna come up and rule the world!
Saddam Hussein?
- Who is it?
- I'm here for la Résistance.
- What's the password?
- I don't know.
- Guess.
- Bacon.
Okay.
Oh, no, it's that kid!
- This is the place.
- Wendy?
Stan? You started la Résistance?
Well, apparently you're more political
than we thought.
Let us get this meeting underway.
There are others coming.
Wow, a lot of people showed up.
Okay.
Terrance and Phillip
are supposed to be killed,
and we think that sucks ass!
Yes?
We were to understand
there'd be pie and punch.
There isn't any.
Terrance and Phillip
are supposed to be killed,
so we think we should prank call
a bunch of policemen
and have pizza sent to them
that they didn't order!
- May I?
- What?
Terrance and Phillip
are currently being held
at a Canadian internment camp
two kilometers outside of town.
They're to be executed tomorrow during
a star-studded USO show
for the troops.
Tomorrow?
Once the show begins,
we should have about one hour
to get Terrance and Phillip
out of their cell
and into this clearing.
There, we will all rendezvous
and, together,
take Terrance and Phillip
safely back to Canada.
Wow, dude, Wendy's new guy is smart.
You must all meet me at the rendezvous
point at precisely 10:00 p.m.
Sneaking into the show and breaking out
Terrance and Phillip
will be the most dangerous part,
so I'll go myself.
No! We're going!
We started la Résistance.
We'll get Terrance and Phillip
and meet you at the rendezvous point.
This will be very dangerous.
Are you quite sure?
Fuck that!
Cartman, do you want
that V-Chip in you forever?
We're going.
Now let's run through the plan.
Oh, boy! Military action, Ned!
Let's kill us
some goddamn Australians!
I think we're fighting Canadians.
Canadians, Australians,
what's the difference?
Yeah. This uniform makes me feel
like a tough, brute man, Mr. Hat.
It sure does, Mr. Garrison.
Oh, boy, I can't wait for
our first shore leave
so I can get me some fucking poontang.
Pay attention!
Tomorrow night is the USO show
for all you troops!
There will be celebrities, followed by
the execution of Terrance and Phillip.
After the show, we will finally be
sending ground troops into Canada.
So let's strategize.
Map!
Our sources have told us
that the Canadians
are preparing for our invasion,
so we must use caution.
Each battalion has
a specific code name and mission.
Battalion Five, raise your hands.
You will be the all-important
first attack wave,
which we will call
Operation Human Shield.
Hey, wait a minute!
Now keep in mind, Operation Human
Shield will suffer heavy losses.
Battalion Fourteen?
Right. You are
Operation Get Behind the Darkies.
You will follow Battalion Five here.
And try not to get killed, for God's sake.
Are there any questions, men?
Yes, soldier?
Have you ever heard of
the Emancipation Proclamation?
I don't listen to hip-hop.
After that, we will march
into the heart of Canada and we will...
I'm coming to get you!
What's wrong with this thing?
It's fucking Windows 98!
Get Bill Gates in here!
You told us Windows 98 would be faster
and more efficient
with better access to the Internet.
It is faster. Over five million...
All right, men, get lots of rest
and prepare to go into Canada!
After you have Terrance and Phillip,
quietly make your way to this ridge.
We will be waiting for you there.
We cannot wait for long,
so if you're not there at 10:00,
we'll have to leave.
- Got you.
- You are indeed brave,
but you will need help from someone
who's done this sort of thing before.
- Here's the address of The Mole.
- The Mole?
He is an expert in covert operations.
A mercenary for hire.
Your first task will be obtaining him.
Get lots of sleep.
Tomorrow, we will all be
risking our lives for freedom.
God has smiled upon you this day
The fate of a nation in your hands
And blessed be the children
Who fight with all our bravery
Till only the righteous stand
You see the distant flames
They bellow in the night
You fight in all our names
for what we know is right
And when you all get shot
and cannot carry on
Though you die, la Résistance lives on
You may get stabbed in the head
with a dagger or a sword
You may be burned to death
or skinned alive or worse
But when they torture you
you will not feel the need to run
For though you die
la Résistance lives on
Blame Canada! Blame Canada!
Because the country's gone awry
Tomorrow night these freaks will fry!
Tomorrow night, our lives will change
Tomorrow night, we'll be entertained
An execution
What a sight
Tomorrow night
Up there, there is so much room
Where babies burp and fiowers bloom
Tomorrow night, up there is doomed
And so I will be going soon
Shut your fucking face, uncle fucka
You're a boner-biting bastard
Uncle fucka
Looks like we may be out of luck
Tomorrow night, we're pretty fucked
Why did our mothers start this war?
What the fuck are they fighting for?
When did this song
become a marathon?
- I want to be up there...
- When Canada is dead and gone
There'll be no more Celine Dion!
They might cut your dick in half
and serve it to a pig
And though it hurts
you'll laugh and dance a dickless jig
But that's the way it goes
In war, you're shat upon
- Though we die...
- I want to be up there...
...la Résistance lives on!
Blame Canada! Blame Canada!
- Tomorrow night!
Oh, boy, I'm so excited!
Just one more day
until we can take over the world.
I don't know if I can sleep,
if you know what I mean.
This book is really interesting.
It talks about how people
communicate differently.
Like, I communicate by wanting you
to ask me questions, and you...
Hey, that is interesting! Let's fuck!
Saddam, I'm trying to have
a nice conversation with you.
Hey, Satan.
Now that is just not appropriate!
Come on, I'm just fucking with you!
It's not real!
- Well, that is still not appropriate.
- Hey, daddy.
It's not real, either! Come on, guy!
Soon the world will belong to me!
It's Saddam,
he doesn't nurture my emotions.
He just wants sex
and can't learn to communicate.
You're right, I should leave him!
I'm just gonna tell him,
"Saddam,
I'm going to Earth to rule alone!"
I'm strong and I don't need him!
Today's the day for the USO show
we're so happy we get to go
I don't know but I've been told
Canadian pussy is mighty cold...
Ike, you have to stay in the attic
'cause if they find you,
they'll put you
in a Canadian concentration camp.
Don't worry, Ike,
we're gonna put an end to this.
And then I'll make Mom come home
and we'll all be a family again.
All of that is home.
- Hello?
- Hi. We need to speak with The Mole.
I'm sorry, The Mole is grounded.
He can't come out and play.
- What?
- He's a kid?
He said very naughty things about God.
Well, can we just talk to him
for five seconds, please?
Well, all right. Christophe?
Hi, we're gonna go rescue
Terrance and Phillip
from the USO show and...
- Who are you? Who sent you?
- That Gregory kid.
He said you could sneak us in.
Are you telling me that you intend to
break into the USO show,
filled with thousands of soldiers,
and break out Terrance and Phillip?
I thought it was a pretty stupid idea, too.
We're la Résistance!
We wanna save Terrance and Phillip
and stop the war and stuff.
I can't help you. I'm grounded
in my room for the next three days.
So are we.
Our parents think we're home right now.
Why are you grounded?
Why? Because God hates me,
that's why.
He has made my life miserable.
So I call him a cock-sucking asshole
and I get grounded.
- So will you help us?
- Very well.
Meet me in the backyard
in five minutes.
We'll show God that we're not gonna
fucking take any more...
- What? Christophe, get in here!
- Coming, Mother.
I must be strong. I must be strong.
Saddam, I need to talk to you.
You better get packing, bitch.
We have to go.
We're running out of time.
Saddam, sometimes you can love
a person very much,
but still know that they aren't
right for you.
What the fuck are you talking about?
You treat me like shit, Saddam!
I'm leaving you!
I'm going up to Earth to rule alone!
No. No, you can't do that!
- I'm sorry, but I have to be strong.
- Satan, please, give me another chance!
- I have to go to Earth!
- You don't even have respect for me!
Sure I do, guy. Please, just hear me out.
Some people say that I'm a bad guy
They may be right
But it's not as if I don't try
I just fuck up, try as I might
But I can change, I can change
I can learn to keep my promises
I swear it
I'll open up my heart and I will share it
Any minute now I will be born again
Yes, I can change, I can change
I know I've been a dirty little bastard
I like to kill, I like to maim
Yes, I'm insane, but it's okay
'cause I can change
It's not my fault that I'm so evil
It's society
Society
You see, my parents
were sometimes abusive
And it made a prick of me
But I can change, I can change
What if you remain
a sandy little butthole?
Satan, don't be such a twit
Mother Teresa won't have shit on me
Just watch
Just watch me change
Here I go
I'm changing
You see, I've really matured.
- All right.
- All right!
- Come on. We have to hurry.
- I love you.
Ladies and gentlemen
of the American Army,
welcome to the USO show!
Get ready for loads of entertainment
and fabulous celebrities,
followed immediately by the nasty
execution of Terrance and Phillip!
This is the USO show
where those military bitches
intend to kill Terrance and Phillip.
- Oh, my God!
- God?
He is the biggest bitch of them all.
We have to hurry. We rendezvous
with the other kids at 10:00.
You realize that by doing this,
we could be grounded for two,
perhaps even three weeks.
- We're willing to take that risk.
- Then let's go.
And now, here are your hosts
for the evening,
Sheila Broflovski and Big Gay Al!
Al, tonight is a very special night,
do you know why?
They're having a sale at Merv's?
No, because we're going to abolish
Canadian smut!
That's right, Sheila!
Bring out the condemned!
Today is a great day for democracy!
Phillip, this is worse than that night
I fell asleep
and you put your dick in my mouth
and took a picture!
I know, Terrance. I know.
Well, Sheila,
while you're getting set up over there,
let's bring out our first act,
Yippie the back-fiipping dog!
Be careful not to touch this wire.
Motherfucker...
Fuck...
Shit, the USO show has started!
We are running out of time!
Do you see Terrance and Phillip?
Yes, but they are heavily guarded.
We have to dig from here
so as not to be seen.
Come on, bitches.
Hey, Mole,
do you know where the clitoris is?
- The what?
- The clitoris.
I have to find the clitoris so I can
get this Wendy girl to like me again.
You need to stop thinking
with your dick!
You have to be on your toes
because I am not going to be
grounded again!
Not for you. Not for anybody.
Men, when you're out there
in the battlefield
and you're looking into the beady eyes
of a Canadian
as he charges you with his hockey stick
or whatever he has
and people are dying all around you,
just remember what the M.P.A.A. Says.
"Horrific, deplorable violence is okay,
"as long as people don't say
any naughty words!"
That is what this war is all about!
What?
Shit!
Move, move!
Okay. We will split up here.
Let's synchronize watches.
- We don't have watches.
- You don't have watches?
Dude, you didn't say
anything about watches!
What do you think this is, kid?
TV kiddie-hour where we all sit around
and lick Barney
the dinosaur's fucking pussy, huh?
This is real life, with consequences
you take to the grave!
- Dude, we don't have watches.
- Shit! Did you bring the mirror?
- Got it!
- And the rope?
- Check.
- And the buttfor?
- What's a buttfor?
- For pooping, silly.
Now, listen carefully.
I will dig under the stage,
and with that bedrock,
I will need more time.
Stan and Kyle, get near that stage
and stall the show any way you can.
Do whatever it takes
to keep that show going
- until I get to the prisoners.
- Okay.
Cartman,
over there is the electrical box.
You must sneak over there
and shut it off
before I return with Terrance and Phillip
or the alarms will sound
and I will be attacked by guard dogs.
- Got it?
- Okay.
You must shut off the alarms!
I fucking hate guard dogs!
I heard you the first time,
you British piece of shit.
If anything goes wrong,
make a sound like a dying giraffe.
What's a dying giraffe sound like?
- Okay.
- Let's go.
- Be careful, dude.
- Careful?
Was my mother careful
when she stabbed me in the heart
with a clothes hanger
while I was still in the womb?
Damn, dude. That kid is fucked up.
- How are those chairs coming, Sheila?
- Al, we're minutes away.
Super! In the meantime,
here's pint-size pixie and darling of
the indie movie scene, Winona Ryder!
Hi, guys.
I'm super psyched to be here today.
What you're doing
for our country is so cool.
I mean war, man. Wow. War, you know?
Wow.
Okay! And now for your enjoyment,
here's my famous ping-pong ball trick!
Oh, my!
"Shut off the power, Cartman.
This is very important, Cartman."
Dude, did you hear
what Winona Ryder's doing?
We can't miss this.
There, I didn't miss one!
That's my ping-pong ball trick!
Well, that's all the acts
we have for you tonight,
so let's just get on with the execution!
- Oh, no. We have to stall him.
- More! More!
Yeah, more!
You big sillies!
You want to see more of me?
Yeah! Big Gay Al! Big Gay Al!
Big Gay Al! Big Gay Al!
Well, I do have a little song
I wrote about the war.
But we haven't rehearsed.
- Sing it!
- Yeah, sing it!
- I can't.
- Sing the fucking song!
Well, all right, if you insist,
I'll sing my song.
I believe it goes a little bit like this.
Bombs are flying
People are dying
Children are crying
Politicians are lying, too
Cancer is killing
Texaco's spilling
The whole world's gone to hell
But how are you?
I'm super, thanks for asking
All things considered
I couldn't be better, I must say
I'm feeling super
No, nothing bugs me
Everything is super when you're...
Don't you think I look cute in this hat?
I'm so sorry, Mr. Cripple
But I just can't feel too bad
for you right now
Because I'm feeling
so insanely super
That even the fact that you can't walk
can't bring me down
He's super, thanks for asking
All things considered
he couldn't be better, he must say
I'm super
No, nothing bugs me
Everything is super when you're...
Don't you think I look cute in this hat?
These little pants
this matching tie that I got at Merv's
I'm super
In the barracks
and the trenches as well
- Stick 'em up!
- Big Gay Al says
- "Do ask, do tell"
- Skittles
Yes, he's super
and he's proud to be gay
Okay?
Everything is super when you're gay
When you're gay!
Again! Again!
Who's there?
Son of a gun! Heck!
They're coming?
But our moms won't listen to us!
Okay, everybody,
just wanna take a minute here
to thank all our wonderful sponsors
we had tonight on this USO show.
He's almost got them.
We are here to rescue you.
After I release you,
follow me through the tunnel.
- You guys! Seriously!
- What, Cartman?
Kenny! I saw Kenny again!
Did you shut the alarm off, Cartman?
Cartman?
Shit!
Hey, did you hear that?
Sounds like a giraffe is dying over there.
- Shit!
- A spy!
Get him!
Shit! Shit!
Oh, no!
Come on, Mole, come on!
Shit! Shit! Fucking guard dogs! Shit!
The alarms, they went off.
Yeah, that was my bad. Sorry.
Hold me. It's so very cold.
There is no hope now.
You must get out of here.
- We can't leave without you!
- It's okay, I'm done for.
No, we can't leave without you!
We don't know where the hell we are!
Where is your God
when you need him, huh?
Where is your beautiful,
merciful faggot now?
Here I come, God.
Here I come, you fucking rat.
Now the light, she fades
And darkness settles in
But I will find strength
No, Mole. Hang on.
I will find pride within
We'll get you home.
Because although I die
I can't face my mother.
Our freedom will be won
Not alone.
Though I die
La Résistance lives on
Shit!
Okay, folks, here it is,
the moment we've all been waiting for,
the execution!
The day is ours!
Oh, no, dude, it's happening!
We have to tell them
about Saddam Hussein and Satan!
No way, dude!
My mom can't see me here!
Kyle, you have to stand up
to your mother! Come on!
Gentlemen, do you have any last words?
Last words? Let's see. How's aboot...
Get me the fuck out of this chair!
How's that for last words?
All right, anonymous, ready the switch.
- Wait!
- Stanley!
- Eric!
- Kyle!
- Go on, dude, tell her.
- I can't.
You can't kill Terrance and Phillip.
If they die, Satan and Saddam Hussein
are gonna come take over the world!
Throw the switch, Mr. Garrison.
Hey, I'm supposed to be anonymous.
Goodbye, bastards!
No!
The Canadians are attacking!
Run for your lives!
Come on.
We have to shut off the power!
Fuck!
Hey, some little fat kid saved us!
Terrance and Phillip, wait!
We have to get you
to the rendezvous point!
Ned, behind you!
Be not afraid.
Oh, my God!
- Behold my glory.
- What are you?
I am the clitoris.
The clitoris? I did it! I found the clitoris!
Stan, you must not let
Terrance and Phillip's blood
be spilled on the ground.
Wait! You're supposed to tell me
how to get Wendy to like me.
There are more important matters
right now.
No way, dude! I looked all over for you
and now you have to tell me
how to get Wendy to like me!
Dude, you just have to have
confidence in yourself.
Believe in yourself
and others will believe in you.
Chicks love confidence. Now go, hurry!
The clitoris has spoken.
Stan! Stan, are you okay?
I see you failed in your mission.
I should not have sent a boy
to do a man's job.
Come on, everyone,
we've got precious little time.
Die, Canadian, m'kay?
- Did you hear that Terrance? I farted.
- You did? Just now?
Terrance and Phillip!
We have to get them
to the rendezvous point!
Hey, it's Mr. Garrison!
Children, take Mr. Hat.
Please, get him out of here.
Holy shit!
This V-Chip is getting all screwy!
Take cover in the trench!
All right, men! Human Shield up front,
then Operation Get Behind the Darkies.
Remember, Human Shield,
protect our tanks and planes, too!
Holy mother of Jehoshaphat!
Fire on my command!
All right, squad, just like I told you.
One, two...
Yousa people gonna die?
- Fire!
...three!
What in the...
- Great plan, Chef!
- Operation Human Shield, my ass!
My God, this is terrible!
This is what we wanted!
We wanted our children to be
brought up in a smut-free environment!
But we didn't want this!
Where are you going?
We're going to find our boys!
For God's sake, Sheila,
we're going to get them killed!
Kyle, all those times I said
you were a big, dumb Jew,
I didn't mean it. You're not a Jew.
Yes, I am! I am a Jew, Cartman!
No, no, Kyle,
don't be so hard on yourself.
What the hell am I still holding this for?
Mr. Hat! No!
Fuck this, dude. I'm getting out of here
before I get in really big trouble.
- I heard that.
- Stan!
Dude, I found the clitoris,
so now I think I can get Wendy
to like me again.
That's swell, Stan.
Yeah, I guess all's well
that ends well, huh?
We can go home now, you dipshit!
- What's wrong with this thing?
- Come on.
We can't let Terrance and Phillip die
or else the whole world's gonna end!
- Terrance, look!
- There they are!
Phillip, we're done for!
All right, men, fire!
Goodbye, Terrance.
- What is this?
- Don't shoot!
I'll take care of this.
Kids, get out of the way now!
- Kyle!
- I'm not gonna let you kill them, Mom!
What? What? What?
I'm not moving!
Stand down, children.
You can still see fart jokes
on Nickelodeon.
No! This is about more than fart jokes!
This is about freedom of speech,
about censorship and stuff.
What about Ike, huh, Mom?
Did you forget that your own
adopted son is Canadian?
I'm doing very important things.
But, Mom, you never took the time
to talk to me.
Whenever I get in trouble,
you go off and blame everybody else,
but I'm the one to blame. Deal with me.
You keep going off
and fighting all these causes,
but I don't want a fighter.
I want my mom.
Poor little fellow.
No!
Terrance!
- Holy shit, dude!
- Young man, you watch your mouth!
My time has come!
You are really fucked now!
It's Saddam Hussein! Shoot him!
What a dumbass!
You have spilled
the blood of the innocent!
Now begins two million years
of darkness!
Good job, Ms. Broflovski! Thanks a lot!
I was just trying to make the world
a better place for children.
Yeah, and you brought
enough intolerance
to the world to allow my coming.
Now, everyone bow down to me!
Bend over!
What have we done?
Saddam, I am the dark ruler, not you.
Relax, bitch.
You're better seen, not heard.
I can't.
Let's start by building a big statue of me
right over there
where that fat kid is standing.
Hey, don't call me fat, butt-fucker!
Yeah, Cartman, do it!
Damn! Shit!
Respect my fucking authority!
Yes!
Hey! You need to
watch your mouth, brat!
Dog shit taco!
Quick, Satan, do something!
Try this on for size.
Blood-drenched
frozen tampon Popsicle!
Hey, buddy, I know I was mean before,
but don't worry, I can change.
Okay.
Not!
Fuck, shit, cock, ass, titties, boner,
bitch, muff, pussy, cock, butthole,
Barbra Streisand!
What are you waiting for, bitch?
Destroy him.
Come on, you weak,
stupid come-bucket! Save me!
That's it!
I have had enough of you!
Hey, guy, relax!
He spent so much time convincing me
I was weak and stupid
that I believed it myself.
I have you to thank, little one.
You showed me
that I had to get away from him.
Just make any wish you want,
and I shall grant it.
- Are you sure, Kenny?
- What did he say?
He said that his wish is for everything
to go back to the way it was
before this horrible war.
Kenny, you realize that means
you'd go back, too?
Very well, then.
I will pull all my minions back.
I guess I'm destined to live in hell.
Alone.
Hello. What's this?
Hi, there, little guy.
Would you like to go to hell with me?
Sure. I bet we could be
best friends, Mr. Satan.
Feel free to come back and visit us
any time you want, Satan.
I just might do that.
Thank you, Kenny.
Yeah, thanks for going
back to hell for us.
You're a real pal.
Goodbye, you guys.
I'm alive. Where's Mr. Hat?
Wow! We were all dying
and now we're fine!
That's super!
What the fuck's going on?
You see, Mom? After all that,
it was Can'tmars filthy fucking mouth
that saved us all.
I'm sorry I didn't pay attention
to you, Kyle.
But, Wendy, what about Gregory?
Stan, I never really cared for Gregory.
- You didn't?
- No, dude. Fuck Gregory!
- Fuck him right in the ear!
- Thank you, clitoris.
Everything worked out
What a happy end
Americans and Canadians
are friends again
So let's all join hands
and knock oppression down
Good Lordy, I'm found
Don't you know our little lives
are now complete?
'Cause Terrance and Phillip are sweet
Super sweet!
Thank God we live in this quiet
Little, pissant, redneck
Podunk, jerkwater
Greenorn, one-horse
Mudhole, peckerwood
Right-wing, whistle-stop
Hobnail, truck-driving
Old-fashioned, hayseed
Inbred, unkempt
Out-of-date, out-of-touch, white-trash
Kick-ass, mountain
Town!
Look!
Guys, up there is Hodun.
Someone needs to stop Clearway Law.
Public shouldn't leave reviews for lawyers.