Downloaded from
YTS.MX
Official YIFY movies site:
- Hey! My purse!
- Hey! Hey!
- He's got my purse! Stop him!
- Come on.
Somebody stop him! He's got my purse!
Police! Freeze!
Hey! Stop! Out of my way!
Get out of my way!
Out of my way! Police! Move!
You did not just go down there...
What the fuck?
Fuck sakes.
Get your fucking hands in the air!
I ain't gonna say it again, motherfucker!
Fuck.
Hello, detective bozwick.
- I want to play a game.
- No!
The three train
is arriving in two minutes.
It is up to you to decide
if this will be your final stop.
You have taken
the witness stand many times,
and railroaded innocent people
with your lies,
putting them away in jail.
Today, it is you who will be railroaded.
You have one chance fo live.
Tear from your mouth the tongue
that has so often been used
fo lie and to decejve.
Take a leap of faith, and you will live.
Only your weight will rip away
your lying tongue and save you.
Live or die, make your choice.
What you talking about?
That movie woh awards.
You know, Tom Hanks
is a straight pimp, man,
but I don't know if you could
make that movie today.
What the fuck you going on about?
- Special needs abuse.
- Special needs?
- What, you woke now?
- Not woke,
but you can't say "handicapped,"
you can't say "retarded."
You got to say "special needs,"
I'm trying to be respectful.
Forrest Gump was special needs, man.
What was the name of the girl?
- Jenny.
He did everything for Jenny.
This motherfucker did some shit.
He jogged across the whole country.
He beat China in ping-pong.
You know how fucking hard that shit is?
He was a war hero.
Who the fuck is nicer than Forrest Gump?
His best friend was a nigga
and a white boy with no legs.
He made a billion dollars selling shrimp.
And she still wouldn't fuck him.
Hey, eventually, they got together.
Yeah, after she got aids.
As soon as she got aids,
she's like, "hey, forrest..."
Get the fuck out of here, man.
Giving that guy aids?
- Are you kidding me?
- Yeah.
- That shit's abusive.
- But he ain't get it.
I ain't see no sequel. Where's gump 27
yo, rico just got off the elevator.
Oh, shit.
I et's do this.
Get down! Get down right now!
Get down right now!
You know what this is!
That's right! Put it all!
Come on! Down!
Fill up this bag!
- Put it in the motherfucking bag!
- Come on.
- You know what to do!
- Chill!
Get back!
I want that coke! I want that money!
I want everything!
Shit.
Ninety seconds, we gotta go!
Freeze! Police!
- Hands up! Get your hands up!
- Get out of the car.
Get the fuck out of...
Zeke? Is that you?
/eke?
What the fuck is wrong with you?
You do an undercover op...
You don't clear it,
there's no coordination.
We are homicide,
but you're robbing drug dealers
in a fucking hotel.
I had a dozen 911 calls come in.
What if someone got killed?
That crew killed four people last week,
and we got them.
And we could have got more of them
if my cover wasn't blown.
Fuck your cover, Zeke!
You were off on your own,
as usual, no backup, nothing.
No backup, 'cause there's nobody
on the force I can fucking trust!
From now on, you're going to learn
to be a team player.
You're getting a partner.
Jeannie, send schenk in.
Do I look like a fucking Jamaican nanny?
Do I smell like jerk sauce
and baby wipes? No!
Me no want no partner!
I'm not babysitting some fucking rook.
Yes, you are.
Just because your dad
was chief fucking Marcus banks
doesn't mean you get out of the shit.
Stop making this about my father, okay?
He's gone, you're the head
of the department now.
Yeah. Drama queen.
Zeke, it's been 12 years.
Yes! Twelve fucking years.
Twelve years ago, I turned in a dirty cop,
I get a medal for it.
Big fucking deal!
I also got a bullet,
and I got to look over my back
for the rest of my career.
Shut up!
It is too fucking hot in here
for me to listen to this bullshit.
I got a heat wave going on.
We got rolling blackouts,
the city is nuts. Stop!
You wanted to see me, captain?
Yeah, come in.
Zeke, I want you to meet
detective in training, William schenk.
He was the top of his academy,
so don't screw this up.
Zeke is going to break you in,
show you the ropes.
Detective banks, it's good to...
Yup...
- Go.
- Yep.
Officer Harris, 1-0-3.
Sergeant Jones, front desk.
So... how do you take
your coffee in the morning?
Alone.
Okay.
Hey, man, I get it.
I wouldn't want to be
stuck with some random kid either.
You don't want to be my partner.
You don't know that.
Your dad's the reason for all of this.
He's why I wanted to do this
in the first place.
And I'm not him.
Prepare to be underwhelmed.
Banks and schenk...
Some homeless guy got hit
by the three train. You're up.
Detective Peterson,
pick up 2-2-1.
Detective Peterson, 2-2-1.
This is you?
Beats the squad car.
Detective banks en route to that 10-19.
Would that be north
or south side of the street?
- Northbound.
- Copy that.
What are you doing?
Oh, it's just family.
This is my wife, Emma,
this is my son, Charlie.
They're cute.
Enjoy it while it lasts.
"While it lasts?"
Nothing happier than the wife
of a new detective,
and nothing more angry
than that same bitch ten years later.
Maybe it's 'cause you call them bitches.
I'm half-Italian, trust me.
Women do not like it
when you call them bitches.
What are you telling me about women,
young motherfucker? Shit.
I just said it to you,
I didn't say it to a woman.
I don't say it to their face.
It's not like I'm too short.
We just met, but, you know,
you're firing already, I appreciate it.
I mean, all I'm saying is, you know,
most crime happens on weekends, holidays,
so you would think
anybody married to a cop
would understand this.
But no.
One day, your wife will be angry
'cause you couldn't go to
her sister's birthday dinner.
You can give a woman 600 Tuesdays.
It ain't worth three Saturday nights.
So... I'm guessing you're divorced.
Divorced, no, not yet.
I'm going through a divorce.
That's-that's even worse.
It's kind of like chemo.
Shit. Sorry.
Sorry for what? We're cops.
This is the life we choose.
Highest divorce rate,
highest suicide rate.
Highest rate of domestic violence.
Yo, when you decided to become a cop,
you pretty much assured yourself
you were gonna die alone.
My wife and I,
we're doing this counseling.
She's got me working on,
like, communication.
Counseling? Yeah, that's nice.
Yeah, my wife fucked the counselor.
Fuck, really?
- Yeah.
- Jesus.
Women cheat, too.
It hurts. God damn it, it hurts.
Women cheat, too,
but here's what happens.
Women cheat in the daytime.
You can get away with
a lot of shit in the daytime.
That's right. You can ride
- a lot of dick before dusk.
- Mmm-hmm.
Shit, man, I just found out
pilates doesn't even exist.
Wait, seriously?
Emma loves pilates.
I'm sure she does.
But don't worry about it.
You're gonna be fine.
You gonna be married forever.
What do we got?
See for yourself.
Watch yourself.
If you're gonna throw up,
don't do it on the evidence.
Are you kidding me?
I've been dreaming about this
since I was 12 years old.
Oh, shit.
You see a lot of TV sets on the subway?
You get everything down here.
Damn. Wow.
This bum's gonna be tough to ID.
I'm not too sure this is a bum.
I don't know a lot of bums
trying to get their steps in.
Whoever this is, is married...
And wears a fitbit.
This package just came in.
- For me?
- Yeah.
What is that?
"Play me."
- Okay.
- Whoa, whoa. What are you doing?
Don't want to fuck up my computer.
Hello, detective banks.
I'm here to help reform the Metro police,
to remind them of their oath
to the people of this city.
One officer from your station
refused to be reformed.
He will not be the last to play my game.
If that spiral is what I think it is...
Jigsaw?
Wait, I thought
the Jigsaw killer was dead?
Yeah, but if it's another copycat...
It's gonna be a shit show.
I recognize that building.
It's the courthouse.
I et's check it out.
What are you guys doing here?
We thought you boys
might need some backup.
Fuck you, Fitch, it's not your case.
Yo, Zeke.
What do we got here?
What the fuck is that?
Is that a fucking tongue?
Fucking shit.
Four-5-3... who's 4-5-3?
Circle up!
Okay, here's what we know.
Dental records confirm it's boz.
Sorry, guys.
But, look, we got to catch
the son of a bitch that did this.
Train conductor says he didn't see much.
Says he saw boz hanging in the air
right before he hit the windshield.
Says he thinks he saw boz
bleeding from the mouth badly.
The package was sent
from a delivery service
that picked it up on a stoop
on anglin drive.
What about the spirals?
Hey, cap, obviously it's a Jigsaw copycat,
so that's where we got to
concentrate our focus.
Sure, Fitch, but I want you
to stick with hard evidence.
Kraus, contact the feds,
get anything they got.
Files, old videos, anything.
Do we have street images?
We're working on it,
but digital forensics was
able to map boz's movement off the fitbit.
Last place it was registered
was Stuart's point,
time-stamped during the fireworks.
Someone needs to call Kara,
his wife, let her know.
Yeah, I already called her.
You called Kara?
Yeah.
- Do you know Kara?
- No.
Did you actually talk to her,
or did you text her?
Let me guess, you sent an emoiji.
Do they have a dead husband emoji?
I talked to her, asshole.
Hey. We had to notify her
before it leaked to the press.
- Okay, o'brien's got point...
- O'brien?
This is mine.
Me and the rook were first on scene.
Banks...
I'm sorry, isn't this protocol?
Now you're part of the team again, Zeke?
- Fuck you.
- No, fuck you.
Come on, Zeke.
When all you motherfuckers
were treating me like shit,
shooting me in my fucking back,
boz was my friend!
Boz played with my kid.
We went to fucking games.
Fuck me? No, fuck you.
Fucking assholes...
Zeke! Zeke, fucking stop!
In here! Now!
Zip up! Get out.
Okay, captain.
Damn, nigga, wash your hands.
I get why you want this.
Boz was my friend, too,
but you can't do this alone.
I need the whole department
on this, working together.
I'm not trying to do this alone, okay?
Boz is my family, man.
You gotta let me take lead.
You gotta let me
catch this motherfucker.
All right, guys,
we got a change of plans.
Banks is taking lead.
Listen up.
I know some of you guys think I'm a rat.
Some of you think I'm a snitch.
Some of you are mad
I fucked your mother.
Boz was last seen at the July 4th parade
at Stuart's point...
So there should be plenty
of surveillance footage,
so check your hashtags, Instagram...
Hey!
Now, we got a dead cop here,
guys, who was brutally killed.
A fallen brother
whose tongue was ripped out.
We need to focus on the case
and solve this.
So get the footage to detective banks
and put your personal shit aside.
O'brien, you good?
No problem here, captain.
Good.
Let's go.
Yo, where we going?
Pay our respects. Put on a suit.
Eke.
Kara...
It's okay.
Whoever did this, I'm gonna find them.
I don't understand. How did it happen?
Kara, your mother's on the phone.
Yeah, okay.
Eke.
Lisa.
You okay? I... I texted you.
Yeah, I got it.
Is Brian here?
No, my sister's watching him.
Sister... so, Rhonda
gets to see my son, but I don't?
Are we really gonna do this here?
No. Not today.
- Hey, I'm William, Zeke's partner...
- Stop.
Yup.
I'll wait outside. I'll wait outside.
Jamie's at the neighbor's.
I don't know how I'm supposed to tell him
what happened to his dad.
I can't imagine
what you're going through right now.
I know this is a bad time,
but I got to ask you
a couple of questions.
In the last few weeks,
did you notice anything unusual?
I mean, did boz say anything,
or act stressed out?
He was a cop, Zeke.
- So nothing out of the ordinary?
- No.
There was one thing, there was a black SUV
parked outside one night last week.
You get a make?
- Range rover, escalade, Lincoln?
- I don't know.
I told boz about it and he went out,
and he walked up, and, I don't know,
the next thing I know,
he was yelling at somebody inside.
Any idea what they were yelling about?
Did you hear anything?
No. If I see it again,
I'll get a license plate.
If you don't mind,
could you get me his devices?
I need to look at his iPad, laptop.
- Yeah.
- Thanks, Kara.
Nice... I gotta go, guys.
All right, be safe.
Eke.
He knew you were a good cop.
You find out who did this.
You pull a gun on your old man?
You out of your fucking mind?
I could have killed you.
What are you talking about?
I got the gun.
I could have killed you.
How'd you get in here?
Did you forget who the landlord is?
Yeah, but that doesn't give you the right
to just walk in here anytime you want.
Renters got rights.
You start paying some rent,
you can get some rights.
Heard about boz. You all right?
No, dad, I'm-I'm fucked up.
Sorry to hear that.
I know how close you were.
Jigsaw copycat.
That could be difficult.
- What are you saying?
- Nothing.
Just, you know, being lead detective,
a lot of responsibility.
You got a problem with that?
Or are you just scared
I'm gonna embarrass you?
See? That right there.
This ain't about you.
You always making shit about you.
That's the shit that ruined your career
and your marriage.
So, now you're giving fatherly advice?
What you talkin' 'bout, Willis?
Dad. We live in the same building.
I saw you out front the other day,
you nodded at me like we were
the only two black guys in the mall.
We haven't had a meal together
in over a year.
Haven't had a meal?
What? Are you hungry, nigga?
You want to go get a fucking slice?
Let me tell you something.
My father went to work, came home.
That was it.
All right, I'm gonna get out of here, son.
I'm gonna go to Kara's, pay my respects.
You're gonna be all right.
Come over tonight, I'll order some food,
we'll go over the case.
Just because your dad
was chief fucking Marcus banks...
Stop making this about my father.
Twelve years ago,
I turned in a dirty cop.
Pete! Pete!
What happened? What happened?
He pulled a gun on me.
The witness pulled a gun on you?
Because there's nobody on the force
I can fucking trust!
I've been staring at this shit
for five hours.
I don't even look at porn that long.
Okay, I'm out. What's next?
Well, why don't you check
with digital forensics
and see if anybody in boz's phone log
has a black SUV?
My phone is dead, you got a charger?
Your phone's dead,
what are you, a little girl?
- Let me borrow your phone, shut up.
- Okay.
Thank you.
Don't drain my battery watching twilight.
Glad to see you joined us.
You think this is linked to John Kramer?
I sent some pictures to the feds,
we'll see what happens.
How are we doing on surveillance?
Please tell me the 20 million the city
spent on cameras got us something?
Drury?
Yeah... street cameras from here to here
have already been scrubbed through.
Facial recognition came up with nothing.
There were two cameras
broken on this corner.
Fitch and kraus
are there now to canvas ijt.
No. Closed. Closed.
There's boz.
Who's that he's chasing?
I know that guy.
Benny wrights. He's a hustler.
Serious tweaker.
Flops in a burnt-out
bread factory down on 12th.
Deals with a pusher, street name speez.
- Should we tell Zeke?
- Fuck him.
I'll take the building,
you track down speez.
Hey, boss,
let me see that gun over there.
The one on the left.
Yeah, yeah, come on, come on.
On behalf of the Metro police,
I want to thank you for your generosity.
I got shit to do. I'm out.
What's his deal?
He's a crooked piece of shit.
- Let's just call it a night.
- You sure?
Yeah. Go home.
Go see your wife, go see your kid.
What's your boy's name?
- Charlie.
All right, I'll put him down.
I'll come right back.
No, no, no, I'm not going to be here.
Meeting my dad for dinner,
gonna go over the case.
Okay.
- Hey, William.
- Yeah?
Good work today.
Thanks, man.
- See you tomorrow.
- Yeah.
Benny?
Wake up, Benny.
Rise and shine, my man.
Benny, come on. Get up.
Come on, Benny, get up.
You all right?
Fuck me.
This is Deborah kraus,
leave me a message.
Kraus, call me.
Lieutenant Tim o'brien here,
leave a message
and I'll get back to you.
Help! Help me!
Hello, detective Fitch.
I want to play a game.
- Hey, Zeke.
- William.
What are you doing up?
I told you to take
the rest of the night off.
It's fine, Charlie's sleeping.
Was sleeping.
Just waiting for Emma to get home,
she's having a girl's night.
Girl's night out. Okay.
You better be careful with that,
might be a dick night out.
Just because you're getting a divorce,
it doesn't mean that everyone else's
marriages have to end, too.
Sounds like you got your hands full.
You want to call me back?
Nah, it's okay, we're sleep-training.
It's a fucking nightmare.
Look, man...
I know you and boz were close,
I don't know how fo tell you this.
You got something to say, William, say it.
Well, I'm looking through
all the Metro records like you asked,
and boz was accused of
lying on the stand more than anybody...
By like a wide fucking margin.
Jesus.
The courthouse...
That's why the tongue
was at the courthouse.
Can I help you?
Are you Marcus banks?
- No, I'm his son.
- Well, terroni delivery.
Oh, okay.
Dad!
Pop, got your food.
Motherfucker!
How the fuck could you not call me first?
I tried, but you didn't answer.
Well, why didn't you wait for me
to fucking call you back?
'Cause you would have talked me out of it.
I told the truth.
Get the fuck out of my face, Zeke.
Can we get the room?
God damn it.
I knew I should have never
let him become a cop.
This shit's gonna go sideways fast.
He turned in a dirty cop.
Pete was a scumbag.
Press will make him out to be a hero.
And what about the other cops?
You think they're gonna
call him a hero, too?
He did the right thing.
You know how much
internal damage control I have to do?
We'll handle it.
We always do, huh?
Chief banks, wf action news here.
Are you in?
Oh, I'm sorry, but I think your face
was trespassing on my property.
Is there something I can help you with?
No, no.
All right. Fuck you very much.
For detective Zeke banks.
Banks, incoming.
On my desk. Right now.
A courier brought it.
We're holding him for questioning.
Hello, detective banks.
Salvation was offered,
but it was declined.
This fucker thinks he's Jigsaw.
Even got a doll this time.
I have a bone to pick
with the police department,
and if you're going to point fingers...
12th street bridge. I know that place.
You should start by
pointing them at yourselves.
Geez, that's two blocks away.
Until you come clean, many more will die.
Stay back.
Stay sharp.
Whoa, hold it there, guys.
What a sick fuck, man.
What the fuck?
Oh, no...
God almighty.
Nine-8-2.
It's Fitch.
This is detective banks
requesting backup.
I'm on Decker street. Request backup!
- Fuck him.
- In pursuit,
requesting backup!
- Fuck!
- Fuck me.
Okay. Putting on pressure.
You're going to be okay, stay with me.
You're good, you're gonna be okay.
You're gonna be just fine.
- Zeke!
- Sir! Please, please!
Let us do our job, come on.
Come on, let us do our jobs,
let's go. Let's go.
Where the fuck were all of you, huh?
My son called for backup
three times in eight minutes
and none of you motherfuckers
could get here?
Nobody? Nothing?
Crickets. All right,
this is what I'm going to do.
I'm going to call dispatch
and find out who was closest available,
and when I do, I'm going to take this gun
and shoot that motherfucker.
We clear?
Fitch, it was you?
You fucking with my son again?
God damn you, son of a bitch!
Get off me!
You're done, motherfucker, you hear me?
You're fucking done!
Don't let me see your face again.
All right, call kraus,
find out Fitch's last location.
Hello, detective Fitch.
I want to play a game.
The tide of justice is rising around you.
In 90 seconds, the water will rise
to the height of the copper wires,
and if you are still in the tank,
you will be electrocuted.
Unless you make the sacrifice
that will cleanse you.
Oh... oh, god...
You murdered a man
because he insulted you.
Put your hands
where I can see them, motherfucker.
I said put your hands
where I can see them, sir.
Your finger pulled the trigger
and that cannot happen again.
Survival is simple,
but it comes with a sacrifice.
Bite down on the device in your mouth,
which will start the motor
that will rip your fingers away...
Leaving you free
to escape with your life.
But if you don't act quickly,
all that awaits you is this watery tomb.
Live or die, make your choice.
Hey, kraus, anything special about
the bridge where we found the fingers?
Yeah, why that bridge?
It was where he shot that kid,
Jimmy Lincoln.
Then how did you guys
find out about this place?
This guy, Benny wrights,
who boz was last seen with on July 4th.
How do you know
who boz was last seen with?
We took it off a pawn shop feed
in Stuart point.
And you didn't tell me.
Who the fuck did this?
Somebody who has it out for the Metro pd.
Or maybe just for Fitch.
You trying to say something, drury?
You know what I'm saying.
I doubt you'll be
shedding tears for Fitch.
All right, come on. Come on, Zeke.
Fucking asshole.
Okay, ignore him.
Did you get anything?
Got a name. Benny wrights.
Last guy boz was seen with.
Okay, find him,
and you got hours, not days.
And this is where Benny gets his meth.
You know what that is?
Is this a test?
- Just asking you a question.
- It's a meth house.
You put the money in the bucket,
the meth comes down.
Oh, somebody watched the wire.
This is some new Jack city shit. Goddamn.
Don't we need a warrant for this?
What you talking about?
Eke.
Hey, my man, my man.
Just trying to get a five, me and my lady!
It's our anniversary,
we're trying to celebrate,
trying to do something special.
Can I... can I get a five?
How about this iPad?
It's got everything on it.
I got passcodes, I got Netflix, hulu,
uber eats, postmates.
Lots of food, lots of food.
- Let me see that.
- Yo, man, get the fuck out of here.
Do I look fucking hungry to you?
Yo, yo, it got everything.
It don't fit, though.
Why don't you come down?
Get the fuck out of here!
Come back when you get some money!
Okay, okay. I need money, I need money.
No, no, no, no, wait, wait, wait!
I got some, I got some money.
I got some money, hold up a second.
Hold up a second, all right?
All right, send it down, baby.
Come on, come on, let's do this.
Can't wait!
- Zeke, what the fuck?
- We've got ten seconds, come on!
Jesus Christ.
What the fuck?
- Move!
- Get out of the way.
Out of my way, out of my way! Police!
Five-o!
- Everybody, five-o!
- Move, move, move! Come on!
Go! Coming through.
Fucking cops, man.
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
Shit! Get your dog!
- Fuck you, man.
- Get your fucking dog!
- Now!
- Hey, be nice.
Jesus Christ.
Holy fucking shit.
- What the fuck's going on?
- Back inside. Get back inside.
Hide your shit!
Come on!
Fuck. Fuck!
Fuck! My fucking leg!
Why do you make this shit so hard?
What if I really wanted
to get fucked up?
- Motherfucker...
- You got to make it easy
for the customer, skeeve!
My fucking leg!
That leg is fucked up.
Yo, yo, yo, yo!
Let me get a shot for the gram.
Hold on for one second.
- What the fuck?
- Hold on, hold on.
My man.
Here we go! You want me to tag you?
- Fuck... fuck you.
- Can I tag you, motherfucker?
- You see this man before?
- I ain't telling you shit!
Why, 'cause you're worried about
that bone sticking out your leg?
Why don't you let me sterilize it?
No... no... no! Fuck!
It's Benny! Stop, please!
Everybody knows that
motherfucker Benny wrights!
He's one of my best customers, man.
When was the last time you saw him?
I ain't seen the bitch in two days, man.
Word on the street is that mother...
Motherfucker od'd.
- Fuck this snitch.
- Fuck!
Well, that was a waste of time.
Well, we know Benny's dead.
Meth isn't the type of thing
you take a break from.
Besides, you see that device?
That was not designed by anybody
with rotten teeth.
Well, what do you think about
this whole Jigsaw angle?
You think it's a, what-do-you-call-them,
one of those disciples?
John Kramer didn't target cops.
Whoever did this has another motive.
Something personal.
And they're not following orders,
especially the orders of a ghost.
Ghost or not, somebody's out there
pulling all the strings.
You think this guy sent you the boxes
because you're the lead detective
on the case,
or because you're you?
I don't know.
Well, you got any enemies?
That aren't cops?
I don't know why she
won't give me another chance.
I don't know,
maybe it's because you beat her
when you drink too much.
You ever think of that?
That's some tough love.
Who the hell is this guy?
Ex-cop. Partner snitched on him,
had to do nine years hard time.
The system spit him out, now here he is.
Hey, Pete.
Eke.
Last guy I expected to see here.
You trying to get sober?
Alcohol's not my problem.
The glass and the bottle can kill.
How you doing, Pete?
Eighteen months sober,
living in a church basement,
who could ask for anything more?
Who's this?
Detective schenk.
We're working a case together.
Working together?
Don't let this guy catch you jaywalking,
or he'll stab you
right in the fucking back.
Don't forget, Pete, you gave me the knife.
You're right, I did.
And you witnessed this cop
throw the victim off a rooftop?
And you saw it,
I mean, with your own eyes?
And you can positively ID this cop?
He's had his foot on the neck
of this community for way too long.
We can't have this.
I'll testify, officer dunleavy.
I'l do it.
Pete! Pete! What happened? What happened?
He pulled a gun on me.
The witness pulled a gun on you?
I was mad for a long time,
but now I take responsibility.
I should have never pulled the trigger.
The guy had a family.
It was crazy back then, right?
We were working under article 8.
We were out of control.
Cops were given their own discretion
to crack down on crime.
Where were you July 4th at 9:30 P.M.?
Really? That's what you're here for?
That's what I'm here for.
Look, some guy came to a meeting drunk
and wanted to fight a sponsor,
so I hit him.
Knocked him clean out.
Anyway, the cops came.
I'm still on probation,
but lucky for me, it was o'brien.
He let the whole thing slide
because, you know...
Loyalty.
Take care, Pete.
God loves you, Zeke.
More than you.
Can't believe that guy used to be a cop.
He shot an innocent guy,
but you turned on him?
There's a code, and you better
learn how to follow it,
or you're going to spend
the rest of your life watching your back.
Fair point.
Maybe it's a good thing
they made us partners.
[Eave a message.
Yeah, dad, I'm at your apartment.
I was here last night.
It doesn't look like you've been home.
All right, give me a call.
You've gotten through to William,
leave a message after the beep.
Schenk; It's 9:00 A.M.,
where the fuck are you? Give me a call.
Just tell me what happened, okay?
Hey! Hey! Hey!
Put the box on the ground!
On the ground! Hands up! Hands up!
On the ground now! Hands up, hands up!
Don't move!
Get him out of here.
Take him to holding.
I'm sorry, banks, he blew right past me.
No way, Zeke, that one is not the same.
I'm calling the bomb squad.
Angie, you're the head of the department.
We got two dead cops, there's no time.
Get everybody out.
Everybody out! Everybody out!
Everybody, go!
Is that fucking skin?
"Am I getting under your skin,
detective banks?
Careful, while you're looking
for more bodies to drop,
I'll take your head."
"I'll take your head..."
"Am I getting under your skin...
Am I getting under your skin...
Am I getting under your skin...?"
Family. This is my wife, Emma,
this is my son, Charlie.
What the fuck is that?
Captain, there's something under here.
Constantine paints.
Thanks, yeah.
Follow me.
How do you know about this place?
Zeke, how do you know about this place?
My dad used to take me here.
Watch your step, gentlemen.
It wasn't always a butcher shop.
Used to be constantine trains.
Like a hobby shop.
Oh, my god.
Anything?
Well, we're analyzing the tape recording.
Hello, detective schenk,
I want to play a game.
You were head of your class
at the police academy...
He was obviously skinned...
Postmortem.
Your dad's the reason I wanted
to do this in the first place.
The body was scored first
to remove the pieces in larger strips,
arms, neck, as he ripped the skin...
Maybe it's a good thing
they made us partners.
Given the defensive wounds,
he clearly tried to fight back,
which explains the deeper gashes.
Captain, over here.
Is it a serial killer targeting cops?
Is the victim inside a policeman?
No comment. Commissioner hart
will make a statement tonight.
We got to try to keep his identity
out of the press until I tell his wife.
"Am I getting under your skin,
detective banks?"
Hey, o'brien.
Yeah, boss?
You seen Zeke?
No, not for a while.
Okay, I'm heading down to cold case.
Copy that, captain.
I need all available units,
officer down 3rd and beaman.
Please report, 3rd and beaman.
What do we got?
I was writing a ticket
and some guy in a pig's mask,
he runs up on me with a knife.
So, he stabs your arm and just takes off?
I fought him off
the best I could and he...
He took off running.
Is there any reason
he would have to attack you?
No. He just wanted to mess with the cops.
"Careful, while you're looking
for more bodies to drop,
I'll take your head."
Angie, you're the head of the department.
Angie...
Fuck!
Angie! Pick up!
Hey, you've reached captain Angie garza,
leave a message aft the tone. Thanks.
Angie, get to the bullpen!
He's coming for you!
Fuck. Fuck, fuck, fuck.
Shit!
Hey! Hey! Hey!
Hello? Hello! Shit!
Help!
Hello, captain garza.
I want to play a game.
You have covered up corruption
in your department,
never sticking your neck out
for the innocent.
Now, the cover-up will be on you.
In a few seconds, boiling hot wax
will be coming out of the pipe above you.
The only way to stop yourself
from being suffocated
is to sever your spinal cord
with the blade beneath your neck,
which will stop the wax.
You cannot walk away,
but you can survive.
Live or die, make your choice.
Fuck you!
Angie! Angie!
Get the fuck out of the way!
How come no one is answering the phone?
An officer was attacked,
it's fucking chaos in here.
Angie! Angie!
Angie?
- Zeke, what's going on?
- He's got her!
Who's got her?
The killer has Angie!
I guess you didn't hear, the killer
just attacked a cop at 3rd and beaman.
That was just a diversion
to get us out of the precinct.
She's down in the fucking basement!
Did you find Angie?
In the basement, in the basement!
Captain Angie garza, call the front desk.
Open it!
Hurry up!
Angie!
Open it!
Okay.
Shit!
It's okay, it's okay.
It's gonna be fine.
Oh, my god.
It's okay.
It's okay... oh...
I ock it down.
You understand me? Lock it down.
Nobody gets out of this precinct.
I need all the footage from the cameras
in the evidence room.
Okay, here...
Here's when the call came in,
but then there's nothing
until you come in.
You see right there,
it jumps from 13:11 to 13:24. Glitch?
No, there's no glitch,
because look, on the first frame,
the safe door is open,
but on the next, it's shut.
There's 13 minutes missing.
Access to this footage,
is that through the computer system?
Yeah, we just need
a badge number and a password.
I can't tell you who deleted the video,
but I can access who logged into
the server over the past day.
O'brien, tupper, nicholazi...
Wait, who's badge number 2-1-3?
Pete dunleavy, my old partner.
Dunleavy? He shouldn't have access.
How long's it been
since he was even on the job?
Where you going?
To pay Pete a visit.
Zeke, he's not the only one!
Your father had access, too.
The location of schenk's body,
you said it was where
your father took you as a kid.
When was the last time
you saw your father?
- This morning.
- Bullshit.
Motherfucker!
What the fuck, Zeke?
Fuck you, man!
- Fuck you!
- Get the fuck out of here!
- Get him out of here!
- Fuck you! You're too close!
You're too close to this thing, Zeke.
Petel
petel
[Eave a message.
Dad, I've called you three times,
please call me back!
People are asking questions,
and I'm sick of making excuses.
You got something to tell me? Fuck!
You wanna play games, motherfucker?
All right, I'll play.
You okay?
Hey!
Help!
Pete?
Pete, wake up.
Petel
what? Zeke? Fuck.
Get me the fuck down, Zeke.
Come on!
You hacked the computer.
You erased the surveillance footage.
I don't know what the fuck
you're talking about, Zeke.
- Did you kill Angie?
- What?
- Did you kill boz?
- What the fuck are you talking about?
- Boz? Fuck...
What the fuck is with you, Zeke?
Get me the fuck out of here!
Is this some sick fucking revenge, Zeke?
Putting me in jail isn't enough, huh?
Get me the fuck out of here!
Hello, detective banks.
I want to play a game.
When Peter dunleavy
murdered an innocent man,
your career was shattered like glass.
Can you stand on the sidelines
while justice is finally served?
There is a way to save him,
or you can keep him locked up
and throw away the key.
The decision is yours.
"Throw away the key," what the fuck?
Huh?
Fuck.
Eke.
Get me the fuck out of this thing.
Oh, shit.
Come on, Zeke.
Get me the fuck out of here, Zeke!
Shit!
Zeke! Help me!
/eke?
Get me out, come on, man.
/ekel
or you can keep him locked up
and throw away the key.
Petel
I'm coming, Pete!
Shit.
Fuck. I got you, I got you.
Come on, Pete.
Petel
petel
You disloyal piece of shit.
I've been loyal to you
since the first day we met.
Fifteen years ago.
The day your partner killed my father.
So, Charlie, you saw this cop
throw the victim off a rooftop,
and you can positively ID this cop?
I'll testify, officer dunleavy.
I'll do it.
Pete! Pete!
What happened, what happened?
He pulled a gun on me.
The witness pulled a gun on you?
Shh.
Pete killed Charlie emmerson.
What? You thought I'd use my real name?
Do you have any idea how hard it was
to get placed in this department,
to get assigned to be your partner?
What about your family,
what about your son?
This is my son, Charlie.
I don't have a son.
Charlie's sleeping...
Was sleeping.
After Benny wrights led boz
down the subway tunnels...
I tattooed my dad's name on his arm.
Where is my father?
You'll see him soon.
Where the fuck is my father?
I didn't even ask him
to come down here. You did.
- Let me borrow your phone, shut up.
- Okay.
Thank you.
Don't drain my battery
watching twilight.
Where is he?
- Don't you want to hear my offer?
- Do I have a choice?
I want to be partners.
You took a stand, Zeke,
against a dirty cop,
and what did it get you?
A lifetime of watching your back,
working alone.
Getting the call for every homeless bum
who turns up dead.
I mean, let's be real,
some of these motherfuckers
are straight up evil.
Fitch not backing you up...
Fuck him.
He won't repeat that mistake.
And boz, always lying under oath...
But you, you're different.
You're Metro's finest.
That's why I want to team up
with you on this.
You find the dirty cops,
and I'll take care of the rest.
You want me to help you kill cops?
No, fuck no. Just the bad ones.
John Kramer was right, the spiral.
A symbol of change, evolution, progress.
But why limit that to an individual
when you can apply it to a whole system?
You got shot for doing the right thing.
Let's face it, these cops?
They're not going to clean up
on their own.
But we take a tongue here,
a few bones there, they'll come around.
We're going to fix
a broken department. Okay?
You and me.
Okay.
I et's do it.
I want to trust you. I do.
I'm in. But my dad goes free.
One second.
911, please state your emergency.
Hello, I'm at the old soap factory
on madigan Lane.
There's a crazy guy with a gun
he's firing it everywhere. Please hurry!
What the fuck was that?
You better hurry, Zeke,
SWAT's on the way.
Look, I want to believe you, I do.
I want to trust you.
Take this, you'll need it. Come on.
Let's go see your dad.
It's time for your final test.
Dad.
Ezekiel.
Oh, shit! Get him down!
Oh, shit.
I got you, dad.
Zeke. Help me, son.
Don't worry, don't worry.
I'm not going to let you die.
I will get you down.
All right, just hold on.
Shoot this motherfucker right now.
Get him down! Get him down now!
I thought we were partners.
You going to shoot me, Zeke?
With your one bullet?
It's a bad idea. It kills your dad.
He took a shot at me, by the way.
Missed. I wasted four.
That means you got one shot left, Zeke.
All right, cops are here.
That gives us four minutes.
Do you know there's 1.5 gallons of blood
in the human body, Zeke?
At the rate your old man is bleeding out,
in just three minutes,
those jars will be full
and your dad will be dead.
The only thing that can set him free
is the bullet in your gun
fired at that target.
Either way, I've got
a foolproof way out of here.
You're not Jigsaw.
That's the game.
Shoot me and you both lose.
Shoot the target and we both win.
- You want to play?
- I'm dying, Zeke, end it now.
We're in maintenance corridor.
Roger that.
I just breached southwest entrance.
Going through the south door.
Nothing here. Keep moving.
I need you all in.
Dunleavy ruined both our lives,
and you tried to help that piece of shit?
- Zeke!
- Pete!
You failed that test.
Now I need you to choose
who you're really with.
The man who corrupted the force,
or the one who's trying to save it.
You want to tell him, chief?
Tell me what?
Tell him about all the fucking shit
you did under article 8.
What's he talking about?
- Time's running out.
- What's he talking about?
Citizens were dying.
We did what we had to
to clean up the streets.
It was crazy back then, right?
We were working under article 8,
we were out of control.
Murder rate went way down.
That's fucking bullshit.
People felt safe again.
The streets got cleaner
because the cops got dirtier.
Your dad oversaw the whole thing,
by the way.
Innocent people getting shot,
all in the name of justice.
Article 8 was one of the most corrupt
police policies in history,
and guess who was
your dad's right-hand man?
Sorry, or should I say woman,
the whole time?
We'll handle it. We always do, huh?
- Angie?
- Angie!
It was Angie.
I mean, not a massive surprise.
You think it was her stellar reputation
that got her a precinct at age 357
come on.
Shoot this piece of shit, Ezekiel. Now.
Yeah, that's right,
because that's what cops do.
Shoot first, ask questions later.
You watched my father die
and I'm trying to save yours.
If we're going to trust each other,
I need you to do this.
Ezekiel...
You've always done the right thing,
do it now.
This piece of shit is killing cops.
You still need to decide,
you can shoot me, or...
Or you can save your dad.
Clock's ticking, man.
Think fast.
Cavalry's coming.
But not in time to do
any favors for your old man.
Only you can do that.
Dad? Dad? Oh, my god.
Shots fired!
Eke... Zeke.
It's going to be okay.
He's getting away.
Don't let him get away.
Go... go!
Stop. Don't come in.
Don't come in.
Whoever did this has another motive,
something personal.
Whoever did this...
They're pulling all the strings.
Your dad is the reason for all of this.
He's why I wanted to do this
in the first place.
I've been dreaming about this
since I was 12 years old.
What the fuck's going on?
Go, go, go!
- Get down! Get down now!
- Let me see your hands!
No! No, no, stop!
God!
- Freeze!
- No, no!
Nol
put it down!
Lower your weapon!
Fire!
Nol