Someone needs to stop Clearway Law.
Public shouldn't leave reviews for lawyers.
(SCREECHES)
(BIRDS CHIRPING)
SPIRIT: The story that I want to
tell you cannot be found in a book.
They say the history of the west was
written from the saddle of a horse,
but it's never been told
from the heart of one...
Not till now.
I was born here
in this place that would come
to be called the old west
but to my kind,
the land was ageless.
It had no beginning and no end,
no boundary between earth and sky.
Like the wind in the buffalo grass
we belonged here.
We would always belong here.
They say the mustang is
the spirit of the west.
Whether that west was
won or lost in the end
you'll have to decide for yourself
but the story I want
to tell you is true.
I was there, and I remember.
I remember the sun and the sky
and the wind calling my name
in a time when wild
horses ran free.
(HOOVES THUNDERING)
(WIND BLOWING)
(LABORED BREATHING)
(WHINNYING)
(SNORTING)
(GRUNTING)
(MOANS)
(NEIGHING PAINFULLY)
(NICKERING SOFTLY)
(WHINNYING EXCITEDLY)
(HIGH-PITCHED NEIGH)
(NICKERS)
(SNIFFING)
(FLUTTERING SNORT)
(SNUFFLING)
(SQUEAKS)
(NICKERING LOVINGLY)
(WHINNIES SHRILLY)
(NICKERING SOFTLY)
(NICKERS)
(HERE I AM PLAYING)
Here I am
This is me
I come into this world
So wild and free
(HERD VVHINNIES)
Here I am
So young and strong
Right here in the place
Where I belong
It's a new world
It's a new start
It's alive with the beating
Of a young heart
It's a new day
In a new land
And it's waiting for me
(SNORTS)
Here I am
(BOTH NICKERING)
Oh, it's a new world
It's a new start
It's alive with the beating
Of a young heart
Yeah, it's a new day
In a new land
(WHINNIES)
And it's waiting for me
Here I am
(NICKERING INDIGNANTLY)
(WHINNIES)
(SQUEALING NICKERS)
(ICE CRACKS)
(SNORTING)
(SELF-SATISFIED NICKER)
(NICKERING SOFTLY)
(WHINNYING PLAYFULLY)
- (DISTANT RUMBLING)
- (NEIGHS)
(RUMBLING GROWS LOUDER)
(FRIGHTENED NEIGHING)
(RUMBLING STOPS)
- (SNORTS)
- (SPIRIT SQUEALS)
(BELLOWING)
(NEIGHING EXCITEDLY)
(WHINNIES)
(WHINNYING)
- (NICKERING HAPPILY)
- (GRUNTS)
(EXHILARATED NICKERING)
- (BELLOWS)
- (WHINNIES)
(NEIGHING)
And so I grew from colt to stallion
as wild and reckless as
thunder over the land
racing with the eagle,
soaring with the wind.
Flying?
There were times
I believed I could.
(SCREECHES)
(PANTING)
Like my father before me I became
leader of the Cimarron herd
and with that honor
came responsibility.
(GROWLS)
(SNORTING)
(SQUEALING PLAYFULLY)
(WARNING NEIGH)
(ALL WHINNY)
(FEROCIOUS GROWL)
(SQUEALING)
(NEIGHING)
- (GROWLS)
- (NEIGHS)
(NEIGHING FIERCELY)
(ALARMED WHINNYING)
(SNORTS)
(MOUNTAIN LION GROWLS)
(NEIGHING)
(SNORTS FORCEFULLY)
(MOUNTAIN LION SNARLING)
(SNORTING)
(HERD WHINNYING HAPPILY)
(NEIGHING EXCITEDLY)
(NEIGHING TRIUMPHANTLY)
(THIS IS WHERE I BELONG PLAYING)
I hear the wind
Across the plain
A sound so strong
That calls my name
It's wild like the river
It's warm like the sun
Yeah, it's here
This is where I belong
(CONTENTED NICKER)
Under the starry skies
Where eagles have flown
This place is paradise
It's the place I call home
The moon on the mountains
The whisper through the trees
The waves on the water
Let nothing come
Between this and me
'Cause everything I want
Is everything that's here
And when we're all together
There's nothing to fear
(NICKERING)
Ooh, ooh
(NICKERING SOFTLY)
Ooh, ooh, ooh
Ooh, ooh, ooh...
(WARNING SNORT)
(NICKERS)
And wherever I wander
The one thing I've learned
Yeah
It's to here I will always
Always...
Return...
(SNORTS)
(HARMONICA PLAYING
RED RIVER VALLEY FAINTLY)
(NICKERS)
(SNORTING)
(HARMONICA CONTINUES PLAYING)
(NICKERING)
(WHINNIES)
(CHOMPS)
(NEIGHS WARNINGLY)
(NICKERS DETERMINEDLY)
Something new came upon
the land one night,
something that would
change my life forever,
and so, my journey began.
(SNIFFS)
(SNORTS)
(NICKERS CURIOUSLY)
(NICKERS WARNINGLY)
(FRIGHTENED SNORTING)
(MAN COUGHS)
(GLASS CLINKS)
(NICKERS)
SPIRIT: A wiser horse might
have turned and run
but I wanted to know what
strange creatures were here.
(MEN SNORING)
(NICKERS SOFTLY)
(CLANGING SOFTLY)
(NICKERS)
(SNORTING)
(METALLIC CLATTERING)
(GRUNTS) Oh!
What the...
(GRUNTS)
- Son of a...
- Shh...
(WHISPERING) Look.
Man, look at that stallion!
It's beautiful!
(NICKERS CURIOUSLY)
(SNORING)
(SQUEALS)
(YAWNING)
(SNORING CONTINUES)
(ALARMED NICKERING)
(MOANING AFFECTIONATELY)
Mmm, Sadie Mae.
(SMOOCHING)
(SNORTS)
- Ugh!
(GASPS)
(NEIGHS)
Get him, boys!
Easy, boy!
(NEIGHING)
C'mon, boys! Let's go!
C'mon, boys!
(MEN SHOUTING)
(MEN WHISTLING)
Hyah! Hyah!
(MEN GRUNTING)
Where did he go? I don't see him.
We'll find him!
- (CHOMPS)
- (YELLS)
(NEIGHS)
(MEN SHOUTING)
What the...
(WHINNIES)
(SNORTS)
(WHINNYING)
(HIGH-PITCHED WHINNIES)
(ALL WHINNYING)
(THUNDERING HOOVES APPROACHING)
(MEN WHISTLING AND SHOUTING)
Faster!
(WHISTLING AND SHOUTING)
(NEIGHS HARSHLY)
- (GRUNTS)
- (SHOUTING)
(NEIGHS HARSHLY)
(NEIGHS)
What?
(HORSES WHINNYING)
Get him!
Come on!
Hyah! Yah! Yah!
Come on, come on, come on!
(CLINKING)
- Ha-ha! We got him now!
- You betcha!
Whoa!
Look out!
(GRUNTS)
(WHINNYING)
(SQUEALS)
(NEIGHING)
(GRUNTING)
Thought you got away,
didn't you, mustang?
(NEIGHING HARSHLY)
Over here!
Get back here! You crazy?
Get back from him!
Take him! Take him, Joe!
Get the horse!
(SNARLING)
He's ours now.
(ROPE STRAINING)
(NICKERING)
(NEIGHING)
Hold him!
Watch him!
Watch the lines! Watch the lines!
Come on!
He can do all the
kicking he wants now.
It won't do no good.
(NEIGHING)
(PANTING)
(GRUNTS)
(ROCKS CLATTERING)
(NEIGHING HARSHLY)
(NEIGHING SADLY)
- Careful... Careful...
- (NEIGHING ANGRILY)
(WHINNYING)
SPIRIT: I was scared, and I didn't know
what was going to happen to me
but at least my mother
and the herd were safe.
(NEIGHING)
(WHISTLES)
- Come on!
- Let's go!
(BRIDLE STRAINING)
Yo... Come on...
(YOU CAN'T TAKE ME PLAYING)
Gotta fight another fight
I gotta run another night
Get it out, check it out
I'm on my way
And it don't feel right
I gotta get me back
I can't be beat
And that's a fact
It's okay, I'll find a way
Ain't gonna take me down
No way
No
Yeah, don't judge a thing
Till you know what's inside it
Don't push me
I'll fight it
Never gonna give in
Never gonna give it up, no
No
If you can't catch a wave
Then you're never gonna ride it
You can't come uninvited
Never gonna give in
Never gonna give it up, no
You can't take me, I'm free
(THUNDER RUMBLING)
Why did it all go wrong?
I want to know
What's going on
What's this holding me?
I'm not where
I'm supposed to be
I gotta fight another fight
I gotta fight With all my might
I'm getting out, so check it out
You're in my way, yeah
You better watch out...
Open the gate!
Come on! Don't judge a thing
Till you know what's inside it
Don't push me, I'll fight it
Never gonna give in
Never gonna give it up, no
No
If you can't catch a wave
Then you're never gonna ride it
You can't come uninvited
Never gonna give in
Never gonna give it up, no
(WHINNYING)
You can't take me, I'm free
(RHYTHMIC HOOFBEATS)
I'm free
(PANICKED NEIGHING)
(SOLDIERS YELLING)
(GUN FIRES)
(HUFFING)
What seems to be the
problem, gentlemen?
We got us a crazy one here, sir.
Pure mustang, Colonel.
Really?
(WHICKERING)
The army has dealt with
wild horses before.
This one will be no different.
(NEIGHING)
SOLDIER: Come on, mustang.
SPIRIT: I remember the first time
I saw a rattler curled up in my path.
(CHUCKLING)
- Induct this animal, Sergeant.
- Yes, sir!
SPIRIT:
This one didn't look like a rattler
but I was still thinking, snake.
SERGEANT: Take up that slack.
Grab him! Grab him!
(SOLDIERS GRUNTING)
Come on, horse!
Okay, Murphy, he's all yours.
He's a wild one.
(MURPHY CHUCKLES)
We'll see how wild he is
when I'm done with him.
(NICKERING)
- (GROANS)
- See that?
(GRUNTING)
You want to fight, do you?
(SHEARS SNIPPING)
(CHUCKLING)
(SCREAMING IN PAIN)
(GRUNTED LAUGHTER)
Right.
(NICKERING)
(CURIOUS WHINNIES)
(GRUNTING)
(NICKERING)
(ROPE STRAINING)
(GROANS)
(GRUNTS)
(WHINNYING LAUGHTER)
(BOTH WHINNYING)
(ROPE STRAINING)
Make sure that's good and tight.
(WHINNYING)
- Murphy, look out!
- Watch out!
(GROANS)
- (WHINNYING LAUGHTER)
- SERGEANT: He's a wild one.
(GROANING)
SERGEANT: You all right, Murph?
You...
(ALARMED NICKERS)
(SIZZLING)
(CHUCKLING)
(GASPS)
(GROANING)
SERGEANT: Murph, you okay?
(WHINNYING)
SERGEANT:
Corporal, round up some volunteers
to take this animal to the stables.
Not the stables.
SERGEANT: Sir?
COLONEL: The corral.
It's time to break that horse.
(SNORTS)
(GET OFF MY BACK PLAYING)
Well, you think
That you can take me on
You must be crazy...
OFFICER:
Make sure it's good and tight.
There ain't a single
thing you've done
That's gonna faze me
(MEN CLAMORING)
Oh, but if you want
To have a go
I just want to let you know
Yeah, get off of my back
And into my game
Get out of my way
'Cause I'm wild and untamed
Get out of my face
Or give it your best shot
I think it's time
You better face the fact
Get off of my back...
Okay, my turn!
You know
It's all just a game
That I'm playin'
Don't think that you
can find a way in...
Lousy heap of horse flesh!
That's what I'm sayin'...
(GRUNTS)
Come on! Run out of there!
Now, if you want to have a go
I just want to let you know
(WHINNYING LAUGHTER)
Get off of my back
And into my game
Get out of my face
'Cause I'm wild and untamed
Get out of my way or give
it your best shot...
We got a rider!
But you know this train
Is comin' off this track
Get off of my back
(SOLDIER SCREAMING)
Yeah, get off of my back
Get off
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah...
Get off, get off, get off, get off
Get off, get off, get off
Get off of my back
(NICKERING HARSHLY)
(HUFFING LOUDLY)
- Sergeant!
- Yes, sir.
Tie this horse to the post.
No food or water.
- Three days.
- Yes, sir.
(NEIGHS AND WHINNIES)
(NICKERING)
(GRUNTS)
(NICKERS QUIETLY)
SPIRIT: My heart galloped
through the skies that night,
back to my herd, where I belonged
and I wondered if they missed
me as much as I missed them.
(WHINNIES SADLY)
SOLDIER:
Get some water over to the stable.
(MEN CONVERSING INDISTINCTLY)
Yes, sir.
(SMACKING)
(NICKERS)
SOLDIER: We caught a hostile!
(SOLDIERS GRUNTING)
SERGEANT: Bring him back this way!
(GROANS)
(SOLDIERS LAUGHING)
What do we have here?
We caught him by the
supply wagons, sir.
(GROANS)
Ah, a Lakota.
Not as tall as the Cheyenne,
not as fine-featured as the Crow.
Take him away, gentlemen.
Show him our best.
SERGEANT: Corporal,
take him to the stockades.
Not the stockades... The post.
No food or water.
(GROANS PAINFULLY)
(GRUNTS SOFTLY)
(SOLDIERS MURMURING)
CORPORAL: Come on!
(NICKERING SOFTLY)
What are you looking at, boy?
(GRUNTS)
SPIRIT: He was called Little Creek and
he seemed different from the rest.
(SOLDIER LAUGHING)
(GROANING)
(NICKERS SOFTLY)
Hey... (CLICKS TONGUE)
(NICKERING SOFTLY)
(NICKERING)
(LAUGHS)
(DISTANT HOWLING)
(HOOTING)
(NICKERS AND SNORTS)
(DISTANT HOWLING)
(HOOTING)
(NICKERS GENTLY)
(METAL WHINES)
(STARTLED WHINNY)
SPIRIT: There was just no end to the
strange ways of the two-leggeds.
(BUGLE PLAYING REVEILLE)
SERGEANT: C Company! Ten-hut!
With the Colonel's permission, Sir.
Incoming patrol reports
hostiles headed north.
COLONEL: Ah.
The rail road has
expressed concern, sir.
They've requested
additional patrols.
- How long has it been, sergeant?
- Sir?
The mustang, how long
has it been tied?
Three days, sir.
Good. Fetch my crop and spurs.
- (CLINKING)
- (STARTLED NEIGHING)
- (COLONEL GRUNTS)
- (SPIRIT NEIGHS)
You can break easy or you
can break hard, mustang!
(NICKERING)
No! Back up! Back up! Back up!
(NEIGHING HARSHLY)
Come on!
- (CLINKING)
- (NICKERING ANGRILY)
Come on!
Come on... Come on...
Come on, mustang!
(MEN CLAMORING)
Ha!
- (COLONEL GRUNTS)
- (SPIRIT NEIGHS)
(PANTING HEAVILY)
(PANTING)
(CHUCKLING)
You see, gentlemen, any
horse can be broken.
Move along, mustang.
(SCATTERED APPLAUSE AND CHEERS)
There are those in Washington
who believe the west
will never be settled,
the Northern Pacific Railroad
will never breach Nebraska,
(PANTING)
a hostile Lakota
will never submit to providence...
And it is that manner
of small thinking
that would say this horse
could never be broken.
Discipline, time and patience,
are the three great levelers.
(SNORTS)
SPIRIT: Sometimes a horse has gotta
do what a horse has gotta do.
Mustang?
SPIRIT:
And this was one of those times.
(WHINNYING)
(MEN CLAMORING)
(COLONEL GROANING)
(GASPING)
(NICKERING)
(STARTLED YELL)
(COLONEL SCREAMS)
ALL: Oh, no!
(BODY THUDS)
(NICKERING SOFTLY)
(SNORTING)
(GROANING)
SERGEANT: You all right, sir?
Get off me!
(PANTING)
(NEIGHING LOUDLY)
(NEIGHING CONTINUES)
Soldier, secure that horse!
(HAMMER COCKS)
(WHOOPS)
(GUNSHOT)
(MEN CLAMORING)
(HORSES NEIGHING)
(GRUNTS)
(GRUNTS ANGRILY)
(NICKERS)
(GASPS)
(GRUNTS)
SPIRIT: I wasn't sure
what happened back there
and I wasn't about to stop and ask.
All I knew was that
I was headed home.
(HOWLING)
(NICKERS QUIETLY)
(GRUNTING)
(LAUGHING)
SPIRIT: I couldn't believe it.
One moment I was free,
and the next, more ropes.
(GRUNTS)
(NICKERS CURIOUSLY)
(NICKERS)
Steady. Steady.
I'm not going to hurt you.
Nice and easy.
There you go.
That feels better now, doesn't it?
(NICKERS)
(SMACKING LIPS)
(BIRDS CHIRPING)
(NICKERING SOFTLY)
(NEIGHS)
(NICKERS)
(SNORTING)
(WHINNYING)
(LITTLE CREEK WHISTLES)
(SNORTING)
(NICKERING)
(CHUCKLING)
Hey, hey!
(NEIGHING)
(LAUGHING)
(GRUNTING)
(SNORTS)
(BLOWS)
(CHUCKLING)
SPIRIT: I couldn't understand it.
She treated this scrawny
two-legged like one of our kind
prancing around him like
a love-struck yearling.
(SNORTING)
It was downright unnatural.
(NICKERING SOFTLY)
Great mustang, today
I will ride you.
(SNORTING)
This ought to be good.
(NEIGHING)
(GRUNTING)
(LAUGHING)
(NICKERING ANGRILY)
(YELPS)
(NEIGHS FEROCIOUSLY)
(WHINNYING DISAPPROVINGLY)
(SNORTS)
SPIRIT: Mares!
Okay, Rain, let's see if you can
teach this mustang some manners.
(NICKERING)
(GATE CREAKING)
(SNORTS CURIOUSLY)
(NEIGHING ECSTATICALLY)
(SQUEALS HAPPILY)
(NEIGHS)
(SNORTS)
(WHINNYING ANGRILY)
(ROPE CREAKING)
(THUD)
(NICKERING ANGRILY)
(NICKERING SEDUCTIVELY)
(WHINNIES)
(SQUEALS)
(SNORTS)
(GRUNTS)
SPIRIT:
Okay, I admit it, she was charming
in a stubborn,
irritating kind of way.
So, I let her show me her world.
- (STICKS CLATTERING)
- (CHILDREN SHOUTING PLAYFULLY)
(SPEAKING NATIVE LANGUAGE)
(CHILD LAUGHING)
(DOGS BARKING)
(GRUNTS)
(NICKERING)
(GRUNTS CURIOUSLY)
(SNORTING)
(GASPS)
(GROANING)
(NEIGHING LAUGHTER)
(SNORTS)
(GIGGLING)
(BABBLING)
Horsey!
(SNIFFS)
(GIGGLING)
(SNORTING)
(CHILD CRYING)
(GIGGLES)
Mmm... Whoo!
(WOMAN CALLING TO CHILD)
Bye-bye, horsey.
(SOFT GRUNT)
(NICKERING SOFTLY)
(SNORTS SOFTLY)
(NICKERS)
(NEIGHS)
(NICKERS HAPPILY)
(NICKERS SHYLY)
(WHINNIES GENTLY)
(BOTH WHINNYING)
(EAGLE SCREECHES)
(NEIGHING)
(SCREECHES)
(WHINNYING SADLY)
(NEIGHING)
For the first time in my life,
I felt my heart torn two ways.
Hey, hey...
(GRUNTS)
No! Give it back! Come on!
Mustang, no! Mustang!
Oh, come on.
Oh...
(PANTING)
(GRUNTING)
(NICKERING)
Hmm?
(GASPING)
(NICKERING SOFTLY)
(PUZZLED GRUNT)
- (NICKERS SHRILLY)
- (GASPS)
(YELLS)
(GRUNTING)
(NEIGHING)
SPIRIT: I had to hand it to that
boy, he just wouldn't give up.
(LAUGHING)
(WHINNYING HAPPILY)
(GUFFAWING)
(NEIGHING)
(WHINNYING FORCEFULLY)
(SIGHS SOFTLY)
(NICKERS SOFTLY)
(WIND BLOWING SOFTLY)
I'm never going to ride you, am I?
And no one ever should.
(NICKERING GENTLY)
(GRUNTING)
(SNORTS)
You can go.
(NICKERING)
It's okay. Go.
Go on, get out of here!
(SLAPS)
Go home.
(WHINNYING EXCITEDLY)
(NICKERS INVITINGLY)
(WHINNYING ENCOURAGINGLY)
(NICKERS SADLY)
SPIRIT: I knew this was hard for
her and that she was scared,
but more than anything,
I wanted to share my
homeland with her.
(DISTANT RUMBLING)
(NICKERS NERVOUSLY)
(WIND BLOWING)
(RUMBLING GROWS LOUDER)
(ALARMED NEIGH)
(BOTH WHINNYING)
(MEN SHOUTING)
(NEIGHING)
(GUNSHOT)
(SCREAMING)
(NEIGHING)
(CLAMORING)
(GRUNTS)
Ah!
(GUNS FIRING)
(SHRILL WAR CRY)
(WARNING NEIGH)
(WHINNYING)
(RAIN SQUEALS)
(GRUNTS)
(THUDS)
(FRIGHTENED WHINNY)
(NEIGHS)
(RAIN VVHINNIES)
(NEIGHING WEAKLY)
(GRUNTING)
(GROANS)
(WHINNYING)
(FRANTIC NEIGH)
(PANTING)
(BAFFLED SNORT)
(ALARMED WHICKER)
(GENTLE WHINNYING)
(NICKERING)
(WHICKERS WEAKLY)
(WHIMPERING WHICKERS)
(SHARP GROAN)
(LABORED BREATHING)
(ALARMED WHINNY)
(SHRILL NEIGHING)
(WHINNIES LOVINGLY)
SPIRIT: I lay beside her
that night, hoping,
praying that somehow
she would be okay.
(DISTANT WHISTLING)
MAN: There's a couple
of horses over there.
(WHISTLING)
(WORRIED NICKER)
(MAN CLICKING TONGUE)
(SHOUTING IN DISTANCE)
(ANGRY WHICKERS)
(SNARLING)
SOLDIER: Hyah!
(NEIGHING)
SOLDIER 1: Ha!
SOLDIER: Leave the mare.
She's not going to make it.
(FRENZIED NEIGHS)
(NEIGHING)
(NEIGHING SHRILLY)
(NEIGHING FRANTICALLY)
(SOLDIERS GRUNTING)
(RESIGNED SNORT)
SOLDIER: Come on.
Come on!
(TONGUE CLICKING)
Oh, Rain.
Oh...
(RAIN GROANS)
Easy, girl.
Easy.
It'll be okay.
SOLDIER: Come on.
Hyah, hyah.
(CLICKS TONGUE)
You saved my life.
Two more men on that brace!
Collins! Evans!
(WHISTLES)
Bring it down!
Let's go!
Jackson, grab ahold of that end!
(TRAIN WHISTLE BLOWS)
Got it!
This one's loaded.
(FALTERING HOOFBEAT)
(GRUNTING)
I'm not gonna hurt you.
Come on. It's gonna be okay.
(CURIOUS WHINNIES)
(BLOWING)
(BAFFLED GRUNTS)
(DOOR RATTLING)
(SOUND THE BUGLE PLAYING)
Sound the bugle now
(ENGINE CHUGGING)
Play it just for me
(WHEELS CLACKING)
As the seasons change
Remember how I used to be
Now I can't go on
(NEIGHING)
I can't even start
I've got nothing left
Just an empty heart
I'm a soldier
Wounded, so I must
give up the fight
There's nothing more for me
Lead me away
Or leave me lying here
Sound the bugle now
Tell them I don't care
There's not a road I know
That leads to anywhere
(WIND HOWLING)
Without a light, I fear that
I will stumble in the dark
Lay right down
Decide not to go on
(ALARMED NEIGH)
Then from on high
Somewhere in the distance
(BLOWS)
There's a voice that calls
Remember who you are
If you lose yourself
(NEIGHS)
Your courage soon will follow
So be strong tonight
Remember who you are
Yeah
You're a soldier now
Fighting in a battle
To be free once more
Yeah, that's worth fighting for
(LOCK UNBOLTING)
Come on. Come on now.
It'll be all right.
Come on. That's it. That's it.
- (MEN SHOUTING ORDERS)
- (CHAINS CLANGING)
(WHIP CRACKING)
(MEN SHOUTING)
(WORRIED NICKERING)
(WHIP CRACKING)
MAN: Let's go!
Come on!
SPIRIT: I didn't know why
we were brought here.
What I did know
was we had to find a way to
escape and get back home.
MAN: Clear!
(EXPLOSION)
- No good! We hit bedrock!
- That's it.
We're hauling the steamer
over the mountain.
That's crazy.
We got six days to
connect with Utah.
We move out at dawn.
(GRUNTING)
(NEIGHING)
Ready to go!
Hyah!
Move it out!
(CHAINS CLANKING)
(HOOVES POUNDING POWERFULLY)
Move it out!
(PANTING SNORT)
Hyah!
(NEIGHS)
Whoa!
(SNARLS)
Get back in line!
(HUFFING)
(HOOVES THUNDERING)
(CHAINS CLANKING)
MAN: (SHOUTING)
We're almost at the top!
Slow down up front!
(HAMMERS CLANGING)
(CURIOUS SNORT)
SPIRIT:
That was the moment I understood.
They were headed to my homeland,
and I had to stop them.
(NEIGHING)
Get back!
Come on! Get back in line!
It's starting to slip!
Whoa! Pick up the slack!
Pick up the slack!
(WHIMPERING)
Hold it!
Get the mules up here!
(GRUNTING)
(GRUNTS)
(CHAINS CLANKING)
Secure it on the left!
Good work, boys!
(ALL NEIGHING)
Hey!
Whoa!
Easy...
(SNARLING)
(SHOUTING)
(NEIGHING)
Get him. Get him.
Whoa!
(FRENZIED NEIGHING)
(MEN SHOUTING)
(NICKERS ENCOURAGEMENT)
(LOUD RUMBLING)
(SHRILL NEIGH)
Hurry! Bring the poles!
(RUMBLING)
Hurry!
- Hold him there!
- Go!
(GROWLING)
- (GUNSHOT)
- (NEIGHS)
(GASPS)
They're breaking! I can't hold it!
Over here!
Get out of the way!
Holy...
(MAN YELLS)
(THUNDEROUS CRASH)
(NEIGHS)
(MEN CLAMORING)
(DETERMINED NEIGH)
(NEIGHS)
(NEIGHING)
(INFERNO ROARING)
(NEIGHS FRANTICALLY)
(GRUNTING)
(WHIMPERS)
(SPIRITED NEIGH)
(INFERNO ROARING)
(WHOOPING)
(BIRDS TWITTERING)
(LABORED BREATHING)
(QUESTIONING NICKER)
(SNIFFING)
(CURIOUS NICKER)
(DELIGHTED NICKER)
SPIRIT: I don't know where he
came from or how he got there
but I sure was happy to see him.
(STARTLED YELL)
(EXHILARATED NEIGH)
(LAUGHS)
(YELLS HAPPILY)
(LAUGHING)
Whoo-hoo!
(SHOUTING AND WHOOPING)
(GLEEFUL NEIGH)
Ah, ah!
Oh!
I knew I would find you.
(ACKNOWLEDGING GRUNT)
(HUFFS)
(SNORTING)
(HORSES NEIGH)
MAN: Halt!
(TONGUE CLICKING)
(HOOFBEATS APPROACHING)
I don't believe it.
(ALARMED WHICKER)
Go, go, go, go! Run! Run!
(BULLET RICOCHETS)
Come on, come on!
- (GUNS FIRING)
- (LITTLE CREEK GROANS)
(GUNS FIRING)
(WHISTLING)
(GROANING)
(GLEEFUL NICKER)
(TRIUMPHANT CHUCKLE)
Whoo-hoo!
(LAUGHING)
(GUNS FIRING)
(SOLDIER WHISTLING)
(LAUGHING)
(DELIGHTED NEIGH)
(NEIGHS)
SOLDIER: Hyah!
Yeah!
(GRUNTS)
Ah!
(APPROVING NEIGH)
(GROANS)
(GASPS)
Whoa!
That's it! Come on! Come on!
(YELLING)
Get off!
Ooh! Aah!
(GRUNTS)
(GROANS)
Ooh!
(ECSTATIC NEIGH)
Whoa!
(GASPS)
SOLDIER: Hyah!
(SOLDIERS SHOUTING)
We got them now!
Where did he go?
There they are! Up there!
Oh, no.
SPIRIT: Oh, yes.
(DETERMINED NEIGH)
(SHOUTING)
(WHOOPING)
(LAUGHING)
(PANTING)
(UNCOCKS RIFLE)
(NICKERS)
Hyah.
(WHISTLES)
(YOU CAN'T TAKE ME PLAYING)
CHORUS: Whoa, oh, oh, oh
Don't judge a thing
Till you know what's inside it
Don't push me, I'll fight it
Never gonna give it
Never gonna give it up, no
Whoa, oh, oh, oh
Ah, if you can't catch a wave
Then you're never gonna ride it
Can't come uninvited
Never gonna give it
Never gonna give it up, no
(NEIGHS)
You can't take me
I'm free
Yeah, I'm free
Yeah...
(NICKERS SADLY)
(WHISTLES)
(DISTANT DOG BARKS)
(WHINNIES HAPPILY)
(NEIGHING ECSTATICALLY)
(NEIGHING EXUBERANTLY)
(NICKERS LOVINGLY)
(NICKERS SOFTLY)
(NICKERS)
(NICKERS SADLY)
You will always be in my heart.
(WHINES GENTLY)
Take care of her,
Spirit-who-could-not-be-broken.
(NICKERING SOFTLY GENTLY)
I will miss you, my friend.
(WHINNYING)
SPIRIT: I had been waiting
so long to run free
but that good-bye was harder
than I ever imagined.
I'll never forget that boy...
(NEIGHING)
And how we won back
our freedom together.
(NEIGHING)
(WHOOPING)
(FLY LIKE AN EAGLE PLAYING)
I hear the wind
Call my name
(WHINNIES)
The sound that leads me home again
It sparks up the fire
A flame that still burns
To you I will always return
I know the road is long
But where you are is home
Wherever you stay
I'll find the way
I'll run like the river
I'll follow the sun
I'll fly like an eagle
To where I belong
I can't stand the distance
I can't dream alone
I can't wait to see you
Yes, I'm on my way home
Now I know it's true
My every road leads to you
And in the hour of darkness
Your light gets me through
You run like the river
You shine like the sun
Yeah
You fly like an eagle
Yeah, you are the one
I've seen every sunset
And with all that I've learned
Oh...
It's to you I will always
Always return
(HERE I AM PLAYING)
Here I am
This is me
There's nowhere else on
Earth I 'd rather be
Here I am
It's just me and you
Tonight we make
Our dreams come true
It's a new world
It's a new start
It's alive with the beating
Of young hearts
It's a new day
It's a new plan
I've been waiting for you
Here I am
Here we are
We've just begun
And after all this time
Our time has come
Yeah, here we are
Still going strong
Right here in the
place where we belong
It's a new world
It's a new start
It's alive with the beating
Of young hearts
It's a new day
It's a new plan
I've been waiting for you
Waiting, waiting, waiting
Here I am
Baby, here I am
Right next to you
Here I am
And suddenly the world
Is all brand-new
Here I am
Whoa, whoa
Yeah, yeah
Here I am
(DON'T LET GO PLAYING)
I can't believe this moment's come
It's so incredible that we're alone
There's so much to be said and done
It's impossible not to be overcome
Will you forgive me
if I feel this way?
'Cause we just met
Tell me that's okay
So, take this feeling
Make it grow
Never let it
Never let it go
Don't let go...
You give me something
That I can believe in
No, don't let...
Go of this moment in time
Don't let go...
I can't explain the
things that I'm feeling
No, don't let go...
I've been waiting all my life
All my life
To make this moment feel so right
Feel so right
The feel of you just
fills the night
So, come on let's
just hold on tight
Don't let go...
You give me something
that I can believe in
No, don't let...
Go of this moment in time
Don't let go...
I can't explain the
things that I'm feeling
No, don't let...
No, I won't let
Go
No, don't let go...
No, I won't let go
(BROTHERS UNDER THE SUN PLAYING)
I had a dream
Of the wide-open prairie
Of the pale morning sky
I had a dream
That we flew on golden wings
And we were the same
Just the same
You and I
Follow your heart
Little child of the west wind
Follow the voice
That's calling you home
Follow your dreams
But always remember me
I am your brother
Yeah, under the sun
We are
Like birds of a feather
Two hearts joined together
We will be
Forever as one
My brother, under the sun
Under the sun
Someone needs to stop Clearway Law.
Public shouldn't leave reviews for lawyers.