Someone needs to stop Clearway Law.
Public shouldn't leave reviews for lawyers.
Happy birthday to me!
Happy birthday!
- Oh, my God!
- Anybody want this?
That's what happens when
you do a mercy invite.
I believed you wanted
to invite everyone.
Dad, I can't invite everyone in my
art class except for one person
without social
networking evidence
inflicting more pain on that
person than was intended.
And I'm not a monster.
I'm proud of you.
I think.
She gets detention a lot
and she yells
at teachers sometimes.
There was that rumor
that went around
that she just kept
running away from home.
Um, maybe she can Uber.
I seriously believe
that we can go home now.
Um, did I mistakenly convey
this was a democracy?
We are not going
till she gets picked up.
Uh, the car broke down.
I'm just gonna
take the bus.
You're not taking a bus.
I'll drive you home.
Claire has almost saved her half
of the money she needs for a car.
Isn't that right?
This'll be one of the few times left
I can drive you guys around. Huh?
Uh, I...
You won't be able to
hear my dad tell jokes
that only he thinks
are funny
for an entire car ride
unless you come.
You don't really
wanna miss that.
Wow! I got more gifts
than I thought I did.
Can I put this
in here?
Yeah, I'll get it.
Thank you, Marcia.
Maybe he just is into...
Maybe he's just content
where he is.
Hey. Can I help you?
What?
This is the one.
He's really funny.
He does
these weekly videos.
See? It's so random.
That is so weird.
Yeah,
you have a crush on him.
- I don't get it.
- Pause it.
Yeah, go back.
Why don't you get it?
I just don't get it.
He's blond and he's cute.
No, his eyebrows
are just like...
Shut up. His eyebrows?
That's the one thing
you couldn't get?
Yeah.
Oh, my God.
Oh. You see
what he does, though?
How does he even do that?
That's the whole
point why I'm showing you.
Genius!
So bad.
Hey!
Pardon me, sir. I think
you have the wrong car.
We woke up in here.
What the hell is going on?
What are we doing here?
What happened to my dad?
He's out there.
Do you know what
happened to my dad?
I choose you first.
It's only gonna be
a minute.
Pee on yourself.
No!
No.
Open the door!
Hey, are you okay?
He wanted me
to dance for him.
The outside door
is locked.
Everything's okay.
We're okay.
I hear
the tiniest little splash
and here it comes.
A freak of nature,
like this.
So, he comes across
the stream
and he's so tall
that the water doesn't even
get to his belly.
Then he stops.
And my heart's
coming out of my chest.
You got buck fever.
Uncle John's got buck fever.
That's not true, Casey.
Your daddy's a liar.
How big was the rack?
It was huge.
Where are you supposed to
look when you shoot, Casey?
At the body.
Then why was he
looking at the rack?
'Cause he had buck fever.
She'll say anything you say.
You gonna do that
when you get your
mentored hunting license
in three years?
No, sir.
Make sure you put your
gloves on after you finish.
Your feet and your hands
get cold first out there.
Three students abducted.
The father of
one of the students
woke up dazed
in King of Prussia,
reportedly drugged.
He found the kids
and the car missing.
Neighbors are in disbelief.
A normally quiet community
is reeling after this abduction.
If you have any information concerning
the whereabouts of these girls,
you are urged to
contact the police.
It doesn't matter
if you open that door, Claire.
There's a second locked door.
He's gonna come in
here again, any second,
and we're not letting him
take one of us out again.
We just cried and screamed
and we didn't hurt him
because we were afraid
to get him upset.
God, that's victim shit.
Jesus!
We should fight him.
We should drop
a crazy-ass bomb on him.
I saw him carry one of you
and lay you on the bed
like you weighed nothing.
One punch from him
would knock one of us out.
I took six months
of Kenpo karate class.
And you distract
the assailant with pain.
Everything is so easy
for you guys.
You do one thing, you can
predict the next thing.
It's not the way it's gonna
be in this situation.
We're not
getting out of here.
You're saying that you're not gonna
fight with everything in you?
You know the only chance...
The only chance we have is if all
three of us go crazy on this guy.
We have to hurry.
We need you, Casey.
Claire's smart.
Let's listen to her.
I'll do it if
you're gonna do it, too.
We can win.
He'll hurt us.
No. Shut up.
Both of you.
You're gonna pick your miserable
self up and help us get out of here.
Blow me.
And your six months of karate at the
King of Prussia Mall can blow me, too.
No! No, no, you can't
do this today!
You can't do this
right now.
Why do you do this?
Why do you act like this?
Why do you act like
you're not one of us?
When you're aiming, Casey,
always keep
both eyes open.
Cover your target
with the barrel
then move with it
to get its pace.
I'm warning you, it's gonna be
frustrating the first times.
You're gonna shoot
under it or behind it.
You'll learn to
stay with it.
Females are smarter
than the males.
But you know that,
it's like humans.
Females use their nose
to stay alive.
They make sure
they have cover.
They always remember they're
trying to stay alive.
Bucks go off
by themselves.
Bucks get dumb
during mating season.
Boys make
too much noise.
Yes, they do.
I'm better
than a boy, right?
Yes, you are.
Hey
I'll let you know when I hear
something that makes sense.
We don't even know
what this is yet.
Hey! I was inspired.
No, no, no, that one.
That one, before the pink
frock coat with the thorns.
That's supposed to be
like a tailored jacket,
but I'm gonna hand-print it
with newspaper headlines.
I'm a simple blouse and
skirt person, but these...
These are
very artistic, Barry.
Just the kind of thing Hamptons
ladies would spend $15,000 on
to wear once
at a charity ball.
Shut up!
You know,
I can't stay too long.
This is just a visit.
Well, tell me
what's going on.
What, you mean the email?
No, just the usual things.
Just feelings of
being overwhelmed.
The terseness of your email made it
sound specific and time-related.
Are you looking
for something?
No.
No?
I'm just admiring.
I'm better now.
How's work?
It's great.
When I last spoke to them,
they believed you were
a model employee.
They found you meticulous
and conscientious.
You know this, right?
I do.
You've managed there
for 10 years.
You're functioning
very well, Barry.
And it's a rare and wonderful
place for you to work.
Yes, it is.
You know, of all my other
clients with your disorder,
you've been the most
consistent at your job.
Did something happen, Barry?
How old are you?
Just... The Internet is
inconsistent on this point.
Why is that on your mind?
Who's gonna look after us
when you retire or pass on?
You know, we're gonna have to
take care of ourselves
and nobody even believes
that we exist.
If ever something
were to happen to me,
I've made arrangements with a colleague
from Baltimore to take over.
Hmm.
Hey, do you, uh...
You live alone?
You know this.
I'm sorry,
I just meant how long?
Always.
That must be so lonely.
Uh, you know what?
I'm doing much better.
I shouldn't have emailed you. I'm just...
Look at me.
I'm too impulsive.
By the way,
is anybody listening?
Does anybody care about us?
Yes.
The University of Paris has asked
me to do a lecture, in fact.
I'm going to be doing it
via Skype from right here.
People are believing more.
Let's meet at
our usual time next week.
I would rather
you didn't leave, Barry.
Did something happen?
Don't worry.
This was just a visit.
I'm doing much better,
I actually...
Don't you want
your sketches, Barry?
You're usually very
protective of them.
Yeah.
Thanks.
I'll see you next week
at our usual time.
Thanks for fighting
for us, Dr. Fletcher.
Thanks, Dr. Fletcher.
Welcome.
I just think
I'm gonna blow it.
No, you'll be great.
I'll see you next week.
Okay, thank you.
...DJ's exclusive million dollar
Holiday Bucks Bonanza.
I don't know how you work
with those people.
What people?
Your patients.
You can't use your thumbs
to spin the wheel, dumbasses.
They always use their thumbs.
Oh.
Well, we look at people who've been
shattered and different as less than.
What if
they're more than us?
What?
Do you believe them?
Your patients.
Just between you and me.
Yes, I do.
Hmm.
Flick it! Flick it!
...coming up next,
right after this.
I don't believe it.
No offense.
No.
...but when you call,
we'll send you
a second easyfeet
absolutely free!
Just pay separate processing.
So that's two easyfeet...
Now, that,
I need to buy that.
He's back.
There's a lady outside.
Dennis,
admit what you've done.
Don't get upset.
Don't tell me.
I'm getting frightened.
I thought that you had this
under control.
Please tell me
it's not too late.
The food is waiting.
Is she in that room?
We're here!
Help us!
We're in here!
What is this?
How many are there?
No, don't go in there!
Don't go in there!
Don't worry.
I'll talk to him.
He listens to me.
He's not well.
He knows
what you're here for.
He's not allowed
to touch you.
He knows that.
Mmm-mmm.
Hmm?
Karen.
Joe.
They said you can't have your own
panel at the national conference.
They conceded, however,
that you can be part of
the mood disorder panel.
It's not a mood disorder.
Oh, I'm aware of
your beliefs, Karen.
Well, were they open this
time with the new evidence?
One of your
arguments is a dog?
You submitted video of a
dog acting differently
to one of your patients
at different times?
It is more dramatic
than that.
They are what
they believe they are.
The brain has learned
to defend itself.
You speak of them like
they're supernaturally gifted.
Like they have
powers or something.
Karen, these are patients.
They have been
through trauma.
And perhaps now they are capable
of something we're not.
We have brain scans now.
DID patients have changed their
body chemistry with their thoughts.
He's just trying to
scare us.
He was having a full
conversation with himself.
What was that line about?
"The food is waiting."
Does everyone get
how wacked this is
and that we need to
get out of here now?
No.
Please, keep your area neat.
The bathroom,
it's unacceptable.
To make it easy,
I've color-coded these.
Use the blue bottle
for the floor
and the pink bottle
for the ceramic surfaces.
Uh...
Patricia has reminded me that I
was sent to get you for a reason.
That you are sacred food.
And I promise
not to bother you again.
Maybe he has a dog
or something.
You think he's gonna
feed us to his dogs?
Casey.
Casey!
My name's Hedwig.
I have red socks.
He's on the move.
What?
He's...
on...
the...
move.
Who?
Someone's coming for you
and you're not gonna
like it.
You guys make noises
in your sleep.
Tell us.
I'm not supposed to say.
But he's done
awful things to people
and he'll do
awful things to you.
I have blue socks, too.
We're his food?
How old are you?
Nine.
So you're not the guy
that took us?
No.
You're not the lady?
What are you, blind?
You don't know
how they think?
No, they don't tell me much.
I just ate a hot dog.
Could you help us, Hedwig?
No, I'm not even
supposed to be here.
I stole the light from Mr. Dennis,
but he'll be back real soon.
I can't steal the light for too
long or he'll know and get angry.
Etcetera.
See you!
Wait.
We heard something.
We didn't understand it,
but now we do.
Do you know what we heard?
What did you hear?
Come here.
I'll whisper it to you.
Okay.
This guy
is coming for you.
You're a big fibber.
I never lie, Hedwig.
But Mr. Dennis,
he said that he followed
those two girls for four days
and that he knew
that they were the ones
that he would want.
When you're not around,
Dennis and the lady
talk about it.
They talk about how he wants
a boy this time.
They're going to
give him you.
No, Miss Patricia,
she said...
She said she's not mad
at me anymore.
She sings to me sometimes.
I think Miss Patricia
is still a little mad at you.
Miss Patricia thinks I'm...
She thinks I'm stupid.
She thinks I make
silly mistakes.
Look at me.
We're like your babysitters.
We'll let you watch TV
and make you a fun dinner.
We all need to
get out of here.
You could show us
the way out.
We could be gone
before anybody gets back,
but we have to hurry, Hedwig.
We have to hurry
and get out of here.
Wait a minute.
It took forever to
get this place safe
without the nosey bodies
that work here finding out.
You can't get out of here!
I have to blow my nose.
No, wait!
Please don't go!
Who's coming?
This is
seriously scary.
No one's coming.
He said something.
He said something
about making the room safe.
This is
all new drywall.
What was unsafe?
Wait.
Wait, are we sure
about this?
Casey, you were right.
There's something here.
He was covering up a way out.
Tell me if you see him.
Casey,
tell us what you see.
He's here.
You can't let him in!
This is our one chance.
We're not gonna
make it.
Yes, we are!
What?
Hey, what are you guys doing?
Hey.
Okay, quit it.
Okay, guys?
Let me in.
Give us a second.
We're changing.
What are you guys doing?
Let me in.
Guys, you're not being funny.
You're being bitches!
Now, I'm gonna slap you!
I'm gonna slap you
in your face.
Just give me
as much time as you can.
You're gonna get me
into trouble.
Guys...
All right, push up.
Hey!
I thought I lost you.
Would you, uh...
Would you step outside,
please?
You like to make fun of us.
But we're more powerful
than you think.
Step outside.
Please.
You shouldn't trick children.
That shows who you are.
Look at your sweater.
It's ruined.
It's dirty.
Remove it.
I'm trying to be good.
You will not see
your friend again.
She will be kept separate.
You take off your skirt.
You take off your shirt.
Clothes you got
all dirty from the dust.
One identity in an individual with
Dissociative Identity Disorder
can have high cholesterol.
One.
There have been cases where one
identity is allergic to bee stings.
The others are not.
Are there moments where two identities
can coexist at the same time?
There are times
when two identities
can take the "light"
or "the spot"
or consciousness
at the same time.
This happened with a student
that I was working with.
And her left and right hand
were taking notes
in different handwritings about
separate things at the same time.
The differences in the
identities can be dramatic.
As much as the difference
between you and me
and every person
in that auditorium.
The identities
have different IQs.
They have different
physical strengths.
One personality is
a Russian weightlifter
and can lift three times
his body weight.
Their ability to hyper-focus
and have different
experiences is astounding.
Have these individuals,
through their suffering,
unlocked the potential
of the brain?
Is this the ultimate doorway
to all things
we call unknown?
Is this where our sense of
the supernatural comes from?
It's about depth
and curves...
Hey, you see that one?
It's kind of like
a chenille sweater-dress.
Who are you?
Barry.
I don't think you are.
I've developed
a nose for sensing
whom I'm talking to
and whom I'm not.
Have I done something?
You've emailed for
an unscheduled appointment
two days in a row.
We're just
feeling overwhelmed.
Garden-variety issues.
I think Orwell or Jade
or Samuel or Heinrich
had the light for a moment
and emailed me.
And you're here to
tell me everything's okay.
I emailed you.
May I talk to
one of them, please?
That can't happen.
I...
I told them that I wanted to
spend the session
with you today.
I'm gonna ask again.
To whom am I
speaking with now?
Dr. Fletcher, it's Barry.
It doesn't seem like Barry.
Barry is
an extroverted leader.
Yes, I am.
I'm gonna take
a professional guess
based on the description
of all 23 identities
that live in Kevin's body,
that I've gotten from Barry.
I think I'm talking
to Dennis.
But he's been banned
from the light
because, among other reasons,
he has a proclivity to watch
young girls dance naked,
which he himself knows
is wrong
and has fought against
with little success.
I'm encouraged
we can finally meet.
And I've guessed this
because you've adjusted the chocolate
dish twice since you came in here
and I understand
you have OCD.
I see. Now, I see.
That's clever.
That's clever,
but I'm not Dennis.
And you and Patricia have
been banned from the light
for quite a while now.
Primarily, shall we say,
because of your beliefs.
Patricia and Dennis
are very unstable.
I'm not Dennis.
Have you both
taken charge now?
Please believe me, I'm Barry.
You must forgive me.
My job is to challenge you.
And, as you must know by now,
I have plenty of
opinions about
how everyone should live
their lives.
Ask me something
about fashion.
I'll prove it.
Look, look, look. Lindt.
Yeah, look.
You see? I'm not Dennis.
You want me to do
something else?
You got ice cream?
Oh, this shirt's
a cotton blend anyway
and the collar is
from three seasons ago.
Snood? I mean, come on.
Jai, what health-conscious
fast food purveyor
did you originally solicit
to buy these chicken wings
you've so lovingly reheated
in a minor suicidal gesture?
Hooters. And you can't just
throw them out, Dr. Fletcher.
Oh, this is wrong
on so many levels.
We finished about 3:15,
so look around 3:18.
You're getting a little soft
around the middle, Jai. Mmm-hmm.
The authors of Hooters play
on our incessant need for fat
and man's incessant need to be in
the proximity of augmented breasts.
It's like Henry V
ran a fast food franchise.
It's a good place,
Dr. Fletcher.
Right.
How'd you know
the trash would be spilled?
How can I say this, Jai?
You're not the most
meticulous of people.
This guy isn't
very neat, is he?
He walked
right through the trash.
No, Jai.
Any normal person
would have walked around it.
That was an act.
What are you
up to, Dennis?
Or is it Patricia
who's deciding things?
We're not gonna die.
Bad things happen.
But not like this.
Casey...
Talk to me.
We need to get to a window
or a door, or something.
Don't you think?
The thrill, Casey,
is about whether you can
or can't
outsmart this animal.
See, you didn't used to
like to come out here.
This is like our
family tradition, right?
Good shot, big brother.
Thank you, John.
I have your meal, sleepyhead.
Eat.
It's good?
It's got paprika
in it.
I'm sorry.
I think I'll put a pretty
flower in your hair.
There we are.
That's to show
how important you are.
Come along.
We'll have a proper meal.
I understand.
This must all seem
so unsatisfactory for you.
But we are doing
the best we can.
Good?
Hmm?
Can Claire come eat with us?
No.
No, I'm afraid
that can't happen.
She almost ruined
our big reception.
Mmm...
I've heard that Asian people's
music aids digestion.
I'll make you
a second sandwich.
Do you know,
a family of lions
can eat 35 pounds a day?
A buck can lose 30% of its
weight during mating season,
chasing does around.
They're crepuscular, right?
It means they travel around
during dusk and dawn.
Good for you.
It's crooked.
Forgive me.
I don't know if you know,
but tigers have only 30 teeth.
That's 12 less than a dog.
I thought
that was a fun fact.
No.
Marcia.
Marcia, listen to me.
Go to your room.
Shut the door.
Do it now.
"In the sun,
we will find our passion.
we will find our purpose."
You've always
been protected.
You've never
truly suffered.
And that's why
we chose you.
You've always been asleep.
You never had a chance.
The dark-haired girl,
she's gonna be kept in another closet.
You might as well know
at this point.
The Beast,
he's coming for you.
All three of you, you're
gonna be kept separate.
You've got...
You've got a crumb
on your shirt.
Please take it off.
Just...
Just take it off.
Hey.
Ah.
It wasn't nice,
what you said about Miss Patricia.
You lied.
I'm sorry
about that, Hedwig.
You guys lied to me,
made me scared, etcetera.
Mr. Dennis, he says
you wear a lot of shirts.
I like this shirt.
Thank you.
Do you know who Dennis
and Miss Patricia are?
No.
Every one of us
has to wait in a chair,
and Barry, he decides
who stands in the light.
But Barry lost that power
because of me.
I can wish myself into the
light anytime I want.
It's a special power.
Barry just has to keep sitting
in his chair if I want him to.
That's why Dennis and Miss Patricia
said I could be with them.
Dennis and Miss Patricia,
they believe in The Beast
and what he can do.
Have you seen him?
The Beast?
No. Can I kiss you?
I wanted to kiss the other
girl with the dark hair,
but she's in trouble.
So, do you want to?
I mean, I don't know
much about kissing, though.
Yeah.
Okay.
Uh...
Okay, here we go.
One...
Two...
Three.
You might be pregnant now.
Am I a good kisser?
Yeah.
I like dancing.
Do you like dancing?
I like dancing to
my CD player in my room.
Kanye West
is my main man.
We got my CD player
set up in my room,
right next to my window.
I'm like...
We gots the moves.
Wow.
Maybe I could watch you dance
and listen to music with you.
No, my music's in my room.
Oh. Right.
Maybe
you could sneak me there.
Are you trying
to trick me?
Etcetera?
I'll tell on you.
I'm telling on you.
I'll tell you something.
And you can tell me
if I'm lying or not, okay?
Mmm-hmm.
Like a test. Okay?
I get into trouble
at school, on purpose.
So I can get sent
to detention.
To get away from everyone.
So that I can be alone.
Okay, I'll show you
something cool in my room.
Okay.
But after Mr. Dennis has finished
his getting-ready ritual.
I have to go.
He's got an appointment.
When I fall asleep,
one of the others keeps trying
to reach the doctor lady
to tell on us.
That pant,
it's got a red lining.
You can see it in
the long slit down the side.
We have been talking about
silk-and-wool blend for 20 minutes.
Can I guess that you emailed
me in the middle of the night
for an emergency session
due to garden-variety issues?
I was down and I emailed you and
I woke up and I feel better.
I feel better.
I had a thought.
Mmm-mmm.
I want to talk about
the incident at work.
It's okay, Barry.
You're safe.
I just want to bring
the details back.
We'll just talk
about the details.
A high school from
Camden, New Jersey
was on a field trip
at your place of work
and two young ladies
came up to you.
And one took your hand
and put it under her shirt
on her breast
and the second one
did the same
and then they just ran off
laughing to their friends.
You surmised that it
might be on a dare.
You said
they were 17 or 18.
it upset you for days.
It was just a teenage prank.
I get that now.
And see,
that's my mistake.
I believe that I went over this
incident with you too fast.
Although you said
you were fine,
and the other identities
I met with said it was fine,
I believe that
this brought up issues
from when you were
a child and abused.
Sometimes another
incident of abuse
can cause suppressed
personalities to take the light.
Dennis, if this is you,
I completely understand
why you felt the need to take
over and protect the others.
Please!
Doctor, not this again.
The others told me
that you and Patricia told
the group about this Beast.
And I told them that these
are just scary stories
that Dennis and Patricia tell
the others to scare them.
How this Beast
can crawl on walls,
like the best rock climbers using the
slightest friction and imperfections
to hold his body close
to seemingly sheer surfaces.
How his skin is thick and tough
like the hide of a rhinoceros.
Do you really believe
the stories about The Beast?
Hmm.
If this is you, Dennis,
I understand
why Kevin needs you.
You are strong
and disciplined.
You are precise
and you will not be
taken advantage of.
You can trust me.
For example,
I do have the ability to use Kevin's
full name and bring him forward
as he has in the past.
But I wouldn't do that.
I know that that would
be chaos for all of you.
Everyone would
grab the light.
I don't want to hurt
any of you that way.
You don't have to hide.
I know you are someone
who cares for Kevin.
You are not evil to me.
You were necessary.
Dennis.
Is that you?
They keep calling us
The Horde.
The others, you know?
Miss Patricia and I,
we are ridiculed.
Now, we're not perfect,
but we don't deserve to be ridiculed.
We're all struggling.
They have to admit that.
I am pleased to
meet you, Dennis.
You, too.
I assume you don't know who emailed
me for the emergency sessions?
One of the others.
Are you in charge?
Yeah,
we've taken charge.
We're the only ones
that can protect Kevin.
We're all here
to protect Kevin.
He's very weak.
He doesn't know
how powerful we can be.
Would you mind telling me when
you first came into existence?
And how you and Patricia,
the other undesirable identity,
became aligned?
That's okay.
Do you still have
strong beliefs?
That depends on what.
This story of The Beast.
One thing, Dennis, that may
comfort you if you are confused
is that you've met
the other alters.
You're all in a room
in chairs, right?
Yeah.
But you never met
The Beast.
Because he doesn't reside
with the rest of you.
Because he resides in the train
yard, as the story goes,
because Kevin's dad
left on a train.
But the fact is,
you and Patricia have
never met The Beast.
Have you?
No.
That's because
he's not an alter.
He's not the 24th identity.
He's a fantasy.
Hurry up! Let's go!
Come on, it's time.
Wow.
I know.
This is your CD player?
Yeah.
You don't like it?
It's not new...
No!
No, I'm just, uh...
I'm confused.
You said
it was near a window.
Oh, that's here!
Watch.
Now, it's closed.
Now, it's open.
Did you think
it was a real window?
So you could leave, etcetera?
Help me get out
of here, Hedwig.
Just get me the keys
and let me out the door.
Please.
Miss Patricia says that nobody
will make fun of me anymore
when The Beast comes!
She says that everyone
will see how amazing I am
and then all of the silly mistakes,
they won't matter anymore.
I think you should go
back to your room. No!
Wait, please,
I wanna hear
your Kanye West albums.
Show me your room.
Let's stay here.
I'm sorry I asked to leave.
I can't.
You said you wanted to show
me something cool, right?
No.
Show me something. Please!
I don't want to.
This!
Wow.
It's nice.
It's not a toy.
This is real?
Yes!
It's Mr. Dennis'.
He doesn't even know
I stole it.
Pretty cool, right?
You can listen
to people talking
and they don't even know
you're listening.
Who does this talk to?
Don't touch that.
I just wanna see
if it works.
Hey, what are you doing?
Don't touch those buttons.
You're gonna get us found out.
Yeah, East gate here.
What up?
Don't talk.
Hello?
I'm gonna slap you!
Who's this?
Hello. Hello,
my name is Casey Cooke.
I'm being held in a basement.
I've been abducted with two other girls.
Who the hell is this?
Hello?
Casey Cooke.
I've been abducted.
You need to find me.
Betty, is that you?
This isn't funny.
Call the police.
I must be near you.
I'm being held
in a basement or something.
Okay, Betty, listen.
Tell Larry and Fish
I said hi.
Tell him I still got
his orange headphones.
I don't know where I am.
There's a man here.
He abducted us
and he's going to kill me.
I only have
a few hours left.
Please.
I'm begging you.
Somebody save us.
Wait, who is this?
And how did you get
one of our walkies?
Put your hands
together in contrition.
"In the sun,
we will find our passion.
"we will find our purpose."
I read that on a sympathy
card in a supermarket.
It was for funerals,
but I thought it was beautiful.
Dennis will explain the
meaning of this evening.
The Beast is
a sentient creature
who represents the highest
form of humans' evolution.
He believes the time of
ordinary humanity is over.
I hope this makes you
feel calm.
You will be in the presence
of something greater.
I was gonna ask
for your last shirt,
but I won't.
Because tonight
is a sacred night.
It's almost over.
Casey. Come on.
Let's pretend
we're animals again.
Come on.
Casey, come on.
This is our game.
I'll tell your dad
you're not being nice.
Come on,
take off your stuff.
Animals don't
wear clothes.
Come on.
Yeah, yeah.
Hey, Casey bear.
This isn't funny.
Is it loaded?
Casey.
I'm your uncle.
Stop it, Casey.
Put that gun down.
I'm getting upset.
I'm about to get very angry.
Give me the gun!
Could have killed me.
This place is closed. You can't get in.
No, it's okay.
Hello, Dennis.
One of the others
emailed me just now.
Is everything okay?
We're fine.
Dennis,
Kevin is really lucky
to have you.
You are quite extraordinary.
I just don't want
you guys to get hurt.
You think
we're extraordinary?
I like you, Dennis.
May I come in?
And can we talk?
I know you wanna
tell me something.
Why don't you just tell me?
We're very similar,
you and I.
Both on the outside,
looking in.
Please, sit.
I don't get many visitors.
Uh, I'll get you some water.
They got a proper
quarters for me
in a building
on the south side,
but we prefer it here.
When they promoted me
to head of maintenance,
they said I could have it.
Who are you
going to meet?
I wanna talk about
Kevin
and what his mother
did to him.
I remember it all.
I'm happy you're
suddenly so open.
Kevin's mother had
rather malevolent ways
of punishing
a three-year-old.
Is that when you arrived
in the light?
Yeah.
The one way to
avoid her attention
was to keep
everything spotless,
everything perfect.
I know you're coming from
good intentions, Dennis,
but there are other ways
to help Kevin now.
I've lost so many patients
into the system.
I want you to know, Dennis, I
will never stop fighting for you.
My patients have
become my family.
They are what I've chosen instead
of a more traditional path.
I hope you feel you can
be truly honest with me.
I actually wanna be
honest with you.
I lied before.
When you asked
if I'd ever met The Beast,
I said no.
That really isn't true.
You wrote about a woman in Germany
who'd been blind for 10 years.
And then, it was discovered
that she had DID.
Then three of her identities
developed sight.
And you speculated that her
optical nerves regenerated
because of her beliefs.
What are you
trying to say?
There are things,
Dr. Fletcher,
that all of us would
find hard to believe.
Are you trying to tell me
there's a 24th identity?
You protect the broken.
When you said that you thought
this situation was extraordinary,
I knew you can
maybe understand.
Understand what?
The Beast
is real.
He's just emerged.
You were right
about everything.
What does he look like?
He's much bigger than I am
and I'm the biggest
of all of us.
He's tall.
He's very muscular.
And he's got
a long mane of hair
and his fingers are
twice the length of ours.
He believes
we are extraordinary.
That we don't represent a mistake,
but our potential.
You say the same things.
He's on the move.
What does that mean?
I don't understand.
He can't be real.
There must be limits to what
a human being can become.
And there's another
whole part
of the story, isn't there?
About the eating
of the impure young?
What does impure even mean?
Well...
We should discuss that
so that you can
understand fully.
Understand what?
Sometimes,
there's just no other way.
Who are you going to meet?
Him.
You know what?
I would love to take notes
on all of this.
We should
probably discuss this
in a proper session tomorrow.
Really?
You're okay with this?
This has been so wonderful,
you being so open.
I can see that
you feel very empowered
by the philosophies
of The Beast.
I'm going to go now.
I knew you would understand.
I'll see you.
Would you mind
if I used your bathroom?
No.
It's down the hall,
near the stairs, on your left.
How we doing?
I'm okay.
Are you real?
Who is it?
Help me.
Is someone there?
Please help me.
They will never reach
their potential.
They don't really matter.
Listen to me, Dennis.
I should've listened better.
I should've understood
what you're capable of,
how powerful you are.
Patricia says your way
isn't working.
The world
will understand now.
Dennis, this is
an egregious wrong.
These young women
are suffering.
This is a crime.
I can't let you
keep them here.
We've gotta stop this.
This identity is monstrous.
I'm really sad
you feel this way.
Can't you see?
He is formed because of
your time in this place.
There's a lady.
Someone's here.
We need to
get out of these rooms.
Is there anything
in your room?
Anything that we could use?
There's nothing
in here.
There's a hanger.
Thank you, Dennis.
Here you go, sir.
It sounded like there were slide
bolts on the outside of our doors.
See if you can move the lock
through the crack in the door.
Stay calm.
We're getting out of here.
We're gonna get Casey.
You can do this, Marcia.
With regard to
Chahamana's defeat
and Muhammad of Ghor's
conquests
between 1192 and 1200,
I would liken it to
Muhammad's brazen ultimatum
that Prithviraj
either apostatize or fight.
Like Prithviraj's defiance,
we should stand up
to The Horde's advances.
In the face of their scare tactics,
we should show...
I hate my insulin shots.
No one else around here
has to take them.
Why do I have to
have diabetes?
All the doctors,
besides Dr. Fletcher,
say that we're
the same person.
Just personalities, huh?
How do you explain
I'm the only one
that needs these,
you motherfuck...
I'm wearing cargo pants
from the '90s.
And a scarf.
If it wasn't for the Varvatos
T-shirt underneath,
I'd be a mess.
I got no taste
for things right now.
I'm worried sick.
I have a very bad feeling
that I'm losing time.
I decide
who gets the light, right?
I think
someone is stealing the light
from me when I'm not aware.
The Horde keeps obsessing about
the ones who haven't suffered.
I don't know where they're going
with this, but it scares me.
Picture yourself
in a couple hours at home.
On the couch,
in that ugly-ass sweatshirt
that you love.
It's an animal!
He goes like this if there's
a coyote or something.
Kevin, Kevin.
Thank you
for helping us till now.
I guess I should tell
Dr. Fletcher about this,
but she'll worry.
She's such a sweet woman.
I believe I will go
for a nice walk
and think this
through organizationally.
Thus ends my journal
for Monday.
Ciao.
Claire.
Marcia.
Claire, let's go.
"Kevin Wendell Crumb."
Kevin Wendell Crumb?
Kevin Wendell Crumb.
Kevin Wendell Crumb!
You made a mess.
Come out here.
Kevin Wendell Crumb!
You made a mess!
Get out here!
Who are you?
What's happening?
Something horrible.
What'd I do?
Did I hurt you?
Dr. Fletcher.
Who did that?
You did.
I swear, I was on a bus.
I don't remember
anything after that. I...
This is still
September 18, 2014, right?
There's a shotgun I bought.
It's in the bottom cabinet,
hidden behind things.
The shells are in my uniform
closet out in the service hall.
Kill me.
Then kill me.
Wait, no!
Don't do that!
He can't handle reality.
My name is Jade.
Has Dr. Fletcher been
getting our emails?
This is what we have to do.
As in 1008,
when Anandapala suffered the
Shahis' most crushing defeat
and Mahmud overran the
entirety of the Punjab region,
taking the famed temple
of Kangra,
we have been wronged
by this alliance,
this horde of Patricia,
Dennis and the boy.
Their actions
do not represent us.
They are every...
Everybody,
just take a minute!
Oh, baby girl.
They've been stealing control
of the light from me.
But the group
are gonna work through this.
Honey, my name is Barry.
You shouldn't
have used the walkie-talkie.
They almost caught us.
Stop it, Hedwig!
They were right.
Look at you.
You're so frightened of us.
Dennis and Miss Patricia
are in charge because of me.
I'm gonna give the light
to them now.
No one's allowed to
make fun of me anymore.
Thank you, Hedwig.
Everything's fine now.
Kevin Wendell Crumb.
Kevin is asleep.
We've made him sleep
far away.
You can call his name
all you like, dear,
but he's not
going to hear you.
The Beast has
shared with us his dream
of a larger group
to sustain him.
No.
Ten to 12 unworthy young
next time.
This is just
the start.
Let go!
Help!
No! No!
No.
It runs in our family.
My daddy died, too.
Same way.
Heart attack.
But you don't need
to worry.
I'm going to
take care of you.
Now,
you won't be giving me
any trouble, will you?
I know you won't, sweetie.
We are glorious!
We will no longer be afraid.
Only through pain
can you achieve
your greatness!
The impure
are the untouched,
the unburned, the unslain.
Those who have not been torn
have no value in themselves
and no place in this world!
They are asleep!
Fuck!
Your gun cannot hurt me.
Can't you see
I am not human?
Kevin is a man.
I am much more.
You are different
from the rest.
Your heart is pure!
Rejoice!
The broken
are the more evolved.
Rejoice.
What in the name
of Mary and Joseph?
What are you doing
in this area?
Just keep walking, honey.
They won't do nothing.
Vince, call the police.
She said some people got hurt
in the area below maintenance.
Okay.
Now, I'm just gonna
check you.
Third deceased name of Dr.
Karen Fletcher.
Still trying to
locate the family.
Casey Cooke's guardian's here.
Your uncle's here.
You ready to go?
It didn't go through.
We are
what we believe we are.
Holy shit!
This is so cool!
They're gonna believe
we exist now, right?
They're gonna have to.
So what do we do now?
We trust in him.
He'll protect us.
Look at what he can do.
Let him show the world
how powerful we can be.
The suspected
murderer Kevin Crumb
suffers from the controversial
psychological disorder DID.
The rumors coming out of the
scene are almost unbelievable.
There are conflicting stories
if the suspect is alive or dead
after sustaining
two point-blank gunshots.
Reports even indicate
one of his personalities
is an amalgam of
the various animals
in the Philadelphia Zoo
where he worked.
The press is already referring
to the alleged attacker
by a dark name leaked by
a source close to the case.
Because of his many personalities,
he is being called
The Horde.
This is like that crazy
guy in the wheelchair
that they put away
15 years ago.
And they gave him
a funny name, too.
What was it?
Mr. Glass.
Oh, yeah.
Someone needs to stop Clearway Law.
Public shouldn't leave reviews for lawyers.