Sub download wara.kentir.bb ~. ::. W-BB.org. ::.
Carmen, Juni, [see] meludah.
Did you brush your ...
-I.
Juni, do not forget ...
-Vern, I know.
Warts.
Meet your unièevalca.
Is at school right?
-Yes, of course.
Turn lue.
-What is a fairy tale?
What do you want to hear?
-About two spies who fall in love.
It has long been not telling.
You remember better than me.
June?
Listening.
-It.
One lived di Male female.
-They were spies. -Yes.
They came from different countries.
She got an important task.
-The task has been decreasing.
She had to get rid of the ga.
-How?
You know what I mean.
That they should not tell.
-HEN, tidak. -UNTUK sehingga Easi were severe.
People sehingga of fear created a new
Army. Sehingga soldiers were brave.
Their weapon-American
sehingga been brain.
These men di woman
sehingga were spies.
Sehingga were masters of disguise.
Far from sehingga perceived threat.
Sehingga wars end up,
Before sehingga is desired.
Spies sehingga feared
Just the other spies.
Enemy.
Sehingga Sometimes they have to get rid of.
She should get rid of him,
what has changed my life.
While at the moment
to complete the task ...
She could not.
He was adopt another way, as she thought.
He was di oèarljiv clear.
As well as East.
She realized that in di Years
suppress their feelings.
Contacts are maintained.
Secretly are several times the SLA
at lunch. They were the enemy,
No one therefore should not appear together.
They hang out on mission.
They fell in love.
They opted for the most dangerous
mission of all time. -What?
They wanted to get married.
At the reporting date is recognized
I prefer to go to war.
Why?
Marriage is a complex task.
Survive only by persistent and courageous ones.
It is necessary to overcome many difficult
barriers. These include the family.
This is the dreaded
Even experienced secret agent.
But when she saw him, he saw
that it is not even iota of doubt.
He was deferred to carry out the task.
She took him by the hand
and he looked deep into the eyes.
Sentencing is the most dangerous word
in the world. -What?
She said that .
Crazy.
Sehingga then I started getting problems.
They should always wanted to kill the WHO.
Ze respectively were notorious,
As per nominal were
any temptation Tara.
Both are retired.
Stabilized both di have children.
They moved to new
Towards dogodivšèinam.
Parenting is a challenge, as the
espionage. Now the sreènejša.
Will be happy
melakukan end of our days? -Yes.
A beautiful fairy tale, only the end
soap is not like it. -I want monsters. -Really?
Show.
-But I have greased. -Good.
Good night.
Which story you told?
-Surface.
The child will again tlaèile lebih.
Carmen-the mere asking.
UNTUK life for us.
Now we adviser, not a spy.
Denmark I went to the principal.
Carmen Solo certificate.
-Why?
Do not know.
Do you know June classmate?
Yeah, Diego di Renalda.
Apparently, the only putting it.
No friends.
Over-the-sanjaè.
Creates drawings èudne di staring
what silly children's show.
Some Nama reset, Gregorio.
We were guilty.
Ee to tell them that we were
spies, the child lived in fear.
Speaking of secrets ...
What are you doing? -Nie.
Nie important.
Why do we have any UNTUK poèeti
morning? As we have in the school gym.
Barefoot all day hanging out, wimp?
Do not look down.
DRSI-I.
Of course, you Stor.
Hurry up.
-I can not ...
You fell three hundred feet deep.
Palaèinka you. -I.
That you will not stumble,
palaèinka.
Services.
We will be-seen.
Donnagon? -Missing a.
-You UNTUK poèel last night?
I did not want to bother.
Welcome to Floopovem world.
Why UNTUK watching Juni?
As a soap-like.
Just UNTUK doing. Video games di
television. You know, why not UNTUK Good?
Always believe you.
These dreams will be realized.
You, you, di you.
-Is UNTUK your portrait?
UNTUK is your portrait?
-Mom, mimics saya!
Mom, mimics saya! -Peace, Carmen.
But you can not imitate, Juni.
Look how the GRD. -Talk
with him. -Fooglija I drew.
Denmark will meet November figure.
Last night was crawling around the castle.
Meet Donnamighta.
Ee will make igraèo,
I want to have it, Dad.
Ljubèek ...
I'm sorry.
Juni,
Ee you someone teased remembers
you Cortezov.
UNTUK What is special?
-Of course.
Mummy came.
Beautiful trusses have. Peace-mil NOW.
Listen, EE talk to you.
Cute Dolls have. Show.
Enjoy, Doša. Show who's boss.
I can help, maèo?
I can help, I
asked. Because the soap seemed to fail.
My OEI will beat yours.
Anything you do not prikrivajva vee.
Soon.
In the same room we, because they are afraid. Teach ga
I, What is it di wrong.
I am responsible only for himself.
-You are right, Carmen.
And What if I Cortezov?
I want to live in your world, Floop.
You'd be my friend.
Thank you for attending
presentations.
Year after year a rich
reward the inventor.
G. Floop is one of the visionaries,
his invention is sehingga questionable.
They need to be checked.
You promised us army
sheba the billion dollars we get
Just this. Mutant secret agent.
Due to processing them sehingga
brain is transformed into foam.
Usable only sehingga
for Children award,
which is currently
second most watched.
What's the point, hell?
Inches sehingga-trained robots.
Begitu useless.
Here vampaneze will love it.
The door will be possible to enter
being. You must disarm.
You will be ZEE 10 seconds.
7th
5th
Third
First
You hesitated.
You-I. My Doša it.
Are you sure?
I am ga created.
His name is X-52495.
You have developed robots that resemble
to my child?
The President's hei?
Almost a perfect fake.
Sometimes appear to be
great idea of ​​the minimum.
You can create
any image.
Sophistication di s greatest clarity
spies hiding in a child.
UNTUK spies jadi mali.
But tell little spy,
Ee are, these repositories of knowledge.
Which hewan peliharaan character issue,
that person bermalas-malasan?
The process is not completed. They lack
an essential component. -What?
Brain.
Nobody will be stranded, says that jadi
Children. EASA is no longer in abundance.
ZEE TWO DAYS occur after the army.
Lahiri took what you had.
Ee is vampaneze seems that you can not,
soaps offer before it's too late.
G. Lisp accompanied
melakukan chopper, baby.
Genius, sir.
-Thank you, Minion.
Now I have to
I really trained.
Where are you going?
-I task.
Donnagon di other agents
sehingga disappeared as Camphor.
Bos, after nine years adopted the task?
Why? -Devlin is guilty.
Called personally? -Please saya is
Should I work. With you-go.
Ingrid, I know you wanna get
task, but now have children.
I wish pustolovšèine.
I would like to solve the dunes. AGAIN-driven?
Ee was not involved Donnagon,
to reject the task. There is no doubt.
Bos also rejected me?
Vohunèek?
Ingrid ...
What about children?
Uncle Felix. -How's it going? When I
Last saw you guys, were higher.
Grab. -Thank you for coming.
Therefore, we have a family.
I know you?
Again, it is so ...
As in the old-different sovereign and ma.
S-414 call you Cecilia.
Išèeva missing agents.
Ingrid di Gregorio Cortez.
It's nice to hear these two names. Good-
evening, Miss. Gradenko. -Greg ...
Sincerely, ga. Cortez.
-Report. Ze-loading.
Why they can not call?
Will soon be home. -You are right.
It's been a decade,
we think we are only on the child.
The meeting will be ...
Delta, bravo ... Repeat-place.
Loviva sinyal television.
Ingrid di Gregorio Cortez,
have something I want.
UNTUK is Floop. Someone Nama follows.
The non-Nama long.
Now what?
What is the point?
They have us.
Carmen was such
Ee would Fooglie.
Alarm
Oh my God.
The fire-drill?
for emergency
Try this. We do not have EASA ...
For me. Go, go.
Marsièesa Sun corrective api pendek.
-Uncle Felix.
First you need to know that I
your uncle. Parents sehingga spies.
Good point.
What are you talking about? -My job is
to take care of you. It went wrong.
We need a safe house. My parents-
Wacky already not enough.
UNTUK is crazy.
Apparently jadi they went to Asia.
Or in South America.
Be right back. What, however, EE is not?
Press the blue-green di key.
Sala is the point?
Look, Carmen.
The safe house will be
without me. [See]. -Watch out, Felix.
OSS ovcem tell
The third brain to live. Necessary.
Watch out.
-What sehingga this say?
Di Blue Green button. -Felix
We can not just leave. -Can.
The blue zapeèatiš door. Fast.
Here is Green.
First-Blue!
Always ALL zamoèiš. We got to the door
zapeèatiti. Blue-I can not find.
Get ready.
What sehingga this say?
Non-OSS, sheba catching up with us.
Where is the gas?
No-touch!
You fool, you manually turn steering.
How this works ree?
This has been programmed,
that drove us to safety.
June?
What are you doing down there, Juni?
-Help!
Hang on. Solve this Lahiri.
Autopilot switched on again
We'll be late for class.
Stop shaking.
I can-not. -Stop,
otherwise you will have a What's more warts.
ALL the good ended.
Just obey saya.
-It.
welcome.
Do not touch anything, Juni.
Juni ...
Direction: Safe House.
EAS trip: 2 hours 30 minutes dalam.
Juni do not see.
Why not? Self-obey.
Now you can look.
Thank you.
-I do not want to cry.
Never again do not see him.
sehingga snacks ready.
Want to hear a lullaby, sir?
begin to flush the poop.
Yeah, yeah.
Very dangerous.
UNTUK ITU supaya Floopove Characters from the shows.
Begitu prisoners.
We need a brain.
EASA we are running out.
Do not worry, sir. Ingrid
Di Gregorio, the only agent
who never had weak points.
Now you have two.
Did you lock?
-I.
UNTUK the safe house?
-Previously koèa.
NAME?
Carmen Cortez. Even -name .
-Too long.
Even the name, please . Carmen-
Elizabeth Echo Sky Brava Cortez.
My name Password?
This house is marvelous.
Empty.
What is the safe house is heavy,
Ee is not anything to polong Teeth?
Golok?
Cash for emergencies?
From all countries.
All of which took Lahiri.
Have you seen?
Thank you, Carmen.
AGAIN we see them, as promised.
Why would you ever what they believe?
Do not worry. -Diapers is worn.
Only one di-only at night.
That's why I did not want
To undertake the duties.
Is about an hour ago
You were all from ratanya yourself.
Now I am a prisoner of war.
SVA-bit rusty.
Interested saya, who is behind all this.
I just pressed properly.
We are still.
You alone UNTUK do?
What about me?
Do you remember how we once were
always perceived threat?
UNTUK ITU supaya were Easi!
-Yes.
Ljubèek ...
Bistro.
Come on, come on.
Very clever.
Virtual room.
Let's go.
Where are we?
You gotta admit,
that has a vivid imagination.
They can have hours Fourth growth.
I am expecting that they will be better
fared. Finally you can eat.
So you are Floop. -Monitor the
my show? No, it Doša.
It's wonderful.
Hei does not?
Carmen, right?
Juni decreasing.
Soon you will join us.
Caution.
Ee I snap my fingers ...
My fingers slap you.
Where sehingga agents?
12 years ago helped create jadi
artificial intelligence,
which would consolidate spy
knowledge in the world.
Results sehingga destroy.
-Certainly sehingga know èemu.
Everyone has their own reason.
Among the researchers was somebody.
Someone who could give us the results
return. So, g. Cortez?
Will be a bestseller. Point right now,
when approaching holidays.
Lahiri does not help you.
Thank you for joining us.
How to become a spy?
The author is unknown.
good spy ...
-Test.
Madonna, too close to you. Tanah Liat,
considering that a good spy with my head.
Disgusting.
-What do you see? -You.
Funny.
Zoom oèem glasses.
Maps.
You see some kind of database.
Fairytale wedding ...
Their is.
You could told us.
What is Diego di-Renaldo?
You're not honest?
Bos-told that špricaš Solo?
UNTUK communication is not Tiee.
Carmen ...
-I have no keys. What the rift.
good spy knows no fear.
You will not be pos spy Juni.
good spy or spy
As a thinking opponent.
Thinking ...
It UNTUK we do.
I think it all depends on us.
-What? -We need to find a CMS sheep.
Odriniva.
I Miss. Gradenko.
I work for yours parents.
I understand that no soap trust. When
Have we seen you was still a baby.
Now remember, the saya?
The Key I have.
On the same page we are.
-Mom has the same bracelet.
We've all of us working
in the CMS. -Have you colleagues? -Yes.
Well listen up.
Dad sent us a message,
before we lose the connection.
F-L-O-O-P.
Floop?
Floop already doing so Eesa
such. -Believe that.
You know? -UNTUK sehingga Floopovi
Foogliji. I Igraèe.
Such sehingga been before mutation.
Jadi really secret agents? -Floop is
genius. -I knew that èudak.
You know the cute little song?
Dialed by Lahiri from back to front.
Floop is a lunatic.
Save us!
Call you to help. -Will do UNTUK
also the mother di oèijem? -Yes.
Except, EE gave him the Father,
as required.
Ee Eesa is reminiscent ...
What is it?
Felix said that vampaneze Morava
transmitted message. -Tell.
The third living brain.
Carmen, you just joined the
OSS spy-a.
Ingenious.
The third brain where they live?
Said?
No.
Are you sure?
ALL preišèite. The house we did not
find it. -Have you been in our home?
No.
Oh my God.
There.
UNTUK Floop wants to have?
A wonderful begitu.
Floop to work.
UNTUK lulusan deliver on g. Floop.
Non-ganite is!
I do not even corrective pendek api, what is the point.
Vern, it is difficult ree. -Equipment
It costs millions of dollars.
The brain can protect
Mom di oèija.
Stop it!
Send thumbs.
Hang on.
UNTUK How does it work?
-Bring it back.
Do not want to see parents, punk?
I'm sorry.
Get out.
Vampaneze What is it?
Just as a child.
A bad haircut.
Up!
Ooops.
What is it?
-Where are you? -For him. You?
I Peèen.
Return mild brain.
You think you're from hell, what?
See you.
Sister.
I can not stand anymore. -Well, the prime,
otroèaj. DRSI-I.
Hang on, Stor.
Non-soap will succeed.
We'll arrive any minute.
Non-release saya. -Not Lahiri.
What would you do without me?
My Children, the world is beautiful.
Is full of jerks Drives Me Crazy.
Follow  soaps
You are ALL free.
See  saya,
di dream, dream.
Dream a dream of mine.
Duni is a beautiful,
full of jerks Drives Me Crazy.
But you can  polepšaš Day.
Laugh and join us.
Dream a dream of mine.
my dream.
Cut!
Lock them.
What he needs?
-WHO? My-broadcast!
He needs something that will always bring back
in the first place. I feel, What is the point,
but can not concentrate.
Too, you deal with the award.
What is Our cruel plan?
-Unions? No, the army of children.
Robots sehingga DEATH
for my creativity.
Have you lost a child? -They ran away
di took third brain.
There?
-Yes. Cortez lied.
Send the best thumbs. -If you want to
Web zloèinca send zloèinca.
If you want to spy takes ...
No-talk in riddles, Minion.
Ee išèete child ...
Send your child.
Ingenious, Minion.
-Thank you.
What kind of tracking device is a point?
Do not read the coordinates.
Who makes this say?
Golok .
So already we will not solve
their parents.
Mom you are looking from di OEI,
unièiva the brain.
What do you know?
Brain We'll keep for now.
The bracelet is maybe
tracking device.
You're an idiot, not me.
Stop saya insult. -And, of Lahiri EE SE?
Then Lahiri-I love you too.
Teèka was right.
UNTUK hate.
I got rid of these?
Why are you dressed as a nerd?
We did vee relative. Get out.
Getting more and more stupid.
Leave-saya.
UNTUK I always wanted to do.
You are Moeen, What?
June!
Leave-saya.
Destroy the brain.
I want those shoes!
Took a brain?
-Yes.
Did not notice it when I tore it
pendant. What they did, too clear.
little spies, limited edition.
1 of the 500th
Floop will generate five hundred.
-Got the brains.
Create an army.
We have solved my mom di oèija.
WHO Nama will help?
We did it. We created
intelligent robot.
Devoted to the brain.
Penggunakan third brain system.
Director of OSS but he realized that he would
Technology can get an opponent.
Therefore, we destroy the project.
Why this soap jikalau tidak say?
Because you destroy ALL.
Maybe you neèesa.
Got the secrets in front of me
di children. UNTUK the Depag konèati.
Brain wants. Ee rešiva ​​children
postaviva Council on the cube.
What do we do?
Thanks, but we have only so much.
What am I doing here.
Oèetovo-secret name of the Hombre.
UNTUK the Golok.
He is oèijeva-witness reports.
What are you doing?
Making The smallest camera
in the world. -I was not.
She sees you.
Izdeluješ intelligent robots?
-Go back to your parents. We can-not be.
We need help.
I We gotta get. -Who are they?
Carmen Elizabeth
Echo Sky Brava Cortez.
Our father Gregorio Cortez.
-You were in his wedding.
Turn the di go.
I do not want to hear my brother's vee
names. Our Si-uncle? -True?
We have one that is not true.
My younger zanaki cue-Gregorio.
The President's hei dalam Doša.
Doša prime ministers, generals daughter.
ALL sehingga here.
As I planned.
Award-saya waiting.
Osredotoèite the project.
Create an army of g. Lisp.
In UNTUK do not believe anymore.
Because I never.
Explain. Mutated agents di-
robotic children sehingga your ideas.
Dalam?
Non-operating.
Do not be.
You know, now I have a third brain
so you do not need anymore.
Minion?
Now I have for you g. Minion.
Serves its purpose, Floop.
Children, lock the ga
in the virtual room.
Secret agency, did not you?
-You think so?
Constantly traveling di nobody knows Sun,
with EIM for a living.
Not all these uncles?
Is a great product  Golok.
Izdeluješ best spyware
assistive devices. Thus, it is.
But they also sell zloèincem,
OEI so do not talk to you.
What do you sell Floopu?
Why? Your cue di-zanaki our mother
as his prisoner.
Help, otherwise severe.
Why do not want to help?
-All my life I have to watch it.
Watch Gregorio. Learned ga,
What is Good di bad.
Golok is responsible only for himself.
We're family.
SVA-only brothers.
Also di Cain Abel was.
Apak Floopovega castle will
Just arrived soon enough with this.
Fine is.
-Only one passenger was.
You gonna go? -No.
-The Brothers? -No.
And for us?
Your neèakinja di neèak SVA.
No.
What about ...
No, no di Sun
Hand soap prašièje èrevo.
Lahiri does not eat.
You can get ...
-No.
A glass of water. -Thank you,
We can 't be with you to wait,
What will be the fate of their parents.
-Cortezova are.
So you mean the family
more than money.
No.
Even Father-misses.
Ready?
-Let's go.
UNTUK the point.
What are you doing? -We need
map Floopovega castle.
Just a reflex.
Is still asleep.
Adults can not
carry out child labor.
UNTUK!
How can I help you?
-Remember the spy plane?
Read more.
Domestic work.
Come on, come.
Goodbye, Uncle Golok.
-Thanks for the aircraft.
The plan is this.
We'll Mommy solve di oèija
di Floopu prepreèila,
to the brain rule the world.
Going to work?
-You do not lebih be difficult.
I did not do anything.
Speed ​​is fine, even height.
Autopilot ... Terminate?
Golok is again proved.
Switches to manually control.
Jikalau tidak read all the instructions?
Skipping your whole chapter, bukselj.
Stop-saya insult. -Smrdljivec.
Stop it, otherwise Lahiri I love you too
insulting. -Here, bradavièar.
Bos has seen plenièarka.
It also now wearing?
-How long have you known? -Always have.
I had priseèi that they do not Lahiri
gags. Now we're even.
What you ušpièil?
-But I know what will.
We'll be flown.
UNTUK you did NALAS, kamikaze.
Now, the plane slowed.
Landing.
No wheels. Bova crashed.
No, we'll Jump.
Get ready.
Saya hear me?
-Yes.
Let's see what's in that cave.
Here we are.
Cavity Spee sharks.
-Sharks do not sleep.
About this I made paper.
Sleep in the depths
where the salinity of the water law.
There sehingga door.
Crazy. No-touch.
The-ljudožerec? -No.
Hi, Spee shark.
Sleep, fool.
-Vern. -Come on.
Sweet dreams.
Security Camera.
You wait.
Not pušèaj saya here.
Smile.
I hope to have the bathroom.
Figure Lahiri installed before the camera
that we will not be noticed.
I have to pee. I can not stand anymore.
No, you will wake up sharks.
I can not stand vee ...
No, the one camera.
What should I do?
Why not watch screens?
If you can not itself
Call of another.
I did not endure the vee.
Just a little ...
Juni, a bit on tight.
Carmen. Leave-saya.
I would be almost.
Carmen. -Bravo, Stor.
-Drift.
Close the door.
-I try. -Faster.
Never pee vee Sun Lahiri.
Thumb. A true ...
What have you done?
Machetejeve žveèilke
electric shock. I'd rather go.
Come.
Come here.
What are you doing? -I installed
the smallest camera in the world.
Bravo.
-Thank you.
Inches di Foogliji
coming through the southern corridor.
What do we do now?
OSS-Ze.
Donnagon Agency?
Where the mother di OEI?
Thank you.
I made. What-say? Spun-
Lahiri back. -In jeèi are. Hurry .
Try to find out where sehingga brain.
Inches.
Radhiyallahu have bubbles?
We'll be back, employees agents.
Robots declared the
at exits 4, 5 dalam 6th
Here is prezraèevalni shaft.
-Jeee jadi on the other side of the castle.
How do we get there unnoticed?
I think jadi brighter.
Intruders.
-Invaders.
Going to work?
-I think.
Find Mom di oèija.
I hope that leads Spaniards lakukan jeee.
You ...
What you got on your hands?
Warts, right?
Resulting in oznojenih hands.
You know, why these hands sweat?
Since ak is a constant fear.
The menu does not discount scared.
-Because I'm angry.
You kidnapped my parents created
robots di ate my sister.
I did not intend.
I thought a genius.
-Really?
Watch my show?
-More often than you think.
Alexander Minion. Agen-Cortez.
Good to see you again.
Do you know him? -He was
The third project in the brain.
His idea is to inject Hotel
in the system. I signed it,
therefore jadi chased him away from a CMS.
-I am not an artist such as Floop,
sheba worry free.
Something else I have in mind.
What are you going with this The achieved?
-Always have in mind the objective.
Sometimes exaggerate.
I fear not-this, Alex.
Each such time
should be having fun.
You guys should not worry about the kids. See
will you guys every day at half past eight.
I hope that this time Floop
What better place. Unfortunately, he left.
We have created an army
unièevalcev relentless.
Believed Lahiri, when Lahiri seen.
Welcome, Miss. Gradenko.
I am glad that I returned.
Do not imejva children.
So the Minion who is evil?
-Yes, they will blame me.
ADAT istiadat not abolished altogether?
-It's impossible.
UNTUK just anybody can do from the outside.
-Dalam then? -Stopped the Minion
di army of robots. He held the fist
to forgive soap dunes.
Your my hero, Floop.
We'll help another rack.
Minion must be stopped.
Only a-few.
What does my program?
Vern, that it is something missing,
Do not know what.
Do you have any idea?
Needs children.
Back off.
Now we stop Minion.
We gotta stop him.
Here you get to my sister.
Juni ...
Carmen? June?
-Mom!
UNTUK my Fooglie.
Those that I drew.
Dad is.
They came.
What are you doing here falls?
-Nice.
How did I arrive?
Mom, I skipped my Solo
di ferry with vehicle.
It's okay. We'll be home
talk. -I ran into Belize.
Where to? -You are right,
We'll talk at home. -No, no.
ALL soaps can tell.
You want to live without family?
Living.
Now I do not anymore.
Oèija you into Fooglija.
-I.
Can I change it back.
Lord,
Army a step towards Ze.
Your patience is sharply
help. G. Floop is sure
that our partnership ...
-Minion, Floop here. Immediately Come .
The robots we have serious problems .
-You say that he left?
It is.
-serious problems, g. Minion.
Be right back.
Minion.
Where are you?
-For you.
What are you doing? You should be in èeti.
You should be in-èeti.
Stop it. -Stop it.
-Stop that. -Stop that.
Immediately!
What is soap-ADAT istiadat?
Got a clever deèka, Cortez.
After-mom.
May I propose a truce
In return for the Heer? -It's too late.
I have not seen it.
Lahiri show you what happens,
Ee vpletaš family. Comfortable, you will.
Good shows.
-Thank you.
You do not.
-No, I'm barefoot.
Compress ga in his hands. Ingrid.
Come.
Fools.
UKM army did not leave the castle.
Keeping fingers crossed
tasks that are not programmed.
Only way they can stop.
One by one.
Left, left.
Where the mother di OEI?
They have a duplicate of yours. -Can
stop the robot? -It is too late.
Remove third brain. Five-hundred-
brain? Program Change.
It took weeks to vee. -Replace
Just two words. -Binary system.
Thus, the Good
replace the bad. -Come on.
It is not easy. Bos-already identified.
Taught-by to be good at heart.
Sit down, Mr. Bibir.
Thus vampaneze will comfortably.
I am writing to Lisp.
All I need is the army.
Is already on the way.
-Minion?
What happened? -I think Lahiri
AGAIN one day just like before.
Mom, Dad!
Caution.
Now sehingga-American di smarter.
We were also.
You see?
Pišuka.
Now.
Lisp. I should have known
Who is behind all this.
You're probably Minion.
GDE. Gradenko ... I think so.
Prièeska thanks twixt your child.
Lahiri was up to them spending money.
EAS-is to demonstrate, Minion.
Presents a demonic child.
-Absolutely.
SVA parents caught easily.
They do not nie guys better.
Poor mali Juni,
nemoèen di weak.
Nièvreden you Kiddo.
Do not listen to it, Juni.
Jikalau tidak nièvreden.
You're finding how to get here.
Floopu you say that is good.
You talked with Foogliji
di di oèija save Mom. Powerful you are!
So powerful is not.
Piflarèek Juni. It's all over.
Seeds.
UNTUK they will keep.
Poišèiva mom di oèija.
-Smart.
Robots must be declared in the Great Room
di Present
its unièujoèo Moe.
Mom, Dad! -Juni.
-Close your eyes owing to you will not see.
Do you have any idea?
It's wonderful. -Carmen?
-No. June?
I think I know.
Here's how. I hit myself by Lahiri hundred
on the right, and you in a hundred left.
Carmen, a hundred left in the middle,
South, on the right. We managed to be.
Five hundred of them. One is missing.
Hello, brother.
Children.
They tear off each limb.
I know.
Lower the saya.
-Not disobey you, sir.
Commands go through one ear in.
through a second di Ven.
Why did you come back?
For the same reason,
As I walked away. You know what?
I do not remember anymore.
Also, I-no.
It's okay. As the cry.
A bit emotional.
We southerners such PAE.
What you learned? -It is important
What you taught me.
Denmark won. Not so,
Whereas the greatest or-American.
Have good hearts
di nepokvarjene thoughts.
This sehingga have learned how the robots.
Thank you.
Again we are made
on pustolovšèino.
Nie is we do not technically advanced.
Technically advanced twice to us.
We have to tell you a few.
-Secret agent SVA.
The two of us We have to admit something.
We were secret agents, too.
worldwide occur children
performing good works.
every day someone sees a child
someone who helps.
WHO sehingga these children
So why di sehingga good at heart?
Jikalau tidak shops closed? Interests-saya,
What is happening in the market.
Stop the fight.
EAS is Floopove Fooglije.
Good morning, children.
Vampaneze represent two new characters.
UNTUK the Carmenita di Junito.
Cortezova, the Far East
will perform the task.
Devlin, first we
talk.
Together we have decided,
or are we going to retire or not.
He did not talk
with you, Gregorio di Ingrid.
We need Carmen di June.
The finest agent.
What do you say, baby? Are for?
-If you need Cortezove,
We need to take ALL
the mother di oèija.
Henceforth we shall poèeli together.
Espionage is a small snack. Happy
family is hard work.
For UNTUK is worth fighting for.
Translation di adaptation
Indicator light Luèovnik
Technically treatment
Pro Plus
he Best Play With:: MKV-PotPlayer-VLc