Someone needs to stop Clearway Law.
Public shouldn't leave reviews for lawyers.
(PEOPLE CHATTERING)
Ladies.
Baccarat.
Exquisite.
(WOMEN GASPS)
(MAN SPEAKING
FOREIGN LANGUAGE)
Tihomir.
Hang up.
Bradley Fine.
I'm honored.
Pleasure's all mine.
Tell me where the bomb is.
10 seconds,
or you're dead.
Interesting.
You see, when my men
and I hid it...
I made sure to erase
any witnesses.
(MAN GROANS)
And then I erased the erasers.
Which means,
I'm now the only one
who knows...
just where that
dangerously compact
and transportable nuke is.
So...
I'd say I have
more than 10 seconds.
Well then, in that case,
I'd say you'd better start...
(SNEEZES)
(GUN FIRES)
Oh, fuck!
Oh, my God!
Why did you do that?
I didn't do it on purpose.
There's like a ton
of pollen in here!
Oh, God! Christmas
on a cracker!
Did you take
your medicine?
I forgot it on the plane.
I told you this morning,
I put extra
in all your jackets!
You did?
Great. Shit! Thanks.
No, you know what?
That's on me.
Because I heard you
sniffle a while ago
and I did nothing
with that information.
So that's blood
on my hands, really...
Okay. You know what?
You got three coming in.
Get out the
back door now. Move.
(GUN FIRE)
Anybody in here?
Yeah, we got one coming
around the corner, now.
(GUNSHOTS)
(MAN GROANS)
Your three guests
are coming out
that door behind you
right now.
Watch your six.
Yahtzee.
Oh, zinger!
(LAUGHS)
I should've brought
more bullets.
I thought they were
chocolate sprinkles,
which I would eat,
normally, by the fistful...
but this tasted like...
There's no other way
to say it, really.
Like a rat's arse.
Guys, can you please
keep it down?
Unfortunately, there's
vermin in the ceiling again,
and I hate
to say it, but...
they've pooped
all over your cake.
I'm going left?
SUSAN: No.
I need you to go right
and head down the tunnel.
You've got one coming
around to your right,
and he's got a swarm
behind him.
That's my girl.
Oh, I don't know.
(GRUNTING)
Watch your back.
Oh, that was
a close one, Fine.
Who's the finest of them all?
You are.
♪ Oh, Bradley, you're so fine
♪ You're so fine,
you blow my mind
♪ Hey, Bradley!
Oh, God, duck!
(GROANS)
Nice moves, Fine.
Pilates has been
working out for you.
You noticed?
Yeah, you just seem looser.
Like, in your hips.
I mean athletically speaking.
I don't know. I guess
you don't seem so awkward.
(WHISPERING)
Shut up!
Going straight?
No.
Go right up the stairs.
You're gonna find
a little friend
on the first landing.
(SCREAMS)
Thanks for your help.
SUSAN:
You're clear to the top.
Get moving.
MAN: Oh, my God!
The rats can fly!
Come on, you guys!
All right, Fine.
Stop at the door.
You got a guard approaching.
I'll tell you when.
Wait for it,
Fine. Three...
Two, one. Now!
Oh, dear,
did I forget to knock?
They're clawing at my hair!
I can't see!
What do you mean,
you can't see me?
I'm good. You've got
SUVs approaching.
Go to the dock!
Dock. Excellent idea.
Boyanov's boat
is at the end.
(PEOPLE SCREAMING)
Uh... No keys, Coop.
The panel's on the lower left
under the steering wheel.
You can hotwire it.
I can't get to the wires!
Okay, then stay down
and hold your ears!
How will I hear
your beautiful voice?
Stop being adorable
and get down!
Lock on coordinates
43.16547...
27.94654...
and fire, now.
Whoo!
(FINE LAUGHS)
Close one!
Nice drone work, Coop!
I could kiss you.
Oh!
(CHUCKLES)
Well, I would accept that
with an open mouth.
(LAUGHS) Soon as I'm back,
dinner is on me.
Great work, Coop.
Hey, pick up my dry cleaning
for me, would you?
Also, get my car.
Oh, sure. No problem.
Oh, and I have to fire
my gardener.
He keeps running over
the sprinkler heads
with the mower.
Can you cut him loose
for me?
Um... Yeah. Oh, yeah, sure.
You kidding?
I'd love it!
You're the best.
Smell you later, pal.
God. Poor Jaime.
The thing is,
Jaime, that...
Uh...
Oh!
These are your children?
Your children, here?
Yeah, I have children.
I just have to cover
those eyes.
They're looking
right at me. Um...
Please, don't fire me.
No. Jaime, I would never.
This is more of a review.
(HUMMING)
Oh.
Jaime.
(SINGING IN SPANISH)
Yes.
♪ The lawnmower
(BOTH VOCALIZING)
Right to
that lawnmower.
(JAIME SINGING IN SPANISH)
You're a killer, Susan.
(SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING)
♪ The heart is a hunter
♪ And hard as a stone
♪ Cold blood in the chamber
♪ Bullets and bone
♪ Into the night
you will fall
♪ Where there's
no wrong or right
♪ Rough justice for all
♪ Love is powering lust
♪ You may find
my smile deceitful
♪ But after it all
♪ Who else can you trust?
(FINE AND WAITER
SPEAKING FRENCH)
Ah!
These look delicious.
I don't wanna be critical,
but this is very chewy.
Coop. You're eating
a hand towel.
Just cleansing my palette.
(CHUCKLES)
Jeez. You had to take me
to such a dump?
(LAUGHS)
Come on, cheapskate!
Burger King was booked up.
Ha!
Sorry. I'm having dinner
with Gallagher over here.
Guard your fruit!
You could. You're funny.
Your timing is perfect.
Never as funny as you,
Super Cooper.
To another
successful mission.
Go team.
(WHISPERS) Go team.
Hey, I've been thinking.
Yeah.
I couldn't do
what I do without you.
And I've been thinking
about doing something
special for you...
So...
Good gravy, Fine.
Oh. That's...
It's a crazy cupcake!
You love cakes.
Well...
I'm not a big cake...
I make cakes. Yes. I
see the connection.
Now you can wear a cake.
How did you know I don't care
for traditional jewelry?
I can't seem to
stop looking at it...
and it can't
stop looking at me.
Imagine how awkward
it would've been
if it'd been a diamond ring
or something.
Ooh...
Not a diamond ring! No!
I would've had to say,
"I don't want to marry you!"
I don't want
your muscly arms and hands...
rubbing my back with Nivea
for the rest of my life.
And our three kids run in,
you know...
Karen, Tommy and Billy...
and we'd say,
"Get out of here!"
And they'd just all
have that beautiful jaw...
and sky-blue eyes, and a full mouth.
I mean...
no, thank you.
I'll just, you know,
I'll just...
Can you give me a little
jewelry I can actually wear?
Not gonna wear it?
Yes. Yeah.
I was just saving it.
Put it on!
Look at that.
Wow, that's a...
That is an adjustable toggle.
Adjustable toggle.
You don't see that
with a lot of jewelry.
It's so you.
Is it?
Wow, perfect.
(LAUGHS)
Oh... Somebody's jealous.
Seriously, I couldn't do
what I do without you,
in my earpiece.
I could never do
what you do.
Can you imagine me as a spy?
Oh, my God.
Out in the field.
Yeah.
With a gun!
What?
"Hi, terrorists.
Oh, golly!
"Oh, I shot myself!
Whoops!
"I meant to shoot you,
not me!"
That's probably
what I'd say.
"Hey, terrorists,
you better watch out,
"or I'll make you
a chocolate cake.
"Do you like chocolate? Well,
then I'll make you a vanilla."
They would never
let me be a spy.
I can't even
dress like a spy.
Look at you
and your tailored...
Everything is cut right.
And mine is like a lumpy
pumpkin sack dress.
Oh, come...
It doesn't even have a label.
Does not have a label.
I think my mom made it.
No, stop.
I should get on my hands
and knees and start scooping.
Good God.
Go easy on yourself.
Okay.
We're a perfect team.
That's why we work.
Yeah.
Come here.
Come here. Close.
(SILVERWARE CLATTERING)
I think
you're getting pinkeye.
What? No.
Right there.
No, that's not...
Did you wipe your eye after
you cleaned out the cat box?
I don't have cats.
Why did I think that?
I don't know.
You should get some.
They're good company.
ELAINE:
We've intercepted chatter...
that the weapon is still being
offered to the highest bidder.
Someone other than Boyanov
knows where that nuke is.
It's probably
his daughter, Rayna.
She's really the only
person he's trusted.
Jesus, Cooper,
do you have pinkeye?
Go home. You're going
to infect everybody.
Told you.
No, it's not
pinkeye, ma'am.
It's just I'm having a bit
of an allergic reaction.
Well, I'm allergic
to disgusting
childhood illnesses,
so stay away from me.
Sorry.
Anyway, you're right.
After Boyanov's death,
Rayna went to a safety deposit
box at a DSK bank in Varna.
The chatter picked up
later that night.
What do we know
about her?
I can pull up her file.
Oh, that's stuck.
It's just a little
warm in here.
Pull up my file...
Jesus! Not my keyboard
with your pinkeye-infected
fingers!
Why don't you
just cry directly
into my mouth
while you're at it?
It really is just
an allergic reaction...
Sit down. I'll do it.
Okay, I'm gonna go sit down.
ELAINE: Rayna Boyanov.
Majored in international law
at Oxford.
Top of her class.
Been living in London
for the past 10 years.
We know she has been
communicating
with the heads of several
terrorist organizations.
Most ominously...
Solsa Dudaev,
the al-Qaeda-funded leader
of the Chechen Martyrs'
Brigade.
We have compelling evidence that
he has the machinery in place
to get that nuke
to New York in time
for next week's
UN General Assembly.
I'm already packed.
One of our sources was told
she has taken up residence
outside of Sofia.
Go get her.
Grab my things, Coop.
Jesus, Cooper, go put on
some sunglasses or something.
I feel like you're a Gypsy,
cursing me with it.
Yep, I'm on it.
Yeah, that's all good.
Oh, Fine?
Hi.
Hey, Super Cooper.
Oh! Um...
I just was feeling
a little weird about...
Oh, yeah? ...some of the stuff,
and I think the intel...
on Rayna's location
seems a little too easy.
I just...
Something doesn't feel right.
It'll be right when
we get Rayna behind bars
and that nuke
back in our hands.
Yeah, sure. I just...
I don't know. All my alarm bells
are going off with this one.
Really? Well, then, it's
okay 'cause I have a plan.
You and I gotta stop going
on these awful missions.
Run off together.
Do you mean that?
What?
Do I mean that?
You got me. You kidder.
You sucker! No.
You should have seen your face!
You were like...
(MIMICS STAMMERING)
(ELEVATOR BELL DINGS)
(CHUCKLES)
Fine, I'm sorry if I...
Don't be.
God, I admire you.
NANCY: "I admire you"?
Well, did he at least say it
in a flirty tone that says...
"And because of my admiration, I
shall now take my shirt off...
"and penetrate ye"?
No.
The only way he'd
invite me to his bedroom
is if he wants me
to fix his bed.
I'm so stupid.
Can I just have a sip of your wine?
Mmm-hmm.
It's quite buttery.
Wow. Okay, we could
order you your own glass.
That was mine!
My life is a disaster.
No, it's not.
I'm 40, I live by myself...
I haven't been
in a real relationship
since Jerry left me
three years ago.
Well, Jerry was a jackass.
When I gave up teaching
to join the CIA,
I thought everything
was gonna be different.
I thought I was gonna be
this amazing spy.
I'm just the same boring
person I was before.
Well, for what it's worth,
I think you're brilliant
as you are.
You're exciting. Come
on, let's cheer you up.
Okay. My nephew
loves this. All right.
Okay. Thanks.
Isn't your nephew three?
My God.
That's the same face.
Okay, this will be different.
Exactly the same face.
This will be different.
Ready? Aah...
That's the exact same thing.
How is that
the same thing?
There was a little bit
of tongue there.
Please stop.
That's not cheering me up.
Do you know what? I'm glad
you said that to Fine.
I am, because you
play it too safe.
I still hear
my mom's voice...
"Well-behaved women
often make history."
Yes, you do know
the phrase is...
"Well-behaved women
seldom make history"?
Yeah. That's never
how she said it.
What were her others?
"Just blend in."
"Let somebody else win."
Classic. I got that a
lot in high school.
And there was, "Give up
on your dream, Susan."
She used to write that
in my lunchbox.
Oh...
I mean, look, okay?
What's really so
different between us
and Karen Walker?
I think literally everything.
No, hang on, no,
because you were
just as good as her
at the Academy.
She's had more successful
missions than even Fine.
Oh, she's the worst.
Look at her. She thinks she's
so perfect, doesn't she?
"Hi, I'm Karen Walker,
super spy." (GIGGLES)
Perfect hair.
Perfect face.
She probably cries herself
to sleep every night.
I don't think she probably does.
She probably does.
And not, like,
sort of cute, little tears.
Like, really sort of
silent, kind of big.
(SOBBING)
I don't think that's what...
Like a sort of upside
down kidney bean.
"This is what I look like
when I'm asleep."
Shut up, be quiet.
She won't know who we are.
She's so full of herself.
Hi. Hey, Nancy.
Hi, Susan.
BOTH: Hi!
Look at you two cuties
sitting here being all cute.
Aw!
(CHUCKLES)
Oh, you.
Can I have
an Old Fashioned, please?
The service is really slow.
Super slow. Good luck getting
that in the next hour.
Here you go, Miss Walker.
Thank you.
Oh.
Wow.
Alan and I go way back.
I come here all the time.
So do we.
Right, Alan?
Hey, Alan. Alan!
Big A, Big A!
Whoo-hoo!
Al! We got a whole...
Miss Walker,
are these two bothering you?
No, thank you. They're fine.
Okay.
SUSAN: Alan!
He's the sweetest.
He totally pretends
not to know. It's a game.
NANCY: He's funny.
Yeah.
Well, anyway,
I'm taking some time off,
so I'll see you guys
when I get back.
Oh.
Where are you going?
Capri.
I believe it's "Cahpri." That's
how the locals say it, anyway.
Oh...
I wish I could just
stick around here...
curl up with a good book.
But I have a yacht full of
friends waiting for me.
Wow.
Yachts are the worst.
They seem
so glamorous, but...
They're the worst.
NANCY: Boo, yachts.
Anyhoo, I'll see you guys
when I get back,
all freckled and tan.
We're gonna see you.
Bye.
Bye!
(BLOWING RASPBERRY)
Oh, sorry.
Susan is ill.
It's her stomach.
Oh, my God.
Thank you for that.
Why would you do that?
I panicked.
What a great moment.
Just look at her.
NANCY: I know. That dress.
Look at that confidence.
You're not even allowed
to smoke in here.
I'm gonna go home.
No, come on.
Yes.
Susan.
Feel better.
Thank you. Yeah.
Fine, you good?
FINE: Okay, Coop.
Just pulling up.
Susan, you're killing it.
Oh, good.
It's the chicory.
Yeah.
Any sign of her in the house?
Heat sensors
aren't picking anything up.
There's some kind
of interference.
I don't like this, Fine.
I'm up for the challenge.
(COCKS GUN)
Let's go in.
Shoot, there's something
wrong with your camera.
Can you switch it out
for a new one?
FINE: Too late.
(SUSAN GROANS)
FINE: No security.
(SCOFFS)
Her father would never have
left himself this exposed.
Pull back, Fine.
This is too easy.
I like things that are easy.
(NECK CRACKING)
Oh, my God, Fine!
I don't know how
you do things like that.
Hey.
Who's the finest of them all?
I don't know.
I'm guessing you?
Drop your weapon.
Fine, what's happening?
Let me guess.
Whoever is in your ear
wants to know
what's happening?
(SOFTLY) He's about to die.
That's what.
An awfully big gun
for such a little girl.
Oh, God, don't say
stuff like that.
Okay, there's a knife rack
directly to your right.
The way she's holding the gun,
she's not experienced.
If you duck and lunge, you can
get the knife and disarm her.
Did someone just suggest that
you grab one of those knives?
No, no, no!
Damn it!
Fine!
Can they see me right now?
Let me adjust
the angle a little bit.
(GUNSHOT)
(GASPS)
Oh, my God, Fine.
His name was Bradley Fine.
He worked for the CIA.
Other top agents include
Matthew Wright,
Timothy Cress...
Rick Ford and Karen Walker.
Come on, Fine. Come on.
I know who all
your active agents are.
So, unless you'd like
the body count to grow...
I suggest you stay
far away from me.
Now grab some tissues,
because shit's about
to get real sad.
FINE: No, no...
(GUNSHOT)
Oh, my God, Fine.
As Deputy Director...
I have never had
a more difficult duty...
than to bid farewell
to colleagues taken from us.
From Dover,
to the family services...
to memorials like these...
it's tough to say goodbye.
There's nothing you
could have done, Susan.
Bradley Fine was more than
just a coworker and a friend.
He was part of our family.
And as family,
even knowing that the universe
has a plan
for each human life...
it's hard to accept
the sudden loss
of such a good
and decent person.
SUSAN: (ON TAPE) Okay, there's a
knife rack directly to your right.
Susan, I got your assessment
report on Rayna Boyanov.
I know you're probably feeling
a lot of emotion right now...
but please refrain from using
the term "thundercunt."
Oh, my God. I didn't
realize I wrote that.
I'm sorry.
Nancy, I'm sending
you a photo.
It's in pretty bad shape.
Can you enhance it?
Mm-hmm.
Paris?
How the fuck did this twat
find out our fucking names?
We don't know.
And dial it way back
with the "T" word, Ford.
You're not immune from the
HR department. Grow up.
And "twat" means something
completely different in England.
Here it means a vagina.
Anyway, obviously
we're talking about a mole.
It could be a mole, they could
have hacked our system.
It's anyone's guess.
The bottom line is Rayna
Boyanov is about to sell...
a small-scale tactical
nuclear weapon
to a terrorist
organization...
and we don't know
where she or the bomb is.
Fortunately, our analyst
Susan Cooper found a lead.
Rayna had the number
of Sergio De Luca...
and we've long
suspected De Luca
of working as an intermediary
with terrorist groups.
Rayna may be using him
to find buyers for the nuke.
The number was to an office
he keeps in Paris.
I told you to send me in
there instead of Fine,
and you didn't.
And now Fine is dead.
I'm going the fuck in.
You can't.
We need someone to follow De
Luca without being detected...
and that will hopefully
take us to Rayna...
but it can't be any of you.
Here's what we do...
I go into the Face/Off
machine, get a whole new face.
I turn up,
they never know it's me.
Do you have quarters?
Because it costs 50 cents.
What, I gotta pay?
No, because it doesn't exist.
Yes, it does!
I heard Cress and Wright talking
about it in the shitter.
I'm pretty sure
they were pulling your leg.
You pair of fucking vaginas.
Seriously,
you've got to cut that out.
Jesus. Look, one of us
has to go in.
Doesn't matter
if we've been exposed.
We've all gone deep before,
and we've always
gotten our guy.
Guys, this is more than
just a kill mission.
We can get Rayna, De Luca, and
some top terrorist leadership...
and get the weapon back
if we do this right.
We just need someone
who can shadow them
without attracting attention.
We need someone invisible.
I'll do it.
Okay, thanks, lunch lady.
I'm serious.
I have never
been out in the field.
Exactly. Stupid fucking idea.
My point is that
it's highly doubtful
that I've ever been exposed.
But you worked with Fine.
They may have
a record of you, too.
SUSAN: Possibly.
But the odds of them
knowing my face are very low.
Miss Crocker, I would
really like to do this.
For Fine.
What are you gonna do? Bring one
of your cats as a sidekick?
I don't have any cats!
You're not seriously
considering this, are you?
Look here, Betty...
Ford, if you call me
Betty Crocker,
I will rip your fucking
heart out of your chest.
Not only did I
become a citizen
and take a vow
to protect this country...
I also took a vow to avenge my
fallen comrades. We all fucking did.
No, we didn't.
Not me.
I'm pretty sure we all took a fucking vow.
I remember it.
I remember raising my fucking
hand and saying some shit.
If you think
I'm gonna sit by
and let you send in
a fucking secretary...
to do my work...
you might as well accept
my resignation now.
If I can jump in,
I am technically, uh,
classified as an agent.
Look...
SUSAN: Full agent. So...
agent, agent, agent,
I'm an agent.
Are you considering this?
For your safety, and the safety
of those around this table...
I am considering it.
Then consider this,
I quit.
And I know there's a fucking
Face/Off machine.
You're just keeping it
secret from me.
Okay.
That hasn't happened before.
(DOOR CLOSES)
It is quite
a lovely office.
What's your deal, Cooper?
What do you mean?
You got a fiery side?
I really did, in that report,
mean to write "cunning."
I've been going over
your files.
You were top of your class
at the Academy,
in all computer
and support skills.
No surprise there.
But you have a certain...
tame demeanor
around the office,
that says you've never
even held a gun.
So imagine my surprise...
when I saw footage from
this drill back at The Farm.
SUSAN: Is that...
I can't even...
Is that me? I can't really...
(GUN CLICKING)
SUSAN: (ON COMPUTER)
Stupid gun!
Somebody definitely
sped this up.
Ooh! Camera angle
and stuff make...
(YELLING)
Cooper, Cooper, stop!
Jesus Christ, what are you...
Ouch.
Out of context, that's...
I must have watched
this 15 times now...
because what the fuck?
I almost put it up
on YouTube.
I was, to say the least,
uncomfortable with the event.
But I would also like to say,
it was over 10 years ago.
The instructor
was not harmed.
Fine was your mentor, right?
Yes.
Why did you not
become a field agent?
Well, we're such a great
fit and a great team.
Fine made
some great points.
Maybe I match better with,
just staying...
In his ear.
Well...
Yeah, he sniped you.
All the top agents used to
do that before I got here.
I really thought he made
some great points.
Women.
All right, have you had any
field training since then?
10 years is a long time.
No, ma'am.
Normally, I would send you back to
The Farm, but there's no time...
and I can't take a chance of
anyone leaking your name.
(LAUGHING)
Am I going?
You're going.
Okay. Jeez. Sorry.
But it's a track and report
mission only.
Got it.
We'll be giving you
a new identity.
You'll no longer be
Susan Cooper.
I had a few ideas for that.
Your new name...
I was just spitballing
and I thought...
Seraphina,
Maddox, Gisele...
Carol Jenkins.
If I may, ma'am,
there was a 13-year-old girl
named Carol...
that used to kind of take me
around the neighborhood...
and use my braid
as a dog leash...
and make me
beg for biscuits...
Carol Jenkins.
Yes. Carol Jenkins, huh?
Carol Jenkins
is a single mother of four...
temporarily relocated
from Delaware
to increase sales
for a software company.
Okay, that is...
a different occup...
Is there a problem?
No.
I was just wondering if this was my
family, or if I had taken hostages.
I'm just not sure...
how De Luca is gonna take me
seriously if I look like this.
De Luca is not going to
take you anything.
In case
you did not hear me...
you are not to make
direct contact
with any of the targets.
Track and report.
We're setting you up
in a surveillance office
across the street
from De Luca's.
You'll be tapped into
the same telecom trunk...
and have access to voice and
data coming into his office...
and that is as sexy
as it gets.
One mistake,
and we've got a nuclear bomb
in the hands of terrorists.
Do you understand?
Yes.
Go see Patrick. He's got
special equipment for you.
Oh, my God.
What are you doing?
Did you come up
with your spy name yet?
Mine would be
"Amber Valentine."
That sounds like
you're an adult film star.
No, I did the spy
name formula.
"Amber" was the name
of my first pet,
and I grew up
on Valentine Street.
That's how you come up
with your porn name.
I thought it was your spy name!
No!
What would yours be?
"Meatball Martin
Luther King Jr. Boulevard."
Yeah.
Wow.
Oh, my God.
This is so exciting!
(LAUGHS)
You're a spy!
I know! I know!
Oh, my God!
You're gonna get
one of those!
SUSAN: No, I'm not!
Look at that!
NANCY: That looks high-tech.
It's like the future.
Patrick.
Susan.
Hey, Patrick.
Yes.
I was given specific
instructions by Elaine
to tailor these
gadgets to you.
SUSAN: Wow. NANCY: Wow,
look at that watch.
These are not yours.
Oh.
Is that a rape whistle?
Elaine wanted you
to only be carrying items
a single woman travelling
through Europe would have.
But she could get that
at any pharmacy.
Not this whistle.
When you blow
through this whistle,
a small, poisonous
dart flies out...
neutralizing your target.
Also, it needs your
fingerprints on it to work.
That is really neat!
Stop it, that's amazing.
That is really super cool!
I love that!
This anti-fungal spray
can freeze and disable...
any security system.
Wow.
That is quite an image to be
carrying all over Europe.
It's also a pepper spray.
Why not just make it
look like pepper spray?
That's a pretty good idea.
Well, next time.
I can wait,
if you want to print up
a new label.
No, I'd have to turn
the printer on again.
I don't really want to.
Each of these
are filled with chloroform.
Wow, that is an unsettling
amount of hemorrhoid wipes.
Makes me kind of wonder...
what, exactly,
is going on back there.
I wouldn't know.
I don't have that problem.
If you ever feel like
you have been poisoned...
chew one of these.
Have I done something
to you to upset you?
Because this is
a peculiar theme.
Finally, every agent gets
a night vision scope...
hidden in their watch.
I have heard about this.
I've been looking...
Oh.
Who's that?
That is Bette Midler
and Barbara Hershey.
From Beaches.
How much am I supposed
to like Beaches?
I would imagine a lot,
if you have the watch.
Hey, Pat, I'm flying!
PATRICK: Anthony!
Don't wear out
the battery on that.
Am I getting that?
No, you're not
gonna get that.
I've already packed your bags.
Hurry up and get dressed.
Carol Jenkins has to get
to the airport immediately.
And may I say...
I think it's very brave
of you to sacrifice
your life for your country.
I'm not sacrifi...
I'm coming back.
Let's see.
Hey, Pat! I'm gonna totally
crop dust these guys.
Way to go, Anthony.
(FARTS) Oh, just pardon me.
(FARTS AGAIN) Oh, God.
I think I shit my pants.
(SEXY POP MUSIC PLAYING)
You look amazing, Susan.
I look like someone's
homophobic aunt.
SUSAN: Wow.
Hotel Modiere, please.
(GASPS)
This is so exciting.
Ooh.
The Louvre.
Wow.
That's a beautiful hotel.
Not that one?
I hope it's that.
Is it that one?
Nope. Oh...
Maybe next time.
I think we're getting into
a little dicier of an area.
Ooh. That's a little unsavory.
I think we can probably
go back towards...
my hotel.
No, no, no.
No, this...
I don't believe this could be
the Hotel Modiere.
This is. Yes, it is.
(GLASS SHATTERING)
(SIRENS WAILING)
(WOMAN YELLING)
(DOG BARKING)
(WOMAN SOBBING)
(MAN LAUGHING MANIACALLY)
Oh, man.
Keep it together,
Susan, okay?
Nancy?
(GASPS)
Please tell me
you can hear me.
I'm here. I've got you.
Okay.
You'll be pleased to hear the
bats have officially gone.
We are now vermin free.
Did you get your gun, Carol?
Yes, and don't call me that.
Oh, my God. Cripes. I think
I'm having a heart attack.
I can't do this, Nancy. Fine
was the real spy, not me!
Don't worry.
I'm here for you, okay?
Everything is gonna be fine.
I'm gonna talk you
through this, all right?
Put your camera in.
I want to see your room.
No, you don't.
It's that bad.
Martha Stewart had
a breakdown, kind of feel.
NANCY: Oh. Wow.
Looks like they put you up
in The Shitz-Carlton.
Try and get some sleep...
and we'll get started
first thing in the morning.
I don't know what I'm gonna do
when I see that Rayna woman.
I want her dead
for what she did to Fine.
Okay. Deep breaths.
Listen to me. You're not gonna
get anywhere near her...
so there's nothing
to worry about.
Oh, God. Really?
Guys...
there's a mouse on my tits.
I think you're safer there.
All right. Good night.
Night.
Ah!
You got this, Susan. Okay.
You're a warrior.
You're a weapon. Okay?
This is no sweat. FORD: Looks
like you're sweating to me.
Jesus!
What are you doing
in my room?
What, how did I get into
this shit-box hotel room?
Because I'm a real spy.
I thought you quit.
We have to stop the sale
of a nuclear bomb...
and they send in someone who looks
like Santa Claus' fucking wife.
Did you forget?
I am undercover,
because you're not
supposed to be here.
I make a habit of doing things
that people say I can't do.
Walk through fire...
water-ski blindfolded...
take up piano
at a late age...
and I'm gonna
take down De Luca
and Rayna and Dudaev...
and I'm gonna
get that bomb back.
Why do you even
care what I do?
You really think
you're ready for the field?
I once used
defibrillators on myself.
I've pulled shards of glass
out of my fucking eye.
I've jumped
from a high-rise building...
using only a raincoat
as a parachute...
and broke both legs
upon landing.
And I still had to pretend
I was in a fucking
Cirque du Soleil show!
I've swallowed
enough microchips
and shit them
back out again...
to make a computer.
This arm has been ripped off
completely...
and reattached
with this fucking arm.
I don't know
that that's possible.
I mean, medically.
During the threat
of an assassination attempt...
I appeared, convincingly,
in front of Congress...
as Barack Obama.
In blackface?
That's not appropriate.
I watched the couple that
raised me explode in a van.
I watched the woman I love
get tossed from a plane...
and hit by another plane,
midair.
I drove a car
off a freeway...
on top of a train...
while I was on fire.
Not the car.
I was on fire.
Jesus, you're intense.
I took this
from your minibar.
Well, that's not right.
You're gonna ruin
this mission.
No, you're gonna ruin
this mission!
No.
You are.
No, you're going to!
You, times infinity.
Aw...
Could this hotel
be more murder-y?
(OBJECTS CLATTERING)
Okay, so my office
is in here...
which means that De Luca
is right across
the street at 39...
Oh, God. Tell me that's not
De Luca's building?
De Luca must have known
we were coming.
What am I supposed to do now?
Okay, don't panic.
Lemonade out of lemons.
Stay focused. We can do this.
(SPEAKING FRENCH)
Okay, I've got it.
I'll run it through the system.
It will take a few minutes.
NANCY: Nothing's coming up.
Might just be a looky-loo.
SUSAN: Keep looking.
I've got a feeling
about this guy.
I've got a feeling you're
about to fuck things up.
(GROANS)
Oh, bugger me with a fish pole.
It's Ford.
Sharon, Ford's in the field.
Did you know this?
Until he checks in,
there's nothing I can do.
You go make some friends,
and stop stalking me!
Was it your mission
to tip off the target
so he burns everything
in advance?
If so, well done.
Phenomenal job.
I'm sure they got suspicious because they've
been seeing you all over the place!
You're gonna
get yourself killed.
Nothing kills me.
I'm immune to 179
different types of poison.
I know, because I ingested
them all at once...
when I was
deep undercover...
in an underground,
poison-ingesting crime ring.
Wow.
It was like dog fighting.
But instead of dogs fighting,
it was humans
ingesting poison...
and rich people would bet...
whether we would
live or die.
Yeah, I'm having
a hard time with this one.
I died for five minutes,
and then I came back to life.
What's he wear...?
He looks like
he's in the cast of Newsies.
Does Crocker
even know you're here?
I don't need
anyone's permission
to save the country...
and avenge my dear friend
Bradley Fine's death.
You didn't even like him.
You used to call him
"Beverly Whine"!
You had him as Secret Santa
and you gave him tampons!
It's called
the rivalry of men.
You wouldn't understand.
Unless you've got a dong up
underneath that skirt.
That is super rude,
and don't say "dong"...
and don't do that!
Nobody sees me
when I don't want them to.
I move like a fucking shadow.
(SPEAKING FRENCH)
He's gone all sorts of rogue.
Sharon says he really did quit.
Elaine couldn't stop him.
He's out for blood.
Yeah, real tough guy in his
Louis Vuitton backpack.
Nancy, do you see that?
It's the man from the fire.
I'm following him.
Oh. Exciting!
And I'm following you,
following him,
so I'm having
quite a day, here.
Do you think Ford's
leading him into a trap?
Idiot doesn't even know
he's being followed.
He's meeting
with some woman.
I don't recognize her. You
have any idea who she is?
No, it's hard to make out.
Can you get any closer?
Nancy, our guy
just switched out
Ford's backpack.
It's a setup.
Uh...
I gotta go warn him!
(SHOUTING) Ford! Ford!
Look out!
I gotta get through!
I left my baby in the shop!
Get out of the way!
Let me through, I'm sick!
Susan, tell them
you've shat your pants.
That would get me
out of your way, for sure.
I've shat my pants!
Excuse me. Ford!
He's got a friend.
Hello, everybody!
(SPEAKING FOREIGN LANGUAGE)
(DANCE MUSIC PLAYING)
(SINGING IN GERMAN)
Ford!
I need the mic!
No! I need...
No!
No, no, no!
Susan, you're meant
to be blending in.
What are you doing?
God! Move!
(AUTO-TUNED VOICE)
Rick Ford!
Give me the mic!
How are you doing
this in heels?
Oh, God.
Rick Ford!
They switched the bag!
Oh, fuck.
(SHOUTING)
Get out of the fucking way!
Move!
Get out of his way!
♪ I want to see
(PEOPLE YELLING)
Oh, no.
Nancy, I'm in pursuit
of one of the terrorists!
He took my picture!
He's gonna blow my cover!
You're in pursuit?
What in God's name are you
gonna do if you catch him?
Knock him out with a hemorrhoid wipe.
I don't know!
I'm just gonna track him
and report his location.
This all seems
very Rick Ford-y to me.
I do not condone these sexy
but reckless actions
of yours, Susan!
(PANTING) Oh, God.
He went into a building.
Okay.
Well done. That's it.
Time to call it a day.
Location is officially noted.
I'm following him in.
What?
I'm doing this for Fine.
(COCKS GUNS)
(EXHALES)
(SOFTLY) He's at
the top of the stairs.
Oh, gosh, please be careful.
You are incredibly
out of your league.
This is just like when I
watched myself in a sex tape.
There was just a lot of floundering
and laughable moments.
Nancy, I need you to
not talk until I ask you to.
I'm sorry, it's just that
I'm really nervous.
Be careful, Susan.
Okay.
(EXHALES SLOWLY)
(GRUNTING)
Oh, hey.
Imagine running
into you up here.
I was just looking for my bird.
Just looking...
Hey, Mr. Beanbag!
(WHISTLES)
You like birds?
All right. All right.
I'm gonna give you
a warning.
I don't wanna see any more of
that funny bomb stuff, you know?
All right. That's enough.
Drop the knife,
or I'll shoot.
I don't think you will.
You see, it works better when you
have the bullets inside the gun.
Oops.
I guess that CIA training
isn't what it used to be.
I guess you're
right, asshole.
(GROANING)
(BONES CRACK)
(SCREAMS)
No, no, no!
Oh, God!
Oh, Susan, what did you do?
Oh, God, not on him.
Not on him!
(GASPS)
Oh, God,
why did I have that stew?
ELAINE: Well, Rayna's people
obviously knew Ford was in Paris.
And getting footage...
of a CIA operative setting
off a bomb in public...
would be a PR coup
for any terrorist group.
Do we have anything on
that woman he met?
Facial recognition
isn't showing anything.
They were all over Ford.
Are you able to track him?
Goddamn Ford is still
off the grid in Paris.
I know because
he keeps trying
to hack into our
system for intel.
He's like a dog that gets
loose from his yard...
and keeps humping
and shitting his way
through the neighborhood.
Would be a lot easier if...
Oh, my God!
Oh!
SUSAN: Okay.
Ford's is bigger.
This is uncomfortable.
Why do they always point at it?
We can see it.
He's dead though, isn't he?
Aw. That's a waste.
SUSAN: Oh, God. A video.
(CAMERA CLICKING)
I can only imagine
what this is.
DE LUCA: You get
everything on camera.
Base out of the hotel,
and go back there
after the attack.
I'll take Renaldo to Rome.
"Renaldo."
Do we have a record
of anyone with that name?
Not that I'm aware of.
DE LUCA: Nicola.
Are you
listening to me?
I was just testing
the camera.
Stop it!
Find Ford!
Wow.
Oh...
Come on, what is wrong
with this person?
Oh, damn it.
Well, now the screen's
frozen. Hang on.
Come on,
not the hourglass.
Cooper, put down
the goddamn camera.
Nancy, can you pull up
Fine's POV cam
from Boyanov's office?
Look on the desk.
There's some photos there.
See if you find one of him
standing next to a car.
Renaldo is a Rolls-Royce.
Hack into the Rolls'
tracking system.
That car is a Wraith,
so it has a satellite-aided
transmission.
Then tap into Boyanov's feed.
His GPS should tell you
exactly where De Luca
is in Rome, right now.
I'm gonna head
to the airport.
Forget it, Cooper.
You're coming back
immediately.
Ma'am, I really think
I can do this.
And I'm not one
to toot my own horn,
but you know what?
I'm gonna toot...
and say that I just saved
a lot of people.
We are so close to getting
Rayna and that bomb.
Pull back the rug
in the corner.
Oh...
You'll be given
a new identity.
Oh, thank God.
Oh, no!
Your name is Penny Morgan.
You're a divorced
housewife from Iowa.
You've sold
more Mary Kay products...
than anyone else
in your state...
and you've traded in
the free car you've won...
to fund a trip
through Europe.
My hobbies are decoupage
and needlepoint.
I collect porcelain dolls...
and I'm the vice president
of the Ames Garden Club.
I couldn't even be president?
Maybe I should just be married
to one of the dolls...
just to make it extra sad.
Ten cats.
Why do I have ten cats?
Is that even legal?
Fine always got to be
a businessman.
One time
he was a race car driver.
Well, there's the ten cats.
Just missing a shirt
that says
I've never felt
the touch of a man.
Cooper, you're right.
You did good work back there.
That would have been
a real mess.
Thank you, ma'am.
You still went
with the cat lady.
It was already
in the floor.
Ah.
(MAN WOLF-WHISTLING)
(SPEAKING ITALIAN)
Great, that's a real
confidence builder.
Did you find De Luca?
NANCY: He's been
at the Majestic Hotel,
but he's just left,
heading...
south, okay?
I'll guide you to him.
I've sent an ally
to drive you.
Elaine said nothing fancy,
so I've gone with earthy.
(HORNS HONKING)
Ooh. Whoa.
You wanna stop the car?
(SPEAKING ITALIAN)
Hi.
Hey!
(SPEAKING ITALIAN)
Oh.
Welcome to Roma!
Thank you.
I'm Aldo.
Like the shoe store
found in American malls.
(LAUGHING)
I'm Penny, like the penny.
Like a penny!
Or like penne alla vodka!
Okay.
Did you just grab my butt?
Yes.
Come. We need
to get you to De Luca.
(POP MUSIC PLAYING)
(TIRES SCREECHING)
SUSAN: Jiminy Christmas!
Oh, my God!
(SCREAMING)
Don't worry, I have you!
Ah!
Aldo, slow down!
Nancy, are you sure this guy
is even an agent?
Absolutely.
He's the best!
There have been some
complaints filed against him.
Watch the road,
watch the road!
Watch the road!
Oh, my God!
Wow, Aldo is making
great time.
(SCREAMING)
A dead end!
This can't be right!
Oh, my God!
Ah! God!
Intriguing lady,
we are here.
Now, you must go...
because I fear if I stare
into your beautiful green
eyes a moment longer...
I will fall in love.
Oh! Too late.
My God, does
that ever work?
I will take that as...
That's a "no."
A "no."
Take that as a "no."
(SPEAKING ITALIAN)
You were
just hitting on me.
I like to play the odds.
Yeah. Well, good luck.
Here is my phone number.
Memorize it, then burn it.
These people we are dealing
with, they like to...
How you say?
Murder entire families.
Do you have
something for me?
Do I have something
for you?
Would you like
something from me?
Not that.
What do you want from me?
You're supposed to have an
envelope with my gun in it.
I don't have a gun.
I am just aroused
from looking at you.
It was joke.
There is no gun.
They said you would no longer
be needing one.
Good luck!
Ciao!
Good gravy. Was Pepe
Le Pew not available?
NANCY: Stop
complaining, Suzie.
You're getting more action
than I have had in days.
Months.
Years.
Three years and 40 days.
Do we have an update
on De Luca?
Yes, he should be
pulling up...
right about now.
(EXHALES)
Oh, wow. He is hot.
I'm not gonna lie to you. I don't
think I can be objective anymore.
I'm rooting for that guy.
I want him to win.
I'm joking, Susan.
Don't report me.
He's handsy.
Let's set up camp in
the pastry shop behind you.
According to Aldo, De Luca
spends all night in the casino.
I'm going in, Nancy.
Susan, you heard Elaine.
Track and report.
No contact!
I'll track De Luca inside,
then I'll report.
And if he initiates
contact with me...
I'll just go with it.
Susan!
Your "cat lady" look is not
gonna fit in in there.
That's why Penny Morgan is
gonna burn her cat T-shirt...
and spend some
of that Mary Kay money.
This is full-blown rogue!
♪ Yeah, I'm a diva
♪ Living in the club
I don't need nobody
♪ I'm doing my own thing
♪ All I really want
to do is party
(MAN WHISTLING)
(SPEAKING ITALIAN)
You guys are terrible!
I really hope De Luca is still
in there, for your sake.
And they're not gonna
reimburse you for all that.
You should have gone
to cheaper stores, Susan.
Okay, I'm going offline,
Nancy.
No, wait!
Susan!
♪ I'm a diva
♪ Doing my thing
Don't need nobody ♪
Well, buongiorno, boys!
If I'm not out in 10 minutes,
it's because I won the place.
Let me just
rub that for luck.
Oh, that's an oily scalp.
I'm sorry, but I have
to check you in.
Your name, please?
Penny Morgan.
I don't see you on the list.
I'm so sorry.
She's with me.
Darling.
(GROWLS)
You're late.
The way you look...
I'd say it was more
than worth the wait. Come.
Let's get a drink.
Ow. Ow.
Such a gentleman.
You look absolutely stunning
tonight here, darling.
What the fuck are you doing
in here, arsehole?
That's quite a tone
change, isn't it?
What are you doing in here?
You are completely
compromising me right now.
I'm compromising you?
Fucking hilarious.
You were about
to cause a scene
trying to get into
this fucking place.
Give me a little credit. What
do you think I'm gonna do?
Run over there and be like,
"Hey, I'm a crazy lady!
"Where's the buffet?
I'm from the Midwest.
"Where's Blue Man Group?"
I am not an idiot, Ford.
You are an idiot.
You should not be
in this casino...
because De Luca is here and
I need to get close to him.
How you gonna do that? How
you gonna do that, Cooper?
What, are you gonna
seduce him?
That your big fucking plan?
Yeah, what if it is?
Why is that so hard
to believe?
Because you look like a flute
player in a wedding band.
That's fucking why!
I'm here to take De Luca out.
Ooh. It sounds romantic.
I hope you get lucky!
God damn it, if I was trying
to sound romantic...
you'd be lying on the floor,
soaking wet and breathless...
wondering what came over you.
But I'm not, so get the
fuck out of my way!
I need you to rein it in,
buddy, okay?
If you take out De Luca, we don't
have a shot at getting Rayna.
So take it down, like,
5,000 notches!
Take it down?
That's how you get
polonium-210 slipped
into your drink...
and go 18 months
in intensive care
for radiation poisoning...
and go six months
without eyesight...
while everybody you've
ever loved is gunned down!
Really? Everybody
that you love
has been gunned down,
and just you survive?
Did you ever think that maybe
everybody you love
is not being killed...
but they're
killing themselves
because they can't stand
to be around you?
This shit's the real deal,
life and death.
This, the field...
is a hell of a lot different than
sitting behind your fucking monitor...
googling shit.
Stay away from me, Ford.
And do not let
De Luca see you.
And by the way,
I can see your gun
sticking out
of your back pocket.
Unless you're so extreme that
you've got a second dick...
coming out of your hip!
Konnichiwa.
Ma'am,
these seats are reserved.
Of course they are.
I'm gonna have to ask you
to wait outside.
Yes, absolutely.
Nope, not a door?
I knew that.
Of course it's not a door.
It probably
happens all the time.
It's never happened before.
Okay.
Ma'am.
Yes.
Now, right here is okay.
No more exploring, please.
Okay. Lovely.
MAN: (SOFTLY)
From Mr. De Luca.
(EARPIECE BEEPING)
Nancy?
Susan. Oh, my God! Hi!
I found her.
I found Rayna.
She's with De Luca.
You did it!
Excellent tracking
and reporting, madam.
Oh, my God.
Somebody just put
something in her drink.
NANCY: What is it?
Is it poison?
I don't think
it's a fiber supplement.
She killed Fine, Nance.
I could really enjoy just
watching her die right now.
She's the only one who knows
where the bomb is...
so Dudaev would never
get his hands on it.
Oh, God, Susan.
What are you gonna do?
Excuse me, ma'am.
Hi, do you speak English?
Because I think somebody just
put a roofie in your cocktail.
Are you sure
it wasn't you?
What? No! God, I would never!
Could you point
the man out?
He just kind of
zipped out that door.
He's wearing a purple bowtie.
(INAUDIBLE)
Thank you, Miss...
Oh. Penny. Morgan.
But it's no trouble, really.
I think us ladies have to
watch out for each other.
This kind of thing
happens all the time.
People often try
to roofie you?
Once, I asked someone
for a Tylenol,
and they gave me
a Tylenol PM.
I'm not sure what
their intentions were, but...
It seems
they may have found him.
Would you come with me
to identify him?
Yes. Of course.
I'm happy to help.
(SOFTLY) Holy shit.
My friend here
said she saw you
put something in my drink.
I don't know
any of you people. Okay?
I'm just in Rome
on business.
I was about to head back
to my hotel and go to sleep.
Perfect. Just in time
for a nightcap.
Apparently, there's nothing
wrong with it.
I don't want your drink.
(INAUDIBLE)
Fuck you, Rayna.
Mmm. Scrumptious.
So, joke's on you.
(CHOKING) Fuck you!
Fuck you!
(GURGLING)
How long was I out?
You fainted just long enough
for us to laugh at you.
What happened?
It was all a dream.
I'm just kidding.
A man's throat dissolved.
Sorry, I'm not usually,
you know...
Oh, thank you. That's...
surprisingly polite.
Sorry about that.
I've seen a lot of things
in my day. I just haven't...
I have never seen that,
exactly.
Penny, do you feel the need
to tell anybody about
what you just saw?
I'm not gonna tell anybody.
That asshole
got what he deserved.
I knew from the second
I saw him, I thought...
"That guy doesn't
deserve a throat."
So, good on you.
I would like to take you
to dinner to say thank you.
And we must discuss
this hideous dress.
It's just hysterical.
Oh, good,
that's what I was hoping for.
And by the way...
Hristo was supposed to be
looking after me at the bar...
and making sure nobody
put anything in my drinks.
(SIGHS)
(SIGHS) They'll give him
a talking-to.
Seems fair.
Maybe dock him a day's wage.
(GUNSHOT)
Or shoot him in the head.
That always works.
Rome is quite amaz...
Rome is the worst.
Yes.
So boring and tacky.
I'm so glad one of us
finally said it. (LAUGHS)
You have lipstick
on your teeth.
Really?
Looks like you ate
a box of crayons.
Damn it.
Here we are.
These should have been brought
out when we first sat down.
That's exactly
what I was thinking.
So far, I'm riddled with
disappointment at the service.
So sorry.
Signora, I apologize.
I once saw someone eat...
one of these before.
This is... strange.
Do you always tear your food
up into little pieces?
You look like a squirrel.
I was just checking
for the consistency.
Mmm.
You eat like a baby.
Thank you.
So, do you like to have a
look at the wine list?
Yes. Penny, you can order.
Okay. Oh!
Has some heft.
Okay.
I'm feeling a red.
Kind of a red.
I like a lot of noise.
I like a little bit of...
kind of a barky finish.
I tend to like a white...
with the grit of a hummus...
that's, of course,
been thinned out.
Just kind of jump up
in the front of your palate...
and then rip back
and sizzle.
Almost a mineral
kind of dirt finish...
if we're having meat. Okay,
here, this is looking...
promising.
Something with...
This one has
nice hints of toast...
and dogwood,
I assume? Hmm?
Uh...
I will have
the Sapori e Delizie.
Right.
That is the name
of this restaurant.
Yes, I'm aware of that.
So, why don't you
surprise us...
with something
that we don't know?
Like a delicious
bottle of wine.
Right. Sorry, I will be back
in five minutes, okay?
So hard to get
good help these days.
Don't you find that?
I find that.
I know who all
your active agents are.
Okay, I'm sensing, uh...
Can I do a little do over?
I, uh...
I really don't know
how to order wine.
I'm from a small town
in Iowa.
I saved up my money
to come on this Rome trip.
I had a little jar
on my desk at work...
and everybody said, "You're
never gonna make enough money."
But I did, and I'm here.
And then I meet you,
and I can't afford...
to eat at a place like this,
and I'm just trying
to impress you...
and doing a really
poor job of it.
I thought as much.
Your cheap prom dress doesn't
exactly scream sophistication.
Oh.
Well, I didn't go to prom,
so maybe it is...
When I was a little girl
growing up in Bulgaria...
which is the worst,
by the way.
Poor people everywhere and
cabbages constantly cooking.
There was this woman who was
kicked out of her house...
and she lost
all her money.
She couldn't even
sell her body.
So she became a clown
on the streets.
She would perform all her
tricks standing in mud,
and just cry and cry.
You remind me of this woman.
Oh. Thank you.
I don't know what it is, but
there's something about you.
The fainting,
the way you talk...
your terrible
sense of style.
I did get this at
quite a lovely...
It makes me sad
to think of you here
spending all your
savings on Rome.
Come on.
We're going to Budapest.
Budapest?
I have some business
to finish there...
and you can take my private
jet when we're done...
anywhere you want to
get home.
My way of repaying you
for saving my life.
Okay.
Is there a problem?
No. Not at all. Let's go.
Hey! Wait, what?
I'm just talking
to the girl!
Okay, okay.
Let's not make a scene.
Let me just
get my room key out...
and I'll grab a bag
and pack my things.
It's Susan.
She's sending a code.
RAYNA: No, they can
fly you back later.
"Shut...
And if the rest of your clothes
look like that dress...
"...down...
...I can send someone
to burn them for you.
Ha-ha.
"...the power."
Quite a zinger!
Shut down the power
to the Casino Di Rome.
What?
Shut the entire bloody
grid down, then! Now!
That would be great.
(GRUNTING)
MAN: Everybody, please remain
calm and stay where you are.
(GRUNTS)
Oh, no!
What's happening?
(RAYNA SCREAMS)
(MOUTHING) I've got this.
What the fuck just happened?
God damn it.
Oh, my God! Rayna.
Thank God
your hair broke your fall.
I don't know what happened.
The lights were going out, and I
don't know if it's a robbery.
Two of your guys slammed
into me and took you down.
I think one of them
touched my bottom.
I don't know which one,
but I definitely felt a hand.
Are they gonna be okay?
I wouldn't
worry about them.
Their fate has just
been sealed.
Sorry. I'll let you go.
Shame on you!
Wow.
This is a really jazzy plane.
Is this yours?
It was my father's.
You've never been
on a private jet before?
Oh, no.
I did get upgraded
to premium economy once...
which was pretty plush.
Premium economy.
Sounds like a pen
for dirty animals.
Yeah, probably.
But it was not
quite like this.
Thank you.
Why are you being
so nice to me?
Can't just be because
I remind you
of some sad Bulgarian clown.
You remind me of my mother.
Oh.
Really?
You know that you and I
are pretty close in age.
You're funny.
It's the Bulgarian
clown in you.
Okay.
She was marvelous.
But she was different.
Eccentric, like you are.
Oh.
The moment I saw you
standing there
in that abortion
of a dress...
Ah... Come on.
...it was as if to say...
"This is what I've got, world.
It's hideous, but it's mine."
This was her.
(GASPS)
Oh, wow.
Hey, how'd you get
that picture of me?
I look amazing.
Hello, doppelganger.
She was the only person
I could ever trust.
Well, here's to your mom.
To my mother. And to you.
And here's to you.
You may never
be as wise as an owl...
but you'll always
be a hoot to me.
What a stupid fucking
retarded toast.
You're delightful.
As are you.
Mmm.
Now, where did you say
we were headed?
(CLEARS THROAT)
Headed?
Did you say where?
Oh, God.
PATRICK: If you ever feel like
you have been poisoned...
chew one of these.
Chew one of these.
What happened?
I've never seen somebody
dive for
stool softener before.
That's one thing
that happened.
What did you do?
Did you drug me?
Of course I did.
I told you,
I can't trust anybody.
I had to look
through your things.
Anyway, tell me...
are your hemorrhoids
particularly large,
or just tenacious?
Stop texting!
I'm not texting,
if you must know.
I'm playing Candy Crush
and I just made level 95.
God, that is so rude!
(GUNSHOT)
Jesus, Colin,
what the fuck are you doing?
I'm sorry, Rayna, but there's
been a change of plans.
Who paid you off, Colin?
Colin hasn't worked here for,
like, eight months.
I'm Fredrick.
Is that why
you're doing this?
Because I don't remember
your fucking name?
Let's just say
there's some people
who really want
what you're selling.
You don't have to do this.
I can give you a very
comfortable life, Col...
Um...
You forgot my name again,
didn't you?
No, I didn't.
Yeah.
It's...
Don't say fucking Colin.
Fuck! I don't give a shit
what your name is.
You're the fucking help!
Nice try, Colin... but Stan
and I already sold it to...
It's Fredrick!
(GUNSHOT)
Fredrick!
Sorry, lady, but they only
paid me for one...
Ow!
(SCREAMS)
Come on!
Rayna! Go to the cockpit
and level us out!
Like I know how to fly
a fucking airplane!
That was weird.
Ah!
Blow that thing
all you want, lady.
Yeah? Why don't
you blow me, Colin.
Ow! It's Fredrick.
Ah!
(ALARMS BEEPING)
(WHIMPERING)
Oh, for fuck's sake!
I got it.
I know what to do.
Are you okay?
No!
I've got a dead man's
head up my ass.
This one's for Fine.
Downdraft!
Not again!
Do you have any idea
what you're fucking doing?
(GROANS)
The controls
are so sensitive.
(FARTING)
Oh, God.
One of these dead fuckers
just shit his pants.
Okay, wait a minute.
I got it.
I think I got... Okay.
Okay.
Good thing I learned to use
that flight simulator app, huh?
Congratulations,
Penny Morgan.
You just blew your cover.
Now put the plane
on autopilot and get up.
Any bullshit, and I'll
blow your CIA brains
all over that control panel.
I know what
you're thinking.
And you're wrong.
My real name is...
Did you come up with
your spy name yet? No.
Mine would be...
Amber Valentine.
What are you, a porn star?
You're fucking
hilarious, huh?
I'm a private bodyguard,
and your father hired me
to protect you.
Bodyguard? You? Please.
That's funny, because the
way I see it, without me...
you would currently be crashed
in the Alps right now.
Or you'd be
laying in a morgue
with a hole burned
in your throat.
You little spoiled
piece of shit.
Why would my father hire
somebody like you?
Because he trusted me.
And for whatever
fucking reason,
he loved you.
Didn't even want you to know
I was watching you.
So he was the one
that made me come up
with this whole loser
Penny Morgan bullshit.
Yeah, "You look
just like my dead mama.
"Wah."
And fuck you for saying
I look anything
like that fucking beast.
No wonder your father
never had the son he wanted.
You fuck that monster once...
and you just drop
the fucking mic and walk out.
Fuck you. Everything
you've said is a lie.
Oh.
What happened? Did I hit
a little sore spot?
Yeah, he always wanted a
son, and you knew it.
Look, he wanted you
to take over the business.
He was just afraid you were
gonna get yourself killed.
So if you wanna live, and you
wanna unload that bomb...
you stick with me.
And if you got
a problem with that...
you know what you
can do, Rayna?
You and your bullshit accent
can land this fucking plane
by yourselves.
Okay, bodyguard.
But if I find out you're lying
to me about any of this...
I'll show you ways to die
you never even dreamed of.
Now, let's go to Budapest.
I need a fucking drink.
Yeah, I bet you fucking do.
(SIGHS)
Oh, my God.
♪ People want my power
And they want my station
♪ Stormed my winter palace
But they couldn't take it
♪ Try to pull my status
But they couldn't fake it ♪
Welcome back to the Four Seasons
Budapest, Miss Boyanov.
Don't talk to me.
You're not my friend.
Get away from me.
Move. Move! I got it.
So, what's the plan?
Who are we meeting?
You're my bodyguard,
not my business partner...
so just focus
on guarding my body.
So not knowing
who we're meeting tonight
is gonna make me
extra effective.
That's okay. I get it.
I got shit to do.
You'll probably be fine.
Why don't I go get you
a nice dress to be buried in?
Dumbass.
I'm meeting
a potential bidder,
if you must know.
If they don't top
the current offer,
the sale
will happen tomorrow.
Where?
I don't know yet.
Anton!
Ouch!
Anton is part of my
security team, psycho!
Yeah, well, guess what?
I don't like his face.
I don't like the looks
of your face!
And who the fuck are you?
I'm the person that's gonna
cut your dick off
and glue it
to your forehead...
so you look like
a limp-dick unicorn.
That's who the fuck I am.
Your name should be
"Mr. Bag o' Dicks"...
not "Anton."
Okay. Jesus.
Let's just calm down, okay?
Does he not look like a bag o' dicks?
Enough.
I can see why my father
liked you now.
Amber is my hired bodyguard.
Be more like her.
And your head better not have
broken my fucking phone.
We've got a big night
ahead of us.
Don't be afraid
to clean yourself up, Amber.
Take a shower
is what I'm saying.
Yeah? Don't be afraid
to hit water yourself.
You smell like a dead hooker
that washed up on the beach...
then roasted in the sun
for a week
before anybody found
her body.
Okay. You need
to take it way down.
I'm sorry, that's too much.
Okay, that was too much.
Jeez!
Too much.
God.
What are you staring at?
I will destroy you.
And then after
I'm done destroying you,
I'll take a picture
of what's left...
of your body, and I'm gonna
text it to your mother.
With a little note that says
his last words were...
"My mother was terrible.
You did this to me."
That's so fucking mean.
Yeah, I'm so fucking mean.
You're just
figuring that out?
Give me your coat.
This is a man's coat.
Yeah, but I don't
see a man, do I?
I see a reject from
The Sound of Music.
It was my mother's coat,
but she's very masculine.
You look like ABBA took a shit
and put a trench coat on it.
Well, I won't
give it to you.
I've been in this dress
for 12 fucking hours.
Give me your coat.
No.
Yeah. No, I won't give...
This is my coat.
I'm gonna reach through
your fucking body...
and rip out your back
like a fucking werewolf.
Without tearing the jacket.
Just so I can
wear your jacket,
and give you a final
"Fuck you."
Oh, no, you won't.
I'm gonna take
that fucking coat.
(GROANING)
I warned you, you Swedish
gummy fish motherfucker!
ANTON: Ouch!
Oh, my God.
Nance?
Oh, my God, Susan!
Hello. Hello?
Just say something
to me, please.
Susan? Anything.
I cannot handle this,
Susan!
There is nothing
in real life
that someone could
do to a spy...
that is filthier
or more upsetting
than what my brain
will cook up right now.
So save me from myself,
Susan!
Because you know
what's going to happen.
I'm gonna get chattier,
aren't I?
Did you know that you can't
ever change having big pores?
Oh, my God, Nancy,
you are driving me nuts!
I couldn't talk because I was in
an elevator filled with people.
You're all right.
Oh, thank God.
You disappeared for 12 hours.
We didn't know what happened!
I had to take out my earpiece
and my camera.
Rayna's on to our agents
and she was gonna
spot my equipment
from a mile away.
You're with Rayna?
You're not supposed to be
within a mile away of her.
Nancy, I know,
but I'm in deep
and I'm getting
such good intel.
Please,
I just need to remain
on radio silence
just a little bit longer.
Well, don't worry,
because I'll be able
to keep a better eye
on you now.
What are you
talking about? How?
What are you doing here?
Elaine wanted to know exactly
what you were up to...
so I tracked your earpiece.
They sent me here to find you.
They sent you?
I'm as unknown as you are,
so they thought
my cover was safe.
Did they give you
an identity?
It's so cool.
I said I wanted to be
Amber Valentine... What?
...and they let me use it.
I don't know why you got
to pick your identity.
I had to go
as a freaking cat lady.
RAYNA: Amber!
BOTH: Yes?
Who is this?
I'm sorry. I didn't know
the police were here.
This is my colleague,
detective.
The one I fucking
told you about.
No, you didn't.
Yes, I did, Helen Keller!
You're both named Amber?
What did I tell you
about talking to me?
Nothing. You just said
nothing about talking.
You want me to have Cagney
and fucking Lacey
explain it to you?
Cagney's coming down
your fucking throat.
Lacey, she's gonna
come up your ass.
I'm gonna meet them
in the fucking middle...
and play your heart
like a fucking accordion.
I'm gonna pump
that shit until it pops.
You Swedish bitch.
You wouldn't dare.
You gonna cry, you little
Swiss fucking pussy?
I'm not gonna cry.
You're crying now!
I'm not!
It's so fucking hot!
You know, just, let's leave
Anton alone for now.
Please.
What's your name?
Susan Cooper.
What?
Sorry, it came out.
What did I...
She's not supposed to
fucking say her real name.
She's one of my best. She's
highly fucking skilled.
Very skilled.
At what? Getting things
out of a high cupboard?
(LAUGHS)
Don't do that.
That's very good!
Because I'm tall.
Weirdly, I'm not very good
at reaching high things.
A doctor once said to me I have
the muscle capacity of an infant.
My arms are like two noodles.
(RAYNA SCREAMS)
(GUN FIRE)
Susan, get Rayna
to safety, now!
I've got her.
Go!
Get away!
Oh, my God!
Who puts a roof on a scooter?
What are you, the Pope?
Ooh!
(SHOUTING)
Get out of the way!
Oh!
(HORN HONKING)
Oh, my God!
This guy is driving crazy!
I can't keep up with him!
Wait a minute.
I got it.
All right, little detour.
Oh, God.
Let's do this!
(ALL YELLING)
I am so badass!
(MEN CLAMORING)
I got it.
I know what you're saying.
You're no prize yourself!
Get back to work!
Where are we going?
Smells like cheese
under here!
Apologies.
I may be sweating...
cheese because I had
quite a hearty lasagna.
Fucking ridiculous
clown show!
This fuckery stops now.
(REVS SCOOTER)
(ENGINE REVVING)
Excuse me, do you know
if there's a Popeyes Chicken
around here?
What?
I saw a KFC down the way,
but I'm more of a Popeyes guy.
The food
is really weird...
Oh, my God,
I'll ask someone else!
Okay, enough!
(TIRES SCREECHING)
Drop your weapon!
Oh, my God. Karen.
Why aren't you in Capri?
I'm so sorry I shot you.
You must not have known
it was me, either.
I changed my hair.
Oh, yeah.
Looks really good.
Are those extensions?
No, it's just my hair.
You know, a few clips.
Colored.
Okay, if you say so.
I'm sorry. And I'm sorry
about this, too.
(GUNSHOTS)
(PANTING)
Oh, my God.
No, no, no!
Susan! My thighs
are on fire!
I don't care!
Where is Rayna?
I don't know.
She slipped off me.
I was very sweaty.
I thought I asked you
to watch her.
I don't know how she ran so fast,
particularly with that hair.
It must weigh
20 pounds at least.
Maybe she's a witch. Do you
think she put a spell on me?
Karen Walker is dead.
What?
She's a double agent!
Somebody shot her
right in front of me.
I don't know who did it.
I don't know how deep
this whole thing goes.
Oh, my God.
(YELPS)
Get your motherfucking
asses up here!
Now!
NANCY:
But what if she heard?
She didn't hear.
But what if
she did hear?
We weren't even
talking that loud.
A woman like that
has super ears.
Okay, she does not
have super ears...
and I'm only bringing this up
because you asked me to...
but you are putting a very
negative spin on this situation.
Oh, wow. We're going with that
now, are we, Amber Valentine?
Susan Cooper, really?
Susan Cooper?
(ELEVATOR BELL DINGS)
Okay. Here we go.
Okay. We got this.
My legs won't
seem to move.
Okay, Nancy, I realize
that you are scared,
but you are in this now...
and I really, really
need you to hold it together.
Holding it together.
I shall now be the most held-together
person you have ever met.
Okay. Let's go.
Oh, dear.
Be prepared for anything.
She's erratic.
It's impossible to tell
what she's thinking.
Probably because she's
thinking in Bulgarian.
What are you doing? I'm
just tying up my shoelaces.
You're wearing a loafer.
Get over here.
(BUZZES)
(BOTH EXCLAIM)
Get in!
Shit! People are trying
to kill me
and all that's left
of my fucking security team
is you two defending me...
and you look like somebody's
demented aunts on vacation!
Do you have anyone
on your team...
other than this
asthmatic Big Bird?
Yeah, we usually
just use her
for non-physical
security resources.
I'm very non-physically
resourceful.
I do a lot of reading.
I read palms and maps...
and I've read all of
The Hunger Games...
How is that helpful?
I don't know.
I'm panicking!
And you!
You have to stop with these
stupid Penny Morgan outfits!
You have to dress
like an actual human!
Get me more security
when I come back out here
or you're both dead!
(ROCK MUSIC PLAYING)
♪ I am cold blooded
Suck on this, Rayna.
This mission's gonna
cost you money, you know.
The clothing allowance cut off
halfway through the last...
My God, can you just
please concentrate
on getting the new bodyguard?
God damn it! Please!
All right, all right.
Crabby.
I've already contacted
the agency.
Aw. Come on!
You, in this outfit...
Magnifico!
(DANCE MUSIC PLAYING)
Do we have anything yet?
NANCY: No one so far, Susan.
Slightly intimidating
crowd, however.
Hello, you look nice.
(LAUGHING)
Ah, just keep laughing.
Looks fade.
Keep your eyes open.
God damn it,
I told you to dress up.
And take off those gloves.
You look like
Darth-fucking-Vader.
Yeah? Well, you look like
an Ewok died on your head.
I don't even know
what that means.
You're gonna know
what it means
when I split you open
like a Tauntaun.
Whatever.
Keep an eye out
for this woman.
She's the one coming
to make the bid.
He's got a friend.
Very pretty.
I'm glad you know
what pretty is.
You should remember it next time
you're in a clothing store.
(SCOFFS)
I need you to keep
your eyes open.
I may need
your help out there.
To close my eyes
in the presence
of this beautiful body...
would be a crime.
Oh, God.
Nancy, okay,
you know the woman
I spotted in Paris,
the bomber?
She's coming tonight
to make a bid.
She already works for De Luca
so we know something is up.
I need you to keep an...
Son of a bee sting.
Excuse me, he's mine.
Yeah.
I didn't mean
to hit her that hard.
You're like a balloon animal.
Here, take those.
Hi. What are you doing, Ford?
I'm here to help you, Cooper.
You may have found Rayna,
but you cannot lose her.
This isn't fucking playtime anymore!
Yeah?
It's playtime on your face,
with your stupid mustache!
Where'd you get that from,
Mr. Potato Head?
You are gonna
blow my fucking cover.
Yeah? Sunglasses are not a
cover, they're an accessory.
Get out of here!
You're gonna fuck this up without
me around to save your girly ass.
God, I hate you so much!
You can't let your desire for
me put you in danger, Cooper.
Oh, God, you wish, Magnum.
You dance like
a horny eighth grader.
Are you erect?
Get off me!
Blend in,
or get the fuck out!
You get out of here!
(GROANING)
Yeah, who's dominating now?
(GRUNTS)
Fuck!
Don't, you son of a bitch.
You've gotta be kidding!
Get off of me!
You get off of me! Get your
silky shirt off of me!
(STRAINING)
Blend in,
or get the fuck out.
Thank you
for the beautiful ladies.
You guys okay?
(CROWD CHEERING)
Let's welcome Mr. 50 Cent!
What's up, Budapest?
I just had some goulash.
The shit was on point!
♪ Get the party rockin'
Bottles poppin'
♪ Tonight we gonna
turn up till we
♪ Twisted
Oh, shit. She's here.
We can't let
Rayna see her...
so you need to take out her
bodyguards and I'll deal with her.
Ain't nobody orders
me around!
God, do you have
a better idea?
Yeah, we release
a gas in the club...
causing everybody to get
temporary amnesia.
Get 100 sticks
of dynamite...
Oh, God! Just go!
Just go!
Nancy, I need you
to get in here now.
I'm coming, Susan. I'm here!
Pardon. Excuse me.
Okay. I'm here. I'm here.
♪ Turn up
Wow! 50 Cent Piece!
Thanks for letting me know.
Do not let Rayna
see that woman.
Create a diversion, now.
What kind of diversion?
A big one!
♪ Let's enjoy tonight
Like tonight's our last
♪ We can focus on the future
And reflect on the past
♪ We done came so far
I mean, look where we are ♪
50, I love you!
(CROWD GASPING)
Kiss me!
Get her!
Take me now!
Turn around.
Get off!
I'm coming in!
Nancy, I got her.
Meet me outside.
Okay. Right.
I'm fine now.
Thank you so much.
Okay.
I got my wish. That was it.
I've now got to jump Michael
Buble in Croatia. He wants me.
All right, Cooper.
I've got this under control.
You're coming with me.
Oh, my God, Susan!
Okay, bigger diversion.
Huge diversion.
Bitch!
I gotta know
who she's working for.
Get Rayna out of here!
That's not fair!
(HORN HONKING)
Whoa! Whoa!
God damn it!
Nancy, where are you?
Bit indisposed.
It turns out 50 Cent
doesn't have a great sense
of humor or irony.
I need backup!
I lost my gun in the club!
We're probably
more alike than you think!
Oh!
Okay. Okay.
Oh, shit.
Ow!
(GROANS) Why'd I get
rid of my gloves?
(GASPS)
(LAUGHS)
Ow! Motherbutler!
You got a lot of rage
in that jumpsuit.
You dead serious?
God!
Wait! Wait a minute!
This isn't what you want,
or what I want.
This is like what
the Man wants.
Us, you know? Two smart,
pretty brunettes...
kind of breaking
each other down.
I mean, you look similar to a
gal I was in college with.
Things happened.
I think we all dabble.
It's mostly just kind of
stuff with hands and...
God, I can't wait
to kill you.
(GROANS)
(SCREAMS)
Oh...
That's clean through.
Thanks for your weapon.
It's been inside you,
so I don't think
it should go inside me...
Get up. Get up!
You are under arrest
by Susan Cooper...
and the government
of the United States.
Rayna, how did you do that?
I didn't.
He did.
Hello, Coop.
Fine?
Ow...
FINE: Hey.
Coop.
Wake up!
Did you have a nice nap?
You were snoring
very loudly.
That's just really
not the most
upsetting news right now.
My father used to
bring people here.
Did he also make you dress
like a slutty dolphin trainer?
He'd starve them...
torture them.
You name it.
But he especially
didn't like it
when people lied to him.
Not that I bought it.
You knew?
Of course I knew.
I told you, you were better
off in the basement, Coop.
You could have
avoided all of this.
And what, Fine?
Now you're a nuclear
black marketer?
A terrorist?
No...
He's just fucking me.
You're a loud kisser.
Excuse me?
And it's gross
and unappealing.
You look like some
old, toothless woman
sucking the jelly
out of a donut.
Hey, what's it like
sleeping with the man
that killed your father?
Nice try, Coop.
She already knows
it was Cress.
Ah.
Okay.
You've probably always been in
love with him, haven't you?
Talking in his ear...
hoping eventually one day
he'll fall in love with you.
(CHUCKLES)
Poor little,
pathetic Susan Coleman.
That's not my last name,
so it's really not much
of a burn, is it?
Cooping.
No.
Croupon.
Are you thinking "Groupon"?
No, my name's not "Groupon."
Croupe.
Keep going.
Kapowski.
That's getting
further from it!
Well, whatever the fuck it is,
let's just call you dead.
Hey, baby?
I thought we were gonna hang
on to her till tonight.
I changed my mind.
Goodbye.
(CLICKS)
(GASPS)
(CHUCKLES)
Like I'd waste
a bullet on you.
Put her in the room.
Ah!
Hey, Aldo.
Hello, captured lady.
I failed.
I failed the mission.
Fine is alive...
and he's a traitor.
Don't be downhearted.
My mama said to me...
"Aldo,
life is full of sorrow...
"and surprises.
"But, a magnificent
pair of bosoms...
"will..."
Good story.
Susan.
Get away from me.
No, listen.
I haven't got much time.
Why'd you do it, Fine?
This was my only way in.
I had to fake my death
to gain Rayna's trust.
I jammed the signal,
popped out my lens.
It was easy.
I hated to do it to you, Coop,
but I had to. I had to.
Rayna knew
all about our agents...
because Karen Walker
sold her the names.
I just couldn't trust anyone
at the agency
not to give me away,
not even you.
How do I even know
you're telling me the truth?
Did Karen Walker
try to kill you?
You shot her?
I'm deep undercover.
But not so deep that
I can't still protect you.
All right, look me
in the eye.
What?
Really look me
in the eye.
One of your eyes is bigger
than the other.
Really?
No.
You're perfect,
God damn it.
Asshole.
(GROANS) SUSAN: God! (GROANS)
That hurt.
Good, it was
supposed to.
Bosom.
Is he dangerous?
Only if you have boobs.
So did Rayna
really know I was a spy?
No. Not until you blew your
cover back at that kitchen.
I really thought she was more
experienced than that.
Thank God she's not, huh?
Because if she was,
you'd be dead now.
I think they're pretty
good covers...
I gotta go.
We're heading to De Luca's
villa to meet with Dudaev.
Then we're taking him
to wherever the bomb is.
This thing is almost over.
Hang tight.
Hello, bound lady.
Not now, Aldo.
I think Mr. Fine
has underestimated you.
You found your targets,
you tracked them down,
you fought very hard.
Susan...
you are a good agent.
You'll get them
next time, huh?
Unless we die here.
Then you will not.
You know what,
I'm not going down like this.
I need you to untie me.
Bosom. What?
Stop! God damn it!
Just untie me.
No, you heard Mr. Fine.
He's working a plan.
We have to stay put.
Untie me. Now.
That's my ass.
It is very difficult to see
or gauge my position.
You're just simply
grabbing my ass.
Oh. I am, sorry.
Let's roll
to our side.
God!
Oh! Hey!
The knot is very tight,
but I am making progress.
Your hand is way up in there.
My right hand is restrained
from the weight of my body.
Okay. Let's try this.
Oh, God.
(GRUNTING)
Okay. I will
inchworm my way...
(GRUNTING LOUDLY)
You're being very loud.
(GROANING)
Shh!
Wait. I have idea.
God. Another one?
Oh, Jesus.
Don't move.
Wait, wait, wait!
Stay still.
No, no, no!
Yes, yes, yes.
Oh, God!
Yes.
Can't be happening.
Damn it, I was having
such an empowering moment
before this started.
My penis may be gently kissing
the back of your head.
Just untie me
before I crush your nuts.
Oh, please.
If only we had time
for such pleasures.
Go!
Your face and the knot
are about to enter my colon.
Stop licking it!
(BOTH GRUNTING)
It is done.
Thank you, Aldo.
I don't wanna know
why my neck is wet...
but you did excellent work.
Prego.
Turn around,
let me untie you,
and let's get
the fuck out of here.
(SIZZLING)
I need you to alert
CIA and Interpol.
I'm gonna go to De Luca's
and back up Fine.
You know where
the villa is?
I know everything.
One day, lady super spy...
Susan Cooper...
I will fuck you.
(CHUCKLES)
♪ The danger is
I'm dangerous
♪ And I might just
tear you apart
I love this new car smell.
Really nice.
(SNIFFS) Oh. Mmm.
♪ I'm gonna get ya
♪ Oh, ah, oh
♪ I wanna taste the way
that you bleed
♪ I'm gonna catch ya
I'm gonna get ya, get ya
♪ Oh, ah, oh
♪ I wanna taste
the way that you bleed ♪
(MEN YELLING)
Welcome to Lake Balaton.
I found this staircase
and made them build
a house around it.
Our dear Mr. Dudaev
will be arriving shortly.
You are about to become
a very rich woman, Rayna.
Which means you'll have to be
a little more careful...
about the company you keep.
So many people have such
terrible agendas...
like perhaps
your friend here.
I can see his obvious
outer appeal.
You have terrific eyes.
Thanks.
But he also works
for the CIA, doesn't he?
An odd choice of companion for
someone in your work, Rayna.
Doesn't exactly inspire
confidence in those around you.
Fuck you, Sergio. You would never
talk to my father like that.
I never had to.
Mr. De Luca, it's true.
I worked for the CIA,
but they think I'm dead.
I'm with Rayna now, and I'm
here to help you both.
You and Karen Walker
are both double agents.
What's going on
at the CIA?
Drones taking all
the cool assignments?
(BOTH LAUGH)
If we don't get rid
of him right now,
I'm calling off the deal.
Don't you fucking dare.
Yeah, why don't you listen
to that asshole.
Don't you fucking dare.
You're a bit
outnumbered here, Miss...
I'm sorry, what the
fuck is your name?
Susan Cooper.
I'm with the CIA.
Jesus. Rayna, did you invite
the entire agency here...
or are they just having
a company retreat
at the villa next door?
God, you're funny, huh?
It's just me.
It's gonna be
in your best interest
to keep Fine and me alive.
I'm trying, but I'm not quite
following your logic.
You want me to slow it down
for you? Okay.
You're about to meet
with Solsa Dudaev...
a man I've been collecting
intelligence on for years.
And I'm guessing
that your boys here
are too busy manscaping...
to have told you
how he does business.
Because about half the people
he deals with end up dead.
I can tell you what
Dudaev's gonna do
five minutes before he
even thinks about it.
And I sure as shit know enough to
cover up a Russian flag tattoo...
since Dudaev's brother was
killed by the Russian military.
Jesus!
You own a computer?
You heard of fucking Google?
I'll tell you another thing.
You know
your little girlfriend...
the one from
the Paris bombing?
She's just using you
to get to Rayna.
If it hadn't been for me
last night...
she would've kidnapped her
at the club...
and then you'd be
standing here
with your dick
in your hand...
because you'd never
find that bomb.
So you need me, De Luca.
And I'm not gonna help you
unless you keep Fine alive.
Now, let me
get this straight.
You work for the CIA...
yet you're willing to help me
sell a nuclear bomb...
in order to save
this man's life?
Why would I believe that?
Because she's in love
with him.
Yeah, so what?
This idiot
doesn't even know it.
Too dumb to know
I'd do anything for him.
And fuck the CIA, right?
What have they ever
done for me?
Took 10 years of my life,
gave me shitty pay...
put me in a basement with
a ceiling full of bats...
that pretty sure gave me pinkeye
or at least an allergy...
Something got fucked up
in my eye.
I would've been out
a long time ago
if it hadn't been for Fine.
So, yeah, I'll do anything
it takes to keep him alive.
That's pretty pathetic,
right?
(SCOFFS) Extremely pathetic.
God, you're an asshole.
When this is over, I'm gonna
shave that fucking head.
All right, Miss Havisham.
I'll take you up
on your offer.
But if you try anything,
I mean anything...
I'll make
your dream come true
and send you and
your boyfriend to heaven.
Let's go.
Mr. Dudaev.
Welcome to Hungary.
Like Chechnya,
only easier to pronounce.
Enough with the bullshit.
Where is the package?
Once my client
sees the payment...
she'll take us all to its
very secure hiding spot.
Wherever that may be.
I got it, handsome.
100,000,000 Euros
doesn't buy
what it used to, does it?
Nice ice, Solsa.
Right.
He's all yours.
Gentlemen,
if you would follow me.
Here it is.
What is this bullshit?
Bullshit?
Solsa, I'll have you know...
It's the nuke.
Clever girl.
A lead-lined compartment.
RAYNA: Correct.
The lead lining is thick as to
mask any radiation detection.
My father was extremely
good at his job.
DE LUCA: Unbelievable!
You could have warned me,
Rayna.
I've been throwing
my gym clothes
on top of that thing
for a week.
It is beautiful.
Yes, it is.
What the fuck
are you doing?
Conducting business.
Uh-uh.
Put it in the helicopter.
And don't forget
my diamonds.
What the fuck is going on?
De Luca played you, Rayna.
And you led him right to it.
You didn't expect me
to let him have it, did you?
I mean, it's like giving a
Stradivarius to a hillbilly.
I have a buyer
who's willing to pay me
500,000,000 Euros for it.
And Dudaev would've
never been able
to get that bomb
onto American soil.
My buyer will have it in the
middle of New York City...
and use it next week.
So, you know,
if you haven't seen
Phantom yet...
So, what?
Does this mean you're gonna
kill me too, Sergio?
I'm afraid so.
Sorry, Rayna.
It's just cleaner that way.
You understand.
Explain it to me, De Luca!
(GRUNTS)
(SIGHS)
God. He means well.
This day just keeps getting
better and better.
Thanks for the
performance, folks.
But sorry, Rayna,
show's over.
Go! Go!
(GRUNTS)
Holy shit.
Where's De Luca?
Susan!
Get down!
(GROANS)
No!
Whoa! Ah!
(BOTH GRUNTING)
I should have killed you
when I had the chance.
Rayna!
What?
Under the car!
Push it over!
Seriously?
God, use those fucking
bird arms and push it!
(CLICKS)
(LAUGHING)
Oh!
What happened?
Did I get him?
De Luca's got the bomb
on the helicopter. Get up!
Oh, fuck me!
I got this.
No!
Hurry up, hurry up, hurry up!
Hurry up!
Come on!
Kill her!
I've got this.
I've done this before!
Ah!
(GUN CLICKS)
Cooper, you're gonna
fuck this up!
Shut up and help!
Are you kidding me?
Ford, what the hell
are you doing?
I'm gonna crawl up you...
and take out De Luca.
Get your hands off my boobs!
I'm saving you!
Oh, my God.
Those do not belong on those!
I can't get a good grip.
Your pants are too slippery!
You should have worn
coarser pants.
Well, I'm tired of wearing
my fucking sandpaper pants.
Clench your ass!
Clench your fucking ass!
Oh! Get out of there!
Help me out!
You motherfucker!
I'm gonna report you to HR.
(YELLS)
Hang on tight!
I'm gonna swing like
I'm on a trapeze,
and leap my way up
to the cockpit...
(SCREAMING)
I told you you was gonna
fuck this up, Cooper!
SUSAN: Holy smokes!
Ooh, that's high!
(SCREAMS)
God damn it!
Fucking new suit.
This shit ends now!
Freeze!
Oh, my God!
I am not in the fucking mood
for your bullshit!
Yeah? Then you'll love this!
(SCREAMS)
I am not in the mood
for your bullshit!
Back up!
Sorry, spy.
Playtime's over.
Yeah, it is.
Say goodbye to your toys!
What are you doing?
Don't you dare!
Oh, my God!
Don't!
No!
Oh, my God!
(GROANS)
Die!
(GUNSHOT)
Ah!
(WHOOPING)
I just shot a man!
Is it wrong
it felt so right?
It's so me!
Hey! Heroic lady!
In my country,
there is a saying
about women like you...
"Hot as fuck!"
Oh, God. Not now, Aldo.
Go, Susan!
Oh.
That was not part
of my plan.
(GRUNTS)
Just like a woman
to wear jewelry into battle.
Although,
this is the ugliest
fucking necklace
I've ever seen!
Yes, it is.
And it's all yours...
with an adjustable toggle!
(SCREAMING)
(ALARMS BEEPING)
Here we go. No problem.
Come on!
Okay!
All right, I got it.
I got it.
Nice copter!
Where'd you get it?
It's 50 Cent's!
I had to deputize him
to let us use it!
He is so afraid of me!
I'm a motherfucking spy!
Let's go shoot
somebody else!
Simmer down, 50 Cent,
or I'll mount you again.
This day is just getting
better and better!
He wants me!
I think we should land.
I dropped a nuke
in the water.
(EXHALES)
Good job, guys.
Sorry about the lake.
All right, motherfucker,
don't push.
You're gonna
get your pictures.
There's enough 50
to go around.
You know I just helped
kill a terrorist, right?
You ever see Kanye
do some shit like that?
He never, never!
Isn't this wonderful?
I was hoping to spend
the rest of my life in jail.
Give me some quality time
to deal with the fact...
that I was sleeping with
the man who killed my father.
Anyway. Call my lawyer.
Get the Goyard tote
from the hotel.
I need everything on time...
Do you think
I still work for you?
Whatever. Fuck you.
I knew you really liked me.
Hey!
Fuck you too.
Don't touch
my fucking hair!
What are you looking at?
Oh, God, Aldo, don't...
I am too tired
to fend off your groping.
(WITH BRITISH ACCENT)
Please.
I understand completely.
Look, my real name
is Albert...
MI6.
Look, I'm sorry if
my disguise was a bit much.
I just like to really
get into character.
Although I fear
I may have become
overexcited
at certain points.
Little bit.
By way of apology...
should your work ever
bring you to London...
I would love
to take you for dinner.
Okay. Yeah,
I think that would be nice.
Wonderful.
God!
(WITH ITALIAN ACCENT) How you
like my English accent, huh?
I learn it from
the Downton Abbey.
(WITH BRITISH ACCENT)
No, I'm only joking.
Or am I?
Oh, my God.
FINE: Coop.
Great work.
What a job.
Super Cooper.
Really amazing.
Thanks.
ELAINE: Yes, it was.
You really came through.
Thank you, ma'am.
I'd like to keep you
out in the field for now.
Wow.
We need you to fly
to Prague tomorrow...
to infiltrate an international
drug-smuggling ring.
Here's your new identity.
You in, Cooper?
Agent Susan Cooper
reporting for duty, ma'am.
Nobody says or does that, but great.
I won't do that.
Okay.
Thank you.
Francis Mays is an
unemployed telemarketer
living off her
disability checks.
Oh, sweet Jesus!
And who wears reading glasses
in their passport photo?
She's only kidding.
She got ya!
(ALL LAUGHING)
Oh, my God!
That was a good one!
Yeah, actually, I'm not. I
don't have a sense of humor.
No, you don't.
We'll talk soon.
Glad the pinkeye
is under control.
That was actually
an allergy...
Okay. Got it.
So, you're a spy now, Coop.
Yeah.
Congratulations.
Thanks.
I don't think
I'll ever find anyone
as good as you
in the basement.
I think you will.
There's a lot of good people
down there.
So, hey...
I know a great little
restaurant right near here.
Maybe you and I could go
for a nice, long dinner?
You know what,
I'm just kind of feeling
like a girls' night.
You understand, right?
Yeah, sure.
I'll catch you later.
You go have a great time.
Thank you.
You're a lot furrier
than I thought you'd be.
Yeah.
Smell you later, pal.
(CHUCKLES)
Hey, Coop.
All those things you said
about me to De Luca...
Did you mean that?
God, I admire you.
Glad you're still
alive, Beverly,
you silly fucking
girly wanker!
God!
Nice work, Cooper.
Wow. Is that a compliment?
That's not easy
for you to do.
Fuck it. Look, you
did a good job.
Probably just beginner's
luck, though.
There we go.
Where did you get a suit?
I fucking made it,
didn't I?
It's nice.
You still out
of the CIA?
Probably not.
They need me.
I think I need to spend some
time on my own first, though.
Clear my head.
I'm gonna take this
down the coast.
Maybe spend some time in Italy.
Drive it to Greece.
Sometimes a man
needs to go to sea.
SUSAN: Sounds good, Ford.
Good for you.
Take care.
NANCY: Bye.
FORD: Arrivederci.
Do you think
he knows that's a lake?
No, I don't.
Let's go.
Okay.
You can't let anybody see
how sore I am.
I got you.
Okay.
Come here.
My glutes
are really seizing up.
If you're sore,
I'll tell you what.
Take a hot bath and then
we're gonna celebrate.
I hope you like champagne
and beef jerky.
Well... Oh. That's a...
You have to!
Because I stole
a case of it...
I don't know
if I like them together.
...out of 50 Cent's
helicopter!
Slower, slower.
FORD: Cooper,
is this a fucking lake?
How the fuck
do I get to Italy?
(SNORING)
Ow.
MAN: Bosoms.
(SCREAMING)
Ah, stop screaming.
You loved it.
Ugh. God.
♪ Yeah, listen here!
♪ I'm your little heartbreaker
Your little earth shaker
♪ Don't shake
your finger at me
♪ No, no
♪ I ain't misbehaving
I don't need your saving
♪ A little space
is something I need
♪ I'm not that little darling
I don't beg your pardon
♪ I'm trouble with a
capital "T" Yeah, yeah
♪ I'm no angel
There's no stopping me
♪ Here I come, here I come
here I come...
♪ Well I'm your bad seed
rising Ain't no use denying
♪ This girl ain't a good girl
no more
♪ Bad seed rising
ain't no use in crying
♪ I still wear a halo, my Lord
♪ No use denying, this girl
ain't a good girl no more
♪ This girl ain't a good girl
no more
♪ Now listen here
♪ Bless my heart, bless my
soul Like my mama told me so
♪ Never lie, keep it gold
Always take care of my own
♪ 'Cause they're always looking
They're looking out for me
♪ Here I come, here I come
here I come...
♪ Well I'm your bad seed
rising Ain't no use denying
♪ This girl ain't a good girl
no more
♪ Bad seed rising
ain't no use in crying
♪ I still wear a halo,
my Lord
♪ No use denying, this girl
ain't a good girl no more
♪ This girl ain't a good girl
no more
♪ Here I come, here I come
here I come...
♪ Here I come
♪ Here I come, here I come
here I come...
♪ Here I come
♪ Here I come, here I come
here I come...
♪ Here I come
♪ I'm your bad seed rising
ain't no use denying
♪ This girl
ain't a good girl no more
♪ Bad seed rising
Ain't no use in lying
♪ This girl
ain't a good girl no more
♪ Bad seed rising
Ain't no use in crying
♪ I still wear a halo
my Lord
♪ Ain't no use denying
♪ This girl ain't a good girl
no more
♪ Now listen here
♪ This girl ain't a good girl
no more
♪ Ain't no use denying
♪ This girl ain't a good girl
no more
no more ♪
Finished?
Yeah.
Round two?
All right.
Don't do that thing
with your thumb again.
(BOTH LAUGHING)
I can't believe I said it!
I hate myself for saying it!
She said it!
Someone needs to stop Clearway Law.
Public shouldn't leave reviews for lawyers.