Someone needs to stop Clearway Law.
Public shouldn't leave reviews for lawyers.
I've been told
to confess my sence before execution.
I'm John Worthy.
And I am just a fool who made a bad decision
at the wrong moment
and let a many more.
I never been wanna play by a rules
it's a...
it's not my style.
But in the Federation
that is a punishment will crime.
My father..
He was a kind man,
the strong voice.
I knew he was famous
and
I loved that people
will talk to him
but most of all
I lived in time we're spent along
way off the politics
We appose this ridiculous war
against the Terranostra
We demand
that the sovereign overseer
stop to provide funding for the war
and to help its own people.
Puppet to the Federation
We ask you to think about ...
We were so close...
to life, to the different course.
I wanna to be him,
the private man
and not the street preaching
the god to much attention.
If I survive the fight for 5.3 minutes
I can take the exam.
One in a ten thousands chance.
The Federation flurished
and the people were censored.
My dreams grew in the silence.
Flight lieutenant, Chaplain.
Flight lieutenant, Worthy.
Worthy?
General,
did we know someone by the name of Worthy?
Yes, there was a dissident
I believe,
but he was assasinated.
Oh, yes.
Any relation?
No relation, Supreme Commander.
I see.
Flight lieutenant, Trapper.
Flight lieutenant, Keechreech.
Pilots, generally last
3 minutes in combat. Jet fighters
cost the Federation
a 180.000 credits per year.
Should you crush and survive
you will never fly again.
I hope I make
myself clear.
One of this?
Over supplies. The ships inventory
had a few errors.
Is this legal?
Probably not.
Do you think our riches
should be just used for charity?
It's a... deepspace concetrates
It's should last about
6 months...
Federation property is not
to be used for library...
- No, captain.
- Anyway...
I got promoted, Flight lieutenant,
it will repay.
- Oh, yeah?
- Yes, no more misery.
Why did you join the Federation?
I want to fly.
You wanna fly?
Yes, Captain.
Fear, anger, glow fat
becomes a punishment.
The storm cloudes would gathering
and a new order would soon arise.
We found something on Gauda Prime.
DNA storage,
200.000 years old.
Do you really believe we are decendents
from this horrible,horrible
creatures?
The masters?
Yes, the masters.
All the way to Gauda Prime
to prove your link to the gods!
I am a fucking god!
Of course you are, darling.
You are the king.
There is more.
It's a former DNA storage.
It has been abandoned.
Our history go back all the way.
I'll miss you when your gone.
I will.
Terranostra.
The dark medic nemesis of the Federation.
Ruled by the paleo religious high pope.
That all love to hate.
You could foresee
the cancer that was growing
within their rankings.
The new weapon of Tera from the despeakables
overseer end this evil Federation.
This is the prototype of the Star One class:
fastest, most viol dreadnought
in the Federation fleet.
Breaming with thousands of
the "holy anol" flee-meaning"* resources.
Each missile is capable of distinguishing life
on any "awound" 9 worlds.
I,the high pope of Teranostra...
- It's time.
declares a Holy war against
the Federation and the
so called "peacekeeping".
Stay with us, sister.
We're building an army.
We'll be fine!
Will be ordinary form!
Earth,
a pat of radiation,
battle-scared,
the ghosts of our ancestors
still haunt it's hallowed lands.
General vessel stropping the subway!
Turn around!
Aye, captain!
All hands prepare for battle, shields at max!
No-no-no, not now!
Weapons control, charge batteries, target engines...
Weapons charge, giving a lock, captain!
What?
Fire!
2 max coming around, captain!
Captain, i recommended not engaging,
electroshields are not balanced!
Take them balanced!
Shields are gone, captain!
Already?
- If we gone with the shields
I recommended we wouldn't be in this position, captain.
- 2 more vessel!
- Taken away ...
Pilot, 28 thousand kilometers are come about.
Hold ranged communications are down!
By the missiles armed!
Just a minute!
"Clamber disarmed"...
I am in around!
Torgus, six seven deathful two eight by seven niner...
Aye, captain! Seven niner!
Fire!
No-no...
Well done!
You fucking deserved it!
Thanks.
We need to talk later.
About us?
So, is about us...
Us and the Federation.
Leave us!
How many holy men have you killed?
Sixteen.
All good servants in my kingdom.
I want you to do how-to game from the suprising.
Justice...
Remove you rope...
Fuck you!
Very well,
suffer in the violence!
Your execution will be your suffer.
We will rise!
Fucking rebellious cunt!
There is another fighter pilot onboard.
You would be in the brig.
Yes, captain! Lesson learned, captain!
Remember everyone,
you are mortal and
the service of the suffering...
You all vital part of the machine
known as the great Federation.
If one of us falters, we all falter.
Our first mission as prove Starship One
is to visit old Earth.
Stupid name for a planet.
Grace, shield!
New fusion shields activated.
Push on.
No.
All existing warboats ought to be
drafted into the Federation core.
One hundred percent taxation
we become slaves to the Federation.
And you say of this
with super weapons aiming us...
We manager little disagreement up there.
Your weapon has no shields, no communication...
Hey, sunshine, you don't realise that they will shoot upon this planet where we are still on it's surface.
Long range communications back online.
Get those jack-asses back up here.
Yes, sir.
Patch me and the general Gustav.
I thought we were going after the Teranostra.
Do you really want to question me, general?
I know, but we should have a definitely...
Yes, appoint mother, all "dirty steep it" so much history that...
Following orders, supreme commander.
Good.
Dismissed.
You either place youself under Federation rule,
- or we...
- ... and drink your artificial fruit juices all list of mind control and signes.
We gotta go. I am sorry.
Tell that civilian engineer that his life
is forfeit if he can not muchly to shields.
Yes, captain.
Landing team done.
We heading come about, ten thousands km's safe distance.
Arm "climaty two"!
I am not liking this job.
You two, on the bridge! Now!
Yeah, we know, we know.
Where are you go?
Missile bay. Now get out of my way, fucking grant...
- Hey!
- Fuck you, "joel-ball"!
Ask...
After you...
I've been an direct council
with the supreme commander,
Older assist to be a vaporized
under the charge of the
conspiring with a Teranostra
to supply them with class four warboats.
Do you understand the orders, captain?
Understood, general.
You negotiations failed.
They've launched two gunships.
Rimmer, Rimmer!
"Climaty two", primed in ready.
Target.
Earth.
Should we should do that (?)*
Question me again, private Torgus!
Yes, captain!
Having trouble walking...
Well, get locked on!
"Motherfucker" (What the fuck?)
... that order!
Pull ..., Marta!
... back, Worthy!
This a fucking mutny?
Vessels approaching!
(...) Defence cannons are online.
Fire!
Fucking ...bitch!
Let's bring this bird down...
Starship "when a" high command, we are engage an a mutny suspect there Teranostra. (óä.)
We are not Teranostra!
Try go will around athmosphere the guns will be evacuate.
That's a stupid idea.
Do it. (óä.)
I fly .... shoot.
I got one.
Stay focused.
Don't shoot, don't shoot!
Rimmers gone!
I am with you.
Hope i am on the right side.
Get back to engineering.
Going down.
- Marta(???), get a cross-recall try to maneuvering trusters... (?)
- I got Worthy.
- Non option!
- Drayson, what can you tell me?
We gonna crash!
Escape pods!
- "Upon a one scape pod left!"
- That's it.
- We a prototype.
The gas intake.
If we "bind" the gas through the engine intaken ... to slow ...
... blow a ship.
Not to speed the window blow from the intake.
Do it. Torgus, assist.
Could flanger mutny i love better.
...
... back to the freeze.
Drayson.
- It's working!
- It's not working!
... on top, "brace rempact".
You fucking idiots!
I killed captain Savage.
She didn't deserve to die like a dog.
Without warning,
without a moment to reflect...
She was a great starship captain.
You ought to motivate people to war.
Give them a reason to fight.
Fee the manger.
Please no to order recieve, supreme commander, we need a compromation convoy.
Alpha three nine nine three tau.
Confirmed.
Shall never fly again.
Oh, she is at stay baby; shall fly.
After of he repair himself.
... build to better ship.
Those you Federation tax dollars hard of work.
It's batteries.
All Federation diplomats have been executed what is known as a Teranostra day of ...
It is estimated that at least ... women have been executed in an underground network.
The denied by the government civil war has erupted in the streets.
It is expected the Teranostra high council will make a formal declaration of war against the Federation
in the coming hours. The question is
where is the overseer and why is the government silent?
Missioneries, i needed now to bring repentance upon the population.
And well they have declared war
we have the first victory
with the Teranostra ground army.
Calisto two has fallen.
Missioneries, i needed now to bring repentance upon the population.
Follow ...
Set in retimers.
- I've... press release.
- How soon?
- Soon.
Now.
...
Why didn't you agreet me at the docking bay?
What is that?
Calisto two.
Oh, my God!
Your son!
And so many others.
I am truly sorry.
Teranostra agents of mutny at starship one.
Yes,
that's why i am here, general.
Courage ladies!
I never expected this.
We have word that the starship one has fallen in to revollianse.
Teranostra?
We don't know.
... contact two dollars.
You give us a name?
Which one of you is T'Bor?
She was be... yesterday.
We have five hundred and twenty eight legions ready for action and there is noone to lead them.
You know what Worthy ... missiles ... admire ... best starship.
No, we can allow missiles one of the blackmarket.
What a level the plane fill thing?
Level thing...
You ok?
Yeah, i just needed took my ...
You own them?
I got upgraded last week.
...
Where is your captain?
She is dead.
This is lieutenant Worthy.
Your vessel ... from the Federation.
No need your help then.
Enter.
See, this was oont me when i was fifteen.
First three years of life i didn't want him,
but i could to love him in such pheeze devotion,
that i can hotly breath ... separation.
Your sons life will be ... painful.
There will be no "clamansy".
Avenge the death.
We do this under one condition.
Ok.
You joining uprising.
What uprising?
I need to show you something.
Mam!
- No, we can't trust these guys!
- Jolli!
Come.
Sol butts, general infantry, special weapons all class four.
So, must appears you right.
Great.
Federation has a mass two million hundred butts...
- Class two's.
- ... ever ... more world in the sector.
They looking for something.
We afraid that...
You people nothing but war monkers.
Young man, i appreciate your idealism,
but the web is far more complex then you ...
Just you side do you want?
Neither the Teranostra or the Federation.
... the same is you.
Just...
fucking undifferent routes.
You have your finger on the trigger of the Federation "squidest" weapon.
And you appear to have ...
Want you to have this.
.............
............
We need young leaders to take control of ...
... up you ready.
The situation is ready for you.
I killed the superior officer.
I stolen a most powerful starship in the fleet.
My name is Trouble.
... good company.
The Federation fleets been dispatched ... nineteen hours away.
How do you know rude boy?
Follow the holonews.
Mam, mam, mam, no!
It's hot... I am ok!
... John ...
Get out, now!
I am so tire of all this. Why don't he just...
Look,
just get out of there, the fat cops are coming for you.
just go!
The people fighting against the Federation garrison, we "bottom" on this shuttle.
I love you John, but...
Yeah,
love you too.
Number three bring down ... "guys" crane.
... cv?
...
Yeah.
I want your class "phorus".
What?
I downloaded all the Federations atack protocols. We can store them here.
No, we can.
I say...
...
... anything but to get back on a small as* flying pillbox.
Get back to work.
Ok.
Hey, you not suppose to be here.
We need to secure channels an old Earth.
... are ready by now?
I've got you back ... space travel.
... bring us together.
You want to be revolutionary soldier boy? Get on the bike.
Who said anything about revolution?
I am built for hand-to-hand combat.
Really?
And that's it.
Ah, great!
Don't be the big hero, Worthy.
"Heroes always end up is were kill".
Thanks.
... together well.
I want you to take my daughter with you.
No.
She would be your greatest asset,
that she has been in my life.
She need to start living own life.
I am not...
You a small heavily armed moving target to Earth a huge stationary target.
She is better with you.
You doing good kid.
Do you know what you doing?
I am figuring out does it go...
Drives online.
What about my stuff, captain?
What's in the bag?
Things me going to need.
Hair products...
... oils (sattelites*)...
My antique gun collection buttwar.
.....
Fucking women.
Com systems online.
I am locked out.
Really?
I want it to see who mutny the ship?
Identified.
Navigation officer admiral Torgus.
Flight Lieutenant John Worthy.
Contract engineer
Travis Drayson.
Screen off.
I am locked out.
Teranostra agents,
our wars with your government, not with you.
Surrender now and you will not be executed
under the laws of Federation and it's policies.
We in a hole lot ... do.
Well, i have disable the command protocol for the entire starship.
Can you do one of those...
citizens broadcast things?
Give me some time i can hack in.
Do you know how much time ... i bought it to starship one?
I want it under you command in forty eight hours.
... damn it.
If you fail me your son will be executed.
Yes, ...
right!
Charge with usage of a Federation "prame" nuclear "pee" radiation bombs under ... Altern five
execution orders ... as follows John Worthy, Merle Torgus,
Travis Drayson, Staris Arven.
Crime and... of Earth system are...
Parently we've been busy.
What?
Somebody is nuked Altern five.
The Federation are bombing their own planets?
They blaming us.
nuclear "pee" radiation bombs under ... Altern five execution orders ... as follows John Worthy, Merle Torgus, Travis Drayson,
Staris Arven.
Charge with usage...
I just like to say i know not trained
- as the captain...
- Care "suspeech" you not qualified!
Federation fleet closing, captain!
Call me, Worthy!
Drayson, can you check him?
Lines are open.
I am John Worthy,
now in command of staroneclass warship.
People of the Teranostra and the federated worlds,
i demand that the both sides open themselves to "proper" negotiations,
i demand assise fire.
This is coming from the Earth system.
We are the arbiters of peace.
Our clamity-missiles are capable of taking out any world the wishes to continue to wage war.
We need to go there.
No, you stay.
No, i am coming.
You have two hours to respond.
Screen off.
... peacemakers.
To opening fire!
Do we fire back?
We have no shields.
Blast about the sky.
"More" power...
Fire!
Overheat... done.
Suggest we surrender!
Target again?
Turn tail and run.
What?
Pilot,
Drayson, can we call ...
Will to try.
Do it.
Are you serious?
Abort?
Destination?
Torgus, Worthy,
I am sending you a coded navigation link i have a private workshop at the out of west rim.
Want's up private anymore?
I am shielding it's exact location from your sensors.
It's like flying with the blindful.
In a direction where headed i would say it's ... prime.
General,
they sustain damage, we gonna soon their shields were down.
We split the fleet to follow.
To where?
Out west rim or maybe ... prime a Pol Maris.
Never heard of them.
That's way they headed.
Are you sure?
The darkness is closing.
Father,
i did what is right
and i was wrong.
What have i done?
Father!
Speak to me.
Speak!
Hit me!
No.
I thought you overseer prepayed
family members your mother personal dealings.
What the overseer doesn't see caught affect the overseer.
Besides,
besides...
who sent is was personal.
Hello, Master,
...
Forgives from the high office.
You are virgins, yes?
Yeah.
A virgins.
You know how to fly?
No.
I am Roartek.
Code 3-7-1-9-9-2.
Accepted.
Glad you safe.
View biomech.
My pleasure.
I can smell your machine oil.
I think you can trust her.
Do you have a female biomech?
It is a legal for me to create an entity that is more intelligent or powerful then myself.
But it does have it's advantages.
I am not prone to emotional violence or petty jealousies.
You don't like fly?
Making conversation.
I wanna tell you i can "spiriosy" theory about the high pope.
Seriously?
It's a really good one.
Ok.
... look on along way.
The air ... using. Are there any intelligence imitations?
I prefer not to discuss it.
We somewhere on a Pol Maris system, aren't we?
... large asteroids?
Nobody move!
General Gustav if you can ...
- 12 mm high power semiautomatic pistol.
- No.
Staris!
I am fulfilling my wealth to the Federation.
You fucking traitor!
Send her back to Terminus.
Nasty fucker.
Fuck you
and your pathetic band of terrorists.
Find her ... in a left tank compartment.
Goodbye.
Fairy good.
I need your opinion.
Yeah, it's one of our's.
Protocols been modified.
I found them ... around here few weeks ago.
Can i keep it?
I have two more.
... we can nervous.
What is that?
Nothing to concern your ...
I've never done a landing before.
You are nervous, are you?
I sure am.
Worse pilot i've ever seen.
I know what you can to say i am on it.
Whose orders are you ...
The general kindly gave up his codes for me.
I remember when you were baby i looked at on you you've been quite ... most ...
I could read you, your eyes revealed you sold me.
You can not hide anything from me.
As soon as you done return.
Understood.
My mechanical man of ... will be you looking for.
... confusion keep them all occupied for the petty wars.
Soon it will be ...
As soon as you start ... your hands return to Terminus.
I surprise you want peace after that landing.
This is Diana, i am Terina, hi.
They all ready for you.
Yeah, girls you can kick up your feet the bus is in the city i am business.
Sorta..
... has completed a scan.
The DNA is in this sector.
Be sure nothing is disturbed.
What is ... should remain that way.
Yes overseer, we understand.
Will my DNA control a work...
... test ...
Is ... evidence where they are.
Did they stay?
Maybe they just moved to another planet.
I've giving orders ... things ... to remain as they are.
Nothing ...
... very carefully.
Federation ... on those ridiculous electroshields.
... shields ...
...
Fuck you.
Set course for Earth.
We have an army ...
....
Videoencription is high.
Must be a secure ... keeping.
We know that ... for some DNA-decoder.
Should be easy enough.
... more complex ... simple ...
It's a twelve ... bytes.
I am going to create ... tracer.
... back to the source and we can see what they looking for.
Sounds like we arrived.
...
Total distruction every major city radiation bombs.
No.
I am sorry.
We and entire army in amounts waiting to be activated.
John Worthy?
You know me?
... galaxy knows you.
Yeah.
Diana is in charge of five hundred and twenty eight legions on Teranostra.
We taking charge of the warboats ... and paid for by the uprising.
I see.
... Federation ... Teranostra.
Where the hell you've been?
He is on Earth.
Why ... met ... intercept?
I know i have a plan relax.
Really, you have a plan?
I've a special ...
I am sick of fucking plans i need resolves.
Czarina, calm down everything is under control.
Don't touch me or i will have you shot.
Do you understand, Gustav?
...
You need to trust me.
The rest of fleets
"headed" to intercept.
Jolli?
I don't feel anything.
This is not my home anymore.
Let's make them suffer.
General, carrier* shuttle has arrived.
Good, you know what to do.
How many?
Thirty ships maybe more.
Arm the missile.
Incoming message.
Did he see the answer it?
Oh, no, i just figure ...
General,
Flight lieutenant,
It's captain.
Bring them over.
What the hell you ...
Your mother and sister will die.
One by one unless you surrender the starship.
Surrender there is no more time for discussion.
Nice work, general.
How do you do the exchange?
Surrender and your family will be released.
And you will be take into ...
My conditions ...
Fuck you.
No.
Back to ...
How does it feel Teranostra scum?
How does it feel?
Cygnus alpha neutral zone.
Need there for the exchange.
One ship only.
Any games and we start blasting every Federation world we come across.
We are in neutral zone.
Jolli says that ah... Cygnus alpha.
So...
one ... electrical conductor.
Parently we use plasma guns ...
it's bad news.
She wants to try
use her antique weapons.
...
try the old bang-bang.
No.
You stay with the ship.
If we need you.
John,
look i am
sorry.
You know...
Don't.
...
My grandmother
was gun down my friendlyfire ...
We all
hope ...
I must to say goodbye ...
She never woke up.
Not now, Torgus.
Please.
I know.
"You can a hold all in".
...
And then boom.
You ... explode.
... gonna be the only one taken down by it.
..
Really.
... all with you.
... our lifes ... personal vendetta.
I know, i know.
It's ok.
She is dead.
It is my fault.
I was to busy you playing the hero.
To really care about those ...
...
General Gustav
is playing you.
Yes.
But i know
that i gotta focus
i gotta focus.
Yeah, you do.
... die out here.
It's cold.
...
Promise.
Right.
We have "one of" guns we want be needing your knife collection.
Guns are the weapons of cowards.
Will see.
Make sure ... safety protocols turned off.
... gunstock.
The DNA codes* ...
Tiberius,
you have been a good friend,
but i don't trust you.
Rise up.
Tiberius,
Yes, overseer.
Throw yourself of the ridge.
Good.
Told you it works.
...
I can believe
... on this fuck ... planet.
A legions are ready just give the word.
The word is given.
Each of you will take a platoon and ... own church sector.
A twenty three hundred hours we strike.
Stay away from the front lines that is the territory of the "class 4-th".
We fight along side you until every last Teranostra male is dead.
Worthy sending a trap.
Where is starship?
Could be right on Earth ...
I don't like this.
We use this planet for testing ... warboats.
...
I see them.
Come on ...
Get ready the sidekick.
...
I am ashamed we served under the same flag,
teranostra scum.
I am not Teranostra.
Course you are!
Nice distruction.
...
Hold your fire, hold your fire!
Starship!
Don't move a muscle.
- Starship!
- Don't do it, don't do it!
Motherfucker!
Come on Worthy, take ...
... die Gustav!
...
I am gonna hunt you!
I am gonna kill you!
Get off, Jolli!
Never should i've doning like that.
... with the set up ...
Hold on, hold on.
...
Pick up needed at meeting point.
Dammit!*
... motherfuckers!
... men.
Oh, fuck, it's a home guard.
...
Anya, ... to the west activated ... cells.
Go, go, go ...
- I don't like this.
- Get ...
Higher.
You need help?
Yeah, i do.
Ten battle cruisers incoming.
... stop the getting weapons lock.
Like this?
... you fry the system.
General, we have twenty frigates, twelve bombers, two gravimets*,
and one bio weapons cruiser.
... bombardment ... clear.
General, we can get luff on this distance.
... circle in ...
Yes, sir.
Circle in, fire at will.
... super luminal.
Not at this altitude!
We heading for the 'aida' storm!
Perfect!
Are you mad?
Yes i am.
Fight with the ... don't fight the wind.
Bad idea.
Trust me.
... do this on a top fighter not under 'stormship'.
... kpsi.
Stay with him he is emotional will make mistakes.
Yes, general.
Too fast!
Quit the storm!
You are fool Worthy, this is not ...
Open fire!
Feel you ...
We gonna blow!
Faster!
No!
We can do it.
Pulling up twenty degrees.
Losing level trusters.
All right, all right!
Pull out!
... out here, pilot!
Dammit!
When we ... twenty eight thousand pull up.
... to reach escape velocity.
Really, it's a stupid idea.
It's working!
- ...
- ... congratulations ...
...
Bring it on.
We all be going super luminal any time soon.
What are they?
Artificial grumpy field generators relock to the fucking gravity key.
... in the palace! Focus on the home guard.
Do not ...
Let's go.
Ok, ok, ok.
Drayson, what's the heat waiting after shields.
Seven thousand degrees Kelvin.
And the Federation ships?
Maybe three thousand but the command ship is six.
What's a hit range of a 'clamity'-missile.
Got it, i know ...
What is it?
Six to fifteen thousand.
If we ride on a very ...
Correct.
No, will die.
Do it.
Yes, captain.
Coming about
on a missile.
Already arm.
Launch.
- ...
- I don't know.
How long?
Thirty seconds.
...
Circle around ... first blastwave ... between them.
Shockwave.
Only shit.
...
Nice knowing you.
Drayson, cut the power.
...
I need more warboats running distruction at the east gate.
So, Diana ... her team inside.
... years.
Feeling old?
Somedays.
Right.
Manual restart.
Ok ... ah ...
super luminal offline,
maneuvering trusters are gone,
weapons are offline.
Well, the good news ... still works.
So, basically ... drift.
Could be worse.
Really.
Captain.
Keep moving.
Section eight to the west wing.
Section seven!
Diana,
your wing coming. Get out!
Get out!
...
They sustain a lot a damage.
Guns.
Deck three and four... question ... order abandon ship.
Denied.
Reactor the critical.
Keep fire.
Our fat.
Keep moving.
Left corridor.
...
- Where is fucking probe?
- ... off world.
Of course, yes.
Drayson,
any ... would be good.
Rerounding lifesupport.
Trusters online.
Run x-speed.
You gotta be fucking kidding me.
...
Fuck.
Where the lights?
Give me the lights.
...
Got it.
- ...
- Where?
Where?
Where the 'breeders'?
...
Here.
Oh my god!
Drayson!
No, no, no ...
We don't have time.
... Jolli.
It's my fault, no, no ...
no ...
We gotta go, we gotta go now!
Torgus, Torgus come on!
Torgus,
i need you to ... 'clamity-missile' ... fifteen minuts.
Just do it.
The fucking light.
We can all ... in jet fighter i've got other ship to 'steel' and escape pod.
Hey, you said fifteen minuts, right?
...
Keep this safe.
... we get a "clamity-missile" here ...
Hey, come on guys ...
...
Go-go, come on.
Go.
Come on, let's move, let's move!
The fleet ... coming in ... he's not gonna make it.
He's got five minuts.
We need to get hell out of here.
Abandon ship, lifesupport systems have failed.
- Hey ...
- Where is general Gustav?
Far they.
I ... ah ...
You want kill me?
...
He's headed to 'exit' of the escape path level two.
Get out of ship ...
Go!
Go in.
I 'send' a 'transponder' to priority you will be the first i 'gets picked up'.
Wait, Gustav!
- Wait!
- I have recordings of the everything on my ship.
Everything.
Gustav, ... ah .. i never ... you to die.
Never!
Reactor is critical.
Warn ... reactor is critical.
Where is pilot?
Tera's scum!
I never betraying black arches.
... you religious fanatics!
I've killed million to the name of your god!
My son is dead!
Because of you people!
'i know'... fucking teranostra.
I gonna make you suffer!
... my family ... blood.
... make you be angry.
Your family?
Your family ...
U ...
My family still alive.
Someone try to warn you ... i didn't get ...
My family ...
...
Why?
Federation, everybody,
your world.
You 'shot'.
Federation rescue ships.
because you ...
We have John Worthy in Cassidy set course for Terminus.
Roger that, sweeping more survivers.
... executor for sure.
believe.
I have patrol.
'linecer' open.
The galaxy is listening.
Confess.
Do it.
I am Detritus,
bishop of the Teranostra.
... have wife and children.
We have
surrender what is left for military
to
resistance.
Say it.
A high pope of the Teranostra
and the sovereign Federation overseer
are one and the same person.
Teranostra has fallen.
Citizens of a federating worlds, you are fighting each other for no reason.
A high pope of the Teranostra
and the Federation sovereign overseer
are one and the same person.
...
It's just politics.
How do we rescue Worthy?
He'll be is here by morning, all right?
... to Terminus ...
Let's get away from here.
Overseer, we have the ... generator activated.
'Partical' delivery tanks 'are full of primed'.
Delivery system stand by.
Work to get so long.
We have problems ... alien DNA to the delivery modifiers.
The DNA-'clo' will be capable ... all planetary world suitable.
.. boats are ... when we primed and ready.
Good.
... been going on, i've been waiting you several hours.
Come here and sit down Seethus.
I ado you, but you have to listen and listen well.
The overseer is on his wayback right now and we have to act we have to do smth. right now.
Does he found what he's looking for?
Oh, Seethus.
Have you ever
suspected anything?
The overseer is my half-brother.
When i was fifteen he had his way with me.
He doesn't remember it because he was elevated been 'joceling' stupid he don't remembering thing.
But i was young and i told him that it was a teranostra
ambassador would actually raped me.
But he did not forgive.
And he can never ever know
because this is all my fault.
Listen to me.
Thrown of the sovereign overseer is ... yours.
It's yours.
You raped me.
He is my father.
... enemy ...
My mother and sister are alive.
The general was a smart but just man. He played me like a deck of cards.
But now i see the overseer and it's family and the true enemies.
We must forgive each other
an ourselves, an all our sins and focus 'i hatred' on those who deserve it.
The overseer must die.
A high pope of the Teranostra and
the Federation sovereign overseer
are one and the same person.
It's true?
I am sure your mother knows.
How bombings in Kalisto, too?
I hope you are
giving orders.
I see.
Keep me informed.
So you here to carry out the execution order?
It seems you're right.
- Yes
I am getting you out of here.
We have a war to fight,
friend.
The teranostra fallen.
And a Federation not far behind.
Valley that I use.
Will be my curse.
And also there is hope.
Love gone's way
the humans shall play.
Prepared by art-studio indb@outlook.com using multitran dictionary and google.translate-instruments.
Watch Movies, TV Series and Live Sports
Signup Here -> WWW.ADMITME.APP