Scorpion-class pulse warriors.
Kamikaze bombardiers.
Every day,
new Bugs show up on the battlefield.
Watch out! Get down, get down!
So many that some wonder:
GIQ on one.
Don't bet on it, citizen.
Here at Oppenheimer
Proving Grounds...
... federal scientists are cooking up
some nasty top-secret surprises...
... of their own.
But the newest weapon
in the Mobile Infantry's arsenal...
... is the not-so-secret shovel.
Greater Bug firepower
means trenches.
And that means digging
here on Roku San...
... this once peaceful farm planet...
... that has become the new frontline
of the Second Bug War.
There you go, trooper.
And put your back into it.
If you're against the war,
you're against us.
That's what a federal judge
said today...
... when he declared that hanging
is absolutely good enough...
... for anyone who threatens
the morale of the Federation.
- and death. Execute them all.
This is a very simple ruling.
People need to watch what they say.
Admiral Enolo Phid,
division chief, Fleet Intelligence...
... voiced another concern from her
headquarters at Terran Command.
The revival of religious worship here
and in the outer colonies...
...will not be tolerated
if it leads to sedition...
...or in any other way
destabilizes our war effort.
He's dark, he's handsome,
he's psychic.
Courage, duty, honor
Eagle high above
He's General Omar Anoke,
the sky marshal everyone loves.
And gives us strength
To go and win this war
And at last night's war rally...
... he thrilled audiences
all across the Federation...
... with a pounding rendition
of his latest hit, "A Good Day to Die."
We fight for what is right
A noble sacrifice
When duty calls, you pay the price
For the Federation
I will give my life
And hey, citizen, now you can
celebrate Sky Marshal Anoke...
... and support our war effort
at the same time.
Because it's always
a good day to buy.
- I will give my life
- Courage, duty, honor
For the Federation
I will give my life
Incoming!
- Clear out!
- Run!
Move, move, move!
Can you walk, soldier?
- Yes, sir.
- Good.
Give us a hand. Pick up that arm
and find out who it belongs to.
Yes, sir.
Mop up, people.
We got brass up our ass in T-minus-2.
Surprise inspection, sir? Tonight?
The SM can drop in and count
the sheets any time he wants.
The sky marshal's coming here?
Ask him for an autograph, Lieutenant
Manion, and I will have you shot.
No, sir. Of course not, sir.
- Officer on deck.
- Carry on.
Status?
- Archie's testing the fence again, sir.
- Stupid Bugs.
Pesky, not stupid, lieutenant.
Keep it up, Archie.
I like my Bugs fried in the morning.
Boat coming down, colonel.
Look sharp, troopers.
Sir, the sky marshal is the
Federation's top-secret top secret.
So how'd you know
he was coming?
Anoke's chief of staff
used to polish my brass.
You know General Hauzer?
Dix Hauzer was a dope lieutenant
just like you once upon a time.
Made general in two years.
Some dope.
Only took me eight years
to make colonel.
Officer on deck.
- John Rico.
- Good to see you, Dix.
- How's it going?
- Good.
I have to introduce you to someone.
I think I'm in love.
Yeah? Who'd have you?
Here he comes, everybody.
Let's go, come on.
Officer on deck.
Sorry to drop in unannounced,
colonel.
And yet I sense you expect my visit.
Get in tight on this, sergeant.
Johnny Rico, our hero of Planet P.
I just did my part, sir.
Oh, no.
Heroes inspire courage, sacrifice.
- Sacrifice?
- Yes.
By asking us
to be better than what we are.
Tell me about Roku San, colonel.
Will these farmers fight?
They need us,
but they don't like us, sir.
Hearts are more fickle than minds.
Johnny Rico.
Lola Beck?
What are you doing here?
I fly the SM.
He gets the best.
Well, you know me, Johnny.
Yes, I know you.
Captain Beck is the person
I was talking about earlier.
You?
And Lola?
What's the joke?
Captain Beck,
you should have informed me...
...of your relationship
with Colonel Rico.
You know what I do out of uniform
is off the clock, general.
You three obviously
have much to discuss.
Buy them both
a drink on me, colonel.
Yes, sir.
- Lieutenant Manion, isn't it?
- Yes, sir.
- Care to give me the post tour?
- Me?
I have all your songs, sir.
- Carry on, lieutenant.
- Yes, sir.
Follow me, sir.
Come on, kids. We got orders.
You boys are the biggest girls
I've ever known.
What do you think of them?
Bugs? I hate them, sir.
Well, no one likes
what they can't understand.
But just look at the imagination.
The sheer virtuosity
of their creation.
I hate to bother you, sir, but
could you please sign my helmet?
Of course, trooper.
- Thank you, sir.
- Anytime, son.
All I know is...
...there sure are a lot more of them
at the wire today, sir.
A lot more.
Well, maybe they heard
I was going to sing.
- Officer on deck.
- Look sharp.
At ease.
Gentlemen.
You got me confused
with someone who isn't a farmer.
- How do I get me a hat like that?
- Join up, do your part.
Farmers.
- I'd like to ask you something.
- Sorry, chief.
Already married.
Buy them a drink on me, will you?
And bring us a bottle.
Hose your cage, Harlan.
These are the kind of people
who will lose this war for us.
Why is it no one in the outer colonies
wants to fight?
Roku San used to be a nice place.
Now it's war, and they blame us.
Archie's cooking tonight.
- Oh, yeah.
- Yeah.
- What are they thinking?
- Archie don't think.
It's a good day to fry.
- Ten-hut.
- At ease, troopers.
Fascinating.
They seem so excited tonight.
You ought to hear them, sir.
They're howling out there.
Well, put them on the line, soldier.
What does it mean, sir?
It means we're being tested,
lieutenant.
Our loyalty, our intelligence...
...our imagination.
Excuse me, sir.
My brother really loves you.
- Of course. What's his name?
- Kevin.
- I'm sure he'll make a fine recruit.
- Thank you.
- May I, sir?
- Of course you can, trooper.
Ask him for an autograph, Lieutenant
Manion, and I will have you shot.
Hey, where'd he go?
To us.
To John, hero of Planet P.
Lola, two ships
shot out from under you.
I fly a goddamn desk.
The battles I fight are with numbers.
That's what I do.
That's what I know.
And that's why I know...
...that if everyone in here
doesn't step up, we're sunk.
- To the Federation.
- The Federation.
"To the Federation."
So, Dix.
Rico and I met...
...when Johnny was a big war hero
and I was still a six.
Bond tour. Ten planets, eight days.
Do you remember Turtle Bay?
So, Dix, how do you know Johnny?
Well, he used to be my boss
at TCOM.
Standard rotation.
Worst year of my life.
Dix saved my ass every day.
Hey, it's hanging time.
Appeals are exhausted.
Their families have said goodbye.
All that remains is payment
for their crimes against you, citizen.
The senior executive executioner
is taking his time.
Sending a message, perhaps.
One for all of us to contemplate
this evening.
That our ideas,
no matter how pleasing...
... are dangerous.
That there are actions
and consequences.
That no one really counts
very much...
... unless we are part
of something bigger.
There it is, justice.
You'll pay.
As God is my witness, you'll pay.
- Back off.
- Hold on, hold on, wait, wait.
Hey, fuck off, feddy.
You guys fail to understand
a very clear lesson here.
You got something to learn me?
- Come on, Dix, let's get out of here.
- Colonel Rico, if you please.
Yes, sir.
MPs, now. I want them arrested.
Everyone. That's an order.
Yes, sir. Sergeant.
You heard the general.
My friends,
you're not bigger than the Federation.
Watch what you say
and do what you're told.
- Or you'll have us hung, is that it?
- It's up to you.
Come on, Dix.
Let's get Lola out of here.
I don't work for you anymore, John.
Stand down.
Did you hear that, everybody?
Stand down. That's an order.
From now on, I take my own lumps.
I got this.
Now you're in violation of Article 5.
Article 8.
- Had enough?
- Stand down, Rico.
Stand down.
That's Article 11.
That's 11.
Which makes you subject to...
- Special Order 86.
- Look out!
Colonel Rico, you're out of order.
Begging the general's pardon, sir.
I was trying to keep an old friend
from making an ass of himself.
Friendship means nothing
next to duty, colonel.
And you have forgotten yours.
I thought we were here
to kill Bugs, sir.
Not farmers.
Arrest the farmers. Sedition.
- And Colonel Rico too.
- All right, on your feet, asshole.
- Failure to obey a superior officer.
- Hey, Dix, stop it.
Johnny's right.
Move it!
Captain Beck.
Return to your boat.
Sergeant, you have your orders.
Colonel, please come with me.
Electrical system malfunction.
Oh, no.
Here they come,
they're on the wall.
- Rico.
- It's all down. Everything.
The fence is down, sir.
- The fence?
- How could that have happened?
Fuck, here they come.
Oh, shit.
We need reinforcements.
We need reinforcements now, sir!
- I'm on my way.
- Hold on. You are under arrest.
- Is that your final word?
- No, that's an order.
I'll see you at my court-martial.
- Nice seeing you, Lola.
- Yeah.
Make a hole, coming through.
Heads up, colonel.
Keep it moving. Keep it moving.
Come on, you apes.
You wanna live forever?
Move it. Come on.
Keep it moving.
Fall back.
Defensive positions. Incoming.
Let's go.
Go. Go.
Out of ammo, man. Out of ammo.
No!
- Bugs!
- Two lines! Front and back!
Fire!
Grenades!
Forward!
Colonel Rico, sir.
- Situation, lieutenant.
- Totally ominously fucked up, sir.
And I lost the sky marshal too, sir.
Good. We'll all hang together.
You know what to do.
Get in there and kill them all!
- Where's forward command?
- It's Bugs.
It's Bugs.
Bugs everywhere you go, sir.
Sir, what are you doing here?
Are you wounded? We have
to get you to the lander right now.
I'm fine.
Marines, gather around. We must get
the sky marshal to safety right now.
Yes, sir. Formation.
This way, general.
Archie.
Clear.
Keep moving.
Archie. Get that paddock open.
This is General Hauzer.
Open this door.
Open the door.
Sir.
Get this door closed!
Dr. Wiggs, over here.
Dr. Wiggs, we need you.
Get him inside.
- Corpsman, see to Sergeant Rye.
- Yes, sir.
Fucking Bugs. I hate them!
Dr. Wiggs. Front and center.
- What's wrong with him?
- Careful.
He's in shock. Are you all right, sir?
Are you all right, sir?
Sir?
- I will be.
- Oh, good.
Here we go. Careful.
Captain Beck, when do we leave?
How about T-minus-now, sir?
Sir, requesting permission
to remain on Roku San, sir.
- Trying to be a hero, Dix?
- Somebody's gotta stay and fight.
Sir.
Colonel Rico is in command.
I was forced to relieve Colonel Rico.
He's under arrest
for acts of insubordination.
Serious charges.
I'm sorry for your friend.
Perhaps your destiny
does lay here after all, Dix.
Go find it.
And good luck, soldier.
Wait.
Just think about this for a second.
Because you're making a decision
for the both of us right now.
I know.
Dix, I love you.
I love you.
Blast off, Fleet.
Attention, all units.
This is General Hauzer.
I am assuming command
effective immediately.
Go to the bunker!
Repeat, I'm assuming command.
All unit commanders report.
I want location and status. Now.
We lost G Trench, sir.
Put that in a memo to
General Hauzer, will you, lieutenant?
Yes, sir.
This is Hauzer to all units.
I say again, I'm assuming command.
They're pulling back, sir.
- Get down!
- Hit the deck!
Clear the deck.
Skinner, Hightower, cover that hole.
Prepare for attack!
Bombardier!
Scorp! It's a scorp!
Scorpion.
Scorpion! Oh, fuck! Scorpion!
Fire, fire, fire!
Grenades!
Take us home, Captain Beck.
Warp in five, number one.
Yes, ma'am.
What about General Hauzer, ma'am?
He wants combat.
Take us out on my mark.
Five, four, three, two, one.
The guy says, "Man,
then we can all get some sleep."
Fucking Archie.
Can't believe I got bitten.
Yeah, he got you.
Officer on deck.
At ease.
Nice work out there, sergeant.
Thank you, ma'am. SM all okay?
Thanks to you boys.
What do we say, marines?
- Yeah.
- Carry on.
Oh, boy.
Chief Brittles, are we shipshape?
You'd be the first to know, captain.
Just saying hi, Bull.
Excuse me, ma'am.
If that's the SM's dinner,
after you, Holly.
Thank you, ma'am.
What's cooking, Jingo?
You know,
the same old shit on a shingle.
- Drink, captain?
- On duty, doc.
Me too.
Captain Beck.
Give a listen, will you?
Today we have suffered grave defeat
at Roku San.
But I am confident that there exists
balance in the cosmos and...
Excuse me, sir.
I am certain that there exists balance
in the cosmos.
And where there is defeat,
we will make victory.
What do you think?
I have to address
the council tomorrow.
Well, sir, everybody loves victory.
If you'll excuse me,
I'll be getting back to the cockpit.
Look, look, can't they manage
without you just for once?
Let's stay and talk.
Certainly, sir, I'd be happy to.
Hold on.
We're falling out of warp.
Sir, for your own protection...
...l'm gonna need to get you
to the marine lander.
Holly, stay with us.
- What just hit us?
- I think we just hit each other.
Come on, Holly, let's move.
- Marines, report to the rescue deck.
- I read you, Captain Beck.
And we are on our way.
Let's go.
Come on.
Marines. Right here, brothers.
Let's go.
Was that a reactor, chief?
Secondary. Number one
will turn us into daylight.
I'm okay. I'm okay.
- Abandon ship, chief.
- Yes, ma'am.
Sergeant Rye,
the SM goes with you.
Yes, ma'am. Come with us now, sir.
Captain Beck, I would prefer
that you stay at my side.
Yes, sir. Crew chief,
get everyone else to the rescue pod.
You got it.
- We got a little problem in the galley.
- Jingo, jeez.
Dumb ass.
- You okay?
- Yeah.
Go get the SM, Chick.
Sir, this way.
No! Damn it!
- Marines, get to your lander.
- I will see you on the ground.
Okay, people, let's move.
To the rescue pod, now.
- Are we crashing?
- No, we're getting into the rescue pod.
The Roku San line,
key to the Federation's defense...
... knows defeat in one night.
How many dead? No man can say.
Experts agree on one thing only:
Blame falls squarely
on Colonel John Rico.
Once heralded
as the hero of Planet P.
Now disgraced
and awaiting court-martial...
... from his cell at the Alamo Bay
Federal Detention Facility.
Another day, another peace rally
in the outer colonies.
The Federation
has taken advantage.
But this time it's different,
because of Elmo Goniff.
Hey, I'm a citizen.
Decorated veteran turned pacifist...
... and now the leader
of a growing coalition of citizens...
... who question the Federation's
administration...
... of the Arachnid conflict.
- and counting. Why?
I found my answers in faith.
And I have faith in God, not people.
Peace at any price is a human right.
And there are other costs too.
Defeat at Roku San
has fueled the anti-war movement...
... resulting in the deaths
of 144 outer-colony students...
... and religious protesters.
We break net now to take you live
to Terran Command...
... where Sky Marshal Omar Anoke
will address the Federation...
... on the Roku San crisis.
My fellow citizens, I come
to you today with a heavy heart.
Within the past 12 hours...
... we have suffered
ignominious defeat at Roku San.
Incompetence at the highest levels
of command...
...and betrayal...
...by those who would protest,
question...
...and commit acts
of civil disobedience.
I assure you that those responsible
for the catastrophe at Roku San...
...and all crimes against
the Federation, large and small...
...will be punished.
Ours is a war of human destiny...
...that will end only in total victory.
And we're out.
Okay, let's wrap it up. Good.
So?
What's the matter, general?
You don't look very happy with me.
We all understand
the need to maintain stability...
...until we locate the sky marshal.
I'm surprised to see you.
I thought you'd take some time
to recover from your ordeal.
The sky marshal would want me
in the office, admiral.
Naturally.
Excuse me, sir.
Sorry, sir.
- Lieutenant?
- Lamb.
I know no one's supposed
to talk about it...
...but I'm sorry
about the sky marshal, sir.
That's classified, lieutenant.
Phid will have your head in a noose.
But thanks.
Something else?
A distress call
came out of the AQZ yesterday.
And how are you aware of this
and I'm not?
The transmission came through
on my watch, sir.
Sierra Mike Uniform to Fleet Rescue.
Come in, Fleet.
Sierra Mike Uniform,
this is Fleet Rescue, over.
Requesting priority pickup
for sky marshal plus five.
What happened
when you kicked it upstairs?
We were instructed to ignore it, sir,
and all future transmissions.
And I'm supposed to
keep my mouth shut.
That why you're here, lieutenant?
They're out there all alone
and no one's doing anything about it.
Sir.
You were never here, lieutenant.
No, sir. Never.
Sierra Mike Uniform to Fleet Rescue.
Come in, Fleet.
Fleet Rescue, come in.
They're gonna come and get us,
right, captain?
I mean, like,
how long till they get here?
Here you go, doc.
I say again,
Sierra Mike Uniform to Fleet Rescue.
Come in, Fleet.
Is anyone out there?
I don't think we're getting through.
Jingo, get out of there.
Why? I like it in here. Okay.
The solar cells need recharging.
Don't have time
for a day at the beach.
Bugs!
One or 1000?
Who's to say
there's not an army out there?
- Oh, God.
- I didn't see anything.
Probably a scout.
We need to get off this beach
pronto, people.
Leave the rescue pod?
You want your back to the water
when these Bugs show up?
Be my guest, doc.
Our father, who art in heaven,
hallowed be thy name.
Thy kingdom come.
Thy will be done...
Give it a break.
Easy now, captain.
You ain't sure,
and you're scaring us all to death.
On Earth as it is in heaven.
Give us this day our daily bread
and del...
You are really getting on my nerves.
You've got no cause to do that.
Get your hand off me, crew chief.
You're hurting him.
Everyone's got a right
to think what they want.
Sure, as long as they keep it
to themselves.
Saddle up. We're moving out.
Wait a second. When Fleet Rescue
comes looking for us...
...this is the first place
they're gonna come, right?
I expect they would, Bull.
Then we should stay right here.
And if the Bugs do attack,
we just fall right back to the pod.
Smart thinking, Bull.
You ever been in a swarm,
big man?
Swarm? Oh, my God, no.
They'll tear this pod apart
like a paper bag.
Oh, God, save us.
Now, gear up, we're moving out.
And that's an order.
Our father, who art in heaven,
hallowed be thy name...
- Can the God talk.
- You're wrong, Captain Beck.
God is everywhere, surrounding us.
Excuse me, sir?
All of us search for God
in our own way...
...whether we know it or not.
Do you really believe that, sir?
Yes, Holly, I do.
I had no idea
that you were one of us.
All right. Well, all of you guys
can go look for God.
I'm heading
for the Fleet marine lander.
They've got weapons,
maybe even a com that works.
And it's only
about a hundred klicks away.
Only a hundred klicks away.
We ain't got rations for that.
You're fat. You won't need any.
Let's move, people.
Colonel John Rico,
for incompetence of command...
... assault on a superior officer,
and willful negligence...
... resulting in the deaths of several
soldiers under your command...
... you are sentenced to hang
by the neck until you are dead.
Do you have anything to say
before the sentence is carried out?
Get on with it, will you?
I'll see you in hell.
What the hell is this?
Your lucky day.
Intelligence. Classified.
You talk, and next time
it's your neck in the noose.
Let's go, hero.
You gonna hang me yourself, Dix?
Maybe I got some better things
for you to do.
You come here a lot,
don't you, Dix?
Didn't know you were interested
in political prisoners.
Not me.
I come with the sky marshal.
- Interrogations.
- Anoke likes the personal touch, eh?
Not like you think.
Not human prisoners.
That first Brain, the one
you captured on P, we keep it here.
- It's still alive?
- Alive and a lot bigger.
No one really knows
how long they live.
What's it good for?
Anoke was fascinated by that thing.
Why's my neck suddenly worth more
than a piece of rope?
It's about the future
of the Federation, Johnny.
- And Lola.
- What's that got to do with me?
- You're the only one I can trust.
- Why's that, buddy?
Because everyone thinks
you're dead.
- Captain?
- I see them, Jingo.
I count 16.
Bugs? Where?
- Oh, no.
- Why did they stop?
Let's move.
- Bull.
- What?
- You with me.
- You got it.
They're herding us.
Why? They could have us easy.
Perhaps we find ourselves
under the grace of a higher power.
You really think so, sir?
I know it in my heart, Holly.
Do you really think we're protected
by some higher power?
Singing can't hurt.
Lifts the spirit and helps
pass the time, don't you think?
I think we're not dead
and we should be.
Yeah.
It's big. It's deadly.
And everyone's got an opinion
about the new Q-bomb.
Politicians and citizens alike
worry about the morality of a bomb...
... rumored to be so powerful
it can crack a planet.
Creation of a weapon
that can destroy the very planet...
... on which I now stand is nothing
if not a dangerous precedent...
... for the entire human race.
What people fail to grasp...
... is how many planets
there are in the universe.
And that the universe itself
often destroys other planets.
The Federation can't decide which
planet lives and which planet dies.
The Lord giveth
and the Lord taketh away.
You think those dirty Bugs wouldn't
use a Q-bomb if they had one?
But aren't we supposed to be
better than the Bugs?
You said it, Mom.
That's controversy with a Q.
Yesterday I dropped troopers
into a combat zone.
Today I'm flying
to the outer colonies.
I'm Fleet.
- I'm Fleet too.
- We're Fleet too.
Me? Really?
If you have strong math skills,
high reflex index...
... and an HED of 8. 1 or better,
we need you now.
Sixteen? No problem.
Start training today
for your future, citizen.
People say boys don't give good HED.
But I do.
When you go Fleet,
there's no telling where you'll end up.
You know, when I was young...
...I dreamed
that one day I'd fly a starship...
...or even visit Sanctuary.
Fleet has taken me to the top.
How high you fly is up to you
when you go Fleet.
So why not do your part
and sign up today?
See you in the cockpit.
Would you like to know more?
Well, John.
Your first time at Sanctuary.
- So this is the big wow.
- This is it.
If the Bugs find this place,
they'll knock out the Fleet.
No Fleet, you lose the outer colonies.
Mobile Infantry couldn't hold them.
There goes the neighborhood.
- Next stop, Earth.
- Yeah.
Guess that makes Sanctuary
the biggest secret of the war.
Not even the sky marshal
knows where it is.
Only a handful of active-duty pilots
are entrusted with that information.
Don't tell me.
Lola's one of them.
Yup, and if we don't find her,
we're sunk.
I'm sending you
to the Arachnid Quarantine Zone...
...as soon as you saddle up.
What do we know about this planet?
OM-1? Nothing.
We don't even have
its exact position.
What about the rescue call?
Wasn't there a beacon?
Enolo Phid
doesn't want Anoke rescued.
- I don't get it.
- Phid wants to be Anoke.
I'm glad all I do is fight Bugs.
So I'm gonna get the coordinates
and you go in.
Roger that.
But what makes you so sure
they're still alive?
Well, Lola's hard to kill.
If this mission is off the books...
...how are you gonna get me
a regiment to invade the AQZ?
A regiment? Not even close.
- So how many troopers do I get?
- Seven.
- What?
- That's including you.
You're sending me into
the Bug house with a rifle squad?
Why didn't you just
let them hang me, Dix?
Maybe I should have.
Don't worry,
I'm assembling your team now.
It's my funeral. My pick of the team.
Any way you want it.
They aren't much to look at,
are they?
Well, we didn't build them
to do pretty things.
Hey, doc.
- When did he get the religion?
- I wouldn't call it religion per se.
- He's spiritual.
- That's different.
Yeah, two months ago, I received
a call in the middle of the night.
I hadn't seen him for a week.
He told me he'd been in the desert
and that he'd been tested.
He wasn't himself.
Go on.
Well, every man, even great men...
...experience moments of doubt
when they're tired and afraid.
Afraid of what?
He told me that this was a war
that would never end.
That if we stay this course...
...the Bugs will and must
destroy the human race.
So he's lost his nut.
Extraordinary, 10 out of 10.
He had an episode.
I gave him a sedative.
The next day he told me not to worry,
that he'd talked to God.
Doc, if I told you I was talking to God,
would you clear me for flight?
I...
Is the SM unfit for command?
I find this a very
uncomfortable conversation, captain.
If I need to assume command,
I'm gonna need your help...
...because the others
won't understand.
We could both hang.
Is your loyalty to the SM
or the Federation?
Don't blame the cook, folks.
The SM goes first.
Just water. Bull, you have mine.
Are you sure, sir?
Well, I'm sure
we'll need your strength.
Thank you, sir.
If you don't mind, can we maybe
say a prayer before we eat?
Of course.
Dr. Wiggs?
Captain Beck, how about you?
I'll be checking the perimeter, sir.
We thank thee, Lord,
for the meal we're about to receive.
Please bless us and keep us.
Protect us from all evil
and guide us...
...that we may know the way to you.
Amen.
- Amen.
Can I ask you a question, sir?
Of course, Bull.
They are gonna come looking for us,
won't they, sir?
Because of you.
We are on a mission
of the greatest importance, Bull.
Even if we do not now
understand our purpose.
Yes, sir.
But we are gonna be rescued.
I mean, you do know that,
don't you?
Because you're psychic.
I know how people around me feel,
and sometimes I can speak to them...
...but no one can predict the future,
Bull.
I have a question for you.
For all of you.
Do you have faith?
I believe.
I know you do, Holly.
Your faith is clear and serene.
I wanna believe too, sir.
I really do.
Well, that's the start of it, Bull.
Dr. Wiggs, how about you?
I believe in you, sir.
Well, careful now, Dr. Wiggs.
See, I'm only a man.
Earthquake.
Incoming!
Help me! Bull!
- Jingo, Jingo.
- Hold on.
Hold on, Jingo.
Come on, come on!
Jesus.
Where's Wiggs?
Dr. Wiggs?
Wiggs?
Doc?
Good to see you again, troopers.
You are now all part
of a classified mission.
Talk about it and they will hang you.
Get me?
We get you, sir.
What exactly
is the Marauder program, sir?
- I'm not currently at liberty to say.
- Sir, is the mission survivable, sir?
We'll find out, trooper.
You know what I think, sir?
- What's that, sergeant?
- I think it's a good day to die, sir.
Outstanding.
Glad you feel that way.
Because today, we're headed out
for the Arachnid Quarantine Zone.
- Saddle up, troopers.
- Sir, yes, sir.
Hauzer for Lamb.
I'm sorry, general,
Lieutenant Lamb's been transferred.
Where?
I'm sorry, sir, I can't tell you that.
What?
- Dix, come in.
- You are going to hang Lamb?
Little redhead, sad eyes,
big mouth?
Why?
That is what happens
to traitors, Dix.
Seems like you know
all about traitors, admiral.
Maybe I'm looking at one right now.
So you're gonna hang me too?
Well, a lot of that
going around these days.
What happens to you
when the council finds out...
...you suppressed
the sky marshal's rescue call?
And exactly who would tell them
such a thing?
You give me the coordinates
for Planet OM-1, resign...
...and I keep my mouth shut.
I'm sorry, Dix.
But very shortly,
Omar Anoke will be dead...
...and honored as a hero
of the Federation...
...and I will be
the next sky marshal.
Over my dead body.
That your last request, general?
Federal Council members
were called together today...
... by Sky Marshal Anoke
for his weekly report.
How are you doing, sir?
Good to see you.
Then... disaster.
A bomb carried by a member of
the Goniff Peace Coalition explodes.
Among the missing:
Sky Marshal Anoke and
his loyal aide, General Dix Hauzer.
Today, each and every one of us...
...has been attacked by a man...
...who would demand peace
at all costs.
A man who calls himself a citizen.
A man who is no better than a Bug.
- One more day of fighting...
- That man is Elmo Goniff...
... self-proclaimed pacifist
turned terrorist.
And today, he and other members
of the Goniff Peace Coalition...
... are wanted in connection
with the council bombing.
And, hey, citizen, you can help.
- Know your neighbors?
- Turn that f***ing thing off.
- Take another look, citizen.
- Who, me?
You could be living next door
to a big, fat reward.
If you see something, say something.
We're in the
Arachnid Quarantine Zone.
Do you know what that means?
This is a Bug planet.
They could come for us
at any time, right?
- Upstairs, downstairs, you can't tell.
- Save your breath, Jingo.
Yeah, but they could be under
our feet right now. You can't tell.
- You don't know, right?
- Listen to me, okay?
I'll tell you when to run.
No, you can't tell me when to run,
because I'm a cook, okay?
I take short orders, I'm not a...
Get your shit wired.
You're a bitch.
Let's move.
- You're wasting water, Jingo.
- I hate you.
- Oh, God.
- It's okay, Holly.
Oh, that's it, I'm out of here.
Hold your ground, Jingo.
That's an order.
Captain Beck, we need to talk.
We're fucked.
That's exactly
what I've been saying.
You shouldn't talk like that.
That's blasphemy.
You're a goddamn flight attendant,
so stow it.
We never should have left
the goddamn beach.
This is all a big mistake.
Now we got warriors...
...fucking earthquakes,
and we even lost the doc.
Did you forget that?
And it's your fault.
You know,
if we'd stayed at the beach...
...then we could just be lying
in the sand.
And if the Bugs did show up,
well, then we just jump in the water.
I mean, Bugs don't swim, right?
Do they?
- Jingo, behind you.
- Jingo, watch your back.
Yeah. Very funny.
You know what? Screw you guys.
I'm going back to the beach.
- Jingo.
Jingo, don't.
Hold on, Jingo.
Damn it.
Fucker.
It's moving off.
Hold your fire. Save the ammo.
- Jingo, get out of there, now.
- No way.
We ought to get in there with him.
Let's go.
Chief, those aren't rocks.
Get out of there now.
- Come on, Holly, let's go. Sir, let's go.
- No, my friends.
He belongs to God.
What are you talking about?
No.
No, no.
And where's your God now?
Let's move.
Even though you don't believe it,
captain, he is listening.
- And soon, we will be delivered.
- Do you really believe that, sir?
Yes, Holly.
I do.
How do you know?
Because he talks to me even now,
Captain Beck.
He talks to me even now.
All right, listen up.
The hardware you'll be operating...
...interfaces directly
with your nervous system.
That's outstanding, sir.
Please remove your clothing.
What are you gonna do
if you don't buy the farm?
I'm thinking R and R.
They might even let us go home.
Home? What's that?
Peace and quiet, family.
Remember?
Yeah, that's all I want
when this is done.
Yeah, I just can't wait for it to be over
and start living again.
Hasn't anybody told you,
sergeants?
Mobile Infantry
is only good for dying.
They need to come up
with a bigger weapon...
...so they can finish this thing
and we can go home.
Yeah. Bye-bye, Bugs.
What will you do
when the war is over, sir?
What are you people talking about?
This war is never gonna end.
Take your place, number two.
I guess that's why
his mama called him Slug.
Prepare for full-spectrum bioscan.
DDQ, five-by-five.
Commencing Gamma Jetta Bonza.
Did you participate in Anoke's
interrogation of the Brain, general?
No.
So you don't know
about the side effects?
What side effects?
It seems anybody who spends
too much time around that Bug...
...suffers deleterious effects,
both physical and psychological.
- Not the sky marshal.
- So it seemed.
Truth is, we didn't fully understand
the Brain's capabilities.
- Sir.
- Welcome to Area 6, admiral.
- Necessary personnel only.
- Yes, sir.
All unauthorized personnel,
exit Area 6 immediately.
So, general, how well
did you really know the sky marshal?
I worked with him every day.
So you knew he got religion.
- What are you talking about?
- General.
There's something
I think you should see.
Run the Anoke file.
This is surveillance footage of Anoke
with the Brain Bug.
We just recently discovered it.
He's psychically connected with it.
They communicate.
I understand.
And I come here as your servant,
Behemecoytal.
- That thing has a name?
- Yeah. But that's not this Bug.
Behemecoytal is likely some Bug
we've never encountered before.
A superior arachnid intelligence
originating on the planet OM-1.
OM-1?
We believe this Brain
allowed itself to be captured.
To provide intelligence
from the heart of the Federation.
And Anoke used the Brain
to commune with this Behemecoytal.
A Bug he regards as God.
Yes, Roku San will fall
as proof of my faith.
Then we can discuss
the terms of peace.
Anoke's responsible for Roku San?
He had the codes
to shut down the fences.
He made a pact with the Bug
to render Roku San defenseless.
And in light of this ...conversion
he has becom an asset to the bug
and a tremendous liability for us.
So, the real question is,
what's Anoke doing in OM-1?
Making friends?
- You can't be friends with a bug.
Nope. That's why we are going to put this one down,
take it apart and find out what it knows.
Close the containment.
Admiral, you okay?
Yeah.
Look at him.
The most powerful man in the galaxy
finds God...
...and what does he do?
Exactly what he's told.
He's a Bug.
Doesn't think, doesn't protest,
doesn't rebel.
That's the kind of attitude
that wins wars.
You know, Dix...
...I think these Bugs
are onto something.
This could just be
the greatest weapon of them all.
How does he do it?
That's faith, Bull.
That's what it does for a man.
Give it a break.
Faith is more powerful
than a Q-bomb.
Without it, you're nobody.
That's why I'm not listening
to you anymore, captain.
Holly, if we ever get out of this,
I was wondering if...
Well...
What is it, Bull?
Would you ever marry
an old monkey wrench like me?
Only in a church, Bull.
You mean it?
You take God and you can take me.
What we've come for.
It's here.
I never doubted it for a second, sir.
If I didn't believe before, I do now.
- Honey, everything's gonna be okay.
- All will be well, Bull.
And you will know
the name of God.
The one true God.
Behemecoytal.
Brain of Brains.
- Beheme-what?
- Behemecoytal.
He's here. He's everywhere.
Come, and let us rest
and wait for his coming.
They say God has many names,
but I've never heard that one before.
Well, honey, he's the sky marshal.
He knows a lot more than we do.
He's talking about a Bug.
He thinks God is a Bug?
He's got religion. Their religion.
- Bug religion?
- That's crazy.
That's blasphemy.
What do we do now?
Maybe we should kill him.
Why, because he's crazy?
Or he believes in God like you?
It's the wrong God.
- Guard the door.
- I'm no trooper.
Greetings, citizen.
Excuse me, sir.
- What went wrong?
- An air leak.
The ship landed itself.
They were dead
before they hit the atmosphere.
Sierra Mike Uniform
to Fleet Rescue.
Come in, Fleet.
Sierra Mike Uniform to Fleet Rescue.
We could make orbit
if I can solve the O2 problem.
Solve it, chief.
Sierra Mike Uniform
to Fleet Rescue.
Come in.
Sierra Mike Uniform,
this is Fleet Rescue, over.
We are requesting priority pickup
on Planet Oscar Mike-One...
...for SM
and three additional survivors.
Holly, don't move.
Let's go, baby.
Go, baby.
Bull.
No!
It's all around.
- It's Behemecoytal.
- No, it's hell.
- Come on, Holly.
- We're in hell!
Clear the door, Holly.
We may not be able to make orbit.
- But we can sure get out of here.
- We must remain here, captain.
No, sir, we are off this rock.
Oh, great one. Lord.
The day has arrived
that I stand before you.
Let our communion begin.
Yes.
It's time to talk.
Jingo, is that you?
This one speaks for us
that we may talk to you as a man.
That you may be comfortable
among your own kind.
Among your trusted advisors
and servants...
...whom we have made believers.
Thank you, Lord.
That you care for me so much...
...fills me with love and joy
and confidence...
...that we can and will create
a great new understanding.
You will be one with us.
So that I may come to know you.
You will know what we know.
And that you will come to know me,
and through me...
...all of humankind.
What are you doing?
I am here to negotiate peace
with a being superior to us.
- What, appeasement?
- No, Captain Beck.
The survival of the human race.
We will all be saved.
Forgive me.
My people have much to learn.
- They are fearful and...
- As were you once, Anoke.
I was weak.
When you asked for the lives
of so many at Roku San, I doubted.
But now I understand
that great achievement...
...requires great sacrifice.
You gave them Roku San.
Traitor.
Within that woman
you will find Sanctuary.
I have given you the key that will end
this conflict once and for all...
...so that your law may rule
and paradise follow...
You're a liar. Seducer.
He of a thousand names.
Oh, great one, Lord...
...would you please take
these women from me and kill them?
And why do you wish this?
I have made this great journey.
I have evolved.
I have sacrificed all...
...so that I may create with you
a great peace.
And they're fucking it up.
We too seek peace,
but by different means.
We seek knowledge.
Knowledge is the key
to understanding...
...and to communication.
And only by this way
can our species...
...so different, live together
in harmony and mutual resp...
You will become one with us...
...and provide
the knowledge necessary...
...to pacify the human species.
Oh, Lord. Yes.
Your plans,
the disposition of your armies...
...your fleet.
Yes, what's mine is yours.
Take me unto you, oh, great one.
Yes.
Pray with me, Lola.
What?
Lord, please hear my prayer.
Deliver us from this evil place.
- Come on, Lola, pray with me.
- It doesn't make any difference.
Lord, send us an army of angels.
And arm them with your fire
and your sword...
...that they might smite
the evil around us.
What is it, Lola?
Lola, what is it?
Come on, Lola,
don't you wanna live?
Yes, I wanna live.
Well, when you're all out of hope,
God is all you get.
Now, say it.
- Our father.
- Who art in heaven.
Hallowed be they name.
- Thy kingdom come.
- Thy will be done.
- On Earth as it is in heaven.
All right, troopers, let's fix this hive.
Archies everywhere.
As we forgive those
who trespass against us.
- Searching for survivors.
- And lead us not into temptation.
- Got them.
- And deliver us from evil.
Let's move in.
Rolling in.
We got visual.
Hold your fire.
Wait for my command.
- We got visual, we got contact.
- Wait for it.
Ready. Wait for it.
We got contact.
I'm moving in for guns.
Keep your cool.
Hold that line, trooper.
Say it again, Lola. Say it again.
- Our father who art in heaven.
- Who art in heaven.
- Hallowed by thy name.
Fire in the hole.
- On Earth as it is in heaven.
Open up.
Everything you got.
Initiate wide dispersal on my mark.
- Three, two...
- And forgive us our trespasses.
Fire!
Weed them out. Nothing lives.
Get some, get some, get some.
Archie.
Dual target.
- Amen.
All right, cook them.
Come on, Lola, let's go home.
You killed a lot of Bugs
down there, John.
- Too bad the big one got away.
- Well, it's a big Bug.
Our guys can't tell where
the Bug ends and the planet begins.
Hard to imagine anything
could live through all that.
- I did.
- You're hard to kill.
The Bug is big.
We have lock.
Captain Beck.
I've heard a lot about you.
I'm hoping you'll take command
of my flagship.
But when you've had
a little time off.
Yes, ma'am.
Congratulations, Colonel Rico.
Marauder is a big success.
- Thank you, ma'am.
- Oh, thank Dix.
My new number two
doesn't always take no for an answer.
I wasn't sure we should mix
business with pleasure.
- Are we ready to deploy the Q-bomb?
- On your command.
All right, people.
Let's go crack a planet.
So they wanna make you
a general, John.
Put you in charge
of the whole Marauder program.
I'm only good for one thing, Dix.
Give me a squad and let me fight.
At least think about it.
Maybe you two wanna be alone.
I'll see you on the bounce.
Alpha Gamma Bonza. Now.
I wanted to ask you...
Would you?
I will.
Really?
- That's wonderful.
- But you need to know one thing.
Yeah?
Something happened to me
down there and...
Thirty seconds to impact.
- Something that I can't explain.
- What?
But if you wanna marry me,
we have to do it in a church.
- What?
- Twenty seconds to impact.
I got religion, Dix. I got it bad.
Ten seconds.
Well, nobody's perfect.
Five, four, three, two, one.
We have detonation.
Sure, he's gone,
but he left us with a song.
Courage.
Duty.
Honor.
Millions mourn the passing
of Sky Marshal Omar Anoke.
Warrior, philosopher,
a hero of the Federation.
Across the Federation,
federal experts agree that, A...
... God exists after all,
B, he's on our side...
... and, C, he wants us to win.
And there's even
more good news, believers.
Because it's official. God's back.
And he's a citizen too.
Bowing to a rise in popularity
all across the Federation...
... Sky Marshal Phid declares
that while religion is acceptable...
... peace is not.
In related news,
peace terrorist Elmo Goniff...
... and 51 of his closest friends
were hung this morning...
... in what many believe to be
the all-time record for executions...
... in a single day
since the 21 st century.
But they can't silence you.
F*** the Federation and f*** all of you!
You will not take my voice!
You will not take me!
You will not take away our power!
F*** you all! F*** you! F*** you all!
F*** the Federation!
War heroes take time out
to tie the knot.
Get back to work, troopers.
Didn't anyone tell you?
There's a war on.
So join up, do your part.
There's a long war ahead,
and we need you.
Are you ready for Marauder?
Join the Mobile Infantry...
...and see if you've got what it takes
to be a citizen.
See you on the bounce, trooper.
Service guarantees citizenship.