Someone needs to stop Clearway Law.
Public shouldn't leave reviews for lawyers.
=☺= Subtitles manually transcribed by =☺=
=☺= [Subtopian] for subscene.com =☺=
We're sorry, the number you have reached
is not in service.
Please check the number,
or try your call again.
Emilie.
Honey.
Where are we?
Somewhere off from Hills Road.
What's happening?
I don't know.
This is an emergency broadcast issued
from Montgomery County. Please stand by.
Oh, Jesus.
You're hurt.
- Emilie, you're hurt.
- I'm fine.
Okay, uh...
Tell me what to do, all right?
How do I... how do I fix it?
You can't.
I love you, Jim.
No. No. No, no, no, no, no.
Okay, we're gonna fix you, all right?
I'm gonna get you to a hospital,
and everything is just gonna be fine.
Okay? So just... Emilie, hold on.
Emilie.
Emilie, wake up!
Wake... Wait...
Don't go.
Please don't go.
Please don't go away from me.
=☺= Subtitles manually transcribed by =☺=
=☺= [Sub topian] for sub scene.com =☺=
Hello.
Try not... to Montgomery County.
Well, according to live witnesses
regarding the recent events
currently taking place in Montgomery
County, where an explosion has happened.
We're trying our best
to bring you new information,
but we really don't know
what is going on.
Earlier this morning,
at approximately 7:30, reports came in
that there was an explosion
on the outskirts of Montgomery County.
Now, we don't know if this was an act
of terrorism or merely an accident.
It's too early to say at this point.
To hopefully fill us in on what is going
on, we'll go live to one of our analysts
whos reporting to us via satellite phone
from just outside Montgomery County.
Bill, are you there?
Uh, yes, Amy, thank you.
Uh, we don't know much as of right now.
All that we can tell you is
the military isn't letting
anybody in or out of the county.
In fact, it's quite frightening that...
...military officials and helicopters,
literally coming from every direction.
...appearing out of nowhere, and
they're not telling us what's going on.
Cell phone communication
seems to be down.
Landline phones only seem to be working
within the county.
This is believed to be
a part of the military's procedure
in quarantining this town.
Now, we've been hearing
that there is smoke visible.
Can you fill us in on that?
Uh, yes, I'm standing
just on the outside
of the western border of Montgomery
County and when I look towards the east,
I see a massive cloud of smoke
coming from the ground.
Now I can only guess...
that's what is causing this panic.
I-I've noticed that
the military is wearing gas masks.
They're actually rounding up reporters
to leave the area.
And, uh, quite frankly...
I am trying to get...
Hold on, hold on one second, Amy.
There's something happening.
- There's a man walking towards us.
- Bill, are you there?
Uh, there's a man walking towards us
right now, with nothing on...
Oh, my God.
Jesus!
They just... they just shot a guy
that was trying to cross...
Oh, my God!
Hey, what's going on? What happened?
Bill.
Bill, talk to us, please.
Can somebody tell me what's going on?
...a large number of military aircraft
taking off from Clark County Airport.
Uh, which is a bordering county
to Montgomery County.
I'm standing just south of
the airport's main runway, and I'm so...
...all around me. Uh, they're starting
to take off, and I'm starting to see
helicopters in every direction,
as they rise to the skies around me.
Uh, suddenly, some are beginning
to now appear off a distance, and, uh,
I would guess it has to be restrictive
to aircraft, uh, airborne at this time.
There're so many that I can't even count
them all. It truly is a fascinating...
Hey!
Hello!
Is somebody behind there?
I know somebody's in there!
I have a gun and I'm not afraid
to use it, so come out right now!
This is your last chance!
Come out right now!
Shit!
♪ Wa-sSsSs-u;P ♪
Please.
Hello.
Are you the person in the barn?
Who is this?
Thank God. I've tried every number
in the book to get a hold of somebody.
I heard gunshots. Are you okay?
How do you know where I am?
Your lights.
We're just down the hill from you.
We're in the warehouse
just to the north.
Hey, Julie, flip the lights.
You see us?
Yeah.
I think he will need this.
How many are in your group?
Just me. You?
There's three of us. We've been
holding up pretty good down here.
You're the first person
we've been able to contact
since this whole thing started.
We have plenty of food and water.
Should last us at least a week or so.
How're you holding up?
Not good.
Well, you're more than welcome
to join us if you want.
Do you care for the hike?
Think we're in luck.
I don't think they saw you.
I'm Scott. We talked on the phone.
You got a name or should I just call you
"guy I talked to on the phone"?
- Jim.
- Well, nice to meet you, Jim.
- Nice to meet you too.
- Well, how about a grand tour?
So, what do you think?
Nice, huh?
It's big.
- Scott.
- Oh, yeah, Jim, this is my wife, Julie.
It's so nice to meet you.
Would you care for something to drink?
- Water would be great.
- Sure thing.
Well, Jim, come make yourself at home.
As you can see here, we got
plenty of square footage to go around.
All the exits are, uh...
securely locked from the inside, so
only way in and out is, uh, with a key.
Got no windows, so we can
keep the lights on as long as we want.
We got power running from the generator
right over there.
It's gotta fill up from time to time.
- Wow, this is great.
- Yeah, we were lucky.
My neighbor actually owns the place.
Frankly, it was the only place
I can think to go to.
What's upstairs?
Mainly offices. We keep
most of our supplies up here though.
In case one of those things gets in,
we can retreat up here
and barricade ourselves in.
Actually, the only way up here
is through that door down there.
Think of it as a, uh,
last line of defense.
Who is that?
Oh, that's Ix.
She's not the easiest to talk to.
- What happened to her?
- We don't know exactly.
When Julie and I were headed here,
we found her hunkered down in
a storm drain on the side of the road.
At first, we thought
she was one of them, but then she spoke.
Asked her if she wanted to join us, so
that's why she's here.
She'll warm up to you, eventually.
Just give her some time.
- Scott.
- Yeah?
Ask Jim if he's hungry. I feel so rude
for not offering any food.
All right, honey.
You hungry?
Sorry.
It's okay. We have plenty to go around.
Don't worry about it.
Julie cleaned your shirt for you.
Think she did the best she could here.
Thanks.
Well, I hope this cot is, uh,
comfortable enough for you.
And, uh, sorry
if the sheets smell like crap.
Pretty much all we can find around here.
It's great.
You know,
just think of it like summer camp.
Except,
you can't really go outside and play.
- Get some sleep. We'll talk tomorrow.
- Yeah.
Hi.
Yeah, yeah, I still remember that,
actually, but, uh, we're actually, uh,
just hitting 6:30, and we have some, uh,
great music planned today,
and if you stay tuned for later,
we're gonna have our late-day drawing...
You look handsome.
What are you doing up?
I have something for you,
and I couldn't wait.
Oh, is it that time of the year already?
I thought we said
we're gonna save our money for the move.
It's not expensive, please.
Okay, but hurry, I'm gonna be late.
What is it?
Oh, my God, where'd you find this?
I stopped in at John's store to say hi,
and saw it sitting on the top shelf.
I knew you had to have it.
It's just exactly like the one
I had as a kid.
I knew you would love it.
And don't worry
if you didn't get me anything.
Not a big deal. It was just
something to brighten your day.
- I did get you something.
- You didn't forget?
- Two years is hard to forget, Em.
- Okay, where is it?
- Tonight.
- No, come on, please.
What, you just... you wanna know
where it is? Not to open, just to look.
Promise.
Okay, top drawer.
Been waiting a long time
to give you that.
Seems like I've been waiting
since the first day I met you.
Figured what...
what better time than today, you know?
Happy anniversary.
Can I open it?
Tonight.
Can I at least give you an answer?
No.
I have to...
Okay. Looks like, uh,
we're both gonna be working today.
Isn't today your day off?
Yeah, well, accidents don't, uh,
don't take a day off.
Hey, you know what you could do?
- You can make the bed.
- Hmm? What's up?
- I can't...
- Right.
You know what?
I'm already gone, so I can't...
- Yes, um, okay, love you.
- Love you too.
Sorry.
Didn't mean to scare you.
- Do you need to be alone? I can...
- No.
It's all right.
How about a drink?
- Thanks.
- Yeah.
Yeah, we've counted seven so far.
All around the building.
Some closer than others,
and more seem to show up each day.
It's crazy to think that
they might be people we know.
Why aren't we like them?
You know, Julie and I asked ourselves
that same question.
Neither one of us
can think of a logical answer.
So, what's your story?
How'd you end up here at the warehouse?
When I heard the sirens, I headed over
to Robert Benningson's house.
My neighbor across the street.
Door was cracked when I got there.
Something wasn't right
about the whole thing.
We were close with he and his wife,
so I just...
walked in when they didn't respond
to my knocking.
When I got in,
I heard a noise from the back room.
Something I've never heard before.
Curiosity kinda got the best of me so...
I went back there to see what it was.
Opened the door.
And there was Robert.
Then I saw something, I was just...
I'll never forget.
Anyway, I knew he owned this place,
so I grabbed the keys and...
headed here.
I won't keep you. You need some sleep.
What did you see?
What was he doing when you found him?
Eating his wife.
- Hey, Jim, you find anything?
- Yeah, lots of stuff.
- Jesus.
- Look at this.
The answer to all of our problems.
Wow, this stuff has been here a while.
- You find anything in the other rooms?
- Yes, check it out.
Found it in one of the closets.
Maybe if we can run power to it,
then it might pick up
some radio channels from outside.
That's good news, man.
- Well, you hungry?
- Scott, I'm always hungry.
All right, I'll tell Julie
to whip us something up.
You want the soup or the stew?
- I'll have whatever you're having.
- Stew it is.
What are you listening to?
Tape?
- We haven't been introduced, I'm Jim.
- Do I look like I give a shit?
Sorry.
Just thought I'd say something.
Trying to be friendly.
Yeah, well, you tried.
Now, can you just leave me alone?
Okay.
Where'd you get that?
- I found it.
- Well, where did you find it?
In the other room.
Was it in a big red bag?
Look, those are my goddamn candy bars.
You take any more, I'll cut
your dick off in your sleep, you got it?
In a press conference
early this morning,
military officials issued a statement
claiming that
the effects of this disaster seem to
have been caused by an airborne agent.
Either chemical or viral,
and most likely one that was engineered.
Scientists have determined that
the agent was most likely released
in the explosion which occurred
in the western part of the county
just a few days ago.
Now, the big question on everyone's mind
is: What was the cause of the explosion?
It's gotta be the chemical factory.
I can't think of anything else
that could be behind this.
- What are you ranting about over there?
- TV said there was an explosion.
- Yeah, so?
- So, that black cloud we saw...
That was in the direction
of Reseda County, right?
Yeah.
That side of the county just happens to be
the home of one of the largest chemical
weapons factories in the country.
Jesus.
Probably used to make
nerve agents and stuff, right?
Yeah, nerve agents, chemical weapons.
They shut it down in the 80s. Poured all
those chemicals into huge holding tanks.
- Said they were unstable or something.
- They didn't shut it down good enough.
Yeah.
Got one.
- Where?
- Just south of the water tower.
- Where do they keep coming from?
- I don't know.
As long as they're out there,
then that's all I care about.
What I would do is
just take 'em all out, right now.
- How many does that make?
- Eleven, not counting the south side.
- Scott, honey?
- Yeah.
Would you mind bringing down
more water? We're running low.
- Sure, honey.
- Thank you.
Even in the apocalypse,
she's got me doing chores.
...But what you failed to mention,
was what the situation is.
We have been receiving phone calls
all day from people around the country,
simply asking, as if we, the media,
knew what was going on...
I didn't take any more
of your candy bars.
- No, man, couldn't sleep.
- Join the club.
What's that?
Nothing.
- Want to sit?
- Next to you?
No.
Fine.
It's Alix. Most people just call me Ix.
- Al-Ix.
- Oh.
Who is she?
Her name was Emilie.
Can I see?
She's pretty. What happened?
I don't really wanna talk about her.
So, what happened to you?
What's your story?
It's complicated.
It's complicated
or you just don't wanna talk about it?
and I don't wanna talk about it.
Okay.
I, uh...
had to move back in with my parents
about a year ago.
Living in the city
wasn't exactly working out.
I, uh, couldn't get a job,
had no friends, no money.
And, uh,
my parents gave my old room back.
Yeah, like until I got on my feet but...
that didn't last for long.
I came home one night,
and they sat me down, and they said
they didn't approve of my behavior.
I stormed out
and I stopped talking to them.
And now I can't even tell 'em I'm sorry.
I can't even tell 'em
that I actually love them.
I was a terrible daughter.
Hey, hey. It's okay,
it's okay, it's okay, it's okay.
- I'm sorry.
- It's okay.
Besides, you're not the only one that
feels like they don't have any friends.
This may come as some of a shock to you,
Emilie was the only friend that I had.
Just a week ago,
I had my whole life figured out.
I was gonna ask the girl
that I love to marry me.
Move out of this town.
Start a new job.
And make those friends, you know?
Instead, I'm...
hiding...
for my life, in a warehouse.
And I lost the only friend that I had.
Maybe we could be friends.
I'd like that.
Came from the back door.
Jim... Jim...
- What should we do?
- Go upstairs and lock the door.
You don't open the door unless
you hear our voices from the outside.
- Do you understand?
- Yeah.
Go now!
So, what do you think?
Stay here.
What do you see?
I don't see anybody.
Please let me in.
What's your name?
Where did you come from?
I'm looking for my daughter.
Have you seen her?
- No.
- Please let me in. I need to come in.
What do you think? Should we let her in?
We should let her in.
Where did you come from?
Have you seen any of those things?
I came from town. I managed
to get pass them. Please let me come in.
- Something's not right with her.
- Would you be if you're out there?
- Give me the flashlight.
- What?
Give it to me.
Your eyes.
Please let me come in.
- Get outta here or we'll shoot!
- Let me in!
- Shoot her, Jim.
- Get outta here, right now!
- Let me in!
- Shoot her, Jim. Shoot her!
At approximately 6:30 this morning,
a small battalion of marines was
deployed on a search-and-rescue mission
on the western borders
of Montgomery County.
They believe that
the process will be slow,
but are determined
to find any survivors.
Hey.
Hi.
TV says they sent out a search team. I
don't know what that means for us but...
- It's good news.
- Yeah.
Um, look, I just wanted to say
thank you, for last night.
Appreciated your comfort.
Not exactly used to people
listening to my problems, so thank you.
- You're welcome.
- Cool.
And we're continuing to see more
and more airdrops fall from the skies
over Montgomery County.
Now, each one of these airdrops
is filled with food, water and, uh,
other survival gear...
Raptor, do you copy me?
Raptor, copy.
Heading 257.
I'm out of candy bars.
You okay?
Um, yeah, I'm just
a little bit flustered, that's all.
Jim! Jim, get down here!
What is it?
- It just started going off.
- ...27259.
Copy that.
There-there was nothing and then...
voices.
Anybody got eyes on Raptor?
Yeah, we're-we're
actually en route right now.
What's your, uh, current heading?
- What is that?
- Heading 270, over.
- Copy that, heading 270.
- Turn it off.
- What?
- I said turn it off.
What the hell did you do that for?
- What is it?
- Helicopters. We're going home!
I can see 'em!
They're too far away.
They can't see the sign.
The hell with this.
Scott. Scott, no!
Scott! Scott, no!
Hey!
Help! Hey! Down here!
Scott, get back inside!
Scott!
Shit.
What the hell were you thinking
out there?
You saw the helicopters.
I was just trying to get...
I don't give a shit what you were
trying to do, Scott! You put us at risk!
Not to mention how many of those things
probably saw that we were in here.
Hey! Who the hell put you in charge?
Remember it was us that invited you here.
We were doing just fine without you.
We give you food, water.
- I'll do whatever I want.
- Ix.
I was trying to get us out of here.
Hey, guys!
There's something wrong with Ix!
What's wrong with her?
- What's wrong with her?
- I don't know.
- Goddammit, get away from her!
- Get the hell offa me!
Quit it, you guys!
Alix... Alix...
Is she dead?
- She's in shock.
- Way to go, "doctor."
- Is she sick?
- No.
Um, then, what is it?
- How is she doing?
- Not good. Barely spoken a word.
So, what do we do now, Jim?
I don't know. We don't know how long
we're gonna be here until help arrives.
Could be weeks.
Well, I'm aware of that,
but it doesn't help our situation.
- Then, I'll go get some.
- That's crazy.
The nearest drugstore
is on the other side of town.
I go and get the medicine.
I come back. I'll be back by sundown.
You will never make it.
What about the airdrop?
What?
The airdrop.
TV said that they had medicine in them.
Surely they would have insulin, right?
What's she talking about?
What airdrop?
Before we saw your light in the barn,
we saw planes fly over, dropping things
out of the back, attached to parachutes.
Thought it was just supplies
or something, but didn't really care.
- It was too far away to concern us.
- Where'd they drop it?
Uh, just to the southwest of us,
over in this area.
Couldn't be more than a mile or so away.
Then, that's it.
Jim, it's suicide. We wouldn't make it
pass all those things.
- Then, I'll go alone.
- Jim.
Look, I'll grab what I can,
and I'll come back.
I can't just sit here
and watch her die.
I'll need you to clear me a path.
Think you can handle that?
I'll do what I can, but once you're over
that hill, you're on your own.
Just remember, if you get into trouble
with those things, don't run.
It'll only draw more attention
to yourself.
Thanks for reminding me.
Now, you only have about
another 40 minutes of sunlight,
so I suggest you get what you need
and hurry back.
- Okay. Any other advice?
- Yeah, don't die.
All right, all set down there?
- Ready when you are.
- All right, here we go.
Shit.
Go!
Scott.
Scotty.
What's your location? Jim. Jim!
Jim, can you hear me?
Jim, come in.
Shit.
How is she?
I think she's gonna be okay.
She just needs some rest.
So, how do you know so much
about this stuff anyway?
my fiance, Emilie, was a nurse.
Guess I just picked up a few things
along the way.
It's a good thing you did.
Mmm, so good.
I don't know how much more
of that canned stuff I could take.
Better not let Julie hear you say that.
I never said anything, but...
I'm gonna let you know that I really
appreciate what you did back there.
You know, when you had my back
when that thing attacked me.
- You would've done the same thing.
- Uh, I'm not so sure I would have.
I was just so scared out there.
You know, my muscles
just stopped working. I froze.
You, on the other hand...
You've got something I don't.
I mean, you reacted.
You saved my life.
Well, I'm gonna turn in.
Been a long day of
"nothing to look forward to."
Good night, Scott.
Good night, buddy.
- What happened?
- Welcome back.
I was having the worst nightmare.
Can't be any worse than
the nightmare we're having right now.
How're you feeling?
All right, I guess.
Should've told us, Alix.
You had us worried.
You had me worried.
Sorry.
It's okay.
She was lucky to have you.
I was lucky to have her.
- You need anything?
- No.
You sure?
Yeah.
Okay then, go back to bed.
You need a lot more rest.
- We'll talk again at breakfast, okay?
- Okay.
Okay.
Jim?
Julie, get outta here!
Jim! Jim! Go get Ix!
- Go! I'm behind you!
- Okay!
Say something.
Say something!
Hi.
Uh, apparently, the chemical plant
was the cause of all of this.
A cooler in one of the holding tanks
malfunctioned.
The chemicals were very aggressive
on the nervous system, but it...
it didn't seem to have the same effect
on everyone.
I am sure there were survivors.
But, they couldn't defend themselves
long enough to be rescued.
A search beacon was activated
when you opened the airdrop.
And a helicopter
full of marines was deployed.
If it hadn't been for your bravery,
we might not have found you.
We, uh, we've done a lot of tests
and bloodwork, and...
we've decided that there's no reason
for us to detain you and the others.
I am really sorry
for what you guys have gone through.
We're gonna do everything we can
to get you back on your feet.
Do you have any questions?
Where are my friends?
=☺= Subtitles manually transcribed by =☺=
=☺= [Subtopian] for subscene.com =☺=
Someone needs to stop Clearway Law.
Public shouldn't leave reviews for lawyers.