Fight!
This is definitely the wickedest thing
I ever hear in my life!
# Can't nobody do it like I do it
# When I do it, dawg, I do it
# Break it down, put your back into it
Y'all ain't ready for the shit I'm doin'
- # Get up, get up
- # How'd you change the sound?
# Took the other one I had,
swapped it out
# Kept somethin' in the background
# You know the song
Do it with the background
# Show off that body you got
# You got the dance flo' so hot
# You workin' that, you trickin' that
# You trickin' that shit like a plot
# Show off that body you got
# You got the dance flo' so hot
# You workin' that, you trickin' that
# You trickin' that shit like a plot
This is definitely the wickedest thing
I ever hear in my life!
# Get up, get up, get up
# OK, get up, get up
# You can do what you do
and do it well
# Can't nobody do it like I do it
# Do it, break it down
# Get up
# I'm goin' five on the Richter scale
The highest number you can roll is 12
- # Shorty, shake it like a...
- # Show off that body you got
# You got the dance flo' so hot
# You workin' that, you trickin' that
# You trickin' that shit like a plot
# Show off that body you got
# You got the dance flo' so hot
# You workin' that, you trickin' that
# You trickin' that shit like a plot
Whoo-ee!
Yo, Mac. Mac. Mac.
- What?
- Hey, man, you wanna do a lap?
Does it look like I need to do a lap?
- Just go.
- Man, this party's wack.
- Who is this guy?
- This is my little brother Skinny.
None other than.
- So, uh, how you doin'?
- Hey, man, what you doin'?
- Why don't I come back a little later?
- What? No, no...
You must have
the recessive genes in the family.
Recessive what?
Girls here is just stuck up, that's all.
- Is that what it is, Skinny?
- Let's bounce. Where's Tyler?
Where you think he at?
Yeah! Whoo!
- What you doin' with my girl?
- PJ, we're dancin'.
- Shut up, you bitch.
- I didn't see your name on her, man.
Hey, come on, PJ!
- Yeah, check him out!
- White boy's whoopin' on PJ!
Get off him!
- Better rethink your strategy.
- A'ight, man, you got it.
Come on, Tyler, let's go.
Skinny, let's go.
Tyler, let's go, man.
Skinny, come on, man.
- Get off me!
- Go, man.
Why you pushin' me so much?
- Tyler, move!
- Stop pushin'.
You just wanna be Rocky.
- I started nothin'.
- You always finishin' it.
- Wanna pull guns? I'll show you mine.
- Shut up, man.
Do you feel like because you a white boy,
you got to overcompensate sometimes?
Wow! Wow!
- You got me all figured out, Montel.
- I may be Montel, but you Jerry Springer.
Yo, yo, check this out.
- You Montel, you Jerry Springer and I'm...
- Jenny Jones.
Nah. Nah, nah. Nah, man.
- He's like Ellen.
- Except Ellen get more chicks.
Aah-ha-ha!
Hey, shut up.
I can't believe you fought PJ, man.
Hold up. That's PJ.
Man...
- What is he doin'?
- Skinny, what are you...
What the hell you think you doin'? Am I
the only one not tryin' to get us killed?
I ain't afraid of him.
You waited till the car got around
the corner before you threw something.
- That's real brave.
- I ain't afraid of nobody.
I ain't afraid of you
and I'm definitely not afraid of you.
- I'll throw something at you.
- That's how you miss.
Stand still, then.
- Where was it?
- There.
Oh...
Hey, yo, come on, man!
I know this place.
It's that school.
- This don't look like no school.
- It is a school. I'll show you.
Skinny!
- He's your brother. You go get him.
- Come on.
- I ain't goin' in there.
Damn!
Watch yourself.
Come on, man.
Shh, shh, shh.
- This looks like a museum.
- It's not a museum.
Ty, man, quit playin', man.
Look. Skinny's right.
This is a school.
- Arts school.
- I told you.
- Who goes here, then?
- Look like some stuck-up rich folks.
Look at these dudes.
All sweet with the shirts all tight
like they spray-painted 'em on.
Yeah.
It do show off their muscles
pretty nice, though.
- No, I'm just...
- No, no. Don't touch me.
- Mac. I'm just...
- Don't touch me.
I'm just sayin'
they in good shape is all.
- We need to get you a girl fast.
- I got girls. I just don't show 'em to ya.
- Why?
- Y'all are gonna try and take 'em.
- What you talkin' about?
- Check this out!
- Look at this place.
- We got nothin' like this in our school.
That's 'cause our school's broke.
Hey, yo, wait up.
These rich kids get everything.
What is this, man?
Seems like a playground to me.
# Figaro, Figaro,
Figaro, Figaro, Figaro
Look at this stuff.
Let's bounce, man.
- Skinny, what are you...?
- It was a accident.
Skinny, don't worry.
These rich kids can afford this. Look. Ha!
Look, look.
# Oh-wah...
- Hey, heads up!
- Whoa!
Whoo-hoo-hoo!
# La la la-la
I challenge you.
I win!
- It's a rumble.
- Aah!
Oof!
That ain't funny, man.
Look out! Whoa!
Hey, yo, yo, watch out!
Ha-ha!
- Having fun?
- Get off me!
Party's over.
You're comin' with me.
- I didn't do nothin', man. Get off...
- Go, go, go, man.
Yo, Ty!
Man, just go. Go!
- Very noble.
- Shut up, rent-a-cop!
Breaking and entering, vandalism
of the Maryland School of the Arts.
- You a student there?
- No.
You've been in this courtroom several
times. Where are your foster parents?
- Can you answer me with a sentence?
- My foster mom's trying to get off work.
OK, Mr. Gage, look.
This is the way we play the game here.
You break it, you buy it.
200 hours of community service to be
performed at the scene of the offense -
the Maryland School of the Arts.
Whatever.
I got here as fast as I could.
We're back.
- What'd he get?
- 200 hours community service.
Won't make it.
He's never stayed with anything.
Why do you care?
You get your check every month.
- Kids, wash up.
- What did you say?
Wait, slow down. You're makin' Bill dizzy
and he's not even drunk yet.
Guys, come on. Let's just have a nice
dinner before I have to go back to work.
I'm not hungry.
Hey, shut up!
I'm trying to watch this!
# Dress the hater,
no mask, only cape
# I ain't pressed for paper,
thug investigators
# I'm cooler than a 'frigerator,
sweeter than...
Are you going to prison?
How many times
do I have to tell you to knock?
That's where my dad is, at the supermax.
He liked it better at Jessup.
No, Camille,
I'm not goin' to prison.
But they are gonna have to take me
to prison if you don't start knocking.
Get outta here.
Excuse me.
I need that new arrangement.
I see. We were hoping to link the
fund-raiser to the fall showcase. Mm-hm.
So we absolutely
can't do it on a Friday?
I'm Tyler Gage.
I'm here to...
Come in, Mr. Gage.
Take a seat.
We'll just have to move the event till March
and hope the Pratts come through.
Thanks, Denise.
Well, I see that you're
overwhelmed with remorse.
You have no idea of the consequences
of your actions, do you?
Yeah. 200 hours.
Actually, there's a little more to it.
Most of our students
are here on scholarship.
The cost of repairing
the damage that you did
is roughly the equivalent
of one student's tuition.
Do you understand
what that means?
You just cost someone their future.
Sorry.
Look, I'm just here to do my hours.
It says here that your school day
finishes at two.
Per the court's order, you're to report here
and stay until 5:30.
Now, if you'll follow me, Mr. Gage,
I have someone who is
very eager to meet you.
- Mr. McCaffrey.
- Director Gordon.
This is Tyler Gage,
your new intern.
I'd like a daily report
on his activities.
Great. Here you go.
And stop
and bring it around front
and one, two, three,
four, five, six, seven.
And a-one, two, three,
four, five, six, seven, go!
One, two, three, four
and five, six, seven. And up!
And now up!
Um, hello.
Who is that?
Come on, he is fine.
Don't you have a boyfriend?
Yes, and my boyfriend would
appreciate my good taste. Thank you.
One, two, three,
four, five, six, seven.
And a-one, two and three and four.
Good, Nora. Six, seven.
And a-one, two, three,
four, five, six, seven.
four, five, six, seven, eight.
And one, two, three, four...
- Hey.
And a-one, two, three,
four and five, six, seven.
four, five, six, seven, eight.
Good class, you guys.
Good job.
- So I'll see you at rehearsal, OK, Andrew?
- You got it.
- Hey, baby.
- Hey.
- Walk you to your next class?
- I just gotta stop by my locker.
- All right.
- How are you?
- Good. How was class?
- It was good.
Guys, is that our new janitor?
He's not a janitor.
That's the guy who trashed the theater.
Really?
Ooh.
I love a man in a uniform.
Hey.
You with the garbage-man jumpsuit.
How about a wash and wax?
Cool out.
I know that car belongs to somebody.
We'll leave it here
for you to drive over to Omar's.
And make sure he pays
for the last car we brought him.
Whassup, man?
Man, look at this thing.
I think it's got plastic spinners.
What's up with the girls here?
Damn. They look like the girls
from the "Candy Shop" videos.
They might look like 'em,
but they don't dance like 'em.
Oh, yeah? So, you been
workin' 'em out?
I been workin' 'em out.
I been givin' 'em something like...
Whassup?
That's what you showed 'em?
Hey, yo.
- OK.
- Whoo!
- That's whassup?
- And what they do?
Be like twinkle-toes.
Aah! Ha-ha!
What'd you do after that?
Can you please stop thinking about
the senior showcase for one second?
- It's not just that. It's everything...
- Nora. Nora! Look.
Got a track for the showcase. It's the same
tempo, same rhythm as the track you got,
but I really believe this'll take
your routine to the next level.
- Next level?
- Yeah.
- Thanks a lot, Miles.
- Nora, listen, wait.
- Not that it's not already at the next level...
- Quit while you're ahead. Stop.
I need you to stop and take a breath.
You're startin' to make me nervous.
- I know. I'm just stressed.
- You need a break.
Colin's playin' Saturday night.
You haven't been there forever.
- Hold on. Who's Colin?
- Lucy's older boyfriend.
- He's sophisticated. A real man.
- Sophisticated? Real man?
His butt's gonna be surrounded
by a lot of real men when he goes to jail.
How long have you had your license -
six months, seven?
I am very mature for my age.
Thank you.
That's great.
That's so perfect for the witness stand.
# You can get with this
or you can get with that
# I think you'll go with this,
'cause this is kinda phat
# Engine, Engine Number 9
# On the New York Transit Line
# If my train goes off the track
# Pick it up, pick it up, pick it up
# Back on the scene,
crispy and clean
# You can try, but don't
'cause you can't intervene
# We be the outcast
down for the settle
# One play rock,
one play the pebble
# Open the door, you best believe
we're slidin' through it swift... ly
# Niftily,
we can make it hip to be
# What we are
'cause what we be
# Be the epitome,
doo da dippity
# So now I dwell
just to say you're plainer
# Hold your cup
'cause I got the container
# Pass the plate up,
cross the fader
# Black Sheep get played
like a Sony innovator
# Never the traitor...
When are you gonna
stop changin' her music?
- I'm just tryin' to help her.
- Nora, come on.
Just go. Just go.
Please, come on.
Hey, man, what you doin'?
- Come on, man.
- They got that.
- Tired of gettin' dogged on yet?
- Oh, yeah. Let's go.
Whassup?
- Yeah.
- Bounce!
- Throw that, Tyler!
Ha!
A'ight.
Pick 'em up,
pick 'em up.
Come on, man.
Come on.
Hey, man,
put me down.
- Come on, man.
- Ah-ha-ha!
- Get off me!
- You playin', baby?
- Go!
- Mac. Mac.
Got him. Got him! Get him.
Ohh!
Whoo!
- Put my money here, baby.
- Hey, baby. Nice game.
That's wonderful, Jack.
Congratulations.
- You're late.
- Not really.
You're so eager to get to work
you're sprinting off to the supply closet?
It's 15 minutes.
Don't I get a grace period or something?
You've neither earned one, nor are you
entitled. But you can stay 15 minutes later.
Andrew, oh, my God.
What happened?
Came down on my ankle wrong
in class today.
- Are you OK?
- Yeah. It's just a sprain.
Doctor says I have to stay off of it.
I'm really sorry.
- For what? It's not your fault.
- I know, Nora.
It's just that the showcase
means a lot to both of us.
Maybe you could find someone
to rehearse with in the meantime.
I should be back before you know it.
Yeah. Um...
Don't worry about it.
I'll be OK.
All right.
Cool. I'll see you later.
OK.
- What's up, man?
- 'Sup?
- Hey, where you from?
- I grew up in McCulloh Homes.
Oh, word.
That's where my boy Mac is from.
He lives over at Heritage now, though.
Oh, yeah?
I don't live over there no more.
I live with my aunt now.
I'll check you a little later, all right?
- A'ight.
Later.
He only has a bad sprain. I need someone
to rehearse with until he gets better.
You know all the stuff
I have going on with the labels.
How come Miles
can find the time to help me?
No offense to Miles, but he's not involved
in every aspect of the music as I am.
Look, all I need is somebody, Brett,
to rehearse with just for a couple of weeks.
I wanna help you. You know I do.
I'm just so close with my music,
I gotta give it everything I have right now.
Look, you're gonna do great.
You always do.
Yeah.
All right, sweetie.
Thank you guys so much
for coming to the audition.
- Ready?
- No!
Sorry. I'm not ready yet.
Thank you.
Next?
Like this.
Jump. See?
- It's not that hard. OK?
- Yeah.
Hold me. Great.
No.
Thank you.
No! Oh!
- Oh!
- I got it.
- You did it.
- No, no, no...
Thank you. Thanks.
I'll do it.
Do what?
I don't know.
Whatever y'all were tryin' to do out here.
You wanna lift me?
Are you kidding?
Does it look like I'm kiddin'?
OK, I get it. You're not gonna use me
to get out of cleaning the windows,
even if you were capable of dancing.
OK. I'm not trying to get out of anything
and I know you saw me the other day.
Thank you,
but I can find someone else.
OK.
I was just tryin' to help.
OK, wait.
Catch me.
Now what?
Um, um...
Put me down.
No. What about
choreographing a solo?
I don't have time to work out a solo.
Not a good one, anyway.
Have you talked to the sophomores?
I've auditioned a bunch of them.
None of them can handle it.
My dance has a lot of lifts in it
and you know how hard the...
- I can't believe there's no one else.
- None who have the time.
And you say that he can dance?
- He's adequate.
- Adequate?
See, that's my concern.
He's not taking this seriously.
Look, I'm sorry.
It's just you all be talkin' about dancin'
like it's rocket science or something.
It's just for a couple of weeks
until Andrew gets better.
Yeah.
This would be your risk, Nora.
It's your senior piece.
I know.
Don't make me regret my decision.
2:30 tomorrow.
Bring your tights.
Tights? Wait, what?
Aah!
I'm gonna beat you.
Anything interesting
happen in school today?
Malcolm, enough.
No.
Sit down. Thank you.
Eat.
Mm...
Anything special at school today?
I found a rehearsal partner,
so now I won't miss a beat
when Andrew gets back.
Your applications arrived from Cornell
and Brown. I put them on your bed.
Remember our deal, Nora.
If you don't get a job from the showcase,
you go to school in the fall.
OK.
I'm not late.
You're not dressed, either.
You can change in the bathroom.
Done.
- I asked you to bring tights.
- Do I look like I own tights?
- Shoes?
- Move better with 'em on.
Afraid you might slip and fall?
- How you wanna do this?
- I'll start with a combination.
OK.
Step, knee, step, fan,
step, turn, ball change, contract.
- OK?
- Mm-hm.
I'll take it slow.
And... step, knee,
step, fan, and...
- You got that?
- Yeah.
So, from the fan...
turn, ball change, contract.
OK. Um...
Let's do it again.
Five, six, seven, eight. Step, knee...
Oh. My bad.
No. Uh, so... Go.
Step, knee, fan...
Wow.
He looks like the real deal.
- Take a break. Grab a coffee with me.
- I can't. I have a lot to do.
- That's for damn sure.
- Brett...
- I'm sorry. You got a problem?
- No. No, I'm all about rehabilitation.
- We could discuss this outside.
- Why do you think you're so tough?
- Why don't you test me?
- OK, stop.
Brett, everything's OK, all right?
I'll meet you later.
- OK.
- What?
- Again.
And...
Yo, Omar!
Your boys are here, man!
O, look what we got for you, man.
Let's go, baby.
- I heard you havin' a party on Friday.
- Mm-hm.
- Yeah, you know we up in there.
- Uh-uh.
You dudes is froze out,
especially after what happened last time.
- What you mean, we froze out?
- I ain't start that. That was PJ.
That ain't even right.
We can take this car to Stuckey's.
Probably get more money, too.
I'm sorry. Yeah.
You could take this car to Stuckey's.
You know something, Mac? You young
dudes ain't got no respect. No loyalty.
Why don't you bring me a Escalade or
something to get back in my good graces?
- We just got you this car.
- An Escalade.
- We'll get you an Escalade.
- What did you say?
- Nothin', man.
- Yeah, nothing.
So, can I still come to the party?
- Skinny, come on!
- He ain't say nothin' about me.
He said y'all couldn't go to the party.
He didn't say nothin' about Skinny.
Will you shut up?
Ready? Down, up, step, turn.
- Piqué and...
- What the hell is a piqué?
This is a piqué.
We do the turn
and land face to face, OK?
- I get it...
- Do it again.
- It's just...
- What?
It's just stiff.
This whole thing is stiff. It's boring.
Boring?
Don't look at me like I'm stupid.
I know you know what I'm sayin'.
Fine. Well, that's the way it is, so...
Fine.
Ready? And...
Down, up...
step, turn, piqué, and...
- Like this?
- Um...
OK, I am starving.
Tyler's just here until Andrew's back.
And why is this the first time
I'm hearin' about it?
We still have work to do.
Wait. I can't watch?
Is he that bad...?
- Goodbye.
- You can tell me!
OK.
OK, um...
- I'll see you tomorrow.
- All right. I'll see you tomorrow.
OK.
Can you come to the club
and hear me sing with Colin on Saturday?
Ooh, maybe you can bring Tyler.
Can you stop talking
about how hot he is?
OK, Brett's not around, so why do you
keep denying the obvious? It's so obvious.
OK, fine. Tyler's good looking,
but he's annoying.
See? Your guard's up,
and that must mean that you like him.
- You couldn't be more wrong.
- Ooh!
And defensive, too.
You know, that must mean that you,
um... really, really like him.
I'm just sayin'.
Look. Miles sent me another MP3.
Ugh.
Better listen to it now. He'll call
in five minutes, askin' what you think.
You've been gettin' on
Miles' case a lot lately.
Because he's irritating.
Ooh.
- Defensive. What does that mean again?
- Just listen to the track, OK?
Hm.
It's good.
Whatever.
# Whoa-oa-oa
# Step, step, step up
Step, step, step up
- This.
- This is better.
# You step up,
I'll step up, boy
# 'Cause I'm tryin'
to be with you forever...
# No matter what we go through
# You step up,
I'll step up, too
# It don't matter what the haters say
Long as you are my boo
# No matter how hard it gets
# This love will have no regrets
# As long as when we steppin'
on the dance floor, it's me and you
# The rhythm of the beat,
that's my heart
# Cupid shot me
with an arrow from the start
# It's your love
that's got me trapped
# Every time I try to leave,
you bring me back
# So much water,
at times I've cried a river...
I'm so serious.
If you don't stop laughing...
OK, no!
- Are you serious?
- Ready?
# You step up,
I'll step up, too...
Whatever.
I'm sorry.
# This love will have no regrets
# As long as when we steppin'
on the dance floor, it's me and you
# When I step into place,
I feel my feet
# Lifting from under me
# You grab my hands,
spin me around and right before I fall
# You catch me and you say
# Just look into my eyes
and we will make another day
# Boy, no matter what we go through,
this love will have no regrets...
What next?
Six, seven, eight.
Piqué and grab...
# No...
# Boy, no matter...
Turn, down.
# You step up,
I'll step up, too
# It don't matter
what the haters say
# Long as you are my boo
# As long as when we steppin'
on the dance floor
# It's me and you
Lena got Cap'n Crunch.
Peanut butter Cap'n Crunch.
Told you she likes us.
- Camille, would you get outta here?
- Fine.
- It's not my fault!
- It is your fault...
Camille, come here for a second.
Shut up.
You gonna give me a little bit of that?
One bite.
One. One bite.
Hurry up.
That was the biggest bite I've ever seen.
Get your own.
I spit on that spoon.
Yeah, now you give it back.
What... What is this?
- That's a sliding scale.
- What does that mean?
That means I scored more points than you,
so I get more money.
No, no, no.
What about my assists?
I was droppin' dimes today.
- You tripped over your own shoes.
- Twice.
You rolled out of the second one.
You played it off cool.
- You better give me some more money.
- What?
It's getting late.
I gotta bounce.
- Wait, hold on. We'll give you a ride.
- Yo, let me do it this time.
- Skinny, you the lookout.
- Why can't I do it this time?
- Can you do it?
- Yeah.
Let him do it, then.
You know what?
Here you go, tough guy.
See that car right there?
Go get 'em.
- That car has got an alarm on it.
- I know.
He failed.
Yo, I told you that alarm
was gonna go off.
Wait a minute.
Y'all set me up?
Hold up. I got us one.
You shoulda saw your face.
Tsk.
# Can't say I ever felt the way I felt
- # When we were makin'...
- # Love
# Can't stand the thought
that you were mine, but now you're...
# For the takin'
# I realize that we were one,
but now we're two
# You traded us for something
just to pass the time, babe
- That was good. Play it back, Miles?
- I like that.
Nora.
Yo, look who's here.
Sorry, bro.
Closed studio.
Yeah, OK, "bro".
- You're an hour late.
- Yeah. My bad. I got caught up.
For an hour?
Yeah. I had things I had to do.
I'm sorry. Can't we rehearse now?
No. There's other dancers
in the studio now. We can't.
Why you gettin' mad at me?
I'm here every single day.
- I said I'm sorry.
- Sorry's not gonna cut it.
Yeah, we're workin' here, man.
Some of us take this seriously.
Mm-hm.
- Where were you?
- Where was I when?
When we were supposed
to be rehearsing?
I don't think the rehearsing thing
is gonna work out for me.
- What the hell does that mean?
- That means I'm out.
What?! Are you kidding me? You just quit
without even talking to me about it?
Yeah, sorry.
Look, I gotta get back to work.
I can't believe this. I can't believe
I trusted you. That was so stupid.
People make stupid decisions every day.
Besides, it didn't look
like you needed me, anyway.
Mac, get your feet off the table.
Marcus, get your feet off my table.
- Told you, boy.
- Mom!
Don't leave this house. I don't wanna
hear about you getting into trouble.
- We ain't goin' nowhere, Mom.
- That's right.
I'll be back home in time
to make y'all's breakfast.
- Bye, Mom.
- Bye, Mrs. Carter.
Ah, man.
Look, look, weak crossover.
- You think you're as good as these guys?
- Please.
Why don't you try out?
- For the And1 team?
- Mm-hm.
- Why would I need to do that for?
- You should play for the school team.
The school team?
- Yeah, right. They suck. Never.
- Maybe they wouldn't suck if you played.
Is this part of your community service?
What you gonna say next? "This is your
brain on drugs"? Man, forget with that.
- I'm just sayin'...
- All right, man. Just drop it.
Don't see you out tryin' to do nothin'.
You quit everything you start. You know it.
- That's me right there.
- Put it in slow motion, too.
Oh, baby...
Nora?
Where have you been?
It's getting late.
Where do you think, Mom?
You've been rehearsing a lot.
What about your schoolwork?
Rehearsing is the most important part of
my schoolwork. It's kind of the whole point.
Sweetie, I just don't think that dancing...
Dancing is what?
What do you know about it?
When was the last time
you saw me dance?
That's not fair.
You don't have to worry about it anymore.
The guy I've rehearsed with
for the showcase quit today.
So basically, I'm screwed.
You might get your dream after all.
You gotta come to rehearsal.
Nora.
Wait a minute.
Can you hold on a second?
Look, I just wanted to say
I'm sorry about yesterday.
- You don't feel like mopping floors today?
- Look, can you just give me a break?
Do you have any idea how important this
showcase is? Who's going to be there?
- I don't know. People?
- People?
Important people from every
major dance company in the country.
Without this showcase,
I have nothing. I go nowhere.
OK. All right, I get it.
I know all about havin' nothin'. It sucks.
- It does.
- So are we gonna go back to doin' this?
- No.
- No?
- I don't trust you.
- What do I gotta do to prove it to you?
Look, I'll do anything.
Anything?
And up and grand plié
all the way to the ground.
Back up and reach your arm up high.
Touch the sky.
Down forward, touch your toes.
And back up.
Shh!
And pointe and second.
And plié...
Good. Plié...
Shh!
I thought she was gonna
slap me in my face.
Well, this is me.
OK. Why are you teachin' ballet class?
It doesn't look like you need a job.
Oh, you know, it just puts off
coming home a little longer.
It couldn't be that bad.
My mom doesn't get
the whole dancing thing.
- What about your dad?
- He died a couple years ago.
- I'm sorry.
- No, it's OK.
He was the one
who always encouraged me.
Driving me to rehearsals,
watching all my routines.
Sounds like a cool dude.
- Thanks for walking me home.
- All right. Later.
Bye.
Pickup game tomorrow at the courts.
Them cats want a rematch. You down?
I can't make that. I got community service
every day this week, man.
Hey, put that away.
What are you doin'?
Whassup between you and Lucy?
Look like she's kind of feeling you.
- I don't know about that.
- What, you scared?
Luce, Colin is too old for you.
What are you doing?
- It was so...
- Cheesy?
Romantic, OK?
It was romantic...
- Why isn't Nora using this?
- Nora's old-school, man.
I ain't talkin' Sugarhill Gang.
I'm talkin' 'bout Vivaldi old-school. For real.
You should let her listen to it.
Hey, Nora. I want you to hear somethin'.
- Don't start.
- You guys seem to be gettin' along well.
- He's my partner.
- Ah, he's just your partner.
And too many things.
Miles got... What's that, violin?
Some kids to play violin on the track.
Finally working with people
that can play instruments.
I can play, all right.
I just prefer to play with myself.
Whoa. What?
- He makes it too easy.
- No, not play with...
Just listen.
I like it.
I really like it. It's good.
Told you, dawg.
Hey, I was thinkin', um...
You know that turn
where we have our legs behind us?
Thinkin', you know,
what if I went down,
and then we, like,
change levels, like?
I just... I don't mean to be out of line...
No, no. It's cool.
I like it.
Let's try it. Ready?
Five, six, seven, eight.
One, two, three, four.
- That's actually really good.
- Cool.
I think we should do it.
Let's try it again.
Five, six, seven, eight.
I guess I'll just see you tomorrow, then.
- OK.
- All right.
You need a ride?
Um...
You ever even been out to Hampden?
No, but there's a place I go near there.
I'm serious.
Where are you takin' me?
Hold on.
I'm about to show you.
Hold it. Is this...
Is this where you kill me?
Funny.
This is it.
Yeah. I mean...
I got a view just like this,
you know, from my balcony.
- You do?
- No.
- How did you find this place?
- I been comin' here since I was a kid.
My dad was an executive
at one of the shipping companies.
This is where
I imagined my whole routine.
I don't know how you do it.
How you think about
how two people are gonna move and...
I don't know, every detail.
I couldn't do that.
- You've been doing it.
- It's not the same thing, though.
That's how it starts.
I always saw this routine
with a bunch of other dancers.
What do you mean?
Well, if I had enough dancers,
I could have them all starting in unison
and then slowly
breaking out in a canon.
Whoa, what's...
- What's a canon?
- You know, like "Row Your Boat"?
OK, I'll show you. You know
that phrase with the turn and lift?
They all have turn and lifts.
All right, what, in the middle section?
Yeah, I know it.
Instead of doing it together,
you're gonna go first.
- Come on.
- All right.
OK, go on "one".
Five, six, seven, eight.
- # When I'm with you
# You know you make my days
# So beautiful
# With your different ways
- # You make me lighter
- # Yeah
- # I'm movin' with the wind
- # Movin' with the wind
# Love, you know what you've got for me,
I've got for you, too
# We can't pretend
# Give me another chance to breathe in
# You got all the things I need and
# Together, we're just so complete
# You must be the reason I'm alive
# Give me another chance...
Um...
# You got all the things I need and
# Together, we're just so complete...
Um... I, um...
If you saw it with a bunch of dancers,
you should do it with a bunch of dancers.
Where would I find these dancers?
You go to a school bustin' with
kids in tights. Take your pick.
The only ones left are sophomores
and freshmen. They're not good enough.
How do you know
if they're good enough or not?
You didn't know I was good enough.
Well, who says you are?
All right...
Uh-huh.
I'm being kept in the ninth grade.
- Ha-ha-ha.
- Let's go. You ready?
- I can't. I'm late for my hours.
- What about our game?
- I'll do it tomorrow.
You said that yesterday.
Yo, I'm gonna catch y'all later.
Now I'm gettin' pissed.
How many did you say you needed?
Thanks, Miles.
So, um, that's basically
what we have so far.
Congratulations.
You've really expanded your range.
I thought your original piece was good,
but this...
This is very risky, Nora.
But it may pay off. What made you
decide to change your piece?
- Actually, a lot of this is Tyler.
- Nah, it's all you.
OK, fine. He gave me some of his moves
and I gave him ballet lessons.
You've studied ballet?
He's actually pretty good.
He could be a student here.
Unfortunately, our school year has
already begun, but keep up the good work.
Mm, Miles. Miles!
- Lucy, not right now.
- What's wrong? Miles.
Miles, what's wrong?
I heard you guys got signed.
- You heard wrong.
- Everybody says Brett got signed...
- Brett signed without me.
- How'd he get signed without you?
According to him,
the label says he's the only talent.
They wanna put him out as a solo artist
to work with other producers.
- Oh, my God...
- You know what?
I knew Brett had an ego.
I knew he did.
But, damn, I thought he would sit me down
and tell me like a man.
I knew it.
Hey, baby.
Is that why you flew
to New York last week?
Nora, calm down.
You ditched Miles? After all the work you
did together, you dump him just like that?
You haven't heard my side of the story.
You don't have time to tell your girlfriend.
I have to find out through everyone else.
Nora, come on. I'm sorry.
I didn't expect it to happen like this.
It's just happening. All right?
Like we always talked about.
We never talked about
stepping on our friends.
When you're handed your dream,
you take it. You don't ask questions.
- I would.
- You think you would.
But you don't know
until it's right in front of you.
Seriously, would you
have walked away?
I don't know...
but I'm walking away now.
- You're breaking up with me?
- Yes.
This isn't about me or Miles or any of that.
It's about Tyler, isn't it?
No, it's about me, Brett.
Fine.
Remember, that loser's
headed nowhere fast and you know it.
Miss Gordon...
I mean, Director Gordon?
Can I help you, Tyler?
Um...
There's something
that I kinda wanted to, um...
- It's probably stupid.
- Then perhaps it can wait.
You know how me and Nora
have been working together?
It's been... kinda making me think lately
that... maybe I'd like to come here.
- You want to apply to the school?
- Yeah. Kids transfer, don't they?
I was kinda hopin' maybe I could
finish out my school year here.
It's not that you don't have talent, Tyler.
But a lot of kids have talent.
It takes so much more than that.
This is a grueling program. My students
work themselves into the ground every day
just to get a fraction closer to their goals.
We're tough as hell on them in here,
because we know what they're
going to face out there.
Only kids that make it
are the ones prepared to fight.
Yeah, I understand that.
I'm not sure that you do,
not for something real.
And I've already seen you
give up once already.
- That's not gonna happen again.
- Saying the words doesn't make it so.
Then tell me what I gotta do.
I can't.
You have to show me.
Show me that you want it,
really want it.
You do that,
then we can talk.
Now, if you'll excuse me,
I have a 3:00.
Unh...
# Whoo-oo-oo
# I got this girl
# And she's the only thing
that can drive me insane...
Come on, man.
Will you snap out of it?
All right, look, way I look at it,
Brett did you a favor.
Your beats are hotter
than what he can do with 'em.
# It's a crime to admit
that she ain't ten times legit
# My friend,
she's hotter than shh...
# Her sun is shinin' on me
# Anybody that got somethin' so fine
# Now's the time to acknowledge
# Ohh, ooh...
- Come on, man.
- I gotta sit up here and watch this Colin?
Did we come here for him?
I thought we came here for Lucy.
Is that who you been looking at?
He is kinda hot, in that weird way...
Shut up, man. Shut up.
# I got it made in the sun, baby
# Made in the sun, sugar
Made in the sun, honey
# Oh, baby
Thank you. We're gonna take a break.
Be back in five.
Sounds great, fellas.
I gotta get up outta here, man.
Hey, guys.
Have you met my boyfriend?
Hey, man. I'm Colin.
Tyler. Nice to meet you, man.
- This is Miles.
- What's up, man?
Miles. This is the guy
you told me about.
She said you played.
Got a set up if you wanna join us.
- Oh, no. I left my G4 at home, man.
- It's in his bag.
Yeah?
Come on, man,
we're set up. Ready, Luce?
Dude think he slick trying to use
that reverse-psychology shit.
- He seems kinda cool.
- That's part of his whole game.
Man, just go play.
- How are you?
- OK.
- Hey.
I didn't think you'd come...
- That's exactly why I wanted to come.
- Yeah?
- What are you doing here?
- Miles needed a wingman.
Oh.
What's he doing up there?
Trying to be the bigger man.
OK.
- You look beautiful.
- Thank you.
Is everybody ready?
Let's do this.
# Ah-ah, ah-ah
Ah-ah, ah-ah
Ah-ah, ah-ah...
# Yeah...
I didn't know she could sing.
In her words, she majors in dance
because she can already sing.
# On the weekend, on the weekend
On the weekend, on the weekend
Kill it, Miles.
# Back again, hit the lights,
let the party begin...
- So, are you gonna ask me to dance?
- Didn't know you can dance without tights.
# And I think
I'm ready to go, hot...
You don't know
what you got yourself into.
# Everyone in line
and they're payin' a lot
# Drop a Ben,
them drinks are rich
# But the music is free
You want it, you love it
# You need it,
you know you gotta have it
# The music is playin'...
What is that?
# This is for the girls comin' from NYC
I'm feelin' you like you's family
# And everybody down
from L.A. to D.C.
Whoo!
Come on.
# Turn the volume up 3db
# Get on the dance floor
where the music is free
# Slip on until the dawn's gone with me
# While the music is free
- # Slip on until the dawn's gone with me
- # On the weekend...
Now all my ladies,
over to the front.
Show 'em what you got.
# Ooh, hoo-ooh
# Uh-huh, uh-huh, ooh
# Uh-huh, uh-huh, oo-ooh
Fellas...
move like that.
# Uh...
# Uh-huh, uh-huh
Uh-huh, uh-huh
- # I like that
- # Uh-huh, uh-huh
- # Can all my ladies say
- # All the fellas say
- # Uh-huh, uh-huh
- # Everybody say
- # Come dance with me
- # Uh-huh, uh-huh
# And the story goes just like this
# We pack 'em in till the morning,
there'll be no lettin' off
# Dollars droppin' onto the tabletop
# You can shake your thing
and there ain't no cost
- # This is for the girls comin' from NYC
- # I'm feelin' you like you's family
- # And everybody down from L.A. to D.C.
- # Rockin' to the same old-school beat
# This is for the kids
in the clubs and the street
# Turn the volume up 3db
# Get on the dance floor
where the music is free
# Slip on until the dawn's
gone with me
- # This is for the girls comin' from NYC
- # I'm feelin' you like you's family
- # And everybody down from L.A. to D.C.
- # Rockin' to the same old-school beat
# This is for the kids
in the clubs and the street
# Turn the volume up 3db
# Get on the dance floor
where the music is free
# Slip on until the dawn's gone with me
# While the music is free
# On the weekend,
on the weekend, yeah
Come here, baby.
Oh!
I swear, I have never seen
that many people here before.
Get used to it.
That was great.
Come on, you guys.
Let's take a walk by the water.
- Come on, let's walk.
- Let them go. Let them go.
- You're gonna make me say it, aren't you?
- Make you say what?
- I know I been hatin' on Colin.
- Mm, yeah.
But...
He was good.
He was real good.
For someone who's so sophisticated.
Why you always gotta play?
You were, um...
pretty good yourself.
Miles, a little bit.
Just... Yeah, just a little.
I try to do what I do.
Um...
Don't worry about it.
- Lucy...
- I gotta go.
I'm gonna go check our sound levels.
That place is crazy.
Is it always like that?
Yes.
But tonight, Miles and Lucy
were on a whole other level.
You weren't so bad yourself.
Y'all know exactly what you want.
Well, what about you?
What do you want?
I don't know. Nothin'.
Come on.
What about when you were a kid?
All kids want something.
I don't know.
For me, it's just...
better not to want anything.
That way, if it goes away
or... doesn't happen,
you know,
it just doesn't matter.
But you want something now, right?
Like... maybe to go to MSA?
There's a lot of things
that I want now
that I didn't used to.
I even catch myself every once in a while
actually thinking I can have 'em.
Please don't kick me out.
I brought you orange juice.
Bill and Lena went out.
You're baby-sitting.
Thank you.
- Why are you always so tired lately?
- 'Cause I been working a lot.
- Doin' what?
- Why do you ask so many questions?
Never mind. Don't answer that.
Just go get Malcolm's shoes on.
All right.
Oh, throw it.
Got it. You almost got it.
Dancing? You can't dance.
Who can't dance?
You never seen me dance.
Then do somethin'.
Do somethin'?
What you want me to do?
Huh? Huh?
- OK, it was fine. It was OK.
- OK.
- What was that?
- Throw it.
- Where'd you learn that?
- Nothing.
I'm not throwing anything
until you show me what that was.
Yeah, all right.
I get you with the little...
All right.
You can do that,
you can do this.
OK.
Hah, hah. What?
- I love it. All right. So after that...
- Yeah?
Hit, hit...
OK, let's try it all.
- You got the whole thing?
- Yeah.
OK, all right. On "go".
One, two, three, go, all right?
One, two, three, go.
What?
Hit, hit...
Hey.
Can you do "running man"?
You don't know about that.
- Malcolm, can you do the "running man"?
- Yeah!
Oh, yeah. What's up?
- Here we go. He's doing it one-handed.
- Oh, oh.
Whee.
Whoo!
This is you?
Don't be mean.
I was a chubby kid.
What are you saying? If I was
like that now, you wouldn't like me?
No, I could deal
with the chubbiness.
But if you were missing those front teeth,
I couldn't work with that.
Thank you very much.
I was thinking we should talk to
Director Gordon about using the showcase
as your audition to get into the school.
I don't know.
Do you think she'd go for that?
It's about going after what you want, right?
Mom. Um, hey.
I-I didn't know you were home already.
This is Tyler,
my rehearsal partner.
Nice to meet you, Ms. Clark.
You have a beautiful home here.
Thank you.
We certainly like it.
I should probably get going, anyway.
Thanks for showing me those pictures.
Yeah.
It was nice to meet you.
A'ight, here we go.
Ready? One, two, three, go.
- Hey.
- What's up?
- Um...
Look, about the other night -
you didn't tell anybody, did you?
Nah. Uh-uh.
You know, 'cause it's just
musicians, whatever.
You ain't got nothin' to explain to me.
What's wrong?
Why you talking to me like that?
If you wanna be with someone
who doesn't appreciate what he's got,
that's 100% your business.
I just thought you'd be smart enough
to know you deserve better.
Excuse me.
Ready back there? All right.
I wanna hit it hard. All right.
Smooth it out even more than that.
Just want it to look pretty. All right, go.
- Wait, hold up.
- Mac?
Tell me I'm not seeing this, Ty.
Mac.
Hold on, Mac.
Yo, wait up a second.
What you doin', man?
What is that, Riverdancin'?
You gettin' down with your Irish roots now?
- It's not like that.
- Like what?
- It's part of my community service.
- How is dancin' community service?
It's complicated.
- Explain to me. I ain't that stupid.
- Fine...
You were s'posed to meet me
at the courts two hours ago.
I come over here and I see you
blowin' me off for this? This?
You ain't been hangin' or callin' 'cause you
leapin' around with a bunch of rich kids?
They're not all rich.
It's not like that.
All right, Mac, hold on.
There's this girl.
She asked me to rehearse with her
for this showcase thing. That's all.
So you messin' around
with our friendship for a girl?
So it's like that?
- That's a relief, Ty.
- Come on, man.
That's great.
- Hey, Tyler.
- Hey.
What, are you back?
Yeah. Feelin' a lot better.
Thanks for fillin' in for me.
- Can you give us a sec?
- Sure.
Hey, guys.
- Hey. Good?
- Definitely.
I didn't think he was coming back.
He hasn't even been here.
I don't know what to do.
So he's back.
Where does that leave me?
- You don't have to say anything.
- Wait. What does that mean?
I can't believe I bought into this bullshit.
You're really gonna turn your back on me?
That's not what I'm doing, Tyler.
Andrew is a student here. He's a senior...
You're just like Brett.
You use people then you dump 'em.
Why are you making it sound like that?
It's not the same situation. You know it.
So how is it not?!
Have I just been filling in for Andrew?
That's not fair.
I'm out.
Tyler. Tyler, wait.
Gimme a second to figure this out.
# Ooh
# Ooh-ooh-ooh-ohh
# Oh
# Softly as a child
# Born in natural rain
# I predict the seasons
# To go unchanged
# Sometimes in life
# Don't go off runnin'
from what's new
# I became somebody
# Through lovin' you
# Warm was the sun
# That covered my body so
# Reminded me of you...
Hello.
Hi. Is Tyler there?
May I ask who's calling?
It's Nora.
Nora?
No, he's not here.
Yeah, um,
just tell him I called.
OK.
# Oh, I became somebody
# Oh
# Oh-oh
# Ooh-ooh-ooh
That's it. Ball, change, up.
To the left, to the right. Heads up.
Inside, up.
Easy, knee.
Look up.
Up, play right.
All right, thanks.
Five, six, seven, eight.
One and two, three, four. Up.
Aah.
- Andrew, are you all right?
- I don't know.
Oh.
OK, try walking on it.
- I can't do this, Nora.
- What?
You and I both know
I can't pull this routine off.
Here, Mom.
Nora...
- Bet you can't make the shot.
- Bet you I can.
- Whatever.
- Yeah, right, whatever.
Let me do it.
You suck, man.
Hey, yo, Ty.
- Man, what's up?
- What's up?
- Where you been, man?
- You know, around.
Gimme my ball back.
Ain't you gonna be late for ballerina class?
No, man.
I'm through with that.
- So what happened with that girl?
- Nothin'.
- Nothin'? I'm supposed to believe you?
- Yeah, man, you are.
I dunno.
Man that turns his back on his boy...
Deserves a second chance.
Right?
Come on, Mac.
Party tomorrow night at Omar's, man.
Ha-ha-ha.
That's my man.
Uh-oh.
And boogie...
Got it, got it, got it.
Come on, man.
Mom?
Are you OK?
Do you know even when you were a baby
you danced better than you could walk?
It was all you ever wanted to do.
I remember the look on your face the day
we took you to your first dance class.
You do?
I never expected that dancing would still
bring you such joy after all these years.
Seeing you up there on the stage
so happy - it used to make me happy.
- I guess I forgot about that.
- Mom, it's OK.
I am so excited
to see you dance in your showcase.
Oh. Mom...
I don't even have a partner anymore.
Tyler's not doing it and Andrew's out.
Baby...
You can do this.
You've been doing this
by yourself your whole life.
Come here.
You are gonna be great.
Thanks, Mom.
- I'm still gonna win.
- We'll see.
That's why I'm beating you.
Yeah, a'ight, whatever.
I'm gonna come back.
- What y'all up to tonight?
- We goin' to Omar's to watch movies.
Yeah.
I know all about your movies.
You stayin' here, you understand?
What?! Ma... I got to go last time.
Yeah, I know, and that's why
you staying here tonight.
You boys make sure
my baby don't go nowhere.
- All right, Ma.
- Yes, ma'am.
- I'll tuck you in before we leave.
- Shut up.
# Let's go!
All these girls and he don't wanna dance.
Huh? Huh?
Yo, yo, here's the man.
What's up, T?
- What's goin' on, man?
- Nada.
I'm good. So this
your man's spot right here?
Yeah, man.
It's tight.
Yeah, right.
So, I don't know,
what's been goin' on?
Everything cool.
Nora's good.
Yeah?
- Andrew quit, though.
- What you mean, he quit?
He got hurt.
He can't dance with her anymore.
Damn.
- I don't know. Whatever.
- Yeah, whatever.
Why don't you stop the bullshit? I bet you
been mopin' around as much as she has.
- She been mopin'?
- I ain't sayin' nothin', man.
- Did you see a tear?
- Nah.
Mopin'.
Shut up. Let me
introduce you to somebody.
- All right, my man C.
- What's up?
My boy Mac.
Mac, this is Miles. Miles, Mac.
I started tearin' up like a little girl tellin'
them that I go to the School of the Arts.
- Wait, hold up. You go to MSA?
- Yeah.
- That's how you know each other?
Yeah, exactly.
You don't look like
no art-school cat to me.
What's an art-school cat
supposed to look like?
Miles Davis, Tupac, Mobb Deep -
those cats went to art school.
- I'm just sayin'...
- You know what? Just shut up.
Yo, what's up, playas?
Yo, yo, yo, what's up? How y'all doin'?
- Skinny, what are you doin' here?
- The same thing you doin' here.
- Let's go. Out the door. No.
- What are you talkin' about?
Hey, move, man, move.
Let me be here, man.
What's wrong with you?
Let's go. Let's go.
Come on, man.
Here. Matter of fact, here.
Here's some bus money. Go home.
Why I gotta leave?
What you talkin' about?
- Your mom'll kill us if she finds you here.
- Go home.
Man, let me in.
Shh...
Man, I'm lookin' all sexy for no reason.
What y'all laughin' at, man?
- What up, Skinny?
- Don't touch me.
- I'll be back. Watch the car.
- Be right here, PJ.
Kick me out the party.
Hey, yo, get me a 40.
- What you got in the bag?
- My music, you know.
Do somethin', then.
- You want me to show 'em somethin'?
- Put it down.
It's nothin', it's nothin'.
- DJ, can I get up on your table real quick?
- Yeah, you cool.
Watch this.
You're supposed to be
watching the car.
Told you to watch the car, man.
Come get me.
# Take the swing, here's your chance
You got nothin' to lose, make your stand
# The clock is tickin'
and time ain't waitin'
# When ya all alone,
that's what you're facin'...
- You see what your brother's doing?
- Who?
Your little brother, man. Come on.
That boy don't listen, man.
What's he doin'?
Yo, Mac, Ty,
bring some girls out here.
That's PJ's truck.
- Skinny, get out of that truck.
- Man, why?
- I said get out.
- Let's go get him.
Man...
Skinny.
Oh, no, no, no, man.
Yo, Skinny, Skinny.
Say something, say something.
Talk. Talk to me.
Yo, call somebody, man!
Do somethin'.
Call 911!
Get up, get up.
Get up, man, get up!
Hey.
How long you been out here?
I don't know.
How's your mom?
She spoke to me
for the first time today.
- You know they got PJ, right?
- That's not gonna bring Skinny back.
- This ain't your fault.
- That don't bring him back either.
I hate seeing you beat yourself up.
I'm beating myself up? We been
beating ourselves up way before Skinny...
Skinny's dead.
He's gone.
My little brother's gone.
And that's on me, Ty.
I know that.
I ain't stupid.
All the partying,
stealing cars, messin' around.
You don't think I know
it's a bunch of bull?
- We're doing the best we can.
- You really believe that?
You really think this is the best we can be?
No.
I wanna be better.
I wanna do better.
You're right.
We gotta do it for my moms, for Skinny.
For Skinny.
Can you do me a favor?
Yeah.
Will you come somewhere with me?
Have a good show tonight.
Hey, Miles. Hey.
What's up?
- Have you heard from Tyler at all?
- Nah, nah.
How's Nora?
- She's good.
- That's cool.
That's cool.
- What was that all about?
- Thanks, I guess, for...
Hey, guys.
- Hey, what's up?
- Hey.
- Miles, you ready?
- Oh, yeah, you know it.
Great. See ya there.
Luce, have a good show tonight.
You too.
Welcome, ladies and gentlemen,
to this very special evening.
The senior showcase is a highlight of our
year at the Maryland School of the Arts.
Ten minutes, everyone.
- You all right?
- Yeah.
Gimme some. Come on.
- Hey, yo, thanks, man.
- Will you go?
Nora.
- What are you doing here?
- Before you say anything...
Shh!
I don't know where to start. I just...
I'm sorry. I shouldn't have
walked out on you like that.
- Tyler, this is not the time.
- Please let me get this out.
I've made every wrong decision
I could possibly have made.
I'm doing this without a partner.
That's enough.
Nora, check your dancers.
Tyler, I don't think
you realize how important this is.
I do realize how important this is.
That's exactly why I'm here.
You said if I want something,
I gotta fight for it. Right?
That's what I'm doing. I'm fighting for
something real for the first time in my life.
I can't do this right now.
This is everything I've worked for.
I know and I'm sorry. I wanted you
to do this the way you imagined it.
That's it.
I can't.
It's too late.
OK.
Um...
Good luck.
Tyler.
Do you remember the steps?
Couldn't forget 'em
even if I wanted to.
OK, everyone, we're back
to the old dance with Tyler.
Yeah!
OK, let's go.
This is the girl
I was telling you about.
OK.
- Excuse me.
- Sure.
# Ah
# I see you, give it to me
# Stop playin', ah
# Stop playin'
# Let's get it goin', unh
# Whoo, yeah
# Let's get it goin' now
# Unh
# Yeah, unh
# A little louder now
# Come on, yeah, unh
# Let's get it poppin' now
# Yeah, come on
# Unh, unh
# Let's go
# I see you, give it to me
# Stop playin', ah
Bravo!
You were so good.
That's right.
Hey, that was good stuff
out there. Worked it.
That was all pretty good.
You seen me dance before.
But not like that. I ain't
never seen you do nothing like that.
- That was her right there.
- That's her?
And over here,
this is Nora Clark.
- Wow, you were wonderful.
- Thank you so much.
I'd like to discuss with you the possibility
of joining our company after graduation.
- I would love that.
- Yeah, me too.
She's everything you said she'd be.
Who's the male lead?
This is Tyler Gage.
He's a transfer.
Oh, my God.
Wait, a what?
- Don't forget to send me your transcripts.
- Yes, ma'am.
- Very well done.
- We'll see you Monday.
We'll see you on Monday.
- Congrats, man.
- Appreciate it.
Let you do your thing.
I'll meet you at the car.
- You know what that means, right?
- No. What's that mean?
- You're gonna have to get some tights.
- Done.
# He said,
"Hi, my name is so and so
# "Baby, can you tell me yours?
# "You look like
you came to do one thing"
- # Set it off
- # I started on the left
# And I had to take him to the right
# He was out of breath
# But he kept on dancin' all night
# You tryin', admit it
# But you just can't fight the feelin' inside
# You know it
# And I can see it in your eyes
# You want me
# You smooth as a mother
# You're so undercover
# By the way that you was watchin' me
# Ooh, uh
# The way you look at me.
I'm feelin' you, uh
# I just can't help it,
tryin' to keep it cool, uh
# I can feel it in the beat, uh
# When you do those things to me, uh
# Don't let nothin' stop you
# Move
# Ring the alarm
# The club is jumpin' now, so get up
# I said, "Ciara's on your radio
# "Everybody turn it up"
# Spicy just like hot sauce
# Careful, you might burn it up
# You can do the pop-lock,
ragtop, don't stop
# That's the way you gotta get
Get it, make ya body rock
# You tryin', admit it
# But you just can't beat
the feelin' inside
# You know it
'cause I can see it in your eyes
# You want me,
you smooth as a mother
# You're so undercover
# By the way that you was watchin' me
# Ooh, uh
# The way you look at me,
I'm feelin' you, uh
# I just can't help it,
tryin' to keep it cool, uh
# I can feel it in the beat, uh
# When you do those things to me, uh
# Don't let nothin' stop you
# Move
# Ring the alarm
# The club is jumpin' now, so get up
# Ooh, I love the way you vibe with me
# Dance with me forever
# We can have a good time
# Follow me
# To the beat together
# You and me, one on one
# Breakin' it down
# You can't walk away now
# We got to turn this place out, oh
# It's the kids, ridin' big
The police tried to catch ridin' dirty
# In the club before eleven o'clock
Like I'm tryin' to catch it down kinda early
# Her hair, brown and curly
She love the way my ride shinin' pearly
# City boys say she fine and pretty
Country boys say she fine and purty
# My pockets thick as green, it's curvy
Ladies know soon as they see my jewelry
# If bein' fresh is a crime,
I think it's time for me to see the jury
# Chamillionaire stay on the grind,
a hustler like me is hard to find
# I ain't really impressed, yes,
unless it's about some dollar sign
# Ain't no need to call you fine
I know you be hearin' that all the time
# I'm watchin' you do ya step, do ya step
# Yep, it's goin' down
# Ooh, uh
# The way you look at me,
I'm feelin' you, uh
# I just can't help it,
tryin' to keep it cool, uh
# I can feel it in the beat, uh
# When you do those things to me, uh
# Don't let nothin' stop you
# Move
# Ring the alarm
# The club is jumpin' now, so get up
# Ooh, uh
# The way you look at me,
I'm feelin' you, uh
# I just can't help it,
tryin' to keep it cool, uh
# I can feel it in the beat, uh
When you do those things to me, uh
# Don't let nothin' stop you
# Move
# Somebody ring the alarm
# The club is jumpin' now, so get up