This is how we battIe.
This is how it goes down.
Everybody put your hands in the air.
Get your hands up right now.
Let's get it pumping.
Let's go.
Watch Movies, TV Series and Live Sports
Signup Here -> WWW.ADMITME.APP
Come on.
Hey, hey, hey. HoId up, hoId up.
Ain't no fighting in my house.
We do it cIean around here
or we don't do it.
Get on out of here, man.
Anybody want some? We're taking
aII money and aII bets right here.
Anybody want some? Come get some.
Anybody want some, right?
C KiIIuh has entered the buiIding
with his money in hand.
Chance, money in hand.
Let's get it.
Hey. What? What? What?
What?
Mistakes count. Mistakes count.
Chance, it's over for you, man.
-Get off.
-Y'aII know how it goes.
We got a new champion in the house.
-Everybody say, ''C KiIIuh.''
-C KiIIuh!
Anybody want some? Come get some.
Somebody, anybody.
Somebody. You want some?
Anybody want some?
HoId up. What's up? What's up?
What's going on?
I ain't going out Iike that.
What's the matter?
You didn't get enough the first time?
So I suggest you pay up
and go back to where you came from.
One more time.
DoubIe or nothing.
Anybody want doubIe or nothing?
Make some noise.
Money in the bucket.
Put your hands up right now.
The moment of truth.
If y'aII think Chance took it home,
make some noise right now.
If y'aII think C KiIIuh took it home
and represented, make some noise.
The jury has spoken.
So this is gonna be
how it's gonna go down.
The winner tonight
is my boy Craig KiIIuh, C KiIIuh.
C KiIIuh again. He beat him, baby.
It's over.
He knocked the Rock Star off
his pedestaI and took him to schooI.
Where's my money?
Man, I don't owe you no money.
You guys Iost and you know it.
That's your probIem, not mine.
How you wanna handIe this?
AII right, aII right, aII right.
I'II give you the money.
I just need some time.
I was gonna use that money
for schooI.
Man, you mean to teII me
you're out here dancing for tuition?
Get him out.
Look, Iet me expIain how things work
around here.
If I don't have my money by tomorrow,
you're gonna come up missing.
You hear me, boy?
-I think he needs some more.
-No, aII right. I got you. I'II get you--
Get down! Get down!
-Hey!
-Let's get out of here, man.
-Watch out.
-Watch out, man.
-Go, get the wheeIs.
-Go.
-What now?
-What you mean, what now?
This town ain't so big.
We gonna bump into him.
I'm gonna get my damn money.
Two catfish combo,
one catfish and shrimp combo...
...and the six-piece with...?
-Mac and cheese.
-Mac and cheese, okay.
Here, Shorty.
Hey, Chance,
I may need you to work tonight.
I can't, my Iine is up tonight.
I toId you that. Not that you Iisten.
Look...
...I'm moving into the Theta house,
and so is Wynn.
Boy, you move around more
than a brother at a KIan raIIy.
Just moved back in
and you're moving out aIready.
It's not Iike that.
I'm just moving right down the street.
Whatever. I'm here to stay this time,
so don't you go trying to get rid of me.
Look, Pop, just hear me out, okay?
I reaIIy wanna do this. I joined a team.
-I'm putting them moves to use.
-Sounds Iike a distraction.
You promised when you came home
your focus wouId be education.
It is.
That's what I'm trying to teII you.
Make sure you can handIe everything
on your pIate...
...incIuding this restaurant.
He's just happy you're home again,
sweetie.
Nice way of showing it.
-I want the Iobster.
-I am so hungry.
-I'm teIIing you, I thought it was a joke.
-What do we have here?
-Hey, Chance.
What can I get you fine young Iadies?
-Okay. Let's go get--
-Hey, can I take a picture of y'aII?
-I want Santa to know what I want.
-Look, your order's coming right up.
What's wrong with you, Wynn?
Are you done frying up
Sunday's dinner yet?
-Dude, it's time to roII, bro.
-Since when you in a rush to cIass?
Since campus started Iooking
Iike a NeIIy video.
-I'm trying to be a featured extra.
-Hey, Chance.
I need you to come earIy tomorrow
to open up.
Dad, I aIready toId you,
it's homecoming weekend.
How many times
we have this conversation?
Homecoming is the busiest weekend
of the season. We need the money.
AII right. I'II be here.
-Let's go.
-EarIy.
Hey, Mr. Harris, Iove that sweater.
You Iadies enjoy. You Iadies be good.
-Come on, Iet's go.
-I'm out.
Hey, man, check this out.
Five thousand doIIars
and a fuII schoIarship.
Bro, we have to win the step-off
this weekend.
-Dude, I'm teIIing you, man.
-Oh, yeah. Oh, yeah.
-Dane.
-Hey, what's up, feIIas?
-What's going on?
-ChiIIing.
-Everything KooI & the Gang?
-Yeah.
-Most definiteIy.
-Just getting hyped for tonight.
Know what I'm saying?
You know we gotta represent
for your senior year. Touch.
I need you to get controI
of your brother.
-Y'aII aren't Thetas yet.
-I got you.
Homecoming, baby.
Hope they're ready for big Ty....
Hi. How you doing, big brother--?
Dane?
-How are you, sir?
-LAX, my man. You aII right?
-What's up, son?
-How are you?
-You focused?
-I'm focused.
-Ready to get it in, man.
-Okay.
I'm gonna check y'aII Iater, aII right?
-Yeah, do your thing.
-AII right?
-What's going on with that cIass?
-The cIass--?
Oh, the cIass
I was teIIing you about. Fine.
Everything is good. I went Iast week.
I mean,
I'm about to go this week as weII.
Guess who.
-WiII Smith.
-You-- See, you think you're funny.
Trying to hurt my feeIings?
You were supposed to meet me
after cIass.
Right, my bad.
I was saying what's up to the guys.
Oh, aIready putting the guys
before your girI?
No. Come here, I miss you.
You nervous about coming up tonight?
Because I know it means a Iot to you.
Who, me? Nervous?
What I got to be nervous about?
-Let's go.
-I gotta get my sweater, I'm freezing.
Don't worry about it,
I'II meet you there.
Babe, you know, I couId just go
and get Brenda for you if you'd Iike.
Come on.
I wasn't checking for that broad.
Good. You better not be.
-Let's get out of here.
-Yeah.
Yeah. We gotta get ready
for the big night.
Let's go.
Let's hear it, Truth University!
Yes, yes, yes!
As president of Truth University,
it is my pIeasure to weIcome aIumni...
...to another homecoming weekend.
Yeah!
Some have traveIed from far and wide
to be here.
I promise you won't be disappointed...
...because this Sunday,
Truth University...
...wiII host the nationaI
Sprite Step Off competition.
Now, winning teams
wiII receive fuII schoIarships...
...for each team member.
-AII right!
-That sound good?
Yeah!
It gives me great pIeasure to introduce
our new brothers from Theta Nu Theta.
Y'all got to keep up
To keep up
This time we take
the show on the road
That's what Theta came to do
Somebody told you that you can
go by the easy road
-Let's go.
-Nobody told me, nobody told me
But / got, got, got to get to Thetaland
Because the road to Thetaland
is long, rough and rugged
-/t takes a hell of man to make it
-HoId tight in position, come on.
-I can't hear you.
-Ty. Right here.
-Come on.
-AII right, Bryce!
Get yourself off the road
because Theta came through
Yeah!
HoId it tight, yo.
About-face.
-Come on, tighten up.
-AII right, Bryce!
Thetas, reveaI yourseIves.
-Theta greeting.
-Theta greeting!
Please be advised Theta Nu
came to serve you our best, sir
Who wants to come and get down?
All the way down.
Who wants to be served?
What? What? What?
No protection from the truth
Peace be with us
How may we serve you?
Oh, yeah. Oh, yeah.
This work's making me hungry.
I think I want a Coke, a Big Mac
and a what?
SmaII Fry!
-Get it.
-Yeah!
SmaII Fry!
Oh, yeah.
TaIk to them.
PAC-MAN.
Running after these Iadies
as fast as I can.
You supposed to be Theta?
Oh, yeah.
You gangster Iike that?
My right.
TeII them how you feeI.
They caII me LAX
because I stay fIy.
-Yeah, Ty!
-LAX.
Theta what?
-Theta Nu! Theta Nu!
-What?
-Theta Nu!
-Theta what?
Theta Nu.
Y'aII see this? Y'aII see it?
Who's next? Who's next?
-FeeI Iike rocking out?
-Let's do it.
-AII right, Chance.
-Rock out.
-Rock Star!
-Chance!
Yeah.
-Oh, yeah.
-Rock Star!
Yeah.
-Yeah!
-Yeah, boy.
-Rock Star!
It's the new brothers
of Theta Nu Theta.
Yes, honey!
-Get out of here!
-Get back.
Yo, bro.
Mu.
-Oh, get out of here!
-Mu.
Come on, man.
Mu.
Mu Gamma Xi.
We are the outstanding brothers
of Mu Gamma Xi.
We rep where we go
till the day that we die.
Get off my back.
Mu Gamma.
Mu Gamma, Mu, Mu, Mu.
Yo, Craig.
Mu Gamma Xi.
You must think you're Superman,
thinking you can come upstage us.
This is how you wanna
start the weekend?
-CouIdn't wait tiII Sunday, Taz?
-That's how I feeI.
Face it, Dane, you're gonna Iose.
You're gonna Iose huge.
Yeah. It's been two years.
When you graduate, they're
gonna remember you as a faiIure.
Yo, Taz. Taz.
-What you gonna beat us with, man?
-Hey.
-HoId your Iine.
-Threats?
Yeah, Chance, hoId your Iine.
That's your new mascot, right?
Is that who that is?
Oh, the Rock Star, huh?
We've heard him speak.
He do other tricks?
Yo, I got your trick. You want--?
You need to caIm down.
-CaIm down.
-Oh, he gets mad.
You need to be cooI.
Steady, steady. Y'aII be cooI.
-ReIax.
-No, be cooI.
-Ease up.
-He gets mad, huh?
-There we go.
-Be cooI.
-M-U!
-Gamma Xi!
Come on, man.
Theta what?
Theta Nu.
I Iove this!
Show-stopping.
I can't wait to win
one of these bad boys on Sunday.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, man.
Put this thing down.
We gonna have one
soon enough, kid.
-Yes, yes, yes.
-Soon enough.
-Yo, I'm not so sure.
-What?
There's a reason
why we haven't won one since then.
Mus were better tonight.
I mean,
they had some hot moves, man.
They did.
If we don't step our game up,
we're gonna get destroyed on Sunday.
We can say goodbye
to the schoIarship and the money.
Don't know about y'aII,
but I couId use it.
Tuition is crazy, but no way we're
gonna get Dane to change the routine.
But why not?
Why not? I mean, think about it.
Theta's been doing the same routine
since before I Ieft Truth Iast year.
-I can come up with something better.
-ReaIIy, Chance? ReaIIy?
We just got the frat. We just got in--
Hey, Roy, what's going on, man?
We just got into the frat.
You wanna rock the boat?
Come on, man, that's not a good Iook.
It's not. It's not.
One thing's for sure, we're gonna Iose
if you keep stepping on my feet.
Man, forget aII of that.
TeII Nikki to hook us up
with her sorors.
-Pass the baII. Pass the baII.
-No. I'II be right back.
-Come on, stop being greedy.
-Jeez.
Theta what?
-Theta Nu.
-What's up, baby?
-Come here, baby.
I can't stick around...
...because I gotta check on the fIoats
for homecoming.
But I wanted to say congratuIations.
You were amazing.
WeII, I do what I can do.
AII right, aII right,
don't get aII gassed.
I'II see you Iater, right?
Of course.
Okay.
-Let's go.
-AII right.
Hey, can I taIk to you for a second?
What's up?
What happened at the pep raIIy earIier
was unacceptabIe.
And I think you know that.
I wasn't gonna stand back
and watch Taz disrespect us.
But what you did was disrespectfuI
to me and to the frat.
Look, Chance, you're a Theta now,
and we expect a Iot more from you.
BeIieve me, nobody wants
to outdo Taz more than I do.
You Iet me handIe him. Understand?
My man.
-Fellas, keep form.
-All right.
I wanna hear it. I wanna hear it.
Are you kidding me?
That's aII you got?
-I'm trying.
-Not trying hard enough.
We have untiI Sunday, you guys,
to get that routine together. Okay?
Or we're gonna Iose.
Is that what you want?
-We're gonna Iose anyway.
-I'm sorry, you say something?
I didn't hear you.
You got something to say?
Do you have something to say, neo?
-The Mus were dope the other night.
-I don't give a damn about the Mus.
If you have a point, damn it,
you better make it.
Look, a few of us was thinking
that maybe...
...we shouId step our game up
a IittIe bit.
-We doing the stuff from Iast year.
-So now what?
-Maybe I shouId just show you.
-Yeah, maybe you shouId.
Dane. Dane,
we don't got time for this, man.
No, no, be cooI, boy.
Let the boy have the fIoor.
Let's see what he's made of.
AII right.
We couId stiII incorporate
the same moves from our Iast routine...
...but it doesn't hurt
to have a ace up our sIeeves.
For those of you who wanna
incorporate Chance's choreography...
...into the routine, raise your hands.
Looks Iike you guys
better get started.
-Yeah, thank you. AII right.
-Oh, yeah.
You gonna put our fate
in the hands of a neo?
I'II be damned if I Iet Taz win this.
Maybe he can give us the edge
that we need.
That's aII I'm saying.
I hope you're right.
Yes, yes, yes.
Show me what you got there, man.
That's it.
I didn't caII a break.
You got a routine, you better show it.
-AII right.
-So Iet's go, Iet's go.
-Morning, Terry.
-Hey, Shorty.
-Chance in yet?
-Course not.
One more time. Wynn, stay with me.
Remember that right Ieg.
AII right, y'aII, one more time.
DaredeviI, I see you. Right Ieg.
-One more time. AII right, come on.
-No, no, no.
That's enough, that's enough.
Yo, so good job.
I admit it stiII needs a IittIe bit of work.
Don't think this gets you off the hook.
StiII have community service
this afternoon.
On homecoming weekend?
Come on.
-Thought it was aII about stepping?
-And girIs.
Learn to step,
get as many girIs as you want.
Come on, Iet's go. I'II see y'aII Iater.
-Yo, what time is it?
-It's 1 1 :00.
Damn. I gotta go.
-Good morning, come on in.
-Good morning.
Janice. AII right.
Nice to see you. Good morning.
Come in. I don't even wanna hear it.
Come on. Get ready.
Dad, practice ran over. I'm sorry.
-Dad, I said I was sorry.
-Look, Chance, I don't wanna hear it.
I aIready toId you how important this
weekend is, didn't I? Just get ready.
-Here you go.
-Thank you.
You guys enjoy.
Chance, my office, now.
Sit down.
Look...
...you didn't re-enroII in Truth
just to sIack off.
SIack off?
I'm here every day
trying to heIp you out.
I'm entering the show
so I can win schoIarship money.
That frat is not a priority.
Look...
...when your mom died...
...you ran out of here
with no money and no pIan.
You Ieft me
to handIe this restaurant.
Now that you're back home, I wanna
see you take some responsibiIity...
...to see this thing through.
I'm not trying to run your Iife.
I've aIways tried
to be supportive of you.
Now I need you
to be supportive of me.
-Pi.
-Delta.
Pi Delta Mu step.
I gotta admit, man, your girI
is getting it in right now, Chance.
She Iooking kind of fIy too.
AII these fIy honeys here,
and you gotta check out my girI.
What's the matter, man?
You worried about aII this big Wynn?
Don't do that. And I'm good.
I ain't worried about nothing.
-Come on.
-Maybe you shouId, dude.
-Homewrecker, 7 o'cIock.
-Hi.
Man, you better run.
We are the Pi DeIta Mus, and not onIy
are we smart and beautifuI...
...we aIso know
how to get down and dirty.
My girIs are about to show you
something y'aII need to see.
-Pi Delta Mu step.
-Chance.
Pi Delta Mu step.
Aren't you happy to see me?
Slow it down.
Come on.
-Get it, girIs.
-She's cuter than Iast year.
-Is it serious?
-What do you want, Brenda?
I don't know.
You're just kind of on my mind.
I never got a chance to expIain myseIf.
Hey, hey, hey.
It's been a year.
Why now?
Because it's not the same
without you.
I kind of miss you and me.
You know...
...me and you did have
some good times.
Wasn't aII easy saiIing.
You see,
when I needed you the most...
...you wasn't even there.
Too busy hooking up with Taz
to notice.
I deserve that. I do.
But when your mom died,
you shut me out.
And then you transferred schooIs
in FIorida.
What was I supposed to do?
You know,
you're a reaI piece of work.
Everybody makes mistakes,
Chance.
Same number, right?
-Hey, babe.
-Hey.
-Did you see us?
-You guys did good.
-Yeah?
-Yeah.
-How good?
-ReaI good.
-Proud?
-ReaI proud. Let's go, baby.
Okay.
CouId you just drop me
at the stadium?
I gotta check on some stuff
for the game.
Of course.
I was on the way to Ashby anyway.
Ashby? For what?
I got a IittIe community-service gig.
AII the neos have to do it.
Look at you, getting invoIved.
I thought you were too cooI for that.
Chance.
Yo, man, watch it.
-What's wrong?
-Nothing.
-Nothing? You aImost ran a stop sign.
-Look, reIax, okay?
I'm just a IittIe nervous, baby.
That's it.
Okay?
Now, Iet's get out of here.
If I'm Iate, I have to hear from Dane.
I must say, man, the way you got
at Dane this morning...
...that was kind of gangster, man.
Now you're just gonna have to
foIIow through.
-What's that supposed to mean?
-You got Dane to change the routine.
That's big. Just think about it.
If we win on Sunday,
oh, we be Iiving Iegends, man.
WeII, weII...
...if it isn't the Thetas' new mascot
and his sidekick, OId YeIIer.
I know you ain't taIking
with aII that possum around your neck.
You know what?
Your jokes couId use an upgrade.
They're getting kind of oId.
Yeah, kind of Iike them dance steps
you do.
You spit a good game at the raIIy,
but I hope you can back that up.
Last night was just a taste
of what I'm bringing.
When it's aII said and done...
...we'II see who waIks away
with the trophy and the money.
Me.
Trophy on one arm
and your girI on the next.
Because she'II reaIize you're a sucker,
kind of Iike Brenda did.
It sucks, but these things happen,
you know?
-You see that?
-Yeah.
You taIking about that Brenda?
Oh, wait, wait.
-Now, that sucks.
-Hey.
-It ain't worth it.
-That sucks. It does. Sucks.
Now we gonna get back to work.
You feIIas have a good day.
Hey, you gonna heIp us cIean up?
Come on, we need aII the heIp
we can get.
Come on.
It's homecoming weekend.
Truth University, make some noise.
Yeah.
Can't see me. Can't see me.
Can't see me.
Wow, aII right, aII right, aII right.
Okay.
Yo.
We got some bumping and grinding
going on down there.
Somebody is trying to get
some homecoming nookie.
What are you doing?
Come on, man.
Yo, Chance.
You had a Iot of mouth earIier.
Ready to back up that trash
you were taIking?
Yo, yo, yo, you guys
reaIIy wanna do this right now?
Oh, my bad. I mean,
he was just bragging pretty hard.
I just figured he might need a chance
to warm up.
-Is that right?
-Yeah, that's right.
We got nothing to prove.
We good here.
-Come on, Iet's get a drink.
-Yeah, I figured as much, man.
But, you know, whenever you're ready
to Iet the dog off the Ieash....
-I think I'm ready now.
-Chance.
-No, no, no. Let's go.
-Yeah.
You're gonna do this now?
HoId up. I'm seeing
an impromptu battIe jumping off.
Theta versus Mus.
Keep it peacefuI.
This is homecoming, y'aII.
This is homecoming, remember?
Hey, yo. Yo. Hey, yo, chiII.
-Hey, man.
-Hey, watch out.
-Yo, this ain't over.
-Damn right, you sorry-ass Ioser.
-Get off.
-What's wrong with you?
-I mean, come on.
-Man.
Give me my hat.
Where my keys at?
-Don't Iook over here.
-Sorry, my bad.
Chance, what are you trying to prove?
God, you are kiIIing me.
Check it out.
We aII have to be on that stage
Sunday.
Take your revenge out there.
Get in the car.
I Ieft my sweater inside.
Honey, did you see
how they was dancing at that party?
-This day, I can't even deaI.
-ReaIIy.
Why you didn't teII me
my eyebrows was Iooking crazy?
I need serious tweezing.
-It's Wynn.
-Serious tweezing, honey.
Look your phone ain't here, aII right?
What was your deaI earIier, man?
It'd be nice if you'd think of the frat...
...before you show
how to make us aII Iook crazy.
-Honey, what is it?
-Text from Brenda.
Oh, heII, no, Nikki.
-Like, for reaI, caII her right now.
-Rena, I'm not gonna caII her.
-One more time.
-Your phone is not here.
-And I promise this is it.
-Yo, your girI's outside.
You found my phone.
That's why you my--
What's wrong?
Who were you tonight?
-Because it's not the Chance I know.
-Look, I know. And I'm sorry.
I guess it's true what they say.
You never reaIIy know a person, huh?
I mean, baby,
it's reaIIy not that serious, okay? I--
Chance, you toId me
you were over Brenda.
Look, how many times
do I have to teII you?
I'm not thinking about that girI.
I want nothing to do with her.
I saw the texts, Chance.
You're saying
you went through my phone?
-You Iied to me.
-I didn't Iie to you.
Brenda pushed up on me.
And I toId her--
ToId her what, Chance?
You toId her no?
Or maybe?
Know what?
-Maybe I'm not good enough for you.
-Don't--
No, no, no. Because ever since
day one, you never trusted me.
Don't you dare.
Don't you dare turn this around on me,
because this is about you.
Your inabiIity to make a decision
about what you want.
You're the new hot thing on campus
and everybody wants a piece, right?
WeII, I refuse to pIay second fiddIe
to any girI.
I'm sorry.
Look, I don't know what eIse to say.
-HeIIo?
-You busy?
No. Why?
I was thinking
we couId have that conversation.
/n person.
-Where's Taz?
-Where's Nikki?
/'m outside.
Don't you ever wonder
what that wouId be Iike?
If you hadn't Ieft?
It's a party, y'aII.
Not me.
What's up, pIayboy?
Let me hoIIer at you for a minute.
-Yeah, what's up?
-I was Iooking for Chance.
He's not here.
You think I'm pIaying with you,
partner?
WeII, this here be Theta property.
I think you got the wrong house.
I said,
I get it.
Get him.
-Yo, I got your back.
-Man, don't--
Yo, what?
Dane, come on, man.
-Come on.
-Let's go!
Come on, dude.
-I said, Iet's go!
-Let's get out of here.
Oh, my God.
What's up? You aII right?
Come on, baby, taIk to me.
TaIk to me, baby.
Ty, go in the house, go in the house.
Get some heIp.
What's the matter?
I can't do this.
-This ain't right.
-You know what?
You can...
...because it is right...
...and easy.
I aIready know...
...everything you Iike.
HeIIo?
Dane?
HoId on, so y'aII teIIing me
they tried us right on our front yard?
Y'aII know how Iame
that makes us Iook?
-Yo, what the--?
-Ain't no way--
Whoa, yo!
Guys, cooI out.
Let me think this through.
What happened?
Yo, Wynn, you okay?
Yeah, I'm aII right.
I'm on my way to the hospitaI now.
I sure hope that doctor's cute.
These guys came to the house
Iooking for you.
You have any idea who they were?
How the heII wouId I know?
I wasn't here.
ReaIIy? Because they came
asking for you by name.
Why the heII wouId somebody
wanna come after you?
Man, I don't know.
But it couId've been anybody.
-ProbabIy one of Taz's boys.
-These cats were straight hood.
-Straight up.
-Yeah.
Yeah, he Iied about it, but I kind
of think you overreacted a IittIe bit.
You know Brenda. I honestIy think
she's just chasing after him.
-WeII, he's not running.
-That don't mean he did anything.
Come on. You seen her
at that party the other night.
She was jocking him kind of hard.
And I'm Ietting you know now...
...it ain't the first time
and won't be the Iast.
Why'd he Iie
if he wasn't doing anything wrong?
Because he's a man, sweet cakes.
That's just what men do.
AII right, Iook.
Give it some time...
...see how the weekend goes,
and he'II come around.
I trust you.
Cheers.
Yo, Rock Star.
-AII right?
-Yeah, fine.
You shouId see him, though,
you know?
What's up?
Have to teII you something.
CoupIe of weeks ago,
I got hustIed at a dance battIe.
Now they're gunning for me.
Are you trying to teII me that this...
...is because of you?
So why didn't you say anything?
I don't know.
I guess-- I guess I was scared
to get kicked off the team.
I reaIIy, reaIIy needed to win
this competition.
Are you serious?
That's what you're worried about?
I mean, you've aIways been
kind of seIfish, but this is ridicuIous.
Something about you changed.
My whoIe Iife has changed.
Ever since my mom died, I--
Don't put this on your mother.
Don't.
Everything has aIways been
about Chance Harris.
And it's been that way
since we were IittIe.
I'm your boy, Chance.
You shouId've come to me.
-Hey.
-Hey, girI.
So I heard there was, Iike, a huge fight
at the Theta house Iast night.
The IittIe dude you was dancing with
at the cIub Iast night, where he at?
Do I know you?
I reaIIy thought you coIIege boys
was a IittIe bit smarter than that.
-Answer the damn question.
-What you want with him?
-Anybody hurt?
-Wynn got himseIf beat up.
It reaIIy ain't none of your business.
But Iet's just say he owe me.
-What about Chance?
-I don't know.
You Iike catfish?
What are you doing here?
I thought you shouId be home
resting up.
And miss my first game as a Theta?
Come on, man.
I thought it'd be nice
if my best homey wouId roII with me.
PIus it's hard
for a handicapped brother.
I couIdn't get one honey.
Just one honey
to just heIp your boy out, I swear.
-StiII ain't got that boy Iaid yet?
-Oh, reaIIy, Shorty? ReaIIy?
That's what we're doing?
It's not that simpIe.
Don't ruin your homecoming weekend
pining over some guy.
-It screams desperation.
-You're the one that has me worried.
You toId me
something happened to him.
Don't worry about Chance. He's fine.
-Excuse me?
-He's fine.
It's a good thing he wasn't at
the house when the fight went down.
-And how do you know that?
-Because he was with me.
Why you Iet that girI get to you? She
get her Iife making peopIe miserabIe.
-She's doing a good job.
-That's not the point.
Damn, man,
you came kind of deep this year.
Ladies.
Man, Iook,
can you pIease hoId up, man?
I couId use some heIp.
This is not cooI.
Hey. Nikki, baby.
-I wanna taIk to you.
-No. Don't ''baby'' me.
CongratuIations,
you finaIIy made a choice.
Nikki. Nikki!
Can I heIp you?
-We're Iooking for Chance.
-What you want with him?
-Go back and see if he in the back.
-Y'aII can't go there.
-Move, Iady.
-He's not here.
-I'm gonna have to ask y'aII to Ieave.
This pIace is fiIthy.
I think you guys shouId cIean it up.
-Yo, what's going on here?
-Chance.
You aII right? Go outside. Go outside.
Yo, you came after my peopIe, dawg.
-That shit wasn't necessary.
-ActuaIIy, I came for you.
-Where's my money, Chance?
-Look, I don't owe you no money.
I toId you that. You know this.
You pIayed in the streets.
You made the bet.
So either you have my money...
...or you don't.
Hey, hey, hey! AII right, aII right.
Give me tiII Sunday
after the competition.
I'II get you your money.
-Think that's good enough?
-Just give me tiII Sunday.
Now, hoId on, hoId on, hoId on.
Let him go.
So Iet me ask you a question.
What makes you think you can win?
Look, just trust me, I got this.
Word on campus
is the Mus are gonna win.
That's who I got my money on.
Is y'aII betting on a stepping?
But now you're taIking
about messing aII that up.
Tomorrow the Thetas better Iose.
You don't have a choice, fish boy.
Let's go.
-Are you aII right, Chance?
-I'm okay, I'm okay. I'm good.
What happened?
My pIace is ruined.
-/'m gonna fix this.
-Fix what?
-/ got into trouble.
-Trouble?
-Dance battIe. These guys hustIed me.
-You know these peopIe?
-Yes.
-What did you get into?
-TroubIe.
-You have to do with this?
Yes. I'm trying to teII you--
-What are you trying to teII me?
-You never Iisten.
That's why I don't come to you.
I said I'II fix it, I'm gonna.
You're gonna fix what?
What are you gonna fix, Chance?
What are you gonna fix?
Yo, Thetas, Iook who I found. DJ!
-DJ.
Theta!
What's up, man? Good to see you.
-Good to see you, brother.
-Yo, I'm gIad you made it.
-Hey, what's up, neo? That's my chair.
-That's a Iegend right there.
-What you been up to?
-Man, working, man.
StruggIing, striving, grinding.
-You know, you know.
-Oh, yeah.
Chance. Look who feII through.
-DJ?
-Last time I checked.
-What's up?
-What you doing here?
Came to check you out, make sure
Dane's preserving the Iegacy.
Come on,
you know I'm hoIding it down.
Yeah, and I'm hoIding down
your mama, so we good.
-You too?
-Me too.
SeriousIy, man,
I'm excited to see you on Sunday.
My man Chance, he heIped us freak
the routine for Sunday's competition.
-Gonna be hot.
-That's what I Iike to hear.
ActuaIIy, that's what I wanna taIk
to you guys about.
Yo, what you taIking about?
A few weeks ago, I got hustIed
at a dance battIe, 5 grand.
So everything that happened Iast night
was because of me.
They're gonna come after me
if I don't throw the competition.
Look, I never meant to get you guys
invoIved in this mess, and I'm sorry.
EspeciaIIy to you, Wynn.
And you never thought
to say something before?
-Maybe we couId've done something.
-Like what?
Pay them off? Fight them?
No, I'm good.
-HandIe it myseIf.
-You don't have that choice, Chance.
Wynn is hurt, and we're supposed
to go out and Iose to save your ass?
No. I never intended
on throwing the competition.
I understand how important
this competition is to you.
Chance, it's not about me.
It's about the team.
I can see how much damage
I've caused here.
I've done more harm than good.
-Maybe I shouId just quit.
-We don't need him. Never did.
Listen, we changed the entire routine
because of you.
There's no way
you can do this to us.
Dane, teII him
he doesn't have to Ieave.
I got it.
Rock Star, hoId up.
Now, emotions are cIearIy high
right now.
So I gotta Iet the brother
do what he's gotta do, period.
It's another day.
And y'aII are stiII famiIy.
That's what matters.
-Theta what?
-Theta Nu.
There it is.
Keep your head up, brother.
AII right, y'aII.
-DJ, be good, man.
-Peace out.
-Yo.
-AII right.
Figured I'd find you here.
I caught Wynn and Dane
on their way to practice.
They toId me everything.
I came to see if you were okay.
I'm good.
WeII, why aren't you at practice?
Because I just can't do
the competition right now.
What you mean
is you don't want to do this right now.
I reaIIy do care about you.
And I'm not the onIy one.
But that doesn't seem
to mean anything to you.
-Come on, Nikki. That's not even fair.
-Not fair is turning your back...
-...on peopIe that beIieved in you.
-I don't wanna Iose you, okay?
-I don't wanna Iose you.
-Then don't.
Come on, y'aII,
check up, check up, check up.
Now, I know a Iot has happened
in the Iast coupIe days.
We can't worry about that now.
We worry about who's here.
Don't worry about who's not. Who's on
this roof, that's what's important.
I'm gonna teII you right now,
this competition stiII matters.
Now, I'm hard on you guys
because I want you to be the best.
I need you guys to focus.
I'm taIking about razor-bIade-precision
focus, you understand?
We Thetas. So Iet's get it.
Roy, take us home.
Yeah.
Gonna make you proud, man.
Make you proud.
Let's go. Do it.
I Iike what I'm seeing, dawgs.
Top row, Iet that beast out, Iet's go.
Yeah. I want it in the bag.
We are the heart of the party, TN T.
Smashing all you brothers
with a beat.
Okay.
What up, Atlanta?
Your boy DJ Will Power here...
...where we keep you
popping and locking.
Step-off Sunday is finally here.
We've been talking about it.
We've been waiting.
Truth University, you are the host
of the Sprite Step Off Championship.
Teams come
from all over this country...
...to be crowned
the national step champion...
...and to win thousands of dollars
in cash and scholarships.
Better have brought their A game.
This homecoming, Truth,
will be one to remember.
-Hey.
Dane.
Where's your Rock Star?
Don't worry about it, okay, Taz?
Do you.
-AII right. AII right.
-Do you.
Truth University, make some noise!
Yeah!
And now we wanna weIcome y'aII
to our annuaI step show, man...
...brought to you by Sprite.
Tonight, man,
we giving away thousands of doIIars...
...in schoIarships, cash and prizes.
Yo, it's showtime.
It aII comes down to this,
what we do out on that stage.
I know we had a Iot of setbacks.
So what? That's why we're here.
And that's why we're Thetas.
And I'm proud to caII every one of you
my brothers.
We're repping Theta.
Thetas, Thetas.
We're repping Thetas.
Thetas, Thetas. We're repping:
Coming through.
Truth.
AII right, Iadies and gentIemen...
...y'aII ready to do this?
Give it up for Iast year's champion,
Mu Gamma Xi.
Mu Gamma Xi! Mu Gamma Xi!
Mu Gamma Xi!
Truth University, make some noise.
Ten teams started,
but onIy two made it to the finaI round.
AII right, y'aII ready?
Y'aII give it up
for Iast year's champion...
...Mu Gamma Xi.
AII right.
Give it up for our second finaIist.
PIease weIcome back
a hometown favorite...
...Theta Nu Theta.
-I'II give you two a moment.
-Thanks.
Look, I'm-- I'm sorry.
I know.
At Ieast nobody got hurt.
You know,
I'm worried about you, son.
I know I was pretty hard on you
Iast night, but we aII make mistakes.
Part of being a man is owning up
to your mistakes.
I didn't know how to be there for you.
The onIy thing I knew how to do
was work, and that's what I did.
And I was wrong.
I don't ever wanna
push you away again.
You have the right to choose
your own path whether I Iike it or not.
And I need you to know
and feeI comfortabIe to come to me...
...with whatever you need.
You're aII I have Ieft.
That's exactIy why I came back.
I beIong here,
and I ain't going anywhere.
Not again.
I stiII got so much to fix.
I gotta pay these guys,
make things up to Nikki.
-I don't even know where to start.
-You might start with that competition.
Since when do you care
about the competition?
I don't care about the competition.
I care about my son.
Do you care enough
to come watch me?
Yeah.
AII right, y'aII.
Put your hands together.
Make some noise
for Truth University's own...
...Mu Gamma Xi.
Yeah!
-AII right!
-Mu Gamma Xi!
M-U G-A-M-M-A X-/, step.
Mu Gamma.
Mu Gamma Xi.
M-U Gamma Xi.
Hey, ho, hey, ho.
We'll show you how the Gammas go.
Sing it.
You can't touch Mu Gamma Xi.
Mu.
Mu Gamma Xi.
Come on, ya'II, Iet me hear it again
for Mu Gamma Xi.
Mu Gamma Xi!
Mu Gamma Xi! Mu....
This is it.
It's time to go to battIe.
I've been in your shoes.
Those very same boots.
I ain't gonna Iie to you.
Ain't gonna be easy.
Ain't gonna be no cakewaIk.
But you guys have a choice.
You can go out there and give them
exactIy what they expect...
...for the Thetas to Iose again...
...or you can Iook
to the man next to you...
...and you can decide as a team...
...that you're gonna prove them wrong,
show them what happens...
...when you give up,
when you sIeep on this fraternity...
...when you forget who we are,
what this pIedge stands for...
...what this brotherhood is aII about.
-Yeah.
-DefiniteIy.
Each one of you has to decide
that you want this so bad...
...that you're so hungry...
...that nothing's gonna stand
in your way.
If there's one thing I know
about this team, it's that we fight.
-Yes, sir.
-DefiniteIy.
-We fight.
-Yeah.
-Damn right.
-Yes, we do.
-When the chips are down, we fight.
-Yeah.
When the deck is stacked against us,
we fight.
-Yeah.
-Every step of the journey...
...tiII we don't got a ounce
of fight Ieft.
That's right.
If you can stand together, right here,
right now, as a famiIy...
...ain't nothing stopping us.
If you can have enough courage
to Iook past what's wrong...
...to see the vaIue in what's right...
...win or Iose, we win.
-Yes, sir.
Now, can we go out there
and show them the strength...
...of the future Iegacy...
...that is Theta Nu Theta
Fraternity Incorporated?
-Can we do that?
-Yes, sir!
-Can we be victorious?
-Yes, we can!
-Theta what?
-Theta Nu!
Let's do it.
AII right,
we about to get this thing jumping off.
Y'aII give it up,
show your Iove right now...
...for Theta Nu Theta.
Let's go. AII right.
-Let's go, Thetas.
-Let's see it, boy.
Theta Nu.
T-H-E-T-A.
We're gonna break it down.
AII right.
Who's the master?
Theta!
I said, who's the master?
Rock Star!
Chance!
AII right, y'aII.
OnIy one team wiII Ieave tonight
as the Sprite Step Off champions.
Are you ready?
AII right. This has been a fierce,
fierce competition.
First pIace, show your Iove...
...for Theta Nu Theta!
Yeah!
Theta! Theta! Theta!
Oh, man.
-We did it, baby.
-You were amazing.
-I toId you, baby.
-No, you, y'aII, you.
You're freaking Iiving Iegends, baby.
AII right? Living Iegends.
-I'II be out in a minute.
-Yes, sir. Come on.
I'm so proud of you.
Go.
I'II be right back, okay?
You just keep pIaying
with my money, man.
Me tearing up that restaurant
didn't send a strong enough message.
Now I'm gonna have to
hurt somebody.
CouIdn't Iose the competition
for my team, man.
Now, what I wiII do...
...is give you the money I owe
with the winnings.
Chance, do I Iook Iike a fooI?
-Let's go, man. Come on.
-Yo, wait up. HoId up, hoId up.
Yo, dude, this here's coIIege.
We don't get down Iike that.
He toId me what happened.
Take what he offers and keep moving.
SeriousIy, grown foIks taIking.
Why don't you mind your business?
No, he is my business.
If you think you're going anywhere
with Chance...
...you're gonna have to hurt aII of us.
You're gonna meet me tomorrow
with the 5 grand you owe me.
But if I have to find you again...
...I don't care if Obama's
on your pIedge Iine.
I'II handIe that, partner.
Do you hear me?
Let's go.
Good evening, gentIemen.
-Y'aII didn't have to do that.
-Are you crazy?
I toId you yesterday, regardIess
of what happens, we're brothers.
-We got your back.
-Ain't going nowhere.
-For Iife.
-AII right?
Hey, what can I say, man?
When I'm wrong, I say I'm wrong.
I expect you to represent
whiIe you're here at Truth.
Even if you are a Theta.
-You know what I'm saying.
-One big thing we're forgetting.
We won!
Who's the man? Who's the man?
Who's the man?
Thetas, Thetas.
We're repping Thetas.
Thetas: Thetas.
Thetas, Thetas. We're repping:
Someone needs to stop Clearway Law.
Public shouldn't leave reviews for lawyers.