Someone needs to stop Clearway Law.
Public shouldn't leave reviews for lawyers.
STORM RIDER
Sweetheart, you took
the competition by storm.
- Oh, thanks dad.
- Mm, so proud of you.
When the rest of the
competition is here too?
Well, don't get too confident.
Dad, it's called being the best,
not being over-confident.
- I want a horse too.
- Oh! No. You know it's nearly four.
I know what time it is.
Excuse me. Yeah?
No, I told you that
account's in the Caymans.
- Daddy?
- Yes.
- What's Dad mad at?
- Well, I don't know.
- Probably something work related.
- He and mom has been fighting.
They kind of fight all the time.
Will figure that out.
Didn't with your mom.
Hi!
- Hi, Brooke. Want some popcorn?
- No, thanks, Jordan.
- You know, my answer hasn't changed.
- But you know we'll pay you a price.
- I'm not selling Admiral.
- You can probably find a better horse.
- Maybe you're right.
- Yeah. Maybe it'll sprout wings too.
George, George listen to me.  Ok that's
why you're in a six-figure retainer.
No, I don't care.  No!
Just get me a continuance.
No. Are you telling me that you
can't just buy me a couple of days?
I need a new lawyer.
No, you figure it out!
Hey, here you go.
Maybe you should ask for the horse.
For your birthday.
- You think I'm good enough?
You're my little brother, aren't you?
Half brother.
- Got this in town for you.
- Yeah. What is it?
- Cookies. Chocolate chip.
- Oh, my favorite.
Hey, we're not half anything. You're my
younger brother and we're family. Got it?
- Okay.
I'm gonna go tell
Mom about the horse.
You'd better hurry!
And eat your sandwich!
Hey Mom, I know what I want for my...
Where are you going?
Where are we going? We're
leaving.  I packed your suitcase.
It's upstairs in your room.
Go get it and bring it downstairs.
What?
Go get it right now. We're leaving
and we're not coming back.
There you are.
We're going.
You're not going anywhere.
You're on the board.
Not anymore.
I had my lawyer divest me of any and
all holdings and positions in the company.
- When did you do...?
- I am not going down with you, Mitch!
Now, I know you have money
stashed offshore and I want my share.
Even if I did stash money
overseas, you wouldn't see a dime.
- Jordan will.
- What are you doing for money now?
I sold my stocks and bonds
and I closed the house account.
- And I sold some jewelry too.
- And that's gonna last you a week.
Yah, at least I have a week.
- Where are they going?
- Who cares?
- Careful!
- What you got in here? Blocks?
You mean like the
ones in your head.  Go.
- How come I have to go with you?
- Don't argue.
- Where are you guys going?
- Away.
Wait, I forgot my hat.
Well then it must not
have been very important.
Go.  You don't seem
understand, we're in a hurry.
But I forgot my hat!
Oh, we'll get you another one.
Just go.
The captain goes down with the
ship but the crew saves themselves.
Jordan! Jordan!
Jordan, wait!
Wait, I got your hat!
So, how much will you lose?
Everything, including Admiral.
Is there something we could do?
I can't even make change
for a parking meter right now.
- They froze all my assets.
- I could buy Admiral from you.
With what?
I have money saved up.
And I could pay you...
Admiral's 200 thousand dollars.
They're going to seize him
along with everything else.
- I'm so sorry.
- What's going to happen to you?
I already know what's
going to happen to you.
Me?
I've made arrangements with Sam.
You're gonna stay with him.
Uncle Sam?
No! Dad, I can take care of ...
Sweetheart, you're minor.
Okay you stay with Sam,
or they're going to put you through
a court appointed foster care system
and I'm not going to let that happen.
- I know how hard this must be.
- He'll have a good home. I promise.
We're not half-anything.
I've made arrangements with Sam.
You are going to stay with him.
I'm so sorry.
- So how's the gelding?
- Good. I still owe you for him, right?
- It's okay.
- Well, I'll pay. I'm not poor, you know?
I know that.  I told you
not to worry about it.
- Gotta go.  I got a guest to pick up.
- Guest? You have a guest?
Hey, don't say it like that.
I could have a guest.
Well, there's time
for everything I guess.
- Dani Fielding?
- Who wants to know?
The sheriff sent me. He said
Dr. Sam had an emergency call so.
I'm sorry, I'm Kevin Winslow.
I can grab these if you like.
- I can get them.
- Are you sure?
- Yes, I'm sure.
- Alright, suit yourself.
- You were really good whistler.
- I am?  Well, thanks.
- Do you know my uncle?
- Dr. Sam? Yeah. Everyone knows him.
- Do you like him?
- Well, yeah.  Don't you?
I don't know.  I only met
him once when I was six.
Has he ever treated you for anything?
For what?   Hoof and
mouth disease?  Get in.
Wait, what?
- You know your uncle's a vet? Right?
- Don't know.
Diesel!  What's up buddy?
Who's a good puppy?
What's up Diesel?
Who's a good boy?
Need some help?
Diesel huh?
- Yeah.  A good name, huh?
- Yeah, if he's a tractor.
- I'm  taking off.
- Okay. Thanks for the ride.
Don't mention it.
Hello?
Uncle Sam?
Is anybody home?
Apparently he thinks
garbage takes itself out.
Diesel, huh?
You want to help me clean?
Smart dog.
It's a disaster.  Really.
It doesn't even feel like I'm on Earth.
I miss you too.
Oh here I am.  I have to go ...
You made it okay?
Sorry, I didn't hear you come in.
The door was open.
- Extra bedroom this way.
- Are you sure you can find it?
I cleaned up the bed,
it was kind of covered up.
I think you oughta found it.
You know, I got chores.
So I want you to get settled down.
That is much better.
- They gave me...
- Doh!
I'm sorry.  I guess you're not
used to having people around.
No, no I'm not.
Are you hungry?
- Maybe we could go out to eat.
- You like chilli?
- Yeah, I guess.
- Don't you know?
I like it, okay?
I don't know what to do
with stuff in the bedroom,
so I just threw them in the
living room.  I hope that's okay.
I don't want you rearrange my house.
I won't know how to find anything.
How do you find anything now?
I have certain piles
I put certain things in.
I can't afford a maid like some.
We didn't have a maid, but
we didn't live like animals either.
Don't you like animals?
Oh, I love animals,
I just don't want to live like one.
- You're kind of for yourself ain't you?
- I'm what? You live in a dump.
Yeah, well nobody's
ever complained before.
- Oh yah, like who's complaining? Diesel?
- Are you gonna eat or argue?
So, do you know
about daddy's problems?
Nope.
- Don't you have an opinion?
- He goes his way, I go mine.
What?  Did you get
into a fight or something?
I know.
We had a disagreement.
Now I have told him long time ago that
I didn't agree with his financial schemes
and his "minerakina dogamamie" sense
He doesn't have schemes, okay.
He's an honest man is.
It that why he's in
trouble with the government?
It's a misunderstanding.
He'll get it cleared up.
I... well, hope he does.
And you can go home.
You know what?
Maybe I'll just leave right now.
- You can't right now.
- Okay. Why not?
Well, because it's going to get dark soon.
How are you going to find your way?
Fine.
I'm not hungry.
What did I say?
You can't leave right now, it's dark
outside.  I'll find my way just fine.
Daddy wanted me to give this to you.
And here are some cookies,
if you want 'em.  Chocolate chip.
I guess I made it seem like
it was her fault, didn't I?
You don't have to
always agree with me.
What do you think?
Peace offering?
I'm not apologizing,
I'm just being nice.
Good morning.
I made you breakfast.
- Thanks for the present.
- Yeah well.  It wasn't much.
I don't eat meat.
I'm a vegetarian.
Well, I'm a Sagittarian.
Here you go, Diesel.
- Zucchini is a vegetables.
- Do you have any French dressing?
Nope.
- Salsa?
- No.
- Do you have any condiments?
- Ketchup.
- Really?
- Those were really good.
- Sam.
- Jody.
- Well, this must be Dani.
- Hi.
Hi, Jody Peterson.
Oh Sam, you must be
the worst cook in state.
Her first day here and all
you give her is zucchini?
Oh, I didn't know there
was a menu requirement.
- You've been alone way too long.
- I'm not alone.  Am I Diesel?
Here, honey.
Have one of this.
Mmm, excellent.
What? You didn't feed
her last night, neither?
She didn't want any.
Didn't want any what?
Your six-year-old chilli?
What's wrong with chilli?
You know, for a horse doctor,
you don't have much horse sense.
You know, I wasn't feeding horses.
Well here, Sam.  I brought you some pay
for the house call you made the other day.
You don't owe me anything.
I told you already.
What is it with women, anyway?
- It takes some getting use to.
- Yeah, I figured that out.
Yeah, he's never had to
care about anybody else.
Because there's never been
anybody else around here.
Especially not a...
young one like yourself.
You know, that's just
something from Mars to him.
Hmm, I thought this was Mars.
You just hold your ground.
Let that old rooster care about
somebody else for a change.
He told me that you were some
sort of champion show rider.
I am.  I had a thoroughbred.
His name was Admiral.
- Did you have to give him up?
- I had to give up everything.
Hey!
Why don't you come with me.
You need to clean up that pigsty.
- Oh yeah, I'll get around to it.
- When?  Fourth of July?
- Wasn't thinking that soon.
- You know, she's been through a lot.
You know what,
that ain't my fault.
Well, she needs somebody who
loves and cares about her.
I do that, just not at the same time.
Hi!
Hey. Come here.
I've got something for you.
Oh, he's adorable.
- He's small, but he will grow.
- Oh hi, little guy.
- And I want you to have him.
- Me?
Yeah, it's... you know,
like a welcome present.
A mule?
Yeah, a perfect place for him.  Now we
already got one jackass around here.
- He's had rough time.
- Well, what happened?
Big storm up in Cedar Briggs.
His mum was killed by wolves.
That much little guy huddled
in Cedars the next day.
Well, it's the first time he hasn't
bitten anybody who got close to him.
Not everybody is like you.
So what you gonna name him?
- Stormy.
- That's a good choice.
Well, it was really nice meeting you.
You're gonna fit in just fine around here.
Yeah, that's what I'm afraid of.
So you gonna train him?
Stormy?
I don't think you can train a mule.
Well you can't, but
you can outsmart him.
Outsmart him?
My back screen door squeaks.  Every
time, I open it, cats come running.
Lucky you.
Well, they know that I'm bringing them
food scraps.  Cats can't be trained either,
but these are... based
on the screen door opening.
You think I could
train Stormy like that?
Sure.  If you work hard enough you
can get any animal to respond to you.
Look, I gotta go and bags have
to went to a horse this morning.
I'll be back in the afternoon.
Look.  I'm sorry about your dad.
I hope he gets things worked out.
Thanks.
Of course a zebra
can't change its stripes.
I forgot something in the house.
I'll be right back.
That's alright.
- How are you doing?
- Okay.  You?
- I'm good. I heard you got a mule.
- Yeah.
They're not worth much, you know?
Well, that's what my dad always says.
- Okay, I'm ready to go.
- Sweet.
Hi.
You're pretty cute.
Okay.  It's okay.
You're fine.
You're okay.
Hello? Dad!
When are you gonna...
Yeah, but Dad, I really need
a new phone.  I can't even call...
Yeah, I'll go...
He's here.  It's Dad.
I figured I'd hear from you.
You want some training?
Sort of.  Not really much
else to do around here.
- You like corn bread?
- Oh, I adore corn bread.
Well, so does Sam,
but he'll never admit it.
Because he never says anything nice.
- Oh... he tries... sometimes.
- No, he doesn't.
- So, you wish he would, don't you?
- You should just tell him.
He doesn't get that kind of thing.
Has Kevin been around?
- Ah yeah, a little bit.
- He's cute, huh?
I think he thinks he's cure,
don't know if I do.
Yeah well... He's got a
girlfriend, but I think he likes you.
- Oh, I highly doubt that.
- Well, he asked about you the other day.
Yah, just so he would
know when to avoid me.
No, it was more than that.
I've seen that look before.
- You're welcome, Sam.
- I know.  Thanks.
I got to run.
- Do you like Jody?
- Well, I like everybody.
- No, I mean. Do you like Jody?
- What?
She sure likes you.
No, she doesn't.  She just
likes having a cheap vet.
- You get those chores done?
- Yes, I did them.
- All of them?
- All of them.
Who is this?
Wicked witch of the West.
What is she doing here?
- Hey.
- Jordan!  Hey you!
- Uncle Sam, this is Jordan.
- Hey, Jordan. Nice to meet you.
Got something to show you.
Have fun.
Yeah.
- It's Sam, right?
- Yeah.
- I'm Vanessa Fielding. We spoke once.
- Oh!  What did we say?
- So this is Stormy.
- Cool.
- Like that?
- Why can't all we just be together?
- It's complicated.
- Mom's a complication, huh?
Have you talked with
your brother recently?
-  Yeah a couple of days ago.
- Did he tell you he's run out of money?
Well, he's in jail, so it's kind
of hard to get to an ATM.
No, I mean he stopped
paying child support.
Huh, and you came all the way
out here, just to tell me that?
Look.  Are able to help with
Mitch's obligations or not?
I have been, I got Dani.
No, I mean his other obligation.
Your nephew.
You know, he asked me to look after
Dani.  Never mentioned anything else.
I know Mitch has cash stored
in some offshore accounts.
- You know that for a fact, do you?
- Oh yes, because I know Mitch.
Maybe we could help
each other out here.
- Can't you just be my guardian?
- I wish I could Bud.
It's okay.
You're not that far away.
Staying with Aunt Mildred's awful.
She's even worse than mom.
- I doubt that.
- Trust me.
- What does she want now?
- Come on.
- Well, we just got here.
- And now we're leaving. Get in.
- She's a nice lady.
- Yeah, tell me that.
But don't let it get to you, okay?
It's not her, it's Jordan.
She doesn't care about him.
Maybe we can do
something about that.
- So, when they going to need a booster?
- In a year.
- Here you go, Sam.
- Thank you.  Oh, that's too much.
Oh Sam, you saved War Cloud
from pneumonia, should be more.
It's not necessary.
Ah Sam, look.  If you
won't do it for my horse
then why don't you put it
away for raising a teenager.
I know what that cost.
What's that?
It's a poster of the regional
horse show, that is coming up.
- I'll take instead.
- No Sam, take 'em both.
No, the poster will do.
- Good day.  See you.
- All right.
- He's different.
- What do you mean?
I don't know.  Always doing
stuff for everybody but himself.
A kind of different we can use
more of, don't you think?  Come on.
- Having fun?
- Yeah, a blast.
- Why don't you try a couple of rocks.
- And do what? Beat it to death?
Learned to improvise.
Savvy?
I... found this.
Didn't see your truck pull in.
- He's riding pretty good.
- Yeah, he's doing really good.
Would you like to come over to our
house some time and ride our horses?
- Here for a bit?
- Yeah.
You know, I think I'm gonna stay
here and work more with Stormy.
There is a dance coming up in
a few weeks, Western Stomp.
- Would you like to go?  With me?
- I thought you had a girlfriend.
- Who told you that?
- A friend.
- I've had one.
- What happened?
- She didn't want me to see other people.
- Other people?
I don't know, people.
I don't know, I don't really
like country music very much.
I'll bring ear muffs.
- Okay. What should I wear?
- It's up to you.
- Okay, I'll see you there.
- Right.
See ya.
What are you planning
on doing with her?
It's a him.  Doesn't anybody
here know the difference?
Yeah, well, I used to.
I don't know what I'm planning on
doing with them.  It will be something.
- Jody come around today?
- Maybe.
You know, if you were
a little nicer to her,
she might come around
a little more often.
- What's that suppose to mean?
- Nothing.
- You know, you're like...
- What?
- Summer storm.
- A summer storm?
Yeah.  You rumble a long time before
you finally get where you're going.
Well, I'm going to take a ride up in the
mountains.  Let Jody know, if she comes by.
- Oh what...?  So Jody is coming?
- Maybe.
Yeah, she's a summer storm, alright.
Diesel, why don't you go with her.
Get a little exercise.
That's what I figured.
I knew you were smart.
That's my boy. Let's go.
Stormy, no!
Stormy, come back!
Hey, you old dog.
Miss me?
- No!  So you got any muffins?
- Oh, plenty.
So where are they?
At home.  Which is where you're gonna
have to go if you want to get some.
What?  Now?
Well, I thought, I'd have you and
Dani over for supper on Sunday.
Well, you don't have to...
ask the girl.
Why is he saddled?
- Dani took him out a couple of hours ago.
- You know where she went?
- Asked here only where she was going.
- Come on.
Come on.  You know
where she went?  Let's go.
Get on.
Do you know where she is.
- Quit bossing.
- Just go.
Stormy!
Here she is.
- What happened?
- Four wheeler on steroids came by.
- Spooked him, huh?
- Like you wouldn't believe.
- Thanks for the lift.
- Are you walking back?
Oh, I know how.
You know what, I think that I want
to drive back and check on Stormy.
- Good idea.
- It is?
Hey, would you like to come
for dinner on Sunday night?
Yeah, we'd would love to.
Well, now we're on foot.
- You were gonna walk with her any way.
- Yeah, I wanted to impress her.
- What am I?  Chopped liver?
- Close.  Here.
You don't have to pay me,
to walk with you.
- It's for her.
- You want me to walk with her?
No!  She's going to some dance with
that Winslow kid.  What's his name?
- Kevin.
- Yeah him.
I wanted to buy her
something nice to wear.
I thought you could help with that.
- Sure.
- Thank you.
You're welcome.
What are you having?
- Well, what do you mean?
- For dinner.
- Hey, more pie?
- No, you have to stuff it in my pockets.
- It was so good.
- Right.
Hey, I'm going to the city
tomorrow to do a little shopping.
- Would you like to come?
- No, too busy of a day for me.
Not you.
Could we maybe go to the prison?
I would like to see my
dad and visit him if I could.
- Yeah, sure.
- Okay.  Here, I can get these.
You realise the prison is an hour
south of the city to get there.
So we'll leave early.
It's okay.
- Hi, dad.
- Hey.
- I wish you hadn't come.
- Why?
I mean, it's just far.
You're wasting your time.
How is it with Sam?
- Well, it takes some getting used to.
- Not unlike Sam, right?
They offered me a plea bargain.
Do you know what that is?
Sort of.
You see, if I plead guilty, it could...
reduce my sentence.  Take some time off.
You haven't even gone to trial yet.
No, that's why they're offering me
the plea agreement.  It avoids all that.
But you're not guilty,
so don't take it.
This has nothing to do
with guilt or innocence.
It's all about what...
what the jury is going to believe.
- What would I believe?
- That I'm guilty.
So have you made any friends?
- Well, I am going on a date next week.
- That's good.  He's a lucky boy.
- And Jordan came by.
- I miss him.
Vanessa's trying to get
money from Uncle Sam.
- Dracula lady.
- She says that you have money stashed.
She says a lot of things.  And it really
helps Sam isn't that bad, sweetheart.
No, I think I'm getting used to it.
And then when you
get past all his quirks,
you'll see his heart
is in the right place.
- Are you sure he has one?
- Somewhere, underneath all that crust.
I'm gonna go.
Okay.  I'll come back
as soon as I can...
No, no.  I don't... think this
is a good place for you to come.
If something changes,
I'll ask George to call you.
Yeah.
- I really love you.
- I love you too, Dad.
- How did it go?
- Discouraging.
Yeah well, prison does that.
I know he's innocent, and nobody
will believe me. Not even Uncle Sam.
- I wouldn't judge him too harshly now.
- They're brothers.
- Yeah well, so were Cain and Abel.
- What does that mean?
Well, what that
means is that sometimes
things aren't as obvious
as you might think.
You probably shouldn't judge him, as
much as you want him to judge your daddy.
- That Kevin boy, he's pretty cute, huh?
- Yeah, I guess.
Yeah, well you guys are going
to the dance together, right.
Yeah.  But how did you know that?
Well because Sam said he wants
you to have something nice to wear.
- He did?
- Yup.  He's paying for it.
- Uncle Sam?
- Mm hm.  Full of surprises, huh?
- Come on, let's go shopping.
- I don't know.
- Good.  I know just the place.
- Okay.
Move in.
- Hi.
- Woh, you look amazing.
Thanks.
I had help picking it out.
- Hold it.
- What?
- My truck.
- What's the matter with it?
- It sucks.
- No, it doesn't.
It's not good enough for you
to ride in, not dressed like that.
- Come on, it's fine.
- Have her back here by midnight.
I will.
This is for little Annie.  Give her a
couple each night for the next two weeks.
Okay.
- And midnight for this filly.  Clear?
- Crystal.
Looks pretty good, doesn't she?
Yeah.  Too good if you ask me.
- Dad, you think I would do it...
- No?  Oh...
- Hey.
- How are your horses doing?
- Good.  Got a new one.
- You want to see it?
- Yeah, I'd love to.
- Come. Don't step on anything.
- Wouldn't be the first time.
She may have been a competition
horse but we're not sure.
With an emphasis on "we're not sure".
But I would like your opinion, though.
Well, Little Annie is beautiful but,
to give you an honest
opinion I'd have to ride her.
- Well, maybe another day.
- No, now's great.
Now it's great.
She's had some training.
Not a lot but, she's sure got potential.
What will it take to get
her in performance shape?
Three months, at least.
I'd know more if I work with her.
- It's better than riding a dang mule, huh?
- Yeah I think. It can be a pain sometimes.
I don't even know why people have 'em
anymore. They're stupid, they're stubborn.
Yeah, just like some people.
Yeah, well you can't skin
and tan some people, huh?
No you can't.
- So you want to go to the dance?
- No, I want to get back on.
Just afraid of that.
When I get my hands on him...
- You'll what?
- I'll tan his hide.
Oh come on.
He'll drop you like a bag of dirt.
Really?
You know, I'd like to see him try.
Easy there, killer.
You know, you came here to see your
niece dance in her nice new dress.
So she left a little early with
a very nice young gentleman
who come from a very nice family.
Give him the benefit of the doubt.
I'll give him the benefit
of the doubt, all right.
Oh Addy Jane!
Have you seen Kevin or Dani?
- No, not since school this afternoon.
- So they weren't here at all?
If they were, we
didn't see them.  Sorry.
You know, she could have called.
With what?  You told me her cell
phone's been down for months.
- Well, she should have found a way.
- How?  A carrier pigeon?
- You're worse than she is.
- Now you're just an old pigeon poop.
I'm not an old poop.
Or middle aged poop.
- I had a lot of fun tonight.
- I'm sorry about your dress.
It's okay, it's just a dress.
You know a lot about
training horses, don't you?
Well, a little bit.
Girls can surprise you.
- Some girls maybe, not you.
- What is that suppose to mean?
- Easy.  I didn't mean anything by it.
- I'm sorry. Guess I'm a little touchy.
Or defensive.
Suppose you got your reasons.
We didn't really get off on
the right foot anyway.
No, we didn't.
I'd like to make up for it.
Yeah, it's alright.
Late by two minutes.
Yeah, I wanted to make
sure she's home in time.
Mm hm.
- How come you didn't go to the dance?
- You spied on me?
No, no.  I wanted to see
how my investment looked.
- You had a fight?
- We never left my place.
I went and rode little Annie.
Mr. Winslow wanted my opinion of her
and the only way to give him
an honest one was to ride her.
- So Mr Winslow was there all night?
- Yeah, the whole time.
- And you rode little Annie in your dress?
- Yeah, that was what I was wearing.
Thank you.
I had the best time tonight.
The most fun I've had the
whole time I've been here.
- I suppose I owe you an apology.
- No, you don't.
It was the best night in my life.
Yeah, if it wasn't for my mouth,
I wouldn't have any place to put my feet.
I wanna do it, Stormy.  I think
little Annie and I could really win it.
But, that would mean more time
with her and less time with you.
Can you be okay with that?
I love you.
- Morning.
You're up early.
Yeah, felt like kind it was a pretty
daylight.  Made you breakfast.
- Did you clean up in here?
- Yeah, a little bit.
- There's no bacon.
- Do you want to have a heart attack?
- Don't worry, I'll fix it. I'm a doctor.
- No, you're a vet.
Yeah, a vet who likes bacon.
So Kevin's dad asked
me to train little Annie.
- Really? You up to it?
- Yeah. I think I know what I'm doing.
I wish I did.  What about
your chores around here?
Well, I was kind of hoping maybe
you could help me out with them.
Just until I'm done
training little Annie.
I mean, I barely have time
to get her in shape as it is.
- What about Stormy?
- Stormy, she'll be fine.
Well maybe.  She's kind of getting used
to you spending a lot of time with her.
Yeah.
You know what ** me.
- Okay.
- Uh, there's something else.
What's that?
I really like that dress,
but I think daddy wanted me to
use the money for something else.
What money?
The money that I gave you,
the first time I was here.
Yeah yeah, right.
Here you go.
Do whatever you want with it.
- You haven't opened it.
- Why would I do that? It's not mine.
Look, I just thought that you
would have used the money to...
About what?
It's Kevin.
- I'm sorry.
- Why?
Because I thought, that
you use the money to...
You better not keep him waiting.
She likes training their horse
but that's not the only thing she
likes slow at the Winslow and **.
Yeah, you said it.  What, teenage
girls must drive their fathers crazy.
Really wish I had some bacon.
You know, maybe you can
try a little chicken or steak.
You know, something different.
You don't have to eat it.
You better get it from
the store and I'll fix it.
Okay.
- Has he been fed?
- Yeah, but I'm not you.
- What do you mean?
- He's lonely.
- He's a mule.
- Mules have feelings.
Alright darling, come on out.
- You going somewhere?
- Yes, and he can't come with me.
- So you brought him here?
- Yes, well, you're his uncle.
Well, you're his mother.
You outrank me.
I can't take him with me.
- You asked what he wants?
- This is best for everyone.
Yeah sure. You... don't you
even want to say goodbye to him?
Oh, I did already.
Well, I guess you could
help me with some chores.
- See you can get Stormy to eat.
- What's the matter with him?
Well, he's off his feed.
I think that he's... lonely.
Should get you settled
in first, though uh?
You don't seem too
upset that she's leaving.
- She's always running away.
- That's a good point.
- Where's Dani?
- She ran away.
Sure?
No, no.  She's working
with a filly down the road.
Come on.
You think my Mom went
too far, don't you?
Yup, and I hope she stays there.
- You know my sister is coming next week.
- Yeah, I know, I know.
I was hoping you could
help me with the kid.
- You need to get to know him better.
- This kid used to be the first one.
Well, take him with you.
It will be good for the both of you.
I'll come back around this afternoon.
- You promise?
- Scout's honor.
- You're not a Scout.
- I'm not an uncle either.
Howdy.
Good morning, Sam. Who is this?
Your new assistant?
- Yup.
- I'm Dani's little brother.
- Well, hello there, Dani's little brother.
- Hi.
- Dani's over the other corral.
- Cool.
- Go on.
- Good kid.
Hey, thanks for coming out this morning.
Can I talk to you about something?
- Sure.
- Okay.
Hey, Dani!
Hey kiddo!
- Hey, you said you miss me.
- Of course, I missed you.
- Who is this?
- This is Little Annie.
- I've been working with her.
- What about Stormy?
Well, this is kind of more like
the stuff I used to do with Admiral.
- Cool.
- Come on, Bud.
She's spending a lot of time here.
Yeah, well the event's
coming up soon, Doc.
I just don't get to see her that much.
Now look, I'm not trying
to keep her from you.
Oh, I know that.
Ah, it's the competition.
I need that filly to do well.
And Dani is doing
a great job with her.
Yeah, I get it, you know.
She's got her heart set on this, so...
I missed you!
Hey.  Vanessa came by and
dropped him off this morning.
- So, he's staying?
- Well, for a while.
Hey, I forgot to show you this.
What?  Are you serious?
I knew Brooke was going to ruin him!
Who is she?
What do you mean, ruin him?
Just nothing okay.
Just forget it.
- How could you hate her so much?
- I... I don't hate her.
- You don't like her very much either.
- Well, you know, tendinitis does happen.
Yeah, but ...
I worked so hard with him.
Well then, make sure Little Annie
shows everyone how it should be done.
Hey, I have an idea.
Maybe you could ride Stormy.
- Stormy is a mule, Jordan.
- I thought you liked her.
Him and I do but...
He's not a horse.
- You got that one right.
- Is that why you said he won't eat?
- Did I say that?
- Yeah.
He's not eating?
You know what?  Jordan
and I have a lot of work to do.
Back at the...
I don't know.
So, what do you
think your chances are?
- I don't know.
- Horse show is not that far off, you know?
- I know that.  That's what worries me.
- Don't worry.  You'll be great.
Thanks.  But I kind of need
more than you just saying that.
Maybe I can be more.
Who's Brooke?
Just the girl who ruin
my horse and my life.
Oh, glad I asked.
Stupid mule.
It's no use.
He won't eat.
Doesn't mean we can't.
What do you want for supper?
- What have you got?
- A lot of vegetables.
- Anything good?
- And you ain't a vegetarian?
- No, I'm an American.
- Me too. How about one of this?
Yeah.
I've been trying to convert the
wrong ones. Set the table, here, son.
- He wanted to wait up for you.
- He didn't make it.
You know, he's all I have left.
Rather than you.
He's a good worker.  So how's
the training going for Little Annie?
It's good.  Only 10 days
to the competition.
Who is Brooke?
Her mom is the one
that bought Admiral.
- You don't like her.
- It's not that I don't like her. She just...
- You blame her for your problems.
- You have no right to say that.
- Okay.
- It is my life.
It's not your life I was commenting on.
It's the way you're living it.
- Maybe he forgot who you are.
- He didn't forget, he's just mad.
- Do mules get mad?
- This one does.
Nope, nope come on.
Oh, Stormy.
Sam, do me a favor.
Don't listen to her.
You know, you should
keep your kids together.
It's a little more
complicated than that.
You need to think of someone
else beside yourself, Mitch.
You had a real hard time with that.
Even when we were kids, you were
great at taking but lousy at giving.
Listen to me.
Alright?
Even if there was money,
if I told them about it, they would
add at least five years to my sentence.
Do you understand that?
Minimum!
Look, if you don't do something,
you might even lose them both.
- I have already lost them, Sam.
- No, no, you just let them down.
You just... Look, I really don't
have time for this, alright?
It's your choice, little brother.
Good. Left leg, left leg.
You must cut in.
Terrific.  The leg. It's coming in,
coming in.  Good, good.
Hey, you riding pretty
good there, little man.
Thanks.
Is Doc around?
Uh no.  He went into town
but he'll be back later.
Alright.
Just have him call.
Dad's flying to go look at some
new stock over at Grand Junction.
- He want the Doc to go with him.
- Do you have an airport around here?
Yeah, a small one.
My dad keeps his plane there.
Your dad has a plane?  Can I fly in it?
Hey, you don't just ask like that.
Yeah, you could probably
go with dad and Doc.
- Really?
- I don't think it's a good idea.
- When?
- Tomorrow. Just remind him ok, Buddy?
Yeah.
- Thanks for stopping by.
- Don't mention it.
Looks like there's a storm coming.
- Who said it was okay?
- Kevin did.
- You wanna go?
- Do I?
- I don't know. Do you?
- Yes, I do.
What?
- Vanessa called.
- She want more money?
Jordan.
- What did you tell her?
- Nothing.
Look, she still has legal custody.
And I asked Mitch if he has any
money offshore like she claims.
- What did he say?
- He didn't.
- But you think he does, don't you?
- It doesn't matter what I think.
He's been sentenced.
- Nobody told me that. How long?
- Five to ten.
Years?
So, does this mean
we can't go tomorrow?
- I think we can still make that work out.
- Yeah!
- I hope they got out before this hit.
- Jordan said that they could fly over it.
Plane's missing.  The Sheriff got
the Mayday call about an hour ago.
- I'm gonna go see if I can find them.
- Where?
Birchwood Springs.  He said to gather
as many people as you can to go search.
- I'll see who I can get.
- I'm coming with you.
- You can't, I only have one horse.
- What about Little Annie?
There's no way she'd
make it up that mountain.
Stormy.
From the last transmission there
in the Rogers Beau area here,
I think if we start at the base, we circle
both ways, we might just get lucky.
Okay, then let's meet on
the east side of the Beau.
Okay.  I'll set up base at
the Birch Springs campground.
Here, take this, use Channel 4.
Let's go.
- Good luck.
- We'll find them.
Come on, buddy.
Come on.  Stormy, stop.
What's the matter with you?  Come on.
Look.  I know I haven't been there for
you and I'm sorry, okay?   It was wrong.
But I really need you right now.
Okay?
Jordan and Uncle Sam, they're lost
and they might be hurt really bad.
And I can't do this without you, ok?
I really need you.  Please do it for me.
I love you.
Kevin?
Kevin, can you hear me?
Kevin? Sheriff? Anyone?
God help me,
before it's too late.
Cameron?
- He can't hear you. He's unconscious.
- I'm not unconscious.
- Jordan?
- I'm just resting my eyes.
- Yeah well, just rest them some more.
- Uncle Sam, are you hurt?
Yeah.
Don't worry about it.
We got to get these two
down the mountain right away.
- I'm sorry.
- I can't move my leg.
Okay.  Don't move it, just lie
back down.  What about you?
- It's nothing.
- That is not like nothing.
Don't worry about it.
Come here.
I think that Cameron
is hemorrhaging internally.
He is going to die if we don't give
him some help.  Is that thing working?
No, all I'm getting is static.
I think the mountain's cutting reception.
Up there, Elk Ridge Summit.
When you raise them,
they'll know where it is.
- But you...
- Just go.  I'll be here when you get back.
Alright buddy.
Hang in there, okay?
Just a little further, boy.
Sheriff? Kevin?
Anyone?
They can't hear me.
Kevin?
Please, somebody answer me.
Sheriff's down the other side,
but I hear you.  Where are you?
Jody? Jody, it's me.
The plane's just below Elk Ridge Summit.
Copy that. I'll send
Kevin and the search party.
Please hurry.  Cameron Winslow has
internal injuries and he's bleeding in,
and Jordan and Sam
both have broken bones.
Didn't get all that, but somebody will
be there in about an hour, maybe less.
You just get over the hill.
Down and out.
Thank you.
They're coming.
- Any luck?
- Yeah, I got them.
- How long?
- About an hour.
Okay.  We need to tie these ropes
together, so Stormy can pull.
- Wow.  Not bad for a one-armed man.
- That's what all the girls say.
- Dani, it hurts.
- Okay, don't lean on it.
That is the ugliest
horse I've ever seen.
Well, that horse is
going to save your life.
Come on, boy.  Put your
leg in there. There you go.
One, two...
Bring him over here.
We'll meet them down the mountain.
Here he comes.
- Hey! He's hurt pretty bad.
- How did I get here?
- Stormy brought you.
- That's not a horse.
- Where are the others?
- They couldn't make it through.
Well, we have to.
I'll put him on my horse
and ride behind you.
Just don't let him
bounce around too much.
I was wrong.
- About what?
- Mules.
Well, I think the mule
feels the same way.
Yeah.
I'll be back as soon as I can.
The radios work better down below.
I'll call you.
- You look worse than what you say.
- Yeah, I think I might have broken a rib.
- Getting hard to catch my breathe.
- Can you ride, if I carry Jordan?
No!  You take him.  I'll stay here,
I'll be okay.  They'll be back up for me.
Stormy!
Dani.  No!  No!
Let him go!
Stormy!
- But the wolves are gonna get him.
- Dani let him go, ok.  He's on his own.
These wolves are everywhere, ok.
We...
It's going to be dark soon.
We need to build a fire.
- Do you have any matches?
- No.
I can get a fire without matches.
- You have a good fire, buddy.
- Thanks.
- My leg hurts.
- Alright, try not to move it.
- What if the wolf comes?
- Well, don't let him know we're here.
The wolf's right there!
That worked.
Probably won't work again though.
Just keep doing it.
At least it worked for now.
Uncle Sam?
You gotta stay awake.
Enough.
Dani, it's been a long day.
Stormy, where are you?
He's coming back.
Uncle Sam?
Uncle Sam!
Stay back!
Stormy!
You came back.
He brought me here.  He found me
down below and then took off again.
I figured he was trying to tell
me something.  Are you okay?
One time I wished you'd
shown up early and you're late.
As soon as I get him to
the Sheriff's camp, I'll be back.
- Are we there yet?
- Almost, buddy.  Hang on.
Cameron's gonna make it.
Just came over the radio.
- Will you be able to get back on your own?
- Yeah, I'll be fine.
It's a great little mule.
You trained him?
No, more like he trained me.
Thank you.
Let's go home, Stormy.
- Thanks for helping me, bud.
- Are you gonna fix up Stormy too?
I already did.
- You want to do me a favor?
- Yeah.
You want to get him and tie
him on the fence up there?
- Okay.
- Thanks.
Okay little girl.
Are you ready?
Okay, come on.
Come on.
- Did you tell 'em?
- No, I did not.
You know, we gonna go make
some supper.  Nice to meet you.
- What's going on?
- I heard about Admiral.
- There's nothing we could have done.
- Yeah, I know.
- We worked so hard too.
- Yeah.
Well, your new horse, she's beautiful.
Well, I trained her...
but I think you should ride her.
- Me?
- Yeah.
I already talked to the show committee and
they're fine with you riding in my place.
I think you got a real good
shot at winning that trophy.
- But why are you...?
- Because I've already got my mount.
A mule?
Yeah, I... I'm going to be a trainer from
now on.  So do good, I need the exposure.
- I don't know what to say.
- You don't need to say anything.  I do.
I'm really sorry, for the way that
I treated you the last few years.
I just... It's about all my problem
on you and I'm really sorry.
I know that it isn't enough,
but I hope it's a start.
This is the nicest thing
anyone's ever done for us.
Thank you, Dani.
From both of us.
Thanks for giving me a second chance.
Well, you better get going.
I won't forget this.
Go win it.  And don't forget
to tell who your trainer is.
Don't break any
of those, only ones I got.
- These are brand new.
- Well, I didn't say I used them a lot.
- Funny how things change.
- 'Hey, my birthday is coming.
Oh really?
When is it?
In a month.
I was maybe thinking I could...
Just hold that Jordan.
Hello?  What?
You mean now?
Okay.
- Who was that?
- His mother.
She's coming for the boy.  She got
papers from the district court.
No!
- Why don't you just tell her no?
- Go help your brother pack.
- Hey, somebody's here.
- What?  She called from a block away?
It's Jordan's mother.
See if you can get him on the phone.
Yeah, I will.
There's only one person
who can change her mind now.
I would like to get back to
civilization before the year ends.
You know what you
doing to him, don't you?
- Mitch?  I hope he's squirming.
-  Jordan.
That is not my fault.
If Mitch had just...
If Mitch had dumped you two years ago,
this wouldn't be a problem now, would it?
- No need to get nasty.
- Why not?  I'm talking to a pro.
- Why are you doing this?
- Because I can.
We'll get you back.
I promise.
I mean, what can you do?
What can anybody do?
So you're sure you
won't change your mind?
- I would.  For a price.
- Wait!
This is Vanessa.  You sure?
You can verify that?
Oh, I'll be there.
But let's be perfectly clear on this.
9 am tomorrow morning.
Oh, I'll take him.  Fine.
- Sweetheart, get out.
- What?
- Oh honey, you're not coming.
- Come here, you.
Bye bye.
- Who did you call?
- Your father's lawyer.
What did he do?
Nothing, but... we thought he would
reveal some hidden assets to the court.
You mean sign them over to the
wicked witch of the west there.
In order for her to get the money, she
has to sign legal custody over to Sam.
Come on, it's not that big a tale.
So there's something to
show you over here.  Come on.
- Your father, he did the right thing.
- But how did you...
Well, he told me about his hidden assets.
Because he was right about that.
But from the bail I get
drawing away from her,
he had to give up
more than just money.
What?
They added three years
on to his sentence.
- So, I'm staying here?
- Yeah, you're staying here.
You know, I just remembered that
I do have something for your birthday.
His birthday is not for another month.
So who says you only get
presents on your birthday?
Cool!
- Look at that.
- Don't cut yourself.
And someone told me that
I'm a vet not a doctor.
This is for you.
- Here.
- What?  It's not my birthday.
Oh, just open it.
I... Look I would have
gotten down on one knee,
now then I'd have to get all
the way back up again and then...
- So will you..?
- Yes!
Hey, there's something
you guys should know.
What?
Little Annie won.
Looks like you're going to be
training horses from now on.
She won!
- I'm sorry.
- For what?
How I acted.  And...
I'd like to make it up to you.
- Oh really?
- Mm hm.
Watch Movies, TV Series and Live Sports
Signup Here -> WWW.ADMITME.APP