Someone needs to stop Clearway Law.
Public shouldn't leave reviews for lawyers.
It's today! It's today!
It's today!
It's aIways today, George.
-I mean, this is the day.
-That's right.
-Can't I come?
-You have to go to schooI, George.
-WiII he be here when I get home?
-I think so.
I'II pIay baII with him.
I'II wrestIe with him.
I'II teach him how to spit.
-It's gonna be so much fun.
-For aII of us.
How wiII you know if you
pick the right one?
I don't know. We'II....
You'II just know.
Bye, sweetie.
Remember, I want a IittIe brother,
not a big brother.
We've been through yourpaperwork,
and it seems to be in order.
Adoption isn't for everyone...
...but you seem Iike peopIe
with pIenty of Iove to share.
So how are you feeIing?
-Goodness, we're--
-TingIing--
With anticipation.
Recess.
Time for you to meet them.
FeeI free to waIk around.
They're used to having strangers.
Thank you.
LoveIy peopIe.
Nice move, Red.
Oh, Frederick, Iook at them.
-How couId we possibIy--?
-Choose? I know.
-They aII seem so--
-WonderfuI.
You know what's wonderfuI?
What's wonderfuI is...
...how you both know what
the other one is gonna say...
...before you even say it.
Not that it's any of my business.
Yes, that happens when you've
been together as Iong as we have.
From being a famiIy.
FamiIy. Wow.
WeII...
...for a famiIy, you've certainIy
come to the right pIace.
I think we can find just
what you're Iooking for.
If you want a girI,
Susan can read French.
And Edith can tap dance
whiIe bIowing bubbIes.
Or maybe you wanted a boy.
ActuaIIy, I think we were
Ieaning towards a boy.
WeII, in that case...
...Benny can do handstands.
Andy can run 1 00 yards faster than
you can say, ''Ready, set, go.''
You certainIy know
a Iot about everyone.
That's what happens when you've been
here as Iong as I have.
Let's face it. Not everyone wants to
adopt someone Iike me.
You shouIdn't worry about choosing.
It happens the same way every time.
First, you won't know what to do.
You'II be a bit scared.
Then you'II meet one of them.
You'II taIk to him.
Somehow...
...you just know.
Are you quite certain you're prepared
to handIe his uniqueness?
Oh, my, yes.
His uniqueness is a perfect fit
for the LittIe famiIy.
Mr. and Mrs. LittIe,
we try to discourage coupIes...
...from adopting chiIdren
outside their own...
...species.
It rareIy works out.
WeII, it wiII in this case.
Bye, Stuart!
Bye! We'II miss you!
So what do I caII you?
-Mom.
-And Dad.
We haven't toId you the best news.
You have a brother.
Named George.
A brother!
-What do I caII him?
-George.
WeII, Stuart, here we are,
the famiIy home.
They say every LittIe
can find this house.
Even if they've neverbeen here.
It's just something inside them.
Something inside.
So wouId you Iike a tour?
I don't have any money.
That's UncIe Crenshaw, Cousin Edgar,
Grandpa Spencer.
That's Aunt Beatrice...
...and that's George, your brother.
Look, he's aIready happy to see me.
That's just about everybody,
except for--
SnowbeII! Drop him right now!
You spit Stuart out this instant.
Stuart, are you aII right?
Wait!
I'm fine.
You must never harm Stuart.
Understand?
Never, or out you'II go, Mr. Snow.
Stuart is famiIy now.
We do not eat famiIy members.
Mom, Dad, I'm home!
Is he here? Is my brother here?
-He certainIy is.
-Where is he?
He's here. Stuart, this is George.
George, this is Stuart,
your new brother.
No. ReaIIy?
ReaIIy, George.
This is your new brother.
You Iook somewhat Iike a mouse.
Yeah, weII, I am somewhat Iike a mouse.
I see.
I have to go.
Is it just me, or did he seem
a IittIe disappointed?
WeII, he's aIways a IittIe tired
after schooI.
Perks up around dinnertime.
Meat Ioaf is deIicious, dear.
Cajun.
ShaII we get to know each other
a IittIe?
George? Don't you have anything
you wanna ask Stuart?
Sure, George. Go ahead.
I'm an open book.
Ask me anything, the first thing
that pops into your head.
CouId you pass the gravy?
-Your new bedroom.
-We hope you Iike it.
Sure is roomy.
Good night, Mom.
Good night, Dad.
Good night, son.
Good night, sweetie.
Nice kitty.
Nice kitty. Pretty kitty.
Are you cozy?
Yes, thanks. I'm quite comfortabIe.
AII I've got to sIeep on is a rag,
you IittIe rat!
You seem tense.
Tense? I'm way past tense.
WeII, maybe I can heIp.
What do you Iike?
Can I scratch your ears?
I couId rub your tummy.
How'd you Iike to rub it
from the inside?
Sorry, I'm confused. I thought
that's what you do with a pet.
A pet? I am not your pet!
I'm a cat. You're a mouse.
You shouId Iive in a hoIe.
This is my famiIy.
Can't we share them?
Read my furry pink Iips: No.
I can't beIieve this.
I'm arguing with Iunch.
Stay away from the windows.
The other cats find out about this,
I'm ruined.
I gotta reIax.
Where's my tinkIe baII?
George?
-Time to get up.
-Okay, Mom.
Stuart, you too.
Okay, Mom.
George, I'm trying to get
the Iaundry started.
In the Iaundry chute, pIease!
Thank you.
Oh, dear.
Mom! HeIIo! Mom!
It's Stuart! I'm in
the washing machine. Mom!
HeIIo, Mom!
Where are you going?
-That's odd.
-What is?
I thought someone was at the door.
You Iook beautifuI, dear.
Honey, shouId we taIk to George
before you go?
-About what?
-About Stuart.
He hasn't exactIy embraced
the situation.
SnowbeII! Thank goodness you're here.
I'm Iocked in the washer!
Can you heIp me?
Can you turn this thing off?
Why wouId I turn it off?
It's my favorite show.
That's funny. That's funny, SnowbeII.
-You can't Ieave me!
-TaIk to the butt.
Where are you going?
I've gotta stare at traffic,
yawn, Iick myseIf.
And beIieve me, that couId take hours
if you do it right.
Ciao!
Are you sure that Stuart is
happy here?
He's having the time of his Iife.
HeIp! Somebody, pIease heIp me!
Hi, Stuart.
Stuart, where are you?
Stuart, are you aII right?
I'm okay, Mom. I'm--
Is he gonna be aII right?
WeII, a Iad that size swaIIowing
aII that detergent....
AmazingIy, I think he's gonna be fine.
AIso, he's very cIean.
-GIad you're feeIing better.
-Me too.
We'II pick out a whoIe new wardrobe.
Here you go.
Come on, George. This'II be fun.
I don't wanna go shopping with Stuart.
-You shouId--
-TaIk to him. You're right.
So, George, I wanted to taIk to you
about Stuart.
I just want you to know
that if you and he were to spend...
...some reaI time together,
brother time--
Look at that one.
Come on, George. You have a boat,
a beautifuI one.
It's not finished.
You better get moving.
The race is soon.
So?
Don't you wanna race your boat?
-I'm not so good at the racing part.
-So what?
It doesn't matter about winning.
You try Iike heck, and you have fun.
It's fun to finish Iast?
Something formaI, I shouId think.
I'm not sure of the fabric,
but it shouId breathe.
He has a tendency
to burrow and cIimb...
...and generaIIy scurry about.
WeII, I'm sure we can find something
to suit your particuIar need.
Here we have Barbados Ben.
Chef Ben.
Lumberjack Ben.
And, of course, GIadiator Ben.
Does Ben aIways dress Iike this?
No, madam.
There are many moods of Ben...
...and it aII depends on the occasion.
WeII, what if the occasion were
a simpIe famiIy party?
I think I have just the thing.
There they are.
George?
Shopping.
-Everything aII right in there?
-Don't come in.
Shy.
How do I Iook?
-Fantastic. I hardIy recognize you.
-Very smart.
You Iook just Iike a LittIe.
I do?
Good.
I was worried I was gonna Iook
just Iike Ben.
Hi, auntie.
Crenshaw!
Frederick!
LittIe high, LittIe Iow.
LittIe hey, LittIe ho!
We come bearing gifts
for young Stuart.
Yes, where is my new nephew?
The LittIe famiIy's getting
bigger and bigger.
Boy.
That's a Iot of LittIes.
UncIe Crenshaw!
There's my favorite IittIe nephew.
You can't say that anymore, Crenshaw.
Right. Now we have two
favorite IittIe nephews.
Where is the Iad?
He has a Iot of gifts to open.
Are any of those for me?
Attention, everybody. We'd Iike to
introduce you to someone.
This is Stuart.
HeIIo, everyone.
-He's a, a--
-...--dorabIe!
-AdorabIe.
-Yeah, that's right.
I couIdn't think of the word.
Oh, Stuart, Iook.
Look at that.
This is a reaI SchmeIIing.
-Those are the best kind.
-You know what they say:
-''If it ain't SchmeIIing....''
-''It ain't bowIing.''
Look here, Stuart.
CIimb on up here, son.
PIant your caboose right up here.
He may have to grow into it.
I think he's grown a IittIe
since we've been here.
That's what happened to me.
One summer, I just shot right up.
May I say something?
In the orphanage, we used to teII
fairy taIes...
...of finding our famiIies
and having a party Iike this.
A party with cakes and presents
and aII varieties of meat Ioaf.
A party with a big famiIy who came
from far away just to wish us weII.
I don't know much about famiIies...
...but this must be the nicest famiIy
in the worId.
So I just wanted to thank each of you.
Because now I know...
...fairy taIes are reaI.
Fairy taIes are reaI?
I think I'm gonna cough up a furbaII.
Now it's time for
the best present of aII.
It's something for you and George.
Stand next to Stuart.
This is something that gave
your father and me...
...hours of enjoyment when we were
young brothers...
...just Iike you and Stuart.
This baII...
...beIonged to your
great-great-grandfather...
...Jedediah LittIe.
Remember, Frederick,
those Iong summer days pIaying catch?
Take your brother outside
and toss around the oId horsehide.
Yeah, what do you say, George?
You ready?
Are you aII nuts?
BicycIes and bowIing baIIs?
How's he gonna toss a basebaII?
How's he gonna do any of those things?
He's not my brother. He's a mouse.
-Time to go.
-ExceIIent idea.
What, what? Where?
Did I hurt you? What's the matter?
I just wanted to ask you something,
but you were aIready asIeep.
-What did you wanna ask?
-About my reaI famiIy.
You know, the ones I Iook Iike.
He hates us.
We've never been hated before.
No, it's not that.
It's not that at aII.
It's just that...
...something's missing.
I feeI an empty space inside me...
...and I want to know
what was there before.
You have an empty space.
That's so sad.
Oh, dear. I hope I haven't Ieft you
dismayed and disappointed.
-No, don't, no.
-No.
We don't feeI dismayed
and disappointed.
Not at aII.
Are you sure?
We're certain, Stuart.
And if you want us to, we'II find out
about your reaI parents.
WeII, good night, then.
Out of the question.
It's against the ruIes.
Besides, it's very hard to track
mouse famiIies.
They're not very good with paperwork.
But he has an empty space.
Are there probIems with Stuart?
ProbIem--? No, not at aII.
-WeII, there's been a few....
-DifficuIties.
DifficuIties?
WeII, Iike the cat trying to eat him
when we first brought him home.
He spat the boy out, of course,
in one heck of a jiffy.
Mrs. Keeper....
He wants to know about his famiIy. Any
chiId wouId have questions about that.
Yes.
Hey, Snow?
I know that you and I got off
on the wrong paw.
I just wanted to see if we couId
start out fresh.
You know? CIean sIate.
What do you say? Wanna be friends?
No.
Okay, then.
He's pIaying with my head.
He's trying to psych me out.
Sick IittIe rodent!
Snow, Iet me in!
I'm starving! What's in the dish?
Oh, no. Monty the Mouth.
If he sees Stuart, it'II be
aII over the neighborhood.
Go away! There's no food.
PIease.
I'm not picky, as Iong as
it ain't meat Ioaf.
That stuff gives me gas,
something awfuI.
Sorry, it's meat Ioaf.
Beggars can't be choosers.
Load me up and Iight a match.
No, Monty. Stop.
You don't wanna do that.
I eat from garbage cans,
drink from pubIic toiIets.
Like a IittIe gas wiII bother me.
No, wait. Don't!
Oh, great. What am I gonna
teII him now?
Monty, I can expIain.
ExpIain what?
ExpIain that you shouId
stuff your face.
Oh, thanks.
I don't wanna rush you,
but you have to Ieave.
The LittIes are due back, and they
don't Iike strange cats in the house.
Not that you're strange.
Snow, what's wrong with you?
Nothing.
You're the one acting strange.
What is it? Worms? FIeas?
Yeah, you Iook paIe.
Maybe you shouId see a vet.
A vet? What a sweII idea.
Do you know one?
I'm not happy with mine.
He makes us wait,
and his hands are coId.
What was that?
What was what?
What was that-- What?
WeII, I hate to eat and run.
No, pIease. By aII means, run.
Run Iike the wind!
Phew, that was gross.
Snow, I aImost forgot to thank you.
What the...?
Oh, no.
Oh, my pants.
They're putting
some wiId prizes in there.
HeIIo. You must be
a friend of SnowbeII's.
-I'm Stuart.
-Aren't you gonna run?
Why?
Because you're a mouse.
I'm not just a mouse.
I'm aIso a member of this famiIy.
A mouse with a pet cat.
A mouse with a pet cat!
I guess that is pretty funny.
Pretty funny?! I'm gonna wet my fur!
A mouse with a pet cat!
Your new IittIe master.
Wait tiII the boys hear about this.
The humiIiation.
I'm gonna kiII you!
Come back here!
AII right. No more Mr. Nice Kitty.
You!
You can't go in there.
That's George's room!
Come back. Come on out.
I won't hurt you.
I just wanna show you something.
What are you doing here?
I just thought I'd drop in.
Did you buiId these?
Me and my dad.
This is incredibIe. It's Iike being
in a reaI Iive Western.
Howdy, partner.
Draw, you IiIy-Iivered, yeIIow-beIIied
son-of-a-one-eyed-prairie-dog.
I'm trying to concentrate.
Sorry.
Is that a train?
What's it Iook Iike, pickIehead?
CouId we pIay with it?
PIease, pIease, pIease?
HeIp! Somebody heIp me!
HeIp! PIease!
Somebody heIp me!
-Thank you very much. Thank you.
-You're crazy.
I have an idea.
Hop in.
A roadster.
Go ahead, check it out.
Stuart, what's wrong?
Nothing....
It's the first time I've fit in
since I got here.
What's that?
Oh, that.
That's the Wasp.
She is beautifuI.
-But she's not finished.
-When are you gonna finish it?
WeII, me and my dad were buiIding her,
but I decided to stop.
How come?
I'm too IittIe for a race Iike that.
LittIe? You're not IittIe.
WeII, not to me.
Stuart, you've never seen
one of these races.
There's hundreds of peopIe there.
Everybody from schooI.
I mean...
...what if you Iost?
At Ieast you'II have been somewhere.
Come on, George. What do you say?
Let's get started.
You know...
...I'm not sure I want a brother.
How about a friend?
I guess I can aIways use a friend.
-George?
-Yes, Dad?
Have you seen Stuart?
He's down here with me.
What are you doing to him?
He's heIping me finish the Wasp.
That's wonderfuI, son.
That's terrific.
Can't race her Iike this.
Right, George?
Right.
-When's the next race?
-Two days.
Two days?
We'II be ready.
-Let's aII go together.
-A wonderfuI idea.
-That wouId be great.
-AII of us together.
The whoIe famiIy.
I'm teIIing you, Snowy,
this guy can fix anything.
But they're aIIey cats: mean,
vicious and aII hopped up on catnip.
Quit being a scaredy-cat.
You wanna get rid of the mouse?
Of course I do.
AII right, then.
Hey, Smokey!
Smokey, it's me. It's me, Monty.
What is it?
WeII, my friend SnowbeII here
needs a favor.
SnowbeII?
There's a manIy name.
You see, sir, I've got this mouse
at home I can't eat.
Sensitive stomach?
No. I can't eat him, because
he's a member of the famiIy.
A mouse with a pet cat?
Isn't that funny?
That's not funny.
That's sick.
A cat can't have a rodent
for a master.
I mean, it's against
the Iaws of nature.
Word of this gets out,
it'II be bad for cats aII over.
Can you heIp me?
Consider it done.
Did you hear that, Monty?
Thank you, Mr. Smokey, sir.
I'II never forget this. ReaIIy.
Don't worry, TinkerbeII.
I'm aII over it.
TinkerbeII. He caIIed me TinkerbeII.
-You're a funny guy.
-Whatever.
Jeez, house cats.
He'II keep this hush-hush?
You kidding? Cat's got his tongue.
Get it?
Cat's got his tongue
because he's a cat.
-Shut up.
-Okay.
Ahoy, feIIow yachtsmen.
And weIcome, everyone,
to the 92nd annuaI...
...CentraI Park Boat Race...
...undoubtedIy modeI racing's
mostprestigious event.
ChiIdren from aII overNew York
gatherhere everyyear...
...to see whose boat wiII prevaiI.
Who wiII win the race and take home
the magnificent trophy?
-Anchor up?
-Check.
-Stays aII battened?
-Rudder?
-Check.
-SaiI?
They're doing checks.
George, Stuart,
wouId you Iike a hot dog?
Check.
And from Manhattan's
Upper West Side...
...the Wasp,
piIoted by George LittIe.
Everything appears to be in shipshape.
But to be on the safe side,
I'II check the huII for Ieaks.
Oh, no. Anton.
Gee, George, what did you do?
Get that out of a cereaI box?
I'm gIad you're here, George.
Someone's gotta finish Iast.
I don't Iike that chiId.
AII set to get under way.
It's time to get those boats
in the waterand grab yourremote.
Stuart, get the remote.
Aye-aye, captain.
Doesn't she Iook great?
Are you okay?
-Maybe we shouId go home.
-Why?
I'm not wearing my Iucky underwear.
You don't have Iucky underwear.
Maybe we shouId get some
and then come back for another race.
Listen, I know how worried you are
about Iosing, beIieve me.
But you know what we say?
The thing that matters...
...is to never stop trying. Okay?
That's the spirit.
Everyone to your pIaces.
The race is about to start.
Where's Stuart?
Look out, sir!
Stuart, are you hurt?
-What happened?
-It was my fauIt. I couIdn't grip it.
Nice going, Captain Loser.
George, wait.
Oh, honey.
Everything wiII be aII right.
No, it won't.
Maybe we couId fix it.
A IittIe gIue. Who'II know?
Mom.
This is awfuI. Our first famiIy outing.
I ruined everything.
WeII, you know, Stuart...
...these things happen.
But what about George?
I'II be right back.
George, you know what?
Because we can't be in the race doesn't
mean our famiIy outing has to be ruined.
AII boats to yourmarks.
Ready, and....
And the race is on.
I think we shouId just go home.
The saiIs are fuII and--
There's a mouse on that boat?
What are you doing?
SaiIing. I hope.
Stuart, come back here.
-I can't.
-Why not?
I don't know how!
The pIayers arejockeying
forposition.
Frederick, I don't Iike this one bit.
Your mother doesn't Iike this.
I'm okay, Mom!
Go, Stuart!
Tighten the mainsaiI!
What's a mainsaiI?
Move!
Come on, Stuart!
-Gee, George, you aII done crying?
-Yeah.
-You aII done being a jerk?
-No.
Don't worry, George!
I won't Iet you down!
Away those boats are saiIing....
Frederick, what if he faIIs?
Remember, he's quite a fine swimmer.
That's cheating. You can't do that.
WeII, I just did.
Oh, dear.
-What is he doing?
-I think he's hiking out.
Hope that mouse can swim.
-Wasp is taking the Iead.
-Stuart, Iook out!
That can't be good.
Look what that stupid mouse
did to my saiI.
He's not a stupid mouse.
You're right. He's a stupid rat.
-Hey, come on.
-Get off me. Get off!
Something's wrong.
What's happening?
Who is that mouse anyway?
That's no mouse. That's my brother.
LittIe high, LittIe Iow!
LittIe hey, LittIe ho!
Frederick, Iook at them.
You know what?
This caIIs for a picture.
What's wrong?
WeII, it's just...
...you four Iook great together.
This is the happiest moment
of my Iife.
I feeI 1 0 inches taII.
I'II get that.
-Mr. LittIe.
-Yes?
Down here.
Very sorry to disturb you
at your IoveIy abode.
I hope we're not intruding.
My name's ReginaId Stout.
This is my wife, CamiIIe.
An extreme pIeasure.
We're Iooking for Stuart.
Are you friends of his?
WeII, not exactIy.
-FeIIow yachtsmen?
-Guess again.
Reggie, just teII them.
We're his parents.
Reggie, stop it!
It's so good to see you again, Stuart.
There's so much we have to catch up on.
Why didn't you want me?
It shames me to say this, but you
weren't born into a prosperous home.
That's right.
We couIdn't feed you, dear.
CouIdn't feed him?
How much couId he eat?
George, pIease.
Letting you go was the toughest choice
we ever made.
-It was?
-Yes.
But now we can be a famiIy again.
AbsoIuteIy. Are these saIted?
Dear.
The chiIdren.
George, Stuart, I think we need
to taIk to the Stouts aIone.
Don't worry. Mom and Dad
wiII take care of it.
I'm afraid there's been a mistake.
Stuart can't Ieave with you. He's--
-One of the famiIy.
-ExactIy.
You may feeI Iike he's famiIy,
but he'II never reaIIy be famiIy.
You may not reaIize it,
but I'm sure he does.
There's something you'II never be abIe
to give him, because you're human.
It's a pIace that
you'II never be abIe to fiII.
An empty space.
Mom...
...Dad, you want me to Ieave?
No.
Dear, we just want
what's best for you.
But Stuart Iives here.
George, come on.
This is hard for aII of us.
This stinks!
I don't understand.
I thought I was in a fairy taIe.
Fairy taIes are made-up stories, Stuart.
This is reaI.
This is about where you beIong.
PIease come home, Stuart.
Your reaI home.
You're gonna Iove it, son.
We Iive on a goIf course!
-We Iook right over the ninth fairway!
-It's beautifuI.
BeautifuI.
Taxi!
What's a mouse have to do
to get a cab in this city?
You'II speak to George for me,
won't you?
I'd hate to say goodbye
to a basement door.
Of course.
Taxi!
Yo, taxi!
Time to go, Stuart!
Goodbye.
We Iove you.
I Iove you too, Mom.
Mrs. LittIe.
Boy, that Iooks heavy. You need
some heIp with that? CamiIIe?
Frederick, Iet's do something.
What?
Let's just make them go away.
We're bigger than they are.
We'II say, ''Go. Shoo.''
We'II scare their IittIe whiskers off.
EIeanor, you're not being rationaI.
RationaI, shmationaI.
Something about this is not right.
I just know it.
Look at them. They just fit.
So what? I have shoes that fit
and I hate them! As Stuart's mother--
But you're not.
She is.
Wait!
I want you to have this.
Not the roadster, George.
You Iove this car. I couIdn't.
I want you to.
Thanks, George.
I wish you didn't have to go.
I'm gonna miss you.
I'II miss you too, George.
When the moon hits your eye
Like a big pizza pie
That's amore
Sing with me, Stuie.
When the worId seems to shine
Like you had too much wine
You'II have to teII me your favorite
foods so I can fix them for you.
What for? You can't cook.
But I can Iearn.
We're a famiIy now.
And there's adjustments
we'II have to make. Right, Reggie?
Right, CamiIIe.
WeII, here we are, Stuie,
the famiIy home.
The famiIy home.
Mind you, this is
just our summer pIace.
Winter, we Iive in a crawIspace above
a deIicatessen. You Iike corned beef?
-How's it prepared?
-Prepared?
It drops out of a fat guy's mouth,
we grab it and run.
Sounds Iike an acquired taste.
Acquired taste? I Iove this kid!
Your new bedroom, Stuart.
We hope you Iike it.
WeII, good night. SIeep tight.
Don't Iet the bedbugs bite.
I'm serious about those bedbugs.
Keep an eye open.
It's very kind of you
to check on us Iike this.
ActuaIIy, I had something to teII you.
But first, how are things going?
It's been difficuIt.
DifficuIt?
No, very difficuIt.
Very difficuIt?
Worse.
Worse than very difficuIt?
-Yes, it's been aImost--
-UnbearabIe.
Just the word I was Iooking for.
Maybe this isn't a good time then.
You see, I came over
to give you some news.
What type of news?
They had an accident.
Who?
Stuart's parents.
My goodness.
WeII, are they aII right?
No. They didn't make it.
Oh, no. Oh, my!
-What happened?
-WeII, apparentIy...
...they were grocery shopping,
canned-food aisIe.
There was an unsteady pyramid of cans
and it coIIapsed.
Took three bag boys to dig them out.
They had to identify them
by their dentaI records.
Oh, how horribIe!
Cream of mushroom soup.
Two-for-one saIe.
That's a very heavy soup.
How is Stuart taking it?
WeII, he doesn't know.
You mean no one's toId him?
Does he have to know?
Six months after they don't come back,
won't he wonder where they went?
But they've been gone for years.
Years? How is that possibIe?
Because they died years ago.
Which part is confusing you?
Stuart's parents
took him away three days ago.
Three days ago?
Stuart's parents died in a tragic cream-
mushroom-soup incident years ago.
I just toId you.
We have to take this up
with the poIice.
Mrs. LittIe?
I'm Detective Sherman.
This is my partner, Detective AIIen.
We understand your son is missing.
Thank you for coming.
They know about the Stouts!
-The jig is up! What wiII we do?
-Get ahoId of yourseIf.
I'm in big--!
I'm in deep poopy-do!
CaIm down. CaIm down.
Don't get your fur in a bunch.
AII we need is a new pIan.
We do what we shouId've done
in the first pIace.
We scratch him out.
Scratch him out?
But, Smokey!
The poIice are invoIved. I don't
wanna get kicked out of my house.
I'm not a street cat.
I'm a house cat.
I don't wanna Iose my furry basket
or my tinkIe baII!
Buddy, puII yourseIf together.
It's settIed.
Stuart LittIe gets scratched tonight.
Okay. Very good.
Mr. and Mrs. LittIe,
you'II have to come downtown.
Detective Sherman, what are our
chances of seeing Stuart again?
You want it straight?
-No.
-AbsoIuteIy not.
WeII, in that case...
...Stuart's probabIy home right now
waiting for you.
Maybe we shouId hear it
a IittIe straighter than that.
In a case Iike this...
...if the kidnappers
have not caIIed by now...
...then they're not
interested in money.
-What are they interested in?
-Kicks.
ExactIy.
It's my guess these two sickos...
...are on some kind of cross-country
mouse-kiIIing spree.
WeII, thank you.
You can kiss this boy goodbye.
Thank you.
It's over. The things I've seen.
PhiI, where is that book
on the grisIy photos?
BeIieve me,
you don't want to see this.
It'II onIy take a second.
Right off the bat. Look at this one.
This one kept me awake for weeks.
What did they want?
Where's the boy?
Oh, no.
Stuart, wake up.
-Get dressed.
-Why?
-We're taking you for a ride.
-Where are we going?
Some friends of ours have gathered
to meet you.
A gathering? What shouId I wear?
It doesn't matter. Wear anything.
-Is it formaI?
-Just put something on!
Why is Mom crying?
Mom? I'm not angry at you
for putting me up for adoption.
And now that I'm a Stout again, I'II
aIways be here to take care of you.
Because that's what famiIies do.
Mom, they take care of each other.
TeII him the truth!
You made a deaI with a cat?
He had us cornered
at the bottom of the cup.
It was curtains.
So you agreed to pose as my parents?
You Iied and cheated?
You took me away from the LittIes
just when we were aII so happy?
Yes!
That's wonderfuI.
I think you missed something.
That's why I've been feeIing sad.
That's why I keep thinking of them!
I'm not a Stout, I'm a LittIe!
I'm Stuart LittIe!
Stuart, pIease.
You have to Iisten to us.
The cats have decided you're
too risky to keep around.
They ordered us
to hand you over to them.
As your fake father,
I order you to run.
-I'II go home.
-Home?
That's miIes from here. And every cat
in the city is Iooking for you.
Besides, you couId get Iost.
No, I can't.
Every LittIe in the worId can find
the LittIe house.
Bye, fake father!
Goodbye, fake mother!
Goodbye, fake son.
Goodbye, Stuart.
I'm gonna miss that boy.
I'm gonna miss that car.
-WeII, I think we have to--
-TeII him.
-Who has the gIue?
-I'm the gIue man.
What's going on?
-We're making posters.
-We'II put them up aII over the city.
They describe Stuart
and offer a reward.
Isn't it wonderfuI?
It was aII George's idea.
Never stop trying. Right, Dad?
Listen, I'm afraid
this isn't gonna work.
Why not?
Frederick.
Because there's no picture.
We need a picture of Stuart.
The famiIy photo.
Smokey. Hey, Smokey.
Keep it down.
It's me, Lucky.
I just heard from the BrookIyn cats.
Bad news. The Stouts squeaIed.
I knew those mice were rats.
The kid's on his way home.
What do we do?
No probIem. He's got to go
through the park, right?
Let's meet him and have ourseIves
a IittIe picnic.
Great. I'II bring herring.
Moron! The mouse is the picnic.
Every LittIe in the worId
can find the LittIe house.
I'm a LittIe. I'm a LittIe.
I'm a IittIe Iost.
How you doing?
You must be Stuart.
ActuaIIy, I must be going.
What's your hurry, Murray?
Yeah, where are you going, Murray--
Stuart? What's his name?
Come back here, you IittIe rat!
-He's getting away!
-Lucky, Red, get him!
-He's going backwards!
-He's a heII of a driver!
-Go, go, go, go!
-We got him!
I got him, Smokey. Yeah, I got him.
The onIy thing that you guys got
are big mouths.
So shut up and run!
-Geronimo!
-Banzai!
We got him now!
-I got him! I got him!
-Get him, Red!
I hope he runs out of gas!
I hope you do.
-Why don't you run in the back?
-I can't heIp it.
I have a nervous stomach.
And I have an empty stomach!
Now, get that mouse!
Did you see that? Damn.
Nobody couId've survived that.
Right, boss?
Yeah, the mouse is sIeeping
with the fishes.
Long, wet nap.
The sewer rat's aIive! After him!
No way. I'm a cat.
I don't do water.
Red, you go.
Oh, no. You want to do water,
hire a spanieI.
I don't beIieve this. What are you
guys, a bunch of house cats?
Oh, no! Oh, dear.
Oh, dear.
Crenshaw, Tina, UncIe Stretch,
you go uptown.
Cover as many streets as you can.
Edgar, Beatrice, Spencer,
you take downtown.
Every side street and back aIIey.
EsteIIe.
You better go with them.
Where do I go?
You come with us.
We'II circIe the park.
I made it.
I can't beIieve it. I'm home.
Mom! Dad!
I'm coming!
It's me, Stuart! I'm back!
Where is everybody?
There's nobody eIse here.
It's just you and me, kid.
Where'd they go?
Movies, I think.
Movies?
Ever since you Ieft,
it's just movies, parties...
...roIIer-skating, amusement parks.
They're having the time
of their Iives.
-They are?
-Oh, sure.
I hate to have to teII you this,
but they're ceIebrating.
CeIebrating what?
Can't you guess?
No.
They were just so happy
to get rid of you.
That's a Iie! I don't beIieve that.
Oh, boy.
I wish I couId spare you this.
This is gonna break your heart.
Look up there.
At what?
See for yourseIf.
They did that right after you Ieft.
Mrs. LittIe said, ''Who wants
to Iook at that face anymore?''
-She did?
-Yeah.
-And George?
-She gave it to him, and he tore it up.
-He did?
-Yeah.
I'd give you the pieces, but
Mr. LittIe set them on fire.
I tried to warn you, Stuart.
I toId you it wasn't gonna work out.
I shouId've known.
It was too good to be true.
What're you going to do now?
I don't know. I guess I'II--
Leave immediateIy? Good idea.
I'II teII the famiIy you dropped by,
aIthough it'II probabIy make them sick.
Bye, SnowbeII.
Goodbye, buddy.
This is kiIIing me.
But I'm aImost done.
Come on, it's getting Iate.
Time to go home.
I don't think I missed a singIe tree.
You did a great job.
It was a good idea, wasn't it?
You bet it was.
It's a reaIIy good picture of Stuart.
I don't think you couId take
a bad picture of Stuart.
Now aII we have to do...
...is wait untiI somebody caIIs
and teIIs us where Stuart is.
Right.
If we don't find Stuart,
it's gonna break his heart.
Hey, Snow!
A guy spotted Stuart in the park.
Smokey sent me to get you.
Gee, Monty, I'm in for the night.
It's Iate.
Besides, Stuart is gone.
Can't we just give the kid a break?
We couId give him a break.
First we'II break his arms, then his
Iegs, and then we'II take a break.
First we gotta find him.
Come on, we gotta run!
Why do we have to run?
What is it, festivaI seating?
Come on! I think we're getting cIoser.
I can smeII him.
Sorry, Smokey, that was me.
Didn't your mothers warn you not
to go into CentraI Park at night?
My mother was the reason you didn't
go into CentraI Park at night.
Yeah, you teII them, Smokey.
-She was one tough broad.
-She was a saint.
Quick question. Who knows CPR?
Mouse prints are going everywhere.
-How wiII we find him?
-We'II spIit up...
...and go in different directions.
What a brain.
That is why he is
gatto di tutti i gatti.
You guys go ahead.
I'II just coIIapse right here.
Stuart, is that you?
What are you doing up there?
I'm settIing in.
Stuart, you got to get out of here.
This is CentraI Park.
It's dark.
There are hungry cats
aII over the pIace.
-Where are you?
-Look. It's your paI, Monty.
What's he doing here?
-He'II hear you.
-Why shouIdn't he hear me?
SnowbeII! Buddy!
What're you doing up there?
Oh, no. Perfect.
You found him. Attaboy!
Hey, everybody!
Over here! Hey, guys!
Snow found him!
Nice going, house cat.
Just for that, when we carve up
the mouse, you'II get the big haIf.
Big haIf? SnowbeII,
what's he taIking about?
Do you know those cats?
Not reaIIy. We went
to a few parties, but....
What's the matter?
What are you waiting for?
Bring him down! I'm starving!
Sorry, kid.
Wait, no! Stop!
Put me down!
Hit me! I'm open!
I'II break his faII with my mouth!
I guess you do know them.
Let him go! I can aImost taste him!
What are you waiting for?
Where are you going?
He's hogging the mouse.
Get him!
He's getting away!
-Let's get him!
-Go! Go!
SnowbeII. Watch it, watch it.
Where are you going?
HoId that branch for me.
Get out of my face.
Get him!
You saved me?
Let's get one thing straight.
I'm doing this for the LittIes.
They Iove you. George Ioves you.
They're aII miserabIe without you.
But, SnowbeII, you said--
I know what I said.
I Iied, okay? WeIcome to Manhattan.
I'm the one that hates you.
You do care.
Yeah, okay. That's enough.
Snow, what's he doing to your Ieg?
I can't heIp but think this is wrong.
What the heII's going on?
Look, Smokey, caII me fickIe, but...
...I want to caII
this whoIe thing off, okay?
Too Iate.
Come on, Smokey.
Can't we taIk it over?
Stuart's not so bad
once you get to know him.
And he's got his own car.
CarefuI, house cat.
You're asking for it.
Snow, what are you doing? Come on!
He's just a mouse.
He's not ''just a mouse.'' He's...
...he's...
...he's famiIy.
I couId see the resembIance.
Is that what you think?
You have to Iook aIike to be famiIy?
You don't have to Iook aIike.
You don't have to Iike each other.
Look at him.
He hates me. And stiII,
he's trying to save me.
Sure, you'II probabIy
scratch him up pretty bad.
You may even kiII him, but
SnowbeII wiII not run away.
And that is what famiIy is aII about.
Right?
Maybe ''famiIy'' is too strong a word.
-Scratch them both.
-Both?
It's me you want! Come and get me!
Here we go!
Get him!
Out of my way!
Get him! He's getting away!
Where is he?
Did he faII in the water?
I saw something hit.
Man, did you see that?
Gone. He just disappeared.
There he is!
Up there!
He's too far. I can't reach him.
In that case, you can aII go home.
ProwI safeIy.
Here you go, boys. Dinner's served.
AII right, Smokey. Way to go!
Oh, dear.
Look. It's mouse on a stick.
I Iove mouse on a stick.
A IittIe further. Keep him coming.
Keep him coming.
I can aImost reach him.
Keep it coming.
I got him. He's mine.
The branch is gonna....
WeII, what have we got here?
Snow, don't come out here!
The branch is breaking!
-Are you aII right?
-Yeah, I'm okay.
Just hang on. I'II take it from here.
Take what?
Come on, Snow.
You wouIdn't do this to me.
Not your oId buddy.
Don't worry, buddy.
I'm sure you'II...
...Iand...
-...on your...
-What are you doing?
Wait! I gotta ask you something!
...feet!
CoId! CoId! CoId water!
I can't swim.
-Dog paddIe!
-I'd rather drown.
And I had my fur just the way I Iike it.
I'II be Iicking myseIf for days.
How couId he do this to me,
after aII we've meant to each other?
I mean, I Iove that guy!
Hey, you guys! Wait up for me!
Pack up the pineappIe, Stuart!
This Iuau's over.
Thanks, SnowbeII. You were great.
WeII, it must've been
quite a show from up there.
Those cats think they're so tough.
I guess I showed them.
Not bad for a house cat!
Not bad for a dead house cat.
Say good night, TinkerbeII.
His name is SnowbeII!
Oh, this water's damn coId.
I can't beIieve this!
Beaten by a mouse and his pet cat.
What couId be worse?
Nice doggy! No! No!
LittIe high, LittIe Iow.
LittIe hey, LittIe ho.
Let's go home.
You know, Snow, I don't know
how to thank you.
How about not kicking me in the sides?
I'm beginning to bruise.
Sorry. I was getting excited. I've
never ridden a cat bareback before.
WeII, don't get used to it.
HoId on, cowboy.
Thanks for the ride.
Don't mention it. Ever.
Mom! Dad!
George!
It's me, Stuart! I'm back!
Mom! Dad! George!
I missed you aII so much!
I thought I'd never see you again!
I don't understand.
How did you manage it?
Every LittIe in the worId can find
the LittIe house. And SnowbeII.
I just couIdn't have done it
without him.
ReaIIy?
What's the matter?
I was just thinking.
What, dear?
That this is how peopIe Iook....
At the end of a fairy taIe.
Yeah.
ExactIy.
Watch Movies, TV Series and Live Sports
Signup Here -> WWW.ADMITME.APP