Subtitles by explosiveskull
Resync by GoldenBeard
Someone needs to stop Clearway Law.
Public shouldn't leave reviews for lawyers.
We're three kilometers
off the coast, Vertigo.
Keep it steady, Manta.
I'll go rouse the rabble.
Time to move.
I'm good to go.
Sponge and Julie, not so sure.
Didn't Waller get you
a room last night?
Don't be a hater, Floyd.
Or are you just upset because
Waller didn't put you in charge.
Yeah, why is that, Deadshot?
You usually run things.
She asked me if her dress
made her look fat.
She's gotten cranky
since she lost weight.
Not our issue.
Is it, Daddy?
We are just having our second
honeymoon anywhere we can.
Not on my time, convict.
The only one who gets
satisfied tonight is me.
Your target is an underboss in the
Black Mask mob, Tobias Whale,
who happens to sideline
in stolen intel.
Tonight, he's delivering a
flash drive full of nastiness.
Pay-offs to dictators, senators playing
footsies in the restroom, the usual.
More importantly,
he has leaked info
implicating our
very own operations.
Needless to say, Mama would be very
disappointed if you screwed this up.
So keep your heads
on the mission
if you want to keep them
on your shoulders.
Any questions?
Good.
They're all yours, Vertigo.
I'll be on radio silence
till you're done.
Waller out.
You heard the lady.
Show off.
All right, goddamn it.
So I says if the money's good,
who gives a shit, huh?
Hey. Oh...
Ah! Oh. Ugh!
Ah!
You still got it, baby.
And it's all yours, Daddy.
You're that fool, Deadshot.
Ain't this some shit?
Did Black Mask find out about
my sidekick and send you?
I'm gonna mess you up real good.
It's his turn.
Expletive deleted and the
free world is saved again.
Stay down, dog.
What the heck's going on?
This wasn't part of the mission.
Vertigo...
Why?
Aw, honeymoon's over.
What about him?
I'd rather not kill him
at the same wound.
He'd wonder about that.
I say we let the train
run him over.
You're working together?
Working, playing...
We're soulmates.
Even in prison, things can be
arranged.
What about the file?
We make a copy,
give Waller back the original.
She'll never know
and then, when the grieving
widow and I are paroled,
we'll have a little nest-egg.
She knows.
What?
Waller.
She's been listening.
You're lying,
I'm team leader.
She knew there was
a traitor somewhere.
Waller? Listen to me, I beg to you.
Floyd, please, don't let her.
I know, I know I was a bad girl.
And it was all Vertigo's idea.
Please don't let her
kill me, Floyd!
Don't let her blow my head off.
She's down, Waller. Turn it off.
A mercy killing.
Getting soft on me, Lawton?
Just saving on the dry cleaning.
Stop this madness.
You can't get rid of me.
I am not some vestigial twin
you can excise like a skin tag.
Hey, Doc, I'm getting sick
of hearing this guy's crap.
Ain't you got something
that'll knock him out.
Anasthetic!
Where is the anasthetic?
Well, that's just peachy.
No anasthetic?
You're all insane!
Shut your pie hole,
we're gonna do this.
Just show me again, Doc,
one more time.
Voila.
Beautiful.
No. No. No. No!
Drill.
We'll start around the eye.
Oh, thank God, he was
going to disfigure me.
That lunatic. That...
How dare you?
This is an operating theater
not some abattoir.
We have a patient
for you, Professor.
A person in need of
medical attention.
We're wondering if you could
clear your schedule. Hmm?
A patient in need is always
my first consideration.
Good answer.
Mail call, Lawton.
Morning, sunshine.
Get another offer from
Gun Fund Monthly, did you?
No, wait a tick.
It's your little girl, isn't it?
Aw, did she reject another
letter from dear old dad?
How old is she now, 13, 14?
Her uncle bought her any more, eh?
I get bored crazy in that age.
Tell you what, girls like her
need a daddy.
How'd you reckon?
Well, get paroled early
maybe Uncle Digger
can look her up.
Oh! Christ! Son of a...
You could've put my eye out.
Must be gettin' rusty.
Boomer's government property.
You break it, you buy it.
Hiya, cowboy.
How's Trix?
Oh, not that crazy broad again.
My choices have been
dwindling lately.
I heard about
poor little Julie?
Beats all my luck, you know.
But I offered to give her a whole
new makeover with a baseball bat.
Who else?
You heard of Killer Frost?
- The ice queen.
- Yeah.
Crystal Frost, a tough girl
from a tougher home.
Her parents were, well...
Let's just say they could've
used some discipline themselves.
Then her metahuman powers
kicked in,
and suddenly, Mom and Dad
were put on ice.
They never knew how cold
her heart really was.
They say she couldn't be tamed, but I think
Little Crystal's warmed up to us considerably.
And then there's Copperhead, AKA
Sameer Park, a meta contortionist
heavily into extreme
body modification.
If his bio tech tail isn't repulsive
enough, he also shoots acid venom.
Say hello, Copperhead.
The last is Bronze Tiger,
AKA Ben Turner.
Ex-CIA, then vigilante.
Possibly the greatest
martial artist in the world.
If it weren't for his vow never to take
an innocent life, I'd put him incharge.
I can feel the love.
Open wide, Ms. Frost.
Bite me.
Thank you. Try not to move.
We wouldn't want the appartus
to go off accidentally.
It happened once
to the ten-eyed man.
Who?
Exactly.
Insertion's complete.
Task force X is
locked and loaded.
Woo-hoo!
What's this all about, Waller?
This is about making me
happy, Tiger.
This time I'm searching
for something special.
A lost card.
Just call the bank, honey.
They'll get you a new one.
What's it got?
Some kind of code?
You might say.
The last person who had it
was this man.
He calls himself "Steel Maxim."
Seriously?
Late 20s, no distinguishing
marks, except for a tramp stamp.
An Egyptian Ankh.
We think he played a part
in the card's disappearance.
But he's been hard
to track down.
Find him, and I'll slice a year
of all your sentences.
Oh, great, only 87 more
suicide missions to go.
Cheers, Waller.
One more thing.
This one's off the grid.
You'll be dealing with me
directly and only me.
Deadshot will be
your team leader.
I told you before, Waller, I don't
take orders from murderers.
Not even if I said, "Please"?
I answer to a higher authority.
Higher than Waller? That
sounds like blasphemy, mate.
I'd say maybe we should
take this outside.
But that's up to her.
Settle down, love birds.
It's too early to start
losing your heads just yet.
I've requisitioned
this vehicle for your mission.
You're kidding?
Like I said,
this one is off the books.
No hotels...
Roadtrip!
I guess that'll save us from having
to explain him to the concierge.
Hiss.
Hey, we got cheese dogs
and Chicken Nuggies!
Blow me up now.
It's about time.
Your late, you waste of flesh.
Banshee, is that any way
to talk to our associate?
Please, see him in.
Word is, they gave her
six months tops,
so really wants the card
bad now.
It's all there, all the information
Waller has on the card.
Your text said
she sent out Task Force X.
Last night,
I tried to get these to you
sooner, but I have to be careful.
The Wall has eyes everywhere.
I shouldn't be gone too long.
Uh, thanks.
Before you rush off, you neglected to
tell me where Waller is sending them.
Branson.
The man they're tracking, he's been
spotted there looking for work.
What does he do?
He's an...
entertainer.
- Whoa, whoa, whoa.
- Hey!
Park in the back.
Oh, yeah, whoo!
- Woo-hoo, yeah!
- Curb it, clown.
We don't wanna call attention
to ourselves.
Honey, in case you haven't
noticed, nobody's looking at us.
- Split up.
- Dibs on backstage!
Woo-hoo. I like that!
I'm going.
Look at the bag of marbles
on that fella.
You missed your calling, Snake eyes,
chicks would go crazy for you.
Bored now. Going out.
Uh-uh, we're on standby.
Deadshot gave us montior duty.
So much for not taking orders
from murderers, eh, Benji?
Shut it, Boomer.
Sit your ass down.
Make me, dolomite.
I don't kill innocents.
But I doubt if you'd qualify.
Pull it back.
Or I'll rip your mouth in half.
You're on a mission,
you don't wander away, you don't make
trouble, and you don't piss me off.
We didn't see him.
This nut job was
frisking the boys.
I had to cool her off.
Psychotics have needs, you know?
We have needs.
We're moving to the next club.
This is gonna take forever.
Well, we could always
put up some flyers.
Ladies and ladies,
it's that king from Cairo,
the sphinx of kinks,
the sandstorm guaranteed
to blow you away.
Oh!
Get ready to sweat
for the Pharaoh!
Didn't see him backstage.
Me likey.
It's him.
- Banshee! Oh, crap!
- Where're you going?
Shit!
Oh, crap! Oh, crap!
Uh. No!
No!
Oh, this is bad.
Buddy Frankenstein?
Whoa!
Zoom, what the hell?
What are you waiting for?
Do I have to do everything?
Hiya, cowboy, need a ride?
Get us out of here!
Heads up, mate.
Ha ha. Right in the gulleys.
- Something's wrong.
- Yeah, he's too fast for him.
No, he's too slow.
He should've broken into this
jalopy and killed us all by now.
He's still mine.
Frost, on the right!
Pfft. Come on. You don't understand.
I've got a 10:00 a.m. call back
for Bachelor Babe.
Really? Aw, that's
my favorite show.
It's so romantic like you're
the only girl at a frat party.
Oh, you're not going anywhere,
buddy, until we get some answers.
Like why're you
so popular with Zoom?
How should I know?
I've never even seen the guy.
But you knew Silver Banshee.
The second you saw her,
you bolted.
Yeah, everyone knows who
Silver Banshee is.
Uh, no.
Okay, okay, so we crossed
paths a few times. So what?
Listen to this tosser.
How'd a nobody like you
even get Banshee's attention?
Because I was Fate.
Dr. Fate. I used to be
Dr. Fate, okay?
Shut up.
It's true. It's not like
I was the only one.
There have been a lot of Fates.
Uh, they're chosen by
the spirit of Nabu.
Oh, yeah?
Why'd he choose you?
Uh, why not me?
Six percent body fat,
20 inch guns.
Hell, I even took
a magic class once.
So, I was going strong at the end
of this 10k when I saw it, uh...
him.
And at first,
I thought he was God.
I just couldn't figure
what religion.
And Nabu wasn't much of a talker
but when I had that helmet on,
it was like, I didn't need
to hear him at all.
Like, I knew what to do.
Let me tell you,
I was hella hot.
Superhero-hot.
Banshee was sprung as soon
as she laid eyes on moi.
I mean, come on. Sure she
played hard to get at first.
But I know that
she knew what was up.
Oh, she knew.
Oh, yeah.
She knew.
Oh, my God, they did it.
That was sweet day.
I mean, Nabu hooked me up
with my own place.
Sometimes I'd have to
fight off hell dogs,
and you know,
some crazy demons.
But I spent most of the time
dusting his knick-knacks.
This dude had everything
but a dead monkey.
But of all the junk,
the thing that Nabu cherished
the absolute most
was the smallest.
A shiny black card.
It had writing on it.
"Get out of hell free?"
It's crazy, I know, I read about
it in one of Nabu's books.
Supposedly, if you have this
card on you when you die,
you bypass hell and
you go straight to heaven.
Oh, like a DFA pass.
Yeah.
A whole lot of blood should we
start to have a card like that.
Yeah, but only one person can
use it, then it's used up.
All I know is that damn card
screwed up my situation for good.
What do you mean?
I'd been there about
two months, and it gets old.
So one evening, I hit this bar
and I meet this redhead.
And she's so hot.
So I said to her...
You don't know it yet, baby,
but you just met your fate.
Cornball? Yes, but it works.
Especially when I bring her
back to my place.
She had this girlfriend
with her, kinda hard and quiet,
not really my type but
they were a package deal.
Like I'm gonna say no to that?
It started off great.
But after a while,
I got a little suspicious
'cause the butch one hadn't
joined in the fun yet.
I mean, who can say no
to all of this. Am I right?
And I catch her red-handed
boosting the freaking card.
I mean, who does that?
And the only thing they took
was the card.
Everything else was untouched.
Including me.
You think he cared?
He didn't even give me
a chance to explain.
A couple of days later, I called up
my girlfriend, and she was freaking.
She said people were looking
for me, government types.
They were asking about the card.
Like I knew where it was.
Anyway, she blocked me, so I called
up my sidechick, same thing.
Finally, I ran out of options.
So I changed my name and have
been lying low ever since.
Calling yourself "Steel Maxim,"
and stripping.
That's lying low to you?
It's called hiding
in plain sight, sweetheart.
Anyway, you gotta believe me,
I had nothing to do
with the card,
I swear on my life!
So who's Dr. Fate now?
I heard Nabu
picked some chick.
You get all that?
I got it.
He's telling the truth.
Useless.
But at least now,
we know who took the card.
Sounded like Scandal Savage
and Knockout.
But it didn't sound like
their kind of heist.
It's not.
I bet my eyeteeth that her daddy
Vandal Savage is on this.
According to
the Justice League database,
that bastard is
a 50,000 year old caveman
who was affected by radiation
from a meteorite.
Yeah, I know.
Anyway, you might be familiar
with his other nom de plume.
Alexander the Great, Caesar,
Genghis Khan.
He's history's bloodiest tyrant.
And you're going after him.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, I didn't signup
to deal with an immortal butcher.
You didn't sign up for anything.
I run the op the way I want,
and I want that card, Deadshot.
I need it.
It's Savage, Waller,
you gotta give me something.
But we already have Zoom
on our ass.
I can't go back to them
with nothing.
Fine. Ten years.
I'll give you ten years off.
You know what that
means for you?
You're out.
If you're in...
So when do we get the show
on the road?
Drive.
What do we do
with Magic Mike?
Hey!
Not cool.
At least you could call me
a car, assholes.
Which exit, cowboy?
Waller said to keep going
north until we hear from her.
I'm surprised she really
believes this mumbo-jumbo.
- Do you?
- What?
You know, that
you can skip hell.
Beats me. I always thought
this was hell, Captain Kangaroo.
Hey, all right.
First up, that's offensive.
I'll tell you another thing.
If any of us truly
deserves hell, it's Waller.
And that bitch knows it.
My God, the way she does.
I ain't worrying. I know
I'm going to heaven.
Anyone who can put up with
Mr. J deserves a break.
The problem is, sweetheart,
you have to die in order to find
out if the card really works.
Pretty-bloody-embarrassing
if it didn't.
What about you, gunman?
You think the card will work
like the blood you spilled?
Or don't you believe in heaven?
I believe in heaven, Boomer.
Everytime you shut your mouth.
You joke about heaven
and hell, Deadshot.
But trust me, they exist.
There's not a morning goes by
I don't get up wondering
if this will be
my judgement day.
Lined up with the woman I love.
Will face the lake of hell fire with
the same vermin who brought me down.
The only thing any of us can
hope for is divine intervention.
Only through the grace of God can
we be saved from eternal damnation.
For all the blood we spilt...
Everything else is just talk.
So, guess the card
couldn't hurt then, eh?
Dude, this is
the way they left me.
I was kidnapped.
Thats's what they all
say, buddy.
We'll get you something pretty
to wear back at the station.
Hope you like pink.
Sorry, officer.
But I think your tags
are about to expire.
Oh, crap.
All right,
listen up, it turns out
that Scandal Savage and her gal
pal have an apartment in Denver.
There's a hidden safe. I'll
be sending you floor plans.
Yes, sir. We'll be ready.
Wonderful.
A few days without a scalpel in my
hand, I'll start to feel all fidgety.
Better get dressed, babe.
The caveman cometh.
Oh, about time. This little
piggy's been cramping our style.
No peeking.
Madam, I'm a surgeon.
I've seen bodies before.
Not like this one.
Fun!
I don't know why your papa wants me
for a job any bone cutter could do.
My work is art,
it's transformational.
So is your bank account
if you do this right.
I have been wanting this
since I escaped from Apocalypse.
Hmm, what do you think?
Too Wonder Woman?
He likes Wonder Woman.
There's only three.
Some guy in cuffs
and a pig mask.
Kinky.
They usually call up
first, don't they?
Oh, God!
I smell bacon.
You heard me.
So far no one's died.
Let's see how long
we can make that last.
Now.
It's here.
Frost, how about a few
icy cuffs for the ladies?
Balls.
What a world. What a world!
We can't get a clean shot.
The woman is expendable.
I know you could see me, Savage,
I got the card!
You really want to kill me?
I'm guessing no,
but then again,
but who'd have guessed
a caveman believed in hell?
Everyone, get behind me.
No fast moves.
Can't negotiate with him.
Right now, we're just playing
poker, and I've got the wild card.
Well, that makes me feel
a lot better.
Father, we must help her.
Get Pyg onboard.
She's dying, she can't be left.
Get Pyg.
Christ, I thought
you were a lousy father.
Just move back nice and slow.
We're like fish
in a freaking barrel.
If you kill me,
your card gets used up.
If you wound me,
my friends will finish the job.
Either way, you lose
your ticket to heaven.
Give me the card, and I'll
spare all your sorry lives.
Sounds reasonable.
We're so screwed.
Okay.
Oh, come on.
You better be up there
snake man.
Gee, Frosty, it's like
Christmas eveyday with you.
Trust me, that one's
out of order.
Damn it, we're too late.
So they didn't get the card.
At least we know who's got it.
Savage has disappeared
for decades.
I can't lose them.
I understand he took you
by surprise.
What I don't understand is why I'm not
blowing your fool heads off right now.
His ship was as big as a 747.
Your satellite's must've
picked him up.
Savage uses a cloaking device.
He could hide the moon
if he wanted to.
He must've left
some kind of trail.
A heat signature?
A disruption in the clouds?
You better hope
we find something.
Otherwise, this camping trip
is over.
Waller out.
Oh, Benji gets a star.
We should've kept on fighting.
At least one of us would've
gotten out with a card.
Hey, where you going?
I need to get some air.
Well, who's gonna lead us?
You're incharge.
Who wants pizza?
It's okay.
I'm looking for Zoe.
Are you her dad?
Yeah.
Where are you guns?
Cool. A lot of .45s right?
I play a lot of
first person shooters.
I'm PussycatKill
on Blood World.
Why isn't she here?
She stays away a lot.
Crap. You got any?
Where'd she go?
Southside on King street,
There's a drug house.
She usually ends up there.
Don't get me wrong.
She's no tweaker.
Maybe some weed.
Speaking of, might as well
wake and bake since I'm up.
She says she's like you.
Likes to live dangerously.
But she kind of hates you too.
I asked my therapist about it,
but he was already asleep.
Want some?
More for me.
Seen her around here lately?
Sorry.
You lonely, darling?
No, thanks,
I'm just looking for...
Zoe?
Hey, hey, hey.
What's your hurry, buddy?
Tough guy, huh? He got any cash?
Look, you dickless wonders,
I don't have time for this.
You're in trouble, deadbeat.
You shut off your comm lines.
Your kid's not on mission.
You don't understand.
You think you're the only one
who's lost someone?
Remember
the League of Assassins?
You worked for 'em
once or twice.
Once. Lousy benefits.
Went undercover and
infiltrated them the agency.
They found out,
they tried to kill me,
but that's easier said
than done.
So they went after my fiance.
I tracked down and killed
as many of them I could.
Including a few moles
working for us.
I didn't know, but to tell you
the truth, I didn't care.
This story have a point?
Don't make me feel sorry for
you and your rathole existence.
I did everything in God's power
to protect the woman I loved.
But you, you threw
your daughter away.
Shit.
I was holding back
because of your kid,
but now I'm gonna finish this.
Deadshot, you gotta
call the Wall.
She went nuts when
she found out I was incharge.
I says to her, "So how's a girl
supposed to get ahead in this outfit?"
And that's when she got
really pissed off.
Shall we?
It's not her.
I'm here.
You're one lucky guy, Lawton.
You don't know how close you came
to an out-of-body experience.
I took a side trip. So what?
Tiger's incharge.
You heard the woman.
Drive.
Waller wants us to keep going
north for the time being.
We'll take a rest stop here
and reconvene at 1700 hours.
Five o' clock.
Oh!
I think grumpy's staying.
Are you stayin' grumpy?
Yep, grumpy's staying.
I'm gonna order some food.
What do you want?
Anything but chicken nuggies.
I'm going to the can.
I bet she pees icicles.
Hmm.
Who is this?
Listen clsoe, 'cause
I'm only gonna say this once.
32.1 degrees north,
minus 112 degrees east.
What the hell?
- And no onions.
- Tiger.
- They got Frost.
- What?
I'm goin' after them.
Hope you're doing all right.
Sorry if Banshee
got a little rough.
She feels terrible.
Yeah, I'm all up in
my feelings about it.
Honestly, we meant you no harm.
We just want to talk.
Fact is, I'm a fan.
I mean, this gift you have,
it's really quite extraordinary.
I don't think people realize
what you're capable of doing.
What's this about?
Its about a favor.
Everyone needs a favor
once in a while.
Banshee here would like me
to help her go back in time
to seek vengeance against
the clan who banished her.
That bastards!
Blockbuster, uncomplicated
fellow that he is
would like his own island.
Me? I want the card.
Waller can trace me, you know?
She'll be sending them.
What if I can make all that
go away?
And what do you get out of it?
Like I said a favor.
One hand washing the other.
It has to do with
Professor Pyg, I...
I think I finally understand
how he fits in.
And for you, it would take no more effort
than freezing a tray of ice cubes.
I'm listening.
Don't move.
Sorry.
Just a cramp.
I'm telling you,
nothing's moving inside.
Not even the dust and the air.
She's in there, all right.
I want to set up a perimeter.
Boomerang, you take
the north side.
Harley. Where's Harley?
We're coming to get you, Frosty!
Shit.
How's our leadership
thing going?
You sure you got
the right address?
She's in there somewhere.
Zoom may have turned her.
I'll give you 30 seconds,
then I'm done with her.
Look around.
Copperhead, under the house.
Really?
Well, she is like
Frosty the snowman.
Maybe she melted.
Something's off.
We're being set up.
Tell Waller we found her.
Buy her some time.
We think we got
Frost, Waller. Standby.
She's done.
The bomb, it's down here.
Everybody out.
I don't think he looks so good.
Poor Tiger, just when I was
starting to get interested.
Lawton, we just got satellite
photos on those coordinates you gave me.
This canyon shortcut will get
you to Savage ahead of Zoom.
I'm enroute, but it might
take a while.
There wouldn't be a hospital
on the way, would there?
Or a mortuary.
He's a soldier, Lawton.
Dying's an occupational hazard.
Keep your eyes on the road
and your head on the mission.
Why so glum, mate? You got
your job back, didn't ya?
That bloody fool. Our true-blue.
So freaking noble.
Never got that we're just a puppets
trying to get through the show
with our strings attached.
It's quite
a crib Vandal's got.
All that's missing is a sign
that says "Bad guy lives here."
Come on.
How's that?
Mighty beauty, I'd say.
Let's not give each other
handjobs just yet.
You see a way to get inside?
I think we're being summoned.
Poor Piggy.
Looks like he went to market.
This is a warning.
I'd say it's working.
I presume my grieving
daughter sent you.
Children.
I must've sired
a hundred thousand.
You think one would
show me some respect.
If you wanna live another century
or two, hand over the card.
That would be impossible.
Mate, he's gotta have it. Doesn't
work if you don't have it on you.
Not on me.
In me.
Professor Pyg.
I don't get it.
He had Pyg implant
the card in him.
In such a position that to
remove it would kill me.
Why do you even need it? You're
supposed to live for bloody ever.
I'm immortal, not invulnerable.
I've had more brushes with death
in the last ten years
than all
the centuries preceding
thanks to the emergence
of meta humans.
I'm afraid no one lives forever.
It's a neurosynaptic discharge.
Blocks sensory motor
functions pretty quickly.
That is, if you can
still hear me.
That's a hell of an entrance.
Frosty, you got the wrong side.
We're the good bad guys...
God, I've been wanting
to do that for a week now.
Such a quick healer.
You and I have that in common.
Our little favor, Miss Frost?
Lawton.
We should be there at 0200 hours.
You have it yet?
Getting there.
Why are they freezing him?
Not quite.
Just bringing down
his body temperature
to the point where
we can work with him.
You're slow, Zoom, in the old
days, you never needed help.
What's the problem?
You might say everything.
Nice shot.
It was Batman.
In another timeline.
Can't say that I blame him.
Thanks to me, his entire world
was going to die.
Only Flash could turn back time and I was
damned if I was gonna let that happen.
I never saw it coming.
But I felt it.
I tried to vibrate
my inner molecules
to save my brain even as
the bullet was tearing through.
And in that moment, that very
infinitesimal split-second before death,
I drew the Speed Force into me with
every ounce of will power I had left.
And literally by time, I'd expanded my
moment of dying into day, maybe weeks.
But it's like operating
in a fog.
Everything's a little unreal
and warped.
I feel like I'm walking
through water sometimes.
And then when I speed up, I can
feel my life slipping away.
He's ready.
I'm running on fumes now.
But I've got just enough
gas left for this.
Bon voyage, caveman.
Shall we send Savage
some company, Banshee?
You were right, speedy, nobody
knows what I'm capable of.
Why, thanks. Don't mind if I do.
I don't suppose you're
coming back to the fold?
You supposed right, deadhead.
The neck is clear.
And I got the card.
Membership does have
its privileges after all.
Oh, really?
I didn't think
you were a believer.
I'm not, but a girl's
gotta make some money.
How do I put
this up for auction?
Let Waller know
I'll give her the first bid.
You tell that trick bitch
her ass is mine, you hear?
Yeah, I think she got it.
So long, suckers.
Okay.
Let's see how cold-blooded
you can get.
Where's the car?
How close are they doing?
Coopehead's got her,
but not for long.
Waller, I'll see you in hell,
you dirty...
Son of a bitch.
How about helping
old Digger out here, eh?
Hey, hey. Whoa, hey.
Two dead, Waller.
I'll live with it.
Just get me the card.
All for a magic trick.
Oh, ye of little faith.
She'll blow you head off,
too, you know?
You're still not
getting it, love.
I got the card.
No onne's gonna kill me
and waste a pass to the
pearly gates on this tosser.
Benji! Oh, I thought
you were toast, mate.
You okay?
Where are the others?
Oh, dead.
They all killed each other
like cats in a bag.
Savage, Zoom, all of them.
What about the card?
Well, mate, who knows?
Waller's got to bring
a cleaning crew for that.
Even for scum,
you make a lousy liar.
Watch it, kitten, you're not
the only one with claws.
I know you have it.
Give it to me!
Screw you.
Cowboy, Zoom just took off.
- Oh, yeah.
- No, you stay.
Make sure they don't leave.
Goddamn it.
Either your reflexes are back
or mine are short.
Hmm.
I'd say this more than
evens things.
Drop the card and walk away.
What are you gonna do?
Kill me?
Death by a thousand cuts, Tiger.
I'll have that card
by number ten.
Did I say ten?
I underestimated.
Do it. Save me the trouble.
Maybe I'll just ward you too.
I promise you, Deadshot, I'm
good for one last hit of speed.
Any bullet you shoot,
I'll make sure it's lethal.
So go ahead.
Make my afterlife.
Fuck my life.
Kill me.
We got him.
We just crossed the finish line.
I can't save you.
I'm beyond
salvation.
You didn't want her
to have it either.
She doesn't deserve it.
What was her name? Your fiance?
Miyoshi.
Pretty name.
Uh, I'll be damned.
You better have that
freaking card.
Not a scratch on it.
Hmm, it feels cold.
It's a cold world.
This Zoom guy, he disappeared.
I looked around...
Oh, hi, Wally, how's Trix?
She would live.
Are we good?
No one's ever to speak
of this, Lawton, understood?
I'll be seeing you, Waller.
Maybe in heaven.
Subtitles by explosiveskull
Resync by GoldenBeard
Watch Movies, TV Series and Live Sports
Signup Here -> WWW.ADMITME.APP