Someone needs to stop Clearway Law.
Public shouldn't leave reviews for lawyers.
Welcome back to SPEN Sports...
...for another episode of
Are They Still Cool? Surf Edition.
Cody Maverick was set
to become the biggest surfer...
...to come out of Pen Gu
since Big Z Topanga.
He shocked and awed fans and critics
alike with his fresh, new-school moves.
He scorched nine-time champion
and local bully...
...Tank "The Shredder" Evans
and was perfectly positioned...
...to win the tenth annual
Big Z Memorial Surf-Off..
I'm doing great, man. I think
I earned a lot of respect out there.
After I win today,
you're gonna see a lot more from me.
I promise. I'm going to the Outer Banks
to surf with the Hang 5...
...the best in the business.
It's been my dream since I was a little kid
and it's finally about to come true.
Victory, fame and fortune
were all but guaranteed for young Cody.
Until at the last minute, he chose
to protect his friend Chicken Joe...
...from sore loser Tank Evans,
and gave up any chance of the trophy.
Chicken Joe took home
first place that day...
...and has since gained great fame
in the world of professional surfing.
Maverick, however,
has been all but forgotten.
Let's see what he's been up to
in this episode of...
...Are They Still Cool? Surf Edition.
So, Cody, why don't you fill us in...
...on what you've done
the last few years?
First, I have a question for you.
I, uh... Okay, go ahead.
Have you or someone you care about
expressed the urge...
...to ride waves like a pro?
- To be the master of the ocean?
- Come again?
Well, I can show you how it's done
at the Pen Gu Surf Academy.
At PSA, we got all the newest,
sickest moves at the lowest prices.
You want backflips? You got it.
Tail rides? You got it.
Tube slides? Wah-ha!
You bet you got it.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, man.
We're trying to do a show here.
You can't just plug your surf school.
Hi, I'm Lani,
lifeguard and co-founder of PSA...
...where we're all about having fun
and being safe.
Mention this commercial and get
30 percent off your first lesson free!
Free, free, free, free.
Don't waste your money on those losers.
Oh, what now?
You should learn to surf
from a real master.
- Right, gang?
- Yes, sensei.
Hi. I'm nine-time champion
Tank Evans...
...and I want you
to discover your surf success story...
...at Tank's Online Surf institute.
Just send me your
parents' credit card information.
Cut it out, Tank.
- We're trying to film a commercial here.
- No, we're not.
How can you promise these squirts
you'll turn them into winners...
...when you've never won anything
in your life? Look at all my trophies.
Each more spectacular than the last.
Tank, my arms are getting tired.
Fight through the pain.
It's part of your training.
Wanna learn how to shred for real?
Sign up now at TOSI and receive
a free participation trophy with purchase.
Absolutely free. With purchase.
Tank, get out of here.
I'll also teach you about teamwork...
...and proper surf etiquette!
- Okay, cut.
- Wait, stop.
- I am so getting fired for this.
- Stop.
- Come on.
- Ha, ha, ha.
Whoa, hey, wait. Hold on.
I wanna tell you about
my franchising opportunities.
With purchase!
Ugh!
Cody?
Wake up, bro.
It's me.
- Cock-a-doodle-dude!
- Ah!
Chicken Joe.
Or as my Spanish friends call me,
El Pollo Loco.
What made you
come back to Pen Gu island?
You know, I haven't seen my buddies
Cody and Lani in like two years.
And I finally got some time off
from my world tour...
...so I thought I'd stop by and hang out.
Time off from your tour?
Aren't you supposed to be
in Madagascar right now?
Oh, man. I gotta text my manager.
Oh, wait.
This is just a regular clam.
Oh, I missed you, bro.
Look at you, man.
Bigtime pro surfer now.
I dig that wetsuit.
Yeah? Thanks.
It's a little tight around
my nuggets and tenders.
But, my sponsors
like me to wear it, so...
Dude, you have sponsors?
Totally.
They like to give me tons of free stuff.
Boards, wetsuits, wax.
It's kind of a sweet deal.
Yeah, it sounds pretty rad.
Oh, it is, bro.
And I owe it all to you.
If you hadn't saved my life
and let me win the Big Z Memorial...
...I'd never be where I am today.
Heck, you'd probably be the one
with all the sponsors and endorsements.
Surfing on the tour,
being on TV, screaming fans...
Yeah, yeah, yeah. I get it. I get it.
I'm happy for you, Joe. You deserve it.
Hey, Cody. I picked this up for you
while I was on tour.
Oh, thanks, Joe.
I know how much you like
these super buff penguins.
Wow, the Hang 5.
Those guys rule.
Did you surf with them or something?
Nah. I just missed them.
You know those guys,
always traveling the world...
...looking for the next
mondo extreme challenge.
Too crazy for me.
- Chicken Joe?
- Chicken Joe!
- Penguin Lani!
- It's so good to see you.
Chicken Joe,
can you teach us your moves?
You're the "awesome-est"!
Yeah, we wanna learn from you.
Can you give us
a celebrity guest surf lesson?
Yeah, I'd be happy to.
Let's get started right now.
Find me some tacos.
The Hang 5.
Excuse me. Hey, I'm trying to see.
- Come on, buddy.
- Cody Maverick.
I am not spending my whole
entire vacation chasing after you.
Mom, it's the Hang 5.
I've gotta be in the front. Wow.
Ladies and gentle penguins...
...it's the moment
you've all been waiting for.
Behold the most extreme team,
surfing the earth and living the dream.
Coming to you live in overdrive.
Put them together for the Hang 5.
Yeah! Hang 5! Hang 5! Hang 5!
He's the big kahuna,
the leader of the crew-a.
The mammal with a plan...
...Mr. McMahon.
Yeah!
The king of the big-wave riders,
only 50 footers or higher.
To him they're just ripples,
because the H is tripled.
Introducing...
...Hunter.
Look, it's Paige!
She's the best
trick surfer on the world stage.
Her skill and audacity
cannot be gauged.
She's beautiful, fearless
and full of rage.
Let's give it up
for the one and only...
...Paige.
He's the Hang 5's enforcer.
Even sharks and orcas meet their maker
when they go up against...
- ...the Undertaker.
- I'm Undertaker!
He's hardcore times four.
He lives fast, surfs hard.
No regrets.
Don't call him crazy, call him...
...J.C.
If you want some, come get some.
Wow!
Why the long face?
No, I was just remembering
the time I met the Hang 5.
I worshiped those guys. Seeing them surf
made me who I am today.
I worked hard my whole life
so I could be just like them one day.
And somehow it just...
It just never happened for me.
I mean, I love teaching the kids...
...but I didn't think
that's all I'd be doing now.
I always thought
I was meant to be somebody.
Doing big things, inspiring people.
I guess I was wrong.
Does this have something to do with
all that stuff Tank said on the beach?
Cody, you can't let that guy
mess with your head.
He might have all those trophies...
...but he's still a loser.
Yeah, Tank is pretty annoying.
- But it's not just that.
- It's not that hard.
The secret to good surfing
is you just gotta feel the groove.
Chicken Joe?
Oh, I get it.
Well, don't get me wrong.
I love the guy.
He deserves everything he's got.
But I can't help but think, man,
that could have been me, you know?
Famous, successful,
a winner that everyone respects.
I mean, look at him.
He's even a better teacher than me.
Guys, I have officially lost control
of the situation.
Cody? Lani?
Okay, maybe not a better teacher.
We're coming, buddy.
What can I say? Pen Gu's home.
I love my life here.
I'd like to travel
and see the world someday.
But right now,
I got the surf school, my lifeguard job...
...and big waves all year
to keep me busy.
It doesn't get any better than that.
Man, this teaching thing
is harder than I thought.
You know what I dig most
about Pen Gu?
What?
Nothing ever happens here.
Chicken and penguin!
Never mind. Something is happening.
Wait. I've seen that seagull
somewhere before.
Prepare yourselves. It's the moment
you've all been waiting for.
The Hang 5! They're here.
The Hang 5?
The most legendary surf crew
of all time?
- Yes!
- Woo-hoo!
- Oh, yeah.
- Oh, great.
Way to ruin the surprise, kid.
That was supposed to be my line.
You can still say it.
You know what? Forget it.
There used to be respect
for showmanship in this business.
Wait a minute.
I'm the resident Hang 5 expert here.
If they were coming,
trust me, I'd know about it.
Hey, Hang 5.
What's up, little dudes?
You... It's...
Oh, my gosh. My gosh.
We get crazed fans all the time.
But it's like I always say:
A brave man builds his house
on an ocean of milk.
That doesn't make a lick of sense.
It doesn't have to. I'm the boss,
and I like milk and fish.
Because I'm an otter,
and otters like fish.
I just wish you could milk a fish.
I don't really know
what to say about that.
Hey, bro. You know where
we can get something to eat?
Uh, yeah, yeah. Food, right.
You guys eat food because you're
the Hang 5. What about squid on a stick?
Squids? On sticks?
I love impaled food.
Oh, yeah, I'll try anything.
Oh, yeah?
Well, I've tried everything, twice.
Whatever gnarly stuff you can eat,
I can eat twice as much, twice as fast.
Jeez, Hunter. Why do you always
have to be so competitive?
You know what? You should come over
to my place for a backyard luau.
Come on. Come on.
I won't take no for an answer.
- So you should just come.
- Yeah, man. Bring it on. I'm starving.
Tell me more about these squid sticks.
Hey, look at me, Hang 5.
Whoa, hold on there. Be careful.
I know all your moves. Like this.
Unh!
Help! Lani! Help! Help!
Oh, no. Arnold!
- Kid!
- Hang on, Arnold. I'm coming! Hyah!
Hold on.
Whoa! Who's that?
Oh, that's just Arnold.
This happens all the time.
Lani's on it.
Arnold, you know what I said
about going into the ocean by yourself.
I know.
Thanks for having my back out there.
Oh, ha, ha, ha!
Whoa! You all right, little dude?
Yeah. I was just trying
to show you my mad skills.
Heh, heh. You shouldn't try to imitate us.
We're trained professionals.
Some of us with huge muscles.
I'm not gonna say who.
That would be bragging.
Nice moves.
Oh, thanks. You must be the Hang 5.
Guess that explains the whale.
Oops! I forgot to lock it.
Hey, Lani. Guess what.
I'm throwing a luau
for the Hang 5 at my place.
Oh, yes. Let's luau!
- All right!
- Yeah!
Yes. Come on, Hunter.
Whoo!
Hang 5 is the real deal.
They've done everything.
Snowboard during an avalanche, check.
Skydive into a tornado, check.
Competitive speed knitting, check.
Whatever it is they're about to do,
I wanna be a part of it.
T ell us a story, J.C.
T ell us a scary one.
Yeah! Yeah!
All right. This happened
while I was on tour last year.
We were surfing the infamous
ghost beach of Levesque...
...where they say
even the waves are haunted.
Wh... Were you scared?
Not at first. But it was quiet. Too quiet.
- Then this ghost wave grabs my board!
- Ah!
And then what happened?
So there I am underwater...
He was held down
by almost 5000 psi of pressure.
I read about it in your interview
with Rolling Waves magazine.
- Escargot-go?
- Uh...
No, thanks.
I woke up on the ocean floor...
I've practiced
your breathing technique for years.
I can hold my breath
for almost five minutes.
I'm trying to tell my story, bro.
Can I show you my variation
on your five flipper shuffle?
Go check on the Undertaker.
He's always hungry.
Yes, sir.
All right.
So there I was, 200 feet underwater...
...and I'm freaking out.
Did you do a controlled emergency
ascent to protect your lungs?
Uh, yeah.
- How did you know about that?
- Cody taught us that at our surf school.
That guy?
Um...
Interesting.
If you kids think J.C.'s dumb old stories
are cool, watch me uproot this tree.
Unh!
Anyways, wanna hear
about the time I fought off a shark...
...with nothing but my camo shorts?
Yeah!
Mr. Undertaker,
do you wanna try some of the...?
- More.
- Coming right up.
Hey, have you seen my friend Cod...
Whoa, man, don't eat me.
I'm not the food.
Can you at least
lay an egg or something?
Scary? Yeah, I get that sometimes.
They say it's because
I don't smile or talk a lot.
- But I'm just shy. Okay?
- Ah!
Oh...
Little of this, little of that.
All right, add some spice.
Oh, yeah. Prepping that squid.
Would you like coconut water?
- That depends. I prefer fish milk.
- Uh...
All right,
then I'll drink your coconut water.
But you better believe I'm gonna pretend
I'm sucking it from a fish's udder.
You know, Mr. McMahon,
I do a little surfing myself.
Cool, cool.
It is cool. And you know what?
I got some ideas for some tricks
that could really change things up.
I'm talking next-level stuff, man.
Oh, yeah? You'll have to
show me sometime.
Really? Let's set a time.
How about tomorrow?
Excuse me a second.
Can I have everyone's attention, please?
What I hold here
is the key that will unlock...
...one of the greatest mysteries
of our time.
Why everything seems to taste like me?
No.
This is a map to the most legendary
surfing spot on the planet.
The Trenches.
I thought that the Trenches were
just, like, made up to scare little kids.
Oh, it's real, all right.
And everything you hear about it is true.
It's hidden somewhere
on Slaughter island...
...the most dangerous
and mysterious place on the planet.
Jagged rocks, huge cliffs.
It's a surfer's graveyard.
And we're going to ride it! RTL!
Am I right, guys?
Heck yeah. RTL!
RTL!
Hey, Joe. What does RTL mean?
I don't know, man. Rumbly tummy...
...something.
Oh, I shouldn't have eaten
all those escargot-gos.
Surfing the Trenches
will be the greatest ride of my life.
And my last.
Because you're gonna die?
- No. Because I'm retiring.
- What?
Boss, you can't be serious.
Hey, I'm not getting any younger.
It's time for me to settle down.
What does that mean? We're
gonna be the Hang 4 from now on?
Maybe not. Big Z always said
Pen Gu breeds great surfers.
I think it's time we add a new member.
Have somebody in mind, boss?
Ha, ha. I'm not gonna give away
the surprise just yet.
But I think I might have found
someone very special.
Yes!
How totally awesome is this, bro?
I'm gonna join the Hang 5.
Can you even imagine
what that would be like?
Yeah, that sounds pretty rad.
But, um, are you sure Mr. McMahon
was talking about you, bro?
What? Who else could it be, man?
He looked right at me.
Hey, Cody. You up?
Yeah. Hey, what's up, Lani?
Hey. So, uh, you got a second?
I need to tell you something.
Sure. I was talking about
how great it'd be...
...if the Hang 5 asked me to join.
Oh, um, okay.
You think they might ask you?
Well, yeah. I mean, why not?
I've been following them my whole life.
And I'm the best surfer on Pen Gu.
Who else are they gonna ask?
Hey, Lani. I told my mom...
...that you told me
that you were going to join the Hang 5.
And then she said
that I should get your autograph...
...because she wants to sell it online.
What?
Whoa! That's awesome, Lani.
Cody, your imaginary friends
are gonna be so disappointed.
So I guess they asked you.
Yeah. Mr. McMahon and Paige
came over to my place this morning.
They said I showed moxie
saving Arnold...
...and they could use somebody
with my lifeguard skills.
They're waiting for me
on the South Shore.
But I don't know, Cody.
This is your dream.
No. No, no... No way.
You can't pass this up, Lani.
It's the Hang 5, all right? You gotta go.
- I'll figure something out. Don't worry.
- Wait, really?
Will you be okay? I don't want to...
Go tell them you're coming
before they change their minds.
- I'll see you there.
- Okay, okay. Bye!
Does that mean you're not leaving
Pen Gu and joining the Hang 5...
...and fulfilling your ultimate destiny
of becoming a legendary surfer?
No, I got an idea.
Come on, you guys.
I'll explain on the way.
Hang 5! Prepare for boarding.
Don't be nervous.
You're gonna do great.
- I have a good feeling about you.
- Ha-ha.
- Thanks.
- Is that them?
Yeah, come on. Get over there.
- Uh!
- Ah!
Do what Cody taught us.
Um... Ah...
Look. Who's that in the water?
It must be Cody Maverick...
...Pen Gu's favorite surfer.
Did you say Cody Maverick?
Let's go watch him.
- Yeah! Let's go see Cody!
- Yeah!
So have you done
a lot of acting before?
Um, yes. I'm more of a Method actor.
And I think Arnold comes
from a Broadway background.
# I am the very model
Of a modern major general #
# I've information... # #
Here we go. Showtime.
Whoa! All right!
Sick.
Whoo!
Kid's got style.
Nice moves, kid.
Yo, Mr. McMahon,
what about we bring Cody too?
Let's see what else he's got.
What? We already said
we were bringing my girl Lani.
I wanna bring the chicken.
In case I get hungry.
That's cool. I gotta warn you, though...
...I'm not a great cook.
- All right, all right, all right.
- Not so fast.
Tank is the one you want.
I heard you're looking for
a champion to join you.
So I brought my resume.
I like your style.
Reminds me of myself at a younger age.
Well, thanks. But, you know...
...I'm not as handsome as you are, sir.
Ha. Of course not. Oops!
Oh, Briana!
- Sorry about that.
- Oh, that's good.
You better take that. Who made
this thing? My trophies never broke.
- Oh! Again.
- Ridiculous. That thing's garbage.
- Take it. Take the whole thing back.
- Funny.
Well, now I have more of her,
so thanks.
This is my guy. Everybody else
has a guy. I want a guy.
Oh, for crying out loud.
Fine. You can keep your rookies.
- Yes! Up top! Headbutt!
- Yes! Ooh!
- Awesome.
- Yeah, I love those.
But they're your responsibility. You've
gotta show them how we do things.
We're gonna challenge you
on all aspects of what we do.
Power, speed,
endurance and teamwork.
May the best mentor-rookie team win.
Bring it on, fool.
Well, obviously Lani and I will win.
Let's do this.
Do you know how to surf?
Dude, I'm a star.
Okay, we're in.
All right. Then that's the way
it's gonna be.
If your guy or girl dies or gets hurt and
I have to carry them all the way back...
...I'm gonna make you
scrub the whale for a year!
All aboard! Next stop, Slaughter island.
So how much did you pay
to bribe those kids?
- Three shells apiece.
- You're such a dork.
Not to mention a failure.
Ha, ha, ha, ha!
When I become one of the Hang 5...
...I'm gonna come back
and crush your surf school.
All your students will be mine.
And they'll be happy. Ha, ha, ha, ha!
- Like me.
- We can't let him win, Cody.
Don't worry. I got this.
Can't this thing go a little slower?
Where would be the fun in that?
We're passing through some
rough waters. It's safer to go fast.
Aaah!
Joe!
Thanks, man.
Almost lost my lunch.
Say no more, Under-bro.
I can hold your hair if you need to yak.
This is just amazing.
Can you believe it?
I'm traveling to the Trenches
with the Hang 5. Ha, ha!
Oh, man. Somebody pinch me.
- You're welcome.
- Heh.
Look, I'm a diva, I'll admit it.
But I'm a power diva.
And I was thinking you fellas
might wanna focus on me more.
We could do a spinoff, Power Diva.
A crime-fighting surfing puff. In
with a bad attitude...
...and a thirst for action.
Oh, it's got blockbuster
written all over it.
# Is gonna stop me now # #
We're almost there.
How can you tell? This fog is so thick,
I can barely see anything.
My shell told me.
It's a map that talks.
What's wrong, bro?
Don't you believe in magic?
We'll be there in four, three, two, one.
Look.
Gnarly.
It's so beautiful.
Are we here? Is this it?
No, we're at the edge
of Slaughter island.
The Trenches is hidden here
somewhere. We're going to find it.
Forward, ever forward,
our intrepid team presses on...
...woefully unaware that no penguin
has ever ventured into the Trenches...
...and lived to tell the story.
Looks like this is
as far as the whale goes.
I got your board for you, Mr. Hunter.
Right here.
- Thanks, Hank.
- It's Tank. It's Tank.
Know what? Hank's better, actually.
- Next stop, RTL!
- RTL!
RTL!
Did they tell you what RTL means?
It means "race the losers."
Let's get that guy.
Hey, excuse me.
Can you take me back to Pen Gu?
I think I left my sunblock.
Come on.
Dude!
Whoa! Look at that.
Killer view, bro.
Hey, rookies!
We're down here!
Whoo! Yeah! Yes!
Oh, my gosh, you can surf on this stuff.
Dude, what is this?
The taste of death.
This is crushed whale bones.
I should move here.
The conch is telling me
we have to keep moving.
This place is dangerous.
So let's head out.
What's so dangerous about it?
Hold on. What's that, conch?
Okay, I'll tell him.
Conch says, shut up!
- Heh, heh.
- Hey.
From up here it looks like the sand pit
will take us straight into the island.
That'll save us a ton of time.
How about a race?
Last team to the bottom
waxes all our boards tonight.
You're on, fool.
Cody and I are gonna smoke you.
Yeah, Tank. You're going down.
Ohh, I'm so scared. Not.
Ha! Me and Lani will take you on.
And as always, it'll be ladies first!
Me and the chicken are in too.
Where is he?
Hey, don't take this the wrong way...
...but didn't you used to be taller?
Oh, my gosh,
you're standing in quicksand!
Cody, Lani, J.C., help!
Lani, pull!
I'm trying. He's like a boulder.
I got this.
Come on, big guy.
Let's get you out of there.
How much do you weigh?
- Hunter, help me look for the chicken.
- Already on it.
I found him.
There, by that rock. To your right.
Hunh! Gotcha.
Am I dead? Are you my father?
Come on!
Come on! Come on!
Aah!
Yeah! Go, J.C.
Ha, ha! That's how it's done.
Wow, J.C. Perfect form.
- Thanks, kid.
- Very impressive.
You gonna put me down now?
You're lucky it's leg day.
I'm just gonna sneak in a quick set.
- Thanks, show-off.
- Any time.
Leg-pressing a large, heavy boulder.
Then onto a one-handed handstand...
...all while
still leg-pressing the boulder.
The secret to my amazing physique?
Eat right, exercise and never give up...
...on being awesome.
Hang 5, let's do this!
- All right!
- Yeah! Yeah, dude!
Let's see how these wave jockeys
perform on the dunes.
They have not put in the hours
shredding the sand...
...but, wow, folks,
they're putting on quite a show.
I make this look good.
- Yeah!
- Bring it!
Check this out.
Nice moves, Paige.
- All right.
- We do it old-school.
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
- Lani, I see a shortcut.
- Right behind you.
Ho, ho! In your face, Hunter.
Whee!
Rest in peace.
Yeah.
Whoa!
Ho-ho!
Yeah!
- Bye, J.C.
- Ha, ha, ha. Aw...
This is it.
- Eat my dust, Tank.
- Oh, that's what you think.
- Whoa!
- Ha-ha-ha!
Sand's the best!
Cody!
- You still with me, bro?
- Yeah. I think so.
Ha, ha, ha, awesome.
- Paige, we finished first. I can't believe it.
- Yeah!
That was incredible.
Ho, ho, ho, unh!
That tickled.
- Great job out there, Lani.
- Ha, ha, ha!
Thanks. That was a lot of fun.
Gotta hand it to you, Paige.
You got me good
when you banked off that rib cage...
- ...and landed in front of me.
- I've got a few tricks you haven't seen.
Hey. Check it out.
Hey, flattop. What happened?
You take the scenic route?
Heh, heh. Yeah, you know me.
I'm just a bit of a tourist.
I like to take in the sights.
Remember,
I like a nice high gloss on my board.
Don't get too comfortable.
I'll get you back.
That was quite a spill
you took out there.
How does my dust taste?
You cut me off, you cheater.
Oh? I don't know
what you're talking about.
- I'd never do anything to hurt you.
- Hey!
You should learn
to stay out of my way.
I'm gonna join the Hang 5,
no matter what.
How badly you want to lose
is entirely up to you.
Grrr...
That Tank guy is ridiculous.
He's like a cartoon villain.
Why did you let Hunter bring him?
Everyone is here for a reason.
I want to see how
the rest of the newbies deal with him.
You still think Cody has what it takes?
Look, Mr. McMahon,
I know he wiped out out there...
...but he's a good surfer.
Give him a chance.
I'm not talking about surfing.
I've been watching him.
I think he's a bit of a hothead.
He might want this too much.
Don't worry about it.
He's just like me at that age.
He'll be cool.
All right, we'll see.
Okay, okay. I've got one.
What did the wave say to the surfer?
Oh, what?
Have a swell time!
Get it, huh?
Have a swell time.
Oh, ha, ha, swell. Ha, ha, ha.
Oh, that was good. Swell.
Oh, Mr. McMahon, that's like
the greatest surfing joke maybe ever.
So good. Unh!
Thank you.
What do you call a surfer
that just broke up with his girlfriend?
Homeless!
Dude, Cody. We're just trying to
wax the boards, not set them on fire.
You're gonna burn a hole in that thing.
Tank cheated.
He knocked me off my board.
That's why we lost.
Yeah? I didn't see anything. You sure?
He totally rubbed it in my face.
He practically admitted to it.
That's messed up.
But you know what?
Maybe let it go. It's not worth
getting all bent out of shape about.
We had an awesome day, right?
Were those dunes gnarly or what?
Yeah. That was pretty epic.
And I got to ride with you guys.
It still feels pretty surreal.
I mean, like, I can't believe
this is actually my life right now.
I just... I just wish
that I hadn't let you down.
Let me down?
What are you talking about?
Look, man.
There are plenty of jerks out there.
If it's not Tank, it'll be somebody else.
Just take the high road.
You'll be a lot happier, I promise.
All right, man. You got it.
- Ha, ha!
- Pull.
- Whoo!
- Pull. Pull.
- All right!
- Why are they sleeping up there?
- Mmm...
Maybe they don't like us.
I bet it's a tribal thing, you know?
Paying homage to the surfing gods.
Wrong. None of the above.
It's actually for protection.
Protection? From what?
This is Slaughter island. Who knows
what's creeping around at night?
And you're gonna want to
plant that board a bit deeper, bro.
- Oh!
- Ha, ha, ha...
You guys sleep up in the nosebleeds
if you want to.
Tank Evans is not scared
of some little forest critters.
Neither is my main girl Michelle.
Isn't that right, baby?
Big Daddy won't let anything harm you.
This is Michelle.
We've been together for about...
What is it, babe?... Three years now.
I bought her at a garage sale.
I saw her from across the lawn.
I was like, "Oh, yeah."
Don't get me wrong,
I still ride other boards.
But... But, Michelle, she's special.
Hey, Tank.
Does Michelle have a friend?
Yeah? Well, we're not scared either.
- Yeah. If you're fine with it, I am.
- I ain't afraid of no forest critters.
- Totally cool.
- Okay. Yep.
So we're all fine down here.
Oof!
Well, you all sleep tight then.
Don't let the bed bugs bite.
Oh, we won't.
And the bed bugs will bite you.
Uh...
Don't hate me, man.
I'm just polishing my trophy.
I think I just laid an egg.
I didn't forget about you, babe.
Oh!
Whoa!
Nice hang time.
Cody?
Congratulations. You're dead.
Ha, ha!
What?
That's what happens when you
don't work together in a place like this.
Wait, wait, wait. This was a test?
It was. We wanted to see
how well you work under pressure.
Never split up. Understand?
You stick together, no matter what.
When you're a team,
you always have each other's backs.
Got it?
Well, all things considered,
not bad for your first time.
At least none of you peed your pants.
Right, Hunter? Ha, ha, ha!
I told you guys, I sat in a puddle.
- Oh, yeah.
- All right!
Don't worry, Hunter, bro.
I peed my pants too.
- I don't have any pants...
- Let's go!
...so I mostly just peed on my feet.
I bet you thought it was me
making all that noise. Didn't you?
Yeah. You don't wanna mess with me
when I'm in a bad mood.
Can't sleep?
Yeah, I think I need a minute
to calm down from all the excitement.
My heart's jumping out of my chest.
Yeah, I can imagine.
This has been some day.
Must be a pretty big deal to you.
This is my dream, Lani.
I can't stop thinking about it.
I don't think I blinked once all day.
I didn't wanna miss a second.
Mr. McMahon thinks you're
amazing. He's totally gonna pick you.
I don't know.
I miss Pen Gu.
We've been gone for so long.
I can't wait to tell our friends back home
about all of this.
Heh, heh.
Yeah. They'll never believe it.
I wish every day was like this.
I feel like I'm finally living the life
I've always wanted to, you know?
I wish this feeling could last forever.
Heh.
Yeah, well, you still gotta sleep.
Yeah, in a minute.
Let's soak this in a while longer.
Uh...
Uh!
Cock-a-doodle-dude!
Cock-a-doodle-shut up!
I slept like a corpse.
Come on, guys.
We've got a lot of ground to cover.
Remember what we talked about
last night.
After all, this journey isn't just about
getting to the Trenches.
One of you will be replacing me
on the Hang 5.
Those are some big shoes to fill,
so show me you've got big feet.
Yeah.
It says there's supposed to be
a bridge.
- Boss! Stop!
- Mr. McMahon!
- Wait, wait.
- Come back!
- Rerouting.
- Look where you're going!
- What's that mean?
- Don't go further!
Hey, what's the holdup?
Ha, ha! You're afraid of heights?
Oh, yeah!
Let's have some fun.
I bet you can't get past me.
Oh, you're on.
Whoa, whoa!
Perfectly matched.
This is truly a clash of the titans.
Yeah! Show them
how you do it, Mr. Hunter.
You see that?
He blew right past your guy.
Come on, J.C.
Oh, yeah?
- Yeah!
- Whoo! Ha-ha.
Yeah, he showed Hunter what's up.
- Come on, Lani.
- Whoa. Yeah!
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
Yeah! Whoo!
Ha-ha-ha.
Nice, Lani. Way to go.
Oh, that's cool, but...
Come on, wimp. It's our turn.
Hope you don't fall to your death
or anything.
Whoa, whoa!
Can you do this?
- Cut it out!
- Ls this bothering you?
Is this bothering you? This?
Cody Maverick looks like
he's in real trouble. I can't look.
Ha, ha!
Try not to look so scared in front of J.C.
Tank, seriously, stop. Whoa, whoa.
Okay, okay.
- Dude, come on.
- This is fun.
Uhn!
- No, I'm good. That was my plan.
- Yeah!
That was gnarly.
- Oh... Oh!
- Cody, no!
- Look out!
- Wait for me, guys!
You okay, Cody?
Yeah.
Fortunately, this solid stone floor
was here to break my fall.
Where are the others?
Whoa.
Looks like
we're in some kind of a tomb.
Yeah. Whoever these people were,
they really loved surfing.
I think these little symbols
mean something.
Maybe it's a story.
Yeah, see?
This one's about a guy
who surfed a wave as tall as a mountain.
And this one
shows a guy surfing on sand.
- We did that.
- Hey, check it out.
Whoa. What does it say?
It looks like
the story of a young penguin.
Pretty good surfer, got some fans.
Yeah, definitely looks like
things were going his way.
Yeah, yeah, and then?
Oh! He got eaten by a bunch of sharks.
- Oh! Okay.
- Whoa.
This guy surfed through fire?
Dude, that's hardcore.
Hey, this isn't a tomb.
It's a surfer's hall of fame.
Oh, man. This is so awesome. Wow!
Do you think people
will remember you like that?
A legendary surfer
who did all these amazing things?
Jeez, I hope not.
Really? What?
What are you talking about?
This is what I've always wanted.
To be remembered as a legend,
somebody respected.
You know, like a real winner.
Not me. I want to be remembered
for who I am, not what I did.
Look, Cody,
surfing's awesome and all...
...but there are
a lot more important things in life.
You'll see.
I just want to be remembered.
Lani, Lani, it's okay. It's just me, love.
- Paige.
- You all right?
- Yeah.
- Hello?
Cody? Lani? Anyone?
Conch?
Chicken Joe?
It's me.
Oi, over here.
Is everyone okay?
Just me and the big guy.
There's a little doodle
of a door on this wall.
Do you guys see a lever on your side?
I see it.
Whoa! Righteous door.
Are we glad to see you guys.
Come on, let's go.
Our friends might need help.
Stop. This place is dangerous.
There are lost souls
lurking around every corner.
I can feel them. They seem to be
guarding some kind of treasure.
What kind of idiot
would steal from a freaky place like this?
Ha, ha!
I'm rich! I'm rich! Look at how rich I am.
I wonder how much gold
we can pack on the whale.
Let's come back with a bigger whale.
No, 10 whales.
The conch says...
There's no reception in here.
Let me see if I can get any bars.
All right, there we go.
According to the conch, the penguins
on this island used to worship surfing.
We're in the treasure room of their king,
the wealthiest surfer who ever lived.
A rich surfer?
Now I've seen everything.
Mmm...
Michelle, we have had
some good times together...
...but I think we both know
Tank Evans deserves better.
Don't worry. It's not me, it's you.
Time to hit the road, babe.
Tank needs an upgrade.
Hold on a second. The conch tells me
this place is booby-trapped like crazy.
We take anything, we die.
What? That's too bad.
Well, I didn't get into this
for the money.
Easy come, easy go.
Hey, Tank. Did you hear that?
Don't touch anything.
This place is booby-trapped.
Say what?
Michelle! How could you?
- We've gotta get out.
- Let's go!
- What's happening?
- I don't know.
But let's not wait around to find out.
An old aqueduct.
That must lead outside.
Come on, Cody. It's our only shot.
Oh, yeah! Ha-ha-ha.
- Watch out for the darts!
- Shield yourself with your board.
Stay together.
Oh, look out!
Ow!
Aagh!
Oh!
- Which way do we go?
- Follow me. The conch knows the way.
I hope Cody made it out.
Don't worry, love.
If we made it out, they'll be fine.
I love all you guys.
Are you okay, big guy?
I feel very peaceful.
Must be the acupuncture.
- That's a pretty posh board, Tank.
- What?
- You didn't take that, did you?
- No, no, no.
This is my old board. It just...
Why all the fighting?
There you are.
Oh, Cody. You're okay!
- Oh...
- Oh-ho.
What's with him?
Enjoy it while it lasts.
See, this is the kind of
white-knuckle adventure...
...the power diva is all about.
Imagine, me and like 11 of my besties
traveling the world and kicking butt.
But also making time to hang out
by the pool and gossip.
And at the end of every episode,
I'll slap somebody.
It'll be a huge hit.
Mm. Mm.
Hey, guys.
We found some more firewood.
Great. Have a seat.
I saved you some dinner.
- Uh...
- Oops. My bad.
Was I not supposed to eat that?
Heh, heh, heh.
Aagh! You knew that was for me, Tank.
You snooze, you lose, bro.
Survival of the Tankiest.
Came up with that myself.
I may change it to Hankiest later.
Here, Cody.
I picked these fish heads out of the trash.
I think there's still
some meat in this one.
Nah, I got a better idea.
Hey, what are you doing?
Stop that! Hey, I mean it!
You're dead.
- Yeah.
- Whoa!
- Uhn!
- Ls that all you got?
Kick his butt.
Heh, heh, heh.
Whoa, whoa, wh...!
Whoops! Sorry.
Just stretching my calf muscle.
- Ha, ha! How do you like that?
- My tushy!
Not cool, bro.
You can't trip my guy like that.
Oh, yeah?
What do you wanna do about it?
It's been a while, dude.
- You think you can still handle it?
- Come on now, you can't see me.
Yeah. I want a piece.
Yeah! Take this.
All right. Enough.
It's supposed to be their fight,
remember?
Yeah!
One, two, three. That's it.
We have a winner.
Ha! I kicked your butt with my butt.
Oh, that smells.
That was fun. Let me know
when you're ready for a rematch.
I leave you alone for 10 minutes,
and this is what you do?
I expect rookie mistakes from rookies...
...but you guys know better.
And, Cody Maverick,
we'll never get to the Trenches...
...if you keep starting fights
with your teammates.
Ah! Yeah. Ha, ha!
Oh, wait.
Are we not doing this anymore?
Oh, my bad.
So other than getting
sat on, how do you think you're doing?
Okay, that was not my fault, man.
Hunter called it too early.
- I had Tank right where I wanted him.
- Ha-ha.
Where, on your head?
That's besides the point,
all right? Okay?
Anyways, my head is still in the game,
if that's what you're asking.
This is my one big chance to get off
Pen Gu and make something of myself.
I'm gonna show the Hang 5
I've got what it takes.
And I've been working out too.
Check this out. Can you tell?
Uh! Oh...
Oh, okay.
Can you please go get J.C.?
- Cock-a-doodle...
- You're gambling with your life, chicken.
Right, yeah.
Okay, got it.
Good news, everyone.
According to the conch,
we might reach the Trenches by nightfall.
Then tomorrow morning, it's RTL.
- RTL!
Is anyone ever gonna tell us
what that means?
What? And ruin the surprise?
Hey, guys.
You might want to look at this.
Anyone else get the feeling...
...this island really doesn't want us
to reach the Trenches?
Ideas, anybody?
We sure didn't come this far
to give up now.
The conch says
unless we can surf on fire...
...we'll have to find
another way around.
But this lava lake is huge.
Come on, Cody.
Surf...
...on fire. Hey.
Hey. Hey, guys, wait.
When we were stuck in that tomb...
...I saw some drawings
about a penguin who surfed through fire.
I thought it was just a cool made-up story,
but what if it's not?
What if somebody actually did it?
I have an idea.
It's crazy, but I think it just might work.
Spit it out, kid.
Undertaker, quick, give me a boost.
Who's up for some hang-gliding?
- Yeah! That's awesome! Yeah!
- Let's go! Let's do it!
Hey, Cody. Nice job coming up
with the idea for these hang gliders.
This is the kind of creative, out-of-the-box
thinking we need in Hang 5.
Ha, ha! Thanks, guys.
This is what I've been talking about.
I've got all kinds of ideas.
Like dolphin-powered jet skis.
Underwater breathing devices.
Hey, wait.
What if we put wheels on our surfboards
so we can surf on dry land? Yeah?
Whoa, wheels on a surfboard?
Let's not get too crazy here.
Keep up the good work.
Did you see that?
I'm gonna be in the Hang 5 for sure.
So who's the loser now, huh?
Whatever, chump. It ain't over yet.
Oh, not according to
Mr. McMahon and Hunter.
You better start
packing your bags, Tank.
Because tomorrow,
I'm gonna be part of the Hang 5.
Traveling the world,
doing the most radical stuff.
And you'll just go back to being
a nobody from nowhere island.
And you'll never see me again.
What?
You don't wanna go back to Pen Gu?
What about our surf school?
Lani, come on.
It's the Hang 5, okay?
I'm gonna be famous.
I'll be a hero to millions of kids.
But you're already a hero
to the kids back home.
And to me.
This is different. Can't you see that?
I'll be on the best surf team
on the planet.
I'll finally be somebody.
That's what really matters.
Hey, Cody. Check out my glider, dude.
Coming, J.C.
Come show me how this thing's
supposed to work. Ha-ha-ha.
Eh... Come on, Joe. Let's go.
I guess we're just a couple of nobodies
from nowhere island.
Let's be safe, guys.
This ain't the ocean.
If you wipe out up here,
you'll be a bucket of extra crispy.
Oh, man. Just like my uncle,
Chicken Fernando.
You're going down, twerp.
No more Mr. Nice Tank.
You are not gonna take my spot
on the Hang 5.
Okay, let's see what you got.
On your mark.
Get ready.
- Hey, watch it, man.
- Heh, heh, heh.
- Go!
- Yeah!
Oh.
Hot, hot, hot.
All right!
Loving the lava.
There you are.
You're gonna eat it, Tank.
- Show me what you got. You like that?
- That's not nice. Stop that.
- Hey, that's not fair. Whoa!
- This is fun.
Wait, I'm first?
Ha, ha, ha!
I'm first.
- Payback time. Ha, ha, ha!
- Oh!
Whoa! Whoa!
Whoa!
Grr...
Oh, you are not taking this
away from me, Tank.
- Got you.
- What are you doing?
Whoa! Whoa!
How do you like me now?
Oof! Aaah!
I don't want to be a combo meal!
Hang on, Joe! I got you, buddy.
Whoa. My board. No!
All right!
Who's awesome? I'm awesome.
What's going on, everyone?
The Undertaker saved me from death.
Ironic.
Where's your board?
You destroyed it
when you bumped Tank into Joe.
What? Joe, man, I'm so sorry.
I didn't mean to...
"Sorry" doesn't cut it, Cody.
What the heck were you thinking?
Yeah, man. What'd I ever do to you?
All these years of friendship.
And he still...
He still keeps these... These walls up.
And I don't know
how to break them down.
I just don't know what to think anymore.
Are you kidding me, dude?
This guy has been sabotaging me
since day one.
And you think that makes it okay?
Well, I... Yeah.
I was just trying to win.
So I could prove I can be one of you.
Putting your friends in danger
only proves that you're nothing like us.
The Hang 5 is a family.
We have each other's back,
no matter what.
Lani. Tell them I didn't mean for this
to happen. All right? You know me.
Yeah, Cody, I do.
And that's why
I'm just so disappointed in you right now.
And you were doing so well too.
I told you from the start
this kid's trouble.
He almost got the chicken killed.
That would have been on you, J.C.
Cody's not like that, Mr. McMahon.
He just got carried away
competing with Tank.
That guy's been acting like a jerk
this whole time.
I wanted to know
how Cody deals with problems...
...since you thought he was special.
And now I know. We're a team, J.C.
That kid doesn't care about
anything other than winning.
And he doesn't give two sand crabs
about who gets in his way.
Maybe that's what you saw in him
back at Pen Gu.
Have you thought about that?
Cock-a...
Oh, no.
You guys, come look at this.
"Joe, sorry for everything.
You deserve this more than me.
Your bro, Cody."
Ha, ha, ha! What a stupid note.
"You deserve this more than me."
Hey, is anybody else surprised
Chicken Joe can read? Ha, ha, ha!
We have to find Cody.
He couldn't have gotten that far.
That was pretty sad, bro.
Lani, wait.
I think you gotta let Cody
work things out on his own.
He'll come back when he's ready.
But how can you be sure?
I've been where he's at.
Trust me. He just needs time to think.
It's time we haul our butts
down to the Trenches.
The best waves come at dawn.
Does anyone else think
a storm is coming?
We're counting on it.
Oh, cool. Right on, then.
Whoa!
"Here lies the great hero
of Slaughter island...
...the bravest
and most honored surfer of all.
He gave up his chance
at fame and fortune...
...and he chose to stay with his people
to protect them...
...from the treacherous waters
of the Trenches...
...by performing the sacred rites
of Ride the Lightning."
RTL.
Oh, no. I gotta tell Lani and Joe.
Whoa!
My friends, we finally made it.
Behold, the Trenches.
Whoa. Look at all these
broken surfboards.
Must have been some major wipeouts.
I'm not gonna end up like them.
I'm way better than those guys.
Ladies and gentlemen,
the moment you've all been waiting for.
Hang 5, prepare to RTL!
RTL!
Wait a minute.
Are you telling me that RTL stands for...
Ride the Lightning.
Whoa! Wicked timing
on that delivery, bro.
Surfing during a lightning storm?
You actually planned for this?
Are you guys completely insane?
Well, yeah.
We figured you knew that about us.
Lani, we're all about pushing ourselves
to the absolute limit.
And it doesn't get any more extreme
than this.
I'm sorry, you guys. I can't do this.
Thank you for the opportunity,
but no, thank you.
This isn't for me.
Hey, we understand, love.
No hard feelings.
What about you, Chicken?
Are you ready
for a spot on the Hang 5?
I don't think I'm quite ready
for that big chicken bucket...
...up in the sky just yet.
Oh, hey.
How about an honorary membership?
Heh, heh, heh. You got it.
So how about it, Tank?
So, uh, all I gotta do...
- ...is surf one gigantic 50-foot wave.
- Yup.
It's in the middle of
a lightning-filled thunderstorm.
Oh, yeah.
Also off a beach
littered with jagged coral reef.
Exactly.
But then I'm in the Hang 5
and I'll be famous...
...and make lots of money
selling surf videos.
You gotta do more than surf it,
you gotta survive it.
And make it look good.
You in or you out?
Um... In?
In. I'm definitely in.
This is a good decision.
- Sweet. Headbutt for good luck.
- Oh!
Oh, yeah. I'm gonna miss that if I die.
Then let's RTL.
RTL!
Sweet! Yeah!
I can't watch. But I can't not watch.
I'm a lifeguard, Joe.
I'm supposed to protect
all beachgoers.
I swore a Hippocratic oath.
Hah. Hippos. They're rad.
Are you sure
we have to paddle out this far?
It seems far.
I can't even see the beach from here.
All right, here's how this works.
Don't panic.
Work as a team.
And keep an eye out for each other.
And we'll all make it through this.
Whoa!
Here we go, Tank.
This is your last test.
Mr. McMahon thinks
you're a yellow-bellied coward.
- But I told him...
- What?
...you were the real deal.
Don't let me down, Tank.
Or we'll all die.
Do not...
I repeat, do not go rogue out there.
We're all counting on each other.
Got it?
Okay, here it comes!
- Yes!
- All right!
Come on, Tank. It's go time.
Everybody, ready?
Yeah, I was born ready!
Oh, yeah!
Whoa!
- Ha-ha-ha.
- Come on.
This is the moment
we've been waiting for!
Whoa, this is amazing!
Let's ride!
Yeah!
- No way, man. No, I can't do it.
- Whoa!
Tank, don't!
Stay in formation. It's the only way.
Don't let it touch you.
Unh!
Undertaker, I'm coming for you.
- Look out!
- We're not gonna make it!
Help! I got him, he's been hit.
Move aside! I can save him.
Oh, I hope I'm not too late.
Whoa! Good to get out of that mess.
Oh, crap.
No!
Ah. Ooh!
Oh, man.
This thing is like a lightning rod.
No!
Help!
Tank! Hang on, I'm coming.
Hunter!
Hunter, Hanky needs you.
- Hold on.
- Oh, this is a bad idea, Maverick.
- Stop fidgeting.
- Go left. Go right.
- You're doing it all wrong.
- Enough with the backseat surfing, okay?
My mom's gonna be
so mad at you if we die.
Come on.
No.
Hang on, Under-bro.
Clear.
Aaagh!
Now, that was gnarly.
- You did it.
- Oh, dude. Welcome back.
You okay, big guy?
Forget about me. Go help them.
- What happened to you?
- He came back.
He risked his life to save Tank.
Oh! You could have been killed.
Yeah, I know.
But it's like you said, J.C.
We have each other's back,
no matter what.
I think you have something to say
to Cody.
Thanks, Maverick. Um...
So are we... Are we cool?
Uh...
Yeah, we're cool.
Awesome. We should hang out.
We should totally hang out.
Not bad. Not bad at all.
That's what I saw in him.
Cody Maverick...
...you're one bodacious surfer.
But even more importantly,
a good dude.
On behalf of the Hang 5,
we'd be honored to have you join us.
Gnarly.
Joining the Hang 5
would be the biggest honor...
...of my entire life.
But I... l have to decline.
- No.
- Wait, what?
Dude, are you sure?
Yeah, bro. I am.
All this time,
I thought joining the Hang 5...
...the greatest surF team,
would make me a somebody.
A winner that eveyone respected.
But now I know
I'm already part of a great team.
With the coolest chicken of the sea.
And the best, raddest surfer
on Pen Gu.
Tank?
Oh, right. Yeah.
Friendship is truly the universe's...
...most precious gift.
But what does this mean for us?
Now we're one member short.
- I'm staying.
- Really?
Yeah, our adventures
are too much fun.
Who wants to iust drink
fish milk coladas...
...on the beach all day anyways?
Hey, you guys know
what we've never done before?
Surfed during a tsunami.
Who's up for it?
- Yeah!
- All right!
Dude.
- Ride the RTS.
- Tsunami starts with a T, boss.
Oh, yeah. Ride the RTT. Ha, ha!
Yeah? Yeah? Whoa.
So that's why
evemhing tastes like me.
Thanks, dude.
All right, re rhey
Still Cool? SurF Edition, take mo.
Can you tell us
what you've been up to...
- ...for the last couple years?
- Oh, it's been a crazy ride, man.
But first, I have a question for you.
Oh, no. Not again. Come on.
We're not gonna finish the show
if you keep changing the script.
Are you a fan of the legenday Hang 5?
Wanna learn extreme surF moves...
...like the tombstone pile driver
from the Undertaker?
What about Paige's PTO?
Well, you can learn those
and many more...
...from Pen Gu SurF Academy.
At PSA, you'll learn how to have fun,
be safe and surF like a pro.
Just like my friends,
Cody, Lani and Chicken Joe.
Mention this commercial and receive
a free case of fresh fish milk...
...with your membership.
So stop by the North Shore
and hang out with us.
That's Pen Gu SurF Academy.
Where the sun never sets.
Okay. That's a wrap on this episode...
...of re rhey Still Cool? SurF Edition.
And cut.
You should learn to surF
from a real master.
- Right, gang?
- Yes, sensei.
Oh, oh, oh...
I'll also teach you about teamwork...
...and proper surF etiquette!
- Okay, cut.
- Wait, stop.
Stop.
Yeah. Whoo!
We'll be there in
four, three, mo... Oh! Oh!
I picked this up for you
while I was on tour.
- Thanks, Joe! Ha, ha, ha!
- I know how much you like these... Oh!
Undertaker, quick, give me a boost.
Aah!
Someone needs to stop Clearway Law.
Public shouldn't leave reviews for lawyers.