Watch Movies, TV Series and Live Sports
Signup Here -> WWW.ADMITME.APP
He slaughtered our men...
our brothers...
our sons.
The dead cry out
to us for justice.
On their souls, I swear to you.
The man who took
our loved ones from us...
the man who has brought us
such pain and sorrow.
We Will find him.
We will bring him here.
We will not rest until his blood
flows into this very ground.
We will have our revenge.
Sir? Excuse me.
Yeah.
The finish is included
in the cost of the wash.
That's okay,
I'd rather do it myself.
I'm a little
obsessive that way.
Lenore.
Bryan.
Hi. How are you?
Fine. You?
Mmm, good, good.
Is something up?
No. It's Saturday, two o'clock.
Kim's driving lesson?
Uh... Music lesson
got switched.
The Tuesday one
or the Friday one?
I have no idea.
You know how kids are.
Mmm-hmm.
Especially the ones
who are desperate
to pass their driving
test at the third try.
She's not desperate.
But she failed the test twice, Lennie.
It's important.
So, where is she, really?
I've never been
a good liar, have I?
No, it's not your forte.
She's at her boyfriend.
She has a boyfriend?
Do you want to
come in for a drink?
Yeah.
I think you should.
Why didn't she tell me, for God's sake?
She probably didn't want you
running a full security check...
of everything he's done
since kindergarten.
But she's okay, right?
Yeah, she's okay.
Lennie, tell me
it's none of my business...
but are you okay?
No.
Not really.
We've separated.
Lennie, if there's
anything I can do...
Well, I better...
Thanks for the wine.
Bryan.
Don't.
I don't even know
where the kid lives.
You found her in a city of 12
million people within 72 hours.
Promise me.
I just told you...
Promise.
I'm going to
give her her space.
Let me show you what I know
Let me take you where I'll go
I want to, yeah, share with you
Why won't you let me...
Um... Just wait a sec.
What?
I really like you.
What is it?
Um...
It's okay. It's okay.
Take all the time you need.
Hi.
May I help you?
Is Kim here?
Yeah, and you are...?
Her father.
Mr. Mills, what a pleasure.
I'm Jamie.
Come in.
Can I get you anything?
A drink?
Just my daughter will be fine.
Dad?
Hi.
What are you doing here?
I know how important it is
for you to pass your test.
Wait. Kim, you don't
have a license?
Have you ever tried to
parallel park an Escalade?
I told you to take
the test with my car.
God. Dad.
Thank you.
A pleasure to
meet you, Mr. Mills.
Could we slow down
a little bit, please?
I can't believe you just did that.
You're leaving on
fall break next week.
This is the only time I can get to
do this before I go to Istanbul.
We planned this. When you
make plans, you keep them.
No, Dad, you planned this.
How did you even find me?
Your mom and I were talking.
Why didn't you tell me
you have a boyfriend?
Because I knew
you'd overreact...
and I just want to feel normal
even if I'm just pretending.
Remember to brake
before the stop...
Dad.
Mom doesn't know
where Jamie lives.
GPS?
I had it installed in your phone.
I'm sorry.
You hear so many scary stories of
goings-on with people your age...
Dad, I don't even know how to
start feeling normal again...
but this definitely isn't it.
Kim, you can move.
Use your side mirror.
Perfect. Why couldn't you
do that in the test?
I don't know.
Maybe I didn't really
want a license.
Listen...
of course I know
where you're coming from.
But you have to trust me
to figure this out.
Don't do this again, please?
I won't.
And don't go running a background
check on him with your friends.
I won't.
Okay.
See you Wednesday.
Two o'clock.
Love you.
Hey, I love you.
Yeah.
Sam. Hi. It's me.
Listen. I want you to run a
check on someone. Jamie Conrad.
The usual.
Not too deep.
You got it.
Okay. Thanks.
Sir.
Thank you.
Mr. Pitrel?
I have a registered letter for you.
- Can you take that up, Sébastien?
- Yes, sir.
Here.
Sébastien?
Where is he?
I told you.
I don't know.
Where is he?
Okay.
You want to play with me.
No, no!
But I'm a good player, too.
Shh!
Look.
No, no!
I guess the rules are changing.
This man came to Paris.
He used a card
to come into our house
and kill my friends..
And my brother.
This is your card.
Where is he?
Stu, where are you going?
Come back!
What's happened?
Are you okay?
Yeah, I'm great.
Come in. I'll get Kim.
Hey, hey, hey.
Lennie, talk to me.
We had this trip planned to
China for Kim's spring break...
as a family, to try
and work things out.
And when Stu and I...
I just thought it would
be nice for Kim and I
to be away together...
away from all the tension.
He canceled everything.
All the reservations.
I just can't believe
he did this to us.
I'm just so tired.
Just the fighting, the lawyers.
He's turned into
such a bastard.
I'm sorry, Lennie.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry. This is
really not your problem.
It's my turn to have...
I'll figure it out.
Look...
Why don't you and
Kim come with me?
But we can't impose on you.
You're working.
You're not imposing.
I'm working for three days.
Then you can come over.
It could be fun.
That's so sweet.
I don't know.
I can't think right now.
Sure, I understand.
No pressure.
I leave in the morning.
I work three days. Call me.
If you're coming, I'll hang around.
If not, I'll come back.
That's it.
I'll go get Kim.
Okay.
Thank you, Bryan.
She is definitely coming.
I don't know. Sam, I don't know.
Oh, come on.
You should have insisted.
Mmm-hmm.
Come on, guys.
Cut me some slack.
She's going
through a hard time.
I didn't want to
make it harder on her.
She was confiding in me.
Oh! I didn't know you guys
were still so cozy...
that she shares her
marriage issues with you.
Wait a minute.
I know you guys were close,
obviously, but are you close again?
Close like...
I'll lay money she's still
got something for him.
Don't go there, friend.
Maybe he still
has something for her!
Can we talk about basketball?
For God's sake, come on!
Istanbul.
Thank you, Mr. Mills.
You made my stay
feel very secure.
Thank you.
Have a safe trip home.
You also.
You've reached Lenore. Leave
a message after the beep.
Hey, it's me.
No message from you...
so I guess you probably
found some place to go.
I hope things are
a little easier.
If you ever need to talk
or anything, I'm here.
I mean, I'll be there.
I'll probably
ship out tomorrow.
No news from Kim.
I guess she's busy with
the boyfriend and all.
Dad.
Surprise!
Oh, my God. Kim, baby.
Hey, Lennie.
Hello, Bryan.
I was just leaving you a message.
When I didn't hear, it was...
We wanted to surprise you.
Well, you succeeded.
You guys could have
been surprised.
I could have been out
of here and headed home.
Mom's been calling Sam.
Oh, yeah?
Uh-huh. Yes.
We've been tracking you.
Exactly. You're not the
only one who's got moves.
Apparently not.
Welcome to Istanbul.
Not too shabby, huh?
Wow.
Oh, my God.
Mom, look at this.
Oh, my God!
It's crazy, right?
It's beautiful!
Thank you so much.
My pleasure.
Listen, I'll let you
get settled...
and I'll come and collect
you in half an hour?
Okay.
Later.
Good morning.
Good.
Go.
Fast.
Let's go.
Hey.
You look great.
You, too.
So, where are we heading?
Well, I am going nowhere.
I'm beat.
I'm just going to take a nice
long bath and get into bed.
Lennie. Are you sure?
Yeah.
I guess it's just
you and me, kiddo.
Anything special
you'd like to do?
Kind of. Maybe.
Hey.
You ready to take off, too?
No, I thought I'd stick around
for a couple of more hours.
Really?
Yeah.
Cool.
No. Just kidding.
Come on. Let's go. All right.
It's so crazy here.
On this side is Europe,
and the other side is Asia.
And every conquest since,
for the last 2,500 years...
whether it was the West going
East or the East going West...
they all used this
very same waterway.
You want some tea, baby?
Yeah.
Just one, please.
How do you know all this stuff?
How do I know it?
I read it in a book
on the flight over.
And you can borrow
it if you wish.
Yeah, I would.
So, this Jamie...
Is it... serious?
That was a really
smooth transition.
I don't know.
It's only been a few months.
Are you in love with him?
I guess I'm not sure yet.
Have you ever
been in love before?
Not the way that
Mom talks about it.
How does she describe it?
She said when you guys met...
that it was super special.
Super special?
She said that?
I think the exact
word she used was...
"magical."
Magical, huh?
It's good to see
you again, my friend.
Is everything prepared?
As you requested.
Ah! Perfect.
Yeah?
He's in the lobby.
Wait until he's outside.
And remember, alive.
He's on to me.
I'm leaving.
- Hey.
- Hi.
I thought we were
having lunch in the bazaar.
Um...
Jet lag just hit me...
so I figured I'd veg out by
the pool and let you guys go.
Meet up with you later?
I guess. Okay with you?
Of course. It's fine.
Oh, okay. Bye.
Hey, Kim.
That book I was telling you about?
It's on my dresser.
Definitely.
No adventuring.
I'll go call the car.
Have fun.
Hey, Kim.
I know what you're doing.
What?
Yeah?
The daughter is staying here.
What can we do?
I want all three of them.
Yes?
She thinks we just
fell off the turnip truck.
What do you mean?
She's trying to play cupid.
Oh, I see.
When you first came back...
and said you wanted to
make up for all that time
that you lost with Kim?
Uh-huh?
I thought, "Right.
Three weeks, he's gone."
That was usually about the
limit you stuck around.
Give or take a week.
Not too close.
You really proved me wrong.
I thought you'd never change.
Why not?
I don't know.
Your personality.
When you commit to something...
you focus all
your energy there.
Like a dog with a bone.
Nice analogy.
You know what I mean.
When you give, it's 100
percent of 100 percent.
If I was on to something,
it was just that thing.
Even though I tell myself
I should change...
I could never give it up.
You gave us up.
Mmm-mmm.
No, never.
Not in here.
Driver, turn left.
Lennie, don't.
What?
Will you tell me
what's going on?
It's okay.
Where is he?
You see the gallery entrance
in the middle of the block?
Will you tell me what's going on?
Do you see it?
Yeah, I see it.
When we stop,
I want you to get out
of the car like
you're a shopper.
I want you to go inside.
Will you tell me
what's going on?
Listen to me.
Lennie, there's
no time for this.
Just talk to me!
Listen.
When you exit the back of the
fabric store, turn right.
Take the first
street on the right,
then left on
the very next street.
Go straight until you
come to a set of steps.
There's a red corridor.
It's a lane.
When you exit the lane,
there's a cab stand.
Go back to the hotel.
Get Kim. Get the head
of hotel security...
and demand that he
cordon off your room.
Do not open
the door for anyone.
No room service, no police, no one.
You wait for me.
I can't believe
this is happening.
I need you to focus.
Are you ready?
No.
I need you to be ready.
Come on, focus.
Driver, stop.
Okay, go.
Wait, what about you?
I'll be fine.
It's the guys following us who
are about to have a problem.
When a dog has a bone...
the last thing you want to do
is try and take it from him.
Be careful.
Out of the car.
Come on. Move,
move, move!
Sir! Please.
Please. Sir!
He knows.
Do it now.
Come on.
Shit.
Come on, Kim,
answer the goddamn phone.
He's gone!
Oh, God, no!
Somebody help me!
The key!
Open the door, please!
Shit!
I'll blow his brains out.
Oh, Bryan!
Please!
Drop the gun.
I really wish you were here.
Me too. You have no idea.
What?
My dad's calling.
He's on a date with my mom.
I'll call you right back.
Miss you. Bye.
How's it going?
Listen to me carefully, Kim.
Your mother and I...
are going to be taken.
Daddy!
Oh, my God.
And people are going to
come for you, too.
Leave the place
where you are calmly.
Go to where the book
is I told you about.
There's a door. Go into the
room and hide in the closet.
You got that?
Yes.
Good. I'll call you.
Go, now.
No!
She is in room 422.
No! No!
One, two, three...
four, five, six.
Right turn.
Man singing.
One, two, three...
four.
Boat.
The pool!
Security, fourth floor.
Do you copy me?
Send someone now.
25...
26... 27...
28...
29.
Stop.
She's not here.
- Not here?
- Check her dad's room.
Hammer on metal.
Left. Gear shift
to second.
One, two, three.
Birds.
You have them?
Yes, efendi. Both.
Take them to the shop.
Look!
A flip-flop.
You go left!
C'mon!
Right turn.
Twenty-seven.
Stop.
No! No!
I shot some guy!
Come on, Sam. Pick up.
Hey, this is Sam.
Leave me a message.
Shit.
Are you guys okay?
No, no.
Are you all right?
Yes.
I'm just scared.
Kim, listen to me
very carefully.
I need you to calm
down and pull yourself together.
Okay.
The men who came for you,
did they leave?
Yes. What do they want?
I'm going to find out.
Is Mom okay?
Dad.
Mom's fine.
Okay.
What are we going to do?
I want you to go to the U.S. Embassy.
You'll be safe there.
What about you and Mom?
I'll figure something out.
Where are you now?
I don't really know, Kim.
Dad, how can I tell them
where to find you, then?
You can't.
Now get going.
No.
Kimmie...
No. Tell me what to do.
No, Kim.
Dad, if you tell me what
to do, I can do it.
Kim, this is not a game.
I know that.
It's my parents' lives.
Dad, please.
You're wasting time.
Please.
Tell me what to do.
Can you get out of
the closet safely?
Yes.
If you can,
take the case with you.
Okay.
I'm out.
The combination
is 23-28-84.
Is it open?
Yeah.
Okay. Do you see a map?
Take the map.
You'll see a scale on
the top in kilometers.
Do you see it?
Yeah, I see it.
Take a shoelace from one
of my shoes in the closet.
Use it as a guide.
There's a pen in the case.
Take it.
Draw a circle with the
hotel in the center of it.
It's done.
Make the diameter
three kilometers.
You got that?
It's done.
Draw another circle with
the market in the center.
Okay.
Do the circles
intersect at any points?
No.
Now, take one of
those little cans,
the ones with
the pins on the top.
It's a grenade.
I want you to go to the
balcony with the grenade.
Is there a safe place
you can throw it?
There's a parking garage.
Anyone on it?
No.
I want you to pull the pin
out of the grenade...
count to three
so I can hear it,
then toss it as far as you can.
And then run back
into the room.
Keep the phone on so I
can hear the explosion.
One...
two...
three.
One, two, three...
Dad?
Now draw a circle on the map
with the hotel in the middle...
and the circumference
at 4.5 kilometers.
Do the circles
intersect at any points?
Yeah, at two points.
I'm at one of the two
intersecting points.
Now go outside and look at
the flags on the rooftops.
Do you see the flags?
Yes.
Are they in the wind?
Yeah.
Going east, right?
I think so, yeah.
How did you know?
Now look at the map.
I want you to go to the point where
the circles intersect at the east.
I want you to take
one of the guns,
get to a rooftop,
wait for my call.
And two of the grenades.
Go to the rooftop at
the most easterly point.
Get up to the rooftop.
Wait for my call.
Be casual, Kim.
Blend in.
Okay.
Dad?
Who are you?
Those clothes don't belong to you.
Help!
There's a thief in here!
You know this man?
This one?
No.
What do you want?
You recognize none of them.
To you, they were nothing.
But to other people...
they are sons and grandsons.
Fathers and husbands.
And you killed them all.
Like they were
so many nothings.
And this one?
You recognize him?
You do recognize him.
Him, you didn’t just kill.
Him, you strapped to a chair.
You attached electric
cables to the chair.
You turned the current on...
and you left it on
until his heart burst.
He's the one who kidnapped dozens
of girls and ruined their lives.
He was my son.
Marko, from Tropojë.
And I have come to
take you to Tropojë...
to face you to the people
whose lives you have ruined.
To give them justice.
You mean to give them revenge.
It if gives us peace
call it anything you wish.
I killed your son because
he kidnapped my daughter.
I don't care what he did!
I only know...
I will never see
his face again.
I will never hear his voice.
And as you held him responsible
for your daughter...
I hold you responsible for him.
Your death will not be quick.
It will not be pleasant.
But before you die...
this is what you will see.
Bring her in.
Bryan...
How long will it take for the
blood to rush to her head...
and have no place to go?
About 30 minutes.
You are right.
You're an expert for this.
So you have 30 minutes
to watch her die.
She had nothing
to do with this.
Do what you want with me.
Let her go.
Don't play the hero with me.
Now we are going to
catch your daughter.
She will be sold to the
lowest brothel in this world.
No! No!
She will be abused
by so many men...
that she'll be nothing more than a
piece of meat a dog would not have.
Don't listen to them, Lennie.
Kim is safe.
I spoke with her.
She's safe.
You have to stay calm.
Breathe slowly.
You have to.
I won't let anything
happen to you, or to her.
I promise.
Hello, Murad?
Shh!
Quiet.
We lost the girl.
The girl has gone.
I'll be back as soon as
we get her, then we move.
Come on!
Hold on, Lennie.
Hold on.
What's he doing?
Get out of the way!
Sorry! Sorry!
Come back!
You have to pay!
Lennie.
I'm with you, baby.
I'm here. I'm here.
Come on. Call.
Please, come on.
Lennie.
Bryan.
Lennie. Lennie.
I'm coming back.
Please.
I'm here.
Set off another grenade.
Dad?
You're close.
I want you to keep moving east.
Count to 30 and then
set off another one.
One, two, three...
18,19...
26, 27...
28, 29...
30.
Go out and check
what's going on.
Kim.
Yeah.
Look east. Look for a
white cloud of steam.
I see it.
Run to it. Tell me
when you're there.
I'm going down.
Dad.
Where are you?
I'm right by the steam.
Drop the gun down the vent.
Oh, God, they're here.
They're coming.
Drop the gun, Kim, and run.
Go.
Dad! They're coming.
I'm coming back.
Drop that.
On your knees!
Don't do this.
Please.
Dad?
Dad! Dad!
Baby.
Where's Mom?
Is she okay?
She's safe.
Slow down,
slow down, slow down.
I've got a fare.
I'll be back.
That man had the same
tattoo as the men in Paris.
It's not you they want, Kim.
It's me.
I want you to wait here.
I'm going to get Mom.
Wait five minutes,
and if I don't show up...
I want you to go straight here,
to the American Embassy.
Tell them what happened. Dad...
No time, Kim.
Give me your phone.
You wait five minutes,
not a moment longer.
No matter what happens,
time runs out, you go.
You understand me?
Okay.
No!
No.
Bryan!
Yes?
Move!
You killed him.
I had no choice. Move.
Where's Mom? She's
fine, she's not far.
Where is she?
Come on, move!
I don't want to do this.
Keep going, Kim.
Where are we going?
Go straight. We have
to go to the Embassy.
I'm not sure I can.
Do you know how to shoot? No.
Then drive.
They escaped.
Officer down in Balat.
Copy.
Shit, cops.
I have to stop.
No, I just shot one of them.
Now, go.
Come on, go!
Right.
Back, back, back!
Come on, move!
Come on, Kim.
Go, go!
Faster.
Keep going.
Left!
Yeah.
They're in the taxi!
Keep going.
Oh, no.
Shit.
Stay low. Keep going.
Come on, faster.
I can't.
You can do it!
I can't!
Come on, move! Move.
Dad!
Keep going.
Move!
Right.
Oh, shit.
No!
Come on, Kim. Move!
Go!
I'm trying.
Come on, keep going.
Turn left.
Shit.
Dad!
Keep going. Stay low.
Faster, Kim.
I can't.
Come on, faster!
Dad!
Keep going.
You can make it.
Do it.
Here! Don't stop.
But the soldiers.
They'll move.
Down, Kim!
Nobody shoot.
It's a suicide bomber.
Are you okay?
Yeah.
Keep your head down, Kimmie.
Hey, Bry.
Sam, we're in a courtyard of the U.
S. Embassy in Istanbul...
in a smashed-up car.
Don't ask.
Can you call someone to make
sure we don't get shot?
Yeah, of course.
Thanks.
It's Bry. He's in
trouble in Istanbul.
Mom didn't get away, did she?
No.
Oh, God, Dad.
Tell me the truth.
Is she...
No, no, no, Kim.
No, she's not.
But they have her.
And they will use her until
they get what they want.
Me.
You'll be safe here in the
Embassy until I come back.
Kimmie, it's going to be okay.
Nothing's okay.
Kim, listen.
I have to find them...
and bring your mom back.
And then I have to
make sure these people
never bother us
again in our lives.
What are you going to do?
What I do best.
Mrs. Mills.
What should I do
with you, Mrs. Mills?
I have nothing against you.
You didn't kill my son.
But your husband did.
Now, he betrayed
you by choosing
to save your daughter
instead of you.
He left you here like a dog.
At least my daughter
is still alive.
Mrs. Mills,
you're a good mother...
and a brave woman.
For that, I'm going to
send you back home...
piece by piece.
Shut up!
Ohri, shoot this dog.
Go and see what's happened.
Let's go. Move through
here, to the hammam.
Hurry!
Mirko!
You stay here.
No!
No.
No. Bryan!
Come on!
You can't come in!
Get lost.
Lennie.
I'm here, baby.
I'm here.
I'm coming back, Lennie.
I'm coming back.
Okay?
What are you waiting for?
You have other sons?
Two.
And if I killed you, they
will come and seek revenge.
They will, for sure.
And I will kill them, too.
You can change that.
You can go home,
live your life.
Enjoy your sons,
your grandsons.
And my other son...
Marko.
The son you killed.
Am I supposed to
just forget it?
No.
You will just have
to live with it,
like the parents of all
those kidnapped girls.
Or you can die here.
What are you telling me?
What I'm saying is,
if you give me your word...
I will throw down this gun
and simply walk away.
Why?
Because I am tired of it all.
Lennie, I'm here.
I'm here, baby.
I'm here.
Come on, baby.
It's okay. It's okay.
It's okay.
We're safe.
Bryan...
Kim.
Kim...
She's safe.
We're all safe.
Okay.
Line it up.
That's it.
Now, begin to cut.
Not too fast, not too fast.
Straighten it out.
Straighten, straighten.
That's it.
Stop, stop, stop.
Perfect.
Perfect score.
Great!
Congratulations.
Thank you.
I was perfect.
I've been saying that
since the day you were born.
Congratulations.
So, what would you like
to do to celebrate?
Um...
I think I have an idea.
Yeah?
Yeah. I'll drive.
Of course.
Don't knock it till you try it
Just come out to LA...
Here you go.
Three double-chocolate fudge.
Thank you.
Who's having the strawberry?
I'm sorry, but I
just ordered three.
Actually, the order said four.
I ordered the fourth one.
For who?
Oh, Jamie.
Hey.
Hi.
Hi. Perfect timing.
Jamie.
It's cool if he
joins us, right?
Of course it is, honey.
Dad?
Behave.
It's nice to see
you again, sir.
Nice to see you, too.
Sit down.
Hi.
We got you a strawberry.
Oh, please.
Thanks, Dad.
Don't shoot this one. I really like him.
You know I'm not one
to break promises
I don't want to hurt you
but I need to breathe
At the end of it all
you're still my best friend
But there's something inside
that I need to release
Which way is right
Which way is wrong
How do I say that
I need to move on
You know we're
headed separate ways
And it feels like I am
just too close to love you
There's nothing
I can really say
I can't lie no more
I can't hide no more
Got to be true to myself
And it feels like I am
just too close to love you
So I'll be on my way
You gave me more
that I can return
Yet there's oh, so much
that you deserve
There's nothing to say
nothing to do
I've nothing to give
I must leave without you
You know we're
headed separate ways
And it feels like I am
just too close to love you
There's nothing
I can really say
I can't lie no more
I can't hide no more
Got to be true to myself
And it feels like I am
just too close to love you
So I'll be on my way
And it feels like I am
just too close to love you
There's nothing
that I can really say
I can't lie no more
I can't hide no more
Got to be true to myself
And it feels like I am
just too close to love you
So I'll be on my way
Watch Movies, TV Series and Live Sports
Signup Here -> WWW.ADMITME.APP