Watch Movies, TV Series and Live Sports
Signup Here -> WWW.ADMITME.APP
PHIL COLLINS..
# Put your faith in #
# What you most believe in #
# Two worlds, one family #
# Trust your heart #
# Let fate decide #
# To guide these lives #
# To guide these lives
we see #
CHORUS.. # Put your faith
in what you most believe in #
ALL..
# Two worlds, one family #
Ha ha ha ha ha!
Goodness! Have we ever
gone that fast before?
Let's leap off
the waterfalls next.
Oh, no, Tarzan, dear.
I think I'll pass this time.
Really?
Aren't you having fun?
Oh, yes! I'd love
to spend the afternoon...
swinging through the trees...
and leaping
off the waterfalls...
but I have
some things to do. Yes.
Like what?
Well, like, um... laundry.
Yes. Look at how dingy
this skirt is.
Absolutely filthy.
Yes. Much laundry to do.
Far too much to
allow me to go playing...
and waterfall leaping
and all those wonderful things.
So, run along
and see those falls.
Well, if that's what you want.
It is.
It's absolutely what I want.
Now, you run along.
Oh!
What was that all about?
Why are you trying
to ditch Tarzan?
Why, Terk. Ha ha ha!
I haven't the faintest idea
what you're talking about.
Very well.
You caught me.
You see, today marks
the first anniversary...
of my marriage to Tarzan.
Get out!
You kids have been married
a year already?
Yes. One year to the day.
Now, in England,
couples do special things...
for each other
on their anniversaries...
so I was thinking perhaps
a party or some such.
Oh, Tarzan
will be so surprised...
when he steps into
the treehouse and sees-
Jane, you sure
this is a good idea?
What do you mean, Terk?
Well, Tarzan
kind of has a hard time...
fitting into
your British social events.
Like, remember when your
three friends came to visit?
Oh, I remember this.
It all started
innocently enough...
just a pleasant afternoon
in the jungle.
Aah!
- Gotcha!
- Ha ha ha!
Yes, but you've got to admit...
that I'm getting better
at treetop tag.
Yes. You act more
like an ape every day.
Like an ape?
Uhh! Well, I never...
heard such a sweet sentiment.
Run!
They're comin'!
Who?
Unhand her,
you savage wild man!
- Eleanor?
- Hey! Ow!
JANE.. Eleanor!
Greenly! Hazel!
What are you doing?
We've come to rescue you.
Rescue?
- Stay back!
- Keep away!
Come, Jane! Hurry!
Aah! Greenly!
Back! Back! Captain Jerrold!
Help us!
Good day, Miss Porter, Tarzan.
Captain Jerrold.
Ladies, I'll be heading
back to the ship now.
Enjoy your visit.
What? No!
Don't leave us here!
Don't worry, Jane.
We'll protect you
from the savage wild man.
No, no. You don't understand.
No, let go.
Let go! Let - let go!
I don't need to be rescued.
I tried to tell them...
that you stayed behind
by your own choice...
and that you were
perfectly safe and happy...
here in the jungle,
but they wouldn't listen.
And then, when I told them
about the wild man-
Savage wild man.
Ha ha!
Tarzan is not a savage wild man.
You see, he was raised
from infancy by gorillas.
Of course. Yes.
One of your father's
science projects.
Perhaps you could put it
back in its cage now.
Cage? He's got a cage?
No, no, no.
You don't understand.
Tarzan's not a science project.
He's my husband.
You see, Professor, when you
didn't return to England...
with Jane as scheduled...
we were sure
that something-Uhh!
Something terrible
must have happened...
to keep you here.
Yes,
and then we heard the rumors.
Rumors? Oh, my.
We never meant to cause
so much worry.
Well, as you can see,
we couldn't be better.
Tea?
What an unusual flavor.
- Do I taste a hint of-
- Dirt?
Well, maybe just a hint.
Sorry.
It's the best we can do with
dried figs and banana leaves.
Oh, you've done
a splendid job...
considering
the, uh, you know...
circumstances.
You have quite
a quaintly-crafted home here.
Yes, it does have
its own charm, doesn't it?
In fact, it was originally
built by Tarzan's parents.
Really? Tarzan, do tell us
more about your family.
I- I never knew them.
- Poor dear.
- That's very sad.
They were killed
by Sabor, the leopard...
- Oh!
- In this room.
Right there.
Oh, Tarzan!
If it's not too much trouble...
do you think you could
gather some fruit, dear?
I'll be right back.
JANE.. Oh, no. No hurry.
Really, take your time.
So, how's it going
with the troublemakers?
They aren't troublemakers.
They're Jane's friends.
Eh, same thing.
Personally, I don't trust
anyone who wears clothes.
What are they hidin', anyway?
I like Jane's friends.
They smell nice.
Yeah, well,
they can smell all they want.
I'm just saying,
keep your guard up, Tarzan.
Pretty soon, Jane will want you
to act all civilized...
and then it's
"Good-bye, vines. Hello, pants. "
Jane doesn't want to..
- Aah!
- Nuru and Sheeta!
Hah! Guess we showed them.
ELEANOR..
Ha ha! Oh, dear, Jane.
Tarzan's not at all
the type of man...
we expected you
to settle down with.
Not that
we don't see why you did.
Quite. He's rather
robustly proportioned.
Yes. I'm very happy...
living here
in the jungle with Tarzan.
Happy? In the jungle?
Ha ha ha ha!
My, you certainly have changed.
Changed? In what way?
Well, what Eleanor
is saying is...
the Jane Porter we went
to finishing school with...
was a proper lady,
and now, well...
though it is quite lovely...
you do live in
what is essentially..
A tree. You live in a tree.
But I'm still that proper lady.
I'm still
the same Jane Porter...
that you went to
finishing school with.
I mean, with whom
you went to finishing school.
Yes.
In fact, you'll be
very impressed to find...
that I've already organized
a picnic for tomorrow.
Oh! I do love picnics.
So put on
your Sunday best, ladies.
You'll see
that here in the jungle...
we can be quite civilized.
I got fruit! Mmm.
Oh, Tarzan, this is gonna be
absolutely splendid.
We'll have lunch
and recite sonnets...
and play badminton...
just like those lovely picnics
I hosted in England.
Anyone who was anyone
in English society...
always looked forward
to a Porter picnic.
Be a dear and wear
your father's suit, would you?
Hello, pants.
Good-bye, vines.
Why?
In the civilized world,
men don't wear loincloths.
It's just not done.
I won't wear the suit.
Why not?
You're embarrassed by me.
It's not like that at all.
I won't pretend
to be something I'm not.
Tarzan! Oh.
Gorgeous day
for a picnic, isn't it?
We aren't going much further,
are we, Jane, dear?
I'm afraid..
I hate to be a bother, but..
Our feet are killing us!
It won't be long now.
Aah! What was that?
Jane, I'm sorry to be
a nervous Nellie...
but I thought
I heard something!
Oh, now, now.
Don't be frightened.
Just look around you!
I sort of find it...
rather like an English
garden with..
An English garden
with a 15-foot python.
So, where is your big, strong,
protective Tarzan, anyway?
He was unable to attend.
But perhaps you'll enjoy this.
Oh! My word.
It's incredible.
S- s-spectacular.
Ladies, welcome to my paradise.
If I could
just get up this tree...
Oh, dear.
- Professor?
- Yes, yes.
I'm just on my way up
to see you.. Whoa! Oof!
Ooh! No, no, no!
I can manage. Heh.
Whoa!
Ha! Oh, dear!
Ha ha ha!
What was it that you
wanted to see me about?
You came to see me.
Oh, right, right, right.
I heard about
your little spat with Jane.
She's embarrassed by me.
You know Jane was raised
in a society...
that sometimes values
what others think of you...
more than what
you think of yourself.
That doesn't make any sense.
No, no, no, no.
Much of society doesn't.
If I may, Tarzan...
Jane lives in
your jungle world every day.
Would it be
so terrible to live...
in her civilized world
for just one?
No. It wouldn't.
Thank you, Professor.
That's my boy.
Ha ha ha ha!
Eh... you'll, uh... Tarzan?
Yes, I should
like to get down now...
if you don't... Hello? Hello!
Oh, Jane, this is all so...
Delightful, Jane.
Perhaps the jungle
isn't so savage after all.
We can be quite civilized
when we want to be.
N- now, listen to me, you cat..
you don't even consider
making us your dinner...
because, you see,
I mean, look at us.
We're thin.
We're nearly skin and bones...
and I have it
on good authority...
that the English
taste quite gamy.
Indeed!
- Oh, yes! Quite gamy!
- And gristly!
Run!
Up, up, up! Hurry!
Oh! They're coming!
- We're done for!
- Out of my way!
What was that?
Aah! Ohh!
Oh, my.
That was refreshing, wasn't it?
Yes. Well... ahem.
Jane, I don't suppose
you know where we are?
Lost! Hopelessly lost
in a savage jungle!
Well, that's a bit of
an exaggeration-a bit.
It's getting dark.
What do we do?
Now, girls, I've picked up
a thing or two from Tarzan...
and if there's anyone
who eats, breathes...
and sleeps the jungle,
it's Tarzan.
TERK..
Introducing Mr. Fancypants!
Oh, you look good, Tarzan.
Very civilized.
Jane's gonna be so proud.
TERK.. Aw, darn,
would you look at that?
We missed the whole picnic.
Too bad.
Well, if somebody
didn't stop for termites...
Like they would serve
anything decent at this picnic.
Hey, fancypants, party's over.
Come on.
Let's go chase the flamingos.
Nuru and Sheeta were here.
The panthers? Oh, no!
Jane was always so nice...
and her friends
smelled so pretty.
Oh, why, cruel fate!
Why?
Will this interfere with
my flamingo chasing plan?
Jane and her friends
are still alive...
and we're going to find them.
If we can just make it
to the baboon stream...
we should be able to get home,
right, girls?
Jane, dear, please.
We're trying our best
to follow you...
but I'm afraid that, well-
We're getting blisters!
It's true.
Oh, do forgive
my thoughtlessness.
Here. I know what will help.
Oh, my shoes!
You'll be able
to go much faster...
if we just make
a few minor adjustments...
to the wardrobe.
Oh, good heavens!
No! Oh! Ooh!
But, Jane, they're Italian!
They're patent leather!
- They're...
- Shoes.
Now, step lively, girls.
What if someone sees us?
The only thing
we have to worry about...
is them seeing us.
How do we get around them?
It's dark. Now I'm scared.
Hello! We're with Tarzan.
Panthers run
at the mere sight of him.
That was yesterday.
Today, he's wearing pants.
Huh. You got a point.
This way!
It's just a little algae.
It'll wash right off.
Here.
We'll use these to breathe.
Jane...
I'm not sure I understand.
You expect us to go under this...
Filth?
It's the only way
the panthers...
will completely
lose our scent.
Ahh! I think we've lost them.
Aah! Leech! Get it off!
Ooh! Hurry!
I'm growing faint! Aah!
Accursed leech-
it's sucking
my precious lifeblood!
It's draining my marrow!
It's-
A leaf.
So much for keeping it quiet.
Terribly sorry.
Don't be, Greenly.
Jane, what sort of outing
is this, anyway?
First you strip us
to our unmentionables...
and then you shove us
into the muck.
What will you have us do next?
Grunt like gorillas
and swing from the trees?
If it keeps us alive.
In case you haven't noticed,
this is the jungle.
It's not a garden party...
and I never should have
pretended it was!
But right now,
our survival depends...
upon you doing what I say
without argument!
Are we understood?
That's more like it.
Aah!
So, would it help
if we grunted like gorillas?
Oh, Tarzan! Thank heaven!
Oh, my! I never realized
Tarzan was so... so...
Brave.
Mmm! And muscular.
Whoo!
You say something, Eleanor?
Aah!
No, I didn't say-Oh, Jane!
Uhh!
Tarzan, no!
- Ow!
- Yee-ouch!
Jane, no!
Use this vine. Go!
JANE.. Uhh!
Heh.
Jane!
Oh!
Unh!
Go, Jane! You can do it!
You're almost there!
She's so lucky.
Oh, Jane, thank you
for a truly memorable visit.
You lead a remarkable life.
I envy you, Jane.
You have everything-
and I do mean everything.
He doesn't have a brother,
does he?
Or a cousin? I'm not choosy.
We're going to miss you so much.
Oh, come, now.
Show some decorum.
- Bye-bye.
- Bye, Jane.
Good-bye, Tarzan.
We'll miss you.
Bye-bye.
I'll miss you.
I hope I see you soon.
Jane...
do you miss London?
Oh, well,
every now and again...
but my friends were right.
I have changed, and I like it.
So, Mr. Fancypants...
you think you'd be up
for another round...
of treetop tag? You're it.
Whee! Ha ha!
Hello? Tarzan?
Anybody?
I'm getting rather hungry,
you know.
And so, Tarzan, Jane...
and their valiant
elephant friend...
lived happily ever after.
Didn't they, Terk?
Terk? Oh! Oh!
Sorry, Terk.
You should've said something.
I did.
You must not have heard me...
through the two tons of butt!
Anyway, Jane, maybe
a party ain't the best idea.
Yes. Perhaps Tarzan
would be a bit uncomfortable.
Maybe we'll just have
a simple exchange...
of gifts instead.
Ooh!
Well, what sort of gifts
do men give women...
in the civilized world?
There are many possibilities.
Perhaps a box of candy...
or maybe a dozen
long-stemmed roses...
or, ooh, some rare gem.
Yes. Like a...
Like a diamond?
Yes, Terk.
Sometimes it's a diamond.
And do you remember
the last time...
Tarzan tried
to get you a diamond?
I do remember that.
That is definitely
ringing a bell or two.
I wasn't asking you.
I was asking her.
Right. Sorry.
I'll be good. Right.
Yes, I remember, Terk-
like it was yesterday.
Watch yourself.
These are dangerous lands.
Control yourself, Merkus.
We don't want to give the locals
the wrong impression.
Don't worry. I'll set 'em
right quick enough.
Oh, save it for
the jungle beasts, would you?
We have business here.
And why exactly
do you want to hire a guide?
Forget the guide.
I can handle this place.
You'll have to forgive Merkus.
He's full of
scientific curiosity.
Sit.
We are volcanologists...
who have come
to study the volcano...
on the far side
of your jungle.
Mm-hmm.
There is only one man
with the skills to help you.
R eally?
And who would that be?
Ahem.
His name is Tarzan.
He knows the jungle better
than the animals themselves...
but he won't be easy
to convince.
I'll just let this
do the talking for me.
I'm afraid Tarzan
doesn't speak that language.
Nonsense.
What kind of a man
has no interest in money?
MAN.. Stop that!
Unhand me! Uhh!
You can't treat me like this.
If you ever hunt an animal
in this jungle again...
I will do far worse.
My word.
Who is that savage?
That would be your guide.
Mr. Tarzan!
Mr. Tarzan, wait.
Allow me to introduce myself.
I am Johannes Niels...
and this is
my associate Merkus.
Yes. Well...
we've come to study
the volcano...
on the other side
of your jungle...
and we need a guide
to take us there.
You're not here
to study anything.
Wait!
You found us out.
The truth is,
we're going to the volcano...
to look for... diamonds.
What are... diamonds?
Why, my dear fellow...
you must get out
of the jungle more often.
Diamonds are precious stones
of great value.
Why?
Ooh. Well...
women around the world prize
them more than anything else.
What's that man doing?
It's traditional for a groom...
to give his bride
a diamond ring.
Is this done in England?
NIELS.. Oh, but of course...
the bigger, the better.
Two months of your salary
won't buy much.
Uh... so, Tarzan...
will you be our guide?
I'll think about it.
Oh, I don't trust that one.
We don't need
to trust him, Merkus.
We just need to use him.
JANE.. Why so quiet, hmm?
You're dining with
the most fascinating woman...
in the jungle.
The only one, admittedly,
but still...
I was thinking about...
That is,
I was wondering whether...
Yes?
What are weddings like
back in England?
Oh, well, beautiful,
of course.
The bride's
in white with lace...
and a train so long...
it takes four flower girls
just to carry it.
And the men
wear morning suits...
and there's
music and dancing...
and beautiful flowers
and wonderful food...
and a gorgeous cake
and...
And men give their brides rings?
Diamond rings!
You should've seen the rock
my cousin Gwendolyn got...
big as a strawberry.
Of course, her husband
is landed gentry, but...
Well, then again,
one English wedding...
is really just like
another-not like ours.
Who else can say she had
a gorilla for a maid of honor?
What's all this about, anyway?
Nothing.
I was just wondering.
Tarzan! Good morning.
Jane, uh, good morning.
I'm going... out.
Right. So it appears.
But I'll be back later.
Soon.
Tonight or tomorrow or...
Or soon.
All right,
I'll take you to the volcano.
Excellent.
On one condition.
Here it comes.
I want a diamond for Jane.
Oh. You drive a hard bargain.
Well, all right.
One diamond, it is.
You sure you want to do this?
Ohh. Anything for romance.
Astounding.
He's actually able to
communicate with that beast.
They're probably planning to
cheat us out of the diamonds.
I see right through that savage.
You're exceptionally paranoid,
Merkus.
Still, you'd best keep
a close watch on him.
Make way. Coming through.
Wide load.
One side,
my little jungle friends.
I'm... Whoa!
Does he know them crates
is full of explosives?
If it explodes,
at least we'll get the ivory.
Oh, my, my, my, my.
Fascinating.
Reflexive closure
followed by release.
Oh. Ha ha!
Daddy, why do you think Tarzan
would hide something from me?
Slight tingling, no pain...
Oh! Oh!
Now, that smarts. Ho ho!
When he went out this morning,
he acted very shifty...
as if he were hiding something,
and he isn't back yet.
Tarzan, you say?
He was on his way
to the trading post.
Right, right, right.
Fun's over. Let go.
The trading post?
I think I'd best
get to the bottom of this.
Yes, yes.
Right behind you, Jane.
TARZAN..
Watch your step, Tantor.
Aah!
Crocodile?!
- Aah!
- Easy now.
- Nice crocodiles.
- Aah!
Right! Up the tree!
Aah!
Whew. We're safe.
As long as the tree holds out.
Ah, Jane.
How lovely to see you.
Uhh! Ahh.
Just need a breath or so.
One moment.
To what do I owe the honor?
Do you know where Tarzan went?
Ohh! Always Tarzan.
Perhaps sometime
you'll come by just to see me?
Perhaps.
Now, about Tarzan...
He's guiding two men to
the volcano across the jungle.
What? Whatever for?
None of my business...
but they were
rather unsavory characters.
Goodness.
Did you warn Tarzan?
No. I don't make it a practice
to offend paying customers.
You know, if something
were to happen to Tarzan...
I would hope this is a shoulder
you could cry on.
Daddy, we must get
to Tarzan straightaway.
Raah!
You can come down now.
Thank you.
Waah!
We're almost at the volcano.
Ha ha ha! At last.
NIELS.. I can practically
smell the diamonds already.
It's time, jungle man.
I'm turning on you
before you turn on us.
What are you doing?
Striking first.
I said keep an eye on him.
There's still
a lot of digging to do.
Unless you want to do all of it,
put that away.
But I...
If and when
we find the diamonds...
then you may do as you will
with Mr. Tarzan.
All right,
let me get this straight.
Tantor and Tarzan
are guiding some tough guys...
to the volcano
across the jungle...
but he didn't
tell you about it?
Precisely.
I understand not telling you...
but not telling me?
What are they thinking?
Almost ready.
What does that thing do?
You mean... they were...
and I... Ohh.
Ow!
It's going
to take more than that...
to get my diamonds. Uhh!
But why would Tarzan
be so secretive?
We've always been entirely
open with one another.
Hey, it's Tarzan, all right?
I'm sure he had a good reason.
Perhaps he couldn't tell you.
Whatever do you mean, Daddy?
Sworn to silence.
Maybe those chaps
have something on him.
Monsieur Dumont said
they'd never met Tarzan before.
Very well, then.
Why was he being so cagey?
Unless, of course, he was...
Oh, no, no, no.
Preposterous. Heh heh.
Or is it?
What, Daddy?
Tarzan is...
A spy?
It all fits. The implausible
background story.
I mean, raised by apes?
Really.
Hey, come on.
I was there.
I saw the apes, all right?
But on the outside chance...
who do you
think he's spying for?
Oh, please. There's nobody
to spy on in the jungle.
That's what makes it
so deviously clever.
Aah!
Ohh!
Mr. Niels...
might this be
what I think it is?
Yes. We must be close.
Keep digging.
At the risk of sounding
shamelessly cliche...
we are rich!
Sparkly rocks?
That's what
all the shouting's about?
Mm-hmm. Women wear
these rocks on their fingers.
And they call us uncivilized.
Ahh.
This way, Janey.
TANTOR.. Terk!
What are you doing here?
Jane and the professor...
think those guys with Tarzan
are bad news.
I tagged along to help out.
What kind of bad news?
Oh, real bad-
the worst,
the ultimate pinnacle...
Hey, are those termites?
Now, which one of these
will Jane like?
MERKUS..
I don't think so, mate.
You're not
stealing my diamonds.
I am not a thief.
Maybe, maybe not,
but better safe than sorry.
- No!
- Ohh!
- Tarzan!
- Or whoever you really are.
Unh! Uhh!
Stop him!
Not to worry.
I planned for this.
Ha ha ha!
I showed him, eh? Eh?
Showed him?
You blew the whole place up!
Now we'll never get
the rest of the diamonds.
Perhaps we should
discuss this elsewhere.
Like back on the boat?
Hmm. Sounds like thunder.
Sorry. I got to lay off
those fuzzy leaves.
That came from the volcano!
Uhh! Uhh!
We certainly won't be
getting out the way we came in.
And there's more bad news,
I'm afraid.
- The ground is on fire.
- Precisely.
This volcano is becoming
more active by the minute.
Oh! Oh! Ohh!
We must get to higher ground.
There's no way out.
Hmm. I wonder if...
Oh, no, no, no.
It's quite ridiculous.
What is it, Daddy?
Well, if the magma dome
is directly under us...
then perhaps the volcano's
hollow core is above.
Of course, it's unlikely
that the top of the cave...
is thin enough
to break through...
even if there were a way
to get up there. Oh.
Good show, Tarzan. Ha ha!
Please be careful.
What do you see?
The professor was right.
It stands to reason.
Hold on tight, Daddy.
Hurry!
Fascinating.
If only we could study
the magma properly.
- Perhaps some other time, Daddy.
- Point well taken.
MERKUS..
The trading post is this way.
I think.
That jungle man would
come in handy right about now.
I told you. I can handle it.
Oh!
Is this what
you call handling it?
Run!
We'll just
have to wait them out.
They'll get bored... eventually.
- Ohh!
- Daddy!
Oh, thank you, my boy.
Although, at this point,
I fear it's for naught.
Tarzan?
What on earth are you doing?
Grab hold of me. Hurry.
But we want to go up!
Don't worry. We will.
Is this possible?
Oh! Who cares?
As long as it's working.
Ha ha ha ha!
What now?
Aah!
- Aah!
Oh! Sizzling hot.
Far too broiling
for comfort.
Oh! Oh! Oh!
Ooh! Ah! Ah! Oh!
Ah! Ooh! Ah!
Aah! Invigorating!
Extraordinary! Ha ha!
NIELS.. There, you see?
Now we can get-
Up! Get up!
Tarzan! You're alive.
I hope you're not angry about
that mishap in the cavern.
The diamonds!
No, no, no! Go back!
You want to go back into that?
Please, let me explain.
This is all just
a big misunderstanding.
We're volcanologists.
You should've let me shoot him
while we had the chance!
You can explain that
to the authorities as well.
In the end,
justice was served...
jungle justice.
That's a very nice story...
but I don't
see what it has to do...
with our anniversary.
Well, Tarzan felt bad
when he thought...
he was supposed
to give you a diamond...
and that was just a regular day.
So, imagine how
he's going to feel...
When I step in with
an anniversary present...
and he has nothing for me.
He'll be crushed.
- Aah!
- Good heavens!
- Wow! Incoming!
- Hit the deck!
Uhh!
Daddy? Is that you?
Uhh.
What's left of me, Janey, dear.
What happened?
Well, I was conducting
a scientific experiment...
to determine if there is
a combustible reaction...
between sodium dichloronate...
and bicarbonate of nitrate.
I take it the answer is yes.
You bet your sweet boopie
it's yes!
Anyway,
what brings you all here?
Tarzan and I have been
married a year...
so we were just discussing
what I should do...
to mark the occasion.
Terk and Tantor
have already rejected...
my previous ideas.
Well, you know,
a party would make him feel bad.
And a gift would make him
feel even worse.
All right, then.
Maybe we could,
I don't know...
dance beneath the moonlight?
Ah, splendid idea, Janey.
You can do a nice waltz.
Or a tango.
Maybe even a fox trot.
# Rum bum, rum bum bum bum #
Uh, guys?
Tarzan and dancing?
You remember
the last time he danced?
Oh, yes.
That wasn't
a happy occasion at all.
Blast!
Aah!
Sorry, Nigel, old boy.
And now, Jane Porter,
I turn my attention to you.
Connect antenna.
Right-o. Next.
Insert germanium diode "A"...
into receiver base "B."
Germanium...
Germanium diode?
Absurd. What would I be
doing with one of those...
in the jungle?
But, I dare say...
I can jerry-rig
this waffle iron.
Oh, good heavens.
Forgot breakfast again.
What are you doing, Professor?
Oh, yes.
I'm building a radio, dear boy...
a two-way radio.
Against my better judgment
I ask...
what's a radio?
It's a device
that allows us to communicate...
with people very far away.
- Like people in England?
- I should hope so.
Love to see who's winning
the test matches in cricket.
Now, I just need
one more wire for the tuner.
It was here somewhere before.
I don't... Oh, dear.
I appear to be all out.
But this might do the trick.
Ow! I thought humans were big
on "Please" and "Thank you. "
Ha ha ha ha!
Ah, there, you see?
# Hem hem hum ha ha #
Oh, this is a favorite.
# Hem lum bum bum bum #
# Lem pum rum pum #
Oh, Daddy! Strauss!
How delightful.
# Da da da da dum #
# Dum dum, dum dum #
# Da da da da dum,
dum dum... #
Come, Tarzan, dance with me.
Ohh! Ha ha!
Hmm. Looks like
I'll need another hair.
Ha ha ha ha!
That was very nice, Tarzan...
but not quite a waltz.
What is that?
It's a three-step
ballroom dance in triple meter.
No. What is that?
Duck!
Big duck.
It's an aeroplane.
I think it's in trouble.
It's headed for the river.
Oh, dear.
Perhaps I can pick up
the pilot on my radio.
Are you all right?
Unhand me, sir.
I'm an officer
in Her Majesty's service.
I thought you might need help.
My good fellow...
I have yet to meet
the trouble I cannot handle.
Bobby? Bobby Canler.
I can't believe it's you!
Ha ha ha! Brainy Janey.
Surprised to see me?
Ha ha ha! Absolutely.
What'd I miss?
The beginnings of
a very juicy love triangle.
Oh, sweet.
This could get good.
What ever are you doing here?
Oh, you know,
on a mission for the queen.
But she was good enough
to give me a few days off...
so I thought I'd pop down
and look you up.
Oh, I'm so glad you did.
How ever did you find me?
My dear, your friend Hazel...
is the biggest gossip
on the British isles.
I think all of London
knows you're here.
I'm Tarzan, Jane's husband.
Oh, I'm sorry, Tarzan.
This is Robert Canler.
We practically grew up together.
Robert, this is Tarzan.
Ah, yes.
The chap who came to my rescue.
Sir,
you have deprived England...
of the finest woman
in the Empire.
- Congratulations.
- Thank you.
Now leave.
Tarzan!
Where are your manners?
I don't trust him.
When I look in his eyes...
it's like
Sabor is looking back.
Who the devil is Sabor?
Tarzan,
you're being ridiculous.
I've known Bobby
since I was five.
He's my oldest friend.
FATHER.. Help!
Fire.
Daddy!
Oh, it was just getting good.
Oh! Aah!
Help!
Jane!
Aah!
Shall we leave the flying to me?
Daddy! Are you in there?
Yes, yes, yes.
My latest attempt at radio...
has had some
rather incendiary results.
Sorry to steal your fire,
old boy...
but it was beginning
to look a bit nasty.
- Are you all right?
- I'm fine.
I'm afraid your radio...
will need just a bit
of retuning, Professor.
Yes, quite so.
Do I know you from somewhere?
No, no, no. Don't tell me.
You're my cardiologist
in Khartoum.
No.
- The allergist in Algeria?
- No.
The urologist in the Urals?
He was our next-door neighbor
in Knightsbrige, Daddy.
You remember Robert Canler.
Little Bobby Canler!
Why, of course.
All grown up now, I see, what?
Splendid to see you, dear boy.
Say, you wouldn't
by chance know...
who's winning the test matches
in cricket, would you?
England over Australia
by eight wickets.
Oh, bully.
Spot on. Good for them.
Bobby, I simply
don't know how to thank you.
Well, it was a long flight...
and a spot of tea
would do wonders.
Oh, absolutely.
Coming, Tarzan?
No. He's a bad man, Jane.
My, my.
Look who's jealous.
I'm not jealous.
I just don't trust him.
You don't trust Robert?
Very well.
You certainly trust me,
don't you?
Well... yes.
Then that should be enough.
Please join us when
you're in a more civilized mood.
I apologize for Tarzan.
He's not usually like that.
Oh, I suppose
he's feeling threatened.
Where is it?
As if there could be
anything between us.
You're practically
a brother to me.
Yes, yes.
Quite right, Jane.
Where is it?
Good heavens!
Robert, are you snooping?
Um, yes.
Caught me red-handed,
I'm afraid.
Jane, do you recall
a small music box...
I gave you
just before you left London?
I believe so.
Porcelain, wasn't it?
That's the one.
You don't happen
to still have it, do you?
Well, I might.
To tell you the truth,
I'm not quite sure.
It was my mother's, you see...
and, well,
there's someone back home...
I'd very much like
to give it to.
I'd best have a look, then,
shouldn't I?
Perfect.
Thank you so much, Jane.
Ha. Right.
Now all I need
is that bit of wire.
Perhaps a bit of
nice wiry elephant hair...
would do the trick.
Don't mind me. I just need
to borrow a strand or two.
Stop! I have
sensitive hair follicles.
Come, now.
In the name of science.
No, no, no, no, no!
Tantor! Come back!
The cricket match
is about to start.
Let's go over this
one more time.
You didn't go with them
because...
I don't like tea,
and I don't like Canler.
- And you're jealous.
- I am not.
Right.
Why would you be jealous?
I mean,
sure, Canler's dashing...
and cultured and well-groomed.
In other words,
everything you're not.
So why would you even
consider being jealous?
Maybe you're right.
I thought
there was something else...
but maybe I am just jealous.
Tarzan, Jane loves you.
And you should know by now...
that ain't ever going to
change... ever.
You're right, Terk.
Thanks.
Humans.
They make this relationship
stuff so complicated.
Ah. Here it is.
Excellent. Thank you, Jane.
Don't thank me yet.
We'd better make sure
it still works.
Oh, this takes me right back.
Robert, do you remember
the dance classes...
that we took as children?
Ah, yes.
And as I recall...
you had two left feet.
I'll have you know...
I've become quite
an accomplished dancer.
I'm sure you've picked up
a few steps from the gorillas.
Sir,
prepare to eat your words.
- Here it comes.
- Whoo!
Tarzan?
Ohh. Oh, dear.
Robert, I'm afraid
Tarzan has gotten...
a dreadfully wrong idea
about us.
Terribly sorry, Jane.
Perhaps I should just take
my music box and ship off.
Under the circumstances...
I do think
that that would be best.
I'm sorry that you came
all the way here only to...
Well, what's all this?
Robert, you're not
some kind of secret agent...
are you?
Actually, Jane,
it's more like a double agent.
Terribly sorry you stumbled
across my code machine.
Code machine?
A British code machine?
Quite. And the chaps
on the other side...
are willing
to pay handsomely for it.
Then why did you give it to me?
Ah. Heh.
British intelligence
was hot on my trail...
so as you were
leaving the country...
I slipped it to you
for safekeeping.
Of course, I never expected you
to stay in Africa.
You're betraying England!
How could you?
Is it too lowbrow
to say I did it for the money?
Perhaps.
Is it too highbrow to say...
"God save the Queen"?
Aah!
Oof!
She always was high-spirited.
Uhh!
Oh!
All right, Jane.
Time to stop being
a clumsy Clara...
and use what
Tarzan's taught you.
Uhh!
Ooh. So far, so good.
Aah!
Oh, dear. Whoa!
Ooh! Stop it! Stop!
Eee! Oh! Ow!
Well-played, Jane.
But I simply can't
have you running off...
and telling others
about me.
The Crown takes a rather
dim view of high treason.
Now, I promise you,
that was the last warning shot.
Ohh!
I say, old chap, good show.
Who are you?
Oh. Y-yes.
I suppose
proper introductions are due.
Captain Nigel Taylor of
Her Majesty's Royal Air Force...
counterintelligence division.
Your friend is already here.
- Friend?
- Robert Canler.
Sir, Robert Canler
is not my friend.
He's a rather
dastardly scoundrel.
Are you sure
you're not just jealous?
Jealous?!
Canler stole secret codes.
He betrayed our country.
He shot me out of the sky.
He betrayed your family?
You might say that.
My good fellow,
Robert Canler is a bad man...
a very bad man, indeed.
My apologies for
the Spartan accommodations.
I hope you're comfortable.
Fit to be tied, actually.
I'm sorry
it has to be this way, Jane.
I truly am.
Who-o-oa!
Blast!
Canler's eluded me again.
Tarzan, where are you going?
We can't possibly stop him now.
You can't. I can.
Unh!
My, how dramatic.
Oh, what a bothersome chap.
Tarzan!
Jane!
Ah, ah, ah. Not too close.
Your Tarzan's
a tenacious fellow.
You have no idea.
Blast it, man.
Fall off already.
Let Jane go!
Sorry, old bean.
That's not an option.
- Aah!
- Tarzan, no!
JANE..
Someone has to fly the plane!
Oh, preferably
someone who knows how.
I hope Daddy
got that radio working.
As I told you before...
I have yet to meet
the trouble I cannot handle.
Haah!
Um, Professor?
Yo, Professor, you here?
All right,
the coast is clear, Tantor.
Whew! The last thing I want...
is him plucking
one of my precious hairs.
Ho ho! Got it.
Ow! Ow!
My scalp! My scalp!
Oh. Actually,
it didn't hurt a bit.
Of course it didn't.
I'd never hurt
a friend like you, Tantor.
Perish the thought.
Ha ha!
Now we'll finally be able...
to listen
to those cricket finals.
JANE.. Help!
Daddy, can you hear me?
Janey? Whatever are you doing
at the cricket finals?
I'm aboard Robert's aeroplane.
Ha ha ha!
Which brings up
an interesting topic.
You don't happen to know
how to fly a plane, do you?
Well, I have read
a thing or two on the subject.
Now, let's see. Hmm.
I believe you push forward
on the yoke...
to tilt upwards.
JANE.. Aah!
Or is it pull back?
Pull back, pull back!
I believe you're right, Jane.
It is pull back.
- Sounds right to me.
- Suddenly you're an expert?
Now, landing is quite simple.
Just keep the nose up.
Right. Nose up. Right.
Aah! Ohh!
All right, all right!
You win.
JANE.. Gentlemen?
Brace yourselves.
It's going to be a bumpy ride.
I do believe we have a problem.
Oh, good show, Tarzan!
Simply marvelous!
Yes, indeed. Ha!
I hope you don't think me
ungrateful, Tarzan...
but I have
a code machine to deliver.
And don't try to follow me...
or I shall be forced
to cut this vine.
Jane, it was ever so good
seeing you again. Ta-ta.
I wish the feeling was mutual.
Tarzan!
Uhh!
Aah! Help!
- Help!
- Jane.
Aah!
Unh!
- Aah!
- No!
Oh! Well done, Robert.
Well done.
Thank you, Jane.
So, Tarzan,
no harm, no foul, right?
Land the plane... now!
ROBERT..
Just thought I'd ask.
That ought to hold even
a scoundrel like you, Canler.
Don't worry about me, Janey.
With the possible exception
of Tarzan...
there's no trouble
I can't handle.
Perhaps.
The courts may have
a different opinion.
Good-bye, Robert.
Not good-bye, Jane...
just "until the next time. "
Your instincts were right,
Tarzan.
Robert was up to no good.
Yes, but he did save you...
so maybe
there is some good in him.
All's well that ends well,
I guess.
Jane, do you recall
how hurt Tarzan was...
when he saw you
dancing with Bobby?
Yes.
Well, I'm afraid
asking him to dance...
may reopen those old wounds.
So now what am I left with?
I can't have a party.
I can't give a gift.
I can't even dance
with my own husband...
on our anniversary.
Jane...
anniversaries are very...
civilized notions...
and Tarzan
isn't a civilized man.
All right, then. So be it.
Happy anniversary, Jane Porter.
ALL.. Surprise!
- What is this?
- Our anniversary party.
Ha ha! Party?
It's our anniversary, Jane.
Tarzan, you're wearing
your father's suit.
Yes. I thought I should be
better dressed for a party.
Ah. You three knew all along.
Guilty as charged.
Ha ha ha.
Jane, there's more.
More?
What more could I possibly want?
How about this?
Oh, Tarzan, it's huge!
Did this come
from the diamond mine?
Ha ha. Yes.
I've been waiting...
for the right moment
to give it to you.
You understand my world better
than I ever thought.
Just as you understand mine.
CHORUS.. # Singin'
to the song of life #
WOMAN..
# Movin'to the heartbeat #
# Singin'to the sun and sky #
# I'm flyin'#
# Singin'to the song of life #
# Livin'every moment #
# Singin'
to the day and night #
# I'm tryin'#
# Hard to believe #
# It's not just a dream #
# Singing the song #
# Living the song of life #
# I hear the song
of the moon and stars #
# I hear the chil dren sing #
# It's a celebration #
# Of every heart #
# Of every living thing #
# Singin'
to the song of life #
# Movin'to the heartbeat #
# Singin'to the sun and sky #
# Oh oh oh #
# Singin'
to the song of life #
# I'm flying, yeah #
# Singin'
to the day and night #
# I'm tryin'#
# Hard to believe #
# It's not just a dream #
# Singing the song #
# Living the song of life #
# Livin'#
# The song of life #
# Oh, living #
# Oh, yeah #
# Livin'to the song of life #
# Singin'
to the song of life #
# Oh, yeah #
# There's a rhythm
of this world #
# In every nation #
# Ooh #
#A never-ending song #
# Of celebration #
# Celebration #
#A song
that dances on the wind #
# Sieving through the trees #
# It's opened up
my world and sky #
#And made them new for me #
# Listen to the song of life #
# Movin'to the heartbeat #
# Singin'
to the sun and sky #
# I'm flyin'#
# Singin'
to the song of life #
# Livin'every moment #
# Singin'
to the day and night #
# I'm tryin'#
# Hard to believe #
# It's not just a dream #
# Singing the song #
# Livin'the song of life #
# Oh, yeah #
# Ooh, yeah #
# Ohh #
# Sailin'
on the summer night #
# Flying high #
# High #
# Flying #
# Dancing to
the beating of our hearts #
# In paradise #
# Paradise #
# I hear the song
of the moon and stars #
# I hear
the chil dren sing #
# It's a celebration
of every heart #
# Of every living thing #
# Singin'to
the song of life #
# Movin'to the heartbeat #
# Singin'
to the sun and sky #
# I'm flyin'#
# Singin'
to the song of life #
# Livin'every moment #
# Singin'
to the day and night #
# I'm flying #
# Singin'
to the song of life #
# Movin'to the heartbeat #
# Singin'
to the sun and sky #
# I'm flyin'#
# Singin'
to the song of life #
# Livin'every moment #
# Singin'
to the day and night #
# I'm trying #
# Hard to believe #
# It's not just a dream #
# Singin'the song #
# Livin'the song of life #
# Life #
# I hear the song
of the moon and stars #
# I hear the chil dren sing #
# It's a celebration
of every heart #
# Of every living thing #
# Singin'
to the song of life #
# Movin'to the heartbeat #
# The heartbeat #
# Singin'
to the sun and sky #
# Oh, I'm flyin'#
# Singin'
to the song of life #
# Livin'every moment #
# Singin'
to the day and night #
# Ohhh #
# Singin'
to the song of life #
# Yeah #
# Singin'
to the sun and sky #
# Oh, oh, oh,
I'm flyin'#
# Singin'
to the song of life #
# Singin'to the sun and sky #
# Singin'
to the day and night #
# I'm tryin'#
# Hard to believe
it's not just a dream #
# Singin'the song #
# Livin'the song of life #
Someone needs to stop Clearway Law.
Public shouldn't leave reviews for lawyers.