Submitted here is the story of a little
boy, and a magical christmas wish,
that changed his life...
forever.
It began in 1985, in a
town just outside Boston.
It was christmas eve, and all the
children were in high spirits.
That special time of year, when
Boston children gather together
- and beat up the jewish kids.
- Hey greenbob! Get him!
But there was one child who
wasn't in such good spirits,
little John Bennett.
That one boy in every neighbourhood, who
just has a tough time making friends.
Hey guys, can I play?
- Get out of here bennet!
- Get lost bennet!
- Get out of here bennet.
- Yeah bennet, get lost.
John longed with all his heart, for that
one true friend that he could call his own
and he knew that if he ever found
that friend, he would ever let him go
well, as it does every year,
christams morning finally came
all of the children were opening
their gifts with holiday glee
and for little John bennet, christams
day brought a very special new arrival.
Wow.i guess santa payed attention to
how good you were this year huh...
aww, merry christams John.
"I love you."
He talks.
I'm gonna name you Teddy.
John became instantly attached to teddy,
there was something about that bear
that made him feel as if
he finally had a friend.
With whom he could share
his deepest secrets.
"I love you"
I love you too teddy
you know, I wish you
could really talk to me
because then we could be best
friends forever and ever
now if theres one thing
you can be sure of,
its that nothing is more
powerful than a young boys wish
except an apache helicopter...
an apache helicopter
has machine guns and missiles
it is an unbelievably impressive
complement of weaponry.
An absolute death machine.
Well, as it turned out, John had
picked a perfect night to make a wish.
Teddy...
Teddy?
Hug me.
You're my best friend John.
Did you... did you just talk...
don't look so surprised, your the
one who wished for it arent you?
Yeah... I did wish for it.
Well, here I am...
you mean... we get to be
best friends for real?
For... real.
Forever and ever?
Sounds good to me
John was just about the
happiest boy in the world.
And he couldn't wait to
tell everyone the good news
mom... dad... guess what,
my teddy bears alive
really... oh isnt
that exciting...
No mom, he's really alive.
Look.
Merry christmas everybody
Jesus H Fuck... Lets
all be best friends.
Oh my god.
Get away from that thing,
get over here right now.
But dad... Get over here!
- Listen to your father, come here.
- Helen, get my gun.
Dad, no!
Is it a hugging gun?
Helen, get my gun
and call the police
im sorry mr bennet, I didn't
mean to scare anybody
I just wanted john
and I to be friends
yeah dad, I made a wish last night that
teddy was alive, and my wish came true.
Oh god.
It's a miracle.
It's a christmas miracle.
You're just like the baby Jesus.
Well it wasnt long before the news of Johns
little miracle was sweeping the nation
out of a Boston suburb comes, what is
without doubt the most incredible story
a young boys stuffed animal, has magically
come to life for unknown reasons.
LOOK WHAT JESUS DID!
Before long, teddy had become a
huge celebrity in his own right.
Hello, Teddy.
You surprise me, for some reason I
thought you were going to be taller
I thought you were
going to be funnier.
But for all the fame, teddy never
forgot his very best friend, John
the thunder cant get us, right?
Nope. Were thunder buddys.
And the thunder knows it
were totally safe.
- Teddy.
- Yeah, John?
Do you promise that we'll
always be together?
I promise.
Thunder buddys for life
thunder buddys for life.
And that was a promise that
niether one of them forgot
So... where are John
and teddy today?
Well, let me put it this way
no matter how big a splash you
make in this world, weather your a
Corey Feldman, Frankie
Muniz, Justin Bieber...
or a talking teddy bear...
eventually nobody gives a shit.
TED
Look, all im saying is that
Boston women are, on the whole,
a paler uglier sort than women
from the elsewheres of life.
That's bullshit... what about Lori?
She's hot.
No Lori's from Pennsylvania
thats not a Boston girl
there not that bad...
see, the fact that you have to say there
not that bad, means that they are that bad
you ever hear a Boston girl have an orgasm?
Oh yah, oh yah, hardar hardar
oh god... that was so good. Now im gonna
stuff my fucking face with pepper flan
jesus this is weak, not
even getting me high
im gonna have a talk
with my weed guy
working for me...
I think it sucks, im gonna
have a talk with him
I don't know you want to go to
a drug dealer with complaints
ive known this guy a long time,
ive known him since 9-11
you remember?, I was like, aww
shit 9-11, I gotta get high
is it 9.30? - yeah...
shit, I gotta get to work
I don't know if I can drive.
It's ok. I'll drive you.
I feel fine.
- Fuck.
- Aww, shit.
Aww, Johnny I'm sorry man, that
car just came out of nowhere.
Aww, god is it bad?
- John, may I speak with you please?
- Shit.
Its alright, go go go.
I'll pull out of here
hi Thomas, how are yah.
Asshole!
Thats my bad, I was
sending a tweet.
John, its almost 10 o'clock
I know sir, im sorry
it wasnt my fault
what do you mean?
Well I..i guess I wasnt prepared
for a follow up question
John, all you got to
do is not fuck up
and you get my job when I
go to corporate next month
your the new branch manager
all you gotta do,
is not fuck up...
I realise now. Good,
glad to hear it.
Cos in a month... my life,
could be your life.
A cushy 38 thousand dollar
a year branch manager,
whos personal friends
with Tom Scarritt.
Not a bad life is it?
No.
Let me show you something I
don't like showing people,
'cos I don't want them
treating me differently.
Boom! Thats me and
scarritt wow...
god damn right wow
im gonna dock you for dinging the car
and for showing up late today alright
try and be a little more
responsable tomorrow
I will sir, I promise.
"Not gonna let you down goose"
what?
Top Gun... so... Tom Scarritt...
I know that get out of here ok
thank you sir
and heres your keys, rental agreement,
complimentary map of Boston
than you for choosing
liberty, drive safely
thanks - thanks so much.
Heard you got busted...
jesus Guy, you look like
shit man what happened?
I don't know, I got
fucking wasted last night
and my phone says I texted someone
at 3.15, asking them to beat me up
and then at 4.30 I texted the
same person saying thanks.
- And you don't remember it?
- No, same as last time.
It just seems kind
of gay doesn't it?
I don't know, maybe yeah.
Do you think your part of
some gay beat up underworld?
Like one of those gay beat
up clubs or something?
I don't now, I dig chicks man,
I don't remember any of it
I was so fucked up. I might
be gay I don't know.
Do you mind covering
for me for a bit?
I might go lay down in the John
hey buddys, wheres it hanging?
Hey Alex
what's up? You get in
the club last night?
Ahh, I didn't get in because
the bouncer was douche face
but I make friends in the line
well thats good I guess.
Hey guys, anybody know
a nice restaurant?
Like something where they give out
free bubblegum in the bathrooms.
For what?
Lori and I have been
dating 4 years tomorrow.
I wanna take her some
place really nice.
Aw, congratulations John.
You guys have been going out for 4 years?
My last relationship lasted 6 months.
Then she farted in her sleep.
I'm like, I'm out of here man.
And I was gone
before she woke up.
Wow your not very
tolerant huh...
Lori ever fart in front of you?
Yeah.
- Really?
- A million times.
You italian?
No.
Why?
Nevermind, take her to biniarta
John look, don't you think
after 4 years maybe
shes hoping for something
more than dinner?
Like what?
I don't know. But if it were
me, id be expecting a proposal
oh come on, no ones expecting
anybody to propose...
I mean marriage isnt... i mean... isnt love enough?
I submit love is enough
you can put the ring in her ass...
and let her fart it out?
So bad, but so good...
Hey by the way, don't let
me forget you and I got to
nail down a plan for the
ruins game tomorrow night.
Oh no I cant, I'm
taking Lori to dinner.
For what?
Well, weve been dating
4 years tomorrow.
Ohh... fuck me, nice.
Let me ask you something,
you don't think shes going to be
expecting something big, do you?
- What... like anal?
- No...
like a circular gold
thing on the finger.
Oh fuck that. Its been 4 years Johnny you
and me have been together for 27 years.
Wheres my ring?
Huh... wheres my
ring asshole...
wheres my ring motherfucker?
Put it on my
- fuzzy finger you fuck.
- Alright knock it off
I'm just sayin...
do you think she might be expecting
me to make that kind of a move?
No no no, I don't think
and not only that,
its the wrong time
its a terrible idea, you
got the economy, you
got the credit bubble,
the supreme court
look at Haiti
I guess I didn't
think about that.
Well, you know, it's a factor.
Who are you? -Flash Gordon,
quarterback, New York Jets.
This is the american
fantasy right here.
A professional NFL player is called
upon to save the world. -Yeah.
Tom Brady could do that...
Tom Brady could do that.
- Hey.
- Hey sweetie.
Hey, Lori.
Hi.
- What you got there?
- Turkey burgers
oh turkey burgers, are we having
homosexuals over for dinner?
- Tonight is it?
- Ha, no just you homos.
You kinda just re-worded
my joke, but haaaa.
- How was work?
- Oh it was fine
hows your dickhead boss?
Rex, is fine. He only hit
on me once today so,
its a good thing
hey Johnny how bout a beer huh?
Oh couple of chowbukowskis...
couple of brewstoievskis...
maybe a mibrewstowsky?
Perhaps a teddybrewski...
thats a good one
I think I too want a
martina navratilovaski
oh... no no no
that doesn't work.
Bullshit... that totally worked...
no, no
yeah it does, - it doesn't work
the name has to have a ski
at the end of it, and you
just put brewski at the end
of martina navratilova
I just thought we were
saying funny names.
No, no. It has to have ski at the end
of it, otherwise where's the challange?
If theres no ski at the
end of the root word,
then we'd just be
idiots saying nonsense.
- Hey.
- They found the missing hikers.
- They did?
- Yeah. -What happened?
They said
they got seperated, and
one of them had there
foot stuck under a
rock for like 5 days
you know, if your leg got trapped under
a rock, id chew it off to get you free
- you would?
- I sure would
is that cannibalism?
No, I think its only
cannibalism if you swallow.
Oh yeah, don't worry about
that, 'cos I don't swallow.
Really? 'Cos that's
not what I heard.
Well its not true ok,
im a classy broad
yeah I can see that
umm, listen, speaking of classy chow
bellas a really expensive restaurant
so we can go anywhere else tomorrow. I
really don't care as long as were together
are you kidding me?
No, 4 years we've been going out... im
taking you to the best place in town
I love you I love you too.
And your nasty
you wanna get nasty?
Nasty girl
I don't understand...35 years old and
your still scared of a little thunder
I am not
thunder buddys for life right Johnny.
Fucking right.
Alright come on lets
sing the thunder song
when you hear the sound of thunder
don't you get too scared.
Just grab your thunder buddy,
and say these magic words
fuck you thunder...
you can suck my dick,
you cant get me thunder,
cos your just gods fart
hey Lori... can you set
the alarm for 11 A.M?
I got a lot of stuff
to do tomorrow
hi Lori
morning
ok you ok there sweetheart?
You look a little flustered
im fine, I just didn't
have time for breakfast
and the garage was full ohh
and thats right, my boyfriend
cant sleep through a thunder
storm without his teddybear
I don't understand why you
keep putting up with him...
yeah, the guys 35 and hes working
for a rental car service...
you guys, its not about that.
I don't care about that
id love him if he was a janitor
he has a huge heart
and we laugh a lot
its just a bonus that hes like
the hottest guy in Boston
I don't know, I just wish
hed get his life together
our life... and he cant. And I swear
to god it is because of that bear
you should give him an
ultimatum, its you or the bear
no, I cant do that. That
would devistate him
besides, what... what
if he chose ted?
Well hello there, sorry
if im interupting any
girl talk about Channing
Tatum's index finger
but Lori, I need to
see you in my office
the thing is Rex, I have a lot
of work I need to get through
oh this is work I swear
ugh great.
Good luck, - thank you
hes such an asshole.
Out of control...
hes such a sleaze. 100 bucks says
hes showing her the diving photo
check this out
its me on the high
school diving team
we dove the shit out
of the pool that year
you promised me
this was about work
Lori... why don't you like me?
Im rich, im good looking,
my dad owns the company...
I have a boyfriend. I
have told you this.
Yeah, the guy with the bear
but im talking about a
mature relationship Lori
if we were together, our
babies would be spectacular
I mean, my top of the
pyramid caucasian genes
and your splash of... dark... beautiful...
smokey... baltic...
- Czech?
- Goodbye Rex
ok, that was perfect
would you like me to
wrap your leftovers?
No, I'm good, thank you.
Actually, could you wrap
just this up for me please?
I wanna scare the
shit out of somebody.
Sure.
What are you, like 5 years old?
Yeah
but I read at a 6
year old level, so...
sir... and madam
here is your desert,
and champagne.
Ohh, cristal.
It's a special night, we've
been dating for 4 years.
And hey, all those rich black
people cant be wrong, right?
Doesnt feel like
4 years does it?
No it doesn't
you know, you had no
business being out on that
dance floor.But im really
happy that you were.
This song is so great
oh yeah, Chris Brown
can do no wrong
wow you can really move
you like that huh?
Check this shit out
oh my god
are you ok?
Oh god, I am so sorry
im fine, im fine
Jesus im so sorry, I didn't
see you it was an accident.
- did you hurt your head?
- Yeah
my head hurts a lot
oh man, here, let
me get you some ice
sorry... sorry, does it hurt?
No it... its fine
ok, heres a test to see how
much you actually care about me
you remember the night after the club, we
went and had late night eggs and waffles
till about 5 A.M, we watched a movie
on the little tv in the diner
name that movie... "octopussy"
baby... gold star
and by the way, my
dancing was not that bad
it was pretty bad...
I have cool moves
yeah, and so do people
with parkinson's
thats not how I remember it
ok how do you remember it?
Alright... whatever you say
hey, heres to 4 more years huh
cheers, - you make me happy
I know we said no gifts, but...
We said no such thing...
but I got you something anyway, in
clear violation of the no gift rule
we had no such rule...
Lori, I wanted to give this
to you for a long time
John...
those are the ones you like right?
From the kiosk at the mall
yeah...
you know Lori, some day theres
gonna be a ring in there
but I want to wait till I get
you something really special
I just do have the
money right now
look, im only saying
this because I love you
your not going to have any sort of
career if you wasting time with ted.
Oh, geez. Here we go.
Baby, please ask ted to move out
so we can move on with our lives
Lori, look hes been my
best friend since I was 8
I was not a popular child,
you have to understand
I had no friends
before he came along
hes the only reason I ever
gained any fucking confidence
but your no longer
8, your 35 years old
and unless your too blind to notice,
hes not your only friend anymore.
Can we talk about this another time and
just enjoy our anniversary dinner?
Oh shit, hang on a second
my phone fell under
the seat somewhere
can you call it?
Yeah
is that a new ringtone?
Oh, yeah what is it,
cos it sounds negative
no, no, its from the notebook
this is gonna take some doing I think.
I'll just meet you upsatirs then...
yeah, ill be right there
ugh, Lori... your home early
what the hell is this?
The ladys and I were just
watching Jack and Jill
Adam Sandier plays a guy and his sister its...
its just aweful
its unwatchable, but they're
hookers so its fine
this place is a wreck,
who are these girls?
Oh where are my manners,
Lori this is Angelic,
heavenly, sharinne
and sovereign blanc
I love you girls. You know
somewhere out there, are four
terrible fathers I wish I could
thank for this great night
what is that?
What is what?
Theres a... a shit on my floor
in the corner, there is a shit
oh, yeah, we were playing truth or dare...
ad sharinne's pretty ballsy
theres a shit on my floor!
Well, or... or is the
floor on the shit...
who lives here? Im coming
to get whoever lives here
you owe me lobster money
haha, thats my buddy Johnny, not
the lobster, the guy running it
I found my phone,
whats going on?
Is that a shit?
God there are some
fucked up fish out there
oh look at that one.
Waspy white guy fish
I married the wrong woman, and
now I lead a life of regret
oh look at this guy, I went
to new york once, in 1981
and I just did not feel safe
ted, you gotta move out you...
what
its gotta happen what did I do?
My relationship is at a very
delicate stage, you know
Lori and I just need a
little space right now
plus, a hooker took a
shit in out apartment
oh god - what?
Oh this is so gross
don't tell me, I don't want
to hear about it. You get it?
Oh my god no I didn't get it!
Oh my god I got
some on my thumb
- no!
- Yes I did
you can never cook
with that hand again
oh my god this is the most disgusting
thing ever. -Get away from me
look, that was tough
night for all of us
ted, you mean everything
to me, and so does Lori
I mean im just trying to find a way
to keep both of you in my life
shes making you do it isnt she?
Yes, but that doesn't
mean we cant hang out.
Well hang out all
the time yeah but
what bout thunder
buddys for life Johnny
I know. I just don't know what
to do here I know it sucks
but otherwise im gonna lose her
and I do lover her ted
I know you do Johnny
ill help you get on your
feet out there, I promise
I know, and we'll hang
out all the time right?
All the time
all right fuck it, bring it in come
here, bring it in you bastard.
"I love you"
fuck..shit..sorry thats the...
the thing
im not gay - I know
and your not gay so were fine
we got to get you a job
I look stupid... no you
don't you look dapper
I don't. I look like
snuggles accountant
come on, its not that bad
John, I look like something you give a
kid when you tell them grandma died
look, I know it sucks ok but you gotta make
some money so you can pay for an apartment
I don't want to work
at a grocery store
yeah but you have no skills
I told you, I can
totally be a lawyer
You get the job, were
celebrating after ok?
ahaa, and if I don't get the job...
are we still going to smoke that pot?
Probably yes
ahaa yeah, good talk
coach alright buddy
go get em
and don't worry, ill do my very best
to get this job that I so crave
so you think you
got what it takes?
I tell you what I got... you
wifes pussy on my breath
nobodys ever talked to
me like that before
thats because eveyones mouth is
usually full of your wife's box
your hired.
Shit.
Well, I am a former celebrity
in a minimum wage job.
This is how the cast of different
strokes feels all day, every day.
Aweful, they must feel aweful...
the live ones must feel aweful.
Come on, it's not
that bad, okay?
I got a shitty job and I
assure you I am quite content.
Excuse me.
Im sorry to bother you but,
my son and I couldnt help
but admire your teddy bear
oh thank you - thanks
im Donny this is Robert
I have to say, ive been following
you ever since I was a young boy
and eh, I remember seeing
you on the carson show
you were just wondeful
oh yeah, that was a
weird interview.
Ed thought I was Alf. And he kept
muttering anti semitic comments.
Thought Alf was Jewish
for some reason
have you ever considered selling the bear?
What? Excuse me
I want it
hey... im not an IT
pal im a HE, alright
im sorry little guy, but
my bear isnt for sale,
see ive had him since
I was about your age
hes very very special to me
stand up straight when
your talking to me
why the fuck would he say that?
Sorry, you know you really shouldn't
swear in front of children
uh look, were very interested in the bear.
If you want to make
some sort of arrangement, heres
my address and phone number
you can call me anytime ok?
Will do
look, here it goes, in the really important
pocket for really important stuff
- ok? - Ok see you later
ok come on Robert. Take it easy
what the fuck...
can you imagine what that
little shit would do to me?
I can totally see him taking you
down to the basement and slowly
delimbing while singing some
creepy victorian nursery rhyme
"oh my little sixpence my pretty
little sixpence" Stop it.
" I love my sixpence"
Knock it off
stop it, fuck. Why you
got to take it to that
place..you took it to a...
that was real
now its a real thing. Aww
come on, take it easy
lets just find a better
place to get stoned
well I guess this is it huh?
Yeah, I guess so first
night on your own
yeah, first night in my
beatiful new apartment
well itll be great
when its furnished
yeah. And the guy said it aint hardly
had no murders in it, so thats good.
Okay, so...
- if you need anything.
- Yeah.
I know. Dont worry
Johnny, ill be fine
I know you will.
Alright.
Hey, there.
Hey.
Listen, umm.
I just want to say thank you.
I know what you did wasn't easy.
And I just want you to know
that I love you for it.
And... I think its a new
beginning for our relationship.
Anything for you.
This is all part of the new
grown up John Bennett, so
you better get used
to him really...
well... now I don't have to be
at work for another 20 minutes
well thats perfect, cos
im only going to need 1
you know what my favourite
thing about you is?
Even after 4 years, you
can still surprise me
and to step up and change
such a huge part of
your life just to make
your girlfriend happier
I don't know, I guess
most guys wouldnt do that
well most guys don't have
you to motivate them
I know im not a talking
teddybear, but...
at least you don't have to
make a magical wish to get me
how do you know?
Ohh... is that a Flash Gordon ray
gun, or are you just ahppy to see me?
There you go. Thank you very much, please
come again we have a lot more grocerys
hey uhh, hey Ellen - yeah?
Whos that over there?
Oh thats the new check out girl I
don't know her name. Seems cute
yeah. Very cute
you know what id like to do to her?
Something I call a dirty fozzy
ok... alright... so thats
where well draw the line
hey... how you holding up?
Oh im alright, im just getting
used to things thats all.
It's going to be alright.
I actually went through something
like this with my last boyfriend
- really?
- Yeah
we were together for 8 months
and I really loved him
and then he got deported back to Iran,
so I know what your going through
oh yeah. So I guess we both
lost our furry little guy
we sure did
hey ted. Hey Johnny what are you doing?
Wanna come over and catch a buzz?
Well I could probably
stop by after work
fuck that, I traded off yesterday
so I got the other shift
come on, im bored as crap over here.
Just swing by for a bit...
I cant just ditch work man
im trying to get my shit together and be
an adult here you know, for Lori's sake
Johnny, 5 minuites and ill
kick you out, I promise
just come over. I got
the cheers dvd boxset
and the guy down at the
store told me everybody
talks shit about each
other in the inteviews
youll kick me out in 5?
I will kick you out in 5
John, ill have to kick you out.
I have so much
teddybear paperwork to
get through it is sick
what do I tell Thomas?
Just tell him you
don't feel well
I got to cut out for a
bit, Lori tried to break
up a dog fight and guess
she got hurt pretty bad
oh my god
yeah thats the way she is. She sees
trouble and she tries to help out
and I guess one of these
dogs clamped its jaws on her
forearm, and wouldnt let go
untill a fireman showed up
and had to stick a
finger in its ass
oh jesus. Yeah shes
pretty shook up
up the dogs ass right...
yeah the dogs not
the firemans ass
I thought the fireman stuck
his finger up his own ass
I don't think a firefighter
would do that, I mean...
well go go, take care of it, let
me know how she is. Thank you. -Go
woody harrelson... smallest
dick ive ever seen on a man
see, thats why I watch these things.
Its like a
cool behind the scenes thing
that you wouldnt know
oh hey, listen, try this.
I told my weed guy to step
it up, and he gave me that
what is it?
Its called mind rape, its
actually pretty mellow
it doesn't sound very mellow
well he only had 3 other batches
uh, gorilla panic... uh,
there coming there coming
and something called
this is permanent
come on, spark it up
there you go, you got it
ahahaha, nice good huh?
Good job - yeah
take pride in that. You know,
this place looks great
aww thanks man, its all Ikea,
did the whole place for $47
nice... - yeah how
are the neighbours?
Ah, you know, theres an asian
family living next door,
but they don't have a gong or
nothing so its not too bad
thats lucky - yeah it is
- hows work?
- Sucks
you? You know, not bad actually
I met a girl, shes a cashier
no way, thats awesome - yeah
we should fucking double date, you
me and Lori and... whats her name?
White trash name, guess...
- mandy?
- No...
- marilyn?
- No... - brittany? - No...
- tiff any?
- No... - candice? - No...
don't fuck me on this,
I know this shit
do you see me fucking with you?
Alright speed round.im gonna
rattle off some names, and
when I hit it, fucking buzz
it ok?- I will tell you
you got me? Alright
brandy, heather, shanine, briana,
amber, sabrina, melody, dekota
ciara, bamby, crystal, samantha, autumn
ruby, taylor, tara, tammy, lauren,
shelly, shantelle, courtney, misty, jenny,
krista, mindy, nowel, shelby, trina,
casandra, nicky, kelsey, shauna,
joleen ilene, claudine,
savanha, casey, dolly kendra,
kyley, chloe, demelu
- fucking becky?
- No.
Was it any one of those
names with a lynn after it?
Yes.
Ohh, I got you motherfuker.
I got you.
- Okay, brandy-lynn, heather-lynn.
- Tammy-lynn.
Fuck!
What the hell.
Hey man, you think you can
open more than 1 register?
Theres like a 1,000 people here
theres supposed to be
3 open for gods sakes
stick your finger in
the loop of my tag
you had sexual intercourse ontop of the
produce that we sell to the public
I fucked her with a
parsnip last week...
and I sold the parsnip to a
family with 4 small children
that took guts
we need guts. Im promoting you
you got a lot of
problems don't you?
Alright karim
you suck karim
hello...
hey ted
oh, hey there fella
how are you?
Are you out here all alone?
Uhh, no, no im not
you know, your never alone
when your with christ, so...
no im not alone yeah
yeah me too
you know Robert and I could
give you a very good home
you know, im pretty happy where I am
I just got a shitty new apartment
I could offer you $6,000
in rail road bonds
well you know, since I just returned
from active duty in the civil war
that actually sounds
very appealing
oh wait, sorry that was 150 years
ago and I don't give a shit...
ok
teddy come on, were going to be
late for dinner with your friends
ok, ill be there in a
second baby as you can see,
my dance card is quite full
im going to have to decline
can I just get a hug?
Oh, no... - yeah
and it kills me to have to tell you no.
Because im a people pleaser
but, thank you for creeping up my
night and jesus be with you...-ok
in christ
who was that guy?
Oh, that was sinead o'connor,
she don't look so good no more
how great is this huh? The
4 of us out to dinner
how long have we been
saying we were gonna do...
Lori, how you doing? I havent
talked to you in forever
im good
the companys having there 20th
anniversary party next week, so...
thats something.
Lori's a senior vp at a
pretty huge P.R firm
its not that big of a deal
companys turning 20...so you can
bang it, but you cant get it drunk
right...
yeah she gets it she
enjoys my humour
yeah, I mean Rex is having a house
party, im surprised John didn't tell you
considering you two have seen each other
every single day since you moved out
well you know, its funny cos
whenever Johnny and I hang out
the first item on our agenda is...
whats going on with Lori?
So you know its funny that didn't come up.
It musta have slipped through the cracks
we do, we talk about
you all the time
you remember the other day? I was saying
how great Lori's hair always looks
oh my god it always looks so fucking
great I just want to brush it, you know
right Johnny... i say that
So, tammy-lynn. Why don't you tell
us a little bit about yourself
like where you from? Im always
fascinated to meet teds girlfriends
what do you mean girlfriends? Was there
like a lot of them or something?
No... thats not what she meant at all
right Lori?, Lori you didn't mean that
no, no, what I meant to say was
that teds very handsome, so im
always interested in meeting the
lady that can snatch him up
did you just call me a whore?
What?
You just worry about your own
snatch how bout that honey...
wow, hey... what
the hell happened?
We were having a friendly meal.
This was a nice evening
don't talk shit to me
I just asked you a question
you know, your a frickin
snob you think your
all cool cos you work at
some fancy shit place
whatever.-ok take it easy.
Nice Lori, real nice
me... its not my fault
she cant speak english
oh fuck you. Just cos your in
the business world and shit,
you think everyone should suck
your asshole or something?
Ok, alright. Tammy, come on
honey, lets get out of here. Well
go back to my place for a couple
of vodka and strawberry quicks
you know what bitch, I gave birth
once, I can kick your fucking ass
and you better not show your face
around quincy, you hear me? Ever
I didn't know you had
a baby, is it alive?
What a cunt... I hate
that word - what?
That word, its like an electric saw
slashing everything in its path
why would you say that?
You dint exactly
stand up for me...
im trying to walk a line here. I want
to be fair to you and to him, you know
well I think your being a
little more fair to him
oh, come on...
you know your boss called this
morning asking how my arm was
huh...-yeah because of the dog
fight that I tried to break up
if I had to guess, id say you made up
some bullshit excuse to get out of work
to go to teds. Now...
am I right?
I made you out to be a hero
you know what John, we asked ted to move
out, to give ourselves a chance without it
your not giving anything
a chance if your blowing
off work to get high
with your teddybear
your right. Ive been getting
stoned too much I know that
ive been bumming around with
ted too much, I know that too
you give me one more chance,
I promise I can fix it
John, I need a man. Not a
little boy with a teddybear
I know, done, man
right here in front of you, look at these pecks...
these are man pecks
look at the hair on my upper lip...
thats man hair
I just farted, that
was a man fart
fine...
fine John, but this is, I
swear to god your last chance
trust me, I love you
alright, I love you
I love you so much. You
wont be sorry I swear
did you really just fart?
Yeah... but I pushed it
that way with my hand
I wonder who its
going to hit first
"so if I told them once, I told them a
million times, these numbers do not add up"
who did this to us?
God damn it, I'm
here on business.
Alright, here we go.
Im really glad that you came.
Me too yeah?
Is it ok if I kick your boss's ass?
I mean that
wont effect your workplace
chemistry will it?
Please play nice for you I will
thank you - anything
there she is... i was
worried you weren't coming
hey there squirt, how you doing?
Wheres your bunny rabbit?
- He's a bear.
- Got it.
Oh my god, this house
is fucking huge...
I know, try not to get lost.
Come on in
wow, here are the ladies.
Look at you guys
you guys look amazing
little heavy on the eye
make up, but pretty good
you guys know Lori and Jim right?
...John
hi
listen, why don't John and I
go get a drink at the bar
uh... sure. Great,
well be right back
come on buddy
thats an old sweater huh
this is Wade Boggs
autographed bat
I just barely outbid phil
donoghue for that at auction
wow cool yeah... cool
these boxing gloves worn by
Joe Lewis in his first fight
this is art, get it?
These were John Lennon's glasses
there worth like a million dollars
thats me and Tom Scarritt
ohh... check this out
thats Lance Armstrong's nut
I had it freeze
dried and bronzed
every now and then, when my
lifes getting me down and
things are tough. I just come
up here, and I look at it
and it reminds me that...
things arent so bad
sometimes you feel like a nut
sometimes you don't
so, talk to me Johnny quest, how
are things with you and Lori
you know, things
are great actually
oh thats great that ...is...
great
Lori would hate me for saying this, but
she told me how you are at the office
and as one gentleman to
another, I justwant to say,
I really fucking hope you
get lou gehrig's disease
wow... i think we need to
clear the air here a little
I mean yeah, im kind of a
fun time boss and what not
but look man, I do that with
everybody at the office
im a cook
I have no designs on your girlfriend
we work together and thats it
I think you're a great guy.
And shes a very lucky girl
well thats good to hear yeah
excuse me hey ted
Johnny, were are you you
gotta get over here man.
Why whats going on?
Ok, so
im having a little impromptu thing
with some people at my apartment
and John... Sam
Jones is here what!
Sam jones... Flash fucking
Gordon ...is here
holy shit, what
you remember I said my buddys
cousin is friends with sam jones?
Well my buddys cousin is in town,
and who do you think is with him...
Sam Jones... sam jones is here and John,
his hair is parted down the middle.
Just like in the movie.
Yes! Get over here right now.
Fuck I cant, im with Lori
and im already on probation
I just... i cant
John, Flash Gordon was the most
important influence of our
informative years.he taught us
right from wrong, good from evil
and the word acting apparently has
an extremly broad definition.
Flash Gordon is the symbol of our friendship John.
Come share this with me
I'm coming.
Rex, I gotta go. I'll be back
in like 30 minutes tops ok
Lori can not find out. She
absolutely can not know I was gone
if you can cover for me, im
cool with all that other shit
I got your back on this she
wont know ive been there
alright, this is one man to another I
don't really know you, but im trusting
you as a man. This is serious.
Dude, one man to another,
I got you on this.
Thank you, I'll be back.
I'm going to have sex
with your girlfriend.
Oh Johnny thank
christ, you made it
dude, I got 10 minutes.
Where's Flash Gordon?
Ok get ready
hey sam, this is the guy
I was telling you about
how you doing? Good to meet you
I thank you for
saving everyone of us
your welcome ahh,
he acknowledged it
lets do some shits - with you?
Oh my god... oh my god yes.
Yes totally
lets go
thanks.
- There you go my friend.
- Thank you.
"Death to Ming"
you know, you guys seem pretty
cool you like to party?
Uhh... cocaine right?
Come on dudes, don't tell
me you never done it before
well uh, not recently no.-i thought
that was just for people in florida
you better follow me, come on
Johnny im frightened
We are gonna party like the 80's.
show us how Flash
its easy, we just gotta nail a
lot of girls named stephanie.
Oh, my god Johnny I got so much energy.
We better start doing stupid shit.
Look Johnny, if were ever
going to get serious about
opening a restaurant, we
gotta start planning it now.
- Italian...
- Italian yes
whats the specials on tuesdays?
Eggplant parm
chopped salad, half price. And
its a non restrictive place
wait, what do you mean?
Anybody can come.
- Of course.
- Jews are welcome.
Yeah, why wouldnt they be?
Exactly, thats what im saying
why would you even bring that up? You
don't bring that up, you let them in
so why mention it? No one will
why are we talking about it? Your talking
about it, im just saying let them in
yeah exactly, right, good, ok.
No mexicans though.
This is how everyone
sang in the 90's
trust me, I can do this.
Shut up
let him try man - alright, ok
son of a bitch
well you never should have
trusted me, im on drugs
hey Johnny. I just had a great idea lets
go get drunk at cars on the overpass
oh come on, I do not sound
that much like peter griffin.
You can do any 90's
song with just vowels.
You breaker my wall,
dis my home long time.
We're sorry. It was
an accident, okay?
I try to make duck dinner,
now plaster everywhere.
Chill out, okay? Look, can
we just talk about this?
What's your name? I'm John.
My name a Wan Ming.
Ming?
You blame each other for war,
this bullshit, this all bullshit.
"Death to Ming"
let him go
you crazy, you crazy man.
Come on james franco.
You pay for wall. Move sucker!
Hey.
Hey, guy.
Whats going on?
This is Gerrard, hes the
guy who beat me up.
- And ahh... we're in love.
- Huh?
Turns out im gay, or
whatever I don't know
I had no idea
hey Gerrard, lets go grab
another one of these
how we doing ace?
You coming down?
Yeah, I don't feel so good
oh give it a couple of hours,
youll be golden pony boy
you want a xanax?
Oh shit, oh my god - what?
I gotta go
Lori, I...
Lori
Lori, wait please
im sorry, I messed up.
- I need you out of the apartment tonight
can I just... Give
me the car keys
can I please just explain... No
I was...-i have givin up a
huge chunk of my life for you
I was gonna stop in for like 5
minutes, then Flash Gordon...
just give me the car keys
Lori Lori please, I
love you, come on
hey johnny, there you are
I had to get some air
that guy from your office is on the couch,
making out with that Van Wilder looking guy
you know what, fuck you, I
don't even want to talk to you
what... Do you know
what just happened?
Do you have any clue? My
fucking life just ended
oh come on, shell go home,
shell watch Bridget Jones
some asshole, shell have a
good cry.she'll be fine.
Youll talk to her
tomorrow come on upstairs
are you even listening to me? Do you
even give any thread of a shit?
Of course I do... Johnny, thunder
buddys for life, remember
jesus, Lori was right.i shoulda stopped
hanging out with you along time ago
im never going to have a
life with you around.
Im 35 years old and
im going nowhere.
All I do is smoke pot and watch
movies with a teddy fucking bear.
Because of that, I just
lost the love of my life
Johnny... i... im sorry
I gotta be on my own ted.
I cant see you anymore
John, wait, listen.
"I love you"
so, word through the grapevine
is that your newly solo
Rex, I have a lot of
work I need to get to
I have tickets to norah
jones at the hatshell
tonight, and I would love
it if you'd go with me
You're asking me out a week after
I broke up with somebody?
look, im going to cut
the shit here please
this is the first time you've been single
in all the years you've worked here
just... go out with me one time?
And if your miserable,
and you hate it. Then I
promise, I will never
hint at the subject again
please Rex, I don't
think its smart
im an asshole, I know that. It
worked for me in highschool.
And its been a reflex ever since
Lori, the worst that can happen is you
go on a fun casual date, with a guy
who just wants to prove that he can
be something more than a jerk.
Plus you are a huge catch, and its about
time someone treated you that way
fuck it, fine
sure beats crying myself
to sleep every night
and if that means getting you off
my back, well thats just a bonus
I'll pick you up at 8.
Hey Johnny, it's me.
Go away
Johnny open the door
please, I want to talk
jesus christ, what the fuck man
sorry, look Johnny, I
know your pissed alright
but just listen to
me for 5 seconds
I saw Lori leaving the
apartment with Rex
what?
Im serious John. I went over to talk to
her, maybe take some of the heat off you
and there he was, picking her up
they were going to the hatshell
your fucking unbelievable
you know that
I mean how stupid
do you think I am?
If you think that by making
shit up like that your going
to make me choose some kind
of loyalty to you over her
your out your fucking mind. John
its the truth im telling you
you know what, get out of here
you know what, your acting
like a cock you know that?
What? Im acting like a cock?
Yes, you are. So shut your meat
hole for a second and listen to me
huh?...meat hole, thats
not right is it... no
pudding hole... is that what
they say, no cant be that either
right.cos how can you have any
pudding, if you don't eat your meat
pink floyd thing... the
point is, your blaming
me, for something that
you did to yourself
Lori was right about you.
You cannot take any
responsibility for anything
that goes on in your life
oh and you can?
I don't have to, im
a fucking teddybear
you know something... i didn't tie
you up and drag you to that party
alright, I wanted you to come because
your supposedly my best friend
you cant stand there
and tell me you havent
always seen Lori as a
threat to our friendship
I mean it works out so much
better for you when were
getting fucked up on the
couch at 9A.M doesn't it?
Listen to yourself, what am I, emperor
ming here controlling your mind
That's your choice John.
And you know by blaming
me, you just make yourself
look like a pussy
you know, sometimes I think back to that
christmas morning, when I was 8 years old
I wish id just gotten
a teddy ruxpin
Say that one more time.
teddy... rux... fucking... pin
shit, ou fuck man
fucking stop
why you crying?
My dick is squished by the t.v
im so sorry Johnny so am I man
I love you I love you too
Listen.
you gotta let me help you make
things right with you and Lori
theres no putting things
right, she fucking hates me
look, john, we can get her back
you remember when you were 10? And you
hit that squirrel with your bb gun
and then when we seen it fall from the
tree we both started crying, you remember?
And we ran up to it, and
we tried to give it CPR
and it came back to life.
John, we could do that again
ted, we blew out its rib cage and crushed
its lungs trying to give it CPR.
It died.
Come on, were going
to the hatshell.
Thanks. We're gonna take a short
break, but well be back in a few.
Hey, play chopsticks
you jazzy slut.
Teddy!
How are you?
How you doing you
fuzzy little asshole?
Oh you know, I'm not a hot
half muslim chick whos
sold 37 million records,
but im hanging in there.
Half indian, but thanks
yeah whatever, thanks for 9-11.
hey listen, I
want you to meet a good
pal of mine alright
John Bennett... norah jones
hi - hey there... sweaty
you ready to bring
down the house?
Yes ma'am. Thank you for the
opportunity miss... ma'am... jones.
Thank you.
Jesus, you look fantastic
well, your probably not used
to seeing me fully clothed
I know right. Me and norah met in 2002
at a party at belinda carlisle's house
and we had awkward fuzzy
sex in the cloak room
actually you wernt so bad
for a guy with no penis
yeah. You know, ive written so many
angry letters to hasbro about that
thank you
so im going to give my chops a rest,
and bring a friend up to the stage
hes going to sing a song to a special lady
in the audience who he loves very much
please give a big
hand, to John Bennett
oh... my god
holy shit
I gotta fuck her again
umm high, my names John bennett
and this is for Lori
Collins, cos I love you
and this song always
reminds me of the most
important night of my life.
The night we met
umm, this is the theme song
from the movie octopussy
still better than Katy Perry
you suck, get off the stage
aww come on, give him a chance
your an asshole
oh jesus
someone call an ambulance
that was insane
did you see the way the guys body hit the ground?
It was like a rag doll
id rather just not talk about it
you want to go get a
drink after this?
I feel like I could use one
after seeing a guy almost die
uh nope, I think id rather
just have you take me home
one drink come on
no, not really feeling up to it
alright, I get it
and you know, I don't blame you
I mean thing about it, it was actually
unfair of him to embarrass you like that
just to be clear,
im not embarrassed
so John and I have our problems,
but at least he tried
you know what, I don't feel
like talking to you about this
where you going?
Taking a cab, im going home
finally
down here, not looking up
your towell, swear to god
not looking up your towell, not
looking at your funny business
ted, what are you doing here?
I need to talk to you
listen if your here to fight
Johns battles for him its not...
just let me talk first alright, and
then you can say whatever you want
look, John loves you very much
more than anything in the world
and hes falling to fucking
pieces without you
he knows he screwed up huge.
But you gotta believe me,
it wasnt all his fault alright. I told
him to bail on you that night at Rex's
and he said no, he was going
to stay there with you
and I twisted his arm Lori
so if you just give
him one more chance
I promise I will leave,
and ill never come back
alright... hell be all yours
ted, thats a really nice offer.
But I don't want you to do that
this is between John and me, and
I don't think it can be fixed
yeah because of me
look look Lori, you
want him to be a man
but as long as hes got his teddybear,
hes always going to be a boy
hes waiting down at Charlies right now, so
if you go down there and just talk to him
ill be gone when you get back
forever
and youll see. Hell never
be scared of thunder again
michelob ultra tuscan
orange grapefruit
my god, americas imploding
high ted fuck!
Lori... what... hey
what are you doing here?
You can thank ted
should I... should I sit?
Yeah... if you want - ok
so works good?
Everythings good there?
Yeah, works good
well I guess we cant make
small talk all day huh?
If its ok with you, I just
want to say what I want to say
look I could sit here and
tell you im sorry, and
it was a huge misunderstanding,
im ready to change
but I don't think you want
to hear any of that crap
im not going to try and get you to take me back.
I mean, why would you
ive been a really shitty boyfriend for
the last 4 years, I don't deserve you
Look, I know I didn't take our
relationship seriously. But Lori,
I do love you more
than life itself
and I want is... i just
want to end on good terms
I owe that to you.
Alright, I want you to be
happy, you deserve that.
And I just hope, you know,
that we can still be friends
Thank you for being so honest.
That was pretty much it.
Thanks for coming by.
Yeah.
As you can see, youve been a part
of our family for quite some time.
Welcome home.
Yeah it's kinda funny, I got a lot
of pictures of you guys at my house
Is he all mine daddy?
Yes he is my little
winner, yes he is
ted you've arrived at a lucky time,
its almost Robert's play hour
im guessing you guys
don't have a ps3
im guessing your more of a wooden
horse with a wig kinda family
yeah
eh yeah, no
yeah see theres a cart
ted, you belong to Robert now.
You do as he says
you think your just gonna
get away with a kidnapping?
Its a nice fucking
example your setting.
LANGUAGE!...sorry sorry
you know ted, when
I was a little boy
I saw you on television,
and I thought you were the
most amazing most wonderful
thing id ever seen, ever.
And I asked my dad if I could
have a magical teddybear too
and he said no
can you just email me the
rest of this story...
and I was so heartbroken
and I promised myself
that if I ever had a
son, I would never, ever,
ever, say no to him
ever
maybe no to a snickers bar every
once and a while wouldn't hurt
me and ted are going to
be best friends daddy
yes you are my little chipmunk
happy playtime
jesus fucking christ
I said that word one time
daddy punished me for it
thats a great story, I
felt like I was there
daddy gave me an ouch
now... i have to
give you an ouch
alright kid you win, what you want to do?
You want to play a game?
Its playtime right,
well play a game
yeah, ill play a game - good
uh, alright lets see, how about we
play a little game of hide and seek?
I love hide and seek, ill hide
now hang on there, your daddy likes you to
show good manners, right Tubby McFatfuck
ok, you hide first
great, fantastic. Now, you count to
100 and then you try to find me, ok?
Do I need to wash my hands
before I play this game?
No... thats a weird fucking
question, no just start counting
1...2...3... 4...5...6... 7...
ok, no peeking now, or
youll get kid cancer
8...9... 10...11... 12...13...
- Hey.
- Walking home alone, huh?
Yeah.
Do you need a lift?
Oh im ok, I mean if I get raped, then it
would be my fault for what im wearing
listen, John
theres something that I
need to say to you too
hey, -hey. John, I hope that...
listen I don't want
you to think that...
sorry
I want us to keep talking...
because I think that maybe...
look, whoever this is,
its not a good time
John, its me, can you hear me?
Ted?...listen I
gotta call you back
nono no, John don't
hang up im in trouble
what do you mean?
What kind of trouble?
They got me, that freaky guy
from the park and that kid
who I think is his son, but may
also be his lover, I don't know
wow wow wow, slow down.
Where are you?
Uh..im not sure. Its uh...
hello... hello John...
hello...
your not a very
polite guest are you?
- Shit! - Ted, hello... ted
whats the matter? Is he ok?
I don't know - well where is he?
I don't know, he just
said he was in trouble.
Can you call him back?
No it's blocked.
Wait a second.
Go, take colombus to hylton,
get on the express way.
Hello, 911. I need the
police right away.
This guy took my teddybear.
Hello?
Let me out of here,
you crazy bastards.
Oh... oh... i hear the
fat kid running, I
hear the fat kid running...
that is hilarious
come on, let me out of here
I am a citizen of the United Stated
of America, and I have rights
Robert, seatbelt
should be right here somewhere
Johnny
wow, wow, wow, stop stop
stop thats them, turn around
stay with them
hang on
back off Susan Boyle
oh my god, hes gonna
jump get closer
alright, easy... - come on ted
shit - yes
hey Johnny, total
T.J Hooker right?
Yes!, fucking A right!
Go, go, go.
Daddy
lets see how well you
know these streets
where is he?
Jesus
there he is, pullover
no... you cant have
my teddybear...
holy shit.
Sorry, somebody had to go
joan crawford on that kid.
Come on.
Ted?
Oh my god.
Ahh, shit.
- Jesus, stay here.
- No, no, no, John.
- Wait, John.
- Stay here.
You're mine, Ted.
Screw you pal, I belong
to John Bennett.
But I can give you love
and rocking horses, and dancing
I think we're very
far apart on this.
- Ted?
- Johnny.
Oh, my god.
Ted.
John.
Lori, get the stuffing.
Get it all.
Johnny...
your gonna be ok buddy, can you understand?
Your gonna be fine
jesus, I look like the
robot from Aliens
look at me buddy. I promise,
your going to be ok
I don't think so.
I'm a... I'm... I'm in trouble
I need... I need to
tell you something.
What is it?
Dont... don't ever
lose her again
shes the most important...
most important
part of your life
even... even more than me
shes your thunder buddy now.
She's...
I got it
baby, I don't know if
this is going to work
please, just try
come on buddy
im so sorry
you did everything you could
Ted.
- I'm alive Johnny,
- Oh my god.
Im alive your magic
always worked
your back, I cant...
yeah, I mean when you
sawed me up, you put
some of the stuffing in
the wrong places John
I'm a little fucked up, but will you
take care of me forever and ever?
Nah... im just kidding with
you, I thought it would
be funny if you thought
I was fucking retarded.
- You asshole.
- Come here you bastard.
Welcome back ted.
It was you.
You did it.
Son of a bitch. You
wished for my life back.
No... no no.
I wished for my life back.
I love you.
I love you too.
And I want you to know that
after last night, I don't want to lose
anyone that matters to me ever again
I'm not gonna wait any
longer for my life to start.
Lori
will you marry me?
All I ever wanted was
you John Bennett.
And so, John and Lori and
ted, lived happily ever after
having discovered at last, that all
they really needed was each other
John and Lori were married in Cambridge,
by a very special justice of the peace
by the power vested in me
by the New York Jets
and by the united peoples
of the planet Mongo
I now pronounce
you, man and wife
you may kiss the bride Johnny
thanks so much for coming
my daughter better be alive
you sick son of a bitch
I am so fake happy for her.
Ahh, you know sam, theres only
one way to end a perfect day.
What's that?
Flash jump.
Right.
1...2... 3.
Yeah.
And that's the story of how
one magical wish, forever
changed the lives of three
very special friends.
Ted and Tammy-Lynn continued there
torrid love affair for quite some time.
One afternoon, ted was caught
behind the deli counter,
eating potato salad off of
Tammy-Lynn's bare bottom.
He was instantly promoted
to store manager.
Sam Jones moved back to Hollywood, with
the goal of restarting his film career.
He currently resides in
burbank where he shares a
studio apartment with his
room mate brandon routh.
Remember brandon routh, from
that god aweful superman movie?
Jesus christ. Thanks for getting our
hopes up and taking a giant shit on us.
Rex was forced to give
up his pursuit of Lori.
Not long after, he
fell into a deep
depression and died of
lou gehrig's disease.
Donny was arrested by Boston police and
charged with kidnapping a plush toy.
The charge was dropped
when everyone realised
how completely
stupid that sounded.
Robert got a trainer, lost a
substantial amount of weight,
and went on to become taylor lautner.