Watch Movies, TV Series and Live Sports
Signup Here -> WWW.ADMITME.APP
SPLINTER:
You are extraordinary, my sons.
Unlike anything the
world has ever seen.
Bound for greatness.
Destined to protect the
people of New York.
A dark force is growing.
A criminal organization
known as the Foot Clan.
So named because they step over
the good people of this
city with no regard.
Their leader, The Shredder,
will come at you with ferocity.
His Foot Clan will outnumber you.
The people of New York
will look upon you
as their only hope.
Eyes focused.
Elbows locked.
- Stance low.
- (BLADES SWISHING)
And we begin.
Be one with the blades.
Lead their path.
I know you are eager
to answer their calls,
but your training is
not yet complete.
The world below must
remain your home.
As your father, you must trust me.
Patience.
You're not yet ready
to go above ground.
But I believe when that day comes
and you rise to the streets,
you are going to be responsible
for amazing things.
APRIL: Mr. Rivetti!
Mr. Rivetti. Mr. Rivetti, please.
You're the most persistent human
I've ever met in my life, I swear.
Look, I already told the
cops everything, all right?
But maybe there's a detail
you could've forgotten
to share with the police.
Sweetheart, you don't
forget something like that.
Ten guys storm in here,
broad daylight,
force us to the ground at gunpoint.
And these are restricted chemicals.
Benzyl cyanide and some
deaminating agents, too.
You don't just buy this stuff,
even on the black market.
Wait, you said deaminating agents,
those are used in genetic research.
Is there anybody else
that's trafficking these sort
of chemicals besides you?
There's one other high-security
facility along this waterfront.
But they don't move nearly
as much cargo as we do.
O'Neil! We're live in 30 minutes!
Come on!
Uh... No, no, no, I'll be right back.
Please don't go anywhere.
I'll be right back.
Come on, you're killing me.
- I'm working.
-  That's a paying job?
- Because we have an actual paying job.
- No.
Look, you don't think
that every crime reporter
in the city isn't trying to
work this Foot Clan story?
I know that, but there
is a new angle on this,
and I am this close to getting it.
I just need a couple of more...
(SIGHS)
Let's just stick to
what we're good at.
Let's stick to what we're
good at. We're good at it.
In five, four...
(UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING)
Hi, guys, this is April O'Neil
from Channel 6 News
and I am here in
beautiful New York City
on the first day of spring.
And you know what that means.
It is time to shed that
pesky winter weight.
And here with me today
is celebrity fitness
trainer Harley Pasternak.
- Hi, Harley.
- Good morning, April.
Twenty years I've studied
the animal kingdom.
There are fat pigs,
there are fat cows.
There are no fat birds.
All right, I want you to
visualize a sexy seagull.
So we're going to squat
down and flap your wings.
Right over there. Full extension.
Picture you're leaving the cold north
and you're flying. You're migrating.
Four years of journalism
school so that I can do that.
Four years of my life, Vern.
It's embarrassing.
Look, O'Neil, I get it,
you want to be a serious journalist.
I see you sniffing around the
newsroom for the big stories.
But it's also okay to just
give people something
a little lighter. A little...
Little froth.
- Froth?
- You know, how,
when you get a coffee,
it's just, like, coffee,
then they put a little froth on it.
It's kind of nice.
Vern, that's foam.
Yes, foam, froth, you get the point.
It's just... It's nice,
it tastes good, it's candy.
You ever heard the expression,
"Never take candy from a baby"?
It's because even babies love candy!
It's nice. And you're giving people
something they like
that's good and nice.
They look at you and they see,
"Wow, there's a nice... There's...
"...candy." The point is,
I think that
you should be rewarded,
not punishing yourself. Okay?
And I'm... I'm prepared
to reward you.
I say that we go to my buddy's
old restaurant downtown.
It's very vibey...
- We just ate on the way over here.
- No, I know we just... I'm not saying
for a full meal, we're just
getting appeteasers.
APRIL: I got to go finish that interview.
I'll see you at the office, Vern!
I will see you at the office!
(SCOFFS)
APRIL: I just wanted to
follow up, Mr. Rivetti.
Are you kidding me?
How did you get my number?
If I could just ask
one more question.
Listen, I already told you everything
I know about this crime, everything.
Okay, you wanna know anything else,
you go back down to the docks
and you see my guy Stan.
He'll tell you anything else
you need to know, okay?
And hey, do me a favor.
Lose my number, all right?
Good.
FOOT SOLDIER:
It's clear. Let's open it up.
Container's good.
Move on to the next one.
FOOT SOLDIER 2: Move it out!
Get those to the trucks now!
(METAL CLANGING)
(FAINTLY)
Move out, next point! Go, go, go.
(INDISTINCT YELLING)
(DIALS)
(LINE RINGS)
- Channel 6.
- Chris.
Chris, it's April. I'm at the docks.
We're in the middle of
the evening brief, O'Neil.
Whatever you got can
wait for tomorrow.
No, no, I need...
(THUNDER RUMBLING)
FOOT SOLDIER 3:
(FAINTLY) 2-3-2, clear!
FOOT SOLDIER: That one's loaded.
- Get it out of my way.
- FOOT SOLDIER 4: Copy that.
APRIL: (SIGHS) Damn it.
FOOT SOLDIER 2:
Unit two, area three, move!
(METAL CLANKS)
(GASPS)
(YELLS)
FOOT SOLDIER 3: I've got movement!
FOOT SOLDIER 2:
Keep your eyes over here!
Weapons free!
Hold position!
(GRUNTING)
(FOOT SOLDIERS YELLING)
Retreat! Retreat!
FOOT SOLDIER 2: Get out of here!
(PANTING)
(GASPS)
APRIL: Taylor. Taylor!
Hey. I'm Skyping with my mom.
You have no idea what
I just went through.
I am freaking out.
I saw a Foot Clan attack.
Are you okay?
I was riding my bike by the docks.
It was night, it's dark already
and there are Foot Clan
soldiers everywhere.
Then out of nowhere, there was
this guy fighting back against them.
And he... He left behind this symbol.
And I know that I've seen it before.
I can't remember where.
But there is someone fighting
back against the Foot Clan.
There is a vigilante in this city.
And no one knows, but I do.
I know. And now I have my story.
There is no more froth
and foam for me.
What?
Never mind.
THOMPSON: All right, we need
a lead for tonight. Who's got it?
"Major redevelopments proposed
- "for lower Manhattan."
- No.
I got something.
"NYPD task force taking credit
"for small decline in
Foot-related crime."
- I like that. Let's run with that.
- Yes, ma'am.
STAGE MANAGER: 7:00 AM broadcast,
we have three minutes to air.
Oh, O'Neil. I'll talk
to you in a minute.
I know that I'm actually overstepping
my boundaries by being here,
but I think that you're gonna
want to hear what I have to say.
I actually think that you're all gonna
Um, I witnessed
an attempted Foot Clan robbery
at the docks in Brooklyn last night.
Hold on, the scanner said
that gunshots were heard,
but there were no reports
of any Foot Clan activity.
That's because whatever they were
attempting to do was stopped.
What were you doing
in Brooklyn anyway?
Was there a trampoline convention?
I was in Brooklyn because
I was reporting,
not sitting behind
my desk, McNaughton.
Okay, kids!
Who stopped it?
Well, there was this guy.
I didn't see him clearly,
but he was swinging
these giant shipping containers
and knocking these guys
into the... Into the river.
There is a vigilante that is
fighting back against the Foot Clan.
There's a huge story here!
O'Neil, I think you found Superman.
That's cool.
(PEOPLE CHUCKLING)
The vigilante is real. I saw him.
O'Neil, I'm gonna assume
that you would not come
up here and tell us
this fantastic story without
some tangible proof.
I took this photo of one of
the shipping containers.
I actually think that it
may be his calling card.
(SCOFFS) This is nothing, O'Neil.
This is nothing!
That's exactly the point. Somebody
stopped a Foot robbery
and left no evidence.
There is nothing.
Oh, I get it.
You wanted me to put "nothing"
- on the nightly news.
- Of course not.
You know, I'm gonna pretend
we never had this conversation.
I'm erasing it from my mind.
And the rest of us,
we're gonna go back to work.
Let's hit it!
ANCHORMAN: Hello, everybody.
Welcome to the Channel
6 Morning News.
New developments in that ongoing
sanitation strike to tell you about.
But first, after reviewing the city's
soaring crime rates with
the police commissioner,
Councilman Dan Gregor took
to the steps of City Hall,
reaffirming the city's commitment
to fight against the
rising crime organization
calling themselves the Foot Clan.
He did so on the heels
of a renewed contract
with Eric Sacks and Sacks Industries.
Using the Sacks research
and securities technology,
this city greatly
improves its chances
of bringing the Foot Clan to justice!
(SHREDDER SPEAKING JAPANESE)
Begin!
(GRUNTING)
(GRUNTS)
(SHREDDER SPEAKING JAPANESE)
Your men are weak.
It's no surprise your missions fail.
We couldn't have
anticipated the vigilante
showing up at the docks,
Master Shredder.
(SPEAKING JAPANESE)
You have been trained
for such contingencies.
But we've never seen
an enemy like this.
Their size.
Their strength.
They're not human.
I don't believe in fairy tales.
It's what society wants to
reduce the Foot Clan to.
A myth.
But the Foot Clan
will rise again.
Capture the vigilantes
however you can.
Use innocent people as bait.
No one will stop us in our quest
to reclaim victory.
We will own this city.
ANNOUNCER: Ladies and gentlemen,
please join me in welcoming
the NYPD's top benefactor,
Eric Sacks.
- (APPLAUSE)
- (SACKS CHUCKLING)
SACKS: Please, please. Please.
Sit down, sit down.
I have to say,
it's wonderful to see so many
people out here tonight,
especially in a neighborhood so
hard hit by the Foot's crime wave.
Years ago, my life was
touched by tragedy.
I was a young scientist working
with a world-class team
on cutting-edge research.
And our laboratory was attacked,
set fire to, robbed,
by the cowards that call
themselves the Foot Clan.
Several of my employees
lost their lives that day.
And it is in their honor,
in their memory,
that Sacks industries,
whether through Sacks Biomed,
Sacks Robotics or Sacks Construction,
will remain committed
to keeping the city of
New York, our city,
- safe.
- (APPLAUSE)
So whenever someone
takes flame to this city,
I will be there to put the fire out.
And that's a promise.
Thank you. Thank you.
Thank you.
MAN:
Great work, sir. Very inspirational.
Mr. Sacks. April O'Neil.
You worked with my father.
Oh!
I can't believe it.
I haven't seen you since...
APRIL: Since his funeral.
It was a long time ago.
Yeah.
I just wanted to tell you that your
words really resonated with me,
and I hope to one day contribute
to the city in the way that you do.
Well, it looks like you're
doing a pretty good job.
Channel 6, very impressive, April.
Um... Thank you. It's, uh...
It isn't exactly everything
I anticipated it would be.
As long as you are true to yourself,
your father will always
be proud of you.
Mr. Sacks, we have
to be uptown at 7:00.
I'll see you on TV.
- (ENGINE REVVING)
- (CAR HORN HONKING)
APRIL: Eric Sacks was so inspiring.
I know this is a story
that actually matters.
The superhero one?
That's a good idea.
I should chase that down.
(PEOPLE SCREAMING)
Where's everybody going?
(SCREAMING CONTINUES)
- O'Neil! Where are you going?
- APRIL: Hey.
- VERN: April!
- Hey!
What are you running from?
Wait, wait!
DISPATCHER: Shots fired,
Broadway and Centre Street.
DONATELLO: Surveillance
uplinks are showing heavy,
heavy Foot Clan activity at
the Broad Street platform.
RAPHAEL:
They're taking hostages, dude.
LEONARDO: But you know we're not
supposed to go above ground.
RAPHAEL: We've done this before.
We started something,
we gotta finish it.
MICHELANGELO: This is insane.
That cat is playing
Chopsticks with chopsticks!
- LEONARDO: Don't be an idiot.
- (MONITOR BEEPING)
- MICHELANGELO: Aw.
- LEONARDO: Okay.
LEONARDO: Let's rock 'n' roll, boys!
(CLAMORING)
WOMAN 1: Run!
WOMAN 2: Get out!
FOOT SOLDIER 1: Go, go!
(PANTING)
(GUNSHOT)
FOOT SOLDIER 1: (FAINTLY)
If you want to live, do it! Go on!
(PANTING)
(YELPS)
FOOT SOLDIER 1: Just stay down!
FOOT SOLDIER 2: Get over here!
FOOT SOLDIER 3: Keep moving!
FOOT SOLDIER 1: Keep your
hands where I can see them!
FOOT SOLDIER 2: Move to the side.
(DEVICES ACTIVATING)
- MALE HOSTAGE: They're bombs.
- FOOT SOLDIER 1: Shut up!
On the ground!
Nobody move!
We know you're out there!
If you don't surrender,
we start executing hostages!
FOOT SOLDIER 2:
Get your head down! Don't move!
FOOT SOLDIER 2: Don't make
me tell you again! Not a word!
FOOT SOLDIER 2: Don't look at me!
WOMAN: (WHISPERING)
Don't! Don't do it!
(CAMERA PHONE CLICKS)
(COCKING)
KARAI: You!
Stand up!
RAPHAEL: All aboard!
(DISTANT SCREAMING)
(SPEAKING JAPANESE)
(TRAIN WHISTLING)
- (GRUNTING)
- KARAI: On your 12!
- Come on!
- (GUNSHOTS)
(KARAI YELPING)
(RAPHAEL CHUCKLES)
(GRUNTING)
(MICHELANGELO VOCALIZING)
(FOOT SOLDIER SCREAMS)
RAPHAEL: That's right.
MICHELANGELO: Like a shadow, bra.
LEONARDO: How you like that?
LEONARDO: Let's go! Let's move!
FEMALE HOSTAGE:
They went up that way!
Did you see that?
MALE HOSTAGE 2:
Here, here. They climbed up here!
- Right here.
- Some kind of freak!
MALE HOSTAGE 1:
There were a couple of them!
Whoo! Right past me!
They saved us.
(SIRENS WAILING)
SWAT OFFICER: Go, go, go!
SWAT TEAM LEADER:
Let's go, guys! Both sides!
MICHELANGELO: You see that?
I smoked that dude! S'up?
RAPHAEL: Yeah, boys, bring it in.
DONATELLO: That was amazing.
You were incredible!
LEONARDO: Great elbow, Donnie.
RAPHAEL: Oh, yeah!
That's what I'm talking about.
This is our city!
These are our streets!
MICHELANGELO: You mess with us,
you step into the Wu, whoo, Tang!
RAPHAEL: Ooh, yeah! Did you see that
guy's jaw connect with the concrete?
DONATELLO: He'll be drinking
out of a sippy cup for months!
RAPHAEL: Ah, that's what
I'm talking about, brothers.
Like shadows in the night.
Completely unseen.
(CAMERA CLICKING)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
MICHELANGELO: (WHISPERING)
What was that?
DONATELLO: (WHISPERING)
It's a camera flash.
LEONARDO:
We know it's a camera flash.
RAPHAEL:
Who's behind the camera flash?
DONATELLO:
By my calculations, it's a girl.
MICHELANGELO:
Now we got to kill her...
- DONATELLO: What?
- MICHELANGELO: With kindness!
Give her some flowers,
earn her trust.
- RAPHAEL: I got this.
- Raph, no, no, no! Come on!
(EXCLAIMING)
(GRUNTS)
(PANTING)
RAPHAEL: Give me the camera.
DONATELLO: Ooh, look,
he's doing his Batman voice.
MICHELANGELO: She's so hot,
I can feel my shell tightening.
- We can hear you!
- (WEAPON UNSHEATHING)
RAPHAEL: If you don't give
me the camera, I'm gonna...
LEONARDO: Enough!
Back off, Raph.
(SCOFFS)
RAPHAEL: I only saw Batman once!
LEONARDO: Ma'am, hello. I apologize.
My colleague here
forgot to say "please."
So,
would you please hand
over the camera?
- (GASPING)
- No, no, no, no. Whoa.
Whoa. Chill. It's just a mask.
See? Don't freak out.
Right?
Ah!
DONATELLO:
Oh, I think that went well.
(DISTORTED) Breathing steady.
Blood pressure stabilizing.
Why are we still here playing doctor?
She may have a head injury.
Uh, correction. She's a hot chick
who may have a head injury,
which makes it our civic duty to...
Ma'am, ma'am.
(SNAPPING LOUDLY)
Can you hear me?
Do you know what city you're in?
Do you know where you are?
Have you seen that video where the cat
plays Chopsticks with the chopsticks?
LEONARDO: Can we focus here?
DONATELLO: Guys, please!
Come on. Give her some air.
What are you?
Well, Miss,
uh, we're ninjas.
We're mutants.
Well, technically, we're turtles.
Oh, and we're teenagers!
But we can still have
adult conversations.
(BREATHLESS) Wait, wait, wait. So...
You're...
Ninja, mutant,
turtle, teenagers?
Well, when you put it like that,
it sounds ridiculous!
See, she's looking at
us like we're freaks.
I bet that's why you took
our picture, wasn't it?
To show your friends?
Bro, that's a good thing!
Maybe she has hot friends.
- Looking for this?
- Don't break it.
No, no, no. Please.
How many times do I have to tell you?
We don't break things, we fix them.
Donnie already wiped
the phone, genius.
Problem solved, moving on.
- And who put you in charge?
- You know who did.
Ooh, tension! It's been
like 30 whole minutes
since you guys had this argument.
Leonardo, if we want to make it home
before Master, we gotta hustle.
(WHISPERING) Leonardo?
Do not say a word
about this to anyone.
If you do, we will find you.
April O'Neil.
We're on the move, Raphael.
(RAPHAEL GRUNTING)
Raphael?
(GRUNTING)
MICHELANGELO: Yeah!
We'll find you, O'Neil.
I'm sorry, that came across
super creepy, okay? (CHUCKLING)
We will find you, though.
(TURTLES EXCLAIMING)
MICHELANGELO: I was on fire, bro!
Did you see me back there?
Guys, I totally talked to a girl!
ALL: Shut up, Mikey!
Yeah, bra!
(ALL WHOOPING)
(FARTING)
- (CHUCKLING)
- (ALL GROANING)
Mikey, was that you?
MICHELANGELO: (CHUCKLING)
Pepperoni.
APRIL: Leonardo. I know those names.
I know those names.
Raphael, Raphael. Leonardo.
(EXCLAIMS IN DISGUST)
(EXHALES)
YOUNG APRIL: (ON CAMERA)
Good evening.
This is April O'Neil,
reporting live from my daddy's lab.
I know it sounds pretty boring,
but actually, he does
some pretty cool stuff.
Time to put the camera away, April.
YOUNG APRIL: Aw, Dad!
And now I will show you
something amazing.
It's supposed to be
from a different planet
- in outer space!
- Here we go.
Ah!
YOUNG APRIL: Mr. Sacks,
what sort of experiments
are you doing here?
(STAMMERING) Oh, that's
a very complicated question.
- (CAMERA BEEPING)
- We're trying to change the world.
YOUNG APRIL: Look at the camera!
Hello, Splinter.
YOUNG APRIL: And these are
my little turtles, Leonardo,
Raphael,
Michelangelo and Donatello.
(SIGHING)
YOUNG APRIL:
The fans want to see you!
(CHIRPING)
(EXHALING) I knew it.
The vigilante, I saw him.
I saw them! I saw them.
I've known them since I was a
little girl. They were my pets.
They were my childhood pets,
and they were named after
Italian Renaissance painters.
Mom, I want to move back home.
- (ALL WHISPERING)
- Is he here?
I don't see him.
Donnie?
My thermal scans indicate
there's a 74% variable
that there's a 61 %
chance he's not...
MICHELANGELO:
That he's not here, guys.
- That he's not here.
- Okay.
Fall in, quietly.
(TURTLES GRUNTING SOFTLY)
(DEVICE BEEPING)
(MICHELANGELO GRUNTING LOUDLY)
RAPHAEL: Dude.
So, guys, if it wasn't already
obvious with that girl,
dibs.
(BOTH SHUSHING)
If Master Splinter catches us,
he'll send us back to the Ha'shi.
I ain't going back to the Ha'shi.
Every time we're in the Ha'shi,
it's because of you.
Well, bro, you won't
have to worry about me
dragging you down anymore.
What's that supposed to mean?
I'm going out on my own.
First chance I get.
How are we gonna finish our
hip-hop Christmas album, bro?
You're the hype man!
(SHUSHING)
- Shut up.
- (ALL SHUSHING)
Shut up.
I got glop in my eye.
Shh! He's not going anywhere.
We all stick together.
Sorry I spit in your eye, bro.
- Shh!
- Guys? Guys.
We got a bogey.
MICHELANGELO: Uh...
(TURTLE GROANING)
SPLINTER: Where have you been?
We weren't... (STRAINING)
I forgot to soak my retainer!
I'm totally sleepwalking!
Look, Mikey's sleeping and walking.
He's totally innocent. (GROANS)
Enough! You disobeyed a direct order.
Why did you go above ground?
What happened?
(PANTING)
- SPLINTER: Very well.
- (WHIMPERING)
If that's how it's going to be,
- to the Ha'shi!
- (TURTLES GROANING)
O'Neil! All right, what was so
important I had to get here?
- Okay. Are you ready?
- Yeah.
Okay. (CLEARS THROAT) You know how
- I saw the vigilante?
- Yeah.
But I had no photos or
evidence to show you,
so I just sounded crazy.
- Yes.
- Okay. But I saw him again.
Well, I didn't see him again,
I saw them, because there's four.
There's not just one, there's four.
And I was standing as close to
them as you are to me right now.
What'd they look like?
(EXHALES) I'll show you.
What?
Like this.
Like turtles?
Well, they don't look like turtles
because they are turtles.
They're over six feet tall
and they speak English.
(SIGHING)
Oh, my God.
I was awake all night, please look,
I was awake all night
googling all of the thwarted crimes
over the past three months,
and this symbol
appeared at every single one.
Look! Every single one of them.
This one, look. Here,
here, here, here, here.
And it's an ancient Japanese
symbol that means "family."
Wait, it's on my laptop.
I can't believe you
brought me in to do this!
(STAMMERING) It's here, it's here.
- (SIGHING)
- This is my father's lab.
This is the same lab
where these things were born
(STAMMERING) or created or mutated.
Or, I don't know the terminology,
but will you please just look at what
I'm showing you and listen to me.
It's all connected.
The turtles are the vigilantes
and the vigilantes are these turtles.
YOUNG APRIL ON VIDEO: Pizza has cheese,
tomato sauce, all your favorite stuff.
Eat it. You guys
need nutrition. Or not.
I just want to be clear.
You are now telling me that there are
four six-foot talking turtles
walking around New York City,
and no one has seen them but you?
That's what I'm telling you.
(CHUCKLING) I don't mean to laugh,
but is there anything else
we should know about them?
They're ninjas.
I'm sorry, what?
And they do karate.
- Okay, get out.
- (DOOR SLAMS SHUT)
(APRIL SNIFFLES)
VERN: O'Neil!
It could have been worse.
I just got fired, Vern.
How could it be worse?
Maybe it's good.
Maybe you should take a little time,
take care of yourself.
Come on, let me give you a ride.
Not unless you're going
to the Eric Sacks estate.
- April... Hey!
- I'm not giving up on this story.
You gotta put that to bed.
Would all of those
other great reporters
that you worked with,
would they have "put it to bed"?
No. That's different.
How is it different?
They all started exactly
where I am, right?
(SIGHS)
I'm not driving the Channel 6
news van onto the Sacks estate.
- Who asked you to do that?
- Uh, you did.
And a "thanks" would have been nice.
Maybe one day you're
gonna be thanking me.
So, what do you want with Eric Sacks?
My dad used to work for him.
He's the only person
that's gonna be able
to tell me whether or not I'm crazy.
Crazy about what?
- I don't need you to laugh at me also.
- Oh, come on, O'Neil.
This is the Fenwick Express,
it's a judgment-free zone.
A cocoon of safety.
Promise?
I'm insulted that you
would suggest otherwise.
(ENGINE STARTING)
Ooh, 11 hours in the Ha'shi.
Are you sure none of
you want to tell me
where you were last night?
How you holding up, fellas?
Ah! I ain't breaking if
Donnie ain't breaking.
(WHIMPERING)
Experiencing intense
nausea but not breaking.
(CONTINUES WHIMPERING)
Guys? I'm in the zone!
There is literally nothing
that could break me right now!
Starting to break.
Of course, you've all tasted
the five-cheese pizza.
But this,
cheesemongers have speculated
of its existence for centuries.
Da Vinci's original masterpiece.
I submit to you...
(SPEAKING ITALIAN)
the 99-cheese pizza.
Oh!
It's not possible.
Mikey, it's a trap!
A pizza with that variety of cheese
is a culinary impossibility!
- Shall I list the ingredients?
- No.
- Cheddar...
- (STRAINING)
- Provolone...
- Mikey, don't you do it!
SPLINTER: Asiago...
- DONATELLO: Keep it together!
- Taleggio...
(SOFTLY)
I don't even know what that is.
Mozzarella, of course.
All right, all right, all right!
We left the lair because the
Foot were taking hostages
and we kicked some serious butt,
and there was this girl named April
O'Neil who took our picture,
- (GASPING) but we took care of it.
- RAPHAEL: Idiot.
Oh, no, my worst fears
have been realized.
Don't worry about it.
Donnie erased the picture!
We're not in danger.
No. It's April O'Neil
who is in danger!
Find the girl. Bring her here.
But, sensei, you said to not go...
Find the girl!
Find the girl.
APRIL: That's what I told
Thompson and she fired me.
So they're aliens?
No, that's stupid.
They're reptiles.
They help people, I guess.
Heroes in the half-shell.
- Okay.
- Come on. It's not that crazy. I...
The animal kingdom is full of...
I used to have a dog
that could moonwalk.
- Thanks for the ride, Vern.
- Yeah. No problem.
- (CAR DOOR CLOSING)
- Nothing better than
dropping off a pretty girl
at a rich guy's house.
(INTERCOM BEEPING)
Hi, it's April O'Neil,
here to see Eric Sacks.
April's arrived early this year.
I'm sorry to barge in on
you like this, Mr. Sacks.
No, no, no. Please, please.
Thank you.
APRIL: I've been working on a story.
And I have this theory that
there are these vigilantes
that are fighting back
against the Foot.
I think you and my father
may have created them.
Uh, I'm not sure I...
Can you please tell me
everything that you know
about Project Renaissance?
Hmm.
Well, um, it was a dream.
A dream that died with your father.
What if it isn't dead?
That's impossible.
We lost all our research in the fire,
all our specimens, everything.
I've spent the last 15 years
trying to replicate the results.
You didn't lose
everything in the fire.
- This can't be real.
- It is real.
I saw all four of them.
Do you really want to know
about Project Renaissance?
- Yes.
- Come with me.
I was born in Japan,
at a military base in Okinawa.
My father went to Vietnam.
Didn't come back.
I was an outsider in a foreign land.
A freak.
I was a powerless and helpless boy.
Until a local sensei
took me under his wing.
And he saved me.
Taught me lessons that I later
shared with your father.
Ninth-century Japan.
An evil warlord ruled the land.
He poisoned the water supply,
bringing on the dark ages.
Death and disease and
suffering ran rampant.
Not unlike the Foot Clan
and what they'd like
to do to our city.
Then one day, a hero arose.
A great alchemist
discovered the antidote
to the warlord's poison.
The cure-all
for his evil.
Your father and I were trying
to recreate that cure-all.
We developed a mutagen
capable of stimulating self-repair
on a cellular level.
What were you going to do with it?
Imagine New York City,
being victim to a chemical attack.
This mutagen would be able
to reverse its effects.
It would save the city,
it would save the people.
Those test subjects, those turtles...
Running in their blood is the
last of this precious mutagen.
And up until a few moments ago,
I thought we failed.
I thought they died
in the fire. How...
How could they have lived?
Because I saved them.
Of course you did.
April, the mutagen possesses powers
beyond our wildest hopes.
Whatever resources you need,
I'm here.
Let's work together. We'll find them.
The course of human
history may depend on it.
I'll show you out.
(SIGHS)
DONATELLO: Bam! You've been hacked!
By Donatello. Remember me?
Turtle. Four eyes.
But enough about me.
We told you we'd find you.
Meet us here.
And come alone. Or...
Or else we're...
You shall be punished and stuff.
Hello?
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
You told me to come here.
I didn't bring anyone with me.
I did exactly... (GASPS)
Okay! Are you April O'Neil?
Initiating retinal scan.
Scanning, scanning,
scanning, scanning.
Scan complete. It's her.
It's her. Guys, it's her!
Of course it's her, Donnie.
Hey. Really glad you could make it.
Hey. There's someone important we
want to introduce you to, but first...
MICHELANGELO:
Aw, yeah, welcome to my crib, girl.
APRIL: Where are we?
DONATELLO:
Hey, it's our Fortress of Solitude.
- MICHELANGELO: Our Hogwarts.
- DONATELLO: Our Xavier Academy.
MICHELANGELO: Our next generation,
state-of-the-art WonderDome!
(APRIL SNIFFS) Ugh.
Are we in the sewer?
MICHELANGELO: No.
- DONATELLO: Technically, yes.
- MICHELANGELO: Yeah.
Yeah, it's a sewer.
SPLINTER: You brought us here, April.
Splinter?
DONATELLO:
How does she know his name?
Did you tell her his name?
- DONATELLO: Maybe she's clairvoyant.
- Maybe she's a Jedi!
Come closer.
It's been a long time.
Mmm.
You always did have
your father's eyes.
I don't understand.
Don't be afraid.
All will be made clear.
This is crazy.
(SHREDDER SPEAKING JAPANESE)
Why are you here?
Student.
There's been a miracle.
The vigilantes who've been
causing us so much trouble?
They're the test subjects.
Those itty-bitty box turtles that
we thought we lost in the fire?
They're alive, Master Shredder.
And they've grown into something
powerful.
It won't be easy to capture
them, but if we can,
we can finally carry out the plan
that we had all those years ago.
(SPEAKING JAPANESE)
My Foot Clan will have unlimited power.
And you will have your money.
The city will be ours.
(SPEAKING JAPANESE)
Find them.
O'Neil's daughter was
the one who found them
and she will be the one who
will take us right to them.
FOOT TECH 1: There's the ping.
We've breached the cloaking security.
SPLINTER: Listen closely, April.
I don't remember a time
before living in that laboratory.
That fateful night
started like any other.
Sacks gave us our injections.
Your father made sure our
vital signs were strong.
And you, as always,
provided us with a special treat.
After the brothers went to sleep,
I heard loud voices.
There was the smell of smoke.
Alarms sounded.
Your father had discovered the truth
behind the man he was working for.
He set fire to the lab.
His last breath was taken
trying to destroy Shredder's plan.
I was terrified.
But then, you appeared.
And ushered us to safety.
I never had a voice then,
but I thank you now, April.
Mmm.
We wandered the sewers
until I found this place.
It was then that the mutagen
that was injected into our blood
began to change us
in miraculous ways.
I saw how your father loved you
and I knew I had to show that
same love to the turtles.
I became their father
and they became my sons.
Like all children, they were drawn to
the distractions of popular culture.
And I knew one day they would
want to explore the world above.
(UPBEAT POP MUSIC PLAYING)
They would be ridiculed.
(SPLINTER SIGHS)
They would need to learn
to protect themselves,
both mentally and physically.
MICHELANGELO: Hey. Does anyone
want to play Buck-Buck?
Buck one!
Buck two!
Buck three!
Where you going, Raph?
MICHELANGELO: Come on.
I can't do it by myself.
I need all four!
DONATELLO: You're a Buck short.
RAPHAEL: Yeah, that sounds stupid.
Like you, Mikey!
MICHELANGELO: That's why
you're just the hype man, bra.
- See these moves?
- RAPHAEL: Yeah, whatever, man.
SPLINTER: And then I found a way.
(GRUNTING)
First, I would teach myself
the ancient art of Ninjutsu.
(CHUCKLES)
Oh!
(GRUNTS)
The brothers followed my lead,
accelerating at a wondrous rate!
(GRUNTING)
Wassup, bra? Want some of this?
I'm like a ghost!
I'm over here, now I'm over here, bra.
Like a shadow!
I'm a flame shadow fire dragon!
(GROANS) Ow!
SPLINTER:
Their gift was also their passion.
They lived, breathed and dreamed
all things martial arts.
(GRUNTING)
(GRUNTS)
Then, they were ready.
The katana, most noble
of all the blades.
It is the weapon of a leader.
Everything they are,
and everything that they've become
was made possible by the bravery that
you displayed on that fateful night.
Dude.
I was just a little girl.
And you gave us freedom
where others would
have kept us in cages.
LEONARDO: Wait a minute, Dad.
All these years you told us
we were rescued from the fire
by a great guardian spirit,
the Hogo-sha.
That's right.
And this is the Hogo-sha.
What?
MICHELANGELO: (WHISPERING)
My girlfriend's totally the Hogo-sha.
Ow.
Fortunately, our engineers have
been making great progress
in refining the
robotics in your armor.
We're taking it to the next level,
bridging the gap between
ancient tradition
and modern warfare.
(SPEAKING JAPANESE)
Tonight, I dine on turtle soup.
Why did you bring me here?
To find out who you
told of our existence.
Nobody that believed me,
except for Eric Sacks.
(GASPS)
Sacks.
Just as I feared.
Sacks is not a friend.
His soul has been poisoned
by the influence of a dark master.
The Shredder.
Shredder practically
raised Sacks in Japan.
He's like a father to him.
Sacks will do anything
for his master.
Wait, wait.
Sacks and Shredder?
So, why aren't we out
there hunting them down?
Because, Raphael,
The Shredder is a skilled warrior
whose cruelty is ever-reaching!
And you are just teenagers.
(RAPHAEL GROWLS)
The mutagen in your blood
is of great value to them.
Now that Sacks has confirmation
that you are alive,
I fear they will bring
the fight to us.
Oh, no.
FOOT SOLDIER 1:
Stand by to make entry. Let's move!
Go, go, go!
(ALARM BEEPING RAPIDLY)
DONATELLO: Perimeter infringe.
Breached! We have incoming!
Oh, no! Oh, no! We got two breaches.
Fan room, weapons wall!
LEONARDO:
Mikey, flank right! Donnie, on me!
We gotta go! Go, go!
FOOT SOLDIER 1:
Stand by to set charge.
Lock and load. We're going on 10.
FOOT SOLDIER 2:
No live ammo. Tranqs only.
FOOT SOLDIER 1: Take 'em alive!
No! Get back!
(BOTH GRUNTING)
LEONARDO: Donnie!
(GRUNTS)
(GROWLS)
FOOT SOLDIER 1: Engage!
Get him!
(GRUNTING)
There they are! Neutralize them!
DONATELLO: They've got tranq darts!
Well, don't let them hit your skin.
Let's go! Let's move!
(GRUNTING)
FOOT SOLDIER 1: Over there!
FOOT SOLDIER 2: Tango at 12!
Wassup, bra? Oh, you think
you can handle this, huh?
I'm a snapping turtle, fool.
Snap, snap, snap!
I meant to do that! I meant to do it!
(GRUNTING)
We got a breach in the fan room!
Raph! Get to the fan room!
Why are you always
telling me what to do?
Just go! Mikey, you gotta
get April out of here, now!
MICHELANGELO: I got this!
(EXCLAIMING)
April, come with me.
I got a safe place for you to hide.
And if you get thirsty,
I got a secret stash of Orange
Crush behind the fridge.
Don't tell Raph.
Shredder.
SHREDDER: All these years
I've been trying to
recreate the mutagen.
And you?
You just handed it to me.
You will not lay a hand on my sons.
(SHREDDER LAUGHS)
Your sons?
You think you're their father?
(GRUNTING)
Very good, rat!
(SCREAMING)
(GRUNTING)
(PANTING)
Sensei!
(GROANING)
Donnie!
DONATELLO:
Hang on, Leo! Be right there!
(GROWLS)
(GROANING)
You stupid little girl!
April!
(GROANS)
(SCREAMS)
Sensei!
No, my son, stay back!
Sensei! Dad!
Dad! What are you...
What are you doing?
Hide!
No!
SPLINTER: Save yourselves!
(SCREAMS)
(SQUEALING)
Children, drop your weapons,
or your father will die.
(GROANS)
No!
(GROANING)
Where's the fourth?
He's dead.
Destroy this place.
(TURTLES GROANING)
FOOT SOLDIER 1: Keep moving!
(GROANING CONTINUES)
LEONARDO: Stay strong.
Remember, pain's only in the mind.
(KARAI SPEAKING JAPANESE)
FOOT SOLDIER 2: Move along! Go!
FOOT SOLDIER 1: Troop, go!
Move! Move!
(GRUNTING)
(STRAINING)
(SIGHS) Splinter.
(GRUNTS)
(STRAINING)
(PANTING)
(GRUNTING)
RAPHAEL: Sensei.
Master.
(GRUNTING)
Let's get him to the needle room.
Package is secured. En route.
We're carrying three specimens
and will be arriving at the estate
in approximately 40 minutes.
Prepare the containment units.
Inside those turtles
is the most precious
compound on Earth,
mutagen.
And we will drain every last
ounce of their blood to get it,
even if it kills them.
Get the first aid kit! On the shelf!
Hurry. Hurry.
(GASPING)
Raphael?
I'm here.
You must save your brothers.
Stop Shredder.
Sensei.
(ALARM BLARING)
It's some kind of tracker.
RAPHAEL: It's Donatello!
Go, Raphael.
Let's go save my brothers.
We need a ride.
(PHONE RINGING)
O'Neil!
APRIL:
Look, Vern, I need you to meet me
at Cortlandt Alley in
10 minutes, please.
Wait, why?
I can't talk to you
about it on the phone.
Just promise you're gonna be there.
What do you mean, you can't
talk about... You called...
(DISCONNECTS)
me.
(BREATHES DEEPLY)
All right. Want me to
meet you right now?
I'll play your little game.
(WHISTLING)
What's with the hat?
What is with the...
(CHUCKLES) I don't know,
it's a buddy of mine's.
It's just a goof.
What do you want to do?
You wanna head downtown?
Eric Sacks is working with
the head of the Foot Clan.
They just kidnapped
the vigilante turtles
to take them to the Sacks estate.
We need to go. Come on, Vern.
Right, right, right.
The turtles. I forgot.
This is getting embarrassing.
O'Neil, we're both consenting adults.
We're both very good-looking.
You're better, probably.
That's up for debate.
But the point is, we don't
need to make up excuses
- to hang out with each other.
- What?
You want to spend more time
with me. I get it. I would too.
We need to get to the Sacks
estate right now, Vern. Come on!
That's what I'm talking about, O'Neil.
"The Sacks estate with the vigilante..."
- What...
- Drive!
(STAMMERING) You're a talking turtle.
Yeah. Yeah, I'm a talking turtle
and you're a human nerd.
Now that we got that
out of the way, hit it.
I've never been accused of
being a nerd before, but...
I'm sorry...
How did you get in...
How did he get in the...
(TURTLES STRUGGLING)
(SCIENTISTS CONVERSING INDISTINCTLY)
Oh, my.
Wow.
Unbelievable. Let me look at you.
I'm a hard guy to impress, but...
This is just...
(CHUCKLING) Oh, my God.
Wow!
And we were gonna use rabbits!
Can you imagine that?
All we were trying to do
is create an antidote.
LEONARDO: For what?
Say that again.
I want to hear your voice.
(YELLING) For what?
Wow.
Well, uh, we had this plan.
A plan that we're ready
to put back online today.
I'll show you. Karai, um...
Show them.
(SPEAKS JAPANESE)
What?
Do you know my building, Sacks Tower?
Got that great big spire up on top?
- That spire is filled...
- (FOOT SOLDIER STRUGGLING)
with tons of chemical toxins.
No! No!
(GAGGING)
Bad stuff.
That kinda bad.
(GASPING)
In a few hours, Shredder is going to
unleash all that stuff over the whole city.
The initial death toll will shake
world governments to their core.
In 30 days, the city of New
York will be a quarantine zone.
And that is where my
company comes in.
I'm going to save everyone
with the antidote
that is made from the mutagen
that is oozing through your blood.
The government will then send
Sacks Industry a blank check
and I'm going to be rich.
Like, stupid rich.
Shredder will force this
city to live under our rule.
(GURGLING)
We will be gods.
VERN: Yeah, I've thought about...
I've thought about doing,
not becoming a ninja, but I
was doing a bunch of yoga
for like, 10 days at one point,
and, uh, I pulled a hamstring.
- There's the gate right there.
- There it is.
RAPHAEL: Ram the gate.
"Ram the gate"?
This is Channel 6 property.
(YELLING) I said ram the gate!
All right, everybody, strap in!
(ALL GROANING)
VERN: Oh, shit!
RAPHAEL: Go, go, go, go!
(BOTH PANTING)
- (GUNFIRE)
- (APRIL GRUNTS)
(GROWLS AND YELLS)
(GRUNTS)
Follow me!
- (ALARM BLARING)
- (FOOT SOLDIERS CLAMORING)
I'll take this canister to New
York to withdraw the mutagen.
Make sure that you
drain all their blood.
Time to take a bite
out of the Big Apple.
(GRUNTING)
(YELLING)
(GRUNTS)
FOOT SOLDIER: Hey! Get out of here!
(PANTING)
Leo!
About time.
(GRUNTS)
What the...
SHREDDER: Raphael.
Glad you could join us.
(GROWLS)
The fourth cage is for you.
(GRUNTS)
(SHREDDER GROWLS)
(GROANS)
That's harsh, man.
(EXHALES HARSHLY)
(GRUNTS)
(GRUNTING)
The rat did not teach you well!
(GROANS)
Raphael!
You.
RAPHAEL: Focus on me.
Three... Four total turtles.
One's fighting a
robot samurai. Why not?
Donnie!
(RAPHAEL GROANS)
APRIL: Donnie!
What do I do?
- (SOFTLY) Adrenaline.
- What?
Adrenaline.
All right. All right.
(SHREDDER GROWLS)
(RAPHAEL GROANS)
He's going to kill him.
- (CRACKING)
- (GROANS)
(MACHINE BEEPING)
Get up!
(GASPING)
It's working.
(MICHELANGELO GROANS)
(GASPS AND GROANS)
(GRUNTING)
(YELLS)
I think we should move.
(TURTLES GRUNTING)
Oh! I feel really good right
now! I feel like running!
I feel like cleaning!
Who wants to clean the dojo?
I'll clean the dojo!
Endorphins! Endorphins!
LEONARDO: We got to get Raph!
ALL: Raph! Raph!
(ALL GRUNTING)
MICHELANGELO: Are you okay?
Are you dead? Are you okay?
Come on. Come on.
MICHELANGELO: We really gotta go!
- RAPHAEL: Go where?
- MICHELANGELO: Sacks Tower!
New York City! Times Square!
Shredder's going to release a toxin!
It's gonna poison the whole city!
And Sacks is gonna sell the antidote!
MICHELANGELO: Made from the mutagen
- that's in our blood!
- So we've got to get going now!
Good. Let's do it for sensei.
MICHELANGELO: Okay. We're going!
Everybody calm down!
Look how calm I am!
LEONARDO: We got to move. Let's go!
Sacks is airborne!
Flight time to Manhattan, 19 minutes!
Get us out of here, Donnie!
Oh, my gosh, they have guns!
- (GUNFIRE)
- Get down!
(TURTLES SHRIEKING)
(BULLETS RICOCHETING)
(SHRIEKING CONTINUES)
(FOOT SOLDIERS GROANING)
Ha! Are you guys okay?
We're bulletproof.
Sweet!
FOOT SOLDIER: Advance and engage!
- (GUNFIRE)
- (GROANS)
Can you drive that truck?
Yeah!
We're on Raph. Ready?
(TURTLES YELLING)
(YELLING)
(BULLETS RICOCHETING)
(GRUNTING)
(SHRIEKING)
(FOOT SOLDIERS GROANING)
Come on!
Everybody in the truck!
We gotta go, go, go! Move!
Vern, you know how
to drive this, right?
Yeah, yeah, yeah. Just got to
hotwire this thing, I guess.
Classic blue wire/red wire situation.
- Keys!
- Yeah.
Keys are better.
- Drive!
- I'm on it!
RAPHAEL: Come on! Come on!
That's all I need is a
backseat-driving talking turtle!
(GATE CLANGING)
- FOOT SOLDIER 1: Let's go!
- FOOT SOLDIER 2: Move!
Jackal-One-Tango, on your 12!
FOOT SOLDIER: (OVER RADIO) Copy that.
I shouldn't have doubted you.
Sorry I didn't stick up for you.
I can't believe that you're not crazy!
How crazy is that?
(ALL GRUNTING)
FOOT SOLDIER: Target, 12 o'clock!
MICHELANGELO:
Where are we going, guys?
Donnie, what's the fastest
way back to Manhattan?
We just need to stay on this road.
If we can get to the maintenance
hatch at the bottom of the hill,
there's a sewer line
2.4 miles from here.
Mikey! Let them know up there!
I'm on it!
(GRUNTING)
Oh, no.
(BOTH GRUNTING)
- (SHRIEKS)
- (GRUNTS)
(MICHELANGELO GROANS)
(GRUNTING)
(YELLS)
(GROANING)
- Vern, go, go, go, go, go!
- I'm on it!
FOOT SOLDIER: Stop!
Vern, hit the brakes!
Wrong way! Wrong way!
Go around! Go, go, go!
Leo, move, move!
What?
(GRUNTS)
VERN: Opposite, opposite, opposite!
MICHELANGELO: Oh, no!
How far off course are we?
Actually, we're on
a bit of a shortcut.
But we need to keep going down.
Straight down.
Hey!
Just keep
going straight!
What's up, angel cakes?
(GROANS)
(GRUNTING)
Fire!
(LEONARDO STRAINING)
Guys, Leo's in trouble!
My shell's cracked. Just tape it up.
Allow me to be the bad-ass for once.
(GROWLING)
Hang on, Leo. Disengaging.
(GRUNTS)
God, I've always wanted to try this.
(CHUCKLING)
(SNORTS IN LAUGHTER)
(GROANS)
I got you, brother.
One car down, two to go.
(GROANS)
Mikey!
All right, that's it.
I'll take it from here!
Whoo-hoo!
Raph, I'm driving! Yeah! (LAUGHING)
(FOOT SOLDIERS GROANING)
(WHOOPING)
(STRAINING)
O'Neil, what are you doing?
(APRIL GRUNTS)
Yeah, that's good. Make sure
you're getting everything.
(APRIL SHRIEKS)
(GRUNTING)
Vern!
O'Neil! Give me your arm!
Avalanche!
Whoa!
(TURTLES YELLING)
(GROANING)
DONATELLO: Come on, Leo, wake up!
Yeah! If you wake up,
I promise to do anything you say!
Guys! Shredder's chopper is 20 miles
outside of New York City airspace!
Thanks for the
traffic update, Donnie.
You doing sports and weather next?
If you're gonna be nasty about it
then I guess you don't want to know
that there's a 500-foot
drop-off in 53 seconds!
Are you saying there's...
A cliff!
(BOTH YELLING)
We gotta get April out of there!
Raph, heads up!
MICHELANGELO:
Don't forget that old guy!
Hi. Change of plans. Oh, come on.
Guys, get down! Get down!
(APRIL SHRIEKS)
(GROANING)
(GRUNTS)
DONATELLO:
Twelve seconds and we're going over!
Hey, Donnie, do that
fancy slingshot thing!
We got to take Little
Miss Sunshine out!
Batter up!
(GASPS)
(GROANS)
Grab on.
(BOTH GROANING)
(SHRIEKS)
Mikey! Grab the cable!
I got it! I got it!
(STRAINING)
Hold on! Hold on!
(GRUNTING) Oh, no!
No, no, no!
(ALL YELLING)
(SOBBING) Oh, no...
Poor Leo, April...
And that other guy.
They were so young, so beautiful.
RAPHAEL: They ain't dead, numb nuts.
Oh. Right on.
(STRAINING)
I hope you got a parachute
under that shell.
Hey, guys!
It's the maintenance hatch!
Our ticket home!
LEONARDO: A little help, please!
DONATELLO: Guys, we gotta hustle.
Shredder's over New York City!
SACKS: (ON RADIO) Sensei,
the mutagen is four minutes out.
Moving forward as planned.
(TURTLES GRUNTING)
(YELPS)
MICHELANGELO:
Please keep your arms and legs
inside the shell at all times.
DONATELLO: Satellite imagery shows
Shredder's reached the
top of Sacks Tower.
If that's where he's
releasing the toxin from...
DONATELLO:
It's gonna spread all over the city!
RAPHAEL: We need to...
DONATELLO: break a left!
(ALL LAUGHING)
(GRUNTING)
LEONARDO: All right, listen up.
We gotta find the elevators
and get up to the roof.
You guys get out of here.
Get to a safe distance.
No, no, we can go find Sacks
and get our hands on the
mutagen as a contingency plan,
just in case... You know.
Thanks for the vote of confidence.
If we don't make it back,
bring the mutagen to Splinter.
It can save his life.
Sacks's laboratory's
on the 36th floor.
I've already disabled
the security system.
Oh, and, uh...
Good luck!
If I don't return,
remember me, April.
You can always find me
in here.
(GRUNTING)
You're a complicated chick.
Yeah.
- Elevator's just around this corner!
- All right, guys, listen up.
We stick to my plan
and we won't fail.
Fan out in three, two, one.
(ALL YELLING)
- (GASPS)
- Whoa.
(GUNFIRE)
Not the elevator.
Nope.
(SIGHS)
SACKS: The first vial is
filling with antidote now.
SHREDDER: Initiating the
toxin release procedure.
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(TAPPING RHYTHMICALLY)
(IN SINGSONG VOICE) MC Mikey.
MC (BEATBOXING)
(ELEVATOR DINGS)
(YELLING)
(GRUNTING)
LEONARDO: Ready, stance!
Hey, Mikey, remember that
thing you used to say
when we were kids?
You made me promise
never to say it again.
Forget about that.
Still got one in the tank?
I've been holding it in for years.
Guys, we need a plan!
MICHELANGELO: Cowabunga!
(GRUNTING)
MICHELANGELO: Leo!
(WOMAN SCREAMS)
Yeah, we got a 10-10.
Debris falling from the building.
Come on.
- (GUNSHOTS)
- (GASPING)
DONATELLO:
I got this, guys! I'll take him!
Come on!
(GRUNTING)
MICHELANGELO: Oh, no, you don't!
SACKS: Seriously,
you two...
You're adorable, really.
I could just pinch your cheeks!
(GUNSHOT)
(SIREN BLARING)
(PEOPLE CLAMORING)
DONATELLO:
Ugh, guys, he's coming, he's coming!
Guys!
MICHELANGELO: Donnie!
(SCREAMING)
DONATELLO: Come on, come on!
RAPHAEL: Hold on, Leo!
SACKS: I understand a girl
with dead daddy issues.
I do. But you're not gonna stop me.
This is history
repeating itself.
Your father walked in on me,
April, just like you did.
It took a few less bullets
to take him down, though.
(GUNSHOTS)
(WHISPERING) You killed my father.
POLICEMAN:
Move! Move! Go, go, go!
RAPHAEL: Come on, guys!
(STRAINING)
Got you!
(GROWLS)
(GRUNTING)
(SCREAMING)
SHREDDER: Enough. The lesson is over.
Ugh! We're getting our
asses kicked out there.
We only got 50 more seconds
before the toxin's released.
Hey.
Who wants to play Buck-Buck?
Buck-Buck?
- LEONARDO: What?
- Buck-Buck. Tony-on-a-Pony.
Some people call it
Johnnie-on-a-Rock.
LEONARDO: Wait.
Yeah.
Let's play Buck-Buck.
- DONATELLO: But why would we...
- No.
We do what Leo says.
Lead the way.
(BREATHES HEAVILY)
O'Neil!
- (GUNSHOT)
- (GRUNTS)
- Argh!
- (SIREN BLARES)
(ALL STRAINING)
Hmm.
(YELLING)
(SCREAMS) Oh!
(GRUNTS)
Cowabunga.
(GROANING)
Are you okay?
Look, just go get some help and
take the mutagen with you.
- Just go. Go!
- No!
(APRIL GRUNTS)
Just another day in the life
of a man of action. (CHUCKLES)
Ow. No, I'm not getting up.
(BEEPING)
You know how to use this thing?
It's a simple command-line interface.
No one's used this code in 15 years.
I mean, I've read about it online.
But these kind of things take time.
(DONATELLO CONTINUES
INDISTINCTLY)
Thinking there was no way
I'd ever be in a position
where the fate of an entire city
would rest on whether or not I
could hack out antiquated code
on an antiquated system.
I'll buy you some time.
FEMALE VOICE: Toxin disbursement
in five, four,
three,
two...
(POWERING DOWN)
Bam! System disabled!
Who wants Italian?
I'm buying!
Tiramisu for everybody! Ah!
Ah.
LEONARDO: Fall in!
Hold on! Hold it! Hold it!
If the spire falls and the
toxin makes ground impact,
it'll contaminate a 10-block radius!
What are the odds of us
stopping that from happening?
Uh, 0.00000000003%!
I'll take it. Nobody moves,
no matter what.
(TURTLES GRUNTING)
MICHELANGELO: But, Leo...
LEONARDO: I said nobody moves!
Leo, I'm letting go!
Ah! (GROANS)
Shredder!
This is all that's left!
SHREDDER: Little girl.
That belongs to me.
LEONARDO: Hold on! Hold on! Hold it!
(APRIL SCREAMING)
POLICEMAN:
Get back! All the way back!
(APRIL SCREAMS)
April!
RAPHAEL: Come on, guys!
(GRUNTING)
Ah!
RAPHAEL: April!
LEONARDO: Got you, Raph!
Hold on! Hold on! April!
(STRAINING)
RAPHAEL: I got you.
Swing me towards him!
Do it!
RAPHAEL: Leo!
That's my girl.
(STRAINS)
(ALL SCREAMING)
(GRUNTING)
I think this is it, guys!
Does anyone have anything
they want to say?
(ALL SCREAMING)
Donnie?
I'm the one who licks the icing
off the Pop-Tarts every morning
and puts them back in the box.
APRIL: No, no, no, no!
(SCREAMING)
I so did not understand
the ending of Lost.
(ALL SCREAMING)
(CLAMORING)
LEONARDO: Raph?
I just, uh...
If this is our last moment together,
I just want you guys
to know I'm sorry.
I'm sorry I was so hard on you.
Every time I pushed you,
I... I threatened you,
I yelled at you, I pushed
you beyond your limits,
it was because I believe in you!
I believe in each one of you!
I believe in your spirit
and your intelligence
and your potential.
And every time I talked
about walking away,
it was because I was scared!
I just didn't think I was good enough
to stand next to you
and call you brothers and say to you
I love you!
I love you guys so much!
DONATELLO: Raph?
We made it.
Are you crying?
No, ding-dong.
It's just a little dusty out here.
DONATELLO: Okay, the mutagen
is now entering his bloodstream.
Master Splinter?
Nothing's happening.
Why isn't it working yet?
(WEAKLY) Mikey...
- MICHELANGELO: Huh?
- Mikey, come closer.
(WHISPERING INDISTINCTLY)
What did he say? What did he say?
He said, "Please get
your knee off my chest."
(CHUCKLING)
Sensei!
You're alive!
It worked!
I'm sorry. This was all my fault.
You were right. We weren't ready.
No.
It was I who wasn't
ready to let you go.
All you needed was to discover
that your true power lies
in believing in one another.
There she is.
New York's secret weapon.
How's your arm, Vern?
Well, it wouldn't be
much use in a fight.
Not that I was much
use before, but...
- Did you get a new car?
- Yeah.
You're looking at the
new Fenwick Express.
Pretty sweet, huh?
Kind of an upgrade.
I figured I'd need new wheels after
my old work vehicle went boom.
Yeah, Channel 6 gave it to me.
They said don't put a scratch on it, but,
like, lightning's going to strike twice?
So, is that why you called me here,
to talk about your new car?
I know that you're not exactly
a fancy restaurant kind
of girl, so I figured
a creepy underpass in an
abandoned neighborhood
in the middle of the night
was more your speed.
I wanted you to be comfortable.
(CAR HONKING)
(BEATBOXING)
DJ Mikey in the house!
What are you guys doing here?
We figured we owed you a
thanks for keeping our secret.
You had a lot to gain from
telling people about us,
but you had our backs.
Yeah, 'cause that's what
family's for, Raph.
So you guys are driving now?
Yeah, man. I pimped this bad boy out.
Got a 42-inch plasma with the
NBA package, shave ice machine,
7. 1 digital surround sound.
Check the bass, bra.
(WHIRRING)
Uh-oh.
Ooh.
My bad. I'm still
figuring out the buttons.
That was my new Fenwick Express!
I just... I just got that.
We better get out of here.
Want a ride home?
You know what? I think we're
gonna take the subway.
We're going to take the subway.
MICHELANGELO: You sure?
I got a real nice song
that's all cued up.
- It's special, girl.
- RAPHAEL: No, don't.
- For us.
- LEONARDO: Come on, Mikey.
DONATELLO: No, no, no,
Mikey, you promised.
MICHELANGELO: It's happening.
(OTHER TURTLES CLAMORING)
Imagine me and you I do
I think about you day and night
It's only right
To think about...
MICHELANGELO:
I'm making really good headway!
TURTLES: Shut up, Mikey!
I can't see me loving nobody but you
For all my life
When you're with me, baby
The skies'll be blue
For all my life!
Watch Movies, TV Series and Live Sports
Signup Here -> WWW.ADMITME.APP