Watch Movies, TV Series and Live Sports
Signup Here -> WWW.ADMITME.APP
Much more than
just a series of small, isolated incidents...
...it's now apparent that an organized
criminal element is at work.
And at the moment, business is good.
So good, in fact,
that there appear to be no eyewitnesses...
...to any of these crimes.
With complaints ranging
from purse-snatching...
...to breaking and entering...
...police switchboards
have been swamped...
...with the angry voices
of more and more citizens...
...who have fallen prey
to the recent surge of crime...
...that continues to plague the city.
Instead of getting better,
things have actually gotten worse.
Even more alarming is the baffling...
...and often bizarre nature
of these crimes.
Merchandise
of every size and description...
...from skateboards to stereo systems...
...has been disappearing
from store shelves and storage areas...
...at an alarming rate.
Aah...
Even the victims themselves
rarely catch a glimpse of the thieves.
Many don't even know
they've been victimized until it's too late.
In fact, police have yet to come up
with a single eyewitness.
Only a few vague reports...
...of young boys or teenagers
at the scenes have been filed.
But whoever is behind these crimes,
one thing is certain.
These are much more than just a series
of random isolated incidents.
Come on. Hurry up.
Mm.
Good.
Crimes without criminals?
An invisible gang at work?
Who are we gonna call?
Unfortunately,
the police are the only ones available...
...to combat what some are already dubbing
"the silent crime wave."
But perhaps the most
disturbing silence...
...is that coming from city hall.
April O'Neil,
Channel 3 Eyewitness News.
You gotta stop working so hard, April.
What, and give up
all this glamour? Ha-ha-ha.
- Good night.
Bad timing.
You're telling me.
- Get her purse. Hey, get her purse.
- Get away from me!
- What do you think... Help!
- Get herjewelry.
- Hurry up.
- Get the money. I got her watch.
Whoa.
What the hell's going on?
Thought I'd seen it all.
Ready.
All right. You tough guys.
Roll over here. How did you
get yourself into this, huh, kid?
- You all right, ma'am?
- Yeah, I'm fine.
Listen, rest right here
while we deal with these guys.
- Ted, give John a hand.
- What you got there?
Oh, man.
Come on, no fighting.
- Untie me.
- Let's get them in the car.
Damn.
Spectacular.
- We were awesome, bros.
- Far out. Ow!
Yes, dudes and dudettes...
...major league butt-kicking
is back in town.
Oh, yeah.
Awesome.
Ha-ha-ha. Righteous.
Bossa nova!
- What?
- Huh?
Bossa nova?
- Chevy Nova?
- Oh.
Excellent.
- Yeah.
- All right.
- Come on, let's move it. I'm starving.
- Ooh.
Ooh. We're talking
major pizza attack here, dudes.
Pizza. I need it.
Oh, baby.
Oh, man.
All right.
- Evening, bros.
- Whoo!
- Give me three.
- You got it.
We were great. I can't believe it.
Damn!
All right. Shh, shh.
Ha-ha.
We have had our first battle,
Master Splinter.
They were many, but we kicked...
- We fought well.
- Mm-hm.
- Were you seen?
- Mm-mm.
In this you must never lapse.
Even those who would be our allies
would not understand.
Our domain is the shadow.
Stray from it reluctantly.
For when you do...
...you must strike hard and fade away...
...without a trace.
I lost a sai.
- Then it is gone.
- But I can get it back. I can.
Raphael, let it go.
Hey.
Your ninja skills are reaching their peak.
Only one truly important lesson remains,
but must wait.
I know it is hard for you
here underground.
I want a large thick crust
with double cheese...
...ham, pepperoni.
Your teenage minds are broad, eager.
But you must never stop practicing
the art of ninja...
...the art of invisibility.
Oh, but no anchovies.
And I mean no anchovies.
You put anchovies on this thing
and you're in big trouble, okay?
Michaelangelo!
That'll do. And the clock's ticking, dude.
You are still young...
...but one day, I will be gone.
Use my teachings wisely.
I suggest we all meditate now...
...on the events of this evening.
Yeah.
Ninjitsu.
Well, this is like meditating.
Hey, Raph, where you going?
Out to a movie.
That okay with you?
Yeah.
Sock it to me, baby.
- How you doing?
- Fine.
Nice night.
Mm-hm.
Pizza dude's got 30 seconds.
Hey, Mikey, did you ever think
about what Splinter said tonight?
I mean, about what it would be like...
...you know, not having him?
Hmm.
- Time's up. Three bucks off.
- Mm.
Okay.
Now, 122, 122 and an eighth?
122 and an eighth. Terrific.
Where the heck is 122 and an eighth?
You're standing on it, dude.
Just slip it down here.
Give me that.
Hey, this is a 10. The tab's 13.
You're two minutes late, dude.
Oh, come on. I couldn't find the place.
Wise man say, "Forgiveness is divine...
...but never pay full price for late pizza."
I gotta get a new route.
And I thought I delivered everywhere.
Yes, friends, the new Turbo Ginsu.
It dices, it slices...
...and yet makes French fries
in three different...
Whoops!
Mm. Kids.
Hmm.
- There's a joke on the...
- I know.
Ugh.
Where do they come up with this stuff?
- Hey.
- Come back here.
- Somebody stop them.
- Where's the...?
- What?
- Huh?
- Huh.
Mm-mm.
Whoa.
What the hell was that?
I don't know.
Now, that was a crime,
you purse-grabbing pukes...
...and this is the penalty.
Two minutes for slashing,
two minutes for hooking...
...and let's not forget
my personal favorite...
...two minutes for high-sticking.
Aah!
How about a five-minute game misconduct
for roughing, pal?
Hey, Bogie,
now, who died and made you referee?
You did yourjob, now let me do mine.
These JV lowlifes need a lesson.
Not like that they don't.
Not from you.
Well, it looks like you're the one
who needs to be taught a lesson, pal.
Class is Pain 101.
Your instructor is Casey Jones.
Look, I don't wanna fight you.
Well, tough rocks, pal.
A Jose Canseco bat?
- Tell me you didn't pay money for this.
- Ooh.
That's it.
Was a two-for-one sale, pal.
- Hey, what are you, some sort of punker?
- Huh?
God, I hate punkers.
Especially bald ones
with green makeup...
...who wear masks over ugly faces.
- That's it.
- Ooh.
- New batter.
Strike one.
Whoa. Whiffer.
- Ooh. Uhn!
- Home run.
Raphael wins.
One-nothing!
Well?
New game, roundhead.
- Cricket.
- Cricket?
Nobody understands cricket.
You gotta know what a crumpet is
to understand cricket.
I'll teach you.
- Ooh...
- See? Six runs.
So long, freak. I got work to do.
Freak?
Freak!
What the heck was that?
Looked like sort of a big turtle
in a trench coat.
You're going to LaGuardia, right?
Come back here.
I'm not finished with you.
Damn!
Raphael.
Come sit by me.
Couldrt this wait till morning?
You will listen now.
My master Yoshi's first rule...
...was possess the right thinking.
Only then can one receive...
...the gifts of strength,
knowledge and peace.
I have tried to channel your anger,
Raphael...
...but more remains.
Anger clouds the mind.
Turned inward,
it is an unconquerable enemy.
You are unique among your brothers...
...for you choose
to face this enemy alone.
But as you face it, do not forget them.
And do not forget me.
I am here, my son.
Come on, April, you could've
called me last night, you know?
Call it a quirk, but I like to know when one
of my best reporters has been mugged.
I wasn't mugged, Charles.
Besides, I knew you'd just worry and then
rush over here like you did this morning.
From now on,
security is gonna escort you...
...to that Stone-Age van of yours
every night.
- Yes, sir.
- I'm not kidding, April.
Ugh. Hey, Danny, how's school going?
- Fine.
- Oh, wonderful.
So wonderful I have to drive him there
every morning now...
...just to make sure he goes.
See?
That's what he does
when he wants to ignore me.
Sticks his head in those things.
I wonder where the hell
he got those things, anyway.
Charles, give the kid a break.
Just what is going on out there, April?
I've never seen anything like this before.
Like the city's falling apart.
It's getting so you can't step outside
in the daytime anymore.
Well, I'll tell you one thing.
After everything I've heard
out of Little Tokyo...
...Sterns is gonna have some answering
to do this afternoon.
Look. Just take it easy, okay?
He's already got the mayor
breathing down my neck.
We are presently executing a plan
of redeployment...
...that will minimize response time...
...while maximizing coordination
between patrol units...
...in a decentralized networking scheme.
Huh. I'm not sure I understood all that,
Chief Sterns.
Would you mind repeating it...
...in English, perhaps?
What that means, Miss O'Neil,
is that we have everything well in hand.
- You know why crimes have been escalating.
- Guys, look.
- That's her.
- No, I didn't say that either. Miss O'Neil...
...if you would stick to asking questions,
there would be a lot...
- Mmm. I'm in love.
- What do you know about an organization...
...known as The Foot Clan?
There is no evidence
to link such a name to these incidents.
Are you denying that such an organization
known as The Foot exists?
I'm not denying anything.
Again, you're putting words
into my mouth.
- Find her.
- It often seems that somebody ought to.
- Silence her.
- Miss O'Neil...
- She's great.
- An understatement as usual.
- You're telling me.
- The girl is a fox.
Look at the local weather
for this vicinity as it stands at this hour.
O'Neil, get in here.
Time me.
Just what is it you hoped to accomplish
out there besides busting my chops?
I think you know just as much as I do
about this Foot Clan...
...and I don't think
you're doing anything about it.
You expect me to waste manpower...
...because a few immigrants
are reminded...
...of something that supposedly happened
years ago in Japan?
Have you got something else?
Are you trying to tell me
how to do my job?
One-oh-seven, a new record.
Oh, great.
Just great.
We've been waiting for you, Miss O'Neil.
What?
Am I behind
on my Sony payments again? Ha-ha-ha.
Your mouth may yet bring you
much trouble, Miss O'Neil.
I deliver a message.
- Hah!
- Shut it.
All right. That's it.
Are you crazy?
Yeah, Leo, I'm crazy. Okay?
A loony. Okay?
Why?
Why? Why? Oh, I don't know.
Because I wanted to redecorate.
You know, a couple of throw pillows,
a TV news reporter.
- What do you think?
- Ahem.
Raphael, what are you doing?
She got jumped in the subway.
I had to bring her here.
It's the newslady.
Can we keep her?
- Bring water, cold washcloth, pillow.
- Far out.
Oh...
Hi.
Oh, my God. Oh, my God. I'm dead.
- I'm dead, aren't I?
- It's okay.
No, I'm dreaming. I must be dreaming.
Okay. Now, those guys
in the black pajamas, they jumped me.
And that rat...
...I saw you in the parking lot.
That explains you.
- And you guys... Um...
- Hmm?
...I have no idea where you came from.
If you will please just sit down
and calm yourself.
I will tell you where we came from.
It talks.
It is really quite simple, Miss O'Neil.
And he knows my name.
Perfect.
Fifteen years ago...
Why don't I ever dream
of Harrison Ford?
For 15 years now, we have lived here.
Before that time,
I was a pet of my master Yoshi...
...mimicking his movements
from my cage...
...and learning the secret art of ninja.
When we were forced
to come to New York...
...I found myself for the first time
without a home...
...wandering the sewers,
scavenging for whatever I could find.
And then, one day...
...I came upon a shattered glass jar...
...and four baby turtles.
- That was us. Heh-heh.
- Shut up.
- Oh, no.
- Oh.
The little ones were crawling
into a strange glowing ooze...
...from a broken canister nearby.
I gathered them up in an old coffee can...
...and when I awoke the next morning,
I received a shock...
...for they had doubled in size.
I too was growing,
particularly in intellect...
...and I was amazed
at how intelligent they seemed.
But nothing could have prepared me
for what happened next.
One of them spoke.
Pizza.
More words followed...
...and I began their training...
...teaching them all that I had learned
from my master.
Radical. Radical. Radical.
And soon I gave them all names...
...Leonardo...
...Michaelangelo...
- That's me.
...Donatello...
...and Raphael.
I'm not dreaming, am I?
No, I'm afraid not.
Ew. Are you guys sure
you know where you're going?
11th and Bleecker?
Nope. This is only 9th Street. Ha.
- Get it?
- Yuck.
Okay.
Ah...
I'd like to invite you all in...
...but I really don't have anything to offer
you guys except for frozen pizza.
Let's go for it.
You said the magic word.
- You guys eat pizza?
- Doesrt everybody?
Yeah, well...
...all right.
Hey, did she say pizza?
- So you live in an antique store?
- Yep.
Pizza.
Well, above, actually.
What do you guys like on your pizza?
Just the regular stuff.
Flies, stink bugs.
It was a joke. Ha-ha.
Yeah, well, maybe I'll fight Apollo...
...maybe I won't, you know?
What do you think?
- Adrian!
- Ha-ha-ha.
Hey, I got another one.
- This is totally cool.
- Oh, no, not Cagney.
Mmm. You dirty rat.
You killed my brother.
You dirty rat. Mmm.
Whoo-hoo. Ha-ha-ha.
That must be Splinter's favorite. Ha-ha-ha.
Huh?
- It was a joke.
- Hmm?
And speaking of which,
we better get going.
He worries.
Oh. Well, I don't know what to say.
- Will I ever see you guys again?
- Indubitably.
That depends
on how fast you stock your pizza.
- Deal.
- See you around.
- Bye.
- Later.
Ha-ha. No doubt about it. She loved us.
It was the impressions, dudes.
- You wish.
- Hold it.
Splinter.
What's wrong?
555-5215.
- Hello.
Charles Pennington?
Yeah. Who's this?
You got a son named Danny, Charles?
Who is it?
- It's me, Charles.
- It's my boss.
Can you guys...
...hide?
Charles, what's up?
April...
...listen.
I've... You have been working awful hard
on this story lately.
Why don't you take it easy for a while?
Just... Just...
Just let somebody else handle it.
Just for a little while, you know?
Charles, what are you talking about?
It's my story. No way.
Look at you. You're exhausted.
I just had a rough night.
Let somebody else help you
cover city hall.
Charles, that's ridiculous.
What's with you today?
Nothing's with me today.
I just thought you might like a little help.
Well, I don't.
- Hand me a towel, will you?
- Where do you keep the towels?
- Charles, no.
- What's wrong?
I just... I just don't want you to see
my unsightly bathtub ring. Okay?
Just out, out, out.
I have to get ready for work.
Are you sure you won't reconsider
some help?
Hey, Danny,
will you tell your father to relax?
I wish.
Just don't push any buttons today.
Okay?
- That was close. Whoa!
- Hah!
Time to switch to decaf, April.
I don't get it, Danny.
I make enough money to provide
for both of us and you're stealing.
Why?
- I don't know.
- You don't know?
What were you doing
with a car stereo anyway?
Or don't you know?
- Sorry.
- Sorry?
Not as sorry as you're gonna be
after school.
Danny, damn it.
Danny, come back here.
How are you doing?
Check it out, man.
Anything you guys want, we got it.
Anything you want to do...
...do it. Know what I'm saying?
Anything.
You got any cigarettes?
Regular or menthol?
Read them and weep, boys.
- Full house.
- Oh, no.
Mmp! Mm-hm.
Go. Play.
All right.
- Hah!
- Oh!
- Hah! Hah!
- Aah! Ooh!
How's this look?
- Hah! Hah! Hah!
- Ooh.
You. Hm!
Mm.
Good.
Never lower your eyes to an enemy.
Yes, Master Tatsu.
All right.
Yeah. I am.
Master Shredder.
Money cannot buy the honor
which you have earned tonight.
You make us all proud.
Only effort, discipline, loyalty...
...earn the right to wear the dragon dogi.
You are here
because the outside world rejects you.
This is your family.
I am your father.
I want you all to become full members
of The Foot.
There is a new enemy...
...freaks of nature
who interfere with our business.
You are my eyes and ears. Find them.
Together we will punish these...
...creatures.
These...
...turtles.
Master.
This is beginning to sound
less and less...
...like your common,
garden-variety subway mugging.
- Exactly, June.
- Boy, she's a good reporter.
- She's a babe.
- Organization known as The Foot.
I'm sorry, The Foot?
Yeah, I know it sounds like
a funky club for podiatrists...
...but I've been speaking with Japanese-
Americans in the past few days...
...who say that our crime wave
is reminiscent...
...of a secret band of ninja thieves...
...who once operated in Japan.
Are the police looking into this?
I've included everything
in my statement...
...but I doubt very much
that Chief Sterns...
...is taking this possible connection
seriously.
- I see. Well, perhaps if any of our viewers...
- Oh, God.
Mr. Pennington, Chief Sterns' office.
- Contact local police
or get in touch with us...
Pennington, I thought we had a deal!
You still haven't told us
how you got away from your attacker.
It's really quite incredible.
Some citizens of New York
actually came to my rescue.
Who says everyone in the Big Apple
looks the other way?
Seriously,
I would like to take this opportunity...
...to thank one of those individuals
in particular.
And if he's watching, thanks, Raphael.
Studly.
Hey, look. Nyak-nyak.
I think he's blushing. Heh.
I am not.
I think he's actually turning red.
- Uh, hmm. Maybe not.
- Mm-hm.
So, what do we do now?
- What do you mean, what do we do now?
- Splinter's out there somewhere.
I know Splinter's out there.
- Fight?
- Fight.
- Kitchen?
- Kitchen.
- Yeah.
- So, what are we gonna do about it?
What can we do about it?
April's our only link to these guys.
We have to wait
until she comes up with something.
Oh, so that's the plan
from our great leader, huh?
Just sit here on our butts.
I never said I was your great leader.
Well, you sure act like it sometimes.
Yeah? Well, you act like a jerk sometimes,
you know that?
And this attitude of yours
isn't helping anything.
Well, maybe I'll just take my attitude
and leave!
- Why don't you?
- I will.
- Good.
- Great.
Go ahead. We don't need you.
Pork rind?
Pork rind.
Damn!
Hah!
Ha-ah!
Go.
Move it, will you?
You're letting him blow right by you.
- Can you believe this guy?
- Hmm?
Come on. Don't just...
Ninja-kick the damn rabbit.
Do something.
Hey.
- April, hey, you were great.
- Thanks, Mikey.
Ho... She called me Mikey.
Hear anything yet?
Not yet.
They're gonna repeat the interview
at 5 and 6.
And we're gonna have to wait and see
if it helps generate any new information.
Mmm.
Hey, I told them to call me here
immediately...
...if anyone calls the station.
Thanks, April.
We really appreciate,
you know, everything.
Yeah.
Hey, forget it.
Where's Raphael?
Well, I was gonna give you guys
a tour of the store.
- Shall we go get him?
- No.
- He just needs to blow off some steam.
- Yeah.
You guys must be studying
the abridged book of ninja fighting.
Come on, come here. Come here.
I mean, come on.
How do you guys expect to beat me?
Good answer.
I only keep it open part-time,
mostly for my dad.
Heh. He loved junk.
I don't know.
It's dumb to lose money on a business...
...just because you miss your father.
No, it isn't.
Ready?
- This place has everything.
- Yup, just about.
Shh.
Eeeee.
Aah!
Hasrt Raph been gone a long time?
No. He does it all the time. He likes it.
Are you sure?
Don't worry.
He'll probably be back any minute.
Raph!
Is he...?
- No, he's alive. Barely.
- Oh, God.
- Hey, what the...?
- Whoa.
And I thought insurance salesmen
were pushy.
Ohh. A fellow chucker, eh?
What?
Oh-woh-oh. Oh-oh.
Oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh. Wah!
Oh.
Hmm-hmm.
Hah.
Keep practicing.
Take that.
Hey, one of these guys must know
where they're holding Splinter.
So don't knock them all out.
I don't think that will be a problem, Leo.
Gotcha.
Hey, Donnie, Wheel of Fortune, dude.
Bisen-tos. Now!
I guess they're not game show fans.
- And I thought everybody loved Vanna.
- Aah! Whoa!
California roll. Ooh.
Oh, what a spaz.
- Missed again.
- Good thing they aren't lumberjacks.
No joke.
The only thing safe in the woods
would be the trees.
Guys, I'm not so sure if this is,
structurally speaking...
...such a good time
for your buddies to drop in.
- Uh-oh.
- Aah!
Oh, whoa. Wipeout.
- Huh?
- Hmm?
- Hmm.
- Oh, no.
Mm.
Ha-ha. Ha-ha-ha-ha. Oh!
Ooh. Ooh.
Hey, hey, hey.
Hai!
Man, we could really use
Raph right about now.
Now what?
Oh. You guys mind telling me what you're
doing to my little green pal over there?
Mm?
Oh, who is the babe?
Who the heck is that?
Wayne Gretzky on steroids?
Attack.
Aaa-aaa-aah!
Come on, we got to get out of here.
Help me. There used to be
a trapdoor here to the basement.
Yeah, come on, you ugly muggers.
Come on.
We're getting out of here.
Gangway, men.
I'll take care of these guys.
- You coming?
- I'll cover you.
Good idea.
Hi, this is April.
- Leave a message after the beep.
- What?
April, it's Charles.
I'm sorry.
I don't know how else to say this.
You're fired, April.
I'm sorry. I know this comes as a blow.
- You can say that again, Chuck.
- Come on.
Bye, guys, got to run.
Ninja, vanish.
Oh.
What are these freaks?
How do they know how to fight like this?
You will answer.
Then hang there until you die.
Whoa.
Master Tatsu, stop, please, please.
Please, no.
Shinsho.
You'll be all right. You'll be all right.
How can a face so young
wear so many burdens?
So you can talk.
Yes, and I can also listen.
Some say that the path
from inner turmoil...
...begins with a friendly ear.
My ear is open...
...if you care to use it.
- No, I don't think so.
What is your name?
Danny.
And have you no one to go to, Danny?
No parent?
My dad couldn't care less about me.
I doubt that is true.
Why?
All fathers care for their sons.
- How's Raphael?
- Not so good.
Hey, didn't they use this place
in The Grapes of Wrath?
Very funny.
I told you,
I haven't been up here in years.
Can you fix it?
Does that answer your question?
I mean, the block's got a crack in it
the size of the San Andreas.
- Wonderful.
- Ah.
Well, I guess
I've got some walking to do.
What for?
Our nearest neighbor
is about four miles away.
I need to get to a phone,
and I need to call my boss.
You mean Charles?
How did you know that?
Well, he left a message on your machine
just before we got out.
And?
Well, hey, you just saved yourself
an eight-mile round-tripper.
You were fired.
I'm...
- I just saved myself?
- Yeah.
- Uh-oh.
- What did you do?
Did you take classes in insensitivity?
- I was just trying to break it to you easy.
- Oh, well, you failed miserably.
Hey, Broadzilla, you wouldn't be here
if it werert for me, okay?
Oh, and what do you want?
Do you want a thank you?
No. It's me who should thank you
for that privilege, right?
- Fine. Thank you.
- Yeah. No, thank you.
- You're welcome.
Gosh, it's kind of like Moonlighting,
isn't it?
- Heh.
- Mm-hm.
It's strange being back on the old farm.
Even after all these years,
it still feels like home.
My amazing new friends
have suffered their first real defeat.
That's bad enough...
...but they've also lost the opportunity
to find out about their mentor...
...and I'm sure that hurts them
much more than anything else.
Each of them deals with this confusion
in his own way.
Donatello has found someone
to latch onto.
Not even close, zip neck.
The Professor and Mary Ann,
happily ever after.
No way, atomic mouth.
Gilligan was her main man.
They'd be married
and have six kids by now.
Gilligan was a geek, barfaroni.
- You're the geek, camel breath.
- Dome head.
Hmm!
Elf lips.
Let's give this a try,
see if this transplant worked, fungoid.
- All right, here it goes. What are we on?
- Uh...
- G.
- Heh.
Here goes, gack face.
I'm ready, hose brain.
It worked. Uh... Hey.
Leonardo, meanwhile,
has kept a constant vigil with Raphael.
He'll be okay.
And then there's Casey Jones...
...a 9-year-old trapped in a mars body.
He might almost be cute
if it wasn't for that pigheadedness.
Donatello.
He's out with the others...
...they're exercising.
Doing something together, I don't know.
You want some help?
- Ah.
- Hey, I am your man. I am Mr. Fix-it.
All right.
- Let's go.
- Lead the way, toots.
- Toots?
- Oh... Babe?
Sweetcakes?
Ah! Princess.
Do you want to throw me a clue here?
I'm drowning.
You know what? That's okay.
- I'll take care of it myself.
- Fine, that's up to you.
Just don't come around here
asking for my help anymore.
See, I wouldn't ask for your help...
...if you were the last thing
on the face of this planet.
It's coming along nicely.
- Hey.
- What?
Raph.
You're awake. How do you feel?
What's a guy got to do
to get some food around here?
Hey. Hey, he's awake.
He wants some food.
Bring some food.
You're gonna be okay, Raph.
You're gonna be okay.
Yeah, yeah, all right, Leo.
Get a grip, will you?
Listen, Raph.
About what I said before...
...you know...
...about not needing you and all, like...
Leo...
...don't.
Oh, boy, we missed you.
It's a Kodak moment.
The turtles are four once again...
...and yet, still not whole.
A lingering doubt remains.
An unknown
which they can't bear to face...
...their greatest fear.
Splinter!
Your empire flourishes, Master Shredder.
- No, no, no, that's a stereo.
- What more from the rat?
Nothing.
He will not speak.
And the boy who led us to the turtles?
He is still missing.
I do not understand.
Why do the turtles trouble you, master?
They have not been seen for many days.
Something about the way
you described their fighting.
Something familiar.
Something...
...from the past.
- Ointment?
- Mm-mm.
Hey, guys.
Hmm.
Oh, God.
Funny, Mikey.
Leonardo.
Hah. Splinter.
What Russian novel,
embracing more than 500 characters...
...is set in the Napoleonic Wars?
War and Peace.
He's alive.
- Hey.
- Thanks, spaz.
Splinter's alive.
We know, Leo. Of course he is.
We all think he's alive.
I don't think.
- I know.
- Huh?
Huh?
Leo...
...if you dragged us
out here for nothing...
Don't worry. I came prepared.
- Put those away.
- Heh-heh.
Heh.
Now, everybody close your eyes
and concentrate.
Concentrate hard.
I am proud of you, my sons.
Tonight you have learned...
...the final and greatest truth
of the ninja...
...that ultimate mastery
comes not of the body...
...but of the mind.
Together, there is nothing
your four minds cannot accomplish.
Help each other.
Draw upon one another.
And always remember
the true force that binds you...
...the same as that
which brought me here tonight...
...that which I gladly return
with my final words.
I love you all, my sons.
Huh. Huh? Uh... Huh.
So you actually played professionally?
Before I got hurt, less than a year.
I'm sorry.
- So was I.
- Ah-ah-ahem.
Guys, I told you...
...I hate it when you do that, all right?
What is it?
It's time to go back.
Oh, no. Oh.
- Home sweet home.
- Ha-ha.
Yuch.
I know what it's like to travel
without a green card.
This isn't bad.
Nice place, guys. In fact, l...
Are you coming or not, dude?
This is great, it's great.
First it's the farm that time forgot,
and now this.
Why don't I ever fall in
with people who own condos?
Guess it's hard to get
good maid service in a sewer.
Maybe you guys should try Roto-Rooter.
Would you quit complaining?
It's just for the night.
I still don't see
why we don't get started right away.
It's been a long drive, Raph.
And before we go out advertising
to The Foot that we're back...
...we could all use a few hours' sleep.
Yeah.
I know, you're right. I'm just...
What's that?
- Danny?
- Don't shoot.
- I don't think it's loaded, kid.
- Danny...
...what are you doing here?
- Where'd he come from?
- Beats me.
I ran away from home.
Oh, God,
your father's gonna have kittens.
- Does this thing work?
- No.
No, please don't call.
Just let me stay here the night with you.
We can call in the morning. I promise.
- Danny, listen, your dad, he's...
- Hold on, hold it.
Okay, now, what is all this talk
about spending the night down here?
You're a claustrophobic.
- Do you want a fist in the mouth?
- Mm-mm.
I've never even looked
at another guy before.
What he means is that
you're afraid of enclosed areas.
Afraid?
- What, me? Is that what you think?
- Mm-hm.
Ah. Hey, I don't have to take this stuff
about being afraid.
I'm gonna sleep in the truck.
Jeez, these are good.
Thanks.
Do you think maybe I could have one?
- Sure, why not?
- Thanks.
Oh, man, I could really go...
...for a little deep-dish action
right about now.
I had some pizza down here
the other day.
- There might be some left over.
- Mm? Mm? Uh-huh.
- Wa-ah. Wa-ah-aah!
- Ha-ha-ha.
- Well?
- Question.
- Yeah?
- Do you like penicillin on your pizza?
Oh! Ugh.
"Afraid of enclosed areas."
You are here...
...because the outside world rejects you.
And you have no one to go to, Danny?
This is your family.
All fathers care for their sons.
Nice shot, man.
I need a cigar.
Where is my cigar?
Hey.
Great how you did that, it rocks.
I have not seen you for days.
Yeah, I've been down at my hideout
a lot lately.
And do you now hide
from your surrogate family as well?
I don't know.
I too...
...once had a family, Danny.
Many years ago...
...I lived in Japan...
...a pet of my master, Yoshi...
...mimicking his movements
from my cage...
...and learning
the mysterious art of Ninjitsu...
...for Yoshi was one of Japars
finest shadow warriors.
His only rival was
a man named Oroku Saki...
...and they competed in all things...
...but none more fiercely
than for the love of a woman.
Tang Shen.
Shers love was only for my master...
...and rather than see him
fight Saki for her hand...
...she persuaded Yoshi...
...to flee with me to America...
...but Saki vowed vengeance.
I remember it well.
As my master returned home...
...to find his beloved Shen
lying on the floor.
And then he saw her killer.
Saki wasted no words,
and during the struggle...
...my cage was broken.
I leapt to Saki's face,
biting and clawing...
...but he threw me to the floor...
...and took one swipe with his katana,
slicing my ear.
Then he was gone and I was alone.
Whatever happened to this Oroku Saki?
No one really knows...
...but you wear his symbol
upon your brow.
What are you doing in there, boy?
Nothing.
Where have you been?
Nowhere.
You're lying to me.
- No.
- And you're hiding something as well.
Shaah!
They're back.
Master.
There will be no mistake this time.
I go myself.
And the rat...
...kill it.
Come on, men.
- Hey, what do you want?
- Shh, shh.
Recognize me now, kid?
- Hey, what's the deal?
- You got to come with me.
- What are you talking about come with you?
- They're gonna kill Splinter.
Hee-hee-hee. No sweat.
Gosh, I do hope there's more of them.
- Huh?
- Ah.
Good.
Well, where are the keys?
Who are you?
Hey.
- Ahh.
- The name's Casey Jones.
A friend.
Let's get out of here.
A little to the right. A little to the left.
One more time.
A little bit more like that.
And stop. Perfect.
Aah!
- You're a natural, sis.
- Thanks.
Ha! Ha-ha! Ha!
Now, you know, a little Primatene
might just help to clear that up there.
That's gonna cost you, Tinker Bell.
I don't think that you're listening.
You know, I'm starting to pick up
on a little language barrier thing going here.
Fore.
I'll never call golf a dull game again.
Gangway.
Showoff.
What are we just standing here for?
Let's get him.
Do you want to be first, junior, huh?
We have a loyalty to The Shredder.
The Shredder uses you.
He poisons your minds
to obtain that which he desires.
He cares nothing for you
or the people you hurt.
We're a family.
Family? Is that what you said? Family?
You call this here...
...and that down there, family?
Casey.
Hey, dudes, where you going?
Hai!
Ha! Hey, Donnie, looks like this one's
suffering from shell shock. Ha!
Hmm. Too derivative.
Boy, I guess we can really shell it out.
Too clich
Well, it was a shell of a good hit.
I like it. Step up.
Awesome. Ha! Ha! Ha!
Hey, where do you think you're going?
- Hey.
- Hmm.
Hey, wait for me.
Whoop! Yaah!
God, I love being a turtle!
Ha-ha! Yee-ha!
Oh!
Come on, come on.
Aw. No more?
Nyah. Nyak-nyak.
Does anybody have any idea
about who or what this is?
I don't know...
...but I'll bet it never has to look
for a can opener.
You fight well in the old style...
...but you've caused me enough trouble.
Now you face...
...The Shredder.
- The Shredder? Heh.
- Uh...
Maybe all that hardware's
for making coleslaw.
I got him.
- This guy's good.
- Yeah.
- Why don't you go next?
- Thank you.
Uh... Match you for it?
One, two, three. Mm.
- Damn.
- Great. Wah!
Come on.
So much for family, huh?
Yeah, I'm just so hungry, you know.
Now...
...at exactly what point...
...did we lose control here?
Maybe somebody ought to tell him
that we're the good guys.
- Yeah.
- Any thoughts?
I've only got one thought.
This guy knows where Splinter is.
Looks like your boys
are going to need a little...
Where did he go?
Oh, boy.
Leftovers.
Yee-ha!
It's a talent.
Where's Splinter?
- Ah. The rat, so it has a name.
- Huh?
It had a name.
You lie.
Do I?
He dies.
- Huh?
- Weapons.
- Now.
- Oh.
Fools. Ha-ha.
The three of you might have
overpowered me with the loss of but one.
Now your fate will be his.
No.
Oh.
Splinter.
- Aah.
- Yes, Oroku Saki.
I know who you are.
We met many years ago...
...in the home of my master...
...Hamato Yoshi.
It's him.
You.
Now I will finish
what I began with your ear.
Death comes for us all, Oroku Saki...
...but something much worse
comes for you.
For when you die, it will be...
- Without honor.
Oops.
- Splinter, are you okay?
- Oh, Splinter.
Oh, Splinter, we were so worried.
Kids.
- I can't wait...
- I was there. I saw the whole thing.
- All right.
- Whatever.
Okay, okay, move along here.
You, you, come here.
- Tell me when it's on.
- Hold the battery.
All right, guys, let's get to it.
Brian, it's over.
- It's over.
- April.
- April. April, here.
- Danny.
- See you later.
- What's this for?
It's something I owe you.
- Trust me.
- Come on, let's move it back.
You there, come here.
Dad.
Danny?
Danny.
God, where have you been?
I've had the whole city looking for you.
Are you all right?
- Are you okay, Danny?
- It's okay, Dad.
I'm okay, really. I'm okay.
And Dad?
It's just Dan now, okay?
Dan?
Come on, folks.
- Come on.
- What have you been up to?
I want some stretchers in here.
Get some doctors.
Don't move. Get those kids.
Don't let them get away.
April, I told you
there were circumstances.
I really need you to cover this.
I don't know, Charles, you know...
Did you know that May Williams
over at Channel 5 has her own office?
You can have an office.
Yeah, well,
she has her own corner office.
- You can have a corner office.
- Well.
She's one of the highest-paid
field reporters in New York City.
Now you are.
You are a tough negotiator, Charles.
All right, I want some answers.
Now, what in God's name
happened out here tonight?
Somebody better talk to me.
- Yeah.
Go check out the East Warehouse
over at Lairdman Island.
You'll get your answers there.
How are you doing, lady?
All right, let's go.
I've been looking all over for you.
Oh, Casey, hi.
"Hi"?
You...
I look like
I just called Mike Tyson a sissy.
Yeah?
And all you say is hi?
What?
You don't need an ambulance, do you?
No, but I was...
Will you just shut up and kiss me, okay?
I got a report to do.
- I love it when you're pushy.
- Yeah?
Yeah.
Whoo-hoo.
Nine-point-nine-five.
All right, April.
All right, Casey.
Yeah, that's the way to go.
We were awesome.
- Bodacious.
- Yeah.
- Bitching.
Uh...
- Gnarly.
- Ha-ha-ha.
Radical.
- Yeah. Ha-ha.
- Totally tubular, dude.
Wicked.
Hellacious.
- Mega...
- Ahem.
I have always liked...
...cowabunga.
- Hmm?
- Huh?
Cowabunga!
I made a funny.
- Yeah.
- Ha-ha-ha.
Watch Movies, TV Series and Live Sports
Signup Here -> WWW.ADMITME.APP