1
00:00:49,466 --> 00:00:54,092
Don't forget to tell Uncle Louie I left
the red wine and Parmesan in the fridge.

2
00:00:54,179 --> 00:00:55,803
I love you. Bye-bye.

3
00:00:55,889 --> 00:00:57,846
- 'Bye, Judy.
- Send me a picture.

4
00:00:57,974 --> 00:01:00,050
I'll be back soon. Don't worry about it.

5
00:01:00,185 --> 00:01:02,890
- Be careful, now.
- 'Bye.

6
00:01:04,272 --> 00:01:07,107
- Take it easy, now.
- 'Bye.

7
00:01:33,802 --> 00:01:36,672
"California, here we come"

8
00:01:37,180 --> 00:01:39,552
What's wrong? Don't you like my singing?

9
00:01:39,641 --> 00:01:40,969
I don't like the song.

10
00:01:41,059 --> 00:01:44,060
You're going to love California.
You get up in the morning...

11
00:01:44,187 --> 00:01:46,061
...roll out of bed, plop, in the pool.

12
00:01:46,273 --> 00:01:47,304
Yeah, sure.

13
00:01:47,524 --> 00:01:51,438
You'll see. This isn't exactly a dump
we're moving to.

14
00:03:00,597 --> 00:03:05,058
Push, Daniel.
Give it all you've got, kid. Push!

15
00:03:06,019 --> 00:03:09,388
Okay, we've got it. Come on.
Get in, hurry up.

16
00:03:12,234 --> 00:03:15,151
We did it again. Way to go!

17
00:03:42,681 --> 00:03:44,970
Daniel, wake up.

18
00:03:45,058 --> 00:03:49,519
Look off the starboard bow.
Paradise at last.

19
00:03:50,730 --> 00:03:52,273
We made it.

20
00:03:52,899 --> 00:03:54,691
Come on.

21
00:03:54,776 --> 00:03:56,057
This is it.

22
00:03:56,862 --> 00:03:59,400
This is the end of the line.

23
00:04:00,240 --> 00:04:01,699
You're telling me.

24
00:04:02,617 --> 00:04:05,073
Come on. All hands on deck.

25
00:04:06,872 --> 00:04:10,537
We've got to get this thing unloaded
before it sinks.

26
00:04:12,419 --> 00:04:16,167
Look at those palm trees!
Damn, do you know what that means?

27
00:04:16,339 --> 00:04:18,795
Yeah, watch out for falling coconuts.

28
00:04:19,009 --> 00:04:22,959
- Wise guy. No more Newark winters.
- I like winters.

29
00:04:23,054 --> 00:04:26,008
Oh, you like sore throats?
You like frozen toes?

30
00:04:26,349 --> 00:04:27,725
I don't like smog.

31
00:04:27,976 --> 00:04:31,262
- Did I tell you about the pool here?
- About 100 times.

32
00:04:31,354 --> 00:04:33,680
Okay, so make it 101.

33
00:04:33,774 --> 00:04:38,400
Open your eyes, my darling son.
This is the Garden of Eden.

34
00:04:38,487 --> 00:04:42,152
Come on.
Listen, we're in apartment 20, okay?

35
00:04:42,324 --> 00:04:44,151
One flight up.

36
00:05:03,345 --> 00:05:05,421
- Are you okay?
- Don't worry about it.

37
00:05:05,639 --> 00:05:07,181
- Let me help you up.
- Thanks.

38
00:05:07,390 --> 00:05:09,348
I shouldn't have done that. It was stupid.

39
00:05:09,851 --> 00:05:11,844
You must be the new people in 20, right?

40
00:05:11,937 --> 00:05:13,016
Yeah, I guess so.

41
00:05:13,188 --> 00:05:15,596
- Freddy Fernandez, apartment 17.
- Daniel LaRusso.

42
00:05:15,774 --> 00:05:17,102
How you doing? Let me help.

43
00:05:17,192 --> 00:05:20,775
- No, it's fine. It's heavy, man.
- I got it.

44
00:05:21,321 --> 00:05:23,195
- Where are you from?
- New Jersey.

45
00:05:23,281 --> 00:05:24,859
What are you doing out here?

46
00:05:24,991 --> 00:05:28,277
My mom got a job with some company
out here. Rocket Computers.

47
00:05:28,370 --> 00:05:30,113
Flight of the Future. I don't know.

48
00:05:30,205 --> 00:05:33,076
- I never heard of it.
- It's up and coming.

49
00:05:33,917 --> 00:05:38,413
- Is this the only pool you've got?
- That's it. What was that, karate?

50
00:05:39,506 --> 00:05:41,878
- Yeah.
- Have you been doing it long?

51
00:05:41,967 --> 00:05:44,374
- Yeah, a while.
- Did you ever use it?

52
00:05:44,469 --> 00:05:47,340
- A couple of times.
- I bet you could kick some ass.

53
00:05:47,472 --> 00:05:50,426
I'd like to learn that.
Maybe you could teach me.

54
00:05:50,517 --> 00:05:52,593
- Sure. That's cool. Anytime.
- Great.

55
00:05:52,686 --> 00:05:55,806
This place is a dump.
You should go back to New Jersey.

56
00:05:56,940 --> 00:05:58,600
How did you know where I was from?

57
00:05:58,692 --> 00:06:01,609
'Cause I'm from New Jersey.
I got a nose for my own.

58
00:06:01,736 --> 00:06:04,358
- Well what part?
- Parsippany.

59
00:06:04,489 --> 00:06:07,526
- I never should've left.
- My Uncle Louie's from Parsippany.

60
00:06:07,701 --> 00:06:09,278
- Louie Martini?
- Louie LaRusso.

61
00:06:09,369 --> 00:06:11,990
Louie LaRusso? Don't know him.

62
00:06:12,539 --> 00:06:14,615
Hey, pup.

63
00:06:14,791 --> 00:06:16,831
How you doing? You thirsty?

64
00:06:17,586 --> 00:06:19,294
- She's crazy.
- What?

65
00:06:19,421 --> 00:06:22,126
- She's not playing with a full deck.
- She's nice.

66
00:06:22,215 --> 00:06:25,252
- What are you doing tomorrow?
- I don't know. I guess nothing.

67
00:06:25,385 --> 00:06:28,386
We're having a beach party.
Want to come?

68
00:06:28,472 --> 00:06:31,591
- Sure, that's cool.
- I'll come get you in the morning.

69
00:06:32,100 --> 00:06:33,974
Here's apartment 20.

70
00:06:34,144 --> 00:06:35,971
- Is it?
- Should I leave this here?

71
00:06:36,062 --> 00:06:38,898
- Yeah, thanks for the help.
- No problem.

72
00:06:38,982 --> 00:06:42,896
Nice meeting you. Take care.
See you tomorrow morning.

73
00:06:44,988 --> 00:06:48,855
Don't say anything about the pool.
I'll call first thing in the morning.

74
00:06:48,992 --> 00:06:51,744
Did you tell that old lady
where we were from?

75
00:06:51,828 --> 00:06:53,987
Yes. Didn't she remind you of Aunt Tessy?

76
00:06:54,915 --> 00:06:58,747
- More like Uncle Louie.
- I really think we're going to do good here.

77
00:06:58,835 --> 00:07:01,622
I have a very positive feeling.
I'm telling you, Daniel.

78
00:07:01,922 --> 00:07:04,673
I just know it's going to work.
The faucet's broken.

79
00:07:04,758 --> 00:07:08,838
The real estate lady said there's
a fix-it guy. See if you can find him.

80
00:07:10,555 --> 00:07:11,670
What's that for?

81
00:07:12,265 --> 00:07:14,057
- Uncle Louie's dog.
- He's cute.

82
00:07:14,142 --> 00:07:17,096
- I got invited to a party tomorrow.
- Great. You see?

83
00:07:17,312 --> 00:07:21,226
- But you wanted me to help you unpack.
- I don't remember saying that.

84
00:07:22,317 --> 00:07:25,401
I must have had you mixed up
with somebody else.

85
00:07:25,529 --> 00:07:26,774
Thanks, Ma.

86
00:07:30,700 --> 00:07:33,108
Could you tell me
where the maintenance guy is?

87
00:07:33,370 --> 00:07:34,864
Hey, pup.

88
00:07:34,955 --> 00:07:38,703
You go in through there,
turn left, not too far...

89
00:07:38,917 --> 00:07:41,871
...then right, go inside, and you'll find him
on the left.

90
00:07:41,962 --> 00:07:43,504
So I go right then left?

91
00:07:43,630 --> 00:07:47,046
No, left then right, then inside on the left.

92
00:08:06,361 --> 00:08:07,736
Hello?

93
00:08:14,786 --> 00:08:16,530
Are you the maintenance man?

94
00:08:18,415 --> 00:08:20,657
We're the new people in apartment 20.

95
00:08:22,794 --> 00:08:25,416
The faucet's really leaking there.

96
00:08:31,553 --> 00:08:33,213
Could you come fix it?

97
00:08:37,267 --> 00:08:38,892
Can I tell my mom when?

98
00:08:39,603 --> 00:08:40,848
When what?

99
00:08:42,773 --> 00:08:44,599
When you're going to fix the faucet.

100
00:08:44,733 --> 00:08:45,812
After.

101
00:08:46,651 --> 00:08:48,110
After what?

102
00:08:48,236 --> 00:08:49,896
After after!

103
00:09:40,664 --> 00:09:43,914
Could we have the ball, please?

104
00:09:44,000 --> 00:09:45,578
Pretty good.

105
00:09:45,794 --> 00:09:47,169
Show-off.

106
00:09:50,799 --> 00:09:54,084
Sorry. Hey, wait up.

107
00:09:56,721 --> 00:09:59,592
- Who's that blonde in the blue?
- The hills.

108
00:10:00,016 --> 00:10:02,686
- What's the hills?
- Rich.

109
00:10:22,456 --> 00:10:25,291
- I think the blonde is looking at you.
- Yeah, right.

110
00:10:25,375 --> 00:10:29,539
- I think she has the hots for you.
- Who could blame her?

111
00:10:29,796 --> 00:10:32,334
- Why don't you make a move?
- No, I'm eating, man.

112
00:10:32,424 --> 00:10:35,176
- How can you think about eating?
- I'm hungry.

113
00:10:35,302 --> 00:10:39,714
- Maybe they ain't got no moves in Jersey.
- I got moves where I come from.

114
00:10:39,890 --> 00:10:43,472
We've got more moves back there
than here, I'll tell you that much.

115
00:10:44,102 --> 00:10:46,261
Let's see 'em.

116
00:10:48,190 --> 00:10:50,147
Come on, buddy. Go get her.

117
00:10:50,317 --> 00:10:52,559
I'm going.

118
00:10:55,363 --> 00:10:57,901
- Lose something?
- I hope we're not bothering you.

119
00:10:57,991 --> 00:11:00,031
Hey, how do you juggle?

120
00:11:00,118 --> 00:11:05,113
It's pretty easy. You start on the knee.
You just go one.

121
00:11:05,248 --> 00:11:08,368
One at a time. Then you try two.
One, two.

122
00:11:09,461 --> 00:11:12,960
And then three and four.
Try it. Just bring your leg up. Good!

123
00:11:20,222 --> 00:11:24,599
- That was awesome!
- Brew time. Who's for a warm one?

124
00:11:24,726 --> 00:11:25,924
No, I pass.

125
00:11:27,145 --> 00:11:29,434
Who are you kidding?
You're the ace degenerate.

126
00:11:29,731 --> 00:11:34,607
Ex-degenerate. Tomorrow I'm a senior.
I've got one year to make it all work.

127
00:11:34,694 --> 00:11:38,526
And that's what I'm gonna do.
Make it work, all of it.

128
00:11:38,615 --> 00:11:42,565
You must be a trendsetter, Johnny.
Everyone's doing something new.

129
00:11:42,661 --> 00:11:44,203
Take a right. Check it out.

130
00:11:46,498 --> 00:11:49,783
- Forget it, man. It's ancient history.
- Who told you, man?

131
00:11:50,836 --> 00:11:53,161
- I thought they broke up.
- She did, he didn't.

132
00:11:55,340 --> 00:11:56,751
Come on, try it.

133
00:11:56,883 --> 00:11:58,425
Watch this.

134
00:11:59,845 --> 00:12:01,671
I'll get it. I'll be right back.

135
00:12:18,989 --> 00:12:22,025
- Ali, I want to talk to you.
- Leave me alone.

136
00:12:22,325 --> 00:12:24,651
We've been over all this.
I don't want to talk.

137
00:12:24,995 --> 00:12:27,367
I want to talk to you, all right?

138
00:12:28,415 --> 00:12:32,163
- What is your problem?
- Just get out of here.

139
00:12:32,252 --> 00:12:36,036
- That won't solve anything.
- Give me my radio.

140
00:12:36,173 --> 00:12:37,750
I said, give me my radio.

141
00:12:38,008 --> 00:12:40,759
- You promise you'll talk to me?
- Yes, give me my radio.

142
00:12:46,016 --> 00:12:48,554
- You just broke my radio!
- Yeah.

143
00:12:48,977 --> 00:12:50,685
Don't touch it, punk.

144
00:12:53,899 --> 00:12:56,769
- What's going on?
- You want it?

145
00:13:05,619 --> 00:13:07,410
Johnny, stop it.

146
00:13:11,583 --> 00:13:14,252
- Stop it.
- I didn't do anything.

147
00:13:20,092 --> 00:13:21,918
You're a big man now, huh?

148
00:13:22,719 --> 00:13:25,590
You started this. I just wanted to talk.

149
00:13:26,223 --> 00:13:29,888
- Leave him alone and we'll talk.
- Where did I hear that before?

150
00:13:31,269 --> 00:13:33,807
How about you, hero? Had enough?

151
00:13:36,191 --> 00:13:39,275
- Now we're even.
- No mercy, man.

152
00:13:50,497 --> 00:13:53,866
Why don't you hit me?

153
00:13:53,959 --> 00:13:55,369
- It's your fault!
- It's not.

154
00:13:55,460 --> 00:13:57,453
- It's your fault.
- Ever think it's yours?

155
00:13:57,629 --> 00:13:59,289
Why do you always have to fight?

156
00:13:59,381 --> 00:14:02,002
Bullshit. Get on your bikes, guys.

157
00:14:10,642 --> 00:14:12,765
You sure pick cool people
to be friends with.

158
00:14:12,853 --> 00:14:14,892
Where'd you find this guy?

159
00:14:15,313 --> 00:14:17,851
Come on, let's go. He'll be all right.

160
00:14:26,992 --> 00:14:29,399
- Are you okay?
- Just leave me alone.

161
00:14:30,954 --> 00:14:34,323
- I'll help you.
- Leave me alone. I'm okay.

162
00:14:34,416 --> 00:14:38,164
Come on, Ali. Let's go.
It's better if you leave him alone.

163
00:14:44,676 --> 00:14:46,503
Come on, let's go.

164
00:15:03,236 --> 00:15:04,896
Daniel!

165
00:15:09,284 --> 00:15:11,953
- How was the party?
- It was okay.

166
00:15:12,329 --> 00:15:15,246
Must have been more than okay.
I didn't hear you come in.

167
00:15:15,332 --> 00:15:18,202
- Any friend material?
- Some. I got to go.

168
00:15:18,418 --> 00:15:20,245
- Eat first.
- I'm not hungry.

169
00:15:20,337 --> 00:15:23,540
- You need energy to be charming.
- I'm fine, I got energy.

170
00:15:23,715 --> 00:15:25,922
Do me a favour. Take off the glasses.

171
00:15:26,510 --> 00:15:28,467
- Why?
- Because I asked you to.

172
00:15:28,887 --> 00:15:32,837
- It's California. It's the look.
- I want to see your baby browns.

173
00:15:33,725 --> 00:15:36,430
- Come on with the baby browns.
- Are you on something?

174
00:15:37,062 --> 00:15:39,054
- I'm on Minute Maid.
- Why hide your eyes?

175
00:15:39,147 --> 00:15:41,817
- I'm not.
- Take off the glasses.

176
00:15:42,025 --> 00:15:43,223
Now!

177
00:15:48,240 --> 00:15:50,731
My God! How did that happen?

178
00:15:52,202 --> 00:15:55,867
I hit a kerb with my bike.
I wore the glasses so you wouldn't worry.

179
00:15:55,997 --> 00:15:58,323
- It looks worse than it feels.
- Don't do that.

180
00:15:58,417 --> 00:16:01,583
- It doesn't hurt.
- Can you see? You want to stay home?

181
00:16:01,670 --> 00:16:02,666
I've got to go.

182
00:17:03,440 --> 00:17:06,856
- Hey, you guys, Freddy, how you doing?
- Hey, the karate kid.

183
00:17:06,985 --> 00:17:08,728
Let's see the moves.

184
00:17:09,154 --> 00:17:12,274
- He knows how to get his butt kicked.
- I already know that move.

185
00:17:12,949 --> 00:17:14,408
Let's get out of here.

186
00:17:14,493 --> 00:17:15,607
Hey, think fast.

187
00:17:16,453 --> 00:17:18,529
- Hi.
- Hi, how are you doing?

188
00:17:18,622 --> 00:17:22,121
- Your eye.
- It looks worse than it feels. Believe me.

189
00:17:22,250 --> 00:17:23,495
I hope so.

190
00:17:24,127 --> 00:17:26,618
I never got a chance to thank you.

191
00:17:27,089 --> 00:17:30,255
That was nothing.
I'm just sorry about your radio.

192
00:17:30,801 --> 00:17:32,758
I'm more sorry about your eye.

193
00:17:32,844 --> 00:17:34,588
You should've just given it to him.

194
00:17:34,846 --> 00:17:36,388
Why? It wasn't his, right?

195
00:17:37,766 --> 00:17:40,969
- Yeah, it wasn't his.
- We think alike already.

196
00:17:41,686 --> 00:17:43,311
You know what else we do alike?

197
00:17:46,108 --> 00:17:48,433
You've been practicing.

198
00:17:48,527 --> 00:17:51,314
- Cheerleaders, over here.
- I've got to go.

199
00:17:51,446 --> 00:17:54,020
- I'll see you.
- 'Bye.

200
00:17:54,116 --> 00:17:57,781
- Hey, have you got a name?
- Ali with an "i."

201
00:17:58,995 --> 00:18:03,076
- What's your name?
- Daniel with an "I."

202
00:18:04,167 --> 00:18:05,994
I'll see you later.

203
00:18:07,462 --> 00:18:09,004
Definitely.

204
00:18:43,623 --> 00:18:45,533
Get him, Bobby.

205
00:18:52,299 --> 00:18:53,757
Have a nice trip?

206
00:18:54,885 --> 00:18:57,126
Look what he's doing to Bobby.

207
00:18:57,929 --> 00:19:01,049
Nobody hits me. I'm going to kill him.

208
00:19:02,809 --> 00:19:05,051
- None of that on this team!
- He hooked me!

209
00:19:05,145 --> 00:19:06,972
I said out of here!

210
00:19:07,939 --> 00:19:09,683
Back to it. Let's go.

211
00:19:09,775 --> 00:19:12,978
This school sucks! It sucks.

212
00:19:36,051 --> 00:19:40,001
52, 53, 54...

213
00:19:40,764 --> 00:19:44,844
55, 56, 57...

214
00:19:45,936 --> 00:19:48,224
- Fix faucet.
- Come on in.

215
00:19:48,396 --> 00:19:49,974
It's the kitchen one.

216
00:19:50,565 --> 00:19:54,397
1, 2, 3...

217
00:19:54,569 --> 00:19:55,767
Karate.

218
00:19:56,488 --> 00:20:00,355
- Yeah, 5, 6...
- Very good.

219
00:20:01,952 --> 00:20:06,281
- Learn from book?
- And a few months at the Y in Newark.

220
00:20:06,373 --> 00:20:09,078
9, 10...

221
00:20:09,960 --> 00:20:14,040
...11, 12, 13...

222
00:20:17,884 --> 00:20:19,426
What happened to eye?

223
00:20:19,761 --> 00:20:21,588
I fell off my bike.

224
00:20:26,143 --> 00:20:28,052
Lucky no hurt hand.

225
00:20:46,621 --> 00:20:49,788
- Ali with an "i." How are you doing?
- Good.

226
00:20:50,459 --> 00:20:52,831
- Not too hungry today?
- Not really.

227
00:20:53,462 --> 00:20:55,170
Have some pie, I made it myself.

228
00:20:56,965 --> 00:21:00,132
- How do you like the valley?
- It hasn't been dull.

229
00:21:00,302 --> 00:21:01,630
Was Newark dull?

230
00:21:02,763 --> 00:21:04,636
How did you know I was from there?

231
00:21:04,723 --> 00:21:07,095
- I asked.
- Oh, really?

232
00:21:07,976 --> 00:21:10,728
- Are you sitting with anybody?
- With you, if it's okay.

233
00:21:10,812 --> 00:21:13,386
- Sounds great to me. Want some milk?
- Thanks.

234
00:21:14,316 --> 00:21:17,815
- Sorry about the soccer tryouts.
- Those are the breaks.

235
00:21:18,153 --> 00:21:20,988
Remember that guy you had trouble with
on the beach?

236
00:21:21,156 --> 00:21:24,655
- Yeah, King Karate?
- He's my ex-boyfriend.

237
00:21:25,160 --> 00:21:26,987
That's good to know. What?

238
00:21:27,996 --> 00:21:29,538
Yeah, you're right. I know.

239
00:21:29,664 --> 00:21:32,582
- What are you doing?
- It's this little voice...

240
00:21:32,667 --> 00:21:35,585
...telling me I've got to be nuts
to be talking to you.

241
00:21:35,670 --> 00:21:38,707
- That'll be $2.50.
- For both.

242
00:21:39,549 --> 00:21:43,547
- $3.75.
- It doesn't matter, anyway.

243
00:21:43,637 --> 00:21:46,258
- Why's that?
- Because it's over.

244
00:21:47,390 --> 00:21:49,798
- Wait. How over?
- Weeks.

245
00:21:50,060 --> 00:21:51,969
One week, five weeks?
How many weeks is "weeks"?

246
00:22:02,322 --> 00:22:06,402
<i>- Fear does not exist in this dojo. Does it?</i>
<i>- No, Sensei!</i>

247
00:22:06,493 --> 00:22:10,443
<i>- Pain does not exist in this dojo. Does it?</i>
<i>- No, Sensei!</i>

248
00:22:10,580 --> 00:22:15,408
<i>- Defeat doesn't exist in this dojo. Does it?</i>
<i>- No, Sensei!</i>

249
00:22:15,544 --> 00:22:20,087
<i>- Fear does not exist in this dojo. Does it?</i>
<i>- No, Sensei!</i>

250
00:22:20,173 --> 00:22:24,669
<i>- Pain does not exist in this dojo. Does it?</i>
<i>- No, Sensei!</i>

251
00:22:24,845 --> 00:22:30,301
<i>- Defeat doesn't exist in this dojo. Does it?</i>
<i>- No, Sensei!</i>

252
00:22:30,475 --> 00:22:31,590
Prepare.

253
00:22:35,439 --> 00:22:38,854
- What do we study here?
- The way of the fist, sir!

254
00:22:39,234 --> 00:22:43,860
- And what is that way?
- Strike first, strike hard, no mercy!

255
00:22:44,072 --> 00:22:49,233
- I can't hear you.
- Strike first, strike hard, no mercy!

256
00:22:51,329 --> 00:22:53,488
<i>- Mr. Lawrence.</i>
<i>- Yes, Sensei.</i>

257
00:22:54,541 --> 00:22:56,284
Warm them up.

258
00:23:11,767 --> 00:23:14,518
Fighting positions. Jab punch.

259
00:23:14,936 --> 00:23:16,051
Ready.

260
00:23:25,238 --> 00:23:29,402
Guess what.
I'm going to be trained as a manager.

261
00:23:29,785 --> 00:23:31,445
Isn't that great?

262
00:23:32,120 --> 00:23:34,196
The programme's two nights a week.

263
00:23:34,289 --> 00:23:39,829
As soon as a spot opens up, I'm in.
The benefits are great.

264
00:23:40,337 --> 00:23:42,329
They pay for everything.

265
00:23:43,590 --> 00:23:45,168
That's great.

266
00:23:47,052 --> 00:23:49,721
- What's the matter, Daniel?
- Nothing.

267
00:23:52,099 --> 00:23:55,966
Remember when you went to the country
and hated it 'cause you had no friends?

268
00:23:56,061 --> 00:23:57,472
What happened?

269
00:23:58,980 --> 00:24:00,558
I got poison ivy.

270
00:24:00,649 --> 00:24:04,563
You met Kevin and Kenny,
who became your best friends in the world.

271
00:24:06,696 --> 00:24:08,654
You've got to give it a try.

272
00:24:09,032 --> 00:24:11,274
I know it's hard.

273
00:24:11,868 --> 00:24:13,695
We're not quitters, are we?

274
00:24:14,079 --> 00:24:15,490
I guess not.

275
00:24:16,665 --> 00:24:19,749
- What's with the karate place?
- It sucks.

276
00:24:19,835 --> 00:24:22,670
Good. We couldn't afford it anyway.

277
00:24:23,463 --> 00:24:25,123
And the girl situation?

278
00:24:25,841 --> 00:24:28,414
- It's okay.
- Just okay?

279
00:24:28,760 --> 00:24:31,880
To me it looks like
the whole world turned blonde.

280
00:24:32,431 --> 00:24:34,174
You got your eye on anybody?

281
00:24:37,352 --> 00:24:38,467
Cute?

282
00:24:38,645 --> 00:24:39,973
Not cute.

283
00:24:40,856 --> 00:24:44,900
- She's beyond cute.
- But she's blonde, right?

284
00:24:45,152 --> 00:24:48,686
- She's got blonde hair.
- Lucille, let's go, here they come.

285
00:24:48,780 --> 00:24:52,481
- Is she as pretty as Judy?
- She buries Judy in a second.

286
00:24:52,576 --> 00:24:54,864
She buries Judy?

287
00:24:55,412 --> 00:24:59,456
Tell me about it later. I love you.
Careful how you ride home.

288
00:25:01,460 --> 00:25:05,706
She's got an excellent smile.
She's really smart.

289
00:25:08,550 --> 00:25:12,133
I'd say she's beautiful.
I think she's beautiful.

290
00:25:12,846 --> 00:25:14,839
I think she's something else.

291
00:25:16,433 --> 00:25:18,556
She's hot. Definitely hot.

292
00:25:47,631 --> 00:25:52,340
- Looking for a shortcut to Newark?
- He wants to learn karate.

293
00:25:52,427 --> 00:25:57,006
Here's the first lesson: How to take a fall.
Don't think about the pain.

294
00:26:28,630 --> 00:26:30,788
Damn bike! I hate this bike!

295
00:26:30,924 --> 00:26:34,127
I hate this frigging bike! Stupid bike!

296
00:26:35,595 --> 00:26:38,347
What's the matter?
Why did you throw your bike away?

297
00:26:38,432 --> 00:26:41,717
- Because I felt like it.
- Look at me when I'm talking to you.

298
00:26:41,852 --> 00:26:43,050
My God!

299
00:26:45,397 --> 00:26:48,267
Tell me what's going on.
Don't say another bike accident.

300
00:26:48,400 --> 00:26:50,523
- What do you want to hear?
- The truth.

301
00:26:50,652 --> 00:26:53,321
No, all you want to hear
is how great it is here.

302
00:26:53,447 --> 00:26:56,116
Maybe for you, but it sucks for me.
I hate this place!

303
00:26:56,199 --> 00:26:59,864
I hate it, I want to go home!
Why can't we just go back home?

304
00:27:00,871 --> 00:27:02,413
Listen to me.

305
00:27:02,497 --> 00:27:05,284
I cannot help you
unless you tell me what's wrong.

306
00:27:05,375 --> 00:27:06,869
I've got to take karate.

307
00:27:06,960 --> 00:27:10,709
- You took karate.
- Not at the Y, at a good school.

308
00:27:10,881 --> 00:27:14,380
- Fighting doesn't solve anything.
- Neither does palm trees.

309
00:27:14,468 --> 00:27:16,010
That's not fair.

310
00:27:16,511 --> 00:27:20,639
It wasn't fair coming out here
without asking me.

311
00:27:23,351 --> 00:27:24,514
You're right.

312
00:27:25,854 --> 00:27:27,182
I should've asked.

313
00:27:27,272 --> 00:27:31,056
I just want to go home.
I don't understand the rules here.

314
00:27:31,151 --> 00:27:34,271
Let's see if we can figure out
the rules together.

315
00:27:34,362 --> 00:27:37,566
- What about your bike?
- It's safer taking the bus.

316
00:27:37,657 --> 00:27:41,323
Why can't we just go home
and forget this place?

317
00:28:03,475 --> 00:28:06,262
- I'll tell you everything he said.
- You'd better.

318
00:28:19,282 --> 00:28:20,445
How are you?

319
00:28:20,534 --> 00:28:24,531
- What happened to your forehead?
- It's terrible. A gigantic runaway zit.

320
00:28:24,621 --> 00:28:26,412
That's gross.

321
00:28:27,165 --> 00:28:30,866
Daniel, this is Susan.
What really happened?

322
00:28:30,961 --> 00:28:32,918
I got in a bike accident.

323
00:28:33,964 --> 00:28:36,918
What kind of bike do you have?
A Honda? Suzuki?

324
00:28:38,343 --> 00:28:40,252
It's a Miyagi Turbo.

325
00:28:40,345 --> 00:28:42,670
- Yeah?
- Oh, really?

326
00:28:42,764 --> 00:28:45,849
- We're going to the arcade. Want to come?
- Sounds great.

327
00:28:45,934 --> 00:28:48,639
There's this new game I want to show you.

328
00:28:52,482 --> 00:28:57,109
I forgot something.
I'll catch up with you guys in a minute.

329
00:28:57,195 --> 00:28:59,947
- Don't run away.
- I'm not running away from anything.

330
00:29:00,240 --> 00:29:04,368
- We've got to deal with this.
- I'll deal with it my own way.

331
00:29:05,162 --> 00:29:07,368
- Daniel...
- Get off my case!

332
00:29:44,785 --> 00:29:48,035
Did you fix my bike?

333
00:29:48,455 --> 00:29:50,697
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.

334
00:29:50,791 --> 00:29:52,867
I really appreciate that.

335
00:29:55,045 --> 00:29:56,622
Are those real trees?

336
00:29:57,589 --> 00:30:00,080
You like see, come inside.

337
00:30:00,884 --> 00:30:01,999
Thanks.

338
00:30:10,185 --> 00:30:11,976
How did they get so small?

339
00:30:12,104 --> 00:30:13,681
I train.

340
00:30:13,897 --> 00:30:16,305
Clip here, tie there.

341
00:30:17,400 --> 00:30:19,310
Did you learn this in Japan?

342
00:30:19,444 --> 00:30:20,689
Okinawa.

343
00:30:20,779 --> 00:30:21,977
Where's that?

344
00:30:22,656 --> 00:30:23,936
My country.

345
00:30:25,575 --> 00:30:26,856
China here.

346
00:30:27,244 --> 00:30:28,738
Japan here.

347
00:30:29,079 --> 00:30:30,870
Okinawa here.

348
00:30:32,916 --> 00:30:34,541
Did you go to school for this?

349
00:30:34,626 --> 00:30:35,906
Father teach.

350
00:30:36,628 --> 00:30:38,087
Was he a gardener?

351
00:30:38,713 --> 00:30:39,912
Fisherman.

352
00:30:40,048 --> 00:30:41,293
A fisherman.

353
00:30:42,509 --> 00:30:44,300
These are really beautiful.

354
00:30:45,137 --> 00:30:46,631
Come, you try.

355
00:30:46,763 --> 00:30:48,672
I don't know how to do this stuff.

356
00:30:48,765 --> 00:30:51,552
- Sit down.
- I may mess it up or something.

357
00:30:52,727 --> 00:30:54,138
Close eyes.

358
00:30:56,064 --> 00:30:57,095
Trust.

359
00:31:01,111 --> 00:31:02,391
Concentrate.

360
00:31:04,322 --> 00:31:06,813
Think only tree.

361
00:31:08,618 --> 00:31:12,486
Make a perfect picture
down to last pine needle.

362
00:31:13,915 --> 00:31:18,209
Wipe your mind clean.
Everything but the tree.

363
00:31:19,880 --> 00:31:22,881
Nothing exists in whole world...

364
00:31:23,216 --> 00:31:25,339
...only tree.

365
00:31:27,637 --> 00:31:28,800
You got it?

366
00:31:30,140 --> 00:31:31,718
Open eyes.

367
00:31:33,101 --> 00:31:34,595
Remember picture?

368
00:31:35,771 --> 00:31:36,885
Yeah.

369
00:31:37,814 --> 00:31:39,356
Make like picture.

370
00:31:48,950 --> 00:31:51,276
Just trust the picture.

371
00:31:52,287 --> 00:31:54,659
How do I know my picture's the right one?

372
00:31:54,748 --> 00:31:58,615
If come from inside you,
always the right one.

373
00:32:33,203 --> 00:32:34,282
Hi.

374
00:32:35,038 --> 00:32:36,580
Hi, Ma, come on in.

375
00:32:38,125 --> 00:32:41,375
- You fixed your bike.
- Mr. Miyagi fixed it.

376
00:32:42,754 --> 00:32:44,213
Great, thank you.

377
00:32:45,257 --> 00:32:47,545
- How much do we owe you?
- No, please.

378
00:32:47,759 --> 00:32:48,957
My pleasure.

379
00:32:49,302 --> 00:32:50,797
That's very nice.

380
00:32:53,223 --> 00:32:54,503
Hi, champ.

381
00:32:55,016 --> 00:32:56,048
Hey.

382
00:32:57,185 --> 00:33:01,230
- What are you doing?
- I'm trimming my baby tree.

383
00:33:01,773 --> 00:33:03,149
<i>Bonsai tree.</i>

384
00:33:03,775 --> 00:33:04,938
<i>Bonsai tree.</i>

385
00:33:05,277 --> 00:33:06,308
<i>Bonsai.</i>

386
00:33:06,945 --> 00:33:07,976
<i>Bonsai.</i>

387
00:33:08,989 --> 00:33:10,103
They're beautiful.

388
00:33:10,198 --> 00:33:13,033
Mr. Miyagi learned it in Okinawa.
That's where he's from.

389
00:33:13,243 --> 00:33:14,274
Really?

390
00:33:14,369 --> 00:33:15,947
They're so delicate.

391
00:33:21,042 --> 00:33:22,287
For me?

392
00:33:22,794 --> 00:33:24,502
No, I couldn't.

393
00:33:24,588 --> 00:33:26,829
Please, hurt feelings.

394
00:33:28,216 --> 00:33:30,090
That's very nice, thank you.

395
00:33:30,677 --> 00:33:33,049
- Welcome.
- I know just where it will go.

396
00:33:34,014 --> 00:33:35,638
Come on, it's getting late.

397
00:33:35,807 --> 00:33:39,010
- I'll be up in a half hour.
- No, now. School tomorrow.

398
00:33:40,145 --> 00:33:42,897
- Thank you for everything.
- You're welcome.

399
00:33:44,900 --> 00:33:46,643
Don't forget tree.

400
00:33:48,069 --> 00:33:49,314
Must practice.

401
00:33:50,280 --> 00:33:51,395
Thank you.

402
00:33:51,490 --> 00:33:53,613
<i>- Sayonara.</i>
<i>- Sayonara.</i>

403
00:33:54,493 --> 00:33:56,984
- Goodnight.
- Thanks again. See you.

404
00:34:00,624 --> 00:34:03,625
Ma, he gave you the nicest one.
This guy is something else.

405
00:34:03,877 --> 00:34:06,878
You saw what he did to my bike.
This guy is great.

406
00:34:37,536 --> 00:34:41,699
- Happy Halloween. You like?
- Yeah, that's nice.

407
00:34:41,873 --> 00:34:44,660
Passed school today. Lots happening.

408
00:34:46,586 --> 00:34:48,793
What's the matter? You're not going?

409
00:34:48,922 --> 00:34:49,953
No.

410
00:34:50,549 --> 00:34:51,580
How come?

411
00:34:52,217 --> 00:34:54,340
I'm not into dancing that much.

412
00:34:55,846 --> 00:34:57,554
I don't feel like it, anyway.

413
00:34:59,641 --> 00:35:02,310
You're too much by self. Not good.

414
00:35:03,186 --> 00:35:04,597
I'm not by myself.

415
00:35:05,397 --> 00:35:06,677
I'm with you.

416
00:35:07,607 --> 00:35:12,316
To make honey, young bee
need young flower, not old prune.

417
00:35:13,238 --> 00:35:15,314
I don't have a costume, anyway.

418
00:35:16,032 --> 00:35:17,575
If have costume...

419
00:35:18,160 --> 00:35:19,274
...you go?

420
00:35:19,911 --> 00:35:22,070
If I went as the Invisible Man.

421
00:35:22,789 --> 00:35:24,497
Invisible Man?

422
00:35:25,959 --> 00:35:28,165
You know, so no one would see me.

423
00:35:44,936 --> 00:35:46,347
There's Daniel.

424
00:35:46,480 --> 00:35:48,188
- Where?
- In the shower.

425
00:35:48,273 --> 00:35:50,764
- How do you know?
- I just know.

426
00:35:50,859 --> 00:35:52,057
May I?

427
00:35:53,153 --> 00:35:57,020
- I don't know what she sees in him.
- She must be into fungus.

428
00:36:01,745 --> 00:36:04,450
Help me, my flower needs water.

429
00:36:05,874 --> 00:36:08,543
You've come to the right place, stranger.

430
00:36:09,711 --> 00:36:13,495
- I've never danced in a shower.
- A friend of mine made this for me.

431
00:36:14,007 --> 00:36:15,038
Isn't it great?

432
00:36:15,217 --> 00:36:16,925
Where have you been hiding?

433
00:36:17,344 --> 00:36:18,968
I haven't been hiding.

434
00:36:19,054 --> 00:36:22,138
- I haven't seen you around.
- You been looking?

435
00:36:22,432 --> 00:36:24,140
- Sort of.
- Sort of?

436
00:36:24,684 --> 00:36:26,926
I thought you were still angry with me.

437
00:36:27,604 --> 00:36:30,640
- Why?
- Because of what I said last time I saw you.

438
00:36:30,732 --> 00:36:32,689
I've been thinking a lot about that.

439
00:36:32,818 --> 00:36:35,439
I should learn to mind my own business.

440
00:36:35,904 --> 00:36:39,771
No, I think you're right about facing things.
I feel the same way.

441
00:36:40,367 --> 00:36:42,443
I just kind of forgot for a while.

442
00:36:42,577 --> 00:36:45,578
- Thanks for reminding me.
- You're welcome.

443
00:36:47,415 --> 00:36:50,416
He thinks he can do
whatever he wants to people.

444
00:36:51,086 --> 00:36:52,829
- Who?
- Johnny.

445
00:36:53,171 --> 00:36:55,543
I'd love to see him get some
of his own medicine.

446
00:36:55,632 --> 00:36:57,708
What goes around comes around.

447
00:36:57,884 --> 00:37:00,885
- I'd love to be there when it does.
- Me, too.

448
00:37:07,310 --> 00:37:09,184
You want to go outside?

449
00:37:11,148 --> 00:37:12,642
You talked me into it.

450
00:37:18,029 --> 00:37:22,407
- That chicken is wild!
- That guy's using real eggs!

451
00:37:22,534 --> 00:37:24,028
He's great!

452
00:37:24,369 --> 00:37:25,567
No!

453
00:37:32,544 --> 00:37:33,789
Johnny!

454
00:37:38,341 --> 00:37:39,421
Johnny!

455
00:37:43,555 --> 00:37:45,678
- Got that number rolled?
- In a minute.

456
00:37:45,766 --> 00:37:48,173
I'm going to get the guys. Hurry up.

457
00:38:45,867 --> 00:38:47,148
Shit!

458
00:38:47,869 --> 00:38:49,613
Move, man!

459
00:38:54,876 --> 00:38:56,785
Johnny, what's up?

460
00:38:58,880 --> 00:39:01,585
Get out of my way!

461
00:39:02,008 --> 00:39:04,464
- What's wrong?
- It's coming around.

462
00:39:11,059 --> 00:39:12,055
Get up!

463
00:39:14,771 --> 00:39:15,934
Get out of my way!

464
00:39:23,989 --> 00:39:26,147
What the hell are you doing?

465
00:39:26,908 --> 00:39:28,403
Get out of the way!

466
00:40:03,904 --> 00:40:05,564
You ain't going nowhere.

467
00:40:10,786 --> 00:40:12,612
You little wimp!

468
00:40:15,290 --> 00:40:18,493
You couldn't leave well enough alone,
could you, little twerp?

469
00:40:18,627 --> 00:40:21,663
No, you had to push it.
Well, now you're gonna pay!

470
00:40:24,424 --> 00:40:26,583
Where are you going, sweetheart?

471
00:40:26,843 --> 00:40:29,002
How about a front kick, Johnny?

472
00:40:33,517 --> 00:40:34,631
Get him up.

473
00:40:34,726 --> 00:40:36,849
- He's had enough.
- Shut up!

474
00:40:36,937 --> 00:40:40,804
- He can't even stand up.
- That don't mean squat.

475
00:40:41,233 --> 00:40:45,277
- Johnny, he's had enough.
- I'll decide when he's had enough.

476
00:40:45,362 --> 00:40:47,236
What's wrong with you, Johnny?

477
00:40:47,364 --> 00:40:50,484
- An enemy deserves no mercy.
- Right!

478
00:40:51,034 --> 00:40:52,694
You're crazy, man!

479
00:40:57,791 --> 00:40:59,415
Get him!

480
00:41:28,905 --> 00:41:30,234
<i>Daniel-san.</i>

481
00:41:31,741 --> 00:41:32,821
Come.

482
00:42:15,368 --> 00:42:16,567
Leave on.

483
00:42:17,329 --> 00:42:20,449
- It stinks. What is it?
- Smell bad, heal good.

484
00:42:25,170 --> 00:42:27,459
- Where did Spider-Man go?
- Who?

485
00:42:28,048 --> 00:42:30,373
The guy who bailed me out.
Where'd he go?

486
00:42:34,429 --> 00:42:35,508
What, you?

487
00:42:37,849 --> 00:42:40,340
- No way.
- Why "no way"?

488
00:42:40,435 --> 00:42:43,638
- Because...
- Because, old man?

489
00:42:44,898 --> 00:42:46,061
Have tea.

490
00:42:46,650 --> 00:42:47,812
Feel better.

491
00:43:14,094 --> 00:43:15,588
Why didn't you tell me?

492
00:43:15,720 --> 00:43:18,046
- Tell you what?
- That you do karate.

493
00:43:18,890 --> 00:43:21,262
- You never ask.
- Where'd you learn it?

494
00:43:21,852 --> 00:43:22,883
Father.

495
00:43:23,437 --> 00:43:25,476
I thought he was a fisherman.

496
00:43:26,481 --> 00:43:29,233
In Okinawa, all Miyagi know two things:

497
00:43:29,776 --> 00:43:31,733
Fish and karate.

498
00:43:32,195 --> 00:43:35,030
Karate come from China, 16th century.

499
00:43:35,740 --> 00:43:37,780
<i>Called "te," hand.</i>

500
00:43:38,577 --> 00:43:39,987
Much later...

501
00:43:40,579 --> 00:43:45,739
...Miyagi ancestors call "karate,"
empty hand.

502
00:43:47,210 --> 00:43:50,211
I always thought it came
from Buddhist temples.

503
00:43:51,047 --> 00:43:53,123
You, too much TV.

504
00:43:54,134 --> 00:43:56,210
That's what my mother tells me.

505
00:44:00,432 --> 00:44:03,349
- Have you ever taught anyone?
- No.

506
00:44:03,435 --> 00:44:04,514
Would you?

507
00:44:05,270 --> 00:44:07,144
- It depend.
- On what?

508
00:44:07,647 --> 00:44:08,679
Reason.

509
00:44:09,775 --> 00:44:11,185
How's revenge?

510
00:44:13,403 --> 00:44:17,982
You look for revenge that way,
start by digging two graves.

511
00:44:18,992 --> 00:44:21,281
At least I'd have company, right?

512
00:44:21,453 --> 00:44:24,822
Fighting always last answer to problem.

513
00:44:25,791 --> 00:44:28,827
Mr. Miyagi, I don't think
you understand my problem.

514
00:44:28,919 --> 00:44:32,122
Miyagi understand problem perfect.

515
00:44:33,256 --> 00:44:37,206
Your friend all karate student?

516
00:44:37,969 --> 00:44:40,092
Friends? Yeah, those guys.

517
00:44:40,180 --> 00:44:41,722
Problem attitude.

518
00:44:42,307 --> 00:44:45,972
The problem is I keep getting
my ass kicked.

519
00:44:46,186 --> 00:44:49,934
Because boys have bad attitude.

520
00:44:50,899 --> 00:44:53,271
Karate for defence only.

521
00:44:54,486 --> 00:44:56,811
That's not what these guys are taught.

522
00:44:57,364 --> 00:44:58,941
I can see.

523
00:44:59,658 --> 00:45:03,358
No such thing bad student,
only bad teacher.

524
00:45:03,870 --> 00:45:06,159
Teacher say, student do.

525
00:45:07,415 --> 00:45:09,040
Great, that solves everything.

526
00:45:09,126 --> 00:45:13,289
I'll go to the school and straighten it out
with the teacher.

527
00:45:13,755 --> 00:45:17,207
Now use head
for something other than target.

528
00:45:18,552 --> 00:45:21,553
- I was only kidding.
- Why kidding?

529
00:45:22,139 --> 00:45:24,262
I get killed if I show up there.

530
00:45:25,225 --> 00:45:26,803
Get killed anyway.

531
00:45:32,566 --> 00:45:34,143
Would you go with me?

532
00:45:35,777 --> 00:45:37,022
No, I can't.

533
00:45:37,612 --> 00:45:39,404
Why? You said it was a good idea.

534
00:45:39,531 --> 00:45:41,322
For you, good idea.

535
00:45:41,408 --> 00:45:44,362
For me, good idea no get involved.

536
00:45:44,453 --> 00:45:46,908
But you're already involved.

537
00:45:47,038 --> 00:45:48,497
- Very sorry.
- What?

538
00:45:54,588 --> 00:45:56,627
Thanks for nothing then.

539
00:45:57,090 --> 00:45:59,925
Like I didn't have enough problems already.

540
00:46:01,470 --> 00:46:05,004
Now I've got to carry your weight, too.
Don't do me any more favours.

541
00:46:05,098 --> 00:46:07,470
<i>- Daniel-san.</i>
<i>- What?</i>

542
00:46:11,104 --> 00:46:13,393
Okay, I go.

543
00:46:15,650 --> 00:46:18,770
- Excellent, Mr. Miyagi.
- Miyagi.

544
00:46:19,905 --> 00:46:21,019
Miyagi.

545
00:46:21,364 --> 00:46:23,274
What kind of belt do you have?

546
00:46:24,034 --> 00:46:25,113
Canvas.

547
00:46:25,368 --> 00:46:26,483
You like?

548
00:46:27,078 --> 00:46:29,036
J.C. Penney. $3.98.

549
00:46:29,748 --> 00:46:30,827
I meant...

550
00:46:30,957 --> 00:46:34,208
In Okinawa a belt means
no need rope hold up pants.

551
00:46:37,089 --> 00:46:38,880
That's funny.

552
00:46:39,049 --> 00:46:40,709
<i>- Daniel-san.</i>
<i>- What?</i>

553
00:46:42,511 --> 00:46:44,966
Karate here.

554
00:46:46,765 --> 00:46:48,508
Karate here.

555
00:46:49,267 --> 00:46:51,675
Karate never here.

556
00:46:53,271 --> 00:46:54,682
You understand?

557
00:46:56,650 --> 00:46:57,764
I think so.

558
00:46:59,945 --> 00:47:01,653
<i>Goodnight, Daniel-san.</i>

559
00:47:02,864 --> 00:47:05,320
Goodnight, Mr. Miyagi. Miyagi!

560
00:47:06,409 --> 00:47:07,868
Tomorrow morning?

561
00:47:08,245 --> 00:47:09,905
10:00.

562
00:47:15,836 --> 00:47:19,785
Thanks for helping me out
with my friends out there.

563
00:47:33,270 --> 00:47:37,682
- Good morning, Mr. Miyagi.
- How do you feel?

564
00:47:37,774 --> 00:47:42,104
- A little sore.
- You know how drive?

565
00:47:42,195 --> 00:47:44,271
Yeah, I do.

566
00:47:45,323 --> 00:47:49,487
- No, I'm not very good at it.
- Me neither.

567
00:47:49,578 --> 00:47:51,570
I don't have a licence.

568
00:47:51,872 --> 00:47:53,152
Me neither.

569
00:47:53,957 --> 00:47:56,828
I guess it's okay then.

570
00:48:34,331 --> 00:48:37,036
You lose concentration
in a fight and you're dead meat!

571
00:48:37,125 --> 00:48:38,288
<i>- Yes, Sensei.</i>
<i>- What?</i>

572
00:48:38,376 --> 00:48:39,539
<i>Yes, Sensei!</i>

573
00:48:41,129 --> 00:48:42,292
Get up!

574
00:48:44,216 --> 00:48:46,920
Give me 60 pushups on your knuckles.

575
00:48:51,014 --> 00:48:52,259
Combat!

576
00:49:02,400 --> 00:49:04,358
Brown. Robertson.

577
00:49:15,372 --> 00:49:16,534
On guard.

578
00:49:22,212 --> 00:49:23,754
Point. Round kick.

579
00:49:24,089 --> 00:49:26,295
What are you looking at? Finish him!

580
00:49:28,218 --> 00:49:29,593
Return.

581
00:49:32,556 --> 00:49:34,014
Prepare.

582
00:49:37,436 --> 00:49:40,721
We do not train to be merciful, here.
Mercy is for the weak.

583
00:49:41,565 --> 00:49:44,435
Here, on the street, in competition...

584
00:49:44,526 --> 00:49:46,519
...a man confronts you, he is the enemy.

585
00:49:46,611 --> 00:49:50,395
An enemy deserves no mercy.
What is the problem, Mr. Lawrence?

586
00:49:53,869 --> 00:49:55,612
Come on, let's forget this.

587
00:49:56,329 --> 00:49:58,203
Wait, not yet.

588
00:50:00,375 --> 00:50:03,127
Class, we have visitors. Fall in behind me.

589
00:50:10,844 --> 00:50:13,417
I hear you jumped
some of my students last night.

590
00:50:14,014 --> 00:50:16,256
Afraid the facts mixed up.

591
00:50:16,975 --> 00:50:18,517
Are you calling him a liar?

592
00:50:19,019 --> 00:50:20,846
No call no one nothing.

593
00:50:21,104 --> 00:50:23,144
What are you here for, old man?

594
00:50:23,231 --> 00:50:25,473
Come ask leave boy alone.

595
00:50:26,401 --> 00:50:28,857
Can't the boy take care of himself?

596
00:50:28,987 --> 00:50:30,730
One-to-one problem, yes.

597
00:50:31,323 --> 00:50:34,573
Five-to-one problem, too much ask anyone.

598
00:50:34,701 --> 00:50:37,073
Is that what's bothering you, the odds?

599
00:50:37,537 --> 00:50:39,329
Well, we can fix that.

600
00:50:39,748 --> 00:50:42,155
<i>- Feel like matching, Mr. Lawrence?</i>
<i>- Yes, Sensei!</i>

601
00:50:42,292 --> 00:50:43,537
No more fighting.

602
00:50:43,627 --> 00:50:46,034
<i>This is a karate dojo, not a knitting class.</i>

603
00:50:46,171 --> 00:50:49,338
You don't come in here,
drop a challenge and leave, old man.

604
00:50:50,175 --> 00:50:53,211
You get your boy on the mat,
or you and I will have a problem.

605
00:50:53,303 --> 00:50:56,553
<i>Too much advantage, your dojo.</i>

606
00:50:57,557 --> 00:50:59,052
Name a place.

607
00:50:59,726 --> 00:51:01,007
Tournament.

608
00:51:05,565 --> 00:51:08,519
You've got real nerve, old man.

609
00:51:09,903 --> 00:51:11,943
But I think we can accommodate you.

610
00:51:12,697 --> 00:51:14,524
Can't we, Mr. Lawrence?

611
00:51:14,699 --> 00:51:16,158
<i>Yes, Sensei.</i>

612
00:51:16,952 --> 00:51:18,031
Fall in.

613
00:51:22,707 --> 00:51:25,115
Ask one more small request.

614
00:51:25,836 --> 00:51:27,246
Make it fast.

615
00:51:27,587 --> 00:51:30,624
Ask leave boy alone to train.

616
00:51:31,800 --> 00:51:34,255
You're a pushy little bastard, ain't you?

617
00:51:34,344 --> 00:51:36,337
But I like that.

618
00:51:40,225 --> 00:51:43,309
No one touches the prima donna
until the tournament.

619
00:51:43,437 --> 00:51:46,770
<i>- Is that understood?</i>
<i>- Yes, Sensei!</i>

620
00:51:48,608 --> 00:51:50,186
But if you don't show...

621
00:51:51,695 --> 00:51:53,272
...then it's open season...

622
00:51:55,323 --> 00:51:56,604
...on him...

623
00:51:58,368 --> 00:51:59,649
...and you.

624
00:52:26,271 --> 00:52:27,813
I can't believe this.

625
00:52:28,482 --> 00:52:30,439
- I cannot believe this!
- What?

626
00:52:30,525 --> 00:52:33,894
What you just got me into.
You said you'd make things better.

627
00:52:33,987 --> 00:52:36,145
- I did.
- How?

628
00:52:36,448 --> 00:52:40,066
How? I saved you two months of beating.

629
00:52:40,786 --> 00:52:43,786
Great, now I've got something
to look forward to.

630
00:52:48,752 --> 00:52:50,910
How much further is your house?

631
00:52:51,755 --> 00:52:53,463
Other side tracks.

632
00:52:53,715 --> 00:52:55,957
Are you in the oil business, too?

633
00:52:56,885 --> 00:52:59,590
Not everything is as seem.

634
00:52:59,679 --> 00:53:02,253
Reminds me of Newark.
What are we going to do here?

635
00:53:02,349 --> 00:53:03,843
Start training.

636
00:53:04,267 --> 00:53:05,810
Much work be done.

637
00:53:06,019 --> 00:53:08,178
Tournament here before you know it.

638
00:53:08,605 --> 00:53:10,348
That's what I'm afraid of.

639
00:53:14,736 --> 00:53:18,604
That teacher was really wacko.
You really think I can beat that guy?

640
00:53:18,698 --> 00:53:20,157
No matter.

641
00:53:20,867 --> 00:53:23,702
Wacko teacher attitude rest in fist.

642
00:53:23,870 --> 00:53:25,779
Stupid, but fact of life.

643
00:53:25,872 --> 00:53:27,699
Win, lose, no matter.

644
00:53:27,999 --> 00:53:30,704
You make good fight, earn respect.

645
00:53:30,961 --> 00:53:34,709
- Then nobody bother.
- They'll bury me where I fall.

646
00:53:35,507 --> 00:53:39,718
Either way, problem solved.
Wait right here.

647
00:53:48,770 --> 00:53:50,099
This is great.

648
00:53:57,737 --> 00:54:01,652
- I forgot to give you this back.
- You keep.

649
00:54:01,741 --> 00:54:02,986
Thanks a lot.

650
00:54:03,785 --> 00:54:06,739
- Ready?
- Yeah, I guess so.

651
00:54:09,708 --> 00:54:11,747
<i>Daniel-san, must talk.</i>

652
00:54:14,045 --> 00:54:15,789
Walk on road.

653
00:54:16,214 --> 00:54:20,710
Walk right side, safe. Walk left side, safe.

654
00:54:21,219 --> 00:54:26,676
Walk middle, sooner or later,
you get squished just like grape.

655
00:54:27,350 --> 00:54:29,426
Here, karate same thing.

656
00:54:29,519 --> 00:54:34,265
Either you karate do, yes, or karate do, no.

657
00:54:34,608 --> 00:54:39,104
You karate do, "guess so," just like grape.

658
00:54:40,238 --> 00:54:41,863
Understand?

659
00:54:43,033 --> 00:54:44,776
Yeah, I understand.

660
00:54:45,744 --> 00:54:47,286
Ready?

661
00:54:48,413 --> 00:54:49,742
Yeah, I'm ready.

662
00:54:49,915 --> 00:54:51,325
Yes.

663
00:54:53,627 --> 00:54:56,082
First make sacred pact.

664
00:54:57,339 --> 00:55:02,084
I promise teach karate. That's my part.

665
00:55:02,385 --> 00:55:09,633
You promise learn. I say, you do,
no questions. That's your part.

666
00:55:11,103 --> 00:55:12,301
Deal?

667
00:55:12,938 --> 00:55:14,480
It's a deal.

668
00:55:19,361 --> 00:55:23,061
First wash all the cars, then wax.

669
00:55:23,615 --> 00:55:28,076
- Why do I have to...
- Remember deal. No questions.

670
00:55:28,328 --> 00:55:30,285
Yeah, but...

671
00:55:31,206 --> 00:55:36,164
Wax on right hand. Wax off left hand.

672
00:55:36,545 --> 00:55:39,415
Wax on, wax off.

673
00:55:39,714 --> 00:55:43,249
Breathe in through nose,
out through mouth.

674
00:55:44,469 --> 00:55:47,091
Wax on, wax off.

675
00:55:47,180 --> 00:55:49,885
Don't forget to breathe. Very important.

676
00:55:50,142 --> 00:55:52,929
Wax on, wax off.

677
00:55:53,228 --> 00:55:55,517
Wax on, wax off.

678
00:55:55,605 --> 00:55:57,349
Where did these cars come from?

679
00:55:58,525 --> 00:55:59,900
Detroit.

680
00:56:18,587 --> 00:56:20,081
Wax on...

681
00:56:20,839 --> 00:56:22,796
...right hand make circle.

682
00:56:22,883 --> 00:56:25,670
Wax off, left hand make circle.

683
00:56:25,969 --> 00:56:28,970
Wax on, wax off.

684
00:56:29,264 --> 00:56:32,384
Breathe in, breathe out.

685
00:56:32,642 --> 00:56:35,679
Wax on, wax off.

686
00:57:08,678 --> 00:57:11,252
Mr. Miyagi, I'm finished.

687
00:57:12,474 --> 00:57:14,217
You want to check these out?

688
00:57:15,560 --> 00:57:16,841
Mr. Miyagi?

689
00:57:19,106 --> 00:57:20,185
Mr. Miyagi?

690
00:57:27,322 --> 00:57:28,567
Hello?

691
00:58:05,485 --> 00:58:08,190
I've been looking all over for you.
Where've you been?

692
00:58:08,321 --> 00:58:10,563
- I don't believe it.
- What?

693
00:58:10,782 --> 00:58:14,032
- Where are you going?
- I'm going to find that idiot.

694
00:58:14,119 --> 00:58:16,824
- No, it's been taken care of.
- Until next time.

695
00:58:16,955 --> 00:58:19,790
- There isn't going to be a "next time."
- There they are.

696
00:58:20,459 --> 00:58:24,041
Watch this.
Hey, guys, it's good to see you.

697
00:58:24,588 --> 00:58:27,292
Sorry about your eye, Johnny.
Your shoulder okay, Tommy?

698
00:58:27,507 --> 00:58:30,461
You guys be careful not to step
in front of any more buses.

699
00:58:31,386 --> 00:58:34,838
<i>Hold it. Remember what Sensei said?</i>
<i>Wait for the tournament.</i>

700
00:58:34,931 --> 00:58:37,304
It must be "Take a Worm for a Walk" week.

701
00:58:39,936 --> 00:58:41,479
You did all that damage?

702
00:58:41,563 --> 00:58:44,315
When you make a wish in the shower,
it always comes true.

703
00:58:44,399 --> 00:58:47,566
- I should have kept my mouth shut.
- No, we've got an agreement.

704
00:58:47,652 --> 00:58:49,312
Yeah? What's that?

705
00:58:49,404 --> 00:58:54,113
They agreed not to beat up on me
and I promised not to bleed on them.

706
00:58:54,993 --> 00:58:57,662
- I don't believe you.
- What can I do, moan and groan?

707
00:58:57,746 --> 00:59:01,162
- Anybody else would.
- Who'd listen anyway?

708
00:59:01,291 --> 00:59:02,370
Me.

709
00:59:03,543 --> 00:59:04,954
Really?

710
00:59:06,004 --> 00:59:10,084
- You feel like listening on Saturday night?
- Sure.

711
00:59:10,425 --> 00:59:12,465
Great! So Saturday night...

712
00:59:12,552 --> 00:59:16,052
...we'll go out, we'll have a good time.
We'll do whatever.

713
00:59:17,307 --> 00:59:20,059
- Is that your address?
- You got it.

714
00:59:21,019 --> 00:59:22,513
Where is this?

715
00:59:23,355 --> 00:59:25,146
- I've got to go.
- Okay.

716
00:59:25,232 --> 00:59:28,233
I'll talk to you later. Great.

717
00:59:29,111 --> 00:59:30,309
All right.

718
00:59:33,865 --> 00:59:38,326
Mr. Harris, can I talk to you?
LaRusso. Third period history class.

719
00:59:38,453 --> 00:59:43,744
I wanted to tell you, I really got a lot
out of that lecture about the Indians.

720
00:59:44,168 --> 00:59:49,210
I was telling my buddies about it.
Could you give us a quick review?

721
00:59:49,298 --> 00:59:51,872
- Sure, I'm free this period.
- Great for me.

722
00:59:51,968 --> 00:59:54,506
No, I got to go.

723
00:59:54,929 --> 00:59:58,380
I guess that leaves you and me,
but that's all right.

724
00:59:58,474 --> 01:00:00,930
You can tell them about it later.

725
01:00:01,018 --> 01:00:05,265
The Plains Indians
were a very primitive tribe...

726
01:00:19,162 --> 01:00:20,656
Come on, Casanova.

727
01:00:48,191 --> 01:00:50,598
- Hi, how are you doing?
- Good.

728
01:00:50,693 --> 01:00:53,018
- You look nice.
- Thank you.

729
01:00:53,196 --> 01:00:54,939
You've got company.

730
01:00:55,031 --> 01:00:58,447
Those are my parents.
Come on, I want you to meet them.

731
01:00:58,576 --> 01:01:00,035
Great.

732
01:01:00,661 --> 01:01:02,453
- Hello, sweetheart.
- Hi, Dad.

733
01:01:02,538 --> 01:01:04,946
This is Daniel LaRusso.

734
01:01:05,041 --> 01:01:08,042
- My parents, Mr. And Mrs. Mills.
- How do you do, Daniel?

735
01:01:09,087 --> 01:01:11,245
- Hello, Daniel.
- Nice to meet you.

736
01:01:11,339 --> 01:01:14,375
- Where are you going?
- I don't know. Where are we going?

737
01:01:14,467 --> 01:01:16,258
I don't know. Wherever you want.

738
01:01:16,344 --> 01:01:19,594
- Golf N' Stuff?
- We're going to Golf N' Stuff, then.

739
01:01:20,640 --> 01:01:23,557
Don't worry about that.
Weren't you going to have that fixed?

740
01:01:23,643 --> 01:01:25,600
I am. I was. I will.

741
01:01:25,728 --> 01:01:29,643
- You live in Encino, Daniel?
- Encino? No.

742
01:01:30,274 --> 01:01:34,355
- Where do you live?
- Out, like Reseda.

743
01:01:36,072 --> 01:01:39,690
- And that's your mother?
- Yeah, that's her.

744
01:01:39,784 --> 01:01:41,064
Hi!

745
01:01:41,452 --> 01:01:44,323
She's waiting for us.
We'd better go. Nice to meet you.

746
01:01:44,414 --> 01:01:47,118
- Not too late, sweetheart.
- Okay, Dad.

747
01:01:51,796 --> 01:01:56,339
- Hi, Mrs. LaRusso. I'm Ali.
- Hi, Ali. Call me Lucille.

748
01:01:57,301 --> 01:02:00,219
- That's a beautiful house you have.
- Thanks.

749
01:02:07,645 --> 01:02:09,223
- Can you drive a stick?
- Yeah.

750
01:02:09,897 --> 01:02:13,812
Put it into second, let it roll,
and when I say "pop it," pop it.

751
01:02:13,943 --> 01:02:15,022
"Pop it."

752
01:02:20,408 --> 01:02:22,733
Don't worry, it's all under control.

753
01:02:23,453 --> 01:02:26,453
She's cute. It happens a lot.

754
01:02:26,831 --> 01:02:31,042
Okay, LaRusso, push! On, you huskies!

755
01:02:31,169 --> 01:02:33,375
Okay, pop it!

756
01:02:34,088 --> 01:02:36,496
We got it on the first!

757
01:02:54,776 --> 01:02:58,987
I'll pick you up at 11:00.
Please, don't be late. Have fun.

758
01:03:02,450 --> 01:03:06,863
- Look at that slide.
- We'll do that next time.

759
01:03:07,872 --> 01:03:10,789
- Why next time?
- You need a bathing suit.

760
01:03:11,459 --> 01:03:14,211
Oh, yeah. Bathing suits.

761
01:03:14,295 --> 01:03:18,459
- Do you play hockey?
- Not professionally.

762
01:04:22,113 --> 01:04:24,734
This is the best time
I've had since I've been here.

763
01:04:24,824 --> 01:04:27,741
- We'll have to do it again.
- Definitely.

764
01:04:28,244 --> 01:04:30,153
Hey, good looking. How are you?

765
01:04:30,288 --> 01:04:31,782
Good. This is cool.

766
01:04:31,873 --> 01:04:34,874
- I just got it. You want a ride?
- Some other time.

767
01:04:35,126 --> 01:04:38,127
- Are you sure?
- Daniel, this is Eddie. Eddie, Daniel.

768
01:04:38,254 --> 01:04:40,081
- How are you doing, Daniel?
- Good.

769
01:04:40,173 --> 01:04:43,339
- Hey, Ali! How's it going?
- Hi, guys.

770
01:04:43,426 --> 01:04:46,629
- How are you doing?
- Want to come with us?

771
01:04:46,763 --> 01:04:50,214
No, I don't think so.
You guys have a good time.

772
01:04:50,308 --> 01:04:52,597
- We'll make room.
- I'll call you tomorrow.

773
01:04:52,685 --> 01:04:55,390
Your little friend can come,
if it's okay with his mommy.

774
01:04:55,480 --> 01:04:56,760
Hi, kids.

775
01:04:57,190 --> 01:05:02,017
- Hey, Mommy, can Daniel come for a ride?
- I really like your car.

776
01:05:10,453 --> 01:05:13,869
- You could've gone.
- I didn't want to.

777
01:05:14,290 --> 01:05:18,952
- It's no big deal.
- Lf I'd wanted to go, I would have.

778
01:05:19,837 --> 01:05:23,206
It makes no difference to me.
Do what you want, I don't care.

779
01:05:55,540 --> 01:05:57,200
This is beautiful.

780
01:06:01,087 --> 01:06:06,164
Mr. Miyagi, this is great.
You've got real fish in there.

781
01:06:08,636 --> 01:06:10,427
This is outrageous.

782
01:06:11,389 --> 01:06:15,600
I thought Chung Lee's restaurant was nice.
You beat his act.

783
01:06:15,685 --> 01:06:18,555
This is paradise. Did you do this yourself?

784
01:06:20,148 --> 01:06:21,642
Are these bongos?

785
01:06:22,024 --> 01:06:23,816
No, I got it.

786
01:06:23,985 --> 01:06:27,484
<i>"Hare Krishna"</i>

787
01:06:27,697 --> 01:06:29,654
<i>Daniel-san, you much humour.</i>

788
01:06:29,741 --> 01:06:32,410
- What are these?
- Japanese sander.

789
01:06:32,744 --> 01:06:35,947
- What do you do with them?
- Funny you should ask.

790
01:06:38,875 --> 01:06:40,417
Right circle.

791
01:06:41,836 --> 01:06:43,378
Left circle.

792
01:06:44,464 --> 01:06:48,508
- It'd be easier going back and forth.
- But you go circle.

793
01:06:48,634 --> 01:06:50,177
Right circle.

794
01:06:50,762 --> 01:06:52,304
Left circle.

795
01:06:53,598 --> 01:06:57,548
Right circle, left circle.

796
01:06:58,144 --> 01:07:00,717
Breathe in, breathe out.

797
01:07:01,397 --> 01:07:04,647
Right circle, left circle.

798
01:07:05,234 --> 01:07:07,560
Right circle, left circle.

799
01:07:07,653 --> 01:07:10,061
Breathe in, breathe out.

800
01:07:12,075 --> 01:07:17,661
Whole floor. Right circle, left circle.

801
01:07:18,247 --> 01:07:19,991
Right circle.

802
01:07:20,541 --> 01:07:22,368
Left circle.

803
01:07:22,752 --> 01:07:26,037
Breathe in, breathe out.

804
01:07:44,816 --> 01:07:46,310
Very good.

805
01:07:48,027 --> 01:07:50,150
Splinters all gone.

806
01:07:53,241 --> 01:07:54,865
I'm finished.

807
01:07:55,535 --> 01:07:57,860
Mr. Miyagi, I'm beat.

808
01:07:58,704 --> 01:08:00,163
My shoulders.

809
01:08:00,581 --> 01:08:01,613
Good.

810
01:08:02,417 --> 01:08:04,374
Go home, get rest.

811
01:08:04,752 --> 01:08:08,667
Come morning, start early. 6:00.

812
01:08:58,264 --> 01:09:00,304
Wouldn't a fly swatter be easier?

813
01:09:01,309 --> 01:09:06,184
Man who catch fly with chopsticks,
accomplish anything.

814
01:09:08,316 --> 01:09:09,893
Did you ever catch one?

815
01:09:10,234 --> 01:09:11,729
Not yet.

816
01:09:14,697 --> 01:09:15,978
Could I try?

817
01:09:17,533 --> 01:09:18,778
If wish.

818
01:09:44,936 --> 01:09:46,928
Hey, Mr. Miyagi, look!

819
01:09:54,445 --> 01:09:56,354
You, beginner luck.

820
01:09:58,408 --> 01:10:03,116
I guess that means I can accomplish
anything, right? No sweat.

821
01:10:03,371 --> 01:10:07,071
First you accomplish paint fence.

822
01:10:18,928 --> 01:10:20,588
All in wrist.

823
01:10:21,556 --> 01:10:25,055
Wrist up. Wrist down.

824
01:10:26,185 --> 01:10:31,310
All in wrist. Up, down, long stroke.

825
01:10:31,399 --> 01:10:34,519
Very good. Up, down.

826
01:10:34,902 --> 01:10:37,061
No look me, look fence.

827
01:10:38,197 --> 01:10:39,229
Up...

828
01:10:40,408 --> 01:10:41,439
...down.

829
01:10:42,660 --> 01:10:46,528
Bend the wrist. Downstroke, you bend.
See? Good.

830
01:10:46,622 --> 01:10:50,241
Long stroke. Up, down. Very good.

831
01:10:50,334 --> 01:10:52,660
Bend your knees. Down.

832
01:10:52,795 --> 01:10:53,874
Up.

833
01:10:55,548 --> 01:10:58,039
<i>Very good, Daniel-san.</i>
<i>Don't forget to breathe.</i>

834
01:10:58,176 --> 01:10:59,967
In, out.

835
01:11:00,053 --> 01:11:01,084
Up...

836
01:11:02,263 --> 01:11:03,378
...down.

837
01:11:05,099 --> 01:11:07,804
Up, down.

838
01:11:08,186 --> 01:11:09,217
Up...

839
01:11:10,021 --> 01:11:11,052
...down.

840
01:11:11,773 --> 01:11:12,804
Up...

841
01:11:13,441 --> 01:11:14,472
...down.

842
01:11:19,363 --> 01:11:21,023
<i>Very good, Daniel-san.</i>

843
01:11:21,282 --> 01:11:23,440
Up, down.

844
01:11:24,744 --> 01:11:26,155
Up...

845
01:11:27,371 --> 01:11:28,830
...down.

846
01:11:34,337 --> 01:11:37,670
Small board, left hand.
Big board, right hand.

847
01:11:37,924 --> 01:11:41,423
- I'm almost done.
- All of fence.

848
01:11:45,556 --> 01:11:50,384
Big board, right hand.
Small board, left hand.

849
01:11:50,812 --> 01:11:52,769
Up, down.

850
01:11:53,815 --> 01:11:55,891
Up, down.

851
01:12:15,336 --> 01:12:16,617
All finished.

852
01:12:17,046 --> 01:12:18,671
It looks pretty good, huh?

853
01:12:19,507 --> 01:12:20,882
Both sides?

854
01:12:25,054 --> 01:12:26,217
Not yet.

855
01:12:42,488 --> 01:12:46,023
<i>Daniel-san. Very good job.</i>

856
01:12:47,660 --> 01:12:49,617
Come morning. Start early.

857
01:13:03,051 --> 01:13:04,213
Up...

858
01:13:04,844 --> 01:13:06,089
...down.

859
01:13:06,721 --> 01:13:08,001
Up...

860
01:13:08,264 --> 01:13:09,675
...down.

861
01:13:38,878 --> 01:13:41,583
Damn it! I can't believe this.

862
01:14:02,151 --> 01:14:03,729
Missed spot.

863
01:14:04,153 --> 01:14:05,398
What spot?

864
01:14:05,571 --> 01:14:09,486
- You didn't tell me you were going fishing.
- You not here when I go.

865
01:14:09,659 --> 01:14:13,242
- Maybe I wanted to go.
- You karate training.

866
01:14:13,329 --> 01:14:16,164
I'm what? I'm being your goddamn slave!

867
01:14:16,249 --> 01:14:18,288
- We made a deal here.
- So?

868
01:14:18,376 --> 01:14:21,330
"So"? You're supposed to teach
and I'm supposed to learn.

869
01:14:21,462 --> 01:14:24,665
Four days I've been busting my ass,
I haven't learned a thing.

870
01:14:24,757 --> 01:14:28,007
- You learn plenty.
- I've learned to sand your decks.

871
01:14:28,094 --> 01:14:31,463
I've waxed your car, I paint your house,
paint your fence.

872
01:14:31,556 --> 01:14:35,470
- Not everything is as seems.
- Bullshit! I'm going home, man.

873
01:14:36,185 --> 01:14:38,142
<i>Daniel-san!</i>

874
01:14:39,272 --> 01:14:41,063
- What?
- Come here.

875
01:14:46,654 --> 01:14:50,782
- Show me sand the floor.
- I can't move my arm, all right?

876
01:14:56,080 --> 01:14:57,361
What are you doing?

877
01:15:03,046 --> 01:15:04,326
What are you doing?

878
01:15:06,049 --> 01:15:10,545
- Now show me sand the floor.
- How did you do that?

879
01:15:10,803 --> 01:15:11,835
Show!

880
01:15:14,974 --> 01:15:16,599
Sand the floor?

881
01:15:19,854 --> 01:15:21,432
Stand up.

882
01:15:23,357 --> 01:15:26,145
Show me sand the floor.

883
01:15:29,155 --> 01:15:30,898
Sand the floor.

884
01:15:31,699 --> 01:15:32,944
Sand the floor.

885
01:15:33,576 --> 01:15:35,699
Big circle. Sand the floor.

886
01:15:36,871 --> 01:15:38,246
Sand the floor.

887
01:15:40,666 --> 01:15:44,166
Now show me wax on, wax off.

888
01:15:52,178 --> 01:15:55,214
- Wax on, wax off.
- "Wax on, wax off!"

889
01:15:55,306 --> 01:15:56,421
Wax on...

890
01:15:57,016 --> 01:15:58,131
...wax off.

891
01:15:59,018 --> 01:16:01,474
Concentrate. Look in my eyes.

892
01:16:01,604 --> 01:16:04,060
Lock your hand, thumb inside.

893
01:16:04,357 --> 01:16:06,100
Wax on...

894
01:16:06,401 --> 01:16:08,144
...wax off.

895
01:16:08,444 --> 01:16:09,725
Wax on...

896
01:16:10,696 --> 01:16:12,239
...wax off.

897
01:16:13,699 --> 01:16:14,898
Wax on.

898
01:16:16,077 --> 01:16:17,322
Wax off.

899
01:16:19,789 --> 01:16:23,039
Show me paint the fence. Up, down.

900
01:16:25,545 --> 01:16:26,624
Up.

901
01:16:27,255 --> 01:16:28,286
Down.

902
01:16:28,715 --> 01:16:29,746
Up.

903
01:16:30,133 --> 01:16:31,212
Down.

904
01:16:31,384 --> 01:16:34,338
Other side. Look eye. Always look eye!

905
01:16:34,887 --> 01:16:37,046
Show me paint the house. Side, side.

906
01:16:41,394 --> 01:16:44,763
Lock wrist. Side, side.

907
01:16:45,732 --> 01:16:46,930
Side, side.

908
01:16:48,359 --> 01:16:51,064
Show me wax on, wax off.

909
01:16:58,119 --> 01:17:00,076
Show me paint the fence.

910
01:17:05,209 --> 01:17:07,416
Show me side, side.

911
01:17:12,300 --> 01:17:14,423
Show me sand the floor.

912
01:17:33,529 --> 01:17:36,400
Look eye! Always look eye.

913
01:17:37,575 --> 01:17:39,532
Come back tomorrow.

914
01:18:26,833 --> 01:18:30,913
Learn balance. Go water, kick.
Learn balance.

915
01:20:14,023 --> 01:20:16,479
What were you doing on those stumps?

916
01:20:16,859 --> 01:20:19,813
- Called crane technique.
- Does it work?

917
01:20:20,279 --> 01:20:22,817
If do right, no can defence.

918
01:20:23,116 --> 01:20:24,658
Could you teach me?

919
01:20:24,826 --> 01:20:27,827
First learn stand, then learn fly.

920
01:20:28,246 --> 01:20:32,290
<i>- Nature rule, Daniel-san, not mine.</i>
<i>- Who taught you?</i>

921
01:20:32,417 --> 01:20:36,165
- Father teach.
- You must have had some father.

922
01:20:37,338 --> 01:20:41,550
- Look, the kid's got a pet Nip.
- He know any tricks, kid?

923
01:20:42,927 --> 01:20:46,545
Excuse, please. Boy cold, must leave.

924
01:20:46,639 --> 01:20:49,260
Kindly remove bottle.

925
01:20:52,395 --> 01:20:55,562
Kindly do it yourself, Mr. Moto.

926
01:21:06,325 --> 01:21:08,484
How did you do that?

927
01:21:08,578 --> 01:21:11,495
Don't know. First time.

928
01:21:16,044 --> 01:21:18,001
Hey, you!

929
01:21:26,846 --> 01:21:31,425
- Hey, not bad. Definitely varsity material.
- You let me.

930
01:21:31,642 --> 01:21:37,597
Should we try the slide on Friday?
I could pick you up about 7:00.

931
01:21:37,940 --> 01:21:40,776
I'm having dinner with my parents
at the country club.

932
01:21:40,860 --> 01:21:43,647
I'll be done by 9:30. Meet me out front.

933
01:21:43,738 --> 01:21:45,149
- Is that cool?
- Yeah.

934
01:21:45,239 --> 01:21:46,615
Johnny, over here!

935
01:21:48,076 --> 01:21:50,697
- What's the matter?
- It's that little voice again.

936
01:21:50,787 --> 01:21:54,369
Pretend you're deaf.
Encino Oaks Country Club. 9:30.

937
01:21:54,457 --> 01:21:57,126
Friday? Great.

938
01:21:57,251 --> 01:21:59,707
- Hi, Ali.
- "Hi, Ali."

939
01:21:59,796 --> 01:22:01,835
I've got to be nuts.

940
01:22:16,062 --> 01:22:18,814
Okay, here. Stop. Throw anchor.

941
01:22:25,196 --> 01:22:27,485
Good. Stand bow.

942
01:22:30,034 --> 01:22:32,110
Not bow. Bow!

943
01:22:33,329 --> 01:22:35,488
- Up!
- What, up front?

944
01:22:36,040 --> 01:22:37,203
Make block.

945
01:22:38,000 --> 01:22:40,408
Left, right. Up, down.

946
01:22:41,295 --> 01:22:44,380
Side, side. Breathe in, breathe out.

947
01:22:46,008 --> 01:22:47,752
And no scare fish.

948
01:22:52,515 --> 01:22:54,638
When do I learn how to punch?

949
01:22:55,476 --> 01:22:57,385
Better learn balance.

950
01:22:57,812 --> 01:22:59,639
Balance is key.

951
01:22:59,856 --> 01:23:03,900
Balance good, karate good.
Everything good.

952
01:23:04,110 --> 01:23:08,571
Balance bad, better pack up, go home.
Understand?

953
01:23:10,032 --> 01:23:11,443
Yeah, I understand.

954
01:23:16,205 --> 01:23:18,827
Did you ever get into fights
when you were a kid?

955
01:23:19,208 --> 01:23:20,453
Plenty.

956
01:23:20,960 --> 01:23:25,752
- It wasn't like the problem I have, right?
- Fighting, fighting. Same, same.

957
01:23:26,007 --> 01:23:27,834
But you knew karate.

958
01:23:28,342 --> 01:23:31,178
Someone always know more.

959
01:23:31,888 --> 01:23:34,461
There were times
when you were scared to fight?

960
01:23:36,184 --> 01:23:39,303
Always scared. Miyagi hate fighting.

961
01:23:40,188 --> 01:23:43,023
- But you like karate.
- So?

962
01:23:44,150 --> 01:23:46,107
Karate's fighting, you train to fight.

963
01:23:48,279 --> 01:23:49,821
That what you think?

964
01:23:54,118 --> 01:23:55,197
No.

965
01:23:55,328 --> 01:23:56,787
Then why train?

966
01:23:59,165 --> 01:24:00,873
So I won't have to fight.

967
01:24:02,794 --> 01:24:04,703
Miyagi have hope for you.

968
01:24:05,421 --> 01:24:08,541
- When do I learn how to punch?
- Learn how punch...

969
01:24:08,800 --> 01:24:11,635
...when learn how keep dry!
- No!

970
01:24:15,807 --> 01:24:19,057
<i>Daniel-san, you're all wet behind ear!</i>

971
01:24:19,185 --> 01:24:20,928
Are you crazy?

972
01:24:22,230 --> 01:24:23,640
You're crazy.

973
01:24:45,294 --> 01:24:46,872
Trouble with Johnny?

974
01:24:47,255 --> 01:24:50,920
- You two lovebirds having problems?
- We're not lovebirds.

975
01:24:51,050 --> 01:24:55,000
- What time is it?
- It's about 9:40.

976
01:24:55,972 --> 01:24:59,092
- I've got to go.
- Do you have a date?

977
01:25:02,311 --> 01:25:04,470
- With whom?
- A friend.

978
01:25:04,564 --> 01:25:06,806
Not that boy from Reseda.

979
01:25:07,066 --> 01:25:08,975
Yeah, he's from Reseda.

980
01:25:09,068 --> 01:25:11,440
He's a nice guy. It's no big deal.

981
01:25:11,571 --> 01:25:15,153
Honey, you've monopolised
the best-looking man here long enough.

982
01:25:15,992 --> 01:25:17,901
- Hi.
- Hi.

983
01:25:19,954 --> 01:25:23,489
I've been thinking,
maybe we can call a truce.

984
01:25:24,042 --> 01:25:27,042
I'm not at war. Excuse me.

985
01:25:27,336 --> 01:25:29,329
Could we please finish the dance?

986
01:26:32,652 --> 01:26:35,107
Don't you ever do that to me again!

987
01:27:27,874 --> 01:27:30,661
I didn't know you were a singer.
How are you doing?

988
01:27:31,711 --> 01:27:35,874
<i>Daniel-san, come inside.</i>

989
01:27:36,424 --> 01:27:39,840
- What's that song you were singing?
- Japanese blues.

990
01:27:41,721 --> 01:27:42,966
<i>Kampai.</i>

991
01:27:44,599 --> 01:27:45,797
<i>Kampai.</i>

992
01:27:53,691 --> 01:27:55,518
<i>Banzai!</i>

993
01:27:56,819 --> 01:27:58,148
To baby trees.

994
01:27:59,989 --> 01:28:02,860
<i>Not bonsai. Banzai!</i>

995
01:28:03,785 --> 01:28:04,983
<i>Banzai.</i>

996
01:28:05,661 --> 01:28:07,903
<i>Banzai!</i>

997
01:28:08,706 --> 01:28:11,114
<i>- Banzai!</i>
<i>- Close enough.</i>

998
01:28:24,514 --> 01:28:27,847
- What are we celebrating here?
- Anniversary.

999
01:28:29,018 --> 01:28:30,810
Whose anniversary?

1000
01:28:32,939 --> 01:28:35,809
Is this your wife?
I didn't know you were married.

1001
01:28:37,693 --> 01:28:41,359
- Damn beautiful, don't you think?
- Yeah, she's pretty.

1002
01:28:43,616 --> 01:28:45,656
First time I saw her...

1003
01:28:46,327 --> 01:28:49,494
...was cane field, Hawaii.

1004
01:28:51,040 --> 01:28:52,321
Beautiful.

1005
01:28:54,252 --> 01:28:56,458
Damn good cane cutter, too.

1006
01:28:59,674 --> 01:29:01,251
Where is she now?

1007
01:29:03,052 --> 01:29:04,215
Drink, drink.

1008
01:29:13,938 --> 01:29:15,313
<i>Daniel-san.</i>

1009
01:29:17,859 --> 01:29:19,104
Look, look.

1010
01:29:24,407 --> 01:29:28,618
First American-born Miyagi
waiting to be born.

1011
01:29:35,710 --> 01:29:37,418
Drink, drink.

1012
01:29:41,883 --> 01:29:43,377
"Sergeant Miyagi!

1013
01:29:43,843 --> 01:29:44,958
"Yes, sir!

1014
01:29:45,428 --> 01:29:50,054
"Sergeant Miyagi reporting.
Killed many Jerry Germans, sir.

1015
01:29:54,687 --> 01:29:56,312
"Sergeant Miyagi.

1016
01:29:56,647 --> 01:29:57,727
"Yes, sir.

1017
01:29:58,524 --> 01:30:00,481
"Regret to inform...

1018
01:30:00,860 --> 01:30:05,273
"...wife have complications at birth."

1019
01:30:07,450 --> 01:30:10,570
Complications. No doctor came.

1020
01:30:12,914 --> 01:30:15,784
Land of free, home of brave.

1021
01:30:16,167 --> 01:30:17,827
No doctor came.

1022
01:30:35,395 --> 01:30:36,593
Mr. Miyagi.

1023
01:30:40,525 --> 01:30:41,687
Are you okay?

1024
01:31:29,532 --> 01:31:34,573
"We regret to inform you
that on November 2, 1944...

1025
01:31:34,829 --> 01:31:38,530
"...at the Manzanar Relocation Center...

1026
01:31:39,208 --> 01:31:41,616
"...your wife and newborn son died...

1027
01:31:41,711 --> 01:31:46,337
"...due to complications
arising from childbirth."

1028
01:32:24,712 --> 01:32:26,123
"Valour."

1029
01:34:13,863 --> 01:34:15,274
Secret to punch...

1030
01:34:15,698 --> 01:34:18,106
...make power of whole body...

1031
01:34:18,743 --> 01:34:22,242
...fit inside one inch, here.

1032
01:34:23,081 --> 01:34:26,366
Power, whole body, one inch, here.

1033
01:34:26,751 --> 01:34:27,866
Now punch.

1034
01:34:28,211 --> 01:34:29,290
Hard.

1035
01:34:31,547 --> 01:34:34,465
You some kind of girl or something?

1036
01:34:34,842 --> 01:34:38,922
Punch! Drive a punch.
Not just arm. Whole body.

1037
01:34:39,180 --> 01:34:41,671
<i>Hip, leg, drive a punch. Make kiai.</i>

1038
01:34:43,559 --> 01:34:46,679
Give you power. Now drive punch.

1039
01:34:47,105 --> 01:34:49,062
<i>- Kiai.</i>
<i>- Once more.</i>

1040
01:34:50,191 --> 01:34:52,148
<i>- Kiai.</i>
<i>- Once more.</i>

1041
01:34:54,862 --> 01:34:56,522
<i>Very good, Daniel-san.</i>

1042
01:34:58,783 --> 01:35:00,491
Hey, pretty good?

1043
01:35:01,202 --> 01:35:02,613
Look at this.

1044
01:35:05,164 --> 01:35:07,655
<i>Wait. Daniel-san.</i>

1045
01:35:10,920 --> 01:35:12,379
What do you think?

1046
01:35:15,133 --> 01:35:18,418
I tell you what Miyagi think,
I think you dance around too much.

1047
01:35:18,511 --> 01:35:22,046
I think you talk too much.
I think you no concentrate enough.

1048
01:35:22,181 --> 01:35:24,933
Lots of work to be done.
Tournament just around corner.

1049
01:35:25,017 --> 01:35:26,560
Come, stand up.

1050
01:35:27,061 --> 01:35:30,893
Steady, concentrate. Focus power.

1051
01:35:36,779 --> 01:35:37,977
Drive a punch.

1052
01:35:38,990 --> 01:35:41,066
<i>Drive a punch, Daniel-san.</i>

1053
01:35:43,536 --> 01:35:47,368
"Happy birthday to you

1054
01:35:48,416 --> 01:35:53,042
"Happy birthday to you

1055
01:35:53,588 --> 01:35:58,415
<i>"Happy birthday, dear Daniel-san</i>

1056
01:35:59,218 --> 01:36:03,465
"Happy birthday to you"

1057
01:36:06,142 --> 01:36:07,257
Make wish.

1058
01:36:09,062 --> 01:36:10,888
I know what I'm wishing for.

1059
01:36:14,817 --> 01:36:16,609
Very good.

1060
01:36:22,325 --> 01:36:24,531
Number one birthday present.

1061
01:36:24,702 --> 01:36:28,285
Mr. Miyagi, what did you do?
You didn't have to do this.

1062
01:36:28,956 --> 01:36:31,494
What is this? I have no idea.

1063
01:36:33,961 --> 01:36:38,042
Mr. Miyagi, this is great.

1064
01:36:40,093 --> 01:36:41,966
Where did this come from?

1065
01:36:42,553 --> 01:36:47,014
Mrs. Miyagi make, long time ago.

1066
01:36:49,936 --> 01:36:53,886
If you ever want this patch back,
I'll understand.

1067
01:36:54,982 --> 01:36:57,058
I know you understand.

1068
01:36:59,028 --> 01:37:00,059
Try on.

1069
01:37:01,322 --> 01:37:04,109
This is beautiful. This is great.

1070
01:37:04,700 --> 01:37:07,370
Do you think I stand a chance
at the tournament?

1071
01:37:07,954 --> 01:37:10,955
Not matter what Miyagi think.
Miyagi not fighting.

1072
01:37:12,458 --> 01:37:14,581
I don't know if I know enough karate.

1073
01:37:15,545 --> 01:37:17,003
Feeling correct.

1074
01:37:18,089 --> 01:37:20,662
You sure know how to make
a guy feel confident.

1075
01:37:21,759 --> 01:37:26,967
You trust the quality of what you know,
not quantity.

1076
01:37:29,350 --> 01:37:31,722
Today you get driver's licence?

1077
01:37:31,853 --> 01:37:35,019
Yeah, look at this.

1078
01:37:35,732 --> 01:37:37,938
Check that out.

1079
01:37:38,526 --> 01:37:40,104
"Daniel LaRusso."

1080
01:37:42,363 --> 01:37:43,478
Congratulations.

1081
01:37:43,698 --> 01:37:45,774
Thanks. The kid's legal, now.

1082
01:37:47,785 --> 01:37:49,944
I never know you have sweetheart.

1083
01:37:50,079 --> 01:37:51,277
No, I don't.

1084
01:37:51,706 --> 01:37:53,081
Look good together.

1085
01:37:54,083 --> 01:37:55,246
Different, but same.

1086
01:37:56,335 --> 01:37:57,960
No. Different, but different.

1087
01:37:59,881 --> 01:38:02,336
Too bad mother not here.

1088
01:38:02,467 --> 01:38:03,795
Shoot!

1089
01:38:04,260 --> 01:38:06,051
- Shoot! Damn!
- What's matter?

1090
01:38:06,179 --> 01:38:10,639
I've got to go. My mother
is making a surprise cake for me.

1091
01:38:10,725 --> 01:38:13,928
- Miyagi understand.
- I wasn't supposed to know. Damn it.

1092
01:38:14,062 --> 01:38:15,639
- That's okay.
- I'm sorry.

1093
01:38:15,730 --> 01:38:17,604
Miyagi once have mother, too.

1094
01:38:19,484 --> 01:38:21,607
Go outside. Something show you.

1095
01:38:21,694 --> 01:38:23,438
- What?
- Number two present.

1096
01:38:23,529 --> 01:38:24,644
Number two present?

1097
01:38:25,156 --> 01:38:29,201
You don't have to give me anything.
You've given me enough already.

1098
01:38:29,869 --> 01:38:31,743
No really, I'm serious.

1099
01:38:33,289 --> 01:38:34,570
Choose.

1100
01:38:38,127 --> 01:38:39,787
Oh, no.

1101
01:38:41,339 --> 01:38:43,166
Hurt old man feeling.

1102
01:38:45,093 --> 01:38:47,381
- Choose.
- Oh, wow.

1103
01:38:58,022 --> 01:39:00,478
I can't believe it.

1104
01:39:04,112 --> 01:39:06,235
What a gift!

1105
01:39:15,790 --> 01:39:17,581
Oh, boy.

1106
01:39:21,129 --> 01:39:22,706
Just remember:

1107
01:39:22,964 --> 01:39:28,669
A licence never replace eye, ear and brain.

1108
01:39:33,766 --> 01:39:35,225
What matter?

1109
01:39:36,144 --> 01:39:39,809
I'm just scared.
The tournament and everything.

1110
01:39:41,899 --> 01:39:45,233
You remember lesson about balance?

1111
01:39:46,863 --> 01:39:48,025
Yeah.

1112
01:39:48,906 --> 01:39:52,441
Lesson not just karate only.

1113
01:39:53,953 --> 01:39:56,409
Lesson for whole life.

1114
01:39:58,416 --> 01:40:01,417
Whole life have a balance.

1115
01:40:03,838 --> 01:40:06,163
Everything be better.

1116
01:40:08,801 --> 01:40:10,212
Understand?

1117
01:40:12,305 --> 01:40:13,764
Yeah, I understand.

1118
01:40:17,977 --> 01:40:19,768
Oh, wow.

1119
01:40:25,902 --> 01:40:28,060
You're the best friend I ever had.

1120
01:40:30,073 --> 01:40:31,271
You...

1121
01:40:32,408 --> 01:40:34,317
...pretty okay, too.

1122
01:40:38,372 --> 01:40:39,997
Go.

1123
01:40:40,833 --> 01:40:42,458
Go find the balance.

1124
01:40:52,053 --> 01:40:54,923
<i>- Banzai, Daniel-san!</i>
<i>- Banzai!</i>

1125
01:41:40,059 --> 01:41:43,309
I give up. Don't shoot! No.

1126
01:41:45,189 --> 01:41:47,894
- Don't leave me. I'm wounded.
- Good, maybe you'll die.

1127
01:41:52,363 --> 01:41:55,779
- I just wanted to apologise.
- Fine, you apologised.

1128
01:41:56,492 --> 01:41:59,327
- I got my licence.
- Whoop-dee-doo.

1129
01:41:59,620 --> 01:42:03,072
- What's with you?
- What do you expect? Cartwheels?

1130
01:42:04,208 --> 01:42:09,748
I just expected some courtesy,
or is that only for people with fancy cars?

1131
01:42:12,175 --> 01:42:14,630
Can't you take a hint?

1132
01:42:19,348 --> 01:42:21,008
Does the truth hurt?

1133
01:42:21,142 --> 01:42:23,550
- You really think that's it?
- I know it is.

1134
01:42:23,644 --> 01:42:25,886
- You're wrong.
- I bet I'm wrong.

1135
01:42:25,980 --> 01:42:30,108
I didn't go out with you
because of a car or where you live.

1136
01:42:30,193 --> 01:42:32,862
Okay, while we're on the subject,
why did you then?

1137
01:42:34,072 --> 01:42:35,352
Why did you?

1138
01:42:35,490 --> 01:42:38,740
I thought maybe you and me
were different.

1139
01:42:38,826 --> 01:42:42,326
I'm from Reseda, you're from the hills,
that's how we're different.

1140
01:42:42,413 --> 01:42:45,663
Admit that you just can't handle
the situation the way it is.

1141
01:42:46,084 --> 01:42:48,788
I can handle it fine. You can't.

1142
01:42:49,921 --> 01:42:53,669
What makes you so sensitive?
She's never been anything but nice to you.

1143
01:42:53,841 --> 01:42:57,376
- She used me to make him jealous.
- She doesn't even like him.

1144
01:42:57,470 --> 01:43:01,171
Who could tell, the way their faces
were stuck together at the country club?

1145
01:43:01,265 --> 01:43:05,512
Right, you didn't stick around
for the exciting conclusion.

1146
01:43:05,603 --> 01:43:07,892
- What, his hand on her ass?
- Her right hook.

1147
01:43:07,980 --> 01:43:11,100
You think she sprained her wrist
doing her nails?

1148
01:43:12,777 --> 01:43:15,731
- She hit him?
- That's an understatement.

1149
01:43:17,949 --> 01:43:22,243
- Why didn't she say something?
- She shouldn't have to, should she?

1150
01:43:41,764 --> 01:43:43,175
Hey, slugger.

1151
01:43:48,730 --> 01:43:50,639
Look, I'm a jerk.

1152
01:43:53,985 --> 01:43:55,645
You are a jerk.

1153
01:43:56,738 --> 01:43:58,280
So, am I forgiven?

1154
01:44:00,283 --> 01:44:02,192
I don't hear anything.

1155
01:44:02,785 --> 01:44:04,612
Sounds like a "yes" to me.

1156
01:44:05,121 --> 01:44:07,493
Come here.

1157
01:44:18,551 --> 01:44:21,124
I guess you know
about the tournament tomorrow.

1158
01:44:21,637 --> 01:44:22,966
Who doesn't?

1159
01:44:23,097 --> 01:44:24,473
Dumb move, huh?

1160
01:44:25,099 --> 01:44:26,891
Not necessarily.

1161
01:44:27,477 --> 01:44:30,050
I don't have much of a cheering section.

1162
01:44:30,354 --> 01:44:31,849
You got me.

1163
01:44:32,732 --> 01:44:35,816
I'll probably get killed in the first match.

1164
01:44:36,986 --> 01:44:38,943
So, we'll leave early.

1165
01:44:53,920 --> 01:44:57,371
- I've got something to show you.
- What?

1166
01:45:00,927 --> 01:45:04,794
- How do you like it?
- Is it yours? Are you serious?

1167
01:45:04,889 --> 01:45:08,340
- It's beautiful.
- It sure is.

1168
01:45:08,434 --> 01:45:10,593
- My God.
- Here you go.

1169
01:45:10,686 --> 01:45:13,723
- You want me to drive?
- It's the '80s!

1170
01:45:15,233 --> 01:45:18,399
- To start, you push that button.
- You're incredible.

1171
01:45:18,486 --> 01:45:22,899
Press the clutch.
Get the lights, no that one.

1172
01:45:23,491 --> 01:45:27,571
Good. Down is first. Let it out slow.

1173
01:45:28,162 --> 01:45:30,238
Hold on!

1174
01:45:31,624 --> 01:45:34,625
This is awesome. How fast does it go?

1175
01:45:35,044 --> 01:45:36,503
Let's not find out.

1176
01:45:40,091 --> 01:45:42,843
- What belt are you?
- Why matter?

1177
01:45:42,927 --> 01:45:45,881
This is open division,
it's only for brown belt or above.

1178
01:45:45,972 --> 01:45:47,715
Boy black belt.

1179
01:45:49,183 --> 01:45:52,766
You'd better hustle. They're starting.
Down the hall, to your left.

1180
01:45:53,104 --> 01:45:55,180
- I'll see you inside.
- Okay.

1181
01:45:55,898 --> 01:45:58,187
Excuse me, Mr. Referee.

1182
01:45:58,317 --> 01:46:01,568
This is not "Miyaji." Miyagi.

1183
01:46:01,654 --> 01:46:03,481
Miyagi.

1184
01:46:03,614 --> 01:46:05,192
Okay, thank you.

1185
01:46:13,958 --> 01:46:18,585
Well, look who we have here.
Our little friend Danielle.

1186
01:46:18,713 --> 01:46:20,290
Hello, Danielle.

1187
01:46:20,381 --> 01:46:23,501
What's the matter?
Mommy not here to dress you?

1188
01:46:24,469 --> 01:46:27,968
I'm talking to you, punk.
Come on, make a move.

1189
01:46:28,056 --> 01:46:29,965
Hey, save it for the ring.

1190
01:46:30,183 --> 01:46:31,214
Come on!

1191
01:46:31,893 --> 01:46:33,885
- All right.
- Let's go.

1192
01:46:34,604 --> 01:46:35,683
Come on.

1193
01:46:35,855 --> 01:46:38,013
Points or no points...

1194
01:46:39,150 --> 01:46:40,430
...you're dead meat.

1195
01:46:41,319 --> 01:46:43,358
I said out!

1196
01:46:45,740 --> 01:46:47,199
Dead meat.

1197
01:46:51,037 --> 01:46:53,528
Way to go, I think he's gonna cry.

1198
01:47:03,883 --> 01:47:09,090
<i>The winner of the first match</i>
<i>in the open division is Rufus Schneider.</i>

1199
01:47:09,680 --> 01:47:13,429
- Mr. Miyagi.
- Hurry. Tournament starting.

1200
01:47:13,518 --> 01:47:14,264
Where'd we get this?

1201
01:47:14,352 --> 01:47:15,098
<i>Daniel LaRusso...</i>

1202
01:47:15,186 --> 01:47:18,637
<i>- Buddha provide.</i>
<i>- ... please report to Ring 3.</i>

1203
01:47:18,856 --> 01:47:20,516
- Where's Ring 3?
- Over there.

1204
01:47:20,608 --> 01:47:24,143
Hold it! Sorry, teachers and students only.

1205
01:47:24,862 --> 01:47:26,440
He doesn't speak English...

1206
01:47:26,531 --> 01:47:30,575
...and I can't understand his instructions
without her. She's his translator.

1207
01:47:31,911 --> 01:47:36,787
- What did he say?
- You remind him of his uncle in Tokyo.

1208
01:47:36,874 --> 01:47:42,035
- I guess it's okay. What?
- He says you're very kind.

1209
01:47:42,296 --> 01:47:44,206
- Thank you.
- Welcome.

1210
01:47:46,718 --> 01:47:49,291
- What are the rules here?
- I don't know.

1211
01:47:50,012 --> 01:47:52,089
First time you, first time me.

1212
01:47:52,181 --> 01:47:55,930
I figured you knew about this stuff.
I figured you went to these before.

1213
01:47:56,018 --> 01:47:57,263
Great, I'm dead.

1214
01:47:57,353 --> 01:48:01,102
- You told me you fought a lot.
- For life, not for points.

1215
01:48:01,482 --> 01:48:03,724
Everything above your waist is a point.

1216
01:48:03,943 --> 01:48:07,394
You can hit the head, sternum,
kidneys, ribs. Got it?

1217
01:48:07,488 --> 01:48:09,695
- I hope so.
- You can do it.

1218
01:48:10,032 --> 01:48:12,405
When are you jerks going to grow up?

1219
01:48:18,833 --> 01:48:21,917
- Where am I, over here at this one?
- Number 3.

1220
01:48:22,003 --> 01:48:24,161
- What's that guy kneeling for?
- I don't know.

1221
01:48:24,255 --> 01:48:27,339
- Don't you know anything?
- Don't get hit.

1222
01:48:36,726 --> 01:48:39,976
Face. Bow. On guard.

1223
01:48:41,314 --> 01:48:42,013
Fight.

1224
01:48:48,488 --> 01:48:49,768
Back on your line.

1225
01:48:49,906 --> 01:48:51,945
Be tough, Daniel.

1226
01:48:54,452 --> 01:48:55,911
Come on, be tough.

1227
01:48:58,956 --> 01:49:02,788
Remember your defence. Points coming.
Concentrate. Focus power.

1228
01:49:02,877 --> 01:49:05,202
Remember balance. Make good fight.

1229
01:49:07,131 --> 01:49:10,381
Run out of the ring once more,
it'll cost you a point.

1230
01:49:10,468 --> 01:49:12,342
On guard. Ready?

1231
01:49:20,728 --> 01:49:22,935
That's one, Daniel, come on.

1232
01:49:25,441 --> 01:49:26,935
One more!

1233
01:49:27,610 --> 01:49:29,188
Move back on your line.

1234
01:49:30,071 --> 01:49:32,396
That's one point, round kick.

1235
01:49:33,658 --> 01:49:36,694
Daniel, you're the best!

1236
01:49:53,636 --> 01:49:54,965
You're dead!

1237
01:51:37,073 --> 01:51:38,864
Point! Winner!

1238
01:52:28,249 --> 01:52:29,529
Winner!

1239
01:52:32,462 --> 01:52:34,538
- It must be tight.
- Yeah, right there.

1240
01:52:35,089 --> 01:52:38,007
- I never thought I'd get this far.
- Make two of us.

1241
01:52:38,092 --> 01:52:39,836
Wouldn't it be great if I won?

1242
01:52:39,969 --> 01:52:43,837
- It'd be great if you survive.
- What do you mean "survive"?

1243
01:52:44,307 --> 01:52:48,387
- I'm fine as long as I don't move.
- You've got to move now, they're starting.

1244
01:52:48,519 --> 01:52:51,723
Are they starting now?
What do you mean "survive"?

1245
01:52:52,899 --> 01:52:56,268
<i>Ladies and gentlemen...</i>

1246
01:52:56,360 --> 01:52:59,812
<i>... may I have your attention, please.</i>

1247
01:52:59,989 --> 01:53:05,232
<i>This is the first semi-final match</i>
<i>of the afternoon.</i>

1248
01:53:07,538 --> 01:53:12,781
<i>Defending champion,</i>
<i>John Lawrence of the Cobra Kai.</i>

1249
01:53:13,044 --> 01:53:16,911
<i>Two-time winner of the All Valley</i>
<i>Under-18 Golden Trophy.</i>

1250
01:53:17,006 --> 01:53:21,752
<i>He'll be facing Darryl Vidal</i>
<i>of the Locust Valley Karate Club.</i>

1251
01:53:22,428 --> 01:53:27,090
<i>Three points wins.</i>
<i>Contestants, please come to the ring.</i>

1252
01:53:27,642 --> 01:53:29,634
<i>Good luck, gentlemen.</i>

1253
01:53:31,729 --> 01:53:33,521
Go get him, Johnny.

1254
01:53:34,399 --> 01:53:35,941
Show him what you're made of.

1255
01:53:36,401 --> 01:53:38,358
Face me, gentlemen. Bow.

1256
01:53:39,028 --> 01:53:41,899
Face. Bow. Ready?

1257
01:53:43,658 --> 01:53:44,772
Come on, Johnny.

1258
01:53:47,578 --> 01:53:49,536
Fast, Johnny. Come on. Do it.

1259
01:53:54,544 --> 01:53:56,287
One point, Lawrence.

1260
01:54:05,930 --> 01:54:07,472
Lawrence, back on the line.

1261
01:54:07,598 --> 01:54:08,927
Way to go!

1262
01:54:09,058 --> 01:54:10,600
Are you all right?

1263
01:54:10,893 --> 01:54:12,091
I'm okay.

1264
01:54:14,397 --> 01:54:15,939
One point, Lawrence.

1265
01:54:20,695 --> 01:54:22,652
Good point, Johnny!

1266
01:54:24,574 --> 01:54:26,447
Point Lawrence. Winner!

1267
01:54:29,871 --> 01:54:35,113
<i>The next semi-final determines</i>
<i>who will face the defending champion.</i>

1268
01:54:35,543 --> 01:54:42,459
<i>Daniel LaRusso, of the Miyagi-do Karate.</i>

1269
01:54:43,801 --> 01:54:45,177
Bobby...

1270
01:54:45,720 --> 01:54:47,677
...I want him out of commission.

1271
01:54:47,805 --> 01:54:50,261
<i>Sensei, I can beat this guy.</i>

1272
01:54:52,101 --> 01:54:55,850
- I don't want him beaten.
- But I'll be disqualified!

1273
01:54:56,147 --> 01:54:57,974
Out of commission.

1274
01:55:01,694 --> 01:55:04,446
<i>Let's go, fellas. Good luck.</i>

1275
01:55:14,207 --> 01:55:16,283
Do what you got to do, Bobby!

1276
01:55:20,505 --> 01:55:24,668
Face. Bow. Ready?

1277
01:55:25,259 --> 01:55:28,047
Watch the control, gentlemen. Ready?

1278
01:55:36,521 --> 01:55:40,518
- I'm sorry! I didn't mean it.
- My leg!

1279
01:55:41,484 --> 01:55:45,564
- Mr. Miyagi, my leg hurts.
- Miyagi here.

1280
01:55:48,032 --> 01:55:52,361
<i>Bobby Brown of the Cobra Kai</i>
<i>has been disqualified...</i>

1281
01:55:52,745 --> 01:55:57,454
<i>... for excessive and deliberate contact.</i>
<i>Under rule 41-2...</i>

1282
01:55:58,334 --> 01:56:02,166
<i>... Daniel LaRusso has 15 minutes</i>
<i>to return to the ring.</i>

1283
01:56:02,255 --> 01:56:04,627
<i>If he is unable to return...</i>

1284
01:56:04,716 --> 01:56:09,009
<i>... John Lawrence will win by default.</i>

1285
01:56:13,933 --> 01:56:15,760
I'll inform the judges.

1286
01:56:17,103 --> 01:56:18,846
You did well out there, young man.

1287
01:56:23,776 --> 01:56:24,807
Damn it!

1288
01:56:24,944 --> 01:56:27,102
Honey, forget it.

1289
01:56:27,238 --> 01:56:29,444
You were great.

1290
01:56:29,949 --> 01:56:32,025
I couldn't be prouder.

1291
01:56:32,493 --> 01:56:34,237
It was just bad luck.

1292
01:56:34,328 --> 01:56:37,116
You would have won
if they hadn't cheated.

1293
01:56:37,248 --> 01:56:39,573
Just leave me alone for a minute.

1294
01:56:39,667 --> 01:56:41,161
We'll be outside.

1295
01:56:46,382 --> 01:56:48,042
Mr. Miyagi...

1296
01:56:50,678 --> 01:56:52,920
...you think I had a chance of winning?

1297
01:56:53,056 --> 01:56:54,633
Win, lose, no matter.

1298
01:56:54,724 --> 01:56:56,633
That's not what I mean.

1299
01:57:01,439 --> 01:57:03,432
Had good chance.

1300
01:57:04,400 --> 01:57:07,318
Can you fix my leg with that thing you do?

1301
01:57:07,570 --> 01:57:09,859
No need fight anymore.

1302
01:57:10,031 --> 01:57:13,482
- You proved a point.
- What, that I can take a beating?

1303
01:57:13,785 --> 01:57:17,485
Every time I see those guys,
they'll know they got the best of me.

1304
01:57:19,248 --> 01:57:23,709
I'll never have balance that way,
not with them, not with Ali...

1305
01:57:27,382 --> 01:57:28,792
...not with me.

1306
01:57:33,471 --> 01:57:34,502
What?

1307
01:57:37,517 --> 01:57:38,892
Close eye.

1308
01:57:59,247 --> 01:58:04,454
<i>Ladies and gentlemen,</i>
<i>this is the moment we've been waiting for.</i>

1309
01:58:07,547 --> 01:58:09,919
<i>Daniel LaRusso's going to fight?</i>

1310
01:58:10,174 --> 01:58:12,748
<i>Daniel LaRusso's going to fight!</i>

1311
01:58:13,136 --> 01:58:17,180
<i>This is what it's all about, folks.</i>
<i>You know it.</i>

1312
01:58:18,182 --> 01:58:20,009
<i>How's the leg, son?</i>

1313
01:58:22,103 --> 01:58:24,345
<i>All right. What a man!</i>

1314
01:58:24,772 --> 01:58:27,097
<i>The final match to determine...</i>

1315
01:58:27,191 --> 01:58:30,192
<i>... who'll emerge victor and champion...</i>

1316
01:58:30,319 --> 01:58:34,613
<i>... of the All Valley Under-18</i>
<i>Karate Championship.</i>

1317
01:58:34,782 --> 01:58:37,949
<i>Daniel LaRusso, Miyaji-do Karate...</i>

1318
01:58:38,661 --> 01:58:40,535
<i>Miyagi-do.</i>

1319
01:58:40,663 --> 01:58:42,952
<i>Miyagi-do Karate.</i>

1320
01:58:43,124 --> 01:58:46,374
<i>... versus John Lawrence of the Cobra Kai.</i>

1321
01:58:46,461 --> 01:58:49,462
<i>Three points wins. Good luck, boys.</i>

1322
01:58:50,131 --> 01:58:52,918
Come on, Daniel!
You've got this guy. You can do it.

1323
01:59:00,058 --> 01:59:01,849
Face me. Bow.

1324
01:59:02,018 --> 01:59:05,303
Face off. Bow. Ready?

1325
01:59:14,947 --> 01:59:16,145
That's okay, Johnny.

1326
01:59:16,240 --> 01:59:17,900
Lawrence, return.

1327
01:59:19,368 --> 01:59:21,195
One point, LaRusso.

1328
01:59:21,287 --> 01:59:22,568
You're dead.

1329
01:59:29,212 --> 01:59:30,706
Daniel, you've got him!

1330
01:59:37,470 --> 01:59:40,387
<i>Point! Jab! That's two for LaRusso.</i>

1331
01:59:41,265 --> 01:59:44,302
<i>Time out. Go to your sensei.</i>

1332
01:59:44,435 --> 01:59:46,095
Turn, kneel.

1333
01:59:46,229 --> 01:59:48,601
Johnny, you're a creampuff!

1334
01:59:49,732 --> 01:59:50,930
Sweep the leg.

1335
01:59:53,486 --> 01:59:55,443
You have a problem with that?

1336
01:59:57,532 --> 01:59:58,812
<i>No, Sensei.</i>

1337
02:00:00,868 --> 02:00:02,244
No mercy.

1338
02:00:11,045 --> 02:00:12,456
One more!

1339
02:00:13,214 --> 02:00:16,215
Two points LaRusso. Lawrence nothing.

1340
02:00:24,183 --> 02:00:27,848
<i>One point Lawrence. 2-1, LaRusso.</i>

1341
02:00:48,791 --> 02:00:52,326
Kick to the side. One point Lawrence. 2-2.

1342
02:01:00,094 --> 02:01:02,336
Out of bounds. Come back in.

1343
02:01:04,474 --> 02:01:06,016
Destroy him, Johnny!

1344
02:01:06,100 --> 02:01:08,389
Come on, Daniel, you can do it!

1345
02:01:29,832 --> 02:01:32,833
Come on, Daniel. Be strong.

1346
02:01:35,129 --> 02:01:36,921
- Are you okay?
- Yeah, I'm okay.

1347
02:01:37,256 --> 02:01:40,708
<i>Whoever wins the next point</i>
<i>will be our new champion.</i>

1348
02:01:45,515 --> 02:01:47,223
Finish him, Johnny!

1349
02:01:55,775 --> 02:01:58,645
It's over, Johnny! You did it!

1350
02:02:02,073 --> 02:02:04,030
Are you okay? Can you go on?

1351
02:02:04,158 --> 02:02:07,361
Get him a body bag!

1352
02:02:09,872 --> 02:02:12,577
Warning for illegal contact to the knee.

1353
02:02:18,131 --> 02:02:20,004
Finish him!

1354
02:02:28,975 --> 02:02:30,517
Winner!

1355
02:02:40,611 --> 02:02:43,281
<i>The new champion!</i>

1356
02:02:44,490 --> 02:02:47,906
- You're all right, LaRusso.
- Thanks a lot.

1357
02:02:52,790 --> 02:02:56,206
Mr. Miyagi, we did it. All right!