Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
Bernie, seriously... this is where
they asked us to meet?
Yeah. What do you mean?
Oh, I think I see her.
Where?
Oh, that's gotta be her.
So, what are we gonna do?
Are we gonna grab a milkshake, Bernie?
Is that why we're here?
Oh, yeah. Yeah, yeah, I guess.
All right. You're gonna
owe me big for this.
So...
You think I should have worn
the other shirt?
You look nice.
I don't know, Gus. Maybe, she...
What if she don't like
the look of me or something?
Bernie. Come on.
Are you serious? What about her?
Aren't you dying to see
what she looks like?
She could be a dog.
No, she isn't a dog.
She could be.
I already know what
she looks like in my head.
She ain't a dog.
So, uh...
You been talking to her for
weeks on the phone, right?
- Yeah.
- Right?
Yeah.
She likes you from talking to you, Bernie.
And I don't think you gotta worry
about her getting a good look at ya.
That ain't never been your problem.
Let's go.
Come on.
Should have worn the other shirt.
I'm the one taking a risk.
Doubling with some girl
I ain't never even spoke to...
let alone seen!
I don't know why this Miriam girl...
says it's gotta be a double date, anyway.
Maybe she's not sure about me yet.
How can anybody
not be sure about you, Bernie?
Yeah. Thanks, Gus.
Yeah, hey, don't tell none of the guys
down at the station about this.
It's not like you've
never been on a date before.
- All set there?
- Uh...
Excuse me.
Are you Miriam?
No.
I'm her friend.
She's, uh...
Hi. How you doin'? I'm Gus.
- Catherine.
- It's nice to meet you.
Okay. We'll talk later.
Bye.
Hi.
Wait.
You are Bernie Webber, right?
Uh, yeah.
Yeah, I'm Bernie.
Hey, you two, let's go grab a drink.
Yeah.
You wanna go?
Sure.
How you doin'? I'm Gus.
You know, for a minute there...
I thought it was Smokey the Bear
makin' a call in that booth.
'Cause of your jacket.
Oh.
Bernie...
Miriam's never been on a boat.
She's scared of the water.
Has she never?
I told her I don't know how she's
gonna date a guy in the Coast Guard.
I'm not scared. I live on the Cape.
Don't worry, Miriam. You know, we, uh...
We all get scared out there.
I'm not afraid of the water, Bernie.
It scares me at night, that's all.
You can't see what's underneath.
Just more water.
You know, I get funnier
as the night goes on.
So, why, uh... Why didn't you
wanna meet me for a date?
Why'd you... Why'd you wait so long?
I didn't know if you'd be a...
If I'd what?
- You know.
- No.
You're so handsome...
I just didn't know
if you'd be attracted to me.
Oh, God, no, Miriam.
You're exactly how I pictured you.
Yeah?
Oh, yeah.
Better.
You know... My brother, uh...
He always says that, "When
you know, you just know."
Which one?
Uh, all of it.
I guess, you know, everything.
No. I mean, which brother?
Oh. Ay...
Uh, Paul. My brother, Paul.
He's the one who fought
over in Germany, right?
In Germany, yeah.
He's the oldest. Father's favorite.
All three of my brothers
went over to the war.
He's your father's what?
Hey.
We should get Miriam
out on a boat tonight.
What do you say, Bernie, hmm?
We take out the dory.
It'll be fantastic.
You know we can't do that, Gus.
We could get in trouble.
Come on, Bernie. It'll be fun.
Rules are rules.
No. We don't gotta row out far.
Just so this sweet girl can say
she's been on a boat, that's it.
A rowboat? No.
No.
No, no. Small boats that...
How about one of those bigger
boats? Tied up to the dock?
If Bernie's with me, I'll do it.
Oh, a fishing boat?
Those fishermen don't want us around,
unless we're pullin' them in.
They think they own the goddamn water.
They're not very nice.
Come on. Don't be such a fathead, Miriam.
Yeah.
Let's go out on the dory.
What's there to be afraid of?
What's underneath, right?
Hey there, Mr. Stello. How's it goin'?
- Hey, Bernie.
- Mr. Ryder.
Hey, so you see that girl
sitting over there?
The one with the coat
looks like a bear, Bernie?
- Yeah.
- Can't miss her.
I said the same thing myself.
Funny you should say that.
Looks like Smokey, right? Smokey the Bear.
I don't know no Smokey, Bernie.
Oh, it's just a cartoon.
Anyway, Mr. Stello, she thinks
she's scared of going out on a boat.
And I don't think
we should row out on a dory.
I don't want her gettin' sick
on that nice, big coat.
So, I was wondering if...
So, you wanna take her on
the Anna G round the harbor?
Yeah.
Can't row out on that dory
even if ya wanted, right, Bernie?
- Carl, stop.
- Year anniversary's coming.
My sister's now livin' in my house.
How's it going with you, Bernie?
That's enough, Carl. He did all he could.
I am sorry, Mr. Nickerson.
I didn't mean to upset you.
Just wanted to ask Mr. Stello
about borrowing a boat.
Got you. I got you.
This is a boat.
Give me your hands.
It's okay.
Now the hacienda's dark
The town is sleeping
Now the time has come to part
The time for weeping
Vaya con dios, my darling
Just, uh...
- Just follow my arms, okay?
- Mmm-hmm.
Stay with me.
- It's all about the rhythm.
- Mmm-hmm.
Okay? So it's, uh... So it's, uh...
Here we go.
One, two, three.
Right, left, right.
One, two, three. One...
I can't one, two, three to this.
- Let's just sit down, Bernie.
- No, sweetheart.
Look, all you gotta do is you
gotta relax and be patient...
and settle in my hand.
Hey, look, just... Here...
settle in my hand. You feel that?
Mmm.
Just listen to the music, right?
And... One, two, three.
One, two, three. Right, left, right.
Right, left, right.
You're doing great.
Now the dawn is breaking through
A gray tomorrow
But the memories we share
Are there to borrow
Vaya con dios, my darling
Will you marry me?
What?
Uh...
No.
Vaya con dios, my darling
Vaya con dios...
Miriam, hold on!
It's cold, sweetheart.
Don't you wanna go back inside?
The band's not through.
It's cold. Do you feel that?
There's a storm comin'.
Okay.
Okay, what?
Okay, let's get married.
I just... I don't wanna...
Wanna what?
Well, it's only been a few months
and it's still winter, after all.
And, look, there's a storm comin'.
It's just like this one
that come through last year.
What does that...
I heard it's gonna miss us.
Yeah, but maybe not. You never know.
You never know.
Some people, they're
just not cut out for this.
Sometimes you go out
and you don't come back.
Are you talking about the storm
or marriage, Bernie?
I think I'm talking about
the storm, right?
You're scared of a storm?
No.
I don't want to disappoint nobody.
And...
I don't wanna lose you. I love you.
So...
Yeah, let's get married.
You sure?
Oh, yeah.
When?
You want me to pick a date? No!
When do you wanna get married?
April 16th.
Okay.
Okay. April 16th it is.
But, uh, I gotta ask
permission from Cluff first.
You gotta ask permission?
Yeah, it's from my commanding officer.
It's Coast Guard regulation.
But I promise I'll ask him tomorrow.
Okay, Bernie.
Let's get you home.
Man, you can dance.
Ah, look at that. It's already
starting to snow. Hmm?
Can you hear me
over this hummin', Captain?
That fracture they welded last month
is not gonna hold in these seas, Cap.
Takes a bad jolt,
she could fracture again.
I don't have to go on deck, Cap.
I can hear it from right down here.
That weld is really hummin'.
It's hummin', sir.
The weld is, uh... Hummin'.
Uh, I'd like to take it down
to three knots, please.
Uh...
If we don't slow her down, Captain,
we might not have a, uh...
A position to hold.
Uh, no problem, Cap.
Uh, holdin' at seven knots.
Thank you, sir.
Hey, Pop?
I hear it.
You wanna go up on deck?
Have a look at those crack arrestors
holdin' that weld together?
Might as well go be get a hat, Popo.
What did he say?
Uh, he says he would like you to
consider taking a hat with you, as well.
Get some sleep.
For the people all said sit down
Sit down, you're rockin' the boat
Hey, Pops!
What do you know about this weather?
It's killin' me and young Eldon here.
Tiny, sure it's the weather?
Maybe it's your singing.
For the people all said sit down
Sit down, you're rockin' the boat
Come on.
The people all said sit down
Sit down, you're rockin' the boat
Shut up, shut up, shut up.
Ah, it's gonna get worse.
Sybert!
I didn't make it topside.
That weld can't hold in these seas.
You gotta slow her down.
I'm calling the captain back.
It's coming in!
- You okay, Pops?
- Yeah.
Go up!
We've got a hull fracture
in the engine room!
All hands muster mattresses...
blankets, whatever you can
get your hands on!
Tchuda.
Yeah, boy?
I can't get anyone on the bridge.
I need you to go up and tell the captain
we got an 18-foot fracture in our hull.
Tell him these pumps
are holding for now...
but we don't put her into
port, we're gonna wreck.
Captain don't understand me, Bouloo.
I know he can't understand you
but he doesn't listen to anyone, anyway.
Jesus, Mary, and Joseph.
- Cold out there?
- Yeah.
You still tryin' to fix that darn thing?
Yeah.
Oh, come on. Fitzy, it's useless.
Let the guy who fixes it come fix it.
I would if he would show up.
What's this on the radio,
ship breaking up?
That's the Fort Mercer.
Fort Mercer?
She's a big lady. She's a T2 tanker.
Started radioin' a couple hours ago.
Apparently she's got
a big crack in her hull.
It's spillin' oil all over the place.
She's, uh, about 20 miles east
off of Nantucket.
It sounds like Boston and Nantucket
are sendin' out their entire fleet, huh?
We could be next.
They're saying gale force winds
50 to 60 miles per hour.
Yeah. Yeah.
...waves at 50 feet. Over.
It's gonna be a mess.
Oh, uh, Bernie, Bernie.
Uh, Miriam called for you.
Yeah.
Good luck, pal.
- Yeah.
- Mr. Cluff?
It's me, Bernie, sir.
Webber. Pick yourself a crew.
Go out there, help them fishermen
secure their boats to the pier.
Oh. Uh, yes, sir.
Sir, I need to ask you a question.
Uh...
I need permission about a girl, you know?
Permission? Permission... For a girl?
Mr. Cluff, it's working.
Yes, sir.
Not now, Webber.
But, sir. It's
not just "some girl," sir...
Not now, Webber.
We're back up.
Cluster here's the Mercer rescue, right?
And this here other pip,
two miles from here.
We must still be gettin' phantom echoes.
How we supposed to tell
where anything is out there?
When's that technician
comin', Fitzpatrick?
And where the hell's Chief Bangs?
Uh...
It's Fitzgerald, sir.
Chief Bangs is in the mess hall, sir.
You makin' fun of my accent
'cause I'm not from around here?
No, Mr. Cluff.
Why are you still standing here, Webber?
Sir, but...
Take Livesey here with you,
go tie up them fishin' boats.
Yes, sir.
You want me to go with Webber, sir?
Secure fishing boats?
You didn't hear me, Livesey?
Uh, yeah, you with Webber.
Sorry, Richie. His orders, you know.
That's enough time,
what do you think, huh?
We're takin' on water, we
gotta launch them lifeboats.
Why you gotta be such a jackass, Brown?
Least we can do, pray for
the captain, Chief Collagen...
Rest of them men. All good men.
Hey, ain't we good men, Quirey?
Ah, don't get me wrong.
Prayin's great, but it ain't everything.
We need to actually do somethin'.
Sybert.
A word.
That hothead Brown, he wants
to launch the lifeboats.
The lifeboats?
Quirey, he wants to do nothin'.
Now, between them, the two of them
are getting the men worked up.
Now, I figure that you know
the boat better than anybody.
You're practically married to it.
So, I think they'll listen to ya.
Listen to me?
Pop, those men don't like me.
Nobody on the ship likes me
but you and Tchuda.
They might not like you, but
they'll know to listen to ya.
We don't know if the captain
got off an S.O.S.
Radio room's gone. We can't call nobody!
It's just Garcia over there
with a little shortwave...
tryin' to pick up chatter.
I mean, as far as we know
nobody even knows we're out here.
Now I'm saying we launch them lifeboats now
and we get off this ship while we can.
How are you gonna get 'em down
in the water in this storm?
It can't be done,
those boats are too small.
It's suicide, Brown.
You can't do this, you can't do that.
What do you want us to do, Quirey?
Just sit up here and do nothin'?
That's it, no officers, no orders.
Every man for himself.
That ain't the way, Brown.
That never did nothing for nobody.
Now, the ship's split...
at the bulkheads separating
tanks eight and nine.
Mr. Sybert says that the other
tanks aren't fractured...
So the air in the ballast
tanks should keep us afloat.
But Mr. Sybert also says that...
Mr. Sybert says this,
Mr. Sybert says that.
He's a big boy.
Let him say it himself. He's right here.
Go ahead.
Uh...
We're sinking.
Yeah, but the whistle works.
So, we should keep blowing that.
Maybe somebody'll hear it.
I don't know,
but we're definitely sinking.
The crack in the engine room
is takin' on too much water.
Pumps can't keep up.
If the water reaches the
air-intake in the engine...
we're going to, uh, lose all the power.
And if we lose all the power,
we lose the pumps.
When we lose the pumps...
She's gonna drop pretty quick.
How long have we got before that happens?
Four, maybe five hours.
We need to buy ourselves some time.
So somebody can find us.
If anybody's even lookin'.
Even if they do know we're here
those seas are big enough.
I mean, it ripped this thing in half.
How the hell are they gonna get out?
That's why I'm sayin' we gotta
launch some lifeboats.
Our luck's runnin' out.
I don't believe in luck, Brown.
Put those lifeboats out in those seas...
they won't last 12 seconds.
You and Quirey both,
you just wanna sit around and do nothin'.
You got a better idea, Sybert,
or you just go back, hide down below?
We're gonna run her aground.
- Huh?
- Do what?
You wanna run her aground, Sybert?
Even if you could with
half a ship, why would you?
She'd break apart,
dump us all out in that sea.
It's our only choice.
We're gonna find a soft shoal,
and we'll lay her up.
We'll slow the water that's coming in.
We'll stay in the same spot.
We'll blow the whistle.
We'll give whoever's coming
to look for us a chance to find us.
You're gonna steer a ship
without hydraulics?
That's your plan? How's that gonna work?
I'm gonna build a manual tiller.
Hey, Sybert, why should
we even listen to you?
The only thing you ever cared
about was this ship.
Man, I'll tell you what.
You two make a cute couple
at the bottom of the ocean.
Me, I'm gonna get on a lifeboat.
Look.
We'll insert a steel beam
into the steering quadrant.
We'll put pulleys
on the end of it for leverage.
And we'll move her manually.
Excuse me. Excuse me.
I think I got the radio working.
Bearing 83 degrees true...
27 miles from Pollock Rip Light.
About 20 miles east of Nantucket...
"East of Nantucket"?
That ain't the Pendleton.
Fort Mercer's emergency condition...
Fort Mercer. That's another T2.
Another tanker split in two besides us.
But if everyone's gonna
help them, who's gonna...
Who's gonna come for us?
How you feelin'?
- You all right?
- Mmm.
Did you, uh, ask Cluff, yet?
No.
Why don't you ask him?
- Webber!
- What's wrong with you?
- What?
You ask him yet? You ask Cluff?
I told you not to tell nobody.
I'm sorry, I'm not havin' a very good day.
I know you're not feeling well...
You know, Webber, you don't
need permission to get married.
No, actually, you do, Chief.
Unless you're underage.
Thanks, Chief, just following regulations.
Let's go get suited up.
Uh, it's not regulation, Webber.
It's just a formality, like a courtesy.
And, hey, did I hear right,
that she asked you?
Following orders, right, Webber?
Yeah. Yeah, she asked me, Chief.
Wow.
Wow. You, uh, sure you got
your pants on, Webber...
or is she wearin' 'em?
Sounds like this girl cut off your...
What, Webber? What? Huh?
Don't you got boats to tie up?
She's my fiancée, sir.
Who asked you...
to be married.
Come on, Richie, let's go.
One moment.
Uh-huh, sure.
I'm sorry, sir. Please speak up.
This line is bad, ma'am.
I'll try and reconnect it to you.
Please, sir. The lines are down.
Bernie? How are you? How's work?
Yeah, it's been one
of those days, you know.
But how are you?
Hey, you're not the radar
technician, are you?
Uh, no.
I was ordered to hole up here
till the storm passes.
Catch a ride back out to my lightship.
Um, you can go wait in
the mess hall, if you want to.
Now is not a good time, you know.
Um, I gotta get ready to go
down to the pier, tie up some boats. So...
I wish you were here with me.
I'm hearin' all sorts of things
about a ship breakin' up, and I...
- Oh.
- Hello?
What, you okay?
Yeah, we just lost our lights.
You better go find 'em, then.
Nantucket's dispatched
their 36-footer to the Mercer.
We got orders to do the same.
You asked Cluff yet? That's him, right?
Not yet, sweet... Uh...
I'll explain later.
- I... I gotta go.
- Okay.
I love you.
I love you, too.
Yeah, bye.
The best part of it is
she had no idea who I was.
Bangs?
Pick yourself a crew
take the 36500 out of Old Harbor.
Proceed to the Fort Mercer...
20 miles east of here
off Nantucket, you hear?
Uh, whoa, I don't believe we'd get
over the bar in this weather, Mr. Cluff.
We're better off takin'
the 36383 out of Stage Harbor.
That would take longer, right?
Not much.
What do you think, Webber?
You're a bosun mate, too.
You know what it's like out there.
Yeah, look. No one's gettin' over
the bar in this weather, Mr. Cluff.
Nobody.
It's a suicide mission.
We should take the 36383
out of Stage Harbor.
It'll take longer, sure.
At least we'll be able to get out.
Godspeed, Chief.
Webber, take Gouthro and
Livesey down to the fish pier.
Yes, sir.
Don't get me sick, Gus.
You shouldn't even be out here.
Why you always raggin' on us, Richie?
Don't take it out on us
'cause you couldn't go out with Bangs.
At least he'll get out.
Screw you. That were a year ago.
Screw you.
No one could have
got over the bar that day.
Bangs coulda.
Oh, really, Richie.
He's not trying to get
across the bar today.
No, he's taking the 36383...
right out from the nice,
protected bay side.
Ah.
Bernie, it doesn't matter
what Richie here thinks...
or Bangs or Carl Nickerson or nobody.
Nobody could have got out
to save the men on the Landry
Sometimes, you know...
Sometimes men die, Bernie.
All right. Here we go.
All right, hang on.
Easy, now. Easy, fellas.
- I got it.
- Okay, up, up, up!
One...
Two.
All together now.
Three!
Tie it down, boys. I got it.
All right. Now we've got a tiller.
We're gonna drive her up on the shoal.
Uh-uh. Brown and them others, they're
getting ready to launch them lifeboats.
They think it's their best hope.
Oh, Pop.
We need every guy we got.
Well, they're gonna take them lifeboats.
What are you tryin' to do, Sybert?
Get off him!
You come up here tryin' to kill us?
Are you trying to kill us?
Back off him.
Get up!
You're out of your mind!
Brown, he just saved your life, okay?
The boat's in pieces. It's gone!
Enough!
That boat is too small for these seas.
And this ship will be sunk by nightfall.
Now, every fella here wants to live...
and the only way that happens
is if we run her aground!
We gotta set up a watch
and look out for a shoal.
I need four men working the pulleys
on the emergency tiller.
I need four men manning
the pumps, aft to steering...
and the rest of you run a bucket line
topside down below...
...communicate with the engine room.
And somebody...
keep blowing that whistle.
You heard him, boys! Now move it! Come on!
Sounds like you're the man now, Sybert.
I hope you didn't just kill us all.
I saw a ship driftin'.
Heard it whistle.
A distress signal. 45 minutes ago, Bernie.
From my house.
Uh...
With the wind blowin' south,
and those currents...
I guess that'd put her close to here
about now comin' up over the bar.
Can't be part of the Mercer, Bernie.
She's off Nantucket,
40 miles southeast of here.
Means she would have
drifted northwest then, right?
I know what I heard.
Know what I saw.
Well, okay, then, uh...
How about we go back to the station
see if we can get to the bottom of it?
Just got off the phone with Boston.
They diverted a plane from the Mercer...
and it sighted the stern
of the tanker Pendleton...
five miles east of here.
Oh, my God.
Two tankers broken in half in one day.
That's gotta be some kind of record.
Boston and Nantucket have dispatched
all their boats to the Mercer.
They can't make it here in this weather.
Webber.
Pick yourself a crew.
Take that 36500 out
and you go over the bar...
and you find the stern of
the Pendleton. You hear?
Uh... Yes, sir.
Um...
You fellas want to get warmed up,
get some coffee?
Bernie.
Yeah.
Uh...
What?
What Carl's trying to say...
This isn't about the Landry
Oh, sure it is.
Richie.
Eight men died that night.
You and Gus and Masachi
couldn't even get out.
What makes you think you can do it now?
You know the bar on this
kind of day, right, Bernie?
Yeah.
That man in there
don't know what he's doin'.
He's sending you out to die.
You can't make it over Chatham
bar on a day like this.
Can't stay afloat for long
on half a ship neither.
Mr. Stello, in the Coast Guard
they say, you gotta go out.
But they don't say you gotta come back in.
That's regulation, you know.
Bernie, better you get lost
afore you get too far out, then.
Oh, don't worry about me, Mr. Ryder.
I can't get lost out there.
I know those waters pretty good.
How could I get lost?
No, no, no, no, Bernie.
What Dave's trying to say...
you should just motor around the harbor
say you tried to get out and couldn't.
You know?
Thank you, Mr. Ryder. Thank you.
But, Mr. Stello, I'm gonna do
my best to get out there.
I don't know if I will, but I'm gonna try.
Okay.
I guess Richie's in.
Who else?
Uh, I don't know, Gus.
You can hardly lift your head.
Who else you gonna take, Bernie?
Fitz is the only other engineman left.
And he's only third class
and he don't got the experience.
I'll... I'll go.
Yeah, I can do the job.
I mean, I can do it. You can't go.
You're sick as a dog, Gus.
He's right, Gus.
One more.
Someone has to go out there
and save those guys, right?
That's why I signed up.
Guess now's my chance.
Seaman Ervin Maske, Stonehorse lightship.
Pumps aren't keepin' up.
Three more feet...
till we lose the engines.
Can you lock that boiler on full?
You crazy to think
you can steer her broken...
with a couple of ropes
and a hand-made tiller, boy.
You got a better idea? I'm all ears.
There! A shoal about a mile distance!
We can make that!
Rudder, 15 degrees to port!
Half-speed if we want to hit it head on!
Gotta make a turn 80 degrees
on the compass to 310!
Rudder, 15 degrees port! Half-speed!
80 degrees to 310 on compass!
15 degrees port! Half-speed!
Rudder, 15 degrees port! Half-speed!
80 degrees to 310 on the compass!
80 degrees to 310 on compass!
Rudder, 15 degrees port! Half-speed!
80 degrees to 310 on the compass!
80 degrees to 310 on compass!
Rudder, 15 degrees port. Half-speed.
80 degrees to 310 on compass.
Thank you, Eldon.
All right! You guys! Now, pull!
Pull, pull, pull! Come on!
Please tell me we're takin' that boat
to a bigger boat.
You ever been on a rescue mission before?
No.
Mostly I just chip paint.
Sometimes I cook for the boys.
Great.
All right, you, uh, take the glory hole.
Maske. Ervin Maske.
Ervin, yeah.
Uh, Richie, drop
the mooring line when you can.
Last known position
of the Pendleton is here.
So, I figure once we cross the bar...
I reckon with the currents
she'll have drifted about here.
That's six miles from us.
So, you think Bernie can get
us out past the bar in this?
I've never seen anything like it.
Yeah, I mean, he's just gotta be sure
that he doesn't pitchpole us, that's all.
Huh?
The power of the waves on that bar
they can pick you up...
they can turn you end for end
over and over again.
There's no way to survive that.
That's pitchpoling.
Hey, Fitz, are we good?
All right, give it a shot!
Free the lines!
Lines freed!
Did Bernie go out, Gus?
Miriam, what are you doing here?
Did he?
Yeah, Cluff sent him.
I wanna talk to him.
- Who?
- Cluff.
Your commanding officer. Where is he?
I wanna find out where Bernie is.
I'm worried about him.
We're supposed to get married.
Miriam, this isn't what
any of the other girls do.
Or wives.
They don't come in here,
and they don't do this.
So?
If you want, I guess you can wait in here.
Listen to what's going on.
Sit down.
Tide's risin'.
Gonna work us off that shoal.
We need to hit it hard.
Yeah, there's no other way.
Wave!
You feel that? She's drifting.
Must have lost the tiller.
We gotta slow her headway
or we're gonna miss that shoal for good.
Close the governor valves,
cut the propulsion.
We gotta isolate the boiler.
We gotta conserve everything
she's got left!
I keep tellin' you, Bouloo.
This boat just bad luck.
It's got nothing... to do... with luck.
Station Chatham, this is the CG-36500.
Do you copy?
This is Station Chatham.
36500, what is your location? Over.
Station Chatham, we, uh...
We are now passing Morris Island.
Heading down the channel
towards Chatham bar. Over.
What's it mean, going over that bar?
Miriam, don't do this to yourself.
Why not?
Why not, Gus?
If I'm gonna be with him, I wanna know.
You're the girl with the bear coat, right?
Yeah.
Yeah, that's me.
You gonna tell me
what it's like out there?
Shoals on that bar are never
in the same place twice.
Flood currents carryin' them
big ocean swells...
that rise up when they hit the shallows,
crash up against that bar.
Outgoing tide crashes up against that bar.
That, uh...
That man shouldn't have sent them out
to cross that bar in a storm like this.
Maybe they can turn back.
Maybe they get lost before.
Can't get out.
You know Bernie, right?
You know he won't get lost out there.
You know he follows the rules.
Yeah, we know.
We all going down to the pier soon.
See if there's anything
we can do down there.
Welcome to come.
Miriam. Miriam!
Miriam, please come here.
Miriam!
Excuse me, are you Commander Cluff?
Who are you?
I'm Miriam Penttinen,
Bernie Webber's girlfriend.
I want you to call Bernie back in.
That girl he was asking me about.
You know what he was gonna ask me?
For your permission to marry me.
Well, that's between you,
him and your God.
Asking me is just a formality.
He can marry you all he wants.
Don't he know that?
But you can't be in here, miss.
It's Bernie.
Chatham bar dead ahead. Over.
36500, Station Chatham.
Proceed as directed
towards Pendleton stern.
I didn't copy that, Station Chatham.
Conditions hazardous.
Why give us permission if
you're sending him out to die?
What the hell?
Gouthro, get her out of here.
Sir, winds have gone from 40 to 60...
since the call first come in.
That's gonna be
hurricane strength in an hour.
Gouthro, he's got his orders.
You get her out of here,
and you get yourself to bed.
You're too sick to be in here.
36500, Station Chatham,
proceed over the bar.
I repeat, proceed.
Once over, travel directly south.
The radar's intermittent...
but it's showing a pip 10 or 12 miles...
...east of Monomoy Point,
moving south. Over.
Station Chatham, this is the 500.
Copy that.
I hear what everyone's saying.
You don't know what you're doing.
Excuse me?
Maybe... Maybe it's because
you're not from here.
You don't know what it's like out there...
What the hell would you know
what it's like out there, miss?
Hmm?
Please, just call them back.
What do you think it's gonna be like
being married to a Coast Guard man?
Please, just call them back.
You gonna come in here scared
every time he out in the water?
Please call them back.
You don't belong here.
Get out of here! Get out of my station!
And go home to where you belong, miss!
Please call them back.
Get out of my station!
Shoal's getting behind us.
Only chance now is a harder turn...
if the chains hold.
But it could capsize us.
That's good, boy.
You need to stand clear, boys!
If those shackles crack
and these chains snap...
it'll rip right through ya!
Here we go.
- Got her moving!
- Yeah!
Hear that?
That's it, that's the bar.
Couple minutes now, boys.
When I was a little boy
So my mother told me
To me! Way, haul away
Haul away
We'll haul away Joe
Now, first I met a Yankee girl
She was fat and lazy To me!
Way haul away
We'll haul away Joe
And then I met an Irish girl
She damn near drove me crazy To me!
Way haul away
We'll haul away Joe
Now way, haul away
We're bound for better weather
To me!
Way haul away
We'll haul away Joe
Hey, hey, boys!
We're not gonna be able
to see much, all right?
So we'll have to listen to
those waves hittin' that bar.
Gotta time it.
So I'm gonna wait for a lull...
and then we go.
We got faith in you, Skip!
Anytime you're ready...
you just go, Bernie, all right?
The compass is gone!
Fitzy! The engine died!
Ahh!
- I got it, I got it!
- No, you don't.
You got about five seconds, boys!
It's gravity-fed, it doesn't know
which way is up and down.
I know!
Come on, fire it up!
Yeah!
Maske! Get back here!
Tide's risin'.
It'll get us through.
But let me know what's comin'.
Hey, Fitz! We made it over the bar.
Back to the spotlight!
Coming out!
We turned too late!
We gotta buy that time back.
Tell Sybert we need 30 degrees
in the next two minutes...
or we'll miss that shoal!
Thirty degrees in the next two minutes!
Thirty degrees in the next two minutes.
We're putting her in reverse.
We're gonna let the ocean push us.
Hold on.
Okay.
Whoa!
You may wanna brace yourself, Eldon.
318!
316!
Close her down as soon as she hits!
312!
Gentlemen, brace yourselves.
Hold on!
Now!
Well...
You did it.
It bloody well worked, Mr. Sybert.
We gotta keep the water away
from the air inlets for the engine.
If we lose power, we'll lose our pumps.
And I'm afraid we're taking on
so much water...
the weight will pull us
right back off the shoal.
Feels funny not to be
moving around, huh, Eldon?
All right.
Let's get to it.
We're heading down to the lodge.
- Everything okay?
- Stop it!
- Hi!
- Quiet down now.
My God, give me a break.
Uh, I was on my way home.
My car spun out into a ditch.
I need some help.
Yeah, all right. We live near here.
We can go back to my house.
I'll call my brother.
He can tow you out. Jump in.
Thank you.
You don't got a coat?
You can move that.
We're bringing it down to St. Martin's
in case there are any survivors.
Oh, uh...
I left my coat at the Coast Guard station.
You got a man there?
Stop it!
Uh, I...
He's not there right now. It's, um...
It's Bernie Webber.
Yeah. Bernie, he's a good man.
We can't find them without
a compass, Bernie!
We got no idea where they are!
Hold on!
- You okay?
- Yeah.
You okay?
I'm having a great time now, Bernie!
Lot of fun!
- Brace yourselves!
- Oh...
Whole lotta... Whole lot of fun here.
Here. Come on, take it. Use it.
Got it, Pop!
We lost the pumps.
The pumps are tripping the breakers.
I'll go check the connection.
Give me the light.
It's not worth a damn, Bouloo.
Sometimes, I wish I didn't understand you.
Sybert, what's going on?
We're using every pump we've got.
We jammed the breakers so
the pumps wouldn't trip them.
We've got about two feet till the water...
hits those air inlets to the engines
and then the ship's dead.
Jesus Christ.
You hear that?
That's the tide rising,
gonna work us off this shoal.
Look, look, this'll at least
give us some time.
Isn't that right, Mr. Sybert?
That right. Sure does, boy.
Yeah, long as we got the generators
keeping the pumps going.
Buy whoever might be coming
to find us a little bit of time.
You wanted to be the man, Sybert.
Now you're the man, right?
Except you got no wife,
you got no kids back home.
You're a single man.
Always hiding down below.
What you got to lose?
All right, that's enough, Brown.
I'm scared, too, Brown.
I got a life, the same as you.
Just don't see the point
in sitting around talking about it.
Station Chatham, 36500.
Do you copy?
Station Chatham, this is Chief Bangs...
CG-36383.
Pollock lightship, CG-36500, do you copy?
Why can't they hear us, Bernie?
We can hear them!
Seas are too high, zero headway,
Station Chatham, do you copy?
Repeat, we're coming home.
Station Chatham to 36383,
return to Old Harbor.
Pollock lightship, CG-36500, do you copy?
- We're all alone.
- Bangs, return to Old Harbor.
You heard Bangs on the radio.
It sounds like he couldn't get out.
Going back in, the storm is getting worse.
We should turn back in, Webber.
Look, Bernie, we already made it out...
further than anybody thought was possible.
Maybe Richie's right.
Maybe we should just go back.
Winds at force of eight to nine.
Repeat: Winds at force of eight to nine.
Heavy snow squalls.
You heard Bangs on the radio!
We got no compass!
We have no way to communicate!
You're...
What? What? I'm what, Richie?
I got us out this far, didn't I?
Not Bangs or Cluff, or nobody else.
I did it!
We did it, Richie.
You wanna turn back around?
No.
No, not now. We came too far.
We're not giving up on them.
Not on my watch.
Just do your job.
Hey, Fitz!
Turn off the beam, Fitz.
We'll run her dark.
Better shot at seeing light
from the Pendleton if we're running dark.
Watch it!
Get back here!
Fitz!
Get your butts back here!
I lost my hat!
Whoa...
Are you okay?
Yeah, yeah.
I'm just tired.
Come on.
You kids go on and play in the bedroom.
You can wait with them, miss,
while I call my brother.
Thanks.
Please call me Miriam.
You think your mother would
mind if I turned on the radio?
Coast Guard Boston, this is the Unimak.
We're at the Mercer bow now,
here in support of the Yakutat.
Four Mercer crewmen jumped
from the deck. All were lost.
Repeat, four men lost.
Several crew members have hypothermia.
We're going to wait until daybreak
to attempt another rescue. Over.
Does no good listening
to all that chatter, Miriam.
Better learning to live not knowing.
How long you been married to Bernie for?
We're...
We're not married yet.
I don't know if I can...
Like I said, Bernie, he's a good man.
Him and some of them others
tried getting out a year ago...
to save my husband Arne
and the crew of the Landry
They were out fishing Monomoy
near Nantucket Sound...
when the boat started taking on water.
A night just like this.
Come on.
We gotta get going.
My brother's on his way to come meet us.
- Thanks.
- I gotta get down the lodge.
Come on, you two.
For the people all said sit down
Sit down, you're rockin' the boat
And the devil may pull you under
By the sharp lapels
Of your checkered coat
Sit down, sit down, sit down
You know who she is?
Ain't Bernie's fault, Carl.
Ain't nobody's fault.
Be like her blaming you.
For what?
You're the one that told them
there's another ship out there.
They're out there because of you, right?
Fitz.
Turn on the search light.
I can't believe we found her.
Look at that.
We're too late.
She's a ghost ship.
- Are you seeing this, sir?
- Yeah.
- You see that guy?
- Yeah, yeah, I see him.
Not sure I believe it.
Where the hell's he going?
Good to see ya, boys!
How we gonna fit them all on this boat?
We're only built to hold 12, includin' us.
That's just regulation, though, right?
How many can she fit?
20, 22, tops.
Wait!
They're coming down here.
- Drop the stanchion!
- Port side!
Come on!
Come on! I got ya!
We got ya!
Maske, get over here!
Come on!
Grab him!
You know where you're going now, miss?
I think so.
Thanks for your help, Mr. Nickerson.
Yeah.
You know...
Bernie ain't out there because of me.
Yeah, I know.
It's Bernie's job to go out, right?
How can I blame you for it?
Nice and slow. Nice and slow.
You'll be all right.
Pete, you're next.
Take it nice and slow. Easy, easy.
Come on!
You gotta go, we're leaving nobody behind!
Eldon, get on the ladder!
Come on, we gotta get them down!
She's slipping!
We gotta get off this ship!
Hurry!
Eldon? How you doing?
I'm scared.
Well...
Gonna be a lot scarier up here without us.
You gotta listen to me!
Eldon.
You just follow right behind me.
If I can do it, anyone can.
Come on!
Tiny!
Tiny! Tiny, hold on!
Hey!
Eldon.
Eldon!
Eldon, look at me!
Look at me!
When I say jump, let go.
You ready?
Jump!
You okay?
We're riding so heavy,
you can hardly steer.
Sir, they're saying there's still
seven or eight up there on board.
Maybe we take these guys back in...
and come back out.
We can't leave them out here alone.
That boat won't last.
We all live, or we all die.
Right?
You, uh...
You did good.
You should be
the last one off, Mr. Sybert.
Last man!
Hey, Fitz!
Turn off that search light, yeah?
We were in radio contact
with the McCullough.
They said they lost four men,
but saved the rest.
The captain of the Pollock Rip
sent word that they...
Mr. Cluff!
It's the 36500! It's Bernie!
It's right there on the radio.
Station Chatham? Station Chatham, copy?
CG-36500, this is Station Chatham.
Webber, is that you?
Yes, sir, it's me. It's Bernie.
We got 32 survivors aboard...
from the tanker Pendleton, sir.
Station Chatham, do you copy?
36500, Station Chatham.
Did you say you have 32 survivors on board?
They rescued them.
They rescued 32 of them!
Yes, sir, 32.
Sir, we've lost our compass,
so we don't know where we are.
But we're gonna try to make it back home.
Can't get back without a compass.
- Not in this weather.
- They're not gonna make it back.
You lost your compass, Webber.
Negative, 36500,
this is the Pollock lightship.
Do not proceed to shore.
We're five miles northeast
of the Pendleton's last known location.
Proceed to our position. Over.
CG-36500, Station Chatham.
Proceed to the Pollock lightship...
and unload all survivors. Over.
What do they know, right?
Right, Richie?
CG-36500, do you copy?
If they know where they are
someone tell me where I am...
because I don't know
where the hell we are.
Webber, do you copy?
I'm not heading out to sea.
No.
This is Station Chatham. Do you copy?
We just got you all off a boat...
so there's no way we're gonna
get you all back up one.
CG-36500, this is Station Chatham.
Webber, your orders are to proceed...
five miles northeast...
and unload all survivors
onto the Pollock...
Sounds like he cut off
his radio, Mr. Cluff.
He's going it on his own.
Bernie Webber.
What do ya know?
How are they gonna find their way home?
He must have shut off his radio.
Those poor boys.
I can't believe that's happening.
Some more stuff in the car.
Power's out now.
- How they gonna see their way home?
- Power's out.
The whole town. The power's out.
- Worse than last year.
- They'll never make it.
Let's get down to the pier.
How'd you find us without a compass?
We, uh...
We just jogged along with
the seasonal currents.
I think we just got lucky.
Yeah.
Lucky.
So, you know how to get home?
To be honest with ya, I'm not sure.
Just disobeyed all my ranking officers...
and they don't know...
so I guess I'd better then, right?
Had the wind on my left going out.
Figure if I, uh...
keep her on my right we ought to be
heading the right direction.
We just follow the lights on shore.
Follow all the lights on shore.
Well, we're in your hands, Captain.
Listen up!
I'll put the sea behind us.
Just let it push us along
till we lay up somewhere.
The storm's easing up, boys...
so we just look for the lights
on the shore to guide us in.
Even if we have to go so far
as Nobska Point, so be it.
We just gotta find land.
Been one heck of a long day,
right, fellas?
Yeah.
Sure has.
But don't you give up hope on me now.
She's a good boat. She'll get us through.
We'll get you home, okay?
We're all going home.
We're with you, Skipper!
Yeah!
Keep your lights on! Like she's doing!
Quick, turn your lights on!
Turn your headlights on! Everyone!
Turn 'em on!
More lights so they can see us!
I think we made it over the bar.
I think high tide carried us over.
Richie, you see that?
Fitz!
Turn on the search light!
Look, you see that?
Is it them?
Well done, Bernie!
You did it, Webber!
Way to go, Webber!
36500 is now docking at the Chatham pier.
There appear to be 32 survivors, sir.
Repeat, they have 32 survivors.
That's right.
Throw it, son.
Attaboy, Bernie!
Give 'em a hand.
Good to see you. Get on up here.
Nice and easy.
We never thought we'd see you again.
This guy's freezing. Give me your coat.
Go on in. It's warm inside.
Let's get you up to the lodge.
Next up. Come on, now. I got you.
Good job, Captain.
Way to go, Bernie.
Webber.
Bernie.
Let's go home.
Are we still good for April 16th?
- Yeah.
I asked Cluff for ya.
He said it's just a...
Just a formality.
Now I know, right?
When I was a little boy
Or so my mother told me
Way, haul away
We'll haul away Joe
We rode it far, homeward bound
Took it free and easy
Setting sail to newfound lands
The wind was high and breezy
We overcome and rose above
The storm that we were facing
Finally arriving home
Together, warm and safely
Hey, haul away
Hey, haul away Joe
We sail on away
With the music playing freely
Our spirits light and gay
We sail on today
Way, haul away
We'll haul away Joe
Now up aloft
This yard must go
We'll pull her free and easy
-== [ www.OpenSubtitles.org ] ==-