Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
This is the house, man.
shot 'em all one by one in the head.
my god, it's so creepy.
come on, it's not that bad.
is there still stuff
in there?
yeah. apparently
when it all happened,
they just packed up and left.
they didn't even take
any of the furniture. it
was all just left there.
wait. so there's
still beds in there?
oh, yeah, there's
still beds in there.
maybe we should check it out.
yeah, we should
check it out. come on.
okay. come on.
what exactly happened?
i heard some really creepy
stuff about the whole thing.
i don't know.
dude was just crazy.
apparently when he was at
the police station,
he said it was just too
easy to kill 'em all.
it was just
too easy to stop.
weren't they found on their stomachs
or something like that?
yeah. they were all,
like, flipped.
so, like,
laying face down.
that's disgusting.
hey! hey!
you ready yet?
come on.
relax.
dude, i thought you'd
be done by now. come on.
yeah, i've almost
got it, okay?
how do you know how
to do this, anyways?
my mom's a realtor.
so he's--
it's one of these codes, okay?
there's, like,
five universal codes and...
yes!
my name is donny reddit.
this may be the last time
i'm ever filming anything.
if you find this,
make sure you tell my mom
i love her.
actually, no.
tell her i hate her.
she's a bitch.
come on.
how creepy is this?
donny, how many people
did you say
were killed here?
i don't know.
like, four or something.
some guy went crazy and just, like,
killed his entire family.
how'd he do it?
he shot them while they
were sleeping in bed.
like, one by one.
what? what?
what the fuck is that?
did you see that?
did you see--
you guys are probably
just freaking out.
there's nothing
actually there.
oh, get out!
get out!
go fuck yourself,
okay?
have you-- how much
you been drinking, huh?
are you drunk yet?
are you completely--
i know. up front,
ooh, yeah, scary.
i'm going to explore her.
we've been in the rest
of the house.
haven't seen anything.
well, not anything.
yeah. i see something.
let's get
the party started.
oh, my god.
this is so creepy.
i like the light on better.
i wonder if somebody died
in here.
oh, look at that.
did you see this clock?
i'm almost done. yeah.
just give me a sec.
you done?
i am so done.
yeah?
it's... you have no--
and i'm almost finished.
i can't believe it.
oh, my god.
jesus. what?
what's wrong?
tyler, off the lawn.
yes, sir.
have a little respect.
hi.
how are you?
tony benson.
nice to meet you.
very nice to meet you.
camilla weldon.
this is my wife virginia.
hi there.
hi. very nice to meet you.
and this is my youngest,
melanie.
hi, melanie.
and we have
sergeant tyler here.
just don't bother him.
he thinks he's the
next steven spielberg.
he films everything.
oh, don't we all. yeah.
and my oldest
daughter lori.
lori, off the phone,
please. now.
get the fuck
out of my face.
okay. let's take
a look around.
great.
just so you guys know,
we do have some other
places available to show you
if you would be
interested in those.
oh, i think i would
be very interested.
i don't think that'll
be necessary.
i have a good feeling
about this one.
after you.
okay, then-- stop.
right this way.
all right.
let's go, troops.
go. come on.
so you guys can see
actually it needs a little
bit of a paint job.
that's completely at your
discretion, obviously.
it's perfect.
great. then let's take
a little bit more
of a look at the place.
tyler.
very nice open floor plan.
honey, here is
your gourmet kitchen.
this house
sucks balls.
are you out
of your mind talking like that?
i don't know--
douglas.
do you understand me?
get out of my face.
just tell me
what this is.
that's something
i'm gonna fix.
absolutely.
it's perfect.
look at these counters.
it's nice. yeah.
it's-- i love it.
it feels like home to me.
it feels like home.
there's space for a garden.
we could have a garden.
a football field mainly.
okay.
a little garden.
well, there could be a football
field there, but over here--
the tire swing comes with
the house, i imagine.
does the tire swing
come with the house?
yes. it comes
with the house.
how do you guys feel
about the house?
tyler, forward march.
come on.
yes, sir.
yeah. so follow me
right this way.
well, what about
this room right here?
is that another bedroom?
yes, that is
a bedroom.
oh.
what?
let's wait out here,
buddy.
dad, what's that?
huh.
yeah.
nothing we can't handle.
this is
totally my room.
okay. so thank you guys
so much for coming.
i will let you guys hang
out and discuss a little bit
how you feel
about the house,
and i will be right outside
if you guys
have any questions.
okay, great. thank you.
okay. thank you.
there's something weird
about her.
be nice, please.
well, what do you think?
i love it, daddy.
thank you.
do you hear that?
well, she doesn't
really know
what happened here,
does she?
look...
they don't need to know
what happened here, okay?
we don't want it to
seem worse than it looks.
this is what we can
afford right now, okay?
i understand that.
i mean,
it has enough bedrooms.
i know, i know, i know.
okay. if it's--
for the money,
it's exactly--
it's all we can get.
we can't move anymore.
okay.
this is it.
are you all right
with it?
i'm all right with it.
you sure?
i'm sure.
i love you.
i love you, too.
we're home!
yay!
oh, my god!
take the family inside.
call 911.
go inside, go inside.
call 911. just do it.
go on, do it.
go, go, go, go.
hey, mom.
hey, honey.
i'm really not in the mood
for the camera today, okay?
you should be
helping someone
and not playing
with the camera.
enough with the camera.
off, please.
yes, ma'am.
make yourself useful, son.
yes, sir.
hey, what are you doing?
i was just talking
to my friend.
his name is john.
oh.
john matthews.
you know he's not
really there, right?
there's no one there.
but i saw him.
hey, look.
doggies!
you guys
are moving in here?
yeah.
it's the new home.
we have to keep moving
because she keeps
getting in trouble.
will you knock it off?
is that right?
what'd you do?
nothing. he's just
being a twerp.
oh. well, i'm greg.
lori. nice
to meet you.
lori.
kristen.
where are you guys from?
north carolina.
nice. well, we live just
a couple houses down
if you guys ever want to
hang out or anything.
sure. i don't know
anyone around here so...
yeah.
funny doggies.
they don't bite.
don't worry.
yeah.
nice doggies.
all right. well, i guess we'll
see you guys around.
cool. yeah.
bye, guys.
bye-bye, doggies.
yeah. but, you know,
like i said, the tires.
i mean, that's
really kicking ass.
so i have, like, probably 16
inch, like, tires around.
yeah.
hey, you guys
know what house this is?
what?
do you know
what house this is?
it's your house.
it's the amityville house.
amityville house?
what's that?
you don't know what
the amityville house is?
you know what
oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
the amityville house.
that's where
they make those cookies.
cookies.
no, it's supposed
to be haunted.
haunted? really?
better get out of here.
yeah. 'cause
everybody knows
that haunted houses,
black people die first.
so you better
get out of here.
hit the road, pal.
no, for real, man?
amityville, for real?
what is that?
gentlemen, i want this
wrapped up by 1400.
move it. come on, move.
ugh.
so why'd you get
that tattoo?
sat down.
the tattoo?
you're a little too young
for that, kid.
yeah. so i think this
is the last of it.
we probably should go
ahead and get on out of here.
i'm ready
to get out of here.
these guys are so lame.
what are they doing?
aha. aha.
did you see that?
i told you it was haunted.
really? just walk away?
come on.
the movers are so stupid.
why would they carry, like,
four boxes at a time
that are so heavy?
what?
are you going to move?
uh, no. i'm making
a documentary.
why are you so grumpy?
i'm working.
now move!
sorry.
that guy is such a jerk.
whoa. my sister's door
just opened.
let's go investigate.
ahh.
that goes in the study.
i'm starting to see what
you mean about this house, kid.
it sucks.
dad!
hey, mom.
oh, god.
tyler, i'm really not
in the mood right now.
but, mom--
but, mom, what?
it's for my documentary.
honey, it's just not
a really good time.
but, mom, please?
do you think
the house is haunted?
no. no, i don't think
the house is haunted.
i just think i didn't
want to live here.
i told your dad
i wanted to keep looking
at other places,
and your dad insisted,
and i just didn't feel
like this place
was a good fit for us,
for our family.
but two people died.
i know that. that's
what i'm trying to say.
god.
that's why i asked
if it was haunted.
honey, let's stop
talking about hauntings, okay?
just take
your camera and go.
i'm not in the mood
to be interviewed.
i'm sorry. just... okay.
it's still 5:00.
what the heck.
dad needs to fix it.
doug. doug.
what?
what? can we talk about
what happened today?
honey, calm down, okay?
i am calm.
this is about as calm as
i can get right now.
i'm sorry.
sweetheart,
what's going on?
a man died--
i am trying to stay calm.
i'm trying to
stay calm for you,
i'm trying to stay calm
for these kids,
but there's a man--
a man died here today.
honey, accidents-- in
this house, in our house.
honey, accidents
happen, okay?
maybe you're used
to seeing accidents.
i'm not used to seeing
accidents, okay?
listen,
just calm down, okay?
you're going
to scare the kids.
they can hear you.
i'm going to scare
the kids?
a man died
in this house.
the realtor died.
what am i supposed
to tell lori and mel?
listen, you're letting
this get to your head.
accidents happen.
the realtor
had an aneurism out front.
what are you
talking about?
i'm not letting
anything get to my head.
people fall down.
the man fell down.
the kids are asking--
calm down. jesus.
the kids
are asking questions.
what am i
supposed to tell them
when they ask me
questions
about what happened
to that man?
honey, accidents happen.
is that all you can say
is accidents happen?
because it does.
i don't like it here!
i don't feel
comfortable here!
you need... i don't
like it here!
i told you i didn't
want to live here!
i told you we should
keep looking,
and you said no,
it had to be here.
it does have to be here,
and you know why
it has to be here.
you know
we have to live here.
why?
this is what we can do.
this is what our means
can afford right now.
i don't like it.
sweetheart, come here.
it's not right.
it's okay.
it's not okay.
it is.
that's just coincidence.
these things happen, okay?
that's such crap!
it's this house!
shh! calm down.
you think that the house made
the guy fall down?
i don't know.
you think the house made lori act
funny and cry in her room?
that's like
every other day, okay?
do you think the house
made tyler act a little funny?
i am sorry, but a man
dying in my house
does not happen
every other day.
there's probably 100 people
that died in this house.
oh, my god. what
are you talking about?
it's a 150-year-old house.
you tell that to mel.
why don't you go
in her room right now
and tell that to her!
that it's
completely normal!
mel loves it here.
to have dead people
in your house!
i'm sorry. it's crap.
i don't feel right here.
what do you suggest we do?
i want to go
someplace else.
i want to keep looking.
please.
come here. sit down.
i don't like this place.
i know, honey.
can you give it
a few more days?
i promise,
everything's fine.
i promise. all right?
i'm sorry.
i'll give it
a few more days.
please.
but after that--
okay. would you do it for me?
yes.
just trust me.
you fucking
little pervert.
get the fuck
out of my room.
i'm really sorry about what
your brother did.
that was not fair.
mom, he was standing in
the crack of my door.
i know, honey.
i will talk to him.
your dad and i will--
he's not going to--
i know. listen,
i will talk with your dad.
we'll make sure it
doesn't happen again, okay?
honey, i know today has
been a really awful day.
it's been a very
upsetting day. i'm sorry.
i just want to go home.
oh, honey, we are home.
mom, no.
yeah. come on, honey.
we all have to try our
best to make it work here.
i'm sorry, but we really
all have to put in 100 %, okay?
mom, someone died
here today.
i know, baby.
i'm sorry. i'm so sorry that
you had to see that.
we have some watermelon.
we have eggs, so we can make
a hard boiled egg,
and we also have
some peanut butter.
we have carrots,
and we also have
some avocado
to make a dip
for you to dip
some chips in.
so we've--and if you want
something to drink,
we also have
some sprite.
we have
a fruit-flavored punch.
we also have
cherry-strawberry flavor.
we have dr. pepper
and we have--
there's some baking powder
if you want me to bake you some
cookies or something.
we just survived our first day
in the amityville house.
creepy.
when our realt or showed
us the house that day,
she died from
an an-an-aneurism.
and then, like,
today the mover,
he was carrying
a really heavy box,
fell down the stairs and
it landed on his head.
it just killed him.
it was weird.
my closet door just opened.
nobody's in there.
aah!
what?
you didn't, like,
accidentally...
the door shut or something?
no. when i went to bed,
the door was closed.
it was locked.
you know it was open
this morning.
wide open.
i was up at 4:00 a.m.
really? that's weird.
i don't know.
it wasn't you?
no, honey.
it wasn't me.
well, you know
what it is.
what?
lori snuck out.
no.
no, honey. no.
the door was wide open.
that little monster
forgot to shut the
door when she came back in.
we just got here.
where would she go?
she doesn't even know
anyone.
excuse me.
that kid with the dogs.
that boy who came
with the dogs.
the boy with the dogs?
oh, my god.
gets here one day.
she meets one kid,
and she's out the window.
that better not be true.
i'm sorry.
it is true.
what else would it be?
well... i can't believe that.
good morning.
breakfast time.
it could've been tyler.
good morning, melanie. you
know how he likes--
good morning,
daddy.
tyler? i highly doubt
it. it could've been him.
my closet door
opened last night.
good morning, tyler.
she snuck out the door.
she snuck out.
what do you want to do?
why are you doing
that bowl?
it's for my friend.
well, your friend
doesn't need that much.
that's good.
just get the cheese.
all right. what do
you want to do about this?
i don't know,
but you think--
he really likes cereal.
my closet door
opened last night.
you can have milk in it.
listen, now.
you, over here now. now.
do you want some
breakfast cereal?
right here, right now.
she's getting
in trouble again.
what?
what'd you do?
what are you
talking about?
you left the door open.
you snuck out
and you left the door open.
dad, what are you talking
about? i didn't leave.
don't lie to me.
this is the fifth time
we have moved
on account of you.
this isn't fair!
five times--
why do you
always think it's me?
go pack your bags,
little girl.
pack your bags.
military school.
douglas, stop.
say goodbye to your hair.
that's a little much.
good lord,
with the hair.
tyler.
do you like juice?
did you leave the back door
open last night?
no, but my closet door
opened last night.
you didn't leave
the back door open.
no.
don't lie to me.
tyler, this is serious.
did you go out?
were you playing around?
mel, did you leave the back
door open last night?
no.
i'm sure.
you sure?
don't lie to me.
why would i come down
here and play with the door?
honey, she didn't leave
the door open.
it wasn't her, okay?
just relax.
sweetheart, don't-- juice.
drink your juice.
okay.
you know what?
we need a day off.
this has been
a long couple of days.
you know what?
movie day.
yay!
we'll all go
to the movies.
movie day. yes!
what do you think?
you want
to go see a movie.
you all go see a movie.
get lunch,
get some ice cream.
please, mommy?
okay. everybody
go upstairs and change.
we're going to go
to the movies.
movies!
yes!
a movie day.
yay. come on, john.
yes. finally.
- sergeant?
- yes.
front and center, buddy.
yes, sir.you're staying
with me, pal.
yes, sir.
come on.
what are you looking at?
huh?
punk.
okay, guys.
we're leaving.
all right. hey, look...
ooh,
what's he doing now?
i'm sorry, okay?
hey, look,
i'm sorry, all right?
it's the emotion
of the new house.
is he apologizing?
i know you didn't
sneak out, okay?
i'm sorry i yelled at you,
all right?
come on, honey.
lori, come on.
let's go. see
you later, honey.
have fun, guys.
see you later. have fun.
bye, daddy.
bye. bye.
bye-bye, daddy.
bye, honey.
bye, guys.
have fun.
okay.
see you soon.
enjoy lunch.
bye.
what are you doing, dad?
shh.
what?
sorry.
get ready, buddy.
let's go.
oh, wait. keys.
where are we going?
just going on a ride.
put the camera down.
what are we doing, dad?
well, you know,
these old houses don't have
security systems,
so we're going
to put one in.
s-o-p.
standard operating
position.
come on. you can do
better than that, son.
uh, standard operating
procedure?
outstanding.
this is boring.
why are we doing this?
just shut your yap
and come over here
and help me.
yes, sir.
piece of crap ladder.
all right.
you have the tools?
yes.
perfect.
what?
tyler.
i need a screwdriver.
there's none in there?
no. go to the kitchen
and get me
a screwdriver.
this is
a socket wrench set.
yes, sir.
now! double time.
jesus.
okay, okay.
where is it, dad?
it's in the drawer
by the chopping block.
crap.
what the hell was that?
nothing, dad.
that was something.
it was nothing.
where did this phone
come from?
tyler!
yeah?
what are you doing?
just a second, dad.
dad! dad! i found this
phone in the kitchen!
i found this phone, dad.
give me the screwdriver.
just a second. here.
here it is.
screwdriver.
here.
thank you.
look, i found
this phone, dad,
and there's a movie on it.
there were some kids
in our house.
what are you
talking about?
look. look at the phone.
there's a movie on it.
look at the phone.
jesus christ.
it's dead.
then i'll go charge it.
tyler, tyler, stop.
yes, sir.
put the phone down,
put the camera down,
and get over here
and help your dad.
yes, sir.
now hold the ladder,
will you?
what the hell was that?
the tools fell.
how did you
knock those over?
i didn't.
tyler.
i didn't-- the camera.
pick 'em up.
maybe the camera saw it.
tyler, turn the camera off.
yes, sir.
get over here.
turn that off,
pick up the tools,
get over here and--
there's something
on this phone.
i don't know what it is.
but i'm going to find
out what's on the phone.
hey, ladies.
how are you?
you look good.
how was the movie?
i'm tired of everybody not
believing me about my closet
and then today
the tool box fell
and my dad
blamed it all on me.
i'm just tired of it.
so i'm going to use
this camcorder
to videotape everything
that happens in my room tonight.
so i'm going
to go set it up.
i just hate it when
people don't believe me.
i can't wait for this ipod
to get charged
to show everybody the movie.
yes?
hey, honey.
it's time for dinner.
okay. but, mom, can you watch
this video, please?
what video?
there's a video
on this ipod.
here.
what am i watching?
there were some kids that
snuck into our house,
i don't know when,
and they--
oh, that is our house.
they were looking
for ghosts.
oh, honey, they're not
looking for ghosts.
yes, they are.
no, sweetie. they're
not looking for ghosts.
they're just playing around
with their cameras.
no, they aren't.
who else do we know that plays
around with their cameras?
they're not
looking for ghosts.
come on.
it's time for dinner.
but--
no, honey. dinner's ready, okay?
yes, ma'am.
come on.
so today when we woke up, the
back door was wide open.
my dad thinks
lori snuck out,
but then he started
apologizing to her
and he put this
alarm system in
because he thought
that old houses
don't have alarm systems,
so he put that in.
i think it's because of
lori, but he doesn't.
i don't know.
and then tonight for
dinner, mel was throwing a fit
because mom wouldn't
give her 'friend' dessert.
so that was awkward.
whoa! it's 3:15.
this is when it all started.
tyler! get upstairs! now!
okay.
go!
whoa. what the heck?
someone must've tried
to break in,
and i guess the alarm
scared him off.
that was just so weird.
it all happened at 3:15
like the original
amityville house thing.
that was just so weird.
what the... what is it doing?
whoa.
what are they doing?
why are they looking at
allthe stoves and stuff?
whoa, never seen
that before.
wonder where this came from.
what the... what-- what's--
what's hap--
what? no, no.
what? no.
what--
what's it doing?
come on, work. work.
we've been in
the rest of the house
and haven't seen it.
oh, my god.
is that our kitchen?
yes,
that's our kitchen.
yes, that's the kitchen.
yes. yes, it is.
does she have beer?
is that beer? that's beer.
i don't know.
just keep watching.
i'm not
exactly sure--
who is this kid?
do you know this kid?
lori, do you know him?
you don't know him?
no, i don't know him.
i'm positive.
you're sure?
all right, all right.
she doesn't know him.
yeah, that's our house.
there's the clock.
you videotaped this
on your phone?
when did this happen?
yes, but
just keep watching.
yeah, when was this?
tyler, where'd you get
this video?
i found it.
just keep watching.
yes.
you found it?
oh! oh!
oh, my god.
you know what?
this is ridiculous.
tyler.
something happened to
them. just keep watching.
something happened-- yeah,
something happened.
just keep watching.
something happens to them.
nothing happens. they're just
screwing around.
yeah, they're just playing
around the rest of the time.
tyler. how long
have you had this?
how long-- just keep--
this is our kitchen.
it's not fair.
you don't believe me.
something did
happen to them.
honey, we know
something happened,
but it's none
of your business.
okay, enough of this.
enough of this.
tyler, we've got
a job to do today.
we're checking
for security breaches.
let's walk the perimeter.
i really want this gone.
i don't want you to have
it anymore, okay? tyler.
come on, buddy.
yes, sir.
tyler!
yes, ma'am. yes, sir.
what are we
doing this for, dad?
someone broke into our house
last night, tyler.
how do you know it was
someone and not something?
hmm. it's got a grate.
it's not that bad.
like a ghost.
what if it was a ghost?
tyler, cut it out,
will you?
how come everybody else gets
to do what they want?
can i please go do
something else? please?
tyler, we're working
today, all right?
so i need you
to cooperate, okay?
dad, dad, look at all the
flies on the window.
tyler, quit
screwing around.
but, dad--
do you want to chop
woodtill december?
why don't we just buy wood?
do you want to chop woodtill
december starting today?
no, but we could just buy
wood. i didn't think so.
john matthews, do
you think that you like
the little star clips that
i put in his ears?
mel, honey.
what, daddy?
who told you
about john matthews?
nobody did.
did tyler tell you?
no.
she's been talking
to john matthews
for the past few days,
and i haven't
told her anything.
that's her little friend.
did you tell her
about john matthews?
no. that's
her little friend.
don't lie to me.
i'm not lying.
doesn't she always
tell you the truth?
who told you, honey?
did lori tell you?
no.
did mommy tell you?
john matthews told me.
no, honey.
not john matthews.
who told you
about john matthews?
nobody told me
about him, daddy.
he's sitting right here.
he's my friend
and he told me
that he used to live
in this house
and he was nine.
what else
does he tell you?
i can't tell you.
it's a secret.
honey, we're just concerned
because daddy saw mel talking
to an imaginary friend
whose name was john matthews.
we're just wondering
if maybe you accidentally
said something?
you know,
john matthews is the guy,
the little boy that used
to live in this house.
dad, like i'd say
anything about that.
i didn't even know that.
well, maybe you were
just chatting with, like, mom
or chatting with that kid
you met the other day
with the dogs.
no. i haven't even
talked to that kid.
honey, you don't have
to get defensive.
we're not accusing you.
you guys are accusing me.
you always accuse me.
will you listen to me?
i'm not accusing you, honey.
we're just asking if maybe
you said something
to one of your friends, maybe
that guy with the dogs.
no. i didn't say anything.
we're trying to figure out
how mel found out
about this stuff.
she's out there--
yeah, that'sa good question,
dad, but it wasn't me.
okay. well, you can
calm down, all right?
please don't get so defensive.
i'm not.
you're being
defensive, honey.
i am not, dad.
just calm down.
i'm just asking
a simple question.
were you and tyler
discussing it?
did you say something
to tyler?
no. i haven't
talked to tyler.
he's been annoying
the crap out of me.
i know. i know.
he's annoying everyone.
he's going crazy.
we're worried about that.
maybe she just heard you--
tyler! tyler!
tyler, you've gotto be
kidding me. mom! -tyler!
hey, mom.
hey, honey.
i'm here to talk to you
about that camera.
do you think you can
get it out of my face?
yes.
thank you.
honey, look, i know
that you're bored.
i know that there
just doesn't seem
to be a lot of stuff
to do around here,
but the camera's
making things worse.
you're always
in everyone's face.
you really need
to lay off lori, okay?
she's a young woman.
she needs her privacy.
okay, mom. i'll try.
do you promise?
i promise. i promise.
douglas!
yeah. be right there.
today it was weird.
first, my dad had us
checking for security breaches
because of last night.
and then mel, she was just
being weirder than usual.
she had a full conversation
with her little friend
john matthew,
and my dad, i think
he finally believes me.
she's talking to somebody.
and then lori, she got me
in trouble today
just 'cause
i was spying on her.
who cares? everybody
gets spied on
every once in a while by
their brother or sister.
and i got lectured
because of that.
nobody knows what it's like
being a kid,
except for kids, that is.
it's just not fair.
my parents don't even
know what i'm going through.
it sucks.
doug?
honey?
doug.
what?
you coming up to bed?
are the kids tucked in?
yeah, the kids
are tucked in.
i'm just going to read for
a little bit, okay?
okay.
i'll be right up.
it's not good to read
in such low light.
gotcha!
what are you doing
in my house?
what are you
fucking doing?
you know this guy?
what's going on?
lori! lori!
go get inside.
i'm so sick of this.
i am tired of it.
you stay away
from my daughter, boy.
you hear me?
i'll blow you
to pieces right now.
i'm sorry.
stay away from my family.
get the hell
out of here now.
move it. move!
see you later, loser.
dad?
dad. dad, what happened?
get inside. we're
calling the cops.
what?
my dad was right
and so was i.
lori was the one
sneaking out.
it was a weird night.
greg comes in, lori's
got to sneak out...
and my dad almost
killed him with a gun.
that was kind of funny.
he gets ready to get
kicked out and leave,
and he gets yanked out.
he goes off the ground
and everything.
it was scary.
that's scarier
than everything else.
it's just, it's just...
son, where's your dad?
he's over there.
hey, gunny.
hey, how's it going?
it's good.
i'm sorry you're
going through all this.
that's all right.
i went around the perimeter
of the whole house
and i couldn't find
anything.
i went through the bushes,
under the tables, everything.
through the trees.
nothing.
so what else
are you seeing here?
well, this kid broke
into the house tonight.
it's that kid, isn't it?
it's a kid.
i don't know his name.
greg. is he-- greg?
i think it's greg.
my daughter, you know,
we're new here.
she met this guy greg.
she turned off the alarm.
she left the back door
open for him.
she did it
the night before, too.
okay.
i came down at 4:00
in the morning.
i got up to do my workout
and the door
is wide open.
i don't know
if he came in.
i don't know what happened.
but tonight i stayed up.
i caught him.
okay. let me tell you
something about this kid.
i chased him
out the front door.
let me tell you something
about this kid, okay?
this kid's trouble.
he is?
yes. he's done this
many times
with girls around
the neighborhood.
he breaks in.
it figures.
and he plays around
with the girls
and he causes a whole
bunch of trouble.
well, my daughter's...
notorious.
we've moved five times in
the past 18 months--
you moved five times?
we've moved five times.
okay.
so this is pretty much
it for us right now.
i mean,
we're staying here.
but, i mean, it's already
starting up, so...
but i chased him out.
he's not coming back.
i mean, if he knows
what's best for him,
he's not coming back.
a lot of people scare this
kidand he still comes back.
so just be wary of that,
but i don't think you
have anything to worry about.
so what i'll do--
since it's night,
i'll come back tomorrow morning and
look around in daylight
to see if there's
anything i can find
just to double check for you
to make sure that
you're okay with that.
that'd be great.
all right?
all right, buddy.
so i'm gonna take off.
i'll be here about 9:00 in
the morning tomorrow.
perfect. okay.
i'll give you a call before--
call me before.
i'm on my way
over here. okay?
i appreciate it, man.
no problem.
have a good one.
appreciate it.
all right.
thanks for coming out.
no problem, gunny.
i did a search around the
perimeter of your house,
and i found a substantial
amount of blood.
what?
there's blood back there.
yes.
what the hell?
so i'm going to refer
this to a detective.
well, what--was it--
there was a struggle?
i can't go into any more
detail than that.
but you didn't see
a struggle?
i really can't go
into any more detail
because it's not
my department.
i have to refer it
to a detective.
so you can't
tell where the blood's from?
i have no idea.
he said there's clothes.
is that right?
there was a shirt.
was it torn up?
i mean--
i really can't
go into more
because i don't know.
i mean, there's clearly
an attack.
i don't want to get
you guys riled up or upset
because-- let's just have a
detective come in,
and he'll do
his investigation, okay?
okay.
a pool of blood?
can i talk
to you guys outside?
yeah.
tyler, god.
tyler.
turn the camera off.
turn it off.
i want to listen, too.
so i'm going to have
the detective
call you guys
this afternoon, okay?
i'm going to be
on top of this.
i'm going to be following
upon all this for you,
giving you updates,
but he's going to handle the
investigation from here.
dna and that type of thing.
great.
forensics, okay?
oh, also i'm going to be--
it was just
a pool of blood?
just a pool of blood.
- thank you, john.
there weren't tracks
or anything.
what the hell?
i have no idea.
that's fine.
so, john, let's give him
a bath after this.
come on, help me get this
stuff out of his fur.
would you please
give me the tape?
will i get it back?
get the tape.
sorry about that.
- not a problem.
- listen, i just want you to know
we appreciate
what you're doing.
i mean, i know this is--
now the get the hair
away from his eyes.
we're really frazzled.
- i understand.
that's why i don't want
to go into more detail.
'cause i don't know
what it is
or i don't know
what it could be.
so i just want to,
you know--
let's just wait and see.
tyler, i said turn the
goddamn camera off, all right?
turn it off! now!
off! off!
i have one more
question, though.
thank you so much.
no problem. i'll be in touch.
like i said, if you need
anything, call.
okay. thank you,
officer.
no problem.
oh.
john, i think it's time
for him to have
his bath now, don't you?
who are you talking to,
sweetie?
john.
honey, are
you always talking to john?
pretty much.
he's my friend, daddy.
now, you know it's okay to
have imaginary friends,
but you don't need
to talk to them--
he's not
my imaginary friend.
all the time. okay?
he's sitting right there.
how you doing?
i'm good.
i was just pushing him
on the swing.
you are?
are you having fun?
yeah.
i love you.
thank you.
hi. how's it going?
good. go ahead
and take a seat.
look, i wish i had more
to tell you folks
at this time, but i don't.
all forensics is telling me
right now
is it is human blood, but
we don't got a body yet.
we got nothing to go on.
so all i can say is
they're going to be
testing the results,
taking them to the lab.
maybe one, two days,
we'll have more of
an answer for you folks.
all right.
and before
i head out of here,
i just want to
ask you both a question.
and it's going to be
off the record,
but has anything else
unexplainable happened here?
well, our son felt
like that there was a--
no, no.
no, whoa, whoa.
what'd your son say?
i mean, our son, he
runs around with a camera
and films stuff,
and, you know,
he say
she sees weird things,
but there's really
nothing that has happened
besides, i mean,
the stuff you know about.
right. but in addition to
that, has anything else--
well, there's--unexplain
able happened?
i mean, this is some pretty
crazy stuff out there.
what--what--
yeah. the alarm has gone off.
the alarm has gone off.
the alarm went off twice.
any sign of a break-in or
anything like that?
forced entry?
no. the doors were open and
we had locked them.
the doors were open
after you'd locked them both.
besides last night, the
night before, i got up.
as far as i know,
we locked the doors
when we went to bed,
but i got up and the door
was wide open.
these doors right here.
the alarm went off,
you know,
last night
and the night before.
at the same time.
you folks aren't from
around here, are you?
no.no.
no? but you're familiar with
the history of this house?
i mean, generally.
as far as the movies, the
books, everything like that?
yeah.
of course.
then you know what happened here
in the seventies, right?
because that really happened.
this kid named ronnie
defeooffed his ma, his pa,
his two little brothers,
and his sisters.
all right.
they killed six people.
now, after that, the
book, the movie came out.
you're all
familiar with that.
but everyone thought
at some point
that ronnie was
responsible for the murders...
...that he wasn't
the one behind it.
it was his sister
and some other accomplice.
they don't know who
the third guy is,
but it turns out
that ronnie defeo,
according to this letter,
was not responsible for the
killing of his family.
it was his sister
who was responsible.
now, this letter came
out, what, like, 1998, 1999,
about 12, 11 years ago.
and since that time,
there have been eight
different families
who lived in this house.
and before that there
were maybe four or five,
and we're talking
about 75 years
of this house
being in this area.
but within the last 12 years,
there have been eight
different families who lived here.
all right. so, okay.
there's been eight
different families. so--
but nothing
has happened to them.
nothing has
happened to them, but...
i don't think one family
has stayed here
longer than one,
two months, maybe tops.
did they give a reason
why they moved?
no, just up and left.
most of them even left their
deposits on the house.
huh.
you got the place
pretty cheap, didn't you?
yeah.
yes.
you didn't give any more
thought about that,
why it might be
so reasonable?
well, we wanted
to think about-- honey.
all right, look,
i'm sorry i even
said anything. look--
it's all right.
it's fine.
the best thing
i can say right now
is that we're going to find
out what we can with forensics
and get back to you as
soon as possible, all right?
we appreciate that.
thank you.
all right.
thanks.
thanks, detective.
if you need anything,
i'll be in here.
just...
you two knew the history of
this house, right?
yeah.
can i ask
an honest question?
why'd you move here?
they need
to fix that clock.
so what did
the detective say, dad?
we need, like, 15 cameras and
motion censors, infrared.
was somebody murdered?
they find anything?
there was, like,
100 people out there.
guns. god,
i hope we have time.
who are you
calling, dad?
yeah. hey, cut,
this is gunny.
i hate it when
my parents ignore me.
yeah, save the small talk
for later, bud.
i know it's been a while,
but i've got a situation
i need you to come up for.
today was kind of messed up.
i've never seen so many cops
in my life.
they were just all huddled
and there was a bunch of
guys with suitcases.
i overhear
done of them saying
that there was just, like,
a puddle of blood.
i don't know
what it was but...
who's this guy?
hey, sir, are you here
to help us?
my man, cut.
oh, look at you, man.
gunny.
five years.
oh, it's been a while.
damn, it's good
to see you, man.
nice house.
oh, thanks.
dude, i'm telling you.
you all right?
man, i've got to tell you,
i've been better.
really?
yeah. i mean, i've got
a situation here.
i'm glad you're here.
did you hear about george?
yeah, yeah.
man, i would've done
anything to be there.
yeah, i thought you were
going to beat the funeral.
i've just been
caught up with--
i got this-- i got
a thing going on, man.
hey, hey, hey.
look, i usually don't
hear from the boss
until things
are real bad.
yeah, they're bad.
i got some shit going on.
what's going on?
i am damn glad to see you.
so let me show you around,
all right?
look, i got these--
i mean, i pulled my gun
on a kid last night.
my daughter--
a gang kid?
no, not a gang kid.
he's a local kid.
my daughter is just--
she's lost it.
she's out of her mind.
right in here.
she's sneaking out all the
time and stuff, i mean, but...
who's telling you-- you mean
this kid broke in?
yeah. i think he came in the
night before as well.
he came in this back door
over here.
with her or--
i don't know.
i caught him last night.
i mean, i scared the
bejeezus out of this kid.
i pulled my gun.
fucking scared his ass
out the front door.
yes, i can see you.
oh, that's
the gunny i know.
whoa.
what is that stuff?
i'm not
a trouble maker.
this is not fair.
yes, it is fair.
and it's not your place
to say what's fair.
i decide what's fair
or is not fair, okay?
do you understand me?
dad, i'm sorry.
i know you're sorry.
i've heard this before.
i've heard this over and
over and over again.
i just don't know what else
to do, all right?
you've been doing this for
over two years now.
you're just getting all--
- crap.
off track.
it never changes.
dad, i'm sorry.
i'm sorry.
that's all
there is to it.
my way. let us in.
let me in.
lori, don't lock
the door, all right?
this is going to happen whether
you like it or not.
you can make it easy or
you can make it hard.
it's up to you.
okay, okay.
gunny?
yeah, come on.
go ahead.
thank you.
lori.
dad.
all right.
maybe i'm thinking up here.
the wire again?
whoa.
what are you
filming me for, kid?
crap.
so how did you get
that cut on your face?
did you burn yourself?
are you some kind
of paranormal investigator?
i'll ask
a different question.
how--are you
and my dad friends?
yeah. i've known
your pop a long time.
since before
you were born.
so what's the camera for?
well, you got people
breaking in.
how do you know it's
someone and not something?
you know, like a ghost?
are you going to help
us catch the ghost or not?
ghost, huh?
yes.
there's some kind
of ghost in our house.
tyler.
yes.
leave him alone.
yes, sir.
fuck.
you okay, man?
yeah.
get your dad for me.
yes, sir.
done.
so i replaced the one
in the living room.
right?
a nice, tight
small camera.
right out back?
yeah. it's taken.
and then i've got
the one out front.
up and down. all right?
douglas?
i really appreciate it.
i'll be right there.
thank you.
all right. good luck.
a pleasure, man.
all right, man.
it's good to see you.
i'm going to check this one
out before i leave.
all right.
come on, upstairs.
cut, no!
doug?
tyler, stay up here.
stop.
what are you doing?
tyler, stay up here.
tyler, knock it off.
stop messing around.
get up here.
mom?
dad?
please. i'm doing
the best i can.
i'm trying as hard
as i can.
i love you.
i can't fight like this.
i'm doing everything
i can do.
i don't know
what else i can do.
i'm doing everything
i can do.
please help.
please help me.
i'm sorry.
whoa. it's almost noon and
mom's still asleep.
she never sleeps this late.
mom? mom?
wow.
i wonder if lori's
the same way.
who cares?
hey, dad.
dad?
what the--
that one
has to be a line.
yeah,
that'd be awesome.
yeah.
dad, she's talking to
john matthews again.
hello.
i'm catscratch.
i just noticed that your
whiskers are curly.
honey, who are you
talking to?
john matthews.
where is he?
right there.
what are you doing?
you stay away
from my daughter.
stay away from my daughter!
where'd he go, honey?
he's outside, daddy.
stay out of my house.
where is he, baby?
tell me where he is.
he's outside.
don't you ever talk
to him again.
do not ever talk to him
again, okay?
okay, daddy.
promise me.
i have everything
under control.
i have identified the enemy.
i have devised a plan, and
you can all relax.
dad, how could you even--
lori. lori.
everything--
- mommy, i'm scared.
oh, my goodness.
don't worry. don't worry.
it's just a breaker.
i'll go check.
sergeant on my six.
yes, sir.
honey... it's okay.
it's okay.
don't be scared.
it's just the lights.
how do you
know it's just the lights.
i know.
it's just the lights.
see?
okay, guys, listen.
there's a new plan now,
all right?
we are leaving
this house.
okay? we're going
to pack what we can.
we're going to go stay with
aunt lynn and uncle eddie.
okay. they're going tobe
home in a couple days,
and we're going to go.
i want you to pack
your blue suitcase.
fill it up with
as much as you can.
i want you to help--
is daddy going?
of course
daddy's going. yeah.
can john come, too?
what is that stuff?
dad, what are you doing?
he's got some crosses.
dad, what is this stuff?
what are the crosses for?
look at this stuff.
what is it?
i think my dad's
totally lost it.
he's got crosses
and candles,
a bunch of other stuff.
i don't know what that is.
see?
he's going crazy.
honey, what are you doing?
this doesn't make
any sense.
in two days we can go
to aunt linda's.
doug, this
is not helping.
mom,
he's fucking crazy.
he's not going
to listen to you.
lori.
dad! seriously?
what are you doing?
where did you even
get this stuff, dad?
mom, what is he doing?
dad! you're such
a fucking loser,
and i hate you.
i hate you.
that's enough.
do you hear me?
i hate you so, so much.
go to your room.
that's ridiculous.
that is so not helping, lori.
that turkey was good,
wasn't it, john?
hey, mel,
are you playing
with your friend
john matthew again?
uh-huh.
can you ask him
something for me?
sure.
ask him what he wants and
if he wants us to go.
okay. what
do you want, john?
okay. he said that
he wants you, mommy,
and daddy to leave.
what about you, mel?
what do you want
again, john?
all right. he wants me
to stay here forever.
oh, and cat
scratch, too.
uh-huh.
forever?
that's a long time.
i know.
why wouldn't i?
okay.
now listen up.
we are bensons.
we're not afraid
of this crap!
do you understand me?
we are at war.
do you understand
this is war?
i've been in afghanistan.
32 people after meat one time.
32 people and i fucked 'em
like frogs.
i fucked 'em like this.
do you understand
what i'm saying?
we are at war!
say "sir, yes, sir!"
prepare for duty!
yes, sir!
killers and collaborators.
the gates of hell.
we are in the gates of hell!
stand down!
die, little bastard! die!
everybody down.
everyone down.
hit the floor.
what the fuck?
okay, everybody
go upstairs.
everybody upstairs, everybody
upstairs, everybody upstairs.
come on, honey.
it's okay. come on.
everybody upstairs.
my dad had
a nervous breakdown.
he's lost it.
we've actually seen ghosts
in the house,
and i think i'm more afraid
of my dad than the ghost.
my mom says we're going
to aunt linda's in two days
or when she gets back
from vacation.
i'm just hoping
i can make it till then.
aah!
oh, my god.
oh.
mom?
Please rate this subtitle at www.osdb.link/3ryrt
Help other users to choose the best subtitles