Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org
Subtitles by explosiveskull
Resync by GoldenBeard
Picket One, copy.
Do you got eyes
on the hostages?
Still negative.
20 bucks
says they don't show.
You two morons
really making bets
on whether a drug cartel
has executed these hostages?
Abso-fucking-lutely.
I believe
that was implied. Yeah.
Just checking. I'm in for 20.
I got two hostages.
No crosswind.
I'm not waiting. 10-50, out.
Bluebill Two,
are you out there?
Over.
Goddamn it!
Dupree, Jesus!
Where's Haines?
Don't know.
Comm's not fucking working.
Give me the pack.
It's evidence.
Ain't nobody
gonna believe this one.
The fuck is that, Cap?
It's above our pay grade.
Haines! Come in. Over.
Haines, goddamn it,
come in. Over!
Sir?
The fuck is that, Cap?
Comm's not fucking working.
Haines?
Light it up!
Gentlemen, remember...
they're large, they're fast,
and fucking you up's
their idea of tourism!
Go!
Eyes up! Come on!
I want the passenger.
I want the pod.
If it's not from here...
- You want it.
- ...I want it.
I need help.
And I have money.
Why should I help
a man with a gun, eh?
All right.
I need you
to mail this for me.
You send it to this address.
Mail what's in the pack,
not the backpack.
Ahora. Go!
Okay.
Back up!
It was so amazing!
Yeah, it was.
Bye, Mom!
- Do it, man.
- No, you do it.
Okay.
Do it.
Oh, shit.
Looky, looky, loo.
Hey, EJ, you hungry?
I'm hungry for an ass-burger.
Mmm. Sounds delicious.
A nice, big, juicy ass-burger.
Oh, yeah.
The hell are you doing?
- He's a goner.
- All right.
Hi, there.
Does, uh, Quinn McKenna
live here?
His post office box payments
are past due.
Department of Defense.
He works for the government,
does he?
MOS-1-1-B-3-V-W-3.
Military designation.
- Ah.
- He kills people...
so you can be a mailman.
Dr. Brackett?
I understand
you enjoy stargazing?
My men
will take care of your dog.
Will you come with me, please?
What am I looking at?
It's exactly
what you think it is. Yeah.
They've been here before.
'87. '97.
Lately, the visits
are increasing in frequency.
Rory, I'm home!
Hey, I got you something.
Hey.
Did you do
one of these after school?
I did all of them.
Oh. Okay.
Well, I got you two options.
We have...
pirate, or...
Frankenstein.
Frankenstein,
you know, green skin?
Threw a girl
to see if she would float?
No. Okay.
Well, let's go with pirate.
Yeah?
This is dumb.
The guys will...
They will still
be able to see.
See what?
That it's me.
You were once
quoted as saying,
"I dropped
from my mother's womb...
I hit the floor...
and I started crawling
through hostile territory
toward my grave."
About right, yeah.
- That's badass.
- It's pretty morbid.
It's pretty dark.
What's with the polygraph?
I thought
this was a psych eval.
We need to know
if you pose a threat.
Oh, I'm a sniper.
Isn't posing a threat
kind of the fucking point?
You spend most of your time
now in-country...
estranged from your wife
and son?
Look, I get it.
Something went down in Mexico
and nobody wants any witnesses.
Excuse me?
You're not here
to find out if I'm crazy.
You wanna make sure
the label sticks.
So, you feel
you're being railroaded?
I can see the tracks
on the floor!
I don't see tracks
on the floor, for the record.
You feel
like you're a stranger
on your own planet,
don't you, Captain?
Like an alien, you mean?
That's what you wanted.
Do I get a cookie now?
He saw something.
- Oh, yeah.
- Yeah.
Wow!
Ow.
You shove me again,
I'm gonna break your neck.
Did I say that out loud?
McKenna.
Last one.
Thanks for your kindness.
Thank you.
Oh, yeah?
You all right over there?
No, don't worry about him.
He's just got Tourettes.
- He can't control it.
- Fuck you, Coyle.
You get used to it, bro.
Welcome to Group Two.
Oh, yeah? What's that?
Like a unit?
No, group. Group Two.
Group therapy, room two.
Oh.
- McKenna.
- Nebraska Williams.
That's your real name?
Gaylord.
- That's a good call, then.
- Yeah, I thought so.
Where did you serve?
Operation
Enduring Freedom, '03.
Went for the Taliban,
stayed for the opium.
That's Coyle.
Friendly fire incident.
Got turned around, fired
at one of his own vehicles.
Now, he tells jokes.
That's Lynch.
Got a medal for blowing up
half a mountain in Mosul.
Entropy.
That's my game.
Things like to fall apart
and I... make it happen.
Just... Just like that.
Ooh! Wow! Oh.
- Hey.
- Hey. Don't.
Don't.
That's Nettles.
Okay, I'm Nettles.
Did three tours flying Hueys.
He loves his Bible.
Hey, Netty?
Is it end times yet?
Yeah, laugh all you want.
But when you're standing at
attention before your Maker...
I always stand at attention
before I make her.
God makes shitty people.
Yeah.
I mean, why do you think
people make war?
Why, Baxley?
Why do we make war?
- Come on, Baxley!
- Because fuck-cock-cock!
- Because we fuck cock-cock?
- Yes, we fuck cocks.
That's it,
because we fuck cocks,
that's why. We get upset.
How'd you snag a ticket
on this shitmobile?
Put a bullet in a CO.
Any particular reason?
He was an asshole.
Keep your head down.
Here, throw this on.
Is it just your imagination?
Or is this haunted room
actually stretching?
Every fucking time?
Your attention, please.
The GRC meeting has been moved
to section 3, room A.
Aha! There you are!
Welcome.
I'm Sean Keyes.
Wow. I heard you basically
wrote the book
on evolutionary biology.
Um, I'm sorry, can I just...
Is that...?
Oh, my God!
Holy shit.
That's alien technology.
This is what
you brought me here to see?
Well, yeah.
Can I... Can I see this?
Can I get into this?
Doc.
Let's go.
- Everything good?
- Yes, sir.
What is it?
Dr. Brackett.
Would you like
to meet a Predator?
Come on.
Please observe
decontamination protocol.
So, how'd they
rope you into this?
I wrote a letter to
the president when I was six.
Told him how much
I loved animals,
and that if NASA
ever found a space animal,
they should call me.
Couple years ago,
I was put on a short list
for a paper
I wrote on hybrid strains.
Computer cross-referenced
the letter, and... here I am.
Dr. Brackett.
Thanks for coming.
I'm sure you have questions.
- Oh. Just two, actually.
- Okay.
Why do you call it
"the Predator"?
It's a nickname.
You know, the data suggests
that it tracks its prey.
Exploits weakness.
Seems to...
well, enjoy it.
Like a game.
That's not a predator,
that's a sports hunter.
Sorry?
A predator
kills its prey to survive.
I mean, what you're describing
is more like a bass fisherman.
Well, we took a vote.
Predator's cooler, right?
- Fuck yeah.
Found his escape pod
in Mexico.
Still looking
for the ship he came in.
He's heavily sedated.
You are
one beautiful motherfucker.
I'm gonna guess your second
question is, why are you here?
Our test results yielded
something a little... odd.
Is this a joke?
We ran the genome
sequence ten times.
This specimen has...
- Human DNA?
- Yeah.
Yeah.
Look, we know
about spontaneous speciation.
Mostly plants and insects,
but...
But some mammals,
sheep, goats, uh...
Yeah.
The red wolf
is known to be a hybrid
between the coyote
and the grey wolf...
Or possibly some form of
recombinant technology...
Guys, guys, guys.
I get it, I get it.
You wanna know
if someone fucked an alien?
Yeah.
Okay, it's got some kind of
atmospheric mask,
biohelmet, and...
What are these? Like,
some kind of wrist gauntlets?
Exactly.
So, where's the helmet
and the other gauntlet?
We've looked, believe me.
Who is this?
He made first contact
with the Predator.
Great.
I'd like to talk to him.
Well, he's
being evaluated, so...
Okay.
Well, before
you lobotomize him,
I'd like to ask him
a few questions.
We have a request to reroute.
Read you
five-by-five. Destination?
Starkweather Dam.
Proceed at once.
You'll be met
by military personnel. Over.
Hey, Baxley!
Question for ya.
All right, here we go.
How do you circumcise
a homeless man?
Here it comes.
Kick your mom in the chin.
Fuck your mother...
- Shut the fuck up!
- All right.
You shut the fuck up.
Hold on, hold on, hold on.
Y'all going too fucking much.
I just wanna know
who this motherfucker is.
Why are you here?
Come on, man,
this is the loony bus.
- Look at this motherfucker.
- Loonies!
Loonies, yeah.
Ah...
I had a run-in
with a space alien.
Oh, shit!
- No, let him...
- Okay, that guy wins.
That's the best story
I've ever heard.
Classic story...
That's the winner right there.
Fuckin' hell.
Would you shut the fuck up?
Oh.
They want to put a lid on it,
so here I am.
Stuck in Group Two.
The sequel to Group One,
only stupider.
Oh, huh.
Give this man
a fuckin' cigar.
Shut the fuck up.
"Would you shut the fuck up?"
It's a conspiracy.
The goddamn space aliens, huh?
What are you
doing down there, Rory?
Uh, just... just playing games.
Well,
dinner's getting cold.
Major?
Weird-ass bogey, sir.
One second it's on the grid,
the next it's ghosting.
Damn it.
We need something in the air.
Get me NORAD.
I feel like I'm missing
something in the research.
There's something
I'm just not seeing.
Look, if this is
the blood, okay, I think...
can you just tell me
what that is?
Because I was trying
to get into this earlier,
but somebody stopped me.
He gave me the hairy eyeball.
- That guy actually.
- Hold that thought.
Sir, NORAD's reporting
a 202 anomaly
possibly heading
our direction.
Is it coming here?
God, I hope not.
Holy shit!
How far away
are we talking about?
Unknown. But it's
definitely heading your way.
Level two alert.
- Level two alert.
- Shit!
Hey, what's happening?
Proximity alert. Bogey's
inbound. Range 200 miles.
Lock it down.
He's awake!
He's awake! He's awake!
Hey!
Hey, hold him down!
Keep him down!
Hold him down!
Oh, shit!
Doc, on me, now!
Move! Move!
Church, Thomas, J.
Move!
Please observe
decontamination protocol.
Chamber secure.
Remove outer garments.
Church, Thomas, J.
Please observe
decontamination protocol.
All personnel, Code Orange.
Code Orange.
This is not a drill.
Sit tight.
There's been a breach.
Do you have an estimate?
Not right now.
I'll give you cover fire.
Get him out!
Movement, twelve o'clock!
Hey. Hey.
Don't let him get away.
Not my space animal.
What the fuck?
Alien.
Your green boy?
Yep.
Goddamn space aliens.
What? What?
Did you not just
fucking see that, man?
Am I going fucking mad?
- Hey.
- Shut up.
- Take it easy, man.
- I didn't fucking see it.
Nettles, be quiet.
Where the fuck is it?
I wanna see it.
Hey!
That's the thing
that killed my men.
Yeah, they'll do that.
We gotta get off this thing.
We gotta move.
Brother, it's a bus.
It moves.
Hey, Baxley!
If your mom's vagina
were a video game,
it'd be rated "E"
for "Everyone."
Hey!
Knock it off.
What's the difference between
five big black guys
and a joke?
Baxley's mom
can't take a joke.
What, motherfucker!
Come on, bitch!
Everyone, on the floor,
face down!
Face down! Now!
Come on!
Keys!
Gun!
Hey! Nettles! Nettles!
Wait, hey! Hey!
You got him, all right?
You got him, brother.
Hey, Nebraska,
you mind, uh, making a detour?
What, for your green boy?
I'm a sniper,
just get me close, baby.
- You wanna kill him?
- Oh, yeah!
Why didn't you just
say so, man?
You're gonna kill
a fucking alien?
Hey. Hold on.
Fuck!
Yo, what the fuck is that?
Easy, easy. Hey! Hey!
- Hey.
- Take cover!
Behind the fucking bus!
What are you doing up there?
Come on. Come on, I got you.
- Yep. I got you, lady.
- Okay.
Let's go! Hey.
Come on, come on.
Goddamn it.
- Sorry.
- Move!
Damn.
Get to the choppers!
Stargazer, I got eyes
on the woman.
Instructions?
- Eliminate her.
- Hey.
Retrieve any contraband.
Roger that, Stargazer.
That's it, that's it, girl.
Hey, Nebraska!
Got it.
Everything okay back there?
You fucking guys.
We found the one place
to hide out
where we don't look crazy.
It's been a long time since
I had a gun in my hand.
What's it feel like?
Like a gun.
Hey, you think she's safe
in there with them?
The girl?
They're soldiers, man.
Sleeping ladies? Nah, bro.
Sit down.
Here.
It's the end of times, huh?
Worst thing
about the end times...
they never fucking are.
So, um...
did he live?
Say again?
The CO? The asshole you shot,
did he live?
Ah.
Yeah. He did.
Yeah, and where is he at now?
You're shitting me.
I missed.
Why did you do that?
- Miss?
- No, shoot yourself.
Doctors asked me
the same thing.
Walked to the hospital with
a bullet in my skull.
- Good times.
- Hey.
Should I be worried?
Probably.
- There we go.
- Did you get that?
- That's too close to her hand.
- Yeah, yeah. Yeah.
But then
she's gonna drop that there.
Guys!
What the hell are you doing?
What is all that shit?
We're trying
to make her feel comfortable.
Come on.
She's gonna wake up and see
a bunch of motherfuckers.
Come on.
What are you doin'?
Nettles! Nettles!
Move!
Get out of there!
Morning, sunshine.
I really wish people
would stop calling me that.
Chill, hey!
I told you
she'd grab it. Ten bucks!
Pay up! Whoo!
Fuck it, fuck it.
- Where's my phone?
- You're not gonna need that.
Oh, that's not cool.
It's okay.
I said it's okay.
Give me the gun.
- Give me the gun.
- No. No.
Oh, she pulled...
Oh! Shit, I told you
she'd pull the trigger!
I should have bet you
that time!
I like her.
I should have bet you
that time!
- I like her.
I like her. I like her a lot.
Give me that,
ding-dong.
Oh, shit! Attagirl.
What? You're a scientist, huh?
What they got you working on?
You're not gonna last a day
out there!
What, you think you're special?
Back at the dam, they were gonna
put a bullet in your head.
They were gonna shoot her?
Yes.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Get out of the way.
See you around.
Eat your pussy.
Wait, what?
How you doing?
No, you just said,
"Eat your pussy."
Hey...
- How you doing?
- No, you said, "Eat my pussy."
What the fuck
is wrong with him?
- I said you're pushy.
- He said you're pushy.
No, you said,
"Eat your pussy."
No. I said,
"Sheesh! You're pushy!"
No, you said,
"Eat my pussy."
No, that's what he said,
I heard it.
- He said... pushy.
- What the fuck?
Which is also fucking rude.
He doesn't mean your pussy
in particular.
You're insane, right?
- Are you fucking insane?
- Probably.
Well, what's it gonna be?
- He's fucking crazy.
- Fuck you, Baxley.
I feel fine.
They were gonna
shoot me?
Why?
Uh, maybe 'cause of this?
Well, I guess I'm in.
Stay the fuck away from me.
What the fuck is this?
What is this?
- What is that? Like a unicorn?
- A unicorn.
- It's a unicorn.
I made a unicorn...
I'm sorry,
it's a piece of shit.
So, what's the upside to me
staying here with you guys?
Uh, maybe staying alive?
We are soldiers.
We're the good guys, okay?
Well, that's debatable.
I read your file.
The guys in Mexico it killed?
They yours?
They're gonna need
a patsy for that.
You're looking at him.
Yeah, I figured.
Ex-sniper with PTSD? That's
actually kind of perfect.
How about you telling us
what you were doing
in a secret base.
Surrounded by
trained soldiers. Mercs.
I'm a biologist, and they have
me on call in case there's...
contact.
What did I tell you?
End days. End days.
Nettles, if you don't stop
with this Bible shit,
I'm gonna set you on fire.
Guys, if we wanna
keep breathing,
we need to find this thing.
Expose it.
It's called the Predator.
It hunts people for sport.
Technically, that's not
a predator. That's like...
Thank you.
- It's a hunter.
- I said the same thing.
A sportsman,
or a hunter, or a fisherman.
Well, look at you...
I was there when it escaped.
It's looking for something.
Equipment. Weapons.
I took its gear.
What?
You took something
from the thing?
- What?
- So, I'd have evidence.
I think I know
where it's going.
What?
Oh, hi, honey, you're home.
- I'm looking for a package.
- A package?
Rory!
Hey! This is
not your house anymore!
Rory!
Hey, buddy. Where are ya?
He's not here.
What do you mean,
he's not here?
Oh, shit!
What? So we
ordered some video games.
No! No! No!
The whole fucking reason
I sent it to a P.O. box,
was so
I didn't put you in danger.
Goddamn it,
we need to find him.
Wait, Quinn,
you're scaring me now.
I specifically said
no first-person shooter.
No combat games.
Did you ever think that
maybe he plays them
to connect with his father?
Oh, my God.
We're doing this again.
Hey! Can you
stop taking all my...
Who are these people
in my house?
Emily, loonies.
Loonies, Emily.
Good evening.
Uh, the brushstrokes on this
are really dynamic.
It's a wonderful piece.
Okay, you need
to put that down.
What exactly is she doing
with her right hand?
They're my unit.
They're soldiers.
Marines. There's his unit.
Hi. You seem like
a really nice...
Oh, no, don't touch me. No.
Hang on. Back up.
Your unit?
What happened
to Haines and Dupree?
They're dead.
And the thing that killed them
is out there looking for Rory.
What are you talking about?
There's something out there.
It tore my friends apart.
What is it?
Like, it's a creature.
Seriously, it's not a person.
Like from the Bible.
- Revelations.
- From the Bible?
That's the most ridiculous
thing I've ever heard.
It's a space alien.
Know who Whoopi Goldberg is?
It's like
an alien Whoopi Goldberg.
Oh, shit!
Shit.
I want a grid search.
Three teams.
Hey!
- No.
- No, no, I'm coming with you.
No, nix that.
Is there a problem?
Thing is, we're
kind of moving targets.
Yeah, in case you haven't
noticed, we're fugitives.
Yeah. Plus, like where are we
gonna get our meds and stuff?
I get it. Fine,
stay here and watch TV.
You know what? If you try
to split? Or draw the Feds?
Or if you jeopardize my son
by your half-assed
yardbird bullshit...
I will come back here,
and I will happily
kill every single
fucking one of you.
Come on,
brothers. Let's go.
Seriously?
It's not our fight.
Is your husband
the man I think he is?
Excuse me?
Tell me
about your husband, please?
He's a security
counter-sniper.
- Mmm.
- Army Rangers.
He supervised
23 close precision engagements
across five continents
and he has 13 confirmed kills.
And he is one of only 14
captains in the armed forces,
to ever receive
a Distinguished Service Medal
and the Silver Star.
So, he might be
a lousy husband,
but he is a good soldier.
Well, sounds like he can
probably take care of himself.
- Yeah.
- Jesus Christ.
That's what I thought.
Fucking pussies.
Where you going, Nettles?
I didn't like your speech.
It didn't really inspire me.
But... he called me a pussy
and nobody
calls me a pussy, so...
- Fuck off, pussy.
- Okay...
Come on, Bax, let's go.
Let's get some.
Before these army fuckers
screw up the whole thing.
Come on, what are you doing?
Let's move.
Hey!
You too, lucky charms.
Coyle, you wanker.
I'd like to watch TV
- with you sometime.
- Okay.
I liked your speech.
I liked the couch.
Whoa, what's happening? What?
Well, we're finding my son,
that's what.
All right,
when all this is over...
Fuck me in the face
with an aardvark.
I just want to be famous.
Ostensibly,
if Forrest Gump
just read the side of the box,
it would tell him exactly
what he would get.
You're using
"ostensibly" incorrectly.
Is this for me?
This is like the reverse
of a clown car.
All right, Nebraska,
let's find some wheels,
nothing flashy.
Copy.
All right. Find my son.
Casey, you're with me.
Let's go.
Hey, ass-burger.
What are you supposed to be?
Leave me alone.
Or what? You'll wash our
hands five hundred times?
Trick or treat?
What's the matter, dude?
Here's a treat,
you little shit.
Oh!
I got a male juvenile.
10 to 12 years old.
Metal cast on his arm.
Yo, McKenna, do you hear that?
Ran right in front of my car.
Moving east on Woodruff.
Repeat, moving
east on Woodruff.
Nebraska, you got wheels?
Yeah, I got wheels.
Something flashy.
Listen, the kid's spooked,
he's rabbiting.
Where's he headed?
Where's some place he knows?
There he is.
Dad!
How you doing, buddy, huh?
I'm good.
Move! Move!
Hey, Doc, come get my kid.
Let's go! Let's go! Let's go!
Come on!
Oh, shit!
McKenna!
Take cover!
Williams!
Get the fuck out of there!
What are you doing?
Get out of there!
Oh, shit!
Oh. Okay.
Doc, the dreads.
What's that all about?
I don't know.
Maybe, like, sensor receptors.
Kind of like cat whiskers.
Whoa! What the...
I'm getting a sample.
It's a fucking space dog.
You okay? Huh?
What, is your mom
cutting your hair now?
You kidding me?
This is
- a once-in-a-lifetime moment.
- Shut up. Please shut up.
All I wanted
was a little sample.
Please shut up.
All I wanted was
a goddamn fucking sample.
Come here.
Sample.
- There you go.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
- Fucking space dog, man.
- My man, you need to...
- It's a fucking...
I can't. I can't.
- Get it together.
- I can't do this.
- Oh, my God!
- Whoa!
Fucking hell!
Fuck!
Go now! Please!
Rory!
Shoot him! Shoot him!
Hey!
No! No! No!
Oh, fuck, fuck. No, no, no!
Cock! Cock! Fuck! Dick!
Suck! Suck my cock!
Fuck! Goddamn it!
Go! Go! Go!
I got him! I got him!
Go, go, go!
On Williams! On Williams!
Rory!
- Take cover!
- Move!
Go! Go!
Come on!
FYI, back at Stargazer,
I was naked and unarmed,
it walked right past me.
Can you tell your kid to tone
down the psychosis, please?
All right, let's do this.
Let's do this.
Wait, and do what?
You know,
we could keep running,
or we give him back
what he wants.
What, this is it?
Oh, my God. Shit.
Shit.
No, no, no! Move! Move! Move!
Hey, come on.
You good?
Fucked!
Let's get
the fuck out of here.
Netty, get the vehicle.
- The rest of you on me.
- Copy.
Move back.
No! No! No!
No!
Incoming!
What the fuck?
Come here!
Roll out! Roll out, let's go!
Let's go, let's go, let's go!
- Move!
- Move out, move out!
Move! Move out!
- Let's go!
- Let's move!
Go, go, go! Let's go!
Let's go!
Move!
Come on!
Move! Come on,
get in! Come on!
Sit down!
Good! Good! Good!
Go! Last man!
Go! Go! Go!
What's the big one?
What's the big one, Doc?
Is that like the male?
He didn't even
give a shit about us.
Just wanted
to kill that thing.
You saw that, right?
Guys! Did you see that? He...
He grew an exoskeleton
under his fucking skin.
What, are they hunting
each other now?
We're still sorting
through it right now.
- Hey, it's me.
- Tell me he's okay.
He's fine.
I'm going to bring him back.
It's okay, don't say anything,
just be safe.
Hey, no! Don't do that!
What? Hello?
Damn it.
You guys fucked
with the wrong family.
- How tall?
- Witnesses say 11 feet.
That's
pretty fucking tall.
Okay.
- Fucked that nigga up.
- Sir?
Nothing.
I'd be careful with that, sir.
You know what I think?
I think this one
went rogue. A runner.
Hmm. And the big one?
He's a tracker.
Sent to take that one out.
Some kind of interstellar
cops and robbers.
Now he's going after
that missing ship.
And whatever's on board.
I want that fucking ship.
We're in the ballpark.
Captain McKenna's son?
Mother confirms.
He has the operating system.
- Get the fuck out of here.
- Thought it was a video game.
So, we find the kid,
we find the ship.
What the fuck we
still standing here for?
You don't want to know
what that one is?
I know what it is.
Our big boy's a hunter.
He brought his dogs with him.
No, it had to be like
a government experiment
or some shit.
Like a robot, or whatever.
Nettles, are you
fucking retarded, man?
Use another word, would ya?
Yeah, man.
Show a little sensitivity.
His son's retarded.
Here you go.
He does this from time to time.
Just give him a minute.
Hey, Lynch.
What's the deal
with these two?
Coyle lit up
one of his own vehicles?
Back in '09, yeah.
It was bad business. Six dead.
What, no survivors?
Yeah, there was one.
It's fucking romantic.
Are you kidding me,
they're friends?
Picture it.
Military inquiries,
sitting outside courtroom,
waiting to go in,
side by side,
- day after fucking day.
- After fucking day.
Unbelievable.
It's the loonies.
All right, kid.
I've talked to your mother.
She's doing fine.
Mom says you're a killer.
Well, I'm a soldier.
What's the difference?
Well, when you like it,
that's when you're a killer.
Are you good?
Sorry I never grew up.
You know...
the way you wanted.
Tell you a secret.
Truth is, kid,
I never grew up
the way I wanted.
Are we gonna get killed?
Nope.
Come on.
Get up.
I'm single.
I don't know if you knew that.
No, I could tell
that you're single.
We got so much stuff
in common, you know...
You like music, I like music.
You like music, right?
- Shit.
- What?
This is more than spinal fluid.
What does that mean?
If I'm right,
they're trying
to upgrade themselves.
McKenna, I got something.
I think I know
what they're up to
on Predator World these days.
You see this? They found this
in the Predator's plexus.
So, remember how I told you
how they take
people's spines, right?
Yeah, for trophies.
Yes! Yes!
From the strongest, smartest,
most dangerous species
on every planet they visit.
Collecting survival traits
from the most
high-end specimens.
I think they're
attempting hybridization.
You're just pulling this
out of your ass.
Did you not see
the new Predator?
It's evolving.
Or being upgraded.
That little boy
managed to figure out
alien technology.
You know,
a lot of experts say that
being on the spectrum
isn't really a disorder.
It's actually the next step
in the evolutionary chain.
Hey, yo!
What the fuck?
Get the fuck away from me!
Yo! Casey!
Casey, get inside.
Casey!
Hey, hey, hey! Calm down!
Calm down! Calm down!
Casey! Look.
I think this thing's
been following us, all right?
- Move, Netty!
- Hey, hey, hey!
- Space dog!
- Move, Netty!
Fuck that.
Hey! You had
your fucking chance.
Look, I'm just saying,
what the fuck is it gonna do?
You know, maybe we can
use it, or something?
Okay, what are we doing?
What are we doing with it?
We're gonna study it. That's
what we're gonna do with it.
What's to learn?
Except Williams sucks
at shooting shit in the head.
Williams, you lobotomized him.
Okay, new rule.
No one shoots my fucking dog.
There it is.
It's official.
You were right,
we can use this.
Shit.
Netty, what is that?
Everybody, tighten up.
- Little man, come here.
- That's an EC-130.
That's not civilian.
Hey, hey, hey!
You are not starting
a firefight with my kid here.
There you go.
Do you wanna help? Go get
a helicopter and some pyro.
All right! On me!
Now go!
- Casey! I'll be right back!
- No, you won't.
Hold on. Hey. See this?
Come on. Let's go!
Let's go! Come on!
Fetch!
Where is it?
Where's what?
The device.
It goes, right in here.
Okay, so, the first Predator,
Thing One.
Why'd he come here? To Earth?
The "Thing One",
as you called him,
arrived in
a hijacked spacecraft.
We think there's
something on it.
Something he didn't want
his enemies to have.
Wait, enemies?
Other Predators.
Like that big one.
So, he brought some what?
Gift for the human race?
I'll help you find it.
We can analyze it...
Shut the fuck up!
Why are they here?
You remember a few years back
when Hostess went bust?
There was a run on Twinkies?
Snapped up
from coast-to-coast.
Get 'em while they still last.
Remember?
How long before climate change
renders this planet unlivable?
Two generations?
One?
That's why their visits
are increasing?
They're trying to snap up
all of our best DNA
before we're gone.
Adapt themselves with it
and then move in.
We're an endangered species,
and they know it.
They thrive
in a hothouse environment.
Maybe they want
to move into ours.
And that dead Predator
was bringing us
a way to stop them.
You've hidden this thing
before in the mail.
So, where is it this time?
Your mother's ass.
Wait, did I say that out loud?
Hey! Hey! Hey! No, no, no.
That is not for you.
That is my son's,
and you are violating
his privacy reading that.
You both need
to leave right now.
Ma'am, I don't wanna
restrain you.
Really? Well,
why don't you try?
You haven't
found the spacecraft?
Why are we trying
to crack the entry code?
Because when we do
find it, wouldn't it be great
if we could
get into the fucking thing?
What's that?
A map.
A map to what?
...give us
a clue of where this place is,
maybe we can try
to get into it.
But if you don't give us
anything, we can't get in!
Hey, Rory, I'm Will.
How you doing?
I understand you know
where the spaceship is.
Golf tomorrow?
Why not?
You two never read
my file, did ya?
What makes you say that?
'Cause you two morons
are making plans for tomorrow.
The worst part is,
you're making me lie to my son.
What lie did you
tell him, hmm?
That I won't enjoy this.
Hey, please, don't.
Look, I don't know
what they told you...
Can you just wait
for a second? Just wait!
No, no, no!
No.
Jeez!
Oh, my God.
Nebraska!
- Yeah?
- You just kill somebody?
Well, he ain't well.
Untie my friend.
They got Rory. We gotta move.
Shit, they rough you up?
Did worse on myself,
back in the day.
What do you want to do
with this guy?
Sorry, buddy,
that was a dumb question.
Yeah, that was
a dumb question.
Casey!
Can I interest you in getting
the fuck out of here?
"Getting the fuck out of here"
is my middle name.
And I thought Gaylord was bad.
What? What's wrong?
Whew! All right.
Hey! Just let me unpack this.
You're saying my son's headed
towards a spaceship
and so is a 10-foot alien.
Uh, 11, actually.
Used to be a contractor.
This thing is a hybrid?
What does that mean?
Meaning it's the Chinese menu
of DNA.
Comprised of the deadliest
species in the entire...
In the entire universe, yeah?
- Galaxy.
- What?
Galaxy. 250 billion stars.
Why go universe? Just saying.
Jesus Tap-Dancing Christ!
That's what you asked for?
Yeah, that'll do.
Saddle up!
It's the best
we could do, man.
Go ahead. Go!
That's it? Another one.
The other one!
Come on.
Let's go get my kid.
Figured something out.
I think we're gonna die.
We're gonna go hunt and fight
the what, the army?
We're not gonna
fight the army...
And some
fucking people from space!
You wanna talk survival, huh?
Fine!
You, yesterday,
you were on a prison bus
barking to yourself,
now you got a gun
in your hand.
Who's a survivor now?
We put bullets in our head
and walk
to the fucking hospital.
We're soldiers!
Nettles, what's our 20?
I can follow
your boy's chopper.
I locked into its frequency.
Fence is hot!
What do you say, buddy?
You think you can get us
in there?
Because I'm not sure
that you can.
Nice reverse psychology.
I can do that, too.
Don't go fuck yourself.
That's good. Come on.
Good. Almost up and running.
Five minutes.
Right on.
It's a translator unit, Rory.
Been trying to figure out
what these
bird-chirping motherfuckers
been saying since '87.
Gave the Harvard School
of Linguistics
a billion-dollar grant.
Voila. Watch your step,
come on.
Goddamn, kid, I don't know
where you get it from.
Put the translator
into the mainframe.
Download everything.
What the hell's
inside there?
It's property
of Project Stargazer.
That's what the fuck it is.
Code three. Code three.
We have motion
at the south fence line.
Send a fireteam
to check it out.
That's my dad.
He's gonna come save me now.
Oh, is he?
Is that what he's gonna do?
I'll tell you what, buddy...
if it is your daddy,
and I truly hope that it is...
he's gotta be just about
the dumbest motherfucker
I've ever met.
I mean, a Ranger sniper
tripping wire sensors?
He's gotta be...
creating a diversion.
It's a fucking diversion.
Oh, shit!
Wow. Howdy.
What, are you gonna kill us
with a fucking tranq gun?
You took my boy, so yeah.
Told you.
Take this, son.
You outta your mind? We
literally have you surrounded.
That's why
you're coming with me.
I just want the boy.
Nobody's got to die.
Dad?
From here forward.
Don't look at the dead guy.
That was pretty good.
You all right? Did I get you?
No, I'm good.
Welcome back.
Fuck you. I never left.
You open your mouth,
I'm gonna blow your brains
right through it.
Come on, just get behind me.
All units. They got Traeger.
They got Traeger.
Let's go. Let's go.
Just tell them
to put the guns down.
Tell them!
If Captain McKenna
doesn't lower his weapon
in the next 10 seconds...
shoot the kid's knees out.
That work for you?
Oh, that's a really bad idea.
My guys got this place covered
on every angle.
That's a funny story.
See, I don't give a shit.
10.
Nine.
Eight.
Seven.
Come on, you just give
the fucking word, man.
Six. Five.
Oh, shit!
Come on, son!
Take them down!
Get down, sir.
Let's go, son. Go!
Come on. Come on.
Okay, take this.
You wanna vanish,
you really vanish, son,
you understand?
All right, we're going home.
I promise you.
It's here.
No! No! No!
Come on,
go around the end there!
Stay on him!
Move, move, move!
- You got him?
- Yeah!
Stay back.
Get down! Get down!
Cease fire!
Cease fire! Cease fire!
- Huh?
- All right.
Hey, McKenna.
Be reasonable. There's six
of you, seven of us.
Fuck!
Who taught you math?
You ain't the only
fucking sniper, white boy.
You can walk away
from this, Captain.
I just want the ship.
- Dad, he's lying.
- Yeah.
McKenna! I don't like this.
What's he doing in there?
It's using the translator.
Hello. I have enjoyed
watching you kill each other.
I came here
to destroy this vessel.
You cannot have it.
What you can do is run.
I detect one among you
who is a true warrior.
The one called McKenna.
He will be your leader.
He will be my prize.
I offer time advantage.
Go.
What the fuck
is time advantage?
Like a head start?
I'm gonna wake up on a bus.
Hey!
I'm coming out!
We're in.
- Baxley!
- Shit!
Watch where the fuck you're
throwing, dickhead.
Will do.
Okay, so we split up.
12 different directions.
- McKenna's the one he wants.
- No, no, no!
We stay together,
or it'll take us one by one.
He's right. It's their MO.
- Grow a dick, will you?
- Nothing's starting!
Son of a bitch. He must have
hacked the vehicles.
If we can get to the helicopter,
go two klicks north.
- Got you.
- Hey?
When this is over, you and me,
we're gonna dance.
I got my shoes all picked out.
All right.
- Fuck.
- No, no, no! Don't.
Here, boy. Fetch.
Here, boy.
Here you go.
That was a valuable weapon.
Let's go.
He'll be coming for us.
Give me the goody bag.
Hey. On Halloween,
this blew up a whole house.
- How do you shoot it?
- You don't.
It just fires by itself
when it's being attacked.
Seriously? Oh, shit.
I heard something.
Hey, man.
That's Predator technology.
Fuck.
That... It's gonna come back.
You got, uh, a catcher
on the wrist.
That's gonna come back.
No!
Quiet. Quiet.
- Let me see. Let me see.
- My fucking hand.
- Shit.
Gotta be quiet.
Moving!
No, no, no!
This way. This way. This way.
There's a clearing up ahead.
Lynch left some pyro up there.
To cover our retreat.
Let's find it
and trap the motherfucker.
You guys go set it up.
We'll lure him in.
- Who?
- You and me.
Yeah? All right.
- Yeah.
- Let's go.
Come on.
Can I talk to you
for a second?
What's this "we" shit?
What, are you gonna
live forever, Coyle?
- Just calm down.
- Calm down?
Me, calm down?
Yeah, okay, thanks, twitchy.
Move, move, move!
Up here. Up, up, up.
Shit!
Okay, fuck this.
Hey! Asshole!
What the fuck was that?
It's a chance for you
to survive.
Go! I got this.
That's the stupidest fucking
thing I've ever heard.
Come and get us, asshole!
Contact!
- Alien!
- Contact!
- He's coming!
Come on. Come on. Come on.
Light him up!
Coyle!
Bax, no!
Traeger!
Baxley!
Die!
Oh, shit.
Fuck.
Move, move!
- Nettles!
- Let's go!
McKenna.
Rory.
I love you.
Hey! I'm the one you want.
Right here! Come on! You...
Dad!
No!
- No! No! No!
- McKenna
No! No!
I hate you,
you stupid fucking...
No! No!
He said he wanted me.
He said he wanted me!
No. He said he wanted McKenna.
The next step
in the evolutionary chain.
Not you. Your son.
Yo, he's taking off.
No!
Come on, man. Come on.
Come on.
Let's take it down!
Come on!
Hang on!
Fuck! Nebraska!
I got you!
Dad, there's a force field
coming online. Look out!
Guys! Something's coming!
Go!
Netty!
Fuck!
Hey, hey, hey.
No, no, no! Bro!
Bro.
No.
Fuck!
Shit!
Rory!
Toss it!
What are you?
Shut the fuck up.
My unit.
Nettles.
Coyle.
I see you saw Lynch's card.
Baxley had this
the whole time.
Nebraska's bad habit.
Son...
these are the ones
that no one's gonna remember.
Just us.
What do you say
we put them to rest?
Captain McKenna.
Hiroshi Yamada.
- Sir.
- First things first.
I want to say thank you
for having such a great kid.
He loves it here.
Yeah, he's something else.
What do we got, Doctor?
Well, I assume
that you know by now,
but the first Predator,
it didn't come here to hunt us.
- He brought something.
- Exactly.
Now, you want
to hear the good news?
The cargo survived.
With some sort of fail-safe.
Before the upgrade Predator
blew up the ship,
a pod escaped.
Jettisoned.
Saved itself.
It seems that our boy
wasn't taking any chances.
He wanted us to have this.
What is it again
you do here, exactly?
He's the world's number one
authority on cybernetics.
Hey, kiddo.
Pretty cool, huh?
Pretty cool.
You got your own desk.
I'll make sure to tell Mom.
So, this is his gift
to humankind?
- Get back!
- Look out!
Everyone, stand back!
Stand back!
Clear the area!
Dad, the pod
sent me a message.
- Rory, what's in that pod?
- Don't know!
Oh, wow... Oh, shit!
- It's got a name!
- Name? What name?
I guess you'd call it,
the Predator Killer.
- Get him out of here!
- Come with me. Let's go.
Get back.
Clear the area.
Eyes on it.
Whatever it is,
it appears to be dormant.
I assume it needs to be...
Eyes on.
Keep your weapons trained.
Get it off!
Get it off me!
What the hell is that?
That's my new suit, bubba.
I hope they got it
in a 42 long.
Subtitles by explosiveskull
Resync by GoldenBeard
Please rate this subtitle at www.osdb.link/6xt5c
Help other users to choose the best subtitles