Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org
Lucky ring on
I feel so much safer
We're coming in hot
Hold on
Let's go
What's the hold up?
Nothing, we're on our way.
Let's go!
Your dude's trippin'
Stay on the wall, beware
- Hey forget this maniac
- I'm not leaving him
Come
You're just gonna rolled up on me huh?
After 8 damn years
What's up with that?
You're in a black ops prison that
doesn't officially exist
I just got the location from a guy named Church
An agency spook
Excuse me?
Agency's official relax
Thank you for this, man.
What a waste of life
You make 1 damn mistake
It wasn't a mistake
It was stupid. You'd done that to me I would've
chopped you into pieces
You would've tried
Hey you want to thank the guys?
The guys?
Where our guys?
Hammer, Guzman..
- Gone
They'd gone?
Yeah
Heard you killed more people than the plague
What about that?
The way they called you "Doctor Death"?
I've been in the medical field
But that was a long time ago
So why'd you get locked away?
Tax evasion
So you're all that's left of The Expendables
We're it
We started out with 5
Built up to 22
I see Barney still hanging the tags up there
See that jingling sounds the tags make
That's a reminder that our brothers are still here
Somewhere
Come on viking
Quit screwing with your blade
Or else you might find your tags up there
Jingling too
Jingling...jingling jingling
Sharpen it when you're done
I think your friend is a little off
Come on Christmas, he's been in
a hole for over a year
How'd he get so lucky
He tried pulling it off his half-assed political assassination
for a few bucks in this place called Swaziland
And he blew it
Self destructive
Yes something like that.
But in all those years he's a good medic.
I would need to do a little checkup
- Why are you so sarcastic?
- You're fake
- Fake?
- Secrets, idiot.
I mean why do you take me off running around the
planet
To save this medical genius
As you describes
For what?
He's an Expendables
Come on
He's an Expandables
So he's 1 of the flock
Well let me tell you something
When you're incarcerated for years
I will come and save you
Thank you
But I doubt it
And I know you'd do the same for me
Truthfully?
You'd let me ride?
Exactly
Hey Doc
What's your name?
Christmas
Is that real?
Authentic
Is that real too?
Oh no, I uh...spend 3 hours every morning
putting this up
This is real
Authentic
Original
Look at that
Ballast is a little off
You uh, a knife man?
Best, ever
I'm the knife before Christmas
Ain't that right Barney
If you say so
Probably freestyling with a blade while you're
still sucking on your dad titties
Trying to learn how to eat with a spoon
Yeah
You want to let us on a little secret you're
keeping
Stay out of my brain
I'm gonna tell you
I can't wait to get home
Eat some good food
Put on some fine threads
Break up my 49' Pontiac
Keep that baby until the engine blows up
You didn't tell him did you?
Tell me what?
We're not going home
We're stopping at a dealer
The delivery of a shipment of bombs Altherometekih
Ow, come on man
That shit is hellfire
Hey we're changing stuff
You know why don't you just pick me up on your way back
We're a man short
Well, you know, I'd love to party with you boys
But, uh, I don't have my shit
That's my shit
That is your shit
Doc, have you thank the guys,
helping you out?
Say something
Uh listen up
It's been a long time since I had a reason to say thank you
So I just want
Oh you know I
Just want to say
Thank you
Sincerity is overwhelming
I think him gonna weep
You know what? Enough
Do not be sarcastic
That was great Doc
You haven't got the time to talk for a long time
You got the gift
It's like writing a book
Churchill is best
I think I made my point
I've moved you too
Stunning
Doc, great to have you back
No better place to be, yeah
About time you boys showed up
Nice boat
Thanks ladies, but I looked myself
Got 3 more just like him patrolling the hub
2 men ground teams every 400m
Good work
Just cause you can fly a plane don't make you smarter than me
I'm sure it does
So you're the reason I've been stuck down here in this shithole
Shithole?
Brother you have no idea
Oh yeah, hahahaha
What the hell is that?
This bitch will solve all your problem
Yeah, maybe for 10 seconds
We're gonna blow this watch -
So now you got that problem too?
You walked into that 1
Come on, look alive, look alive
It was all under control
Yeah, that's what it looked like
Where you've been?
I had a doctors' appointment
Catch up with you boys later
What's he had?
Watch your overhead
Doc go
Ooh sadly, the man attacked me with a knife
He's good
Compared to you
You do not want to see this
See what?
I'll show you
Damn
He's really good
Say it again and I'll shoot you
Get in
Where is the bomb?
It'll be here
Barney looks like the target is right on its time
There is a place in the second
Barney I'm gonna put you down
It can't be
What can't be?
We're gonna shoot this guy or what?
What's the hold up?
He's dead
Who's dead?
Stonebanks
Come on, get in
Come on, move!
Go go go!
Come
Time to load her up
I told you
10 seconds
Hang on
Found you a ride
Time to go
Come on, go go go!
- How much we're getting pay for this?
- Not enough
Go right
You're not gonna fit
Always negative
I'm getting carsick
Hang on Doc
Get out
Come on
Caesar
We're coming your way, where are you?
In this filthy river, behind you
Try to stay as close as you can
Make room for Caeser
Move your ass in
Who's it?
I think it's my guy on boat
---
Hold it, hold it, you got it going
- You alright?
- Yeah
Turn over
Incoming!
Move!
We got you man, come on!
Maybe this will bring you luck
Is he gonna make it?
I don't know
Who did this?
Stonebanks
I thought you killed him
So do I
He shot Caeser to get back in me
Yeah I'm getting out of this business
And so should you
Not yet
If you need any help with
Stonebanks
It's supposed to be the guy named Church
I know who you are
So who are you?
Operations officer Drummer
You don't have to worry about Church anymore
He's um, he's out of the picture
Jesus Ross
What a mess
We gave you everything
Target opportunity, all the intel you could asked for
And you got decimated
And my target went away
Am I wrong huh?
Am I missing something?
Yes, sure you said the target name was Victim
- And?
- It was wrong
His real name was Conrad Stonebanks
We knew him only as Victor Maines
Arms dealer, made billions selling to every psycho warlord in Africa and the Middle East
His own mercenary army is personally responsible
For the torture and killing
2 of the best men I ever knew friend
I don't give a shit what his name is
I don't like him
I want him as bad as you do
This happened on my watch
You fucked up, and I'm wearing it
I'll find him
Again
You have 1 more shot
Nice to finally meet you Barney
Your man are shot to shit, what are
you gonna do for a team
Don't worry about it
I'll handle it
Relax
You're gonna give yourself a stroke
What's with these guys
Do you mind?
Do you think when the artist painted this, he ever thought
it would go for such a ridiculous price?
I mean what is this? Just some paint, brushes, some shape,
canvas, what's the big deal?
It's shit
What do you want for it?
3 million
Done
You know
It's very hard for me to say this
But at 1 time, you guys were the best
Maybe still are
But nothing lasts forever
Hard as it is to hear
We're not the future anymore
Unfortunately for us
We're part of the past
As I see it
If we keep this life up
The only this thing ends
Or all of this
Is in a hole in the ground and no 1 giving a shit
Now, if that's the way I'm suppossed to go out,
I can live with that
For me
But what I can't live with
And I won't live with
Is taking you with me
What are you saying?
That's our call
I'm changing things now
You
Me
All of us
It's over
We're done
Done? You ripped me out
Cut me loose
You'll survive
You all will
You live your lives while you can
Where are you going, Barney?
Hey you think you just pulled the plug and that's it?
- Just did.
- Yeah?
Well it doesn't work that way
What?
We've been through the mud
We shit in the blood
And I've saved your arse more times than I can count
You don't want me to shot this this guy that took Caeser down?
We're not doing that
You know when I joined
I joined for the whole ride
I know you did
Rides over
Bonaparte
Sorry to hear about Caeser
I hope you pulls through with the good ones
Yeah
Well here we are again
What do you need?
New Team
Retired the old ones
Welcome to the 21st century
Any guys you looking for?
Young, hungry to take a bullet
We're going after Stonebanks
Stonebanks
Let's see, I'm not the only one sleeping.
Stonebanks is dead my friend
No, he's not
That is not good
If it was half of what it used to be, 5 or 4 ain't gonna cut it
You're gonna need 50
We gotta move fast, no time
If I go to do it fast then I can't guarantee the best
Just give me something, don't give it to him
What?
Was it a 1 way ticket?
Could be
Fine
I got in line with a few head cases
Couple of these guys are crying up to shoot themselves
Wait
What about these guys?
They're anything?
These guys are pussies
Foreign, expert hacker
Commander pilot
Did 18 month for hacking in Seattle central operating systems
Shut down the whole city for 3 days
Why the hell would he do that?
Because he can
What?
I'm not looking for an office worker
Oh that's not him
Another 1 with a death wish.
You 2 got a lot in common.
I can't do that
You know what?
I'm gonna come around and I'll say it
I belong on you
- You can't do that.
- No.
He was special on that 1
Yeah, yeah, that's the p-----
Always on the damn road going someplace you don't give a damn about
Beat standing still
Yeah I got 2 ex-wives
- and 3 kids I've lost my numbers with disagree
- Hey did you turned off the autopilot?
- I didn't touch the autopilot.
Read this
Are we off course?
Where the hell are we?
Hang on for a second
Is that the Big Dipper?
Yeah we gotta turn around
Next candidate is an expert in field craft and close quarters combat
Luna
Hi
Young lady, meet a friend of mine. Barney Ross.
Barney Ross, Luna. Luna, Barney Ross.
Nice to meet you Mr. Ross
Gentlemen if you'd follow me
Come on
So Luna how are things?
The same thing
What do you do?
Forget this
All right so what are we doing here?
Have a drink
Where's your candidate?
Right there in the red dress about to chop those guys in half
- The hostess?
- Not the hostess
She's the bouncer
I can't do that
You want to slip on a dress and give it a shot
Men
She's good
You wanna see her without heels
When did you last checkup?
I don't know, a while back
Our cholesterol ---
Yeah pretty much
Except with me
I've found a lump in my lung
Buried dark they said
Why shouldn't I see that coming?
Well, what do you do?
I try to make as much money as I can,
fast as I can.
For those kids you know
The 1 you don't talk to
Make some kind of a good impression on them, before I'm gone
Sad isn't it?
Yeah it is sad. I'm sorry.
Nah that's all bullshit, I'm fine
Just checking you're still human
Had you going there now didn't you?
Yeah you did goddammit
That can never happen again
I'll never trust you again
Next kid has a bit of a dark force
Just came across my desk. I don't like throwing in a wildcard.
But this guy is too much to just passed up
Anybody see Felipe
Yo Felipe
This gotta be good Bonaparte
Yeah I bet
Finally got it right
Damn
(In advance)
Meet Barney Ross
Galgo, you sent me another fake resume
Mr. Ross I can do what you need, whatever you need
I am healthier than I look, stronger than I look
Faster than I look
Actually, shit, you were born in 1984
Of course not
But I feel like that I was born in 1984
Do not waste your time, Barney we leave
Mr. Ross, Mr. Ross, Mr. Ross
Please
It's like uh, it's like I have this uh, called the fountain of youth
I mean, not the fountain of youth
Ponce de Leon
Um by the way
I know a little Spanish
Mr. Ross
Age is just a state of mind
You're only old, when you surrender
When you give up, and I haven't, not yet
- Galgo, this shit has got to stop
- I gotta go
This is the third time this month
Seriously, moved on
What's this guy story?
Actually I feel a little sorry for him
His last team dropped him
Back in the day, you couldn't catch him
- Very fast, maybe even faster than you
- No way
Oh maybe
But, what am I gonna say
It's a young man's game
I need a job!
All I know what to do is killing people
And I do that very well
Damn
- What's the story on this guy?
- Found him in DARPA
- DARPA?
- Sounds like a town in North Africa
Defense Advanced Research Projects Agency
Now that's where the brightest military minds develop next-gen weapons
Google it
I'm not looking for weapons nerd
Ah, then you've come to the right place
Yo Marlito
Mars I like you to meet Barney Ross
Now truth is, Mars is as gifted as they get
Whatever you say
What do you say?
What I've got here is an X-25 assault rifle
Laser range, 25mm high explosive burst rounds
Can be programmed to detonate over or behind the target
He'll do
Final candidate, John Smilee.
Guy's got the most in the industry.
A lot of skills, Marines, special operator
- But there is, an issue
- What issue?
Yeah classic authority problem
There's a couple more swimming around in there too
Sorry Barney for wasting your time like this.
He's not the guy I thought he was.
No
I want to meet him
John
Meet Barney Ross
Didn't do much to impress out there today didn't you?
You called me, I didn't call you
Think you'd die for the money?
Maybe you like getting your ass kicked in front of strangers
What do you guys want from me?
You running from something?
I don't know you
But I know you
- Oh yeah?
- Yeah
How's that
Maybe he thinks you got potential and we're short on time.
That's about right?
That's about it
What's your problem?
Your problem is you're rolling around the dirt for chump change
I hear you lost a few friends in the desert
They bought it, and you didn't
And you wear the guilt
I've been there
He's been there
We all lived it
Well you don't know me
I know the type
Bonaparte you're right
He did waste my time
Hey, you didn't waste your time
If we're going after Stonebanks,
we might want to talk about financials now
Normally it's just 10%, but
I figured with Stonebanks in the equation I might want to get my fee possibly now
I mean, not that you're not good for it,
just, if you don't mind
I don't mind
It sounds like you don't have too much faith in me
I don't
How was your occassion?
Ready to go to work?
You find them yet?
He's in Bucharest putting together a deal with some Albanian mobster
And get 36 hours, that's your window
After that he's back off the gird
Satellite map
Coordinates for where he'll be
Interesting guy
Your friend Stonebanks
You're not gonna like this but
They want him alive
Are you kidding me?
They want to try him at Hague
For war crimes
You're gonna give this guy a chance in court?
It's not my decision
- Now never is
- That's the way it's gotta be
Agency's got a local safehouse
You're gonna need it
Don't trash the place
I heard you got a job
That's right
Who the hell are they?
They're with me
And we're not?
Gunner I had told you everything I had to tell you back in the bar
Stop drinking so much
You want to get yourself killed
With those youngsters
Do us all a favor and get the hell out of here
Wheels up in 10
If your guys wanted to fight,
why didn't they just get married?
You seriously somking next to aviation fuel?
Amateur
Amateur assholes
Balugd calls from my grandfather?
Grandpa's about to crash your windpipe
What is this? It's your toy?
Boy?
You want to dance big guy?
Hey! It's just a job
Come on, let's go
Bunch of has been's still trying to be hard
You're young and you're dumb
Jingling jingling
Keep it
You're gonna need it
Never thought you'll be calling that favor
I'm also not happy about it
Got a minute?
What do you need?
Tell me more about this gut we're going after
It doesn't matter you're hired to do a job
What about answering why we're doing this job?
I owe you a salary that's it
Why are we going after Stonebanks?
You have a hard time taking orders don't you?
If I don't know what they are, yeah
I know you don't give a damn about us
I get that
But just tell me why you want to take out this guy so bad
30s to drop
Copy that
Let's go
I can take care of myself
20s to drop
10s
We're on
This guy got more muscle than a cartel king
Maybe he's up for a competition or something
What you're drinking Barney?
Is that like vanilla latte or somehting?
Stay sharp
Moved
You have to think about this again Mr.
I promise you this won't happen again
Move the cart
Nice driving Mars
Good performance
Yeah, too good
Any closer and I'd beat his ass
I believe her
Got 'em
Oh man, this guy's protected better than the president
Yeah, it's like a 5-star fortress
Listen we're not gonna taking him there
I bet the hotel is full of guests
So where do we hit them?
At the meet
We'll hit them on all 4 sides
Hit him hard
Ok, um, so
Our plan is to what? Kick down the door and start spraying bullet?
It's a great plan
If it's 1985
And what's that supposed to mean?
You heard me
You got a better plan?
Much better
Let's hear it
Thorn, you're up
Ok, I'm the plan
This better be good
First I hacked the security grid main server, boom
Bypassed the motion detector laser and biometric sensors, pow
Override the surveillance videos and CCTV systems, ba-bam
An we are in
It's child play
Just like that?
Just like that
Exactly, like that
You better be right
Let's go
So why'd you let your team go?
It was time
They didn't seem to happy about it
If you're looking to go the family route,
it's the wrong job for you
There are different kinds of family
And when my life is on the line
That's my family fighting with me
You know what I mean
Yeah, I know what you mean
Right on time
Ladies First
Go ahead the Thorn
Will you shut up and get in this sewer
And ladies and gentlemen, we officially have eyes in the skies
Copy that
Let's do this
Thought you'd never ask
Good to go
Good luck boys
Heck
What's the problem?
The buyer, they're early
Threat just doubled
You're early
What do you think?
It's ok
When Cain's the little brother
God banish him from civilization
But before that he placed a mark on him
---
It protect him from roving hunters
This is not X-ray artwork
Only oils
Very good
There you have it
Gabil
My pleasure
As always
Can you access nuclear weapons?
I might
But generally I find people a little too emotional for ownership
And I'd hate you killing all my other customers by accident
Or on purpose
In position
Set
I'll pay you what you want
Let me think about it
We're on
Stonebanks is moving, watch it
I will do this
Try again
Open Sesame
Go go go
Move
Go
Barney Ross says hello
Nice job
Trench you copy?
I'm waiting
Got it secured
I'll hurry up
It's boring
Why don't you just a bullet in his head and be done with it
Hey you said we're just taking them out
Good morning
These are your students?
Hey kids what you learnt tonight huh?
What happened to the old crew?
Oh that's right
They stuck their noses into other people's world and got fatally injured
Now they're The Deletables
Hey you hear that kids?
Take note cause that what you're doing right now
Let me show him
You're talking pretty tough your guys incapacitated which is good for you
Why don't you cut me loose and I'll open your meat shirt and show you your own heart
Hey Barney
Why don't the 2 of us just end this? What do you say?
Mix it up, either you snapping my spine or me snapping yours
You know, make it snappy
He thinks I'm joking.
I'm not joking.
You should see me when I'm angry
You'd be very impressed
And very dead
So come on pal
Anything you want to get off your chest
Come on, lay it out
I'm a good listener
You're gonna take me back to the has been crew?
Carved me up around the fire
Very tribal
When we stop, I wanna break every bone on your body
And drop what's left at The Hague
The Hague
I'm a war criminal
Keep laughing
Do you think,
that you could just deliver me like a package?
We were close once
See we started this whole Expendables thing together, see?
Look I've got the marks
It's been faded but, we had a falling out
You went dark
And to dark business Barney don't pretend you're not in it
The baddest survive, those are the rules, I didn't make them up
You see Barney here was content to work for the small end money
As an employee
Now being boss is more lucrative but that's a concept that somehow eluded you
Plus you got that pesky moral conscience
God that stuff gets in the way
He thinks he's the good guy
Keep talking while you can
Sure, you got a conscience that makes you weak
Success, real success
Is being willing to do the things that other people are not
Not everyone's as sick as you
Oh, but you are
Kill any Barney
Blow any shit up
How bout you kids? Killed anyone?
Before you all start grabbing bricks to stone me at The Hague
You might want to check your own hands for blood
But I digress. Where was I?
Yes, business is booming right?
A chopper here, a missile there, guns
Whatever, when suddenly
a competitor
I've been calling Uncle Sam a competitor
Hires my own team. Barney and the whole gang to whack me.
Things got ugly real fast and a lot of poeple got dead
3 former brothers in arms
- Shut your mouth.
- 3 Expendables
Our brothers, men we ate with, fart with, bled with, dead!
He puts 3 slugs into my chest thank God for body armor even I thought I was dead
And then he b--- it out with the casualty, all dead!
Because you couldn't stay out of my business!
Shut your mouth!
Go on, do it!
Go on!
It's hard enough to fathom
I can't believe you forgot
What?
That it's hard to beat an enemy when you're living inside your own head
You see you tie me up
Like an animal
Leave me to the slaughter. You humiliate me. Disgrace me.
And when the time comes to kill you
And it will. I will not use a weapon. I will use my hand
Because I want you to feel the way that I feel right now
Just cause we were brothers
What's that?
It's GPS tracker
How about that?
Hold it
We may need them
I need a body find them
- What happened?
- We found a shitstorm
It's gonna getting worse
This come in for you, 10 minutes ago
Hey Barney
My search party's dead so I'm taking it you're still with us
Now you should've killed me where you had the chance cause that's your last window, and it's gone
Now, I got something to show you here
You want them?
Come get them
What are you gonna do?
Wow, looking a little strung out there kids
And this is what you get for being pawns in Barney's moral chess game
That 1 looks a little slack
You know I feel most bad for you
I don't give a shit how you feel
I do, I have a daughter
I had feelings, anyway
You know, when the CIA, I, er
presume that's who you're working for
Am I right?
I bet you don't even know who you're working for
But for Barney?
Do you know who's he working for?
Does he know who's he working for?
It gets very confusing
Anyway, when the CIA wanted guys doing the dangerous work
in the dangerous places,
they called us. When they didn't want to get their hands dirty,
they called us.
Yup, we cleared every hotspot they had
We bumped the bad guys so that the good guys could rolled in looking like heroes
We killed a lot
But we saved more lives
Than you can possibly imagined
Then the boys on the hills wanting no loose ends
Tried to bury me
I was an American
Working for America
What's?
They'd eat their own children
The lesson here is
Never do business with the government
Never gonna save you that heartache
Never will
So you're getting your old team?
Nah, I've burned that bridge
You know your pride is gonna get you killed
Better me than them
- So you're really gonna go back?
- Yeah
- Alone?
You're an idiot
Thanks for showing up
The I guess our favors are done
But you're still an idiot
The hell did you find me?
People talks
I hear things
You got a mission
I can help
My name is Galgo
Let me fill you in
I am good, very good
At warfare
You know good memory, afraid of nothing
I want to be your friend
I don't need a friend
Yes, you do
Everybody does
I don't have any friends
That's why I know
Besides my friendship issues,
what I really need now is somehting to do
Well not just anything but
what I was born to do
It was a 1 way trip
Excuse me sir, but
1 way trip
is better than no way
which is the way I live now
Help me with the crate
I'm sorry
On the plane Gogo
On the plane, yes. But Gogo no Gogo, Galgo.
- Galgo.
- Gogo sounds like a Parisian hooker.
I am the bridegroom of death
The lyrics of a spanish legion old songs
that we used to sing when we're on a mission in Croatia
That's where I met Mingo
The best point man ever
Some kind of servant you know, ambush
under fire
The coolest cat ever
Just pure eyes in his veins
We were pinned down once like 2 bullets left
I looked over
No 1 bit of sweat
Yeah
Can I help you up there
You're a mechanic now?
Of course I am a mechanic. I am whatever you need me to be sir.
Ok then just be quiet.
Yes, sir
Tiger,
This sniper I knew
I mean, this guy got it all figured out
Wind speed, temperature
Barometric pressure
But you know what he says the most important?
No
Patience
Really?
Yes, I've said this
This thing smells good, what is that?
Kerosene? Gasoline?
Aviation fuel
It's good
The best team member ever, his name was Torres
Holy shit
You wouldn't believe what this guy was capable to do
Un-believable
I'm telling you, man.
- Galgo?
- Yes, sir
I think I know why your team let you go
You do?
Really?
Yes
Last chance
You sure you want to do this?
I like travelling
Good
Uh, who are those guys?
My old team
What the hell are you doing here?
You're stupid enough to get yourself into this mess
We're trying to get you out of it
Come on
We leave for war
Galgo you might want to get out of that seat, Christmas is coming
But it's June
Galgo, get the hell out
Yes sir
My hat
I'm curious
What?
Since when did suicide become your hobby?
I got a will
You know I'm probably the only friend you got
I got a lot of friends
People jump on the tables
I missed you Christmas
I miss you too you demented bastard
You could've loved that demented
Solid structure
That is taking us from 1 place to another
Through unbelievable speeds
Think about it
If God...if God... if he would've liked us you know flying
He would've give us feathers
Do you have feathers?
- I don't have feathers
- It's gonna be a long ass flight fella
It's going to be
It's going to be a long flight but don't worry
I'm here, because I can
Yeah
Thought you should know Barney, you're walking into a shitstorm
NSA ran a signal and frequencies checks on your team's phone
This bastard's not even trying to hide them
Where has he taken them?
They're in
Another honeymoon hotspot
Who is that?
Lee Christmas
Not far off Christmas
Stonebanks's compound is where he trained is goons
It's very heavily fortified
What's up with the local army?
I don't understand a word this guy is saying
Local army status
Small, corrupt
Stonebanks got all the brass in his pocket
Been running his operations through this shithole of a country for years
Wants some advice?
- What's the advice?
- What goddamn language is that?
Look who's talking
What's the advice Drummer?
Forget about what you're thinking
Remember our deal
We need him alive
So he could sit in his courtroom and beat us over the technicality
Those are orders Barney
- You broke the phone
- I got another 1
Think we'll make it back from this 1?
You didn't have to come along
Sure I did
Morons need friends
Gentlemen
Change of plans
This is it?
This is your evac team?
Short notice
Yeah
Very short
Where is your team?
Major Drummer?
No team, this one's off the book
I'm not even here
Nobody's here
I thought Church was asshole
I mean, if you're hysterically strong
You don't even have to go to the gym
You are just strong. You just got it
This is similar to reality
In the 19th century
You know what I mean
Well, this is interesting place
Give me a migraine
I hear that
Don't you think?
Look at the bright side
You run out of bullet
Roger that
Tall 1 doesn't like me
He doesn't like anybody
- What you say?
- He likes you
The hell is that?
What?
The computer strap to your wrist
Nothing
The same thing you were busting that kid's balls about
Nah, I had it for 1
Why'd your team let you go?
Why is it matter now?
I want to know who I'm working with
They are not around anymore
So
This um,
So why they let you go?
They didn't
Benghazi
I wasn't in the army anymore. We were
retreating hostage something like uh
like what we are doing here
It was a beautiful day
No problems
And then it all went bad
We got hit, got off
Waited for support, no 1 came
Everybody died
Except me
Ready to go?
This forces us
To see
Yeah
Thank you
So what do you think?
I think we should get this over with
4 signals
They are ready
This is way too wrong
It's not I don't like it
You know he got eyes on us now
- May I suggest something?
- No. No, later.
That's what I thought
That's fine
Go
Break it
The hell
Hello Barney
I knew you couldn't stay away
But I'm relieved someone will take up the kids
You got them in there, now try gettting them out
But unfortuantely for you
The entire complex has been wired with C-4
It takes a regular Joe about 90 seconds to get out of there.
You got, how about 45 seconds?
He's turned this whole place into a bomb
Maybe not
9% battery? You didn't charge it?
Excuse me but what are you doing?
Try to run some code, should be able to jam the signal
Why didn't you think of that?
Well I use it to check the weather
Will you just shut up and let him do his thing?
You sure you're gonna do this Thorn?
I can do it, I can do it.
Come on, man.
Come on, come on.
Come on
You're good, come on Thorn.
Focus, focus.
Got it
Good job, my boy
We lost override. The signal is jammed.
Send them in
Barney the battery's at 8%. When this thing died, we lose override.
That gives us about 25 minutes tops
Don't pop the bottle yet, we still got troubles
Big trouble
Lucky again bro
Try to enjoy the view because shortly the building that you're currently standing in
Will be surrounded by the ---stan army
- How did you shitheads managed to get captured?
- Shut up!
Step back
That's about to be an accident.
And we're trapped in here.
This is exactly what he knew would happen
Us, tearing at each other
This stops now
We can do this
But only if we do this together
If we work as a team
We just may get out of this alive
And you, I want to make it work
That simple
You got any weapons?
Here's the plan. We're gonna break up into small groups
And go out to the ground floor
Get ready
Come on
You Stay with me
Thorn you stay with me. I want you to take Galgo.
Yeah I don't want to
What, what? Shhh
Don't stop
1 there, 1 there
There's too many
They're on our flank. Bring it to them
That's enough, light them up
Incoming
Up the shaft Thorn. You gotta protect the signal jammer
I thought you could fight
Jesus God, you're ok?
Do not worry I love this
Good keep moving
Relax
I told you you'd give yourself a stroke
We got a tank problem pal
Do something about it
I'm on it
Trench, on your right
That's gotta hurt
Drummer's in the house
Let's go
Time to pick up the tempo boys
Look out for the chopper
Not good
Hold on
This does not happen
You want to do something?
Beware
Oh shit
Hi there
Closer
Yang, hit something
Next
Your name is Luna right?
Luna means moon
Hypnotic, mysterious, magical, like yourself
Would you like to hold my gun?
Goodbye sweet
There is
Come on, drive this thing
See you assholes
Yeah
Damn that's cool
It was all under control
That's what it looked like
This the happiest moment of my life
Jingling jingling
You finished here?
Men
- You're no gonna believe this
- Oh, god
I've been thinking of you the whole time
Can we just go
Come on
Hold up
Where did you learn how to fly?
Warning, we got reinforcements
Shit
Drummer, there's another wave coming
The only way out is up
On my way
Evac in 5
Got it
Everybody get to the roof now
Trench, Yang, come on, clear the roof
Let's go
Damn
- Always this easy?
- Pretty much
How hard can it be to kill 10 men?
You think your idiot can just wound a couple?
Watch closely
And again
Anybody else?
Useless bunch
You want something done right
You got that part here
Yeah the some one right there
Go go go
Don't stop
Come on guys, move it
Drummer we're pinned down
Stop mumbling
Good morning
Let's get to the chopper
Let's go
Go go go go go
Go gotta go
- Yang?
- You're welcome
You're working for Trench?
Yeah, he pay me more money
- Who the hell are you?
- I'm the guy that just saved your ass
Batteries at 2%
Hey Barney, leaving so soon?
Come on, ley's finish this
How you feeling?
Come on, stand up, you'll feel better
Barney where are you?
Loose the armor, I want you to feel this
Barney we gotta go
And don't even think about going after that piece of garbage in the bag
Come on
That's it
We don't need this, do we?
Come on
Barney we gotta go
Batteries at 1%
Come on Barney
What about The Hague huh?
I am The Hague
Batteries gone
Gotta go, gotta go
No don't, wait, wait
I can't wait
You owe me Barney
Barney
Pull me up
You're gonna fire us again, Barney?
Come on
Oh man cohesion
I will kill you
Alright, I'm sorry
- Pull me up you idiot.
- Don't pull him up.
To Caeser
Caeser
Yo Barney
Yeah
I don't think I'll be needing this anymore
You want yur luck back
I hope I didn't stress you
I think you did stress
Good to have you back man
Hail Caeser
You never got him to The Hague
You know Drummer
Working with you ain't turned up to be so bad
I ahven't had so much fun in years
Fun is important
These guys are nuts
You see this tattoo
Yes, you also
Come on, there must be a plan
- Woah, Major Old-School
- Major Badass
I agree with you on this
I am sure I have done enough
That I am worth my weight, in gold you know
Am I close? And since I am as crazy as you
I am sure I feel game
- Galgo?
- Yes sir?
Welcome aboard
Thank god
Because you know I already spent a fortune on this
You know what I mean
I am so happy
Barney thank you
No, no, no, no
- No hugging
Best 2 out of 3
Hey just want to say thanks
For what?
- For caring
- Come on
- You know if you're 30 years younger
- I'll be afraid of you
Cheers
Hey Yang, looks like you had a growth spurt
Tall people don't live long
So you're working for Trench now
I thought you retired
I lie
Good
You guys want to get a room?
So jealous
We came in this thing together, we gonna leave this thing together
Absolutely
Cheers
You know for a guy that doesn't take orders very well
You're pretty good
Yeah?
So when do I take over?
Keep trying
Hey Smilee
Get over here
You do good kid
You look like a proud, demented father
You could've skip at the demented part
That was a compliment
Please rate this subtitle at www.osdb.link/k35v
Help other users to choose the best subtitles