Someone needs to stop Clearway Law.
Public shouldn't leave reviews for lawyers.
My love.
Cara mia.
The ring! The ring!
Oh, no! No, no, no!
Oh, Thing.
Best hand always has the ring.
Dearly be-loathed,
it is indeed a rare privilege
to see our family gathered together
for this Addams tradition.
To commence this ceremony
and deliver these two
into the yawning void of matrimony,
we put the lime in the coconut
and drink them both up.
I now pronounce you...
- Monster!
- Freak!
- You've been here long enough!
- We've had enough of your kind!
Addams aren't wanted here!
Leave already!
I now pronounce you husband and wife.
Quick, put the lime in the coconut
and drink them both up.
Sorry. I couldn't help myself.
This is our home!
Everyone, to the bridge!
Fire!
You two love-bats better fly out of here.
I'll hold them off.
Mazurka!
Grab onto my hairy hump!
I think I can see my house from here.
Oh, no, that's a women's prison.
Oh, Gomez.
Why do hordes of angry villagers
follow us everywhere we go?
We are safe, my love.
That is all that matters.
I want to find a new home
that is shrouded from the world.
Someplace that is truly us.
Yes! Somewhere horrible!
Somewhere corrupt!
Somewhere that no one in their right mind
would be caught dead in!
Unhappy, darling?
Yes. Completely.
Oh, Gomez, you have torn down my walls
and stabbed your name onto my heart.
My wan temptress.
Your hand is as cold as a dead fish.
My love, that is a dead fish.
So it is.
Darling? Is that a wrinkle I see
on your pallid brow?
What's wrong?
We can't run forever, my love.
I want a home again.
I want our children to grow up in peace.
I want to pick out cemetery plots.
Morticia, I swear on my life
I will find us a new home.
And your every wish shall be granted.
Mon amour.
French?
You know what that does to me.
Nouveau riche.
Je ne sais quoi.
- We hit something.
Is he all right?
No, he seems perfectly demented.
State Hospital
for the Criminally Insane.
Gomez?
That must be the asylum.
Oh, thank goodness.
A decent place to sleep for the night.
Thank you, old boy. Lead the way.
It's quiet. Too quiet.
Must be the off-season.
Hello?
There's no one here.
Could it be abandoned?
It's creepy.
- Kooky.
- Mysterious.
Spooky.
Get out!
It's hideous.
It's horrible.
- It's home.
What a lovely morning!
Nice try.
Get out!
Oh, you're always so grumpy
before your morning coffee.
Better.
Lurch, it's time for breakfast.
Thing.
Have Ichabod wake the children.
Lurch, would you mind dusting the house?
Slowly, Cleopatra.
I wouldn't want
my favorite African Strangler to choke.
All right, Ichabod. I'm awake.
Not for long!
Real mature, Pugsley.
Oh, please. You never threw an ax
when you were my age?
Of course I did.
I never missed.
How I wish something would liven up
this already tedious day.
Thanks for trying, Ichabod.
Pugsley? Pugsley?
It's time for sword practice.
Pugsley?
Let the games begin.
Here's Pugsley!
All right, son. That's enough.
Ah, they blow up so fast these days.
Don't make me come up there!
This is your last warning!
My head.
Pugsley, we're supposed to be working
on your swordplay.
Your Sabre Mazurka is two weeks away,
and you've barely practiced at all.
So I missed one practice.
What's the big deal?
The big deal?
The Sabre Mazurka is the most
important day in a young man's life.
It's what makes you an Addams.
It's the day your entire family
gathers around you
and passes judgment on your worth
as a human being.
I hear it's like Thanksgiving.
But swords are so old-fashioned.
I'm more of a demolitions man.
Explosives have no place in a mazurka.
Hand them over.
All of them.
And the TNT.
And the M-80s.
Roman candles. Bang snaps.
Holy hand grenades.
Son, our family hasn't been all together
in 13 years.
They are coming from all over the world
to see you on your special day.
I just want it to go perfectly.
All right, Pop. I'll practice.
That's my boy.
- Putrid.
- Horrifying.
I call spleen.
Wednesday, please,
no ink stains on the table.
Yes, Mother.
Gomez, everyone we've invited
to the mazurka has threatened to come.
I know. Isn't it wonderful?
All Addamses under one roof again.
Yes. But where will everyone sleep?
We'll have Lurch fix up the mausoleum.
It'll be like sleepaway camp.
Very well, darling.
- Uncle Fester!
Brother!
Don't worry, I'm okay.
The plate glass window broke my fall.
Rick 'em, rack 'em, roar 'em, buzz!
Addams is as Addams does!
I am thrilled you're here.
I'm not late, am I?
Actually, we weren't expecting you
for another two weeks.
- So, not late.
- I apologize, darling.
You see, I asked Fester to come early
to help Pugsley with his mazurka plans.
Hey!
No! No! Bad Kitty!
That's a bad Kitty!
If I'd known you were coming,
I would've prepared the dungeon.
Please, don't worry.
I'll sleep in the attic.
You won't even know I'm here.
I've practiced that move
in a lot of people's homes.
Uncle, can you tell us
what's beyond the gate?
Why ever would you ask that, dear?
I heard a strange noise
in the fog earlier,
and I should like to investigate.
There's nothing out there
but boring marshland.
There must be something.
We never go anywhere.
Who knows the untold horrors
we're missing out on?
Darling, we have all the horror
we need right here.
Uncle Fester can go wherever he likes.
Now, now, there are some restrictions.
You know, I can't go to the mall or a zoo
or a building...
When you're older,
you can travel to your heart's content.
But for now, it's safer for you here.
Socrates, come.
Mexico, no-go.
South America, Europe, China, Asia.
Most parts of Africa.
I'm allowed in Antarctica.
You're watching
Home Art & Garden Television.
The world's a big place full of poor souls
who don't know the difference
between shiplap and Shinola.
Well, I'm here to help.
I take your uninspired living space
and turn it into the perfect palace
of your dreams.
No matter how outdated
your design sense, I can help you.
My only flaw?
Sometimes I care too much.
I'm Margaux Needler,
and I'm about to stage
a design intervention!
You're welcome in advance.
Today we're putting the finishing touches
on our biggest project yet.
Assimilation.
We didn't just make over a house.
We made over a whole town!
And in just two weeks
on our live season finale,
you will be able to buy
your very own piece of Assimilation.
That's right.
In a Design Intervention first,
we are putting a whole neighborhood
up for sale.
This will be your chance
to purchase the house of your dreams
in the town of your dreams.
Sounds good? I thought so.
Welcome to Assimilation, neighbor.
This program brought to you
by Neighborhood Peeps.
Your neighbors are watching.
And we're out.
Lovely. Perfect.
Let's set up for the walk-through.
Margaux, did that feel good to you?
No, Glenn. We need more balloons,
more confetti.
- Roger that.
- What are we selling here?
Big dreams.
You know how you get big dreams?
With big ratings.
- Got it.
- Double the balloons.
And I want a blizzard of confetti.
I want so much confetti
that we need snow patrols
to find lost children.
I bet my home improvement empire
on this town.
Every house must sell
or we're out of business.
It's got to be perfect.
- Mom! You're never gonna believe this.
- What is it, Parker?
I found a creepy mansion up on the hill.
I'm so glad you're exploring, Parker,
but I don't have time to talk
right now, sweetheart.
Mama needs to help people.
I need help. Aren't I people?
You're cute. Don't you have
chipper 'n' cheer practice this afternoon?
Run along, honey.
Now, Glenn, what are the numbers
we're expecting?
Mom!
Left a bit, up a bit.
Now down a bit.
Perfect.
And three, two, one...
You made me miss.
Do you know how long it took
for me to set this up?
Look, Pugsley, your mazurka's coming up,
and, well, you're not ready...
even if I am the only one who sees it.
So, pay attention,
and you might actually get through this.
Wait. You're going to help me?
Why?
Because you are my brother.
And... I love... you.
All right. How are you gonna help me?
You see that hole over there?
Go stand beside it.
- That hole?
- That hole.
I don't get it.
Darling, not to criticize,
but is that really as tight
as you can make it?
I'm sorry, Gomez.
I'm just a bit preoccupied
with the mazurka preparations.
Oh, I am as well.
I feel Pugsley is overconfident
and doesn't truly understand
the importance of this tradition.
Good news, everybody. Pugsley's gone.
Wednesday, I know that tone of voice.
Dig up your brother at once.
You're weakening the gene pool.
Hold on. What do you have there?
I'm not sure. I like it.
It's so... What's the word?
Opposite of sad?
Darling, bring that to me.
Strange.
There's usually a murderous clown
attached to the other end of these.
Wednesday, don't move.
What in the name of
all that is unholy is that?
It tastes like cotton candy.
How do you know what
cotton candy tastes like?
Tish, it was my youth.
I made mistakes.
Wednesday, wherever did
this pink thing come from?
Outside. They're everywhere.
Strangest weather system I've ever seen.
What is that?
- Where's it coming from?
- Wait, wait, wait.
The fog. It's lifting.
Well, that would only happen if...
Someone drained the marsh.
But who?
A town. This is not good.
We must go down there
and introduce ourselves at once.
This day is becoming
most wonderfully disruptive.
Let's keep going
with the run-through, okay?
Welcome back. I'm so delighted
to show you my house.
You can own one just like it,
just less large.
Blah, blah, blah.
Sconces, crown molding.
Which leads us to what I call
the salon de grandé.
Cross here, turn, then say something like,
now, before I show you this view,
go to an antiques store,
buy a chair and reupholster it.
'Cause you're gonna want
to sit down for this.
What? What's the matter?
For heaven's sake, what's going on?
Do I have something in my teeth?
What is it?
Not a single gargoyle.
Maybe this isn't such a bad thing.
We have been isolated here for a while.
I can really see myself
dying here!
Play nice, Kitty!
Well, no one is running at us
with torches and pitchforks,
so that's a plus.
You know, darling, I don't think we'll
need to put the family in the mausoleum.
They can stay here.
The family will never be comfortable.
It will be years
before rust and decay set in.
How you doing?
It's all so different.
Pugsley, don't drink it all.
This gentleman wants some too.
Sir, it's all right.
He's had all his shots!
What a nervous man.
Come on, Tish.
Let's explore the neighborhood.
I'm gonna pop in here for two minutes,
and I'll meet you in the town square.
- Agreed?
- Very well, darling.
Good day, all.
Don't let me interrupt your cup of joe,
or whoever you have in there.
So, what's dark and bitter here,
other than yours truly?
We have the...
Madagascar Emerald Peaberry
in a summer patchouli roast.
It has notes of oak, cherry and yoga.
You know, I'm looking
for something a bit stronger.
Let me try that.
Morticia, you have to try
these coffee grounds.
They have a wonderful grit.
Just a moment. What am I hearing?
Join the party,
this is where we all belong, yeah
Everybody come together,
sing our song, sing our song
Life is really perfect,
we are one big family, yeah
Everything is so much better
when I'm like you and you're like me
What's so great about being yourself
When you can be like everyone else
That is absolutely horrible.
It's easy to be happy
when you have no choice
Yes, it's easy to be happy
Hold on.
Unless I miss my guess here,
I believe that is supposed to be music.
They're greeting us
with one of their traditional songs.
- Then we ought to do the same.
- Wonderful idea, Fester.
When we are all together
Say it again until you believe it
I believe it
We believe it
I'd tip my hat to you
I'd do just that,
bum, bum, bum
Take it right off for you
But I haven't got a hat,
bum, bum, bum, bum, bum
I'm just a college boy
Even at that,
bum, bum, bum
I'd tip my hat to you
But I haven't got a hat
Bum, bum, bum, bum
Oh, God!
What'd I do?
How rude.
Gomez, we should return home.
Morticia, this is not the old country.
True, these people are a little different.
But deep down we're all the same.
We have to give them a chance,
get to know them.
We have to win them over.
Win them over?
Well, good morning, neighbor.
Margaux Needler.
Gomez Addams, at your service.
- My wife Morticia.
- Charmed.
Our children, Wednesday, Pugsley.
And my brother Fester.
Hey, neighbor. You know,
we can see right into your windows.
It's nice to... meet you.
As your neighbor, I'd like to offer you
the opportunity of a lifetime.
How would you like a free home makeover
from a world-renowned interior designer?
It will be a challenge, but I could
beautify that old house of yours so fast,
it'll make your heads spin.
I don't want to brag,
but mine already does that. Look.
I should like to see what
this plastic woman has to offer.
Yes.
Well, when is a good time to stop by?
Actually, Miss Needler...
Darling?
Stop by anytime you'd like.
Oh, wonderful! Then it's settled.
I'll see you at your house
first thing tomorrow.
You're welcome in advance.
That woman seems deranged.
Her face reminds me of a death mask.
Deranged? Death mask?
You tell me she's got halitosis,
and I'm hearing wedding bells.
Pugsley,
this is the Addams family sabre.
Three hundred years of Addams
have danced the mazurka
with this blade.
Only when you've shown
me you're ready.
Your father was the greatest swordsman
in Addams history.
His mazurka was the stuff of legend.
So no pressure!
It's all right here
in the mazurka handbook.
Every Addams performs this rite of passage
to show that you're prepared
to defend your family.
It sounds easy, but believe me,
it's insane.
Fester, hand him
the goo-goo-ga-ga baby training sword.
Pop, has anyone ever failed the mazurka?
Once. Your third cousin, Xander.
- Never heard of him.
- Exactly.
Music!
There's someone at the door.
Hi, guys. I'm going up to
this creepy mansion.
If you don't hear from me in 30 minutes,
send backup.
You rang?
Yeah, no. Life's too short. See ya!
Good morning, Kitty.
Greetings, Miss Needler.
Good morning.
I hope this isn't a bad time.
The worst. Do come in.
Glenn?
Welcome to the neighborhood.
Thank you.
Oh, my.
Are you... Are you ready
for your Margaux makeover?
Quite. Pugsley's been climbing the walls
in anticipation.
Well, well, well.
Let's take a look around, shall we?
And before you say anything,
you're welcome.
Now, if we're trying
for a more contemporary look,
well, these sconces have to go.
The sconces were a gift
from dead relatives.
If we get rid of them, they'll be
terribly hurt the next time they visit.
And this is our whine cellar.
We have a lovely collection of whines.
- Are we there yet?
- I want ice cream!
What do you mean
you're out of avocado toast?
This barrel is really bad!
And here's our bottomless pit.
- How do we get across?
- One moment.
We call this surfing the web.
Well...
I'm scared. I'm so scared.
Oh, my gosh.
I'm scared to close my eyes.
I'm scared to open them.
How do all those people fit
in that little contraption?
My vanity mirror
only imprisons 14 souls at a time.
You don't have a cell phone?
That's weird.
I may not have a cell phone.
Well, you don't have a crossbow,
and I thought everybody had one of those.
My name is Wednesday.
Okay. I'm Parker.
How long have you lived here?
My whole life.
Which seems endless.
I've never seen you at school.
- I'm cage-schooled.
- Excuse me?
It's terribly dull. But my mother insists.
I'm actually cutting cage right now.
Okay.
So, what happens at your school?
Not much.
Just friends turning on each other.
Girls making other girls
feel bad about themselves.
- Typical junior high stuff.
- Intriguing.
Can anyone go to your school?
I guess so. But who'd want to?
Wednesday! Great shot.
Mr. and Mrs. Addams,
there's really not much to do
to make this place perfect.
All we have to do is pull down
the side walls,
and then also break down
the other two walls.
Open up the ceiling
by breaking it irreversibly.
Just get this nasty
little floor out of the way.
And there you go.
With just those little touches...
Stop right there.
Don't touch another thing.
It's perfect.
Ms. Needler, you have a gift.
The good news is, I can have
a makeover crew up here
and swinging hammers
first thing in the morning.
What do you say?
We thought you were finished.
Our whole family is coming in two weeks.
Our finale!
Our finale is in two weeks.
Thank you, Glenn.
It's a gracious offer, Ms. Needler,
but you really have done enough.
It's our son's mazurka. You understand.
Thank you.
We're missing Mitch. Where's Mitch?
Get out!
Mitch who?
Gomez, I'll be blunt.
I have 50 houses to sell down there,
and their view of your property is,
well, off-brand.
Fifty houses?
Yes.
You know, ever since my family
was chased out from the old country,
my one dream has been to find a place
we could call home.
Once they see Assimilation...
I think they'll want to stay for good.
What's that?
Thank you so much for coming by, Membrane.
It's Margaux.
Well, then... run, Margaux!
Run, run, run!
That Wednesday girl is a freak.
We're about to be invaded
by a whole army of freaks.
It's tragic when people can't accept
the help they so badly need.
And when that happens,
well, another kind of intervention
is called for.
I agree, Gomez.
The whole family moving here
would be a dream come true.
But I don't trust that Margaux woman.
She's an eccentric, darling.
Give her a chance.
Raspberry preserves.
Must be some kind of
scented embalming fluid.
Wednesday, practice your lurking
on someone other than your father.
He's too easy.
Much better.
Mother, Father,
I'd like to speak with you.
What's on your mind,
my little night crawler?
I spoke with Parker this afternoon.
She's the daughter of
that talking mannequin who came by.
She told me about a communal school
all the neighborhood children attend.
It's called junior high.
Junior high.
Yes. Yes, I have read about those
in my abnormal psychology journals.
Anyone of age can enroll.
I think it would be good for me.
Well, I think it's a capital idea.
What of your studies here?
Your taxidermy is coming along so well.
Mother, would you really deprive me
of the opportunity to torment children
my own age?
Ah, she makes a point.
What's more, with Wednesday in school,
we'd get to know the people here
even better.
Well, Mother?
- Bye Mom!
- Bye, honey!
What?
Have a good day at school, dear.
Do your worst!
Ah, now I understand.
This is a children's prison.
Who's that?
Great.
This is Wednesday.
Hello.
Hey, Parker.
I got something for you.
A moldy sandwich.
You're slipping, Bethany.
You know what? You're right.
- Hey!
- Let's kick it up a notch.
You have no sense of humor.
- Did you see her face?
- I know.
Bethany, is it?
Don't cut your eyes on my crew
unless you're ready to dance.
What did you say, little ghoul?
I don't think you understand.
I'm not locked up in here
with you, Bethany.
You're locked up in here with me.
Whatever.
- What did you do?
- You shouldn't have said that.
There's nothing you can do.
Bethany's way too popular.
Popularity is fleeting.
I prefer to set my sights on something
a little more challenging.
- Like what?
The establishment.
Let's see. Who shall I be today?
How about... Ah, Shelly Longbottom
on Sugar Ridge Lane.
From Shelly Longbottom to everyone.
Did you hear about those Addams people?
Question mark.
Someone told me they're wanted
in 30 states.
You know, they're raising a garden
of man-eating plants.
And feeding them our pets!
Has anyone seen my shih tzu Fifi?
They're gonna turn us all into zombies.
Where are they from anyways?
It doesn't matter.
It's obvious they don't belong here.
Honey? Oh, those awful people
up on the hill...
they're not even on Neighborhood Peeps!
Well, that's suspicious.
If other people are scared,
then I'm scared!
I believe everything I read!
I'm not gonna be the last person
on the block to panic.
If someone posted it, it must be true.
You invite one family in,
then all the families come in.
Do you think we should investigate?
I'm worried for the children.
We need to talk to Margaux!
Open your books, page 43.
Follow the instructions.
- Yuck.
- Oh, I've done this thousands of times.
I don't want to touch it.
What's that?
Flip the switch.
Give my creature life!
Live! Live, I tell you! Live!
It's alive! It's alive!
Oh, my God! Oh, my God!
Get them off me!
Bethany's changed her look.
It suits her.
Awesome. Totally awesome.
- It is an honor...
- And a privilege...
to watch you work.
Hey, do you want to go to the mall?
Why not? I haven't seen
a good mauling in ages.
It's late. I'm worried.
Darling, Wednesday will be fine.
She can take care of herself.
It's not Wednesday I'm worried about.
It's the rest of them.
We may need to provide an alibi.
My love, it's game night.
Wednesday will be home soon.
So why don't you come and join us?
Oh, very well. F-6.
Pugsley, you heard your mother!
Blow F-6!
Fire in the hole!
I'm king of the world!
- Yes!
- You sunk my battleship.
Well done, Pugsley.
Hello, my uglies!
Mother!
I thought I felt my skin crawling.
Grandma, what a surprise.
I thought you were in Prague.
I was. They caught me smuggling
crocodiles out of the zoo.
But I escaped and talked my way
onto a Somali pirate ship.
We got into a heated poker game,
and I cleaned them out.
- Cheating or robbery?
- Both!
Always remember, Pugsley,
it ain't cheating if no one catches you.
I haven't bathed in two weeks.
Or is it months?
That reminds me.
Guess what I've got, Pugsley.
- Candy.
- Oh, yes!
But the mazurka isn't for a week.
Why are you here so early?
Gomez said you needed a little help
with the party,
and I said I got my son ready
for his mazurka.
So of course I'm going to do the same
for my grandson.
I love him.
It's true. I sent for her.
I can't believe you bothered
your mother with that, darling.
Neither can I?
- He said you were in over your head.
- Thank you, Mother!
He said you were more tense
than he's ever seen you.
I didn't say that exactly.
Yes, you did. You said that exactly.
Said he was worried you'd have
a massive facial expression and...
You know, I'm starving. Let's eat.
Not until Wednesday gets home.
Where is that granddaughter of mine?
I've got something for her.
There's my little storm cloud.
Wednesday, where have you been?
Elsewhere.
What are you wearing?
Parker calls it a pop of color.
Well, I certainly appreciate a horse
with a spear through its head.
- The color is...
- She claims it brings out my smile.
Wednesday, you don't have a smile.
Turns out I have a lot of things
you don't know about.
I see I got here just in time.
You were right to call, Gomez.
I'll talk to her. Hand me that bear trap.
Thank you, Grandma.
But I will handle this.
Suit yourself.
When you're done with Fabio,
send him up to my room.
Oh, boy.
Wednesday.
How would you like to join me tomorrow
after the... school
for tea and séance in the cemetery?
Is attendance mandatory?
Come, now, my little raven.
You did so love it when you were younger.
If you like, Mother.
Sleep well, dear.
Don't forget to kick your father
good night.
What's your favorite filter?
I don't know.
I look black-and-white in all of them.
You know, when I met you,
I thought you were super weird.
But now I think you're really cool.
I concur. You're not completely
devoid of merit yourself.
I want to say... thank you.
Oh, how'd that barrette you bought
yesterday go over at home?
Actually, my mother's reaction was...
well, unexpected.
She was accepting. It depressed me.
One never wants to see
one's mother that way.
But I must admit,
walking around in something so garish,
so grotesque,
I was shocked how thrilling it felt.
I wish I could do that.
But my mom makes me wear this stuff,
and it's just so... so...
I believe the word you're looking for
is unfortunate.
I'd love to just go crazy
and wear something that would shock her.
Well, Parker, you're in luck.
You happen to be talking
to the queen of shock.
Hello, Mother.
Where's my little wraith?
Wednesday still hasn't arrived.
We agreed to come up here
for tea and séance,
and now it seems she stood me up.
- Morticia, can you hear me?
- You're not doing it right.
- Press that button.
- I did.
- Did you hear it click?
- Morticia!
It's supposed to be on
when you hear the click.
- Wait, I see something.
- You did it!
Hello, darling!
Now, where's my granddaughter?
Just what I said.
I think she's distancing herself from me.
She's wrapped in a black hole
of emptiness and longing
like all of us Frump women.
- Wednesday...
- It's not Wednesday!
- Who's this?
- It's me, Father.
Morticia, what's wrong with you now?
The world can be so cruel.
And all she wants to do is run toward it.
She's a lot like you that way.
You wanted to see the world,
find yourself, serve time.
Listen, Morticia.
Remember the time you ran away
and joined the Girl Scouts?
We were so worried you were on a bad path.
But when you found out that campfires
were for roasting marshmallows
and not other Girl Scouts,
well, you got bored and you came home.
We were so relieved.
Trust Wednesday.
Like you, she'll do the right thing.
Thank you, Father.
That's most comforting.
Good. Wait a second.
When did I die?
- Twenty years ago.
- Oh, right.
Happy anniversary, darling.
All right, Pugsley.
Let's go through it again.
You got this, Pugsley.
This mazurka's nothing.
You eat swords for breakfast.
You've just got a case
of pre-ball jitters.
It's way more common than you think.
If a mazurka lasts
for more than four hours,
contact your doctor.
From the top. Music.
Pugsley, I can honestly say
that was most definitely...
a thing you did.
Question.
What in heaven's name was it?
The Sabre Mazurka.
You know what?
You've been practicing hard.
Why don't we call it a day?
Hit the showers, kid.
So we're finished?
Ah, yes. Yes, son,
we are most certainly finished.
Okay.
Thanks, Pop. Thanks, Uncle Fester.
This is a complete disaster.
How did this happen?
He's going to make a fool of himself
in front of everyone!
Gomez! You gotta calm down!
There's still a day to get him ready.
Fester, a year wouldn't be enough
to get him ready.
I've failed him, Fester.
I tried to raise him to be an Addams,
but I failed him.
They're going to eat him alive.
I like it like that
Yeah, baby
I said I like it like that
Oh-ohh-ohh-ohh-ohh-ohh, baby
I like it like that
All right, thank you.
Grandma, we already have a band.
They came highly recommended
from the mortuary.
I'm sure they're good.
My sister Sloom is going
to be judging Pugsley.
And if things aren't done
the traditional way,
she won't be happy,
and the mazurka could be a disaster.
But what do I know?
Fine.
- Hey, we got the gig!
- We got it!
One more thing.
Oh, someone's at the door.
I'd better go see who it is.
What's so great about being yourself
When you can be like everyone else
Do not speak to your mother that way.
How dare you enter this house like that.
Wait. Where are your tattoos?
Oh, thank the stars.
Where were you?
Hanging out with Parker.
Is this why you skipped
tea and séance?
Your grandparents
were trying to contact you.
Holy Hades!
Whoever did that to you, Wednesday,
I hope the other guy looks worse.
Nobody did this to me.
This is my new look.
- Do you like it?
- I do not like it.
Everyone knows pink
is a gateway color.
I warned you about sending her
to public school.
Don't worry. Wednesday is never going
to that school again.
- What?
- In fact...
she's never leaving this house again.
Wow, that's some evil eye she's got there.
No. That dead-eye stare is new.
And I think I know where she got it.
Hey, guys. This is me now.
If you like it, hit like.
But who cares if you like it?
I'm living my truth.
Parker!
- Who did this to you?
- I did.
This is my new look, Mother.
I decided that from now on,
I choose my clothes.
Not you.
This is that little creep
Wednesday Addams's work.
She's not a creep.
She's just not like you.
Why can't you ever let
people be different?
Because it's my calling
to make everyone the same.
Too bright! It burns!
Good. Maybe it'll burn away the weird.
I hate it here.
Everything's boring and fake and bright.
Like plastic flowers.
Like... Like you.
Parker, plastic flowers live forever.
Now, you go think about that in your room.
With no social media.
No! Please, no. Anything but that.
Now, go wipe that depressing goop
off your face.
You first.
Those Addamses have gone
too far this time.
I think they're going to need
a little more help.
Hey!
Where are you going?
A friend's.
I hold people prisoner,
not the other way around.
Good luck with your mazurka.
Wait! You're leaving?
Who's gonna torment me every day?
Living under this roof
is all the torment you'll need.
Besides, our parents have made it clear
that the only way to be accepted
in this family
is to be exactly like them.
I can't play by those rules anymore.
Farewell, brother Pugsley.
Tomorrow you become a man.
And I become a fugitive.
Always kind of knew it'd end up like this.
Just didn't think it'd be so soon.
I'll never forget you, Pugsley.
But I'll try.
Pugsley, have you seen your sister?
She's not in her room.
Pugsley, where's Wednesday?
Ticktock. Ticktock, Mother.
You're getting very sleepy.
Pugsley.
She did not go to her friend's house.
She went to her friend's house?
I repeat,
she did not go to her friend's...
When the day is long
And the night
The night is yours alone
When you're sure you've had enough
Of this life
Hang on
Don't let yourself go
'Cause everybody cries
And everybody hurts
Sometimes
I shall be staying with you for a while.
Everybody
Hurts
If this doesn't work, the next house
we flip is gonna land on you.
Marty, listen to me.
Tomorrow, our finale will be
the biggest half-hour
your network has ever aired.
There's just one more thing
to take care of.
This better be good, or you won't be able
to get a job as a doormat!
Yes, yes, yes.
I intend to bring the house down.
You rang?
It! Cousin! You made it!
Please come in. Make yourself at home.
Where did she hide my phone?
I haven't been able to post a photo
of my lunch in almost three days.
And what about in there?
That's my mom's crafting room.
No one is allowed in there.
Then that's where it is.
Weird.
Hidden depths.
What is this?
There's Mr. Haney making a sandwich.
And that guy trying to put
a tiny tuxedo on his cat.
- That's Mr. Flynn.
- Why are you being so difficult?
My money's on the cat.
And there's our science teacher,
Ms. Gravely...
putting her underwear in the freezer?
My mom must've built hidden cameras
into all of the houses.
She really is psycho.
Parker!
Hey, Mom.
We were just looking for you.
What have I told you
about Mommy's crafting room?
Sorry to do this,
but standards must be upheld.
Parker, someday you'll understand.
And, Wednesday...
Well, anyway, Parker.
My mom has a lair and a jail?
I knew I should've picked
to live with my dad.
We're gonna be on TV!
Are we gonna be famous?
Glenn,
what do you want in the frame?
Okay, everyone, listen up.
It's the last run-through
before the finale,
so let's try this one last time, okay?
We're gonna shoot across the town square
to the gazebo,
where Margaux will make
her grand entrance.
So everyone will be walking
this direction across the square.
Judy, you start here.
Ken, you're gonna follow Judy.
You can stand right here and...
Is there a bathroom nearby?
Margaux, they're here!
What are you talking about?
They're here!
The Addams family!
Pardon me.
Excuse me.
What are we gonna do?
What we always do, Glenn.
Help people.
The Addams monsters
are planning to attack
the town tonight!
Exclamation point.
Meet at Margaux's house now.
Salutations, Addams! We're here!
Petunia, I love what you've done
with your hair.
Thanks. I just had it mowed.
Please come in.
Make yourself uncomfortable.
Uncle Onion!
It's been so long!
Yes. So disappointed to see you.
You always manage
to bring a tear to my eye.
Greetings, Dr. Flambé.
How are you doing?
- I'm on fire.
- Good!
This party's gonna be lit.
Auntie Sloom.
You are as radiant
as a barrel of nuclear waste.
Where is the boy?
Pugsley!
There you are.
Come down and say hello
to your Auntie Sloom.
Gomez, this tradition
is not to be taken lightly.
I trust that the boy
has been properly trained.
Yes, once you see how...
It's bad enough this mazurka
is taking place in New Jersey.
Now, where are the drinks?
I'm thirsty.
You've seen them!
You've heard the stories
on Neighborhood Peeps.
Those Addams aren't people.
They're monsters.
And now there's an infestation of them.
They're here to destroy
our beautiful community
and turn into a place that
no design intervention can save.
Addams aren't wanted here!
They're monsters!
They're all monsters!
We need to destroy them first!
Who's with me?
We'll be revealing Assimilation
and all of you to our audience
in just an hour.
Our last chance
to help these people is now.
Bill, John, do you still have
that lovely catapult?
- Yes, we do!
Are you sure about this?
We can't let them
ruin our neighborhood!
- Let's do it!
- I want them out!
No one torments my family but me.
Hair clip, please.
Okay.
- Wha...
- Cage school 101.
He'd better be ready,
or Auntie Sloom will have his head.
He looks very small.
The kid's got some big shoes to fill.
I certainly hope the boy is ready.
I'm not going easy on him.
Heads up!
Hey, alto. You're flat.
Sloom.
Sister.
Darling, I know the last time
we saw each other,
we had that horrible fight.
And I just wanted to tell you,
from the bottom of my heart,
I won that fight,
and I was glad I cheated!
You won?
Still a sore loser, as always!
I want a rematch,
right here, right now.
Auntie Sloom, can I get you anything?
When's the mazurka?
Soon, soon.
Our daughter Wednesday isn't here yet.
If your daughter can't be on time,
then we will begin without her!
Very well, Auntie Sloom.
Attention, please. Attention!
The hour is upon us.
Places!
We gather today to witness my son,
Pugsley Addams,
perform his Sabre Mazurka.
He will begin with a reading
from The Terror,
which commemorates our cries in battle.
And now the transition into manhood.
And now the Sabre Mazurka.
Hold still.
The Addams mustache.
Now you're ready.
Pugsley.
I give up. I can't do it, Pop.
I'm sorry.
I let you down.
You haven't let me down, Pugsley.
I was so focused on doing things
the traditional way,
I forgot to let you be who you are.
Hey! Are you ready
for your Margaux makeover now?
It's Margaux.
She must've turned the whole town
into stark raving lunatics.
Well, I have to admit I admire her work.
- Let's do this then!
- It's locked and loaded, Margaux!
Let's go get 'em!
Fire!
Get out!
Pugsley! What is the true meaning
of the mazurka?
It's about protecting our family
from those who would do us harm.
Go ahead.
Show them what you're good at.
All we have to do
is pull down the side walls!
Everyone, follow my boy!
Hey, guys?
Fire!
Shakalaka bang, baby!
Quick, out this way!
Pop, I'm out of ammo!
We're trapped!
Hope I'm not crashing the party.
Wednesday!
Yes!
Ichabod, quick! Lower your branches!
Everyone grab on!
Margaux Needler never stops
until the project is complete!
Fire in the hole!
Mazurka!
Is everyone all right?
No limbs missing that weren't missing
before you arrived?
My little raven.
I'm so happy you returned.
Of course I came back.
I knew there was no way
you were going to save yourselves.
You were like weak baby squirrels.
It's so good to see you.
And you.
Socrates.
Eight legs. Nine lives.
You were right, cara mia.
People can be cruel.
What have we done?
They're just a family.
A family? Please!
They're a bunch of monsters.
Don't go soft on me, people.
I will relish hounding you
until that nuclear waste dump
of a house is gone
and your mutant family along with it.
Be careful what you wish for,
Miss Needler.
My family and I will never run
from the likes of you again.
Deep breath, Margaux.
Okay, I have a finale to shoot.
Parker, let's go.
I'm not going anywhere with you.
I'm staying with my friend.
Your friend?
Parker, these people are freaks.
If they're freaks, then I'm a freak.
And so are all of you.
Exhibit A, Ms. Gravely.
You put your underwear in the freezer.
Hey, it's refreshing, okay?
Exhibit B, Trudy Pickering.
You sit on the toilet backwards.
Well, where else am I supposed
to put my arms?
Wait. How did you know that?
Because your houses have been infested
with Needler-Vision.
She has hidden cameras everywhere.
- What?
- And watches you all of the time.
- In my private time?
- What else has she seen?
That is over the line.
Shut up! Listen, you lemmings.
This is my town.
You are nothing but a bunch of extras.
We are going to march down that hill
and do a live show.
I expect you to convince those
brainless peons out there in the audience
that this is the perfect place
to buy a house,
or none of you will be
living here much longer.
- Do you hear me?
- Actually, Mom...
everyone can hear you.
You've been live this whole time.
Three million people
are watching you right now.
The real you, for a change.
Please. What do I care
what a bunch of bloggers think?
- Margaux?
- What?
It's the network.
They're taking your show off the air.
What? No. I'll be bankrupt.
Who will buy all these houses?
Okay, watch this. Now's my chance.
Excuse me.
I just tooted.
Furthermore, I think I can help you
get rid of those houses.
What are you talking about?
Well, my dear, you've got a bunch
of houses you need to get rid of
and I got a bunch of family
I need to get rid of.
Hello?
Excuse me. I'm Trudy.
Trudy Pickering.
We never officially met.
Ah, yes. The toilet woman.
Right.
Listen. Please give us a chance
to make it right.
Let us have our own design intervention.
Mother, I spent time with these people.
And it is true, they are odd.
But we shouldn't judge them
just because they're different.
Have a wonderful day.
Thanks! Bye!
Have a good day!
Well, hello there.
Howdy, neighbor. How's the new house?
I love it. I hope you brought
your umbrellas.
You put in a typhoon. What a great idea.
Don't forget the gift basket, silly.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
We got scented embalming fluid,
toes, teeth, a fruitcake,
rat bait, got some dried apricots.
He's like training a puppy.
Adorable but tiresome.
She's the woman of my dreams!
Her breath is like a baby's diaper.
Fester, stop.
Who would've thought a guy like me,
a total zero,
would've ended up with you, an also zero?
Well, do come in.
Now with the house rebuilt,
Pugsley,
we can throw you the celebration
you deserve.
You are Addams, through and through.
Get out!
Oh, how lovely. The spirit's home.
Finally back to normal.
We did good.
I won't tell anyone if you don't.
Someone needs to stop Clearway Law.
Public shouldn't leave reviews for lawyers.