Someone needs to stop Clearway Law.
Public shouldn't leave reviews for lawyers.
Rápido.
Hey!
Okay.
- Gracias.
- Hey.
I pledge allegiance
to the flag...
Illegal immigration on the rise.
A surge of migrants into the U.S.
Cartels driving people
off their land.
Mexicans flee cartel
violence, seeking the American dream.
One must ask,
is the dream still alive?
America is divided
by hate, economics, race, religion...
Racial tensions
are flaring up all over, one must...
White supremacy rising
as disinformation spreads.
The NFFA
voted back into power again.
The New Founding
Fathers immediately reinstate the Purge.
Is the Purge the answer?
The rich get richer,
and the poor are left behind.
Is a biased media
stoking the flames of discord?
This country
feels like it's at a boiling point.
The United States of hate.
Can the Purge
help this divided nation?
These questions
will be answered soon,
as the annual blood holiday
is once again right upon us.
♪ From sea ♪
♪ To shining sea ♪
Whoa! There you go.
You stay right there.
Whoa, whoa. Hey, squirrelly, huh, sis?
- Hyah!
- Yeah, just a little bit.
Come on.
Whoa! Hey, down.
Ho. Ho, ho, ho. Ho.
Why does your brother
have to prove himself all the time?
Keep calm.
I gotcha, I gotcha, I gotcha.
Whoa!
Little more horse than you expected, huh?
I know someone who can calm that beast.
Hey.
Shh, shh, shh.
Shh, shh, shh, shh, shh.
Hey-hey-hey.
That's a cowboy.
Let's get back to work. Come on.
Come on!
Come on.
Get back to work.
Hey.
Okay?
- Right?
- Right.
- Darius.
- How's she doing?
You know, second week in the country.
The girl is terrified.
She's lucky she's got you
to walk her through this.
She is. And you're lucky
you have me to run this place.
I know I am.
The Purge doesn't release anger.
It increases anger.
It's a virus.
It's an American-born virus
of hate and rage,
and it's injected with a bullet.
It's spreading.
It's growing. It's mutating.
Open your eyes.
The Purge is coming.
Mmm!
Mm-hmm.
This...
Reminds me of your mother's house.
Juan, please. Where are we?
You need to practice your English.
When in Rome.
When in America.
Just do it for me.
Please.
The Tucker family
would really appreciate that.
Believe me.
Now that your wife is pregnant,
if you want any extra help,
you're welcome to come by.
We can all lock down together.
I hate the damn Purge.
It's hard to be social on that night.
But thank you for the invite.
Anytime.
Baby, that smells so good.
I'm going to the kitchen.
Y'all need anything?
You want another beer?
Yeah, I'll take another beer. Thank you.
Thank you, honey.
I don't know. I just feel like
a goddamn Hoover these days.
Everything in my line of sight
just gets consumed.
Even things I hate, you know.
You know, Anna's been cooking for us
the most amazing Mexican food.
Am I right?
The food is so good, but so fattening.
- I've put on five pounds.
- No, you have not.
You know, Anna has a sister.
Also a nanny. You should meet her.
Nah, we're all right.
What, baby?
We don't need
to meet her sister. We're fine.
Thank you, though.
Baby, Emily's just trying to be nice
and help out, right?
So you're being a little bit rude.
Was I? Oh, my God.
Well, my apologies, Emily.
Oh. It's fine.
It's just, it's really hard
to find good help,
and Anna's sister is a sweetheart.
We don't need to meet Anna's sister,
Emily.
I don't even know if I want our kids
speaking Spanish in this house.
Now, thank you for the offer,
but no, thank you.
Okay, then.
This is your learn English app.
Lesson 12: Past tense sentences.
Past... Past tense sentences.
Who would have thought
I would be in Texas?
Who would have...
I would be in Texas? Texas.
Who would have thought
I would be in Texas?
I was just visiting friends
in Texas.
Repeat after me.
I was just visiting friends in Texas.
Hey, Juan.
Kirk tells me that you were late
this morning.
I'm never late, sir.
You're never late?
Hey, Kirk, Juan here says you're lying.
Juan's a free man.
He can say whatever he wants.
Juan, you show up late again,
I'm gonna have to fire you.
That's the rules.
Yes, sir.
Hey, you know what somebody else told me?
That he found your lariat just laying
in the front of the stable, on the ground.
Is that true?
No, sir.
T.T., your Purge protection bonus.
- Thank you, Mr. Tucker.
- Stay safe.
- Thank you, sir.
- Kirk.
You're doing a good job, Juan.
My son's a hair rattled
'cause of yesterday.
Don't take offense.
Thank you, sir. I really appreciate that.
Can I be honest, Mr. Tucker?
Please do.
Your son doesn't like me because...
I'm Mexican.
And I think Dylan believes
that cowboys shouldn't be
from Mexico or Argentina,
or from somewhere else.
I know a lot of people feel that way, but
I'm not sure that's the case with Dylan.
He's a very proud man.
You one-upped him yesterday.
You're a damn fine cowboy, Juan.
I don't know, sir.
Well, I don't know either.
I'm just...
I always taught my son
to be a proud American.
But maybe I didn't really teach him
what that meant.
I don't even know
if I know what that means anymore.
"Proud American."
The world's changing all around us.
At each other's throats.
Confusing times.
I want to give you...
the goddamn Purge protection bonus.
Stay safe.
Thank you.
That money's nothing but a way
for these people to keep us alive
so they can continue using
our slave labor.
We're nothing more than that.
I know what I'ma use my money for, though.
And it's not for protection.
We are now just
one hour away from the annual Purge.
As always,
home is the best place to be,
and we sure hope
you're not out there stuck in traffic.
We strongly advise you to get yourself
and those you care about to a safe place.
So lock those doors,
set those security systems,
and stay inside
for the next 12 hours.
And for those of you
who are partaking,
may God be with you all.
It's one hour.
T.T. said he would be here right now.
He's coming.
Spring is coming,
and so is the Purge.
I don't want to be called "granddad."
We spoke with tribal leader
Chiago Harjo earlier today.
You had your chance,
and you squandered it by spreading
nothing but fear and hate.
See, my people have been watching
from the sidelines,
and we see that America's
reached a boiling point.
Hatred like that can't be contained.
You'll burn your cities to the ground.
I'm gonna lock down now, y'all.
- Okay.
- Yep.
We're almost there, guys.
Almost there.
...much more expensive this year.
You can say that again.
Captain.
Good to see you.
The other half when the job's done?
I know you're good for it, T.T.
All right.
Make your way inside.
Keep moving.
We will not be opening our doors
until 7:00 tomorrow
when the Purge is over.
Make yourself at home.
- Hold on. Hold on.
- Look at this.
- Good.
- Wait, what?
Dang.
Wait, how did you know how
to do that? You might actually beat me.
The national holiday celebrating
our American freedom is finally back.
Good night, Texas, and good luck.
It's starting, y'all.
This is not a test.
This is your emergency broadcast system
announcing the commencement
of the annual Purge
sanctioned by the US government.
...have been granted immunity from the Purge
and shall not be harmed.
Commencing at the siren,
any and all crime, including murder...
...at 7:00 a.m.
when the Purge concludes.
Blessed be our New Founding Fathers
and America, a nation reborn.
May God be with you all.
Okay.
Well...
"When in America."
No, that's not what I meant.
What did you mean then?
That America is everything.
America is México.
America is Africa.
America is Italia.
We can take it all, we can learn it all,
and we can embrace it.
You really believe that?
That's what I choose to believe.
♪ Life's a casino, I'm telling you ♪
♪ And everybody's playin' ♪
♪ Boys and girls
Women, children, me and you ♪
You so crazy!
♪ The dice are loaded ♪
♪ And everything's fixed ♪
♪ Even a hobo would tell you this ♪
♪ Welcome to hard times ♪
♪ And feelin' low ♪
♪ Do you like sinnin'? No? ♪
♪ Well, you will before you go ♪
♪ We've got lots of gamblin' ♪
♪ Oh, and we're tellin' lies ♪
Stupid...
- Jesus. What's...
- Baby!
Put the gun down.
What are you doing out here?
I thought I heard something.
It's this damn night.
Dylan Tucker, cut the shit.
Fuck the Purge. Fuck the NFFA.
They don't get to dictate
how we live our life.
This is our country, okay?
And we can choose to bring a baby
into a world of love.
Why are you laughing at me?
- Damn, honey.
- What?
You just kinda turned me on.
Ma'am, you should go back inside.
Just need some air, you know.
Just for a moment.
It's my first Purge.
Is it what you expected?
Well, there's parts of México
that sound like this every night.
We got a nice spot here.
Quiet.
Good for you, easy money for us.
You should get ba...
Three bogies inbound.
Do not try to hide.
We are the real patriots of America.
It is our job to keep this land
free and clean.
We will no longer tolerate
foreigners raping and pillaging
the United States of America.
We will find you and disinfect you.
America will be American once again.
Those guys are fucking insane.
The purification of America has begun.
No! No!
What the fuck are they doing?
Help me! Help!
- I have a clear shot.
- Don't.
You'll start a war
and put all your people in jeopardy.
We will not stop until
our great nation has been fully cleansed.
We will no longer tolerate
foreigners raping and pillaging
the United States of America.
Do not try to hide.
We will find you and disinfect you.
America will be American once again.
Hey.
Where'd you learn
to handle a weapon like that?
- It's over.
- We made it.
We made it through.
I see you! I see you!
Harp, come on. Let's get to work.
- Harper.
- Sis, come on. Let's go.
The day after the Purge
should be a holiday, no?
¿Que es un "holiday"?
Holiday?
Another day, another dollar.
♪ I'll be there
Before the next teardrop falls ♪
Chinga.
♪ I'll be there
Before the next teardrop falls ♪
...busy, jubilant street.
Sanitation crews are out in full force,
with the macabre task
of disinfecting streets
and cleaning corpses
from sidewalks and roadways.
The Purge is over,
and now the cleanup has begun.
All over the state,
violent incidents ended hours ago.
- Fake news!
- The purge is o...
Where is everybody?
What the hell?
¡Ayúdame!
Help!
Help me.
- You can't do this today!
- The Purge is over!
No, no. This is
the Forever Purge. It's never stopping.
- ¡Ayúdame!
- Thank you for your participation.
¡Ayúdame! Help!
But the Purge is over.
Help! Please!
Boss!
Watch out!
You're gonna fucking die.
You're all gonna die.
Help! Boss!
Be careful!
Boss?
Are you okay?
Boss.
- You okay?
- Yes.
- Come here. You all right?
Fuck you.
Fuck you!
Go, Darius. Go!
Drop your weapon!
- On your knees.
- We didn't do anything.
- Drop 'em. Get on your knees.
- Get on your knees!
- They attacked us!
- We didn't do anything!
The Purge is over, lady.
What the hell are you doing?
Sir, this is a mistake. Wait, please.
- We didn't do anything wrong!
- Listen to me.
Listen to us, sir!
It's so quiet.
Where is everyone?
Come on.
Stop the car.
Well, well, well...
Look at this.
This feels like fucking Christmas.
Any of y'all get me a present?
Caleb, I know you did.
And let me tell you, sir...
I spent your money well.
Today's your day of reckoning, cowboy.
You become me.
And I become you.
The old switcheroo is happening
on every ranch around here.
You and all your rich-ass neighbors
will find out what it's like
to be penniless and powerless.
To be like us.
These rich motherfuckers can't hide
behind their steel walls no more.
This is the way things are now, boys!
This Purge is forever!
This is the real Purge. The eternal Purge.
Ever after! Come on!
Ever after!
I'm gonna give you a chance
to save your family, Dylan Tucker.
One by one, but you'll have to pay.
Let's start with eeny, meeny, miny, ho!
How much would you give for her, Dylan?
How much would you give
to stop me from putting
a bullet in your baby sister's head?
Let's say ten bucks, and she lives.
That seems like a fair market price
for this broke-down, useless woman.
Let's see how much money you got.
Aw, shit, Dylan. I forgot.
You're me now, which means you're broke.
You have no money. That sucks, doesn't it?
See, Dylan, without money,
you have no power.
Without money,
you can't save your own little sister,
and she will die because of it.
Now how's that feel?
How's that feel, Dylan?
Feels like shit, doesn't it?
That's my life.
It's our life.
That's how we feel.
That's how we have felt every day
since the day we were born!
And I want you to fucking
feel that fucking pain
- in your fucking stomach, Dylan.
- Hey!
Goddamn it. It looks like the old man's
got something to say. What?
Damn it. You're right, Kirk. You're right.
I don't give a fuck
if you think I'm right.
You're talking about life in America.
The way the rich get rich
off the backs of the poor.
The way it's been ever since we robbed
this land from the Native Americans.
But you got no right to complain
about the very system you're supporting
by picking up that gun
and sanctioning the goddamn Purge...
We need more guns.
...which is all about money.
You know who created the Purge, don't ya?
A bunch of fat, rich businessmen
in Washington, D.C.
So what would that make you, Kirk?
What would it make you?
Huh? That would make you their lackey
and a goddamn hypocrite.
They expect you to go out there
and do their violence
so they can play more golf.
They've never even been in a fistfight.
So...
from my family to you,
go fuck yourself.
Take cover!
We need backup.
Copy that. We're on our way.
Harper.
What the fuck? What the fuck, Kirk?
- The Purge is over, cabrón.
- Dad?
Ever after.
Fuck!
The Purge is over, man.
They're coming.
Dylan!
You need to get up here.
Let's go! You need to get your family!
Harper! Come on!
Harper. Let's go.
Come on. Let's go, let's go.
Come on!
Come on. Jump in.
10-13, we have three
more incidences reported.
Return to precinct.
Copy that.
This is insane.
People not hear the sirens?
- A little busier than last year, huh?
- Yeah.
I shouldn't even be here.
I did nothing wrong.
...male in custody for transpo.
There's no such thing as crime anymore.
Let me fucking go!
Would you shut the fuck up?
Make me.
What's going on, Darius?
I don't know.
Adela...
Let me check the radio.
Maybe there's some news.
People are still purging
all across the country.
"Ever After Purge"
is popping up all over social media.
Continuous purging dubbed...
Where the hell are we gonna go?
We'll find somewhere safe.
First, we help Juan find his wife.
Then we find somewhere safe.
Stay inside your homes.
...take action to stop it.
Still, no one knows...
I know where she is.
Ever after.
This is the first real Purge.
It's never gonna stop.
Let me fucking go!
Shit.
It's blocked.
Hold on.
The station is just a few blocks away.
I hope she'll be there.
We can walk from here.
You go get your wife.
We'll stay here and protect the truck.
But you move fast. It's not safe here.
You don't need to wait for us.
Yes, we do.
I'm coming with you.
You don't have to do that.
No, you don't have to do that.
Yeah, I do.
They saved our lives.
We'll be right here. Now go.
Come on.
I'll take the back.
Good. Come on, guys.
This side.
That is a.30-06.
.30-30.
Yeah, yeah.
AR-15!
Listen to that rhythm.
That is a Glock.
Boom! Boom!
Listen to that bass!
Double-barrel shotgun.
AK-47.
Rat-tat-tat-tat-tat, tat-tat-tat.
Homegrown music
from the heartland right there.
That is American music, motherfucker.
Tat-tat-tat-tat.
Strike up the band!
The symphony sings!
Hold on! We're under attack.
Dispatch, we're outside the precinct!
- Request backup.
- Boom! Boom! Boom!
What?
Okay.
Honey...
I need you to take this.
Don't ask any questions, not right now.
I'm gonna get out of the car.
I need you to lock the door.
- Okay.
- I'll be right back.
Open up, bitch!
Baby!
No!
Yeah!
Cover me!
Go, go, go!
Forever Purge!
You're fucking dead, puta.
Get off me!
You're a pig!
Get the fuck off of me!
Stop fighting it.
Get the fuck off of me.
Come on. Come here.
Motherfucker!
Help me!
Fucking pig!
Kill him!
Think there's some inside.
Pry those doors open!
Let's see what's inside!
Forever Purge!
- Open it up!
- Get out of the way!
Ever after!
What was that?
- Juan?
- Adela.
Juan!
Juan! Juan.
Purge forever!
Over here!
Hold on.
The truck is coming! It's Dylan!
Get in the truck!
Get in!
- The truck! Come in!
- Come on, boss.
No, find safety now.
I need to get to my family.
- We'll help you.
- I'll move faster on my own. I'll be fine.
- Just go!
- Come on!
Here. You saved my life.
- Thank you, Darius.
- Okay.
Adela!
Okay, let's grab everything we can.
Peanut butter?
You found the jelly.
This could work.
As the violence
escalates across the country,
we are still trying to get
more information.
That's right, Ruth.
And we are still trying to figure out
if this Forever Purge
was coordinated or spontaneous.
Various hashtags, "Too much hate,"
"One day not enough"
are all over the Internet.
Fringe conspiracy groups
supporting the Forever Purge
are calling for a new America
to emerge from...
Adela...
...the ashes of a dead country.
...I'm scared to have my baby in this world.
Freedom to hate, freedom to purge,
freedom to die.
The NFFA has advised that anyone
displaying the Ever After flag
will be arrested immediately.
We're in this together.
Breaking news.
We've just gotten word that the NFFA has
declared martial law across the country.
The US military will be sent
into nearly every city
to stop the violence
and restore peace.
Citizens are being told to relin...
¿Bueno?
Juan, I can't understand
what you're saying.
Come on.
The cell things. The...
- Towers?
- Yeah, the towers!
The cell towers.
They are cutting them.
Hey. We just watched
that a lot of cities have gone dark.
Miami is gone.
Austin is under siege.
First responders are overwhelmed.
We're in a state of emergency.
It's all over the country.
The violence is spreading
and not stopping.
So there's nowhere safe to go.
There's no way to get help.
There's that symbol again.
This was planned.
- I got a map.
- I got ammo.
- What?
- Turn it up!
Give it to me.
All right. Well, we need to make a move.
They're gonna be coming here for gas.
Hey! We got news, guys.
What is it?
I repeat, your safety
cannot be guaranteed.
Take this. All right. Listen up.
Due to the waves of violence
currently sweeping the US,
Mexican President León García Soler
and Canadian Prime Minister Sophie Poueche
are opening their borders
for the next six hours.
Mexico and Canada
will take in anyone from America unarmed
and give them sanctuary
until order is reestablished in the US.
Both countries will then close down
their borders, again, in six hours.
Once again, after six hours,
both borders will be closing indefinitely.
There are reports of violence
from all corners...
We gotta go to Mexico.
Let's go.
We don't have a choice.
Authorities are urging everyone to get
to the closest border as soon as possible.
With only
three and a half hours remaining,
thousands of troops
have been gathered...
Entries to Mexico
and Canada are already overwhelmed.
Listeners, do not delay.
Get out while you can.
We will be ending our broadcast here.
Good luck, America. Stay safe.
You don't like me, do you, Dylan?
You don't like Mexicans.
What are you talking about, Juan?
Come on. Be honest.
Let's... how do you say this?
Slice the shit?
- Cut the shit?
- Cut the shit. Yeah.
- You wanna cut the shit?
- I wanna cut the shit with you.
All right, I'll cut the shit
with you, Juan.
I got no problem with Mexicans.
But I will say
I don't understand your culture
just like you don't understand mine.
God's honest truth,
I don't think white people
are any better or worse than anybody else.
But this I do believe:
We should all just stick with our own.
Just leave each other alone.
You might be right.
But we are together now.
The hell is that?
Okay, everybody, wake up.
Wake up! Be alert!
Oh, shit.
Jesus Christ. "Ever After"?
Holy shit.
Okay. They're coming up on us.
Holy shit! They're shooting at us!
Shit. They're slowing us down.
- Pull over!
- How many are there?
- There are two on this side.
- Stay down.
Just keep driving.
Stop this truck! Now!
- Stay down. Everyone stay down.
- Stop this truck!
- I'm just gonna run him over!
- No, baby. No, baby, wait.
- Wait! I got an idea.
- What?
Don't do it.
There's too many of them.
Juan,
get away from the window.
Stay away from the window.
- Ever After, motherfuckers!
- Pull that fucking truck over!
Ever After!
She's one of us!
Purge Ever After!
They're going away.
Way to go, Harper.
The border will close in three hours.
Attention.
This area is under martial law.
Weapons are not permitted.
This is the NFFA.
Clear the area.
I repeat, clear the area.
Surrender your weapons.
The hell is that?
Oh, my God.
Holy shit.
The crossing point is only one mile away.
There's no way through.
It's blocked. What should I do?
How are we supposed to get through?
We'll find a way, Cassidy.
Just keep driving.
We got less than three hours.
Please don't break down.
Come on, baby. We're nearly there.
Baby, be careful.
- It's blocked!
- What?
She's broke down.
Come on, we gotta get out.
Border's just a few blocks from here.
We can make it.
Everybody follow Juan.
Get ready. Stay low! Stay together!
I cover you in three, two, one.
- Come on! Come on!
- Let's go!
This is the NFFA.
Lay down your weapons or you will be shot.
- Purge this country!
- Clear the area! I repeat, clear the area!
Stay close, guys.
Dylan, cover the back!
Stay close!
T.T., cover the right.
Juan! Go, go!
Move, move!
I'm behind you.
Stay close.
Revolution!
Get to the wall. Get to the wall!
- Come on.
- There's the wall, guys!
- Dylan, get back!
- They have a.50 caliber.
Stay with me.
Oh, shit!
Let's use it as cover.
- Surrender your weapons.
- You guys go to the wall!
Get cover! Get cover! Move, move!
To the diner! The diner!
Guys, go ahead! Go ahead!
Come on. We're gonna go across.
Come on, guys. Let's go! Let's go!
Get your head down when you come in!
We can go. Stay back.
- Keep your head down. Keep your body down!
- Yeah. Yeah.
Go!
We need to keep up. Follow me, okay?
Stay down! Stay down.
What is that?
It's a tank.
We're gonna go across to the theater!
- Across to the theater.
- Okay.
When the truck passes, let's make a run.
We have to cross right now!
There's a fucking tank down there.
Come on! Come on!
Oh, my gosh!
Come on. Get in.
Get in! Get in!
Come on!
This is the NFFA.
No, no. Come on. Come on!
- Adela! Are you okay?
- Juan! Juan?
- It's blocked.
- Are you guys okay?
Adela, we'll go around!
Find another way out!
- Baby? Baby, open the door.
- I can't get it open!
- Baby?
The border will close
in two hours and 30 minutes.
Attention.
This area is under martial law.
We people of the mountains
believe at the castle...
...me to ask if you can wait
and go on after sunrise.
Well, I'm sorry,
but there's a carriage meeting me
at Borgo Pass at midnight.
- Borgo Pass?
- Yes.
Whose carriage?
Count Dracula's.
Count Dracula's?
Yes.
Castle Dracula?
Yes, that's where I'm going.
To the castle?
Yes.
Fuck.
A fucking bat. Fuck.
...believe at the castle
there are vampires!
Dracula and his wives.
They take the form of wolves...
Attention.
This area is under martial law.
Weapons are not permitted.
Shit.
It's another tank. We can't go around.
- Wait. Wait here.
- Okay.
All clear.
Let's get out of here.
All good?
Behind you!
T.T.
Clear.
Stay next to the wall, okay?
Return to your homes.
I repeat, return to your homes.
Stay next to me.
I need to get to my wife.
What are you looking for?
We Mexicans leave signs
all over the city to help each other.
Adela is following them.
If we want to find our wives,
we should do the same thing.
Go on.
- Fuck.
- Return to your homes.
- Hold this.
- Okay. Okay.
I repeat. Return to your homes.
- Adela.
- Yes?
How come you know how to fight like that?
I was part of the autodefensas.
What?
A group of women fighting the cartels.
We did damage to them.
They forced me and Juan off of our land.
This is how we got here,
to the States.
Here.
For you.
Okay.
- Army's passed. Come on.
- Okay.
Stay with me. Let's go.
The border will close
in two hours and 15 minutes.
Drop it! Move or I kill you.
Hand 'em over. Down.
Drop your weapons.
There's nothing you can do.
Drop 'em.
You too, amigo.
Come on now.
You're surrounded.
You will be shot.
That a boy.
It's all right, pretty thing.
Come on now. Do it.
Nice and easy.
Good.
You fucking deaf, son?
Good boy.
Look what we got here.
A couple of bad hombres.
Well, I'll be.
There's two of us and two of them.
That right there
is what's wrong with this country.
What do you want to do about 'em, Daddy?
Why don't we give
our fellow Americans here
an opportunity to redeem themselves?
Yeah, I like the sound of that.
Let me explain. You kill the brownies,
and the two of you can live
and stay here
in this great God-loving country.
Help us purify this nation
once and for all.
That's what the Ever After Purge
is all about.
Fuck you, redneck.
Yeah, fuck you, pig.
No, fuck you, bitch!
This country's gone haywire.
It don't know itself no more.
- You don't fucking know yourself.
- Mother, Mother, it's okay.
- Look in the fucking mirror!
- Mother! Hey, it's okay.
Maybe this will help y'all.
You happy now?
Mother.
Gladly.
Let the purification begin!
Fucking dying?
Oh, you fucking little beaner.
You fucking ain't worth shit.
Get the fuck back.
Don't even think about it, brownie.
This is the NFFA.
Lay down your weapons
- or you will be shot.
- Shoot the pigs!
Call for backup!
Shit!
Backup! Backup!
We need backup, goddamn it!
Backup's coming, baby.
Fuck!
Mother, no! No!
- Mother!
- Harper! Let's go!
Mother!
- Take cover!
- RPG!
Mother!
Oh, no. Mother.
This is Alpha Leader.
Request recon, all units.
It's here.
If our men are alive, they will be here.
Help me with the door.
Are you sure that this is safe?
- Stay over there.
- Are you sure that they're here?
They have to be.
Está bien.
Sit down.
I don't see them.
Where are they?
The border will close in two hours.
Adela. Adela!
Oh!
Cassie. Oh, my God.
You okay?
T.T.?
We have
breaking news now. This is just coming in.
We have been notified
that there has been an attack in El Paso
at a US Army military base.
As a result, the NFFA is pulling
all military troops out of El Paso.
Again, the military is retreating
out of El Paso
after suffering massive losses
in their battle against purgers,
including an attack on a US Army base.
And now I'm hearing
that in response to the army's withdrawal,
Mexico will now be closing their
El Paso border crossing point immediately.
Again, the El Paso border point
will no longer be open
to United States citizens
fleeing the Forever Purge.
Americans left behind
at the now-closed border wall
are being slaughtered by purgers.
It is a war.
El Paso has fallen to Ever After purgers
who are going door to door
hunting down anyone
who is not a part of their hate group.
The border is now closed.
This city's gonna get even worse.
Come.
Get out the back. Find Chiago. Move fast.
Tell him to meet us
in the corner of Amboy and Hylan.
Tell him if he doesn't do this,
many good people will die.
Including me. Okay?
Okay, let's go! Follow me.
I know a way to safety.
I need you to stand up
and walk with us, okay?
- Can you do that?
- I can do it. I got it.
The purification will not stop.
This city is now occupied
by the real patriots of America.
Our duty is to uphold
American beliefs and values
while keeping America pure
and free from refugees and terrorists.
We have taken back what is lawfully ours,
and we will now embark on purification
of our nation city by city.
Only full-blooded Americans
are welcome here.
All invaders will be purged.
We control El Paso and all of Texas.
The purification will not stop.
This city is now occupied
by the real patriots...
They're clear.
Just keep your voices down.
Listen. Don't move.
Head down.
Who's that?
It's okay. It's okay.
Is it here?
- Guys?
- It's them.
- Hey.
Chiago, take us to Mexico, please.
Get 'em on board. We're leaving.
Gracias, Chiago.
- Okay. Come on. Come on.
- Let's go.
Go, get in the truck.
Let's go. Let's go.
Alpha Leader, come in.
Alpha Leader, do you copy?
- We've found him.
- Where?
They're headed for the border
through the reservation.
Follow 'em. Don't lose 'em. I'll catch up.
How are you getting us across?
My tribe has lived right on the border
of the US and Mexico for centuries.
We were the only people
who could legally cross.
Then the wall split us.
But there are parts of the terrain
those pendejos can't build the wall on.
Too dangerous.
And we use it to make passage.
We'll take you through.
Some of you deserve another chance.
Are you in labor?
- Cassie, we gotta get you to Mexico.
- I know it's bad timing, baby.
You'll be okay.
There'll be help when we get across.
- Camps have been set up, okay?
- Thank you.
Dylan.
Look.
Damn it.
Juan?
Yeah?
Looks like we got trouble coming.
- Let's go. Come on.
- Go, go!
This is the crossing point.
We're on foot from here. Let's go.
- Let's move! Fast.
- Come on. Let's go!
Follow me. I will guide you.
Let's move it! Fast!
They're getting close. We need to move!
- Hey, honey?
- Yeah?
You go let these people
get you across the border, okay?
- Baby, where are you going?
- Yeah, you go ahead.
I love you. I'll be right behind you.
- You have to go with me. Don't leave.
- Go on. I have to stop them.
- Just focus on the baby, okay?
- Cassie, I'll protect you.
- Thank you, sister. You got her?
- Yeah.
We'll see you over there, all right?
Get her to the medics in Mexico.
Get 'em across the border safely!
That's it. On here.
Sit on it.
Put your knees underneath it.
I'm low on ammo. You guys got ammo?
We have a few guns,
but when the bullets run dry,
draw them in close, use blades.
Give me a magazine.
It's the last round of ammo.
Make it count.
We'll help you.
But it's not your fight.
We've been fighting this fight
for 500 years.
Take what you need.
This is our last stand.
On my ready!
Let 'em get close!
Wait for 'em!
Wait for it!
Are you okay?
Help her.
Now!
Go! Go, go, go!
Take cover! Now!
I'm out!
- Let's go!
- Come on.
I'm out!
- Yeah, I'm out too.
- I have one left.
Come on, motherfucker!
Fuck!
Hunt 'em down and kill 'em all.
Save that Mexican son of a bitch for me.
- Purge and purify. Ever After!
- Ever After!
They're coming.
Good.
We slow them down.
Give our people more time
to get across safely.
You guys stay in here.
We'll cover the back room.
We got this handled here.
Rest of you go stop 'em
from crossing the border.
- On it.
- Got it.
Let's go.
We're gaining on them. They can't be far.
Adela!
Adela. Adela.
- Adela.
- There he is. Grab him!
Adela!
Fucking whore!
Call your people
and tell 'em you need help.
Call out! Now!
Fucking English!
Translate! What are you saying?
- Juan!
- I said speak English!
Translate!
Speak fucking English!
I'll do it! Speak English.
I will cut your throat!
Speak E...
I got him.
Does this translate?
Pendejo.
You made it.
You just crossed into México.
She'll be there.
- Gracias.
Thank you. We owe you our lives.
Hospital?
Hospital? Médico.
- Sí.
- Here?
- Dylan!
- Baby!
- Oh, my...
- You made it!
Look who's here.
Oh, my God.
Baby?
- It's a girl.
- It's a girl?
You wanna hold your daughter?
- Can I?
- Please.
- Hi.
- Thank you.
- Congratulations.
Thank you.
Gracias, Juan.
Muchas gracias, Adela.
It's a girl. It's a girl.
...sheltering over
two million American refugees...
Who knows what will become
of these American Dreamers as they...
There is no end
in sight to the violence and uprising.
As of today,
the NFFA has sent the military
into every major city and county.
The NFFA is being
destroyed by their own creation
as the Purge can no longer be contained
to just one night a year.
In New York, ordinary
citizens are picking up weapons.
They're warring with Forever Purgers
in Times Square.
Reports are now
coming in that large groups of Americans
are banding together
and fighting back against these purgers,
against hate, fear and violence.
All of the United States
as we once knew it may be disappearing...
Who knows? What will
the new America look like when this all ends?
Someone needs to stop Clearway Law.
Public shouldn't leave reviews for lawyers.