Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org
(CAR HORNS HONKING)
(INDISTINCT CHATTERING)
(HONKING CONTINUES)
Listen, listen. No.
Greg, no! I need
those files this morning.
(CHUCKLES) Come on, man.
You can't be that lazy.
(BOY GIGGLES)
GREG: It's not my fault.
(GREG CONTINUES INDISTINCTLY)
(GASPS)
Made myself!
Yeah, made yourself.
That's great. Very impressive.
Made myself!
(SNIFFING)
Come on, man!
What's going on?
Is there a bomb threat or something?
Who are you?
Where's Wilmar?
ID, please.
You're kidding?
Here you go.
(MEN ARGUING IN SPANISH)
Why are they
sending that man home?
Open the trunk, please.
(ENGINE IDLING)
(MUSIC PLAYING ON CAR STEREO)
(SIGHS)
(VOLUME INCREASES)
(MAN SINGING IN SPANISH)
(INAUDIBLE)
(BEEPING)
VINCE: Okay.
Here's your company ID.
Make sure they spelled
everything correctly.
Mmm-hmm.
Company credit card.
Company telephone.
Keys to your company car.
It's a Honda, in Section H,
westside of the lot.
And, last but not least,
keys to your new apartment.
(SOFTLY)
I got you a corner.
You have the address,
correct?
Yeah. Yes.
Okay, and you saw
the doctor yesterday?
For the tracer,
you mean?
It's for your
own protection.
There's dozens of kidnappings
every year here in Colombia,
usually from
companies like ours.
But, with that sucker, they can locate
you anywhere, anytime, no problem.
Hmm.
Bogotá treating
you good so far?
Yeah.
(CHUCKLES)
Don't be scared, Dany.
Belko likes the transition
of its homespun employees
to go as smooth as possible.
So, if you have any
questions whatsoever,
just come to me
or Raziya here, okay?
Hi.
(MAN SPEAKING DUTCH)
(SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY)
(SPEAKING DUTCH)
(SPEAKS SPANISH)
MAN: In English? Sure.
Belko is
a non-profit organization
that facilitates American
companies in South America
in the hiring of
American workers.
(KEYBOARD CLACKING)
(COMPUTER CHIMES)
(CHUCKLES)
What the fuck is that?
It's a little corn cob dude.
Mike, it looks like
someone's eaten off of it.
It's a gift for you.
No.
Here.
Let's put him right here.
Ew! That's disgusting.
I don't want it.
It's good luck.
He wards off werewolves.
Maybe it'll work on Wendell.
(MUFFLED) Asshole.
(SOFTLY) My God!
The man just
does not get it.
Hey, what?
Maybe we should
slow things down.
Mike, I'm barely divorced.
Got married too young.
No, I got married too stupid.
And I'm not any smarter.
Oh, that's great
for me then!
Mr. Norris. (CLEARS THROAT)
Hey, Barry.
Mike.
Leandra, will you set up
that Caracas call for 2:00?
I'll put it through.
(BOTH LAUGH)
(SIGHS)
PowerPoint files from these
documents in two hours, please.
All right?
(MUSIC PLAYING FAINTLY)
What?
Uh, yes.
Okay. Two hours.
I'm Roberto.
I'm Dany.
Leota, will you stop being a
bitch and introduce yourself?
You're an ass, Roberto.
I've already introduced myself.
Yeah.
And we're going
to be friends
and we're going to ostracize you.
(LIPS SMACKS)
(LEOTA CHUCKLES) She doesn't
even know to spell "ostracize."
(LEOTA CHUCKLES)
LEOTA: Oh!
Cute, no?
I don't know.
He's a little too normal for me.
(SCOFFS) Honey, normal
people do not work at Belko.
Oh, Keith.
One's loose.
Oh, shit. Okay,
all right, here I come. (LAUGHING)
Tickles.
Oh, yeah.
Obviously, that's John.
Oh, although,
he prefers to be called Jake.
He thinks it makes
him sound tough.
(LAUGHS) Well, he looks
very, very tough.
He thinks
you're very pretty.
Honey, believe me.
One more bad date, and I am there.
Oh, guard your heart.
He's a total "love 'em and leave 'em"
kind of guy.
Just 'cause he has
a very short lifespan.
He doesn't have commitment issues.
(LAUGHING)
Hi, Mike.
Hey, how are you?
Terry, where is everybody?
I don't know, mate. They sent all
the locals home at the gate.
Mmm, Mike. Next time, you got to
come with us to the rain forest.
Check it out.
The bats let you come right up and
stroke 'em. The kids were in heaven.
Wow.
(CHUCKLES)
Next time, buddy, yeah?
Yeah, totally.
Looks like fun.
(PHONE RINGING)
Security.
Hey, Evan,
it's, uh, Mike Milch up in systems.
Yes, sir.
Hey, uh, who sent all
the Colombian nationals home?
Central. They sent me
an email this morning
saying there was some kind of
security concerns.
I figure somebody made
some threats somewhere
and got 'em
all worked up.
Who are those new guards?
I don't know. They ain't friendly, though.
They got some big-ass dogs.
Yeah.
You have any idea
why they would be
heading into that
old hangar next door?
I don't know, man.
I'll check it out.
(MICROPHONE FEEDBACK WHINES)
THE VOICE ON PA:
All employees,
no matter what you're doing,
please stop and lend me
your full attention.
Hey, it's Jesus!
Shh!
There are currently 80 of you
in the building.
MIKE: What is that?
Intercom?
Do we have an intercom?
THE VOICE: In eight hours,
most of you will be dead.
Your chance of survival increases
by following my orders,
and excelling at the tasks
I place before you.
Your first task
is simply this.
Murder any two of your fellow
employees within the next half hour.
(LAUGHING)
How they are killed, or how
they are chosen to be killed,
is of no consequence.
But if there are
not two dead bodies
in the building
within 30 minutes,
you will face repercussions.
What the...
Not a clue.
Hey, all the lines
are dead.
AGNES: What did that man say?
(SHOUTS) He wanted us
to kill each other?
Panicking is not gonna
help anybody, Agnes.
Calm down, it's okay.
Anything?
No. Nothing.
Calmly, we need to
evacuate the floor.
Mikey, come on.
It's a joke, man.
Yeah, probably, yeah.
But still.
Okay.
Break time.
Hey, let's not take
the elevator, okay?
Let's use the stairs.
Why?
It's less risky.
We're all gonna die.
(CHUCKLING)
Hey,
where you going?
(BEEPS)
(GASPING)
WOMAN: What was that?
What's that noise?
Just go.
Head on down, okay?
Mike, come on.
I'll be right there.
Hey, are you
trying the police?
Yeah. Reception's
usually fine here.
What in bloody hell?
(GRUNTING)
VINCE: Wendell!
Wendell? Wendell,
you're gonna break your foot.
(ALL CLAMORING)
No! How is this connected to the
security check this morning?
I don't know, sir!
God damn it!
(ELEVATOR BELL DINGS)
I just validate, okay?
Hey, Bud.
What do you think, Mikey?
What's this all about?
I don't know. You think you
got a way to get through it?
Blowtorch could do the job,
but I don't know how thick it is.
It could take a while.
What if we try cutting through
one of the walls first?
Wouldn't it be easier to
try to get through cement
than get through whatever that is?
No, no, no.
This metal surrounds
the entire building.
So the whole building's covered?
Yeah.
It's worth a shot, though, right?
The blowtorch?
It's worth a try.
I'll make a call.
Hey, where you guys going?
Roof. See if we can get
someone's attention.
Got anything?
Still nothing.
Thought we'd get a shot here
in the lobby, but...
Can you guys
stick around for me?
Oh, that's great. Like I didn't
already feel trapped in this job.
Hey, listen up,
everybody, okay?
I'm Barry Norris, the COO here,
for people who don't know.
Listen,
I'm aware that
this is a very...
Hell, to say the least,
a very strange situation here.
But I don't believe
there's any cause for panic.
All right? We're still trying to figure
out exactly what the situation is,
but I'm certain there's
a rational explanation.
This is
a government building.
We think maybe somebody
put precautions in place
in case of
a military event.
Obviously these walls.
Now, someone has clearly
discovered this feature,
and they're having
a little fun at our expense.
Okay?
Whoever's doing this, the object
is to get all of you upset.
So let's not play
into that, okay?
Let's just remain calm,
chill out,
and take a few minutes
to figure out
exactly what's happening,
okay?
So, thank you.
I'm gonna go work on that.
And I'll circle back
to you as soon as I can.
Thanks, everybody.
So, someone's just
taking the piss. Right?
(COUGHS)
(SNIFFS)
Hey, what's up?
Are you smoking pot?
What?
We just had our lives threatened
and you come up to hang out?
That dude on the speakers?
Please.
That shit's hilarious.
You guys are insane
for smoking pot at Belko.
They test here.
They'll fire you, you know.
It's from Panama, man.
It's not that strong.
(LAUGHS)
It isn't.
I know.
It ain't melting
at all, Bud.
No, no, look.
It ain't even hot.
What?
Feel it. Feel it.
I've never seen
anything like that.
Do you know what
kind of metal this is?
BUD: Mmm.
I don't really know.
MIKE: Barry.
Sorry, this is rude.
Damn hot with
all these bodies.
Yeah. Um, I think that they
turned the air conditioning off.
Hey, Wendell.
Yo!
Can I get one of those?
100%.
Hey, listen.
It's great that you
calmed everybody down,
but, um, I don't
think this is a prank.
No?
No, I mean,
these walls,
they seem designed to keep
people in just as much as out.
There's no cell reception.
That's not an easy thing to accomplish.
(SOFTLY) Those new
guards this morning?
I saw one of them
heading over
to that old hangar
that's next door.
So my guess is that is
where they're set up.
So what are you saying?
We should pick out
a couple folks to kill?
No, no.
Not at all.
That was a joke, Mike.
Yeah. (CHUCKLES)
I mean, I know.
Um, but I'm not sure how much
people are gonna be joking
if something else
happens.
Something like what?
Something.
Listen, Mike.
In a situation like this,
it's normal for a handful of
folks to panic and overreact.
Would you agree with that?
Sure.
So why don't you consider that you
might be one of those people?
All right?
I brought some bottled water
from the cafeteria.
Why don't you guys
grab yourselves some?
Not getting jack up here, either.
God damn it.
Keith!
I see one!
Who?
Right there! Look!
In the window.
The security guard from this morning.
Hey! Hey!
KEITH: Hello!
LEOTA: Help us!
We're stuck!
We're trapped!
ROBERTO: Help us, please!
KEITH: Come on, man!
(ALL SHOUTING)
Hey!
What the fuck?
You guys,
quit getting so worked up.
I'm sorry.
What, man?
Bro, did you even happen
to read what you signed
when you started
working for this place?
We gave these fuckers
the right to do
practically whatever the fuck
they wanted to do to us.
Oh, kill us?
No, dude.
It's a psychological
fucking test, man.
They wanna see how we'll
react to this bullshit.
Look at me.
Look how fucking chill I am.
They lose, man.
I fucking win.
So just relax
and take the day off, man.
Consider it a present from
corporate fucking America.
(GUNSHOT)
(ALL SCREAMING)
Oh, my God!
What the fuck?
(INDISTINCT CHATTERING)
(GUNSHOT)
Somebody's shooting!
(ALL SCREAMING)
Get down.
(GUNSHOT)
Jesus!
Shit!
(SCREAMING)
(GUNSHOT)
(ELEVATOR BELL DINGS)
No, Mr. Norris.
Be careful!
No.
It's okay.
What the hell?
That's not a bullet wound.
What are you doing?
What the...
The bone...
Jesus.
His head exploded
from the inside.
What?
The tags.
(STUTTERS) When we start working
here, they put tracers.
They implanted them
in the back of our heads.
For insurance.
What if they're rigged to explode?
LEANDRA: What?
That's why the locals were sent home.
They don't have them.
LEANDRA: Wait, Mike!
Lonny...
(BREATH TREMBLING)
Hey, stop.
Don't cry. Okay?
Take this.
Watch my back, yeah?
Mmm-hmm.
Give me a duke.
Okay. Come on, let's go.
Mike.
Mike, where are you going?
Mike!
What are you doing, Mike?
What's happening?
Is it okay? (CLATTERING)
Please. I can help you
look for something.
PEGGY: What's happening?
What are you doing?
LEANDRA: Mike.
What's happening?
What's going on?
Did they catch him?
I don't know.
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
Fuck.
Mike.
(KNOCKING ON DOOR)
Mike, open the door!
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
Mike!
(GROANS)
THE VOICE ON PA:
Michael Milch,
set down
the knife immediately,
or we will
detonate the explosive.
Mike! Mike, please!
Mr. Milch,
we will give you 10 seconds
to cease and desist.
(GROANS)
LEANDRA: Open the door, Mike!
Ten.
Nine.
Eight.
Mike, open the door!
Seven.
Six.
(GRUNTING)
Five. Four.
Mike!
(DOORKNOB RATTLES)
Three. Two.
(GRUNTS)
(PANTING)
Fuck.
Oh, my God, Mike! What in
God's name is wrong with you?
(MIKE GROANS)
MIKE: Shit!
PEGGY: It's okay, honey.
Okay, okay, okay.
Hey.
What's the ice for?
You gonna build
a snowman or what?
It dulls the pain as
he gets stitched up.
WENDELL: Oh...
What is that?
Is that your boyfriend?
This Mike guy?
Because, obviously, Leandra,
your parents never had a conversation
with you about mixed messages.
What?
Leandra, admit it.
Don't you understand?
I've clocked every single one
of the looks that you give me.
Looks?
Yeah, the flirtatious emails,
I come.
Fuck off!
You can do it, Mike.
The fucking world
is falling apart.
Seriously, Mike,
what were you thinking?
Here.
Are you okay?
Yeah.
(GRUNTING)
(PANTING)
There's three cameras
in the bathroom alone.
They've been watching
every bloody thing that we do.
(BREATHES HEAVILY)
(SIGHS)
BARRY: Hey, Evan.
Here, man, have some water.
Me and Lawrence,
we came over here together, man.
He never did nothing to nobody.
Just a dumbass kid, man.
Every time he got pussy,
he thought he was in love.
(CHUCKLES)
I'm sorry about your friend.
Hey, listen.
You have the key to
that armory, right?
Where the guards
keep their weapons?
Anybody else have
keys besides you?
No. I mean,
maybe them ones outside.
Mmm.
I think I should
hold on to those keys.
You think you should what?
I think I should hold on to them.
Make sure they're safe.
Come on, you know
I can't do that, sir.
I'm your boss, Evan.
Okay, then I quit.
All right. I think it's best
I hold on to these keys
until somebody lets me out
of that fucking door.
Don't worry, I ain't gonna
give them to nobody.
Thanks for the water.
MARTY: Did you get it all off?
Is it all off of me?
Hold on, doll.
(DOOR OPENS)
(DOOR CLOSES)
They're trying to freak us out by
shutting down the air-co, man.
That's their plan,
right, Bud?
Right, Bud?
Hmm?
Do you think it is, Bud?
Do you think
that's their plan?
I don't know, Lonny.
(BUD GRUNTS)
She's down, all right.
LONNY: How can you tell?
BUD: I can hear it, man.
The pilot's off. Everything.
Did they do it?
I don't know if
they did it or not.
(SWITCH CLICKING)
But we're gonna fix it.
They're trying
to break us down
so that we start
killing each other, Bud.
You just need to relax,
all right? Hmm?
(FEEDBACK WHINES)
THE VOICE: I hope by now
we've demonstrated
that we aren't
blindly bluffing.
This game's a real one.
Each of you are
deep inside it.
You can choose to follow
our directives, or not.
Either way, you'll be giving us
the results we're looking for.
Fuck you, man!
You are mostly free
to do as you please.
However, you must not
dismantle any more cameras.
And you must not remove
the tag from your body.
Next time we will not provide a
countdown as we did Mr. Milch.
If you break either of these rules,
your life will abruptly end.
There are currently 76 of you
left in the building.
The time is now 12:47 pm.
(ALL TALKING INDISTINCTLY)
Listen!
By 2:47 pm, in two hours,
we want 30 of you dead
through whatever
means necessary.
If 30 of you are not dead,
we will end 60 of your lives
through our own methods.
Christ!
Begin.
Fuck you! Fuck you!
Calm down!
(ALL CLAMORING)
Everybody calm down!
Slow down, everybody.
(SOBBING)
Hey, hey,
Lonny, it's gonna be okay...
Get back off me!
Whoa!
Don't look at me
like that, man.
WENDELL: Move.
Wendell, what are you...
Wendell, stop.
(CLATTERS)
TERRY: Guys, guys, please.
(INDISTINCT TALKING)
What are you guys doing?
Why are you getting those?
Listen, asshole!
(INDISTINCT SHOUTING)
(WHIMPERING)
Where are you going?
I'm just going to find
a quiet place to hide.
Come on!
(ALARM RINGING)
Ah!
Jesus!
What did you do that for?
This shit is hooked up
to the fire department, Chet.
They'll hear it
and come get us.
Everybody calm down!
The last thing we need
to do is lose our cool.
(INDISTINCT SHOUTING)
Knock it off!
Come on!
(ALARM CONTINUES RINGING)
Dickhead!
BARRY: Now come on out here
and let's discuss this.
Raven, what are you doing?
I'm protecting myself,
Michael.
(STAMMERS) Guys, come on!
Cut it out, please!
Evan, does the fire
alarm alert the station
or is it
a self-enclosed system?
It's just us.
Can you turn it off?
What is that?
Lonny, calm down, man!
It's just a fire alarm.
No, it's not. They're trying
to make us kill each other.
Easy, cowboy.
Chill out, man!
Hey, come here.
Get back!
(GROANS)
Whoa!
Wait a second.
What just happened?
Hold on.
Uh... Wait, wait.
(SOFTLY)
Something is happening.
(SOBS) I'm so sorry, Bud!
(ALARM STOPS RINGING)
(CLANGING)
(LONNY GRUNTS)
I didn't see anything.
Okay?
Stop!
I'm just gonna go, okay?
Bud, he fell down
and he hit his head.
It's okay. I should go.
He tried to grab me. Shh!
Wait, wait!
(SHUSHING)
(WHIMPERING)
(SCREAMS)
(SOBS)
BARRY: God damn it!
Now, please, stop putting
words in my mouth.
I'm sorry,
but that sounds to me
like you're saying you wanna
kill innocent people.
No, I am not
saying that at all.
I'm saying that we need
to discuss all our options.
MIKE: We understand.
But we are not going to entertain
the option of killing people.
We? What? Do you got a mouse
in your pocket there, Milch?
Mr. Norris has a point.
TERRY: Absolutely he does.
But we have to think about what
is best for the whole group.
All right, look. I know no one
wants to actually think about
sacrificing 30 lives.
But if it means saving the lives...
No, uh-uh, fuck that.
(ALL ARGUING)
Consider it as
a fucking option.
It does not matter
what the circumstances are.
We do not have the right
to take innocent human lives.
(ALL AGREEING)
And besides that,
there are practical reasons.
Like what?
You can't really
think that they're gonna
let anybody live
to tell about this.
This is not going to stop
after we kill 30 people.
Maybe not,
but it would buy us time
to figure out
another solution.
I can't even believe you're
considering this, Barry.
Vince, we cannot pretend
things aren't what they are.
(STAMMERS)
I might have an idea.
We can...
We can go up to the roof
and put banners up there
letting every car that comes
by know that we're in here.
That way, nobody gets hurt.
We should try that.
Leandra,
this isn't a pep rally.
We are in
the middle of nowhere,
the road traffic
is next to nothing.
The driveway's,
like, half a mile long.
People need to see
these banners.
Then they have
to call the cops,
who have to then get here,
all in less than two hours.
Do you have a better idea?
Yeah, jerking off into a cup
is a better goddamn idea.
Oh, there's something
I can do.
75% of us will die
if it doesn't work.
Okay, no disrespect
intended, Barry,
but some would fare
better than others
if this was turned
into a cage match.
What the hell does that mean?
That means not all of us are
Special Forces trained to kill.
(ALL MURMUR IN AGREEMENT)
Are you questioning my integrity?
I've read both your files.
MIKE: Hey, hey! Come on!
Nobody is
questioning anything.
But we need to work together to
get the hell out of here, right?
I suggest we try the banners, okay?
See if it works.
In the meantime,
if anybody else comes up with anything
better, then we'll go for that.
And how long will that take?
We can do it in 30 minutes.
It's worth trying, Norris.
Come on, let's go.
We won't know unless we try.
(ALL TALKING INDISTINCTLY)
BARRY: Can we sit in
and talk about this?
People!
We got to live in reality.
We're just wasting time.
We don't have time.
There was no...
I can't fucking...
God damn it!
(GLASS SHATTERS)
Terry.
What?
You have kids, right?
Yes.
What's your conscience
telling you here?
What?
Who are you beholden to
first and foremost?
I mean, these people,
they're our friends, right?
Right.
But if you're like me...
My wife and kids need me.
I don't know what
they'll do without me.
Yeah.
We have to be bold here.
This isn't
the time for timidity.
You agree?
Yes.
(WATER RUNNING)
Hey!
It's in
the fucking water, man.
What is?
Some sort of
fucking psychotropic
fucking chemical
or something, man!
It's making us
all on fucking edge.
We're on edge because they just
killed four people, Marty!
Dude! Dude!
I'm protecting us,
motherfucker.
That's gonna get moldy.
Mike.
Mike!
God, Mike, enough!
Enough what?
Listen.
Don't be fucking mad at me
just because I thought that
we should have an open mind.
Oh, an open mind?
An open mind about killing people?
I did not want to kill people,
(INDISTINCT CHATTER ON RADIO)
but we need to discuss things.
It is not a discussion.
It is needling each other into
these bullshit rationalizations.
And the circumstances
do not alter
what is right
and what is wrong.
Evan, would you give me
a hand with this, please?
(SIGHS)
Thanks.
Evan?
Where's that blowtorch
that was here?
It's not there anymore.
(EVAN SIGHS)
(BLOWTORCH HISSING)
Hey.
Hey!
Wendell!
Hold up. Milch?
What are you doing?
This is where security
keeps the weapons.
MIKE: Yeah, I know.
We're getting them out of here.
Why?
Because it's important
we keep them safe.
All right?
We don't want someone
coming in here
and just breaking in.
Evan here won't
give us the keys.
So.
Go ahead, Wendell.
(BLOWTORCH HISSING)
I don't think that's wise.
I think the weapons are safe to
stay exactly where they are.
Quite honestly, Mike, I don't
give a fuck what you think.
That was foolish.
Look, man, he's right.
Y'all can't do this. You don't
need no more weapons in here.
I'm gonna shove this
down your goddamn...
(ALL SHOUTING INDISTINCTLY)
Whoa!
Hey, chill, man. Lower your gun.
Lower that gun, man. Come on.
Who the hell do
you think you are?
Not much, man, but don't try me,
I'm on fucking edge!
Listen, son, we just
wanna make sure
these weapons are safe,
all right?
Shut the fuck up! I swear to God,
I'm two seconds away
from blowing a hole in your ugly,
motherfucking face!
Hey, look at me, man.
Look at me! (BREATHING SHAKILY)
You had a hard day, right?
You saw your friend
get killed.
Come on, man.
I know, I know.
But you don't wanna do this, okay?
You don't wanna do this.
LEANDRA: Put it down.
It's gonna be okay, man.
Just let me
handle it, okay?
It's okay.
It's okay, it's okay.
(GAS HISSING)
Let's go.
(GUNSHOTS)
Well, there.
Jesus, Mike!
Let's go.
Yeah.
You know what, Mike?
(ELEVATOR BELL DINGS)
That was
a stupid fucking move.
We're gonna need help.
(MUZAK PLAYING)
That was hardcore, bro.
(CHUCKLES) Oh, shit!
They know who they fucking with now!
Evan, you wanna just blow
him and get it over with?
Damn.
What?
PEGGY: Yeah, and then we attach
with those and stuff like that.
Mike, where have you been?
Uh, we ran into some problems.
Hey, everybody.
Listen up, okay?
You need to look
out for Norris,
Terry and Wendell Dukes,
all right?
Um, they're working
against us here, okay?
Yeah, now especially.
Hey, we need that rope.
We're gonna be done here in 20 seconds.
It's not really up to the
standards I'd like but...
It's beautiful, it's not a contest.
Come on. Here we go.
Really? I'm trying to
make these things pop.
You want us to
be saved, right?
KEITH: You can put
the finishing touches
when they're hanging
on the side of the building.
The fuck are you doing,
Mike? Hmm?
Are you trying to get killed?
What? (SCOFFS)
What?
Mike, you don't antagonize
those types of people.
Seriously, I'm just starting
to think you're stupid.
Hey, hey, hey.
Fuck you!
What? For saying,
"Hey, hey, hey"?
No, because you need
to be realistic, Mike.
Everyone here is
afraid for their lives.
And at that point, whatever
you think is right or wrong
goes out the fucking window.
It's human nature.
At the end of the day,
people are out for themselves.
You're driving me crazy.
Let's just go take
care of this, okay?
Okay.
Hey, Mike.
We're ready now.
And, uh, obviously, we all just
heard your whole conversation.
Just so you know.
You know it's not a separate room,
it's just a cubicle.
Maybe we'll
just get going.
Yeah, (CLEARS THROAT)
let's go.
For what it's worth, I thought
he was totally out of line
saying "hey" like that.
(INDISTINCT CHATTERING)
(MAN SOBBING)
(MARTY SPEAKS INDISTINCTLY)
(WOMEN SCREAMING)
Did you drink any?
We're doing you a favor.
Move, assholes!
(SOBBING)
(DOOR OPENS)
Shit!
We can hang them from here.
Roll them out.
Tie the corners in knots.
Tie the ropes to the corners.
LEANDRA: Got it.
Yeah?
Oh, fuck.
Keith, don't stop.
Keep going, come on!
No, Keith, don't!
Come on! Help me!
Mike, stop! Mike!
MIKE: Come on! We almost got it!
(KEITH GRUNTS)
KEITH: Oh, shit!
Oh, fuck!
Watch it!
Look out!
Jesus Christ!
Misspelled "hangar."
Mike, what are you doing?
We have to try again.
What and get shot?
(FEEDBACK WHINES)
THE VOICE ON PA:
Please cease and desist
hanging the notices
off the side of the building.
If another attempt is made,
the explosive in the offender's
head will be detonated.
Fuck!
VINCE: Mike, look out!
Mike, stop!
Mike, stop it!
(ALL SHOUTING)
Get down.
Mike, what the hell?
MIKE: No, we can do it!
I can. Come on!
LEANDRA: Stop!
Can you hear me? Stop it!
Do you hear me?
What is wrong with you?
Do you hear me? Come on.
Yeah.
(ROBERTO COUGHS)
Mike, are you okay?
You can't save everyone,
Mike.
So what are you saying? Hmm?
That we just do what they say?
I don't know.
Who the fuck
are these people?
(MIKE SIGHS)
I don't know, Leandra.
I've been thinking.
(SOFTLY) This job...
What is it?
(IN NORMAL VOICE)
I mean, this location.
Out in the middle of nowhere.
That never made any sense.
This building, it's like it was
designed for just this purpose.
They've had these tags in us
for over a year.
Mike, you're saying that the
government's the one that's doing this?
That's who we work for.
No.
Think about it. They've never
seemed to give a shit
about the work
that we actually do.
For the past year,
they've just had us
running in circles like hamsters
on a fucking treadmill.
There's no way, Mike.
There's no way.
(SOFTLY)
What if the only reason
that we've been here
all along, because of this?
I don't know, some kind of
human experiment.
Mike, listen to me. Do you hear me?
That's impossible, okay?
Impossible.
(SCOFFS)
Look at me.
We're gonna be okay.
Now we should go.
Let's go.
Hey.
Just was looking out,
in case them ones come back.
Yeah.
My mother never wanted me to
move to Bogotá for this job.
Back of my head
will be blown off
and the first thing
she'll say is, "I told you."
Mike!
(EVAN EXCLAIMS)
You stay!
Norris,
what are you doing?
Leandra,
you listen to me, all right?
This guy is
putting us all in danger.
He's gonna get
a lot of people killed.
Terry.
Terry, come on,
he's your friend.
(STAMMERS) Yes, I know.
That's part of the reason why.
He's not being rational,
is he?
Keys.
You want the fucking keys?
(SCREAMS)
What the fuck are you doing?
He threw the keys!
What, stabbing him is going to make
them fly up the fucking stairs?
You shut up.
He had to get it anyway.
(GROANING)
What do I do?
She can't stay here.
Fuck!
Get the fuck off of me,
you pin-eyed pervert!
Don't you call me a pervert!
I'm not a pervert.
BARRY: Chill out, Wendell.
Come on.
I said, come on!
(WHIMPERING)
(GROANING)
(INAUDIBLE)
(MUFFLED) I'm sorry, Evan.
(SIGHS)
Give them one mag a piece.
Why do you keep
the rest?
Because I'm the one
that's gonna do this.
Do what?
Isn't that
what we decided?
Do what?
There's too many guns.
It doesn't make sense.
He put them here.
Who put them here?
Our new god.
Okay, like we discussed.
Everybody down
in the lobby.
And then what?
VINCE: Calm down, calm down.
Look, come on, use your brains...
Somebody grab the keys.
(ALL TALKING INDISTINCTLY)
Everybody, stay where you are!
Don't fucking move!
(ALL SCREAM)
What the fuck!
MAN: Come on, let's move!
Come on, let's go!
Fucking move, man.
Let's go!
Guys, come on!
Come on, man.
Fucking move!
(SIGHS)
(GRUNTS SOFTLY)
(GROANS)
(DOOR OPENS)
WENDELL: I'm not babysitting here.
Don't worry about it.
You'll find out
when we get there.
Just get your ass
down the stairs.
(OPERATIC SONG PLAYING)
(INAUDIBLE)
Can I have your attention,
please?
I'm gonna need
everyone with children
under the age of 18
to step forward.
Why?
Barry, you can't do that!
(WOMEN SCREAMING)
BARRY:
Quickly, quickly, quickly.
Excuse me, sir.
Sir, sir.
I send money home
to my, uh, parents
every month for
my little brother.
Is your little brother made out
of your sperm, cocksucker?
No.
Then shut the fuck up!
Get back!
Everybody, back!
(WOMEN SCREAM)
Everybody, step back.
It's gonna help us a lot.
We don't have a lot of time.
So this will make this easier.
Just step back.
Good. Thank you.
If this group would please stand
by that wall, the west wall.
Okay, good. Come on.
Up against the wall.
All right.
Now I'm gonna need everybody
over the age of 60
to please step forward.
WENDELL: You.
Come on, let's go.
Perhaps you should consider
this differently, yeah?
We could do a lottery.
People just can write their
names on a scrap of paper...
Don't undermine me again.
Are we clear?
Clear.
WENDELL: How about you?
Are you over 60?
Let's go, come on!
Hey, you're only
doing this
because of the fucking
chemicals in your system.
Everybody, listen up!
Now I realize that
this is very difficult.
But it's...
This is the right thing.
(PEOPLE TALKING INDISTINCTLY)
This is the only
choice we have.
All right?
In less than 20 minutes,
they are going to kill
60 of the people in this room.
So we need order.
Now the next person
who speaks up,
who says a single word,
we are unfortunately gonna
put a bullet in your head.
Now if this group will kindly
go stand against the east wall.
Go.
Go, go, go.
Seven people.
Fuck!
Okay.
Him.
Let's go.
Her.
No.
Go.
(SHUSHING)
Her.
Go.
Don't touch me!
BARRY: Him.
WENDELL: You, let's go.
(WHIMPERS)
No, I'm not going!
I'm not going!
(SHOUTING INDISTINCTLY)
Let him go.
(ALL SCREAMING)
(SCREAMING IN THE DISTANCE)
(INDISTINCT SHOUTING)
Her.
Please don't kill us.
Him.
(WOMEN SOBBING)
Everyone, shut the fuck up!
Turn on some
music or something.
(MAN SPEAKING
SPANISH ON RADIO)
(SPANISH SONG
PLAYING ON RADIO)
Barry?
What are we doing?
WOMAN: You motherfucker!
Who the fuck are you to decide
who lives and dies?
You will rot in hell for...
(SCREAMING)
That's five.
Six.
Turn up the fucking music!
Please. Please.
(VOLUME INCREASES)
(SOBS)
Seven.
(GUNSHOT)
(MAN SCREAMS)
(WHISPERS) Hey, Terry.
Terry, give me the gun.
(GUNSHOTS CONTINUE)
Terry, it's not too late, man.
I forgive you, okay?
Just give me that gun.
Mike Milch is trying to get
me to give him my gun, Barry.
I didn't do it.
Bully for you.
Shoot him.
No, no, Terry!
Listen, to me.
Look at me, Terry.
No, no, no, Terry, don't!
(YELLS)
MIKE: Go, go, go!
(ALL SCREAMING)
(ELEVATOR BELL DINGS)
(GUNSHOTS CONTINUE)
Peggy!
Look out. Watch out. Look out.
You okay?
Come on, let's go.
(PEOPLE SCREAMING)
(ELEVATOR BELL DINGS)
(PANTING) Dany!
Get in, get in.
MAN: Come on, come on!
Let's go. Come on, come on.
(ROBERTO GRUNTS)
Let's go.
(WOMAN SCREAMS)
(YELLING)
(GRUNTING)
(CHOKES)
(YELLS)
(ALL GRUNTING)
Stop!
I count four more dead.
Don't count, just go.
Get as many as you can.
Let's go, let's go.
Come on.
(CLATTERING)
Whoever's there,
show yourself.
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(FEEDBACK WHINES)
THE VOICE: So far,
you've killed 29 people.
That's one short.
You have two minutes
remaining.
If you don't kill one more
person in the next 120 seconds,
30 more of you will die.
Hello?
(LEANDRA YELLS)
(GROANS)
(SCREAMS)
No! Leandra, please, no!
I was just doing what
Norris told me to do.
Please, I swear!
I'm no danger to you, please.
(SOBS) I'm sorry, please.
I beg you.
Please.
(CLATTERS)
I'm not gonna hurt you.
(SOBBING)
I'm sorry.
(FEEDBACK WHINES)
THE VOICE:
You've come one body short.
We're sorry to inform you
that 31 employees
will now be eliminated.
No!
(SCREAMS)
(ALL SCREAM)
(YELLING)
(BEEPS)
It's all in my mind.
Dude, get the fuck down.
It's all in...
(SOBS) It's all in my mind.
(SCREAMING)
(EXPLOSIONS CONTINUE)
(GASPS)
(EXPLOSIONS STOP)
It stopped!
(BREATH TREMBLING)
They stopped!
(SCREAMS)
(SNIFFS)
(URINATES)
(ELECTRICITY CRACKLING)
(SHIVERING)
(ROBERTO BREATH TREMBLING)
(FEEDBACK WHINES)
THE VOICE: The last stage
of the game is quite simple.
In one hour,
whoever has killed the most
people will be allowed to live.
The current tally is as follows.
(COCKS GUN)
Barry Norris, 11 kills.
Wendell Dukes, seven kills.
Vincent Agostino,
one kill.
Daniele Wilkins, one kill.
Begin.
Hmm.
(SCREAMS)
MAN: No! Don't!
(WOMAN SCREAMING)
Wait! (SOBS)
Vince, it's me.
(SOBS) I'm sorry, Raziya.
(MAN GASPS)
No, no, don't shoot.
Mr. Norris.
Please.
Don't hurt me.
(SOBS)
I know what you want.
Look, Mr. Norris.
You can have me
if you want.
Stop.
Come here.
Can't waste a bullet.
(BARRY GRUNTS)
(SCREAMING)
(DANY GASPS)
(ELEVATOR WHIRRING)
We have to get down.
No!
We don't know
who it is.
Oh, my God!
He works
on the top floor.
(DANY SCREAMS)
(ROBERTO SCREAMING)
(ELEVATOR POWERS DOWN)
Fuck me!
(MUSIC PLAYING ON RADIO)
MARTY: Oh.
Don't get any closer, man.
I'll chop your
fucking head off!
I have a fucking gun!
Don't tell me I don't know
how to use an axe, man.
What are you doing?
I'm getting the bombs
out of their heads. See?
I'm gonna put them
on the wall, man.
And then I'll use them to blow
a fucking hole in the door.
Then we'll get out of here, man.
That ain't going
to work, Marty.
Why you saying that, man?
Fucking negative
thinking, man!
It's a good idea.
Right?
Yeah. Yeah.
I think it's a good idea.
See? I told you, man.
What are you doing?
I want to find my friend.
Then people will know
where we are, man.
Some of these people
are total dicks.
LEANDRA ON PA: Hello?
Hello?
This is...
This is Leandra Florez.
Mike?
Mike, if you're still there,
(SOBS)
I'm on the first floor, okay?
Could you...
Could you please come?
Just come, okay?
If you can.
(GRUNTS)
(YELLS)
Hey, don't move.
It's okay. It's okay.
Liezel, right?
It's not safe here,
we need to go.
(SQUEAKING)
(THUDS)
(GRUNTING)
(DOOR CLOSES)
WENDELL: Leandra...
(GUN COCKS)
That's not right.
Just put that down.
That's Tyson.
He was your friend,
and you killed him.
No.
Yes, Leandra.
It's Barry.
I don't know how many he has.
But I think...
I think I can...
Oh, God damn it!
(SCREAMS)
Push it.
Push the table!
(GROANS) God damn it.
No. No.
(YELLS)
(YELLING)
Oh, my God!
(GASPS)
Mike.
Are you okay?
MIKE: Yes.
(LEANDRA SOBS)
(GRUNTING)
MIKE: What are these?
They're bombs.
One of the cafeteria guys was taking
it from out of people's heads.
Liezel?
(GRUNTS)
(LIEZEL SCREAMS)
(LEANDRA SHOUTS)
(GRUNTS)
(BOTTLE SHATTERS)
(MUFFLED SPEAKING)
Oh, God, no, no!
(MUZAK PLAYING)
(BUTTON BEEPS)
(ELEVATOR WHIRRING)
(ELEVATOR BELL DINGS)
MIKE: You're gonna be okay.
Yeah?
We're gonna get out of here.
I'm gonna get us out of here.
We're gonna go far, far away
from this place.
(CHUCKLES)
(BREATHING RAGGEDLY)
(SNIFFLES)
I love you.
I love you, too.
Okay?
(GRUNTS)
It's gonna be okay.
Keep your eyes open. Hey!
Hey, keep your eyes open.
Leandra?
Don't. Don't.
No.
Leandra!
(SOBBING)
(GUN CLICKS)
(ELECTRICITY CRACKLING)
(BREATHES HEAVILY)
Fuck!
Motherfucker! You killed her!
(BOTH GRUNTING)
MAN ON SPEAKERS: With offices
in over 40 countries,
the Belko Corporation
trains its employees
to face all the challenges
of modern office environment this
dynamic business landscape provides.
Not only do we bring the
world together, we bring...
There is no "I" in "team."
(MIKE COUGHS)
We want our employees...
(BOTH GRUNTING)
They're being paid well...
...be a part of
the Belko family.
(MAN CONTINUES INDISTINCTLY
ON SPEAKERS)
(YELLS)
...here to ensure that you become
master of your own destiny.
A winner, reaching
your highest potential.
The power to be your
best is in your hands.
The time is now.
(BARRY GAGS)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
You didn't change
a damn thing.
Neither did you.
(FEEDBACK WHINES)
THE VOICE:
Congratulations, Mr. Milch.
You are the last remaining
employee of Belko Industries.
Mr. Milch.
You're the voice.
Why?
Mr. Milch.
(YELLS) Why?
Mr. Milch, we would like you
to answer a few questions.
What are you doing here?
What is this?
THE VOICE: I'm sorry,
we're not at liberty
to discuss the particulars
of the experiment, Mr. Milch.
Who are you?
We're part of an international
organization, Mr. Milch.
Some of the greatest
thinkers in the world,
who believe social scientists
must be allowed
to study human behavior
unfettered by
conventional concepts.
And believe me
we've learned
an incredible amount
about the human mind
and behavior
since we started
these experiments.
Why?
What for?
Well, perhaps someday the
world will be better built.
It's not my concern.
Science is method.
We're simply gathering data.
Data?
Just answer our questions,
and we'll let you be on your way, yes?
Now, which emotion
most accurately describes
how you feel in this moment?
A, sad.
B, relieved.
(COMPUTERS BEEPING)
C, confused. D...
So you've been watching
everything that we do in there.
We are not here to answer your questions.
You are here to answer ours.
Well, then I suppose you saw
me pick up those explosives?
And where are
these explosives now?
On you.
You fucking piece of shit.
I put them on all of you.
(INAUDIBLE)
(BEEPING)
(TRACERS EXPLODING)
(MAN SCREAMS)
THE VOICE:
Listen, please, Michael!
(GROANS) Please.
Michael
your actions today...
You believe life is sacred.
Yeah?
(GRUNTS)
(INAUDIBLE)
FEMALE VOICE ON SPEAKERS:
End Stage One, commence Stage Two.
(SPANISH SONG PLAYING)
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org