Subtitles downloaded from www.OpenSubtitles.org
I forgot where I am.
You're at the place
where the killers meet
to decide what to do
with the crippled girl.
Oh, that's right. That's right.
Did you hear that?
That's funny.
That's weird. Those people look
like they're clawing at themselves.
Is that blood?
Claire, are you seeing this?
Claire.
Claire?
What page was I on?
Page.
- I need an extension over here.
- Fall back. Fall back.
You kidding me?
Like another 20 feet.
Don't touch that.
That's for the drywall guys.
I told you he wouldn't do it!
So then the little guy says,
"You have a girlfriend named Wendy, too?
Well, I saw your thing and it said 'WY'."
The big guy says, "No, man, mine says,
'Welcome to Jamaica, have a nice day."'
Christ, McKenzie fell.
Medic, we have a major accident
at the south side of the building.
- We'll need an ambulance.
- Copy.
Jesus.
Give him some room.
- Hey!
- Somebody fell!
- Davis?
- Oh, my God, he just fell!
Someone fell! Over that building!
Oh, my God!
- Watch it.
- Oh, my God!
Watch it. Get out of there!
- Help!
- Look out!
Look out!
God in heaven.
Look, I don't know if you guys
have heard about this article
in The New York Times
about honeybees vanishing?
Well, apparently, honeybees are
disappearing all over the country.
Tens of millions of them.
Just disappearing.
There's no bodies, no sign of them.
They're just mysteriously gone.
It's scary, huh?
All right, let's hear some theories
about why this might be happening.
Nothing? Come on, guys.
- Laura.
- Disease?
Right. Could be a virus or infection.
But it's all over the country.
It's a coordinated event in 24 states.
It's a little tricky.
- Pollution?
- Could be.
I mean, we're just pumping
so much junk into the environment
they're just keeling over.
But there are no bodies. Keep guessing.
Dylan.
Global warming.
Temperature goes up a fraction of a
degree, makes them disoriented?
Maybe.
Jake?
You don't have an opinion?
You're not interested
in what happened to the bees?
You should be more interested
in science, Jake.
You know why?
Because your face is perfect.
The problem is,
your face is perfect at 15.
Now, if you were interested in science,
you would know facts
like the human nose and ears
grow a fraction of an inch each year.
So a perfect balance of features now
might not look so perfect
five years from now.
They might look downright whack
10 years from now.
Come on, buddy.
Take an interest in science.
What could be a reason
the bees have vanished?
An act of nature and
we'll never fully understand it.
Nice answer, Jake.
He's right.
I mean, science will come up
with some reason to put in the books,
but in the end, it'll be just a theory.
We will fail to acknowledge that there are
forces at work beyond our understanding.
To be a good scientist,
you must have a respectful awe
for the laws of nature.
Jake?
How much does the human nose
grow each year?
- Oh, man.
- It's minuscule, buddy, okay?
Don't worry about it. You're gonna
be a heartthrob your whole life.
I was just messing with you.
The Dark Lord.
Don't look into her eyes.
Vice Principal!
What can we do for you?
I'm afraid I have to interrupt you
for a moment, Mr. Moore.
Okay, guys, calm down.
I'll be right back.
- What is that?
- I can't believe it.
- Oh, my God.
- I've never seen anything like it before.
- What's going on?
I don't know.
You excused all the teachers?
The administration makes us teach
with a foot of snow on the ground.
What is this?
- They stopped class.
- Elliot!
All right.
There appears to be an event happening.
Central Park was just hit by
what seems to be a terrorist attack.
Oh, no.
They're not clear on the scale yet.
It's some kind of
airborne chemical toxin
that's been released
in and around the park.
They said to watch
for warning signs.
The first stage
is confused speech.
The second stage is physical
disorientation, loss of direction.
The third stage is fatal.
Central Park? That's kind of odd.
I spoke with the head of schools.
He said we should dismiss the students.
So take your planners home
so we can get back when this is over.
All right? Let's do our jobs.
Hey, you guys still got to work on
your science projects for next week.
What are the rules of
scientific investigation?
Identify variables.
Design the experiment.
Careful observation and measurement.
Interpretation of experimental data.
Hey, guys?
Nothing.
Alacrity. With alacrity, please.
My mother just called my cell again.
She's hysterical. Hysterical.
I told her the probability of something
happening in Philadelphia is very low.
I mean, nobody's telling us
to leave the city, right?
So I threw some figures at her.
It's good to be a math teacher sometimes.
You know, people are comforted
by percentages. Didn't work.
She still wants us to get out of
the city and come out to her house.
But she said for
you and Alma to come.
Yeah, let me think
about that, okay?
Did you hear about New York?
Are you okay?
No, I mean, are you okay?
Yeah, me, too.
Listen, I want to talk about it more.
Julian's mom offered for all of us to
get out of the city and stay with her.
What do you think?
Yo, Chris!
I'll bring Jess and Evette
and I'll meet you at the station.
Listen, Julian, if Alma's acting
weird, just be cool, okay?
What's going on?
She's acting odd.
Just don't worry about it, okay?
Odd?
Look, if she's acting like
she's distant or something...
What?
I can't say any more.
Is she leaving you?
I didn't say that. It's just talk, okay?
Just relax, please?
Hey.
I'm going to tell you something you
should never tell your best friend.
Why is everybody saying that?
I saw her on your wedding day.
Again with the wedding. What?
I walked into a waiting room by mistake,
and she was crying.
She looked up. I saw her face.
She wasn't ready to jump in, Elliot.
That's not who she is.
She's never going to jump in
when you need her, man.
So do federal, state and local
officials have a plan in place
for this type of catastrophe?
Are they utilizing all the
manpower or the money...
- Hi.
- Are you packed?
- Yes.
- What are they saying?
They're evacuating New York City.
Well, our brains come equipped
with a self-preservation mechanism
to stop us from harmful actions.
This is controlled by a combination
of electrochemical signals in the brain.
The blocking of neurotransmitters
by certain toxins
has been proven to cause hallucinations,
asphyxiation and paralysis.
This new neurotoxin is basically
flipping the preservation switch,
blocking neurotransmitters
in a specific order,
causing specific self-damaging
and catastrophic effects.
Just how the toxin works
and who the terrorists are...
It makes you kill yourself.
Just when you thought there couldn't be
any more evil that could be invented.
I'll be packed in two minutes.
Hello?
- No need to rush.
- Sir. Thank you.
Sir, we need to check your suitcase.
Elliot! Elliot! Elliot!
This just in to the Eyewitness News
room and this is the latest development.
Autopsies on the first victims confirm
the toxin is a natural compound.
The attacks remain confined
to the New York metropolitan area.
This is a very,
very disturbing story...
Track three now
boarding for Harrisburg.
Hey, Jess. Where's Evette?
She was at a shop across town,
she got stuck in traffic.
- She's gonna take the next train.
- We'll wait.
No, no, no. She wanted us
to get on this train with Jess.
She'll feel a lot safer.
- Where's Alma?
- Restroom.
Hey, Julian!
Please have your tickets out and ready,
ladies and gentlemen.
I bought them.
It was like getting one
of those Cabbage Patch Dolls
when they first came out.
Madhouse. How are you?
- Good. You?
- Good.
- Okay, good. Why don't we all...
- I'm really glad you chose to come.
Thanks. Elliot, can I
talk to you for a second?
Yeah.
Please show me your tickets,
ladies and gentlemen.
- You told him about our fight?
- No.
- Why did he say that?
- He guessed.
I love you, Elliot, but I don't like to put
my feelings out there for everyone to see.
I'm not that type of person.
Elliot, these are our problems.
I am upset.
I'm going to sit alone and cool off.
By the time we get there I'll be fine.
Is that okay?
Fine.
I'm going to get on the train.
We're not gonna
get to sit together anyways.
Okay.
Hey, babe.
- Hi, Aunt Alma.
- How you doing?
- Hanging in there.
- Me, too.
- What's wrong with you?
- What?
You're wrong about her.
She just needs time to figure it out.
Come on, don't get all sensitive.
- Just give her a chance.
- Okay, fine. If you don't want my help...
- I don't want your help!
- Okay. I heard it.
Jess, could you ask your dad
for my ticket, please?
Thank you.
I'll see you on the train, Jess.
Track 3 now boarding
all ticketed passengers.
Here we go.
When will Mom meet us at Grandma's?
Mommy's gonna get on the next train.
You know how she's always late.
- Come on. Come on. I know. I know.
- Mom.
- Chilly, isn't it today, Sal?
- Maybe a little.
Hey, it's me. I'm on a train.
I just want to say something, okay?
You've got to stop calling me.
You're acting like the
Fatal Attraction guy, here.
I feel like I'm
going to take a shower
and see your silhouette
on the shower curtain.
We ate tiramisu together,
that is it.
I told you that would be it.
You have got to chill out.
What?
When?
In Philadelphia?
- I don't know. What did you hear?
- Oh, my God. I can't believe it.
What's the news?
Apparently Philadelphia
was just attacked.
- Oh, my God. Evette.
- Call Mommy. Call Mommy!
Honey!
Honey...
Yeah, yeah, where are you?
What? What?
I can't hear you.
I said I can't hear you!
Text me.
Text me. I can't hear you!
They think it started
in Rittenhouse Square Park.
Another park?
- She got on a bus going to New Jersey.
- I want to talk to her.
I know, baby. I know. She got out.
She's headed to the town of Princeton.
I want to talk to her.
- Do you have a phone?
- No, I'm sorry.
- You okay?
- They say Boston got hit, too.
- Where'd you hear that?
- A friend from work. What about Evette?
Oh, God. She made it out on a bus.
What the hell is going on, Elliot?
I honestly don't know.
Now what?
It just stopped. I don't know.
- Can't go nowhere.
- They're not telling us anything.
- Well, until we hear from...
- Sir?
Train service has
been discontinued.
This will be the last stop
for all passengers.
Hey! What do you mean?
Where are we?
Filbert, Pennsylvania.
Filbert?
Does anybody know where that is?
Why are you giving me one useless
piece of information at a time?
What's going on?
Hey, why would you just stop?
You can't just leave us here.
Sir, we lost contact.
With whom?
Everyone.
I'm scared. I don't like it here.
I want Mom.
Don't be silly.
We're safe here, okay?
Sorry. She whispers to us
when she gets scared.
We're so much the same, Jess.
I don't like to show my emotions, either.
She's shivering.
I know. I know.
She's never right without her mom.
It's okay.
They're not saying anything.
We're stuck here.
Is Jess okay?
She's not talking.
We're in a small town, Jess.
Nothing will happen to us here.
Don't know what you want?
Then just have the grilled cheese
plain with milk, okay?
Come on, come over here.
No, you know what?
Why don't you stay here?
Stay here, all right?
You can see me from over there.
What?
All right, you want to come with me?
You can come with me and wait in line.
You want to do that?
Bro! Bro, I got it.
Go get the milk.
All right, yeah. Okay.
You know that everyone
gives off energy, right?
It's scientifically proven.
They got these cameras
that can record what color you are
when you're feeling different things.
People that are angry give off a
different color than people that are sad.
See this ring?
This ring can supposedly tell you
what you're feeling.
Let's see what
you're feeling right now.
Yellow! That's cool.
That means you're about to laugh.
I'm not making it up.
That's what yellow means.
You must be about
to laugh or something.
It's probably just
about to come out.
We'll wait.
We got all day.
Oh, my God. There it is! Cool.
That ring really works. That's amazing.
Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
Look at this.
My sister sent it to me.
It was taken an hour ago
at the Philadelphia Zoo.
Mother of God,
what kind of terrorists are these?
They're not sure it's terrorists now.
Moments ago,
in an official statement,
the government moved away
from its initial position
that this was a
terrorist attack.
Authorities are now feeling,
by the sheer number
of incidents being reported,
that a terrorist group being responsible
is becoming less and less likely.
The event appears to be
limited to the Northeast,
where smaller and smaller towns
are being attacked.
Where are we?
The infected area now
includes most of New England,
from Massachusetts to Maryland.
We're dead center.
Everything okay?
If we stay here,
we are gonna die here.
Whatever this is, it looks like it's
not occurring about 90 miles from here.
Let's go.
Anyone got a car?
Can anyone give us a ride?
Hey!
Excuse me, sir?
Sir, could we get a ride, please?
We don't have any transportation.
We're stuck here.
Sir, did you hear what I said?
We don't have any transportation!
- We have a little girl with us. Please.
- Drive. Just roll up the window.
Sir! You're not just going to...
Can you believe
how crappy people are?
There's a car.
Hi. I run a plant
nursery up the street.
We're picking up a few things from home,
then heading
wherever this isn't happening.
We have room.
- We have two others.
- That's okay.
Julian!
Is Julian okay?
We got a ride. He can fit all of us.
Elliot, I can't get Evette on
the phone or e-mail or nothing.
- How long?
- It's been about two hours.
She was on that
bus headed to Princeton.
There's a car over there headed
to pick up friends and family,
they said they
could squeeze one more.
We got to go.
Look, think real carefully about this.
She was looking
for a birthday present for Jess.
Some kind of dollhouse.
That's why she wasn't with us.
I'm just gonna go get her
and I want to bring her back,
and then I'm gonna find you guys.
I just...
I need you to take Jess, okay?
She's gonna be
a lot safer with you.
Don't do this to me.
I'm doing my best
here not to fall down.
I'm sure the probability of
Princeton not being hit is good.
Yeah.
You want me to throw some
figures and percentages at you
so we both feel better?
- Please.
- All right.
62% chance.
62% chance it hasn't even been hit.
- Well, you go get her, Jules, okay?
- Of course, man, of course.
Come on.
This is all some weird event, that's all.
We're all gonna be fine.
I'm gonna find you guys real soon.
I have to go.
I got her, Julian.
Don't take my daughter's hand
unless you mean it.
I'm going to go get Mommy.
Hold our picture.
Take a look around.
We'll be ready in a jiffy.
We're packing
hot dogs for the road.
You know, hot dogs get a bad rap.
They've got a cool shape,
they've got protein.
You like hot dogs, right?
By the way,
I think I know what's causing this.
- You do?
- It's the plants.
They can release chemicals.
You like hot dogs, don't you?
Okay, babies, we are gonna be going,
but we will be back soon, okay?
Oh, plants react to human stimulus.
They've proved it in tests.
Did you get the mustard?
Don't look outside. Stop it!
Stop it! Just look at me!
Just keep looking at me!
Close the vents.
I'm gonna give you a math riddle, okay?
And you're gonna tell me the answer.
What?
How much would you have if I said
I would pay you a penny on the first day
and then two pennies on the second,
and then four pennies on the third day
and I just kept doubling it
and I did this for a month?
How much money would you have
at the end of the month?
- Ten dollars.
- No, higher. Higher, higher.
Just keep looking at me.
Twenty dollars?
No, keep going. Keep going.
Thirty. It's thirty. It's $30.
I'm gonna tell you the answer.
It's over $10 million.
You'd have over $10 million
at the end of the month.
You want to hear another one?
Water contamination has surfaced
as one of the many theories
being taken seriously as to the cause
of the events in the Northeast.
We have to go through
this little community of homes.
Small town called Holcomb,
then we hit the highway.
From there,
we're 30 miles from the state line.
Are those dead animals up ahead?
Stop the car.
- You don't think it's...
- I don't know.
You got binoculars in the back, from
when you were spying on our neighbors.
Can I have the map?
Elliot...
Don't cause a panic, okay?
Jess can hear you.
It's bodies, isn't it?
I knew it would be bodies.
How could it not be bodies?
Please, give me the map.
Well, we have to turn around.
There's a right turn
about a quarter of a mile back.
We're just gonna take a different route,
honey, okay?
Oh, it's the Army. We're safe!
My name is Private Auster.
I'm stationed at West Dover Military Base,
about 10 miles back.
I think they've been affected
by whatever's happening.
I lost communication with them.
When I approached the base,
I saw military personnel
in the barbed wire, in the fence.
So I suggest no one take that road.
There's a town
about eight miles behind us.
There were bodies on the road into town.
Cheese and crackers.
Well, that still
leaves us two directions.
Just stop! Stop the vehicle!
- What's going on?
- Is everyone all right?
We have no communication with anybody.
- I'll talk to them.
- Did you see anything out of the ordinary?
Hello! Please stop!
Excuse me.
Who's Joey?
Oh, it's no one.
Any luck?
I can't get Julian
on his cell phone.
I'm sure he'll be all right.
They'll be okay.
Has anyone seen any other people
on the roads?
Maybe he's on to something.
- What are you talking about?
- I don't know.
Why did it start in parks?
It's the same story.
About eight, nine miles back.
They say there's a bus in a lake.
Five miles back.
There were dozens of bodies.
Okay.
Nobody's going anywhere.
We're gonna stay right here for a while.
There's a woman
talking to her daughter.
She's talking to her
daughter in Princeton.
Isn't that where your friend went?
Come on.
It's okay.
Honey, it's okay.
She's so scared.
You just stay in that room.
You don't open the door for nothing.
Just keep watching out the window
with the tree, baby.
Someone will come and get you soon.
Tell her not to go near the window
with the tree. Just tell her.
Baby, don't go near the window
with the tree.
Ask her if Princeton's been affected.
Honey, someone wants to know
if Princeton's had any problems.
She says everyone's dead outside.
You just stay in your room.
Honey?
Honey, you're talking funny.
What's wrong with you?
- What do you mean? Everyone's dead?
- What?
Stacy... Stacy, you're scaring me.
I don't understand what you're saying.
What, baby?
She's just not making any sense.
Calculus.
I see in calculus.
- Stacy!
- Calculus.
Stacy!
Stacy Ann!
Oh, my God.
- I hear wind from outside.
- Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Stacy, Stacy, Stacy.
Oh, no!
We're going to go back to the car,
okay, Jess?
If we went down that road,
where would that take us?
I walked down a quarter mile,
it was clean.
I can't tell you what's after that,
but it was clean, no bodies, no nothing.
- Quarter mile?
- That's not enough.
Hey, it's better than going back
the other way.
Get a battle plan.
Everybody makes a clean break.
Elliot's resilient, isn't he?
Yeah. He never gives up.
You know, plants have the ability
to target specific threats.
Tobacco plants,
when attacked by Heliothis caterpillars
will send out a chemical attracting
wasps to kill just those caterpillars.
We don't know how plants
attain these abilities.
They just evolve very rapidly.
Which species do you think is
doing it if you think it's true?
Plants have the ability to communicate
with other species of plants.
Trees can communicate with bushes,
bushes with grass
and everything in between.
The radio says these attacks
started happening in the cities
then went to the towns
and now the roads.
That's right.
Whatever's happening is happening
to smaller and smaller populations.
So we shouldn't be on the roads, then.
The terrorists, or whatever
could be watching the roads.
I don't have any reason
to disagree right now.
We are in the area of attack.
If you can't find a way
through the area of attack
we are told to find a safe zone
within the area being attacked.
They're attacking populations.
We need to go where there
aren't that many people.
Where people don't travel.
Now this is Mr. Collins.
He's a realtor that works in this area.
If we go west,
we'll hit a county called Arundell.
It's not on that map.
It would only be on local maps. Dirt roads.
Hardly anybody lives out there.
There's no significant population there.
That's our safe zone.
We wait it out there till it's over.
Is everyone in agreement?
We should go into two groups.
Those that are
ready to go right now
and those that need
to get things from their cars.
We need to stay in groups.
Stay together.
We'll go soon, honey.
We'll go soon.
Maybe we should've waited
for the rest of them,
stayed in a big group,
like the Private said.
Your phone's out, too?
What's wrong?
Okay. I was going to tell you, okay?
There was this guy, Joey.
His name is Joey.
He's at work.
We went out and we had dessert.
I went out and I had dessert with him
when I told you I worked late.
And I didn't work late.
I'm feeling really guilty
in case we're gonna die.
I just wanted you to know that.
You lied to me?
- How much farther is it?
- I don't know.
- We need to keep going forward.
- Who the hell made you boss?
Look, if y'all follow him, y'all gonna die.
You follow me, you're gonna live.
I'm in charge of this group!
Ain't nobody else in charge of this group!
My firearm is my friend!
It will not leave my side!
Private Auster?
My firearm is my friend.
Jesus.
Oh, no.
What, "Oh, no"?
The toxin?
The toxin is affecting them?
Are those people killing themselves?
You were with the Private.
What do we do?
- We need to do something!
- Just let me think.
- They're dying!
- I need a second.
They released it?
We're not near the roads.
We can't just stand here
as uninvolved observers!
I need a second, okay.
Just give me a second!
We are not going to be
one of those assholes on the news
who watches a crime happen
and not do something!
- We're not assholes!
- Just a second!
There were children in that group!
- Elliot, please tell us what to do.
- I need a second, okay!
Why can't anybody
give me a goddamn second?
All right, be scientific, douchebag.
Identify the variables.
That's the two groups.
Design an experiment.
That's what we're in.
Careful observation and measurements.
That's what I'm trying to do.
Interpret the experimental data.
Interpret.
What if it is the plants?
Their group was larger than ours.
This thing has been escalating all day.
Smaller and smaller populations
have been setting this off.
They react to human stimulus.
Maybe people are
setting off the plants?
What are you saying? That guy was crazy.
We have to save them.
They're already dead.
What if they're
targeting us as threats?
This part of the field
may not have been set off.
Something in this field could be
releasing the chemical into the air
when there's too
many of us together.
Let's just stay
ahead of the wind.
Let's just break up into groups.
Come on! Come on! This way!
Come on, follow me!
I'm right here! Keep going!
I'm right behind you!
Here it comes!
Don't you let go of my hand.
Nothing happened.
It's the size of the groups,
I think.
Could this really be happening?
What are your names?
- Jared.
- Josh.
Wait, wait!
I'm going to go see if that truck
has a map. You guys wait here.
Why aren't they looking
into nuclear power plants?
There are 15 or more
in the Northeast alone.
More than anywhere else
in the United States.
There's probably been
some leak or something.
It's probably poisoning the air.
There's a house over there! Come on!
It could have been
some terrorist booby-trap,
someone stepped on
it out in the field.
Yeah, in a field
in Bumbletown, Pennsylvania.
I don't know.
Look, a toxin dissipates quickly in the air.
They're only potent in a certain density.
The source had to be close to that field,
if not in the field.
Here's one.
Plants have the chemistry to do this.
They release co-transporters into the air.
You think it could be plants?
I don't know.
But if it is, and people are
setting it off in groups,
we need to go to the least
populated place we can to be safe.
We can't walk to the borders where this
isn't happening, Alma. It's too far.
Whatever it is, terrorists,
a nuclear leak, plants,
it's probably safe to get
away from people right now.
That must be Arundell.
It's 10 miles from here.
Okay, this place must have a bathroom.
I'm gonna take Jess, then we can leave.
Hurry.
Hello?
My name is Elliot Moore.
I'm just going to talk
in a very positive manner.
Giving off good vibes.
We're just here to use the bathroom
and then we're just gonna leave.
I hope that's okay.
Plastic.
I'm talking to a plastic plant.
I'm still doing it.
You guys ready to leave?
These people must have left in a hurry.
I mean, leaving the front door unlocked?
Hey, everything's fake.
Why is this happening?
I don't know for sure, Josh.
But I read this article
about the coast of Australia.
It said they found large quantities
of a primordial bacteria.
It hadn't been around for billions
of years, it just appeared in the water.
It's toxic to humans, fishermen
who come in contact with it are dying.
It feels kind of similar to that.
With the bees disappearing, I mean,
I don't know, it feels like a pattern.
The nature of events
like the one in Australia
is that they crest and then stop.
We just have to be
alive when it's over.
I don't believe it's nature.
It may not be. There could be some
other explanation. I don't know.
Let's go.
There are people coming!
We can't stay here. It's close to the roads.
More and more people will come here.
There's two groups coming together.
There's too many of them together.
Run. Run.
- Is she your kid?
- No.
- You got kids?
How come? You got a problem?
No. She wanted to wait.
Really? For what?
Me to grow up.
Why are we talking about this?
Sweet. I used to love those.
Can I see it?
You need to take personal responsibility
for yourself in a relationship.
- That'll make a difference.
- Okay. Thank you.
Hey, that's not a toy.
It's got meaning to me.
- Elliot! Look!
- Come on.
Oh, wow.
... is an emergency broadcast.
All those who are still inside
the affected area of the Northeast
are asked to proceed to the police
borders west of your state.
Come on.
This is an emergency broadcast.
... inside the affected area...
Jess needs a 10-minute rest
and some food.
Are you sure?
We should keep going.
I know, but she's only eight.
What?
If we're going to die,
I want you to know something.
I was in the pharmacy a while ago,
and there was a really good-looking
pharmacist behind the counter.
Really good-looking.
And I went up and I asked her
where the cough syrup was.
I didn't even have a cough.
And I almost bought it.
And I'm talking about a completely
superfluous bottle of cough syrup.
That's like six bucks.
Are you joking?
Thank you.
- Maybe that's not a good idea.
- I told her just for a minute.
Mr. Moore,
I think I can open this door.
Wait. We're a gang now?
We're gonna take whatever we want?
- Come on, guys.
- Listen, nobody's home.
We're just gonna
get some food for Jess.
Yeah, and it looks like nobody's
lived here for a long time anyway.
I mean, it's all boarded up.
Maybe we could leave some money.
- What kind of tree is this?
- I think it's a maple.
Not so high.
Okay, Josh, open the door.
Wait!
I see something.
- There's somebody in there!
- You sure?
Yeah, I saw him move.
I see him!
Let's stop.
Is there any way we could get some food?
We have a little girl.
- We just want to get her some food.
- You best leave now.
You ain't gonna bring that
poison gas in here with you.
Sir, it's not poison gas.
There's none out here.
- They said to stay inside.
- We're fine right now.
Nothing's happened out here yet.
I mean, you can see that.
Just listen to our voices.
We're perfectly normal.
Old black water,
keep on rolling
Mississippi moon
Won't you keep on shining on me?
See? We're normal.
You ain't from around here.
You'd best leave now.
Okay. It's not worth it.
Open the door, bitch!
Hey, Josh, don't do that.
He didn't mean that!
- There's more than one in there.
- Jess! Jess, come here.
Stop it, Jess. Listen, we just want some
food for a little girl, you pussies!
- Jess, come here.
- Josh, stop it.
You'd best not let that gas in here.
Sir, the air is fine out here right now.
You don't need to worry.
- You might be with the terrorists!
- I don't think it's terrorists, sir.
- Josh, stop it!
- They're being crazy, Mr. Moore!
- Show your faces!
- Let the gas in...
No!
Jared!
We're gonna get
out of this nightmare.
Elliot!
We have to go.
We have to protect Jess.
Okay?
You've got to three
to get off our porch!
Come here.
No new people have crossed
over the border for a few hours.
It appears those residents that are still
in the affected area of the Northeast
are trying to wait it out.
We have Professor Kendel Wallace
of Carnegie Mellon,
a statistician, here with us.
Professor, what can you tell us?
Calculating by the rise in
intensity of reports of incidents
within the affected area,
one can guess at a crude timetable.
One can see the incident
is rising in sensitivity.
We've seen fewer and fewer people
can provoke the attacks.
The event should be at its most
sensitive tomorrow morning.
Typically, these type of slopes
drop precipitously after cresting,
meaning it could end suddenly,
at any moment.
Of course,
these are only probabilities.
There are some quiet rumblings
that the government may be
involved in the tragic events
playing out in the Northeast.
Now, these rumors have been fuelled
by the statements
of a confidential informant
who claims that the CIA
has facilities in the Northeast,
where they are testing drugs with
some similar psychotropic properties
as a defense against
chemical weapons.
CIA and White House officials
have declined to respond
to these accusations.
Perimeters have been set up
all along the East Coast
from Maryland
all the way to Massachusetts.
This house has no power going to it.
Nobody's driven on this driveway
for a long time, either.
Let me go. You guys stay right here.
That's for Clement.
He's a retriever.
You lost?
You must be.
There ain't nothing
around here for miles.
Why are you eyeing my lemon drink?
I suppose the kind thing for me
to do is to offer you supper.
I ain't gonna ask you again.
I hope the meal was sufficient.
I wasn't expecting guests.
This is a beautiful place.
There's a springhouse in the back.
They used to hide people
from slave chasers back there.
It has a speaking tube running
under the ground to the main house.
You can hear each other
like you were in the same room.
So, what's with you two?
Who's chasing who?
I'm sorry?
Ain't no time two people staring
at each other, standing still,
love in both their eyes,
at the same time, equal.
Truth is, someone is chasing someone.
That's the way we's built.
So?
Who's chasing?
I knew that. I knew that.
Don't touch things that aren't yours.
- Do you have a radio, Mrs. Jones?
- No.
I got enough to fill my time right here.
I mend my own things.
I grow my own food.
Although I ain't got the touch.
Gardens don't grow the way they should.
Never have.
- How do you stay in contact with others?
- I don't.
How would you know if something
were to happen? Like a world event?
Mrs. Jones, something's happened
along the East Coast.
Whatever it is that
you think is so important
that you need to tell me, don't.
Just keep it to yourself.
The world don't care about me.
I don't care about it.
Suppose I have to
let you spend the night.
Guest room's up on the left.
Mind the steps.
I'm scared, Elliot.
It's okay.
I'm sorry about everything.
That Joey thing. I was being stupid.
You've been great taking care of Jess.
I don't like this woman.
There's something Exorcist-y about her.
How could she hit Jess like that?
Well, we need to stay in this house.
You want me to protect you,
this is how we have to do it.
Let's just deal with her.
I hear you whispering.
Planning on stealing something?
No, ma'am, we're not.
Plan on murdering me in my sleep?
What? No!
Mrs. Jones?
Crazy lady.
You trying to steal my things?
No! No, Mrs. Jones,
I actually wanted to talk with you.
- You all are gonna leave right now!
- Ma'am, you don't understand.
There's something happening
in a few states, in this region.
- It's not safe!
- Leave now!
The Lord is my shepherd.
Mrs. Jones,
could we talk calmly for a second?
Just hear me out.
See, I'm a teacher...
Mrs. Jones?
Oh, my God.
Alma, shut the windows
and the doors!
Alma?
Jess?
Hi, froggie! Hi, froggie!
Okay, yeah. Wait.
How old do you think he is?
Is he a baby? I think he's a baby.
He's so tiny.
I didn't know frogs could be like that.
Oh, he got water on my shoe.
Isn't this a cool house?
If we had this house,
we could make it look so pretty.
Get him again. Get him again.
Hey, froggie.
Alma?
Good morning, Elliot.
Sounds like you're right here.
- Close the windows and the doors, Alma.
- Why?
Mrs. Jones just died.
Close the windows.
Close the door, Jess!
- Is everything closed?
- Yes.
- I'm sorry, Alma.
- What's going on, Elliot?
It's happening here.
It could be the grass and
the trees are doing this now.
She was alone when it happened.
Seems like they might have
gotten more sensitive.
It's too dangerous
to go outside, isn't it?
Yes.
This is the end, isn't it?
I wish you were here.
Me, too.
You remember our first date?
You were so quiet.
You bought me the mood ring.
It turned purple when you wore it.
Then you said,
"That means you're in love."
It got you to talk, didn't it?
Then we checked
the little paper chart,
and it turned out that
purple meant I was horny.
- You loved that.
- I had no idea.
Yours was blue.
Peaceful, right?
Right.
What color was love?
I don't remember.
Me, neither.
Elliot?
Yeah?
I was just making
sure you're there.
It's not right for it to end like this.
If we're gonna die,
I want to be with you.
I want to be with you,
and I'm gonna come and be with you.
Elliot, don't!
The event must have ended
before we went out there.
I found the hair clip!
You don't want to be late
for the first day schools are open.
Oh, wait.
I'm just gonna put this right here.
Okay?
- Are you okay?
- Yes, Aunt Alma. I love you.
I love you, too. Come here.
All right. I'll pick you up
after you're done with school, okay?
Bye.
As everyone knows by now,
traces of the neurotoxin have been
found in some plants and trees.
Now, most environmentalists feel
that this event is like
the red tide in the ocean,
but instead of algae killing fish,
this happened on land.
Now, plants and trees
just can't pick up and move
when they feel threatened,
like other species.
They have only one option,
to rapidly evolve their chemistry.
Well.
Kay from Mississippi wants to know
why it started so suddenly,
on a Tuesday at 8:33 and then ended
so suddenly at 9:27 the next morning.
Well, Kay, to be perfectly honest,
this was an act of nature,
and we'll never fully understand it.
And, Doctor, there's been
a lot of speculation
as to why this happened
in the Northeast only.
How do you explain that?
Well, I believe, all right,
and this is just my opinion,
that this was a prelude, okay?
A warning,
like the first spot of a rash.
We have become
a threat to this planet.
I don't think anybody
will argue that.
- And this is a warning.
- A warning?
I think the skeptics would believe that
if it had occurred anywhere else.
That's why most people
believe it was the government.
If it had happened in one other place,
anywhere else,
we could all believe
what you're saying.
I should drop my bicycle off at the
apartment before I go to work.
Can you make Nadia's party tonight?
I should drop my bicycle off at the
apartment before I go to work.
That frightened me.
I should drop my bicycle off
What?
My God...
My
bicycle.
Best watched using Open Subtitles MKV Player