Someone needs to stop Clearway Law.
Public shouldn't leave reviews for lawyers.
What's on the menu?
It could be ceviche
Stinky-oo, it's Pumbaa
Ingonyama
I got to tell you, Timon...
that song always
gets me right here.
Yeah, Pumbaa.
Well, enough of that.
Timon, what are you doing?
I'm fast forwarding to the part
where we come in.
But you can't go out of order.
Au contraire, my porcine pal.
I've got the remote.
But everyone's going
to get confused.
We got to go back
to the beginning of the story.
We're not in the beginning
of the story.
Yes, we were, the whole time.
Yeah, but they don't know that.
Then why don't we
tell them our story?
Hey, I've got an idea.
Why don't we tell them
our story?
Oh, I like the sound of that.
A little backstage tour.
Take them behind the scenes for
a revealing and intimate look...
at the story within the story.
Because what they don't know
is how we really were there...
even though they didn't know
we were there, you know?
Couldn't have said it
better myself.
So, does this mean we're going
back to the beginning?
Oh, no, Pumbaa, no.
We're going way back...
to before the beginning.
Pride Rock.
So majestic.
So powerful.
So bizarrely named.
Pumbaa, how can a rock be proud?
It's a rock.
I think it's because a pride is
what they call a group of lions.
Oh, sure,
the lions get Pride Rock.
And what about us meerkats?
Where I come from, we didn't
have nothing to be proud of.
Why...
When I was a young meerkat
When he was a young meerkat
Very nice.
Thanks.
But maybe it would be safer...
if I just show them
where I came from.
Oh, boy! Do we get
to see where you grew up?
Yeah, Pumbaa,
but it ain't pretty.
Please remain seated while
the camera is in motion.
Here we are.
From Pride Rock
to the pit of shame.
We're so low on the food chain,
we're underground.
But you don't have
to take my word for it.
I'll just let my fellow
meerkats do the talking.
What was that, what was what?
What was that, what was that?
Where, what, where, where,
What was that?
Quick, before the hyena come
Clear.
Dig a tunnel, dig, dig a tunnel
When you're done,
you dig a bigger tunnel
Dig a tunnel, dig, dig a tunnel
Quick, before the hyena come
Dig, dig a tunnel,
dig, dig a tunnel
You could dig
and never get done
Dig a tunnel, dig, dig a tunnel
What was that?
Quick before
the hyena come, dig
Dig a tunnel is what we do
Life's a tunnel,
we'll dig it, too
Dig a tunnel is what we sing
Dig a tunnel is everything
Mud and clay
is a meerkat's friend
Always more around every bend
And when you get
to your tunnel's end
Hallelujah,
let's dig again, dig
Dig a tunnel, dig, dig a tunnel
When it's done,
you dig a bigger tunnel
Dig a tunnel, dig, dig a tunnel
What was that?
Quick, before the hyena come
Dig
Timon! Excuse me.
Have you seen my son?
Has he been through here?
Timon!
Dig, dig a tunnel
Uncle Max?
Uncle Max, relax.
Have you seen Timon?
No, I haven't,
and what a day it's been.
No fractures, no lacerations...
no concussions, contusions,
or injuries of any sort.
As a matter of fact...
there's no sign of Timon's
handiwork anywhere.
That would be...
Timon!
Hey, everybody.
Nice work, Timon.
- Way to go, tunnel klutz.
- Who else could break a hole?
Four in one week, a new record.
Not again.
What? It's called a skylight.
Ho ho.
Isn't that creative?
A skylight. Oh.
I'll just have a word with him.
I... I was just trying
to shed a little light...
on our pathetic existence.
Timon, this can't go on.
Just this month,
you've pulled down four walls...
and collapsed two tunnel exits.
We have to look after
each other.
Our survival depends on it.
What's the point?
All we do is dig...
so we can hide,
and hide so we can dig.
I want to be where
we don't have to dig tunnels...
and live with our heads
stuck in the sand.
What's so bad about dreaming
of a better home?
I want to show you something.
Look, Timon.
Go on, look.
Look out to the horizon,
past the trees...
over the grasslands.
Everything the light touches...
belongs to someone else.
Funny.
I thought you were going...
a whole different
direction with this.
What can I say?
It's nature's design.
She's right.
We're food for other animals,
a moveable feast...
feared by no one
and eaten by all.
But when they die,
they become the grass...
and we eat the grass, right?
Not exactly.
We can't digest grass.
We're grass intolerant.
OK, Max. Thank you.
You've been a big help.
Meerkat,
it's what's for dinner.
Thank you, Uncle Max.
I think uncle Max dislodged one
too many rocks with his skull.
But he's right, Timon.
Oh, I just know there's a way
for you to fit in here.
All right,
who's on sentry duty?
That's it.
That's it,
my son on sentry duty.
Timon the sentry.
Timon the sentry?
Why don't you save the hyenas
the trouble and kill me now?
Just kill me now.
He has a point.
All you have to do is watch for
hyenas and yell if you see one.
Look at Iron Joe.
Don't close your eyes!
Don't look away!
Somebody's got to guard us!
Somebody's gotta protect us!
Well, now I'm convinced.
Listen, it's outside...
up in the breeze,
under the wide open sky.
Isn't that what you want?
Or maybe you would
rather have him...
go back on the digging crew.
No!
Good, then we all agree.
Timon, listen to Uncle Max.
He'll teach you
everything you need to know.
And, honey,
try to make this one work.
Scurry, sniff, flinch!
Good. Now...
what do we do
if we see a hyena?
Scream, "Mommy"?
That's right, mister...
because the world out there
is fraught with danger.
Fraught, I tell you!
Oh, boy. It's the fraught fest.
Rip us limb from limb.
Bravo, Uncle Max.
Way to sell it
to the cheap seats.
Applaud now, sonny boy...
but try clapping when
you don't have any hands.
Scurry, sniff, flinch.
I like the sound of that.
There's more to life than panic
And bein' some other guy's
snack, yuck
I may be delicious organic
But this little entree's
fighting back
I'm gonna put
digging tunnels behind me
And live at a new altitude
I'm gonna reach
for the stars to remind me
That meerkats
are not merely food
For once I'll be
Lookin' out for me
Yeah, I'll tell you what I want
This cat is movin' on
He's a bon vivant
who's missin' out on bon
I'd be a bigger cheese
far from the desert scene
A little cooling breeze,
a little patch of green
And I'll be snoozing
in my hammock
By a rippling stream
Many miles from any tunnel
and the digging team
Looking after number one
will be my only creed
That's all I need
I've always been good
at running away
Well, now I'm gonna run to show
I've always been seen
as the ultimate prey
But now my status ain't so quo
A dream sublime
It's hyena time...
Oh, look,
it's dinner and a show.
And I thought beans
were the only musical food.
Well, hi to you, too.
OK.
This is no time
for horseplay, Timon.
You're supposed to be up there
looking out for...
Hyenas!
Look at them scramble.
And that's just
how I like them...
Scrambled...
And a little bit runny.
Hyenas!
Get in here.
What are you, a meshugginah?
Stumpy? Flinchy? Swifty?
Oh, what a relief.
Everybody's...
Where's Uncle Max?
Max! Run for your life!
Play dead!
Andale!
Almost there!
Suede is the look
for this fall.
Hey, what's going on?
Pumbaa, you're sitting
on the remote.
Oh, sorry.
I thought it was a brownie.
You've got it, Max!
Aww!
Max!
I flinched
when I should've scurried.
Oh, man.
It just never gets old,
does it?
The classics never do, honey.
I...
I guess I owe everyone
an apology.
All right,
so I made a teensy mistake.
Like we all haven't broken
into song on sentry duty before.
Come on.
Let me have a show of hands.
OK.
Maybe it's a little too soon...
but I'm sure we're all going
to laugh about this someday.
Trust me.
I did trust you.
But...
Aw, sweetie...
I'm never going to fit in here.
Nobody even likes me.
Sure they do, honey.
Sure they do.
Besides you, Ma.
Besides me? There's...
I have to find my place,
but it isn't here.
Yes, it is.
We just haven't found it yet.
But we will.
Oh, here's an idea. You can...
Stop with the hair already.
My place is out there, Mom.
Oh, I may not know exactly where
or how far, but I got to go.
No, wait, wait, wait.
I know. If we just...
Ma.
Well, I hope you find what
you're looking for, honey.
I love you.
I love you, Ma.
Oh, Timmy.
My Timmy.
Mom...
Choking. Not breathing.
And people wonder
why I have issues.
Oh, I'll be OK.
Oh, I know you will. You will.
Be careful!
I will.
Don't talk to strangers!
I know, Ma!
Remember,
wash behind your ears!
Ma, I'm not a kid anymore!
Never go swimming
without a buddy!
Got it.
Oy.
What?
What?!
Good-bye, Ma.
And so, with high spirits...
I boldly ventured off...
where no meerkat
had dared to go before.
I put my past behind me, ha!
And never looked back.
Mommy! Mommy!
What am I doing?
Which way should I go?
That depends on what you think.
How convenient.
Enter omniscient monkey,
right on cue.
Well, you know what they say.
When the student is ready,
the teacher appears.
That's it. No more
fortune cookies for you.
Hey, where'd you come from?
Oh, the better question
is, where are you going?
Oh, someplace wonderful,
mister, where...
You didn't happen to catch
the song...
I sang a few minutes ago,
did you?
I didn't have the pleasure.
To recap, I want to live in
some beautiful place outside...
a carefree place where
I don't have to hide or worry.
Life without worry.
You seek hakuna matata.
Harpoon a tomato?
Hakuna matata,
it means "No worries."
Perfect. Mind taking
that stick of yours...
and drawing me a map, bub?
Hey!
To find it, you must look
beyond what you see.
What the heck
is that supposed to mean?
It means look beyond
what you see.
Beyond what I see.
Get a load of the monkey
getting all existential on me.
Beyond what I see.
It's kind of hard to think
with all this music.
Beyond...
what I see.
Oh, wait a second.
It's coming to me.
It's either that slug I ate
or I'm having an epiphany.
I'm going
to the big pointy rock!
Right?
Who was that strange monkey?
Well.
Dream home, here I come.
Hello?
Strange but wise monkey?
You know, first
impressions are very important.
Oh, I thought
you were a scream.
Just eat me now...
and please make it fast.
I got a low threshold for pain.
Easy, easy there, little guy.
I'm not going to eat you.
What? You're not?
Then why were you stalking me?
Well, gee, I saw you go by...
and I figured
a little fellow like you
shouldn't be out here
all alone.
Hey, what about you?
You're all alone.
You are all alone, aren't you?
Yeah. Most animals give me
a pretty wide berth.
They do? Even the hungry ones?
Yeah. I drive
almost everyone away.
People see me coming,
and they run for cover.
They can't get out
of the way fast enough.
You don't say, you don't say.
Must be the gleam
on those vicious tusks?
Strikes fear into their hearts.
Actually, they say
I wreck their appetite.
It's like you have
this... this special power.
Special power?
Well, it's pretty powerful,
all right.
Perfect. You're hired.
Great! For what?
To get me to a little
worry-free haven...
out by that big pointy rock.
And you want me
to come with you?
Do you see
any other big lovable...
chunk of warthog here...
who also happens to have
razor-sharp tusks...
and the ability
to repel predators?
I'm your pig.
You and me, I can tell,
we see eye to eye.
You mean, like friends?
Easy there, big fella.
I'd say more like...
acquaintances.
Well, it's a start.
Put 'er there, acquaintance.
- I'm Timon.
- Pumbaa.
No, really.
All right, then.
Let's hit the road.
You got it...
acquaintance.
So, clear up one thing for me.
If you weren't
going to eat me...
what kind of a wacky,
wild pig are you?
I'm an insectivore.
Oh ho! A bug eater.
Well, me, too.
I just never had a name for it.
I'm kind of partial
to the crawly critters myself.
- How about you, big boy?
- I prefer the ones with wings.
Pumbaa, this could be
the start of a beautiful...
acquaintanceship.
Nants ingonyama
OK, so now we're
back at the beginning.
Right, Timon?
Oh, you got that right, pally.
Ingonyama
At last,
things were looking up.
I had the sun on my shoulders,
the wind at my heels...
A song in my heart.
And to protect me,
a great big fat guy.
You really think I look fat?
Pumbaa, Pumbaa, Pumbaa.
You're a pig.
It's a compliment.
Oh, thank you.
It's the circle of life
And it moves us all
There it is,
the big pointy rock.
Oh, baby, we're almost there.
I think we're a little late.
It's a land rush.
That loudmouth monkey.
He must've blabbed it
to the whole world.
What exactly did he say?
Look beyond what you see.
So maybe you're supposed to look
beyond the big pointy rock.
Maybe I'm supposed to look
Well...
let's have a little look,
shall we?
Beyond what I see.
What do you know?
The monkey's got an eagle eye
for real estate!
Timon, look!
He-he-hey! It's the monkey!
What's that he's holding up?
Aw, who cares?
It's not important.
Come on! My dream home awaits.
I don't do so well in crowds.
Maybe we better go around.
Don't you know
the shortest distance...
between me and my dream home...
is a straight line? Follow me!
- Oh!
- Excuse me.
Goodness.
Make room, make room!
Watch it, twiggy.
I'm walkin' here!
Timon!
There's something
I gotta tell you.
Pumbaa, Pumbaa, Pumbaa.
We'll have plenty of time
to chat once we settle in.
I could really use a rest stop.
Don't worry.
You'll get your second wind.
I got a really bad feeling!
It'll pass!
Trust me. It'll pass.
Oh, look,
the rhinos are bowing.
We'd better bow, too.
Look, sire, how they kneel
before the royal son.
So, I guess that's
your special power?
What a weapon!
You mean, you don't mind?
Are you kidding?
It was a gas!
Well, I don't like
to toot my own horn.
Yeah, that's probably
for the best.
Let's go, Pumbaa!
Lead the way!
This is it, buddy boy.
Home, sweet home.
And I don't gotta share it
with anybody.
Don't you get, you know,
lonely out here?
Lonely? Try commitment-free.
The elbow-to-elbow life
reminds me...
a little too much of home.
This place has everything:
Cool refreshments,
cozy little hammock...
a lovely water feature,
and it's all mine.
Well, it's really coming
together, Timon, so...
so, I guess I'll just be going.
Wait a minute, now. Wa-wa-wait.
There's no law
that says you have to go.
I mean, if you want...
Great! I already
made up two beds!
One for you, and one for me.
Gee, all this construction work
has me bushed.
Think I'll turn in early.
Yeah.
Good night!
Sleep tight.
Dream of bedbugs tonight.
Home, sweet home indeed.
Hey, keep it down up there!
We have neighbors?
We should go say hello.
Noisy neighbors.
There go the property values.
Let's hear it in the herd
and on the wing
It's gonna be
King Simba's finest fling
Oh, I just can't wait
to be king
Oh, perfect. We moved
to the theater district.
Get a load of these guys.
Knock it off!
Just can't wait
Timon, look out!
To be king
I'm OK.
Oy.
Show people.
Chin up, Pumbaa.
Our dream home's
around here somewhere.
You know, Timon,
I once came across a place...
that might be just what
you're looking for.
Spectacular waterfalls...
set in a lush tropical oasis...
a scrumptious array of...
Hey, hey. Forget it, Pumbaa.
I'm a realist, and I'm not gonna
go chasing after some fantasy.
I'm going beyond what I see.
But if you always go
beyond what you see...
how do you know
when you're there?
Oh, I'll tell you how I know.
We're there!
This is a lovely spot.
Lovely, rustic, picturesque.
Home, sweet home, Pumbaa.
Home, sweet...
Whoop!
I... I mean, sure,
it needs a little work...
but it's got good bones.
After all,
this is an elephant graveyard...
and who would ever come
to an elephant graveyard?
Sire, the hyenas
are after the children!
I see carnivores.
Beyond what you see.
Beyond what you see!
Timon?
Would this be a bad time...
to bring up that little place
I told you about?
Hey! This is home,
sweet home, baby!
Home...
Steam! Steam is good.
Steam is... is... is water.
Gotta have water.
You know, for the dream home.
Steam home, dream home.
Steam, steam, steam.
I am perfectly happy
right here!
It's remote, private...
no unexpected visitors.
Somethin' tells me
this ain't...
the traveling company
of "Riverdance".
Beyond what you see.
Beyond what you...
Hey, how am I supposed...
to look beyond what I see
beyond that?
Oh, sorry.
What this place lacks
in water and shade...
it makes up for with searing
heat and blinding sunshine.
Home, sweet home, Pumbaa.
Shall we run for our lives?
Oh, yes, let's.
Hang on, Timon!
This is it!
Good-bye, cruel world!
That's it?
That wasn't so bad.
You can't knock
old Timon down that easy!
Yeah! Bring it on!
Pumbaa?
Question:
Is it possible to fall off
the edge of the earth?
Technically, no.
The earth is round
like a sphere, Timon...
so it doesn't actually
have an edge.
You mind if I pause it
for a second?
Sure, go ahead.
Be right back.
It's a small world after all
It's a small, small world
Everybody
It's a small world after all
OK, I got the jumbo
so we could share.
Were you just
picking your nose?
No, I had an itch
on the inside.
Timon, you OK?
I give up.
But you can't give up.
We still haven't found
our dream home.
Forget it, Pumbaa.
I've been dragging you down
long enough.
I'm going home,
and I suggest you do the same.
Oh, I... I would if I could,
but I can't.
Oh, sure you can, buddy.
I won't stop you.
No, I mean...
I don't have a home.
You don't? What happened?
Are you lost?
No place good enough for you?
What, you're all alone
in this big empty world?
The truth is...
I'm all alone, too.
Pumbaa, you're the only friend
I've ever had.
Y-you mean...
Yeah, Pumbaa... and friends
stick together to the end.
Timon, are you crying?
I'm fine.
I... I just have something
in my eye.
Here, blow.
Here, Pumbaa.
Gee, thanks.
OK, I'm better.
Aw, well.
It's too bad we never found
that perfect place.
Why'd we ever listen
to that stupid monkey?
I think maybe you're
giving up too soon, Timon.
Beyond what you see.
Remember that place
I told you about?
Forget about your place.
Get a load of what I found.
Talk about beyond what you see.
Pumbaa, this is our dream home.
Dramatic views.
Your very own porch swing.
Hot tub and spa.
Well stocked cupboard.
Let's celebrate!
The monkey was right.
We found it, the perfect life.
I'll just whip up
a little something.
He had the perfect name
for it, too.
Come and get it.
Such a wonderful phrase.
It had this rhythm.
Laduda Ladada.
Hot tuna frittata.
No, that's not it.
The spinach armada.
Quiet, Pumbaa.
I'm trying to think.
A spoon of ricotta.
Two words.
A wormy piccata.
Six syllables.
Kahuna colada.
Twelve letters.
A blue enchilada.
Rhymes with...
- Legumes on a platter.
- Think.
This ought to be hotter.
- I forget.
- I got to lambada!
Hey, how can you dance
at a time like this?
I'm dying here.
Sorry about that, pal.
Hakuna matata.
Come again?
Hakuna matata,
it means "No worries".
Hey, Timon, I got an idea.
Let's do a sing-along.
Oh, you tease.
I love karaoke. I'm there.
Wait a second.
Pumbaa, where's the grub?
Oh, you just can't
help yourself, can you?
Sorry.
OK, but this time,
show a little self-control.
Hahuna ma-what-a?
Oh ho ho ho ho!
It means "No worries."
I see.
So, I told the boy
to find hakuna matata...
you must look
beyond what you see.
Oh, a metaphor.
Well, actually,
it's not a meta...
You used a metaphor on Timon?
He takes things literally.
That's it.
He's starving out there.
I just know it.
Max, Timon's out there
chasing metaphors.
I've got to go find him.
Are you nuts?
Nice to have
a supportive family, isn't it?
Well, here I go.
Remember, the journey
of a thousand miles...
begins with the first step.
Thanks. Here's my first step.
Yeow!
Ay!
This bowling for porcupines...
wasn't the best idea?
Yeah. Got to be
right up there...
with bobbing
for snapping turtles.
Oh, that's going
to leave a little mark.
Hey, look, Timon, buzzards.
What do you say,
one more round?
Oh, sure. There must be
some part of me...
we haven't injured yet.
Oh, please?
Oh, please, oh, please,
oh, please, oh, please?
Nah, Pumbaa, I'm beat.
You go ahead.
I'm calling it a day.
But it's no fun alone.
Aw, why not?
One more run
won't change our lives.
Who knows why fate led us...
to little Simba that day.
Maybe it was just
my love of adventure...
or my innate courage...
my valiant
and fearless way of...
OK, who's in charge
of the freeze frames?
Sorry.
Anywho...
rescuing Simba was a cinch.
Then came the really
scary part...
parenthood.
In the jungle,
the mighty jungle
The lion sleeps tonight
In the jungle,
the mighty jungle...
Timon. Timon.
Timon!
- I got to go.
- Go?
Go where?
You know, go... bad.
Oh, go. Why didn't you say so?
Come on, let's go.
When you got to go,
you got to go.
Young lion,
get down from there.
All right!
Man, you guys look like
ants down there.
I'm counting to three.
Yahoo!
One, two...
Three.
In the jungle,
the mighty jungle
Timon.
Oh! Again?
No. I'm thirsty.
You know this means
you'll be up again...
about two hours from now.
Jungle boogie
Jungle boogie, get it on
Hang on, Simba! I'll save you!
Yahoo!
Timon?
The mighty jungle...
We're going to get old
walking across this thing.
Jungle boogie
In the jungle, the might...
Timon?
What have you got
against the concept...
of a good night's sleep?
Actually, I...
I had a bad dream.
Oh, well...
It wasn't me.
Junior had a bad dream.
Why don't you sleep
over here with us?
Mi Pumbaa, su Pumbaa.
All right!
The lion sleeps tonight
Good night.
Sleep tight.
Dream of bedbugs tonight.
Uyy!
My little darling
Don't fear, my little darling
Hey-a, oh, my little darling
Oh, don't fear,
my little darling
Don't fear, my little darling
Hey-a, oh, my little darling
Watch where you aim
that morning breath.
That should come
with a warning label.
What a wake-up call.
Looks like someone woke up...
on the wrong side
of the warthog.
What's the matter, pops?
Had a little too much
hakuna matata?
Sonny boy,
I invented hakuna matata.
Oh, yeah? Well, I perfected it.
Sure you did, sure you did.
Pumbaa, who holds the record for
the world's longest bug belch?
That would be Simba.
All righty, then.
Who's the champion
at slug swallowing?
Simba again.
- Cricket crunching?
- Simba.
- Grub gulping?
- Maggot munching?
- Still Simba.
Snail slurping?
Oh nobody.
We never had a snail eating
contest before.
I don't think
this is such a good idea.
I told you this wasn't
such a good idea.
Thus did the pupil
surpass the teacher.
You've been hanging around...
with the monkey again,
haven't you?
Our Simba is growing up.
Is this the little boy
I carried?
When did he grow to be so tall?
Wasn't it yesterday
When he was small?
Sunrise, sunset
Swiftly fly the years
One season following another
Laden with happiness
And tears
So, you see, that's why
they call it a dung beetle.
Ew. You don't say.
And yet still so tasty.
Oh, yeah,
and they're my favorite, too.
Just what the doctor ordered.
Yep. After a long day
of doing nothing...
it's good to kick back.
Three pals and no worries.
What more could you want?
I'm bushed.
Think I'll turn in
for the night.
I'm out.
Right behind you.
You're killing me.
Timon, it's your turn
to say good night.
Good night.
Sleep tight.
Dream of bedbugs tonight.
You got to admit...
we had a pretty good thing
going there.
We could've gone on
like that forever.
Except for one
teeny weeny little thing...
we forgot to count on.
Nala?
- How did you...
This is a disaster, Pumbaa,
a disaster, I tell you.
You mean because they've
finally found each other...
like two soul mates
joined across the years...
by the bonds of true love?
Sweet, innocent little Pumbaa.
She's going to put a stake
right through the heart...
of our hakuna matata.
Oh, then I guess
we ought to do something.
And I know just what it is.
Pumbaa, we can't let them
feel the love tonight.
Can you feel the love tonight?
That's so romantic.
The peace the evening brings?
Well, that worked like a dream.
It did?
Sarcasm is a foreign language
to you, isn't it?
Look!
Can you feel the love tonight?
She's making those eyes.
He's smiling that smile.
They're laughing...
and hugging...
and... and...
And if he falls in love tonight
It can be assumed
His carefree days
With us are history
In short, our pal is doomed
That's it, buddy.
We gave it our best shot,
but he's a goner.
Maybe not.
You never give up, do you?
Look.
You don't even know
what I've been through.
- I would if you'd just tell me.
- Forget it.
Fine!
Pumbaa, do you know
what this means?
He can't express
his feelings...
and she has commitment issues?
We won.
We split them up.
And that's a good thing?
He seems to be
taking it kind of hard.
Yeah, I know. Look, I...
But it's the best thing for us.
I mean for him.
Let's go, Pumbaa.
I think this storm's
coming to a head.
Hakuna matata
is safe at last, pal...
because nothing's going
to take our boy away now.
He's gone?
What do you mean, he's gone?
It's just like the baboon said.
The king has returned.
You want me
to go over it again?
Yes, please, but be a dear...
and just skip to the part
about Simba,
not that your childhood
wasn't fascinating.
OK, look, Simba's
the rightful king...
but after he disappeared...
Scar proclaimed
himself the king...
and formed an alliance
with the hyenas.
Poor Simba,
the treachery, the villainy...
the sheer indescribable horror.
Blah, blah, blah.
Why is she toying with us?
Oh, this crazy chick
is going to eat us.
Simba has to go home
to challenge his uncle...
and reclaim his
rightful place as king.
Don't you get it?
Simba needs us, now!
He needs us?
Then he shouldn't have left us!
If he wants to run off
to be "His Highness"...
well, I say don't let
the branches hit you...
on the way out.
Leave hakuna matata
to someone who appreciates it.
But, Timon, it's not really
hakuna matata without Simba.
What's gotten into you?
Not hakuna matata?
That's crazy talk,
crazy talk, I tell you.
Nothing's changed here.
We had hakuna matata
before Simba...
and we've still got it now.
We got to go help
our friend, Timon.
Et tu, Pumbaa?
You're just going to walk away,
give up on all this?
What happened to "friends
stick together to the end"?
I was about to ask you
the same thing.
I got everything
I ever wanted right here.
Now, this is more like it...
Elbow room.
Oh, boy, oh, boy, oh, boy.
Hakuna matata
What a wonderful phrase
Ain't no passing craze
It means...
No worries.
You. No, no. Don't say a word.
I know what
you're going to say.
Did you find hakuna matata?
Well, yes, I did.
Thank you very much.
And I am happy.
Happy, happy,
deliriously happy.
I see.
Happy, is it?
So, if you're so happy,
why do you look so miserable?
Miserable, you say?
Why should I be miserable?
Oh, I don't know.
Maybe my two best pals...
in the world deserted me.
They've... they've headed off
on some heroic mission.
My friends are gone.
And my hakuna matata
went with them.
Would you mind?
Ay!
Thanks. I'm glad
we had this talk.
My work here is done.
Friends stick together
to the end.
What was with the running?
If you can call that running.
I was giving you time
to catch up.
Aw, you big lug.
Hop on, buddy.
We got a fight to catch.
Let's whip some grass.
This is the stuff
of legends, an epic struggle...
the place
where heroes are born.
Pumbaa, this could be
our finest hour.
Luau!
If you're hungry for a hunk
of fat and juicy meat
Eat my buddy Pumbaa
here because he...
Let's just
cut to the chase, shall we?
Oh, sure.
What the...
I love the smell of Pumbaa
in the morning.
Hey, hey, hey,
move your tush, honey.
Ma? Uncle Max?
- Oh, Timmy!
- Timon?
What are you doing here?
Looking for you.
Aw. Mommy's here.
Well, let me introduce you
to my best friend.
Pumbaa, Ma, Uncle Max.
Ma, Uncle Max, Pumbaa.
Look, there's Simba,
and that must be his uncle Scar.
Oh, good, they're
talking things out...
which is how it should be.
You know, I have a feeling...
everything's going
to be just fine.
On the other hand...
the hyenas are up there
protecting Scar.
What do we do?
Well, I've got a plan.
How can we help?
Ma, Uncle Max,
you're going to dig a trap.
We're going to need...
dare I say it?
Tunnels, lots and lots
of tunnels.
And, Pumbaa, you and me...
we've got to get those hyenas
away from Simba.
And lure them into the trap?
Ho ho! Nothing gets past you.
Come on, Pumbaa, let's ride.
Something's different
about Timon.
You think?
He's wearing a dress!
Hey, Pumbaa.
What do you call a hyena
with half a brain?
Beats me, Timon. What?
Gifted.
They're talking about us.
For your last meal,
you're going to eat those words.
Ma, I think we got
their attention.
Not yet. Keep stalling.
OK.
You got to be kidding me.
Now, Ma?
Need more time, honey.
Freestyle.
Encore, encore.
No, no, no.
You mean entree, entree.
No, you right.
Let's just eat them.
Is it ready yet, Ma?
Not yet. Keep stalling.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
Hold on a second.
Timon? What are you doing?
Shenzi Marie Predatora
Veldetta Jacquelina Hyena...
would you do me the honor
of becoming my bride?
I don't think so.
Shenzi Marie, please.
I know what you're thinking.
We're too different.
It'll never work.
What will the children
look like?
That violates
so many laws of nature.
Listen to me. The problems
of a couple of wacky kids...
like us don't amount
to a hill of termites...
in this nutty
circle of life thing.
If not now, when?
If not me, who?
I'm lonely.
Can I be your best man?
I say we skip the wedding
and go straight to the buffet.
Now?
Sure, if you're ready.
Now, Max, now!
Hyenas in the hole!
I need help. It didn't work.
Hey, it works for me.
What are we going to do?
What?
Timon, no!
Let's get 'em.
I'd say Scar is down and out.
We did it! We did it!
Where's Timon? Where's my baby?
He's hurt! Oh, no!
Oh, no! He's dead! Or worse!
We got to find him.
We've got to find him.
It's OK, Ma.
Oh, please. It is not OK!
Don't you tell me it's OK!
Timmy!
My son...
the hero.
You missed a spot.
That's so beautiful.
Choking. Not breathing.
I couldn't have done it
without you guys.
That's our boy.
I promised myself
I wasn't going to cry.
You've really come
a long way, Timon.
Did you find what
you were looking for?
I found a place that was
beyond my wildest dreams...
but it still wasn't home.
Let's go home, Ma.
Welcome to our new home,
a predator-free environment.
I got to hand it to you, Timon.
This place has everything.
Well, now that
we're all here, it does.
Crane...
spreads its wings,
turns with dainty hands.
Dig a tunnel, dig, dig a tunnel
We're never gonna dig
another tunnel
Dig a tunnel, dig, dig a tunnel
Never gonna hyena come
Sing the praises of great Timon
The greatest meerkat
we've ever known
Never dreamed
he'd help Simba shine
Proved it's cool
to hang out with swine
Accidentally saved the day
Planned it so
it would look that way
Brought us out of
the dirt and sand
Brought his family
to the promised land
Sing the praises of great Timon
Greatest meerkat
we've ever known
Well, that's it,
the big wrap-up,
the happy ending...
the grand finale.
It's over already?
Well, Pumbaa, that's
the thing about endings.
They come at the end.
Can we watch it again?
Pumbaa, we just saw it.
Maybe tomorrow.
Hey, what are you guys doing?
You didn't tell me
you were watching the movie.
I want to watch, too.
Ma, we just finished.
Show's over.
Well, you're just going
to have to rewind it.
Ma!
Uncle Max,
we're going to watch the movie.
Oh, no!
Hey, I brought extra butter.
Hey, you guys
are watching the movie?
Any story worth telling
is worth telling twice.
- What the...
- Oh, excuse me.
- Excuse me.
- Get out of the way.
Who is this crowd?
Hey, down in front!
Gawrsh!
Aloha!
Watch it!
OK, buddy, you win.
Sure you don't mind?
Hakuna matata.
Sorry.
Timon...
I still don't do
so well in crowds.
Quick before the hyena come
All we do is dig...
so we can hide
and hide so we can dig.
Dig
All we do is dig...
so we can hide
and hide so we can dig.
Dig
Dig a tunnel, dig, dig a tunnel
Keep a-digging, never get done
Quick, before the hyena come
Dig a tunnel, dig, dig a tunnel
Keep a-digging, never get done
Quick, before the hyena come
Hakuna matata.
All we do is dig...
so we can hide
and hide so we can dig.
Dig
Hakuna matata.
Quick, before the hyena,
hyena, hyena come
Dig a tunnel, dig, dig a tunnel
Keep a-digging, never get done
Quick, before the hyena come
Can you dig it?
I can dig it
Oh, yeah
Sure is memories
living in the grass
Grazing in the grass,
it's a gas
Baby, can't you dig it?
What a trip just watching
as the world goes past
Grazing in the grass,
it's a gas
Baby, can't you dig it?
There are so many
groovy things to see
While grazing in the grass
Grazing in the grass,
it's a gas
Baby, can't you dig it?
Flowers with colors
Making everything
out of sight in the grass
Grazing in the grass,
it's a gas
Here we go
The sun beaming down
between the leaves
Grazing in the grass,
it's a gas
Baby, can't you dig it?
And the birds
Darting in and out of the trees
Grazing in the grass,
it's a gas
Yeah, yeah
And everything here is so clear
You can see it
And everything here is so near
You can feel it
And it's real
So real, so real
So real, so real, so real
Can you dig it?
I can dig it, he can dig it,
she can dig it
We can dig it, they can
dig it, you can dig it
Oh, let's dig it
Can you dig it, baby?
I can dig it, he can dig it,
she can dig it
We can dig it, they can
dig it, you can dig it
Oh, let's dig it
Can you dig it, baby?
We, let's dig it
I can dig it, he can dig it,
she can dig it
We can dig it, baby,
everybody, let's dig it
Can you dig it, baby?
The sun beaming down
between the leaves
And the birds
Darting in and out of the trees
Everything here is so clear
You can see it
And everything here is so near
You can feel it
And it's real
So real, so real
So real, so real, so real
Can you dig it?
Oh, yeah
I can dig it, he can dig it,
she can dig it
We can dig it, they can
dig it, you can dig it
Oh, let's dig it
Can you dig it, baby?
I can dig it, he can dig it,
she can dig it
We can dig it, they can
dig it, you can dig it
Oh, let's dig it
Can you dig it, baby?
I can dig it, he can dig it,
she can dig it
We can dig it, they can
dig it, you can dig it
Oh, let's dig it
Baby
I can dig it, he can dig it,
she can dig it
We can dig it, they can
dig it, you can dig it
Oh, let's dig it
Everything here is so clear
You can feel it
I can dig it, he can dig it,
she can dig it
We can dig it, baby,
everybody dig it
It's Timon-a-rama time!
I've never been the type
You'll have a perfect home
To form a hole and hide
When old hyenas come
Above the meerkat role
Where it's a shooting scene
In some organic hole
Then you won't have to fear
And all that circle rot
Is just a cunning plot
For comin' to the crunch
I ain't nobody's lunch
Get on the roundabout
This isn't a diversion,
it's a monkeyshine
I ain't asking for a lot
But what is mine is mine
You never want to argue
with a chorus line
That's all I need
That is all he needs
I'm begging please
Begging please
That is all
I
Need
That is all I need
Someone needs to stop Clearway Law.
Public shouldn't leave reviews for lawyers.