Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
911, what's your emergency?
Hello. This is Centurion Trust.
We have a robbery in progress
at 23 Forsythe Place.
So it's in progress right now?
They're in the building. They're taking
hostages, so as soon as you can.
Sir, are you in a safe place?
Drop the phone.
Sir?
Hello?
All right, you're all set. Thank you.
I hate sirens.
You never know if it's your
own damn house on fire.
Miss Reece?
I'm Chris Kirkham. Come on in.
Hi.
What can I do for you today?
I got another deposit for ya.
Okay.
Thanks for waiting out there.
I appreciate your patience.
We're just crazy after the holiday weekend.
It gets to be a bit of a circus around here.
- My resume.
- Great, thanks. You can take a seat.
All right, let's see what we got here.
And is that all?
Got any marshmallows?
I'm sorry, marshmallows?
Yeah, there's a fire.
We can just skip the marshmallows.
Maybe you might want to meet me
for happy hour when you close?
You are too sweet.
Sounds like somebody got started
a little bit early already on happy hour.
I like to beat the crowds.
All righty, you are all set.
Have yourself a nice day.
Babe, just because it happened once,
doesn't mean every time I meet a woman...
- ...it's gonna happen again at the bar.
- Sorry, next window.
- How may I help you today, ma'am?
- You may help me today.
These bounced.
Insufficient funds.
That's quite impossible. I made
a big deposit yesterday, so fix it.
- Let me see what I can do.
- Yeah, you do that.
You sure you want to brave it
out there, Detective?
Hey, it looks like it's getting kind
of serious out there, you might...
...make sure everybody gets out okay.
Looks like you've worked with some
of the big guys. That's great.
You probably know the drill.
Okay, so a little bit of time
since your last position.
What did you get up to there?
I'm sorry, can you repeat the question?
Just a little bit of time
between your last position...
...what did you get up to there?
What happened?
I traveled.
I spent some time in Mexico with
my church group teaching English...
...and fell so in love with it that I ended
up just staying there for about a year.
- That's fantastic.
- Yeah. It's great.
The only reason I came back was because
someone in my family got really sick...
...so I'm looking for a job
to start as soon as possible.
Fair enough. Okay, gotcha.
I hope they're okay.
Okay, great, well, listen...
...this checks out, we do a background check.
It's just a formality,
but they're pretty thorough.
- You expect any red flags there? Any issues?
- No.
So what happens is, you guys charge a fucking
fee for every single check that I bounced.
I get charged. Okay?
So then what happens is...
hold on. Let me talk.
What happens is I get charged a fee for
every fucking check here that bounced...
...then the people that I paid,
they charge me...
...and the fucking circus
happens all over again.
- Yes, ma'am. I understand.
- I really don't think you do understand...
...because now that my account's
in the red, what?
You're going to charge me another penalty?
Yeah, that's what you guys fucking do.
- So let me ask you something.
- Okay.
When the bank fucks up,
who pays Redd's penalties?
- Ma'am, if you would watch your language...
- You charge me for every goddamn mistake.
How does anybody get ahead in fucking life?
You know what I mean?
- Let me ask you a fucking question, Mary.
- Yes?
Who pays when you make a fucking mistake?
- How'd the marshmallow line work for you?
- Fuck you.
Well, listen, that leaves just timing.
What's your timeline like?
The truth is we have...
...three tellers spots open now.
I can't seem to keep them, so...
Can I ask why?
- If you don't mind me asking.
- No, I understand.
I still want the job.
I mean, it's silly, but since you asked...
...it's an old building and...
...some people get spooked
in here, and they...
...think they hear and see things.
And so, I swear to God, it's just...
...people talking and getting in their head.
- Please? Curb your language.
- Yes. Please. Excuse me.
- If you'll give me your social security...
- Hold on. Hold on.
- Let me talk to a manager.
- Absolutely.
Let's do that. Let's get
a fucking manager around here.
There's a fucking manager here.
There's gotta be some fucking manager here.
Okay. What seems to be the issue?
She had these checks returned.
I've looked her up.
Are you the manager
or just a financial service specialist?
I am Susan, the head teller,
and I'm just trying to see...
- ...if I can help you here, okay?
- The head teller?
Oh, great, here comes the cavalry.
I can't explain it, but...
...in fairness, it's probably worth
telling you that in advance, but...
...I don't make anything of it.
You know, do you spook easily, Miss Reece?
- No, sir. Not me.
- Okay, good. That settles that.
The only thing that spooks is a bad loan.
- That's funny.
- I'm perfectly calm.
- So you checked the record?
- I just want my fucking money.
Okay, ma'am, you don't have
an account with us.
Well, that's a fucking mistake. Check again.
- Is there a problem?
- No. There's no problem at all actually.
- Hey, your shitty life is not my problem.
- Sir, can you let us handle this, sir?
I'm gonna need you to step outside.
Where's the fire? Is it close? Are we safe?
We just need everybody to stay inside.
- Ma'am, please.
- Hey, hey, hey, hey. Don't touch me.
Get her the fuck out of here.
Please, do something about this.
- Keep your hands off me.
- I need you to step outside with me.
Hands behind your head.
Unit 4919, I'm at Centurion Trust Bank.
23 Forsythe Street. I've got a 29 in progress.
Get down.
Fuck that.
Back up, now!
Yeah, that's right. Give me your phone.
Give me your phone.
Eyes to me. Back, back, back, back.
Back up!
Keep your eyes on me at all times.
Unit 4919, is the situation under control?
You say code 21, this ends bad for everybody.
Situation under control.
- Good work.
- Unit 4919, please repeat.
Yes, this is 4919.
Situation under control. Took care of it.
Let's check it out real quick.
I'll be right back.
This is Centurion Trust, we have
a robbery in progress at 23 Forsythe.
Could you please send the police.
In progress right now.
They're taking hostages,
so as soon as you can.
Out now. Safety deposit vault. Let's go.
You want to survive today?
Let's go. Let's go.
Are you sure you want to do this, honey?
Okay, I did a background
check too, Mr. Kirkham.
You live in a nice house
with a white picket fence,
you've got two boys, 7 and 8,
and another on the way.
You make a decent amount of money,
and you've got a pretty enough wife...
- ...so you have no reason to play hero.
- Okay.
- I need you to work with me. Okay?
- Okay. Okay.
- All right?
- Okay, understood.
What are you doing? What are you doing?
- We said don't hurt anybody.
- You fucking hurt somebody.
- I did it to save you.
- I know, thanks. Awesome.
- Using fucking brass knuckles like that.
- I don't have time to be a good person.
- We're either doing this or we're not. Chill.
- We just don't hurt anybody, okay?
- Well...
- That's what... that's what we agreed.
- All right?
- All right. Fine.
Fine.
- I need you to tell them to remain calm.
- Understood.
You remain calm,
the orders are clear, do nothing.
Sit quietly. Say your prayers in your head.
- Do you understand? Okay? Thank you.
- Understood. Okay.
- Sir, please.
- Don't talk. Do it.
It's gonna be okay, Mary.
Good girl. Come on.
Come on, let's go. Come on.
Come on. Come on.
You want me to do this or not?
You're okay. Don't be nervous.
Why so nervous? Why so nervous?
Good girl. Good girls.
Stop.
Just stop.
Get the code. You're doing very well.
Now, stop being so self indulgent,
or I kill the cop.
Sir, stay still. Stay still.
Stay still. Fuck.
Goddammit. Do it right.
Okay. Okay. Okay.
What is so fucking difficult?
Come on. Come on. Come on.
Where the fuck is the rest of the money?
Are you telling me there's all there is?
You're fucking useless.
- You got it?
- Come on, let's go!
- How much?
- Maybe a little over $70,000.
I mean, there might be $5,000
or $10,000 in the teller's station.
- How much? What'd he say?
- 70 grand.
Clear.
All right, that's not enough. Let's go.
Come on, Vee, let's get out of here.
What do you mean? Are you fucking kidding?
- Let's go. Let's go. Let's go.
- What? Let's go? Fucking leave?
We're not gonna leave.
You're not fucking going anywhere.
Come on, we came here for him.
We came here to do this for him...
...and we're not leaving until we do it.
Do you understand that?
- Yes, I understand.
- Okay, then what's the problem?
Does that look like half a million
dollars to you? No. 70 grand.
Should we just go and rob some more fucking
banks or should we just finish this out?
- We leave while we still can.
- We're not leaving and going anywhere.
Let go. Let go.
Look at me. Look at me.
Let's get out of here, okay?
Don't worry, I want to kill you too, bitch.
You've always been a fucking bitch.
- Let's go.
Let's go. All that we planned out.
Drop your fucking gun.
I've got brothers I've got to answer to.
We ain't going anywhere without the money.
You put your gun down, motherfucker.
Please, please, please.
Please, can we not leave without the money?
I hate when you get stubborn like this.
Leah, this isn't a military op, okay?
- We're not leaving without the money.
- Vee, Vee, look at me. There's no money.
- It's a fucking bank. There's always money.
- Then where's the money?
If you know where the money is,
show me where the money is.
Look, I can tell you where the money is.
- I can help you.
- Who the fuck are you?
I'm the assistant manager.
I know this bank inside and out.
First, you're going to
want to disable the alarm.
- What alarm?
- Behind the tellers' windows.
It was set off because you
didn't follow protocol.
You have three minutes, maybe four.
- Then what? What happens?
- Till the police know that you're here.
- Can you please take this bag off.
- No.
- I'm having trouble. I have asthma.
- It doesn't matter. Tell me more.
Look, at 5:20, all transactions
need to be reconciled...
...and synced with the database.
We need to verify the cash...
...lock all the drawers in the safe
and the manager needs to type his pin in.
If that doesn't happen,
the alarm is triggered at exactly 5:20.
Now, the manager can do it or me.
Take the bag off.
Who the fuck are you?
I can... I can help you.
You just have to promise me
that no one else is going to get hurt.
No, you listen to me, all right?
You do as we say, we won't hurt you
and that's it. There's no negotiating here.
The signal is sent, the police come.
It's as simple as that. No one wins.
- That's true.
- Hold on.
All right, no one's going to get hurt, okay?
Get the pin. Let's do this.
Leah.
- So we good?
- Yeah. Yeah, we're good.
Where's the rest of the money?
It's down below. That's where... that's
where the real money is, in the old vault.
- You can get in there?
- It's a private vault.
It's part of the old bank.
We just house it. It's antiquated.
It's not even on the grid.
- We're not prepared for this.
- We're in pretty good shape, I gotta say.
We got the cobalt drill bits,
we got the welder for the back way out.
- Perfect. Then we're going in.
- Depends on the vault. How old?
It's 60, 70 years.
- We don't have time.
- Bullshit.
The whole fucking warehouse is up in flames,
everything is locked up, we got time.
How much money's in it?
$6 million, cash.
- $6 million?
- Bullshit.
No, it's there. The end of
the basement hall, there's a door.
The key is... here, this is it.
The key.
We're in.
The fire we set is going to keep those
cops busy. I'll go down with Kramer.
I'm gonna check it out and make sure
we're good. I'll be back in five minutes.
Time me. You stay up here,
and you keep a lookout...
...and then Michael goes down next
to cut the hole in the water main.
They're not on to us.
Haven't heard anything. We're good.
Supervise the whole operation
from up on high.
Please watch Mr. assistant bank manager,
make sure Cyrus doesn't fucking kill anybody.
In 30 minutes, we will slip out
the back door with $6 million cash.
It's fucking perfect.
Vee, if you can hear me, look at
the cameras behind you. 4 o'clock.
All right.
- Let's go.
- Yeah, right.
I can tell you're a decent man.
You don't know me.
Please, sir.
- Stop talking.
- Please?
- Shut up, let me handle this.
- Sir, stop talking.
If you would've done your job from the
beginning, we wouldn't be in this shit show.
- Yeah, come on, buddy, let us go.
- Sir, let me handle this.
Let me negotiate.
You had a chance to handle this.
- Just let us all go.
- Stop talking. Stop talking.
Stop fucking talking! Shut up!
What are you gonna do? What are you gonna do?
Congratulations.
Yeah, what? What?
You are the first hostage
who's going to fucking die today.
I have to use the restroom.
I have to use the restroom, and I prefer
not going right here in front of everyone.
Shit. Is that it?
Yeah.
- How the fuck are you getting in there?
- It's a combo lock. It's nothing ugly.
Really?
How long?
- 20 minutes.
- Here.
- Stay on two.
- My favorite.
Start.
X marks the spot.
Fuck.
What the fuck is that?
It's got to be a power surge or something.
Watch him.
Unit 4919, what's your status?
Unit 4919, are you still at 23-47?
Can you untie me?
Can you please take the bag off my head?
Don't move.
You stay right there.
Let's go.
I can't pee when you're
pacing outside like that.
What's that? Let's go. Let's hurry up.
You're making me nervous. I can't pee.
You what?
I can't pee when you're pacing right
outside of the door like that. Please?
I couldn't either.
What's your name?
Susan.
Who's in charge?
Who do you think?
That's the problem.
It doesn't seem like anyone's in charge.
Stop talking.
Oh, fuck. You fuck.
I know that your hand
is being forced right now...
...and I don't know by who or why.
I don't hear you pissing in there.
- You got any sisters?
- Yeah.
Yeah? You love them?
Yeah. I do.
- That's good.
- Are those your sisters out there?
You're not like the others.
You don't want to hurt people.
I know you tried to help that policeman.
I know you're not a bad person.
You know, sometimes you just don't
want to piss off the wrong people...
...no matter what you're trying to do.
What happened?
I stiffed the wrong guys, Susan.
And I owe them a lot of money.
So we're here...
...and my sisters...
my sisters are helping me.
Let's go.
I don't hear any piss.
I can't pee.
Susan, we're not here to hurt anybody.
All right?
Let's go.
You need to see a doctor.
Please, let me...
Please?
I want to help you.
You're a good person.
I know it's not in your heart
to do this, please?
You have my word
you're gonna go home to your family.
I promise you.
Put that on.
All right, let's move.
Move, move, move. Right there. Right there.
Right there. Right there. Go, go, go.
What's going on?
Why are you not cutting the pipe?
I'm going right now.
We need to make sure
that we have a way out of here.
I'm doing it.
Let's go. Come on. Let's go.
What's up?
I'm shaken up right now. Like, do
you think we've overlooked somebody?
Like there's someone in the back I think.
You gotta... Leah says we're falling behind.
I don't fucking care. You hear what I said?
Yeah, I heard you. I don't know.
What the fuck do you think,
we're just gonna like slip out the back...
...with a fucking pile of money, and
everything's just gonna be like dandy again?
You'll buy some big fucking
mansion in Stillwood Park...
...and maybe we'll get some daisies
and lay them on Mama's grave.
And we'll be a big happy family again.
Come on, Aaron. You know I fucking love
Leah to death, but you know the minute...
...the minute this shit's done, she's out.
Like always. She's gonna be out.
As soon as we fucking do this,
she's gonna be gone.
I know it. You know it.
I don't know it.
Who cares?
Hey. So what's up?
- He's doing well.
- Oh, yeah?
He's fine.
Kramer?
Vee?
What's he looking at?
What the fuck are you looking at?
Get the fuck upstairs with the others.
Vee?
There's people down here.
- Come on, dude.
- Kramer.
- Piece of shit.
- Give it to me.
Kramer? Can you hear me?
- Kramer, you all right?
- There's no one down there.
Hey, we can actually see you
on the monitor, but what are you staring?
- What the fuck is he doing?
- I don't know, he's just like...
...what is he looking at?
Is he looking out in the hall?
There's people.
What the fuck? It keeps doing that.
Was it doing that up here?
It was doing that down there.
Did you just fucking see that?
What the fuck just happened?
Is there someone down there?
Have you seen somebody when I wasn't
up here? Was there someone down there?
- I'm going down there. Fucking wake up!
- No one's down there.
Michael, we need you
in the lobby with the keys.
Cyrus, count the hostages.
Michael, we need you up here
with the keys to the basement.
Cyrus, count the hostages.
Hold on.
The fucking door's locked.
Come on.
Michael?
No lies. Short answers.
What the fuck is down there?
I swear to God I don't know.
- Did you set us up?
- No.
- You fucking set us up.
Who the fuck is down there?
Do not fucking lie to me.
Please, I don't want you
to get upset and hurt anyone.
You promised that you wouldn't
hurt anyone if I helped you.
- You're lying.
- No.
Who's calling?
I don't know.
Okay.
Make them go away.
Centurion Trust. How may I help you?
Can I please speak to whoever's in charge?
Hold, please.
They want to talk to you.
Hello?
This is Detective Tom Iger. Hello?
Listen, I'm here to help work this out.
Hello?
Can you tell me if everyone's okay in there.
Let's start there at least.
Hello?
I'm here.
Can you let me know you're hearing me okay?
Listen, I get it.
This was supposed to be simple.
Now, it's a different situation.
If you let them go right now,
we can still make this right.
I will work with you every step of the way...
...and I promise you we will make it
right and no one gets hurt.
This is how this is gonna go, Detective.
You're gonna give me 30 minutes...
...and I'll pretend that you never called and
I'll make sure that everyone gets out okay.
The other option, you push us
and these people will die.
- Do you understand me, Detective?
- I promise you, we can work...
The other option, you push us,
and these people will die.
Somebody has a line to the outside.
It's one of your people.
- That's not possible. It doesn't work...
- Why are you lying to me?
It doesn't make sense. It's not protocol.
Who's your head teller?
Who the fuck is your head teller?
Susan Reynolds. Number seven.
- Thank you.
- Please don't hurt her.
Kramer?
Michael?
Shit. Oh, my God.
Okay, no lies.
Short answers. Did you call the police?
- How could I have?
- Then what the fuck is going on?
Answer the fucking question!
It was... the bank.
The what?
You're not gonna believe me...
...and I don't want you to hurt anyone.
Try me.
There's something down there...
...in the basement.
The vault.
We're not alone.
- Okay. Okay.
- I'm telling you the truth.
Who's down there?
No one goes down there, not even security...
...because of what happened back in 1982.
A man tried to rob the bank.
Someone got a line out.
The man, he was deranged.
He held them hostage for days.
No food, no water...
...he demanded transportation, a way out...
...but the police, they kept stalling,
and then he... he snapped.
He made them shoot each other,
starting with the bank manager.
- He dies.
- I can't.
Or I kill two more and you.
Do it.
Now!
The ones that got away, he hunted them down.
One was executed in the depository...
...another one, a desk clerk,
a young woman...
...was found by the basement boiler.
They kept finding bodies.
Some had been burned alive in the vault.
They all died. Every one of them.
And they never caught the man,
no body, nothing.
Gone. No one saw his face,
no one knew who he was.
You think something like that
just goes away with a paint job?
It's still here. Ask anyone who's been
here, and they'll tell you the same.
Something is still down there...
...in the basement in the old bank.
That was good. That was really good.
I felt like I was there.
The man in the mask.
He just snapped? I don't like ghost stories.
You can make this different.
You can walk out that door right now...
...and you can make this right.
This is 120 volts.
And I'd be lying if I said
this wasn't gonna hurt...
...and I wasn't gonna enjoy it.
What are you doing to her?
Why is she on the floor?
You've...
Okay.
Michael? Michael?
Michael.
We had one rule.
One. Fuck!
The cops are outside.
We need to get out of here.
Don't fucking touch me.
We had one fucking rule.
Okay.
What happened?
Kramer's dead.
What?
He took this drill bit
and put it to his head.
He's dead.
Something's going on here.
Something's not right about this place.
I'm... I'm sorry about this.
You've always been there for me.
We're gonna get out of here.
I swear to God,
we're going to get out of here.
There's five times more where that came from.
- What are you guys doing up here?
- Michael says Kramer's dead.
- What?
- Kramer's dead.
- He's not.
- The cops are outside.
They just called. They know we're here.
- Cops are here?
- Yeah.
So.
Fuck that.
Okay, all right, we just go back
to the original plan then. We're good.
We'll be home free.
This doesn't make any sense.
Something's not right. These bills...
...these bills are all from the same year.
These are all from 1982.
It's all from 1982.
- Every bill is from 1982.
- No, it's not.
Every single bill.
Who cares? It's money.
Isn't that what you want?
- Isn't that what this is about?
- Vee! Listen to me for a minute.
- This doesn't make any fucking sense.
- You're losing it, and you're losing it.
- This has triggered some stuff in your brain.
- Vee!
Are you coming at me again? 'Cause I'm not
gonna deal with it. I'm not dealing with it.
You fucking ruined my life.
Is that... are you good yet?
Is money going to make you happy?
You owe me. You don't give a fuck
about anybody but yourself.
You're going to walk away as soon
as we're fucking done, right?
Am I right? I'm usually right about you,
and how much you have hurt me...
...and this fucking family.
If you would just say
you're fucking sorry. Can you?
Can you say you're sorry?
- You owe me. You fucking owe me.
- Get down.
Crazy bitch.
- What the hell is happening?
- I don't know.
But your window just blew out.
What are you going to do?
You're the only one thinking straight,
so what are you going to do?
What? I don't fucking know.
We're gonna get the fucking money
and get out of here. The plan.
- I'm telling you, she's losing it.
- I know.
She's going to crack.
Okay? I don't trust her.
Neither should you. I've seen this before.
I know how it ends. People are
gonna die unless you do something.
No, they're not.
No one's gonna die.
Not even you.
- What's their next move?
- I don't know.
- Why the fuck are they shooting at us?
- Tell me right fucking now.
- I don't know. It doesn't make any sense.
My guess is...
...it's a mistake.
- Are you fucking kidding me?
- No. No.
It's a mistake.
Emotions are as high out there
as they are in here. There's...
...confusion, miscommunication.
You assumed they're organized out there.
I guarantee you they are not organized.
There are probably 3 different departments
all vying for command, Police, FBI, ATF.
Who the hell knows. You don't know
who's in charge and neither do they.
Why would they do that?
It's not a strategic move.
- Unless...
- Unless what?
Unless they're trying to isolate you.
They need to see movement, good faith.
How?
- Release a hostage. It'll buy you time.
- No fucking way.
The only way to save yourself
is to end this peacefully.
Do you think I want to be here?
I'm a hostage just like you.
Please.
Help me.
- What the fuck is that?
- An outgoing call.
Hello. This is Centurion Trust.
We have a robbery in progress at 23 Forsythe.
Please send the police.
In progress right now.
They're in the building.
Can you describe the assailant?
They're taking hostages, so as soon...
Hey.
Please, don't hurt me. Please.
No, no, no, no, nobody...
nobody's gonna hurt you.
What's your name?
Samantha.
- Samantha Campbell.
- What happened to you, Samantha?
My ankle, I think it's broken.
Yeah?
You're not one of them, are you?
What do you mean? I'm not one of who?
Michael!
- What are you doing, Detective?
- Listen to me.
We spotted what we thought was a civilian
in distress, and an order was given.
But you have my word. We're standing down.
We don't want anyone to get hurt.
Including you. You have my word on that.
Do you have any idea who you're dealing with?
I can only control these guys for so long.
Same as me. So you gotta
give us something to work with.
Okay.
Okay. I'm gonna give you
something to work with.
Michael?
Where are you?
Michael!
Right now, there are hostages at gunpoint.
If anything happens to me, two of them die.
- Do you understand?
- I hear you loud and clear.
We're not going to let that happen, okay?
We're going to work through this.
Who called?
We never received any phone calls.
I fucking heard the call. Who called?
We got something on the radio.
It was garbled. It sounded like trouble.
That was it. No phone call.
Get out of here.
Go.
Wait.
Hello. This is Centurion Trust.
We have a robbery in progress at 23 Forsythe.
Please send the police.
In progress right now.
They're in the building.
They're taking hostages,
so as soon as you can.
Did you hear it?
Michael? Hey, come on.
- Michael, I'm serious.
- Look at me. Look at me. Hey, listen.
This hallway, to the right,
there's a first door to the water main.
There's a big hole. Everything's ready. Just
hop in there, and you get out of here, okay?
When we get out of here, we're going to do
everything we wanted to do, all right?
- Where the fuck are you going?
- Look at me.
Michael?
- What? Look, I'm serious.
- I'll see you soon, all right?
Come with me. Please.
- I'll see you soon.
- Michael, I'm serious. Come on.
Alright.
Shit. Jesus.
Holy shit.
Fuck.
Now they have to come in.
The police, they have no choice.
Please, you have to let them go.
- Go.
- Maybe I was wrong about you.
Go.
Hey. Hey.
Hey, come on. Get up.
Hey!
Don't go down there.
Come on. You're gonna be okay.
Come on. Let's go. Let's go.
Leah!
Keep moving. I'll be right behind you.
Michael!
No.
- You take care of your sister.
- I'm not leaving without you.
Go!
It's gonna be okay.
Police are investigating last night's
armed robbery and arson...
...of the Centurion Trust Bank.
According to a statement released
by the department this morning...
...at about 5:15 p.m., police responded
to a call from inside the bank...
...where six employees and one patron
were being held hostage at gunpoint.
Bank employees described five bank robbers...
...three white males, two white females.
The robbers were armed.
The bank employees were transported
to Grant Hospital...
...where they were treated
for injuries and were later released.
The robbers are all believed to have died
in the fire, authorities have said.
The forecast, plenty of sunshine
through today...
- I heard on the radio...
- They're saying that we're dead.
What was that?
What did you see down there?
Because I know what I saw. We were attacked.
By the police.
No, it's not the police.
Come on, tell me, you saw.
I don't know what I fucking saw,
all right? I saw you hesitate...
...when we were supposed to be leaving
and the cops were trying to fucking kill us.
And I saw the vault,
and I saw that it was empty...
...'cause someone went down there and
cleared it out. So where's the money?
Where is the fucking money, Leah?
Where's Michael?
Wait, you were with him. You didn't...
you didn't take care of him?
- He wouldn't come with me. I tried.
- Where is he?
He's dead, Vee.
Don't touch me.
This guy that you're talking about. He's not
showing up on any of the camera footage.
None of the cameras, he's not there.
He's not anywhere to be found.
- What are you saying?
- I'm saying it just doesn't add up.
You know this bank inside and out,
vault's customers throughout the years...
...and yet, you don't
recognize this individual.
I've got six positive IDs...
...six hostages, but you're
telling me that there's seven.
I thought this was just a de-briefing?
Am I a suspect now too?
They took your radio, your firearm.
Any shred of dignity you had left...
...well, I guess you didn't,
because they took that too, right?
- Why did you get special treatment?
- What treatment?
I was a hostage. I barely made it out.
You got your own room. You were
the only hostage that was let go.
- How old was he?
- I don't remember. Forties, maybe.
- Did he say a name? Any names called?
- I don't remember any names.
What were they talking about?
- The vault. And the alarm.
- Could you make out a voice?
He was telling them all the steps they
needed to make to disarm the alarm.
So he did or did not work at the bank?
He must have. He wouldn't know those things.
How the fuck should I know?
Yeah, maybe he worked there.
No, he was not a bank employee.
- Did he say his name?
- He never said his name...
...but I know everybody that's worked
at that bank for the past 10 years...
- ...and I have never seen him there before.
- Are you saying you saw this man...
...but he's not showing up
on any of the bank cameras.
You realize that, don't you?
All the cameras we have,
all the backup systems, he's...
...I mean, he's nowhere to be found.
You've seen employees come and go,
regional managers, auditors...
...yet, you don't know who this guy is?
Hello, this is Centurion Trust.
We have a robbery in progress at 23 Forsythe.
Please, send the police.
In progress right now.
They're in the building, they're taking
hostages, as soon as you can.
That's him.
Where? This guy?
That's not possible.
That's one of the original
hostages from 1982.
What's wrong?
It won't start.
All right, pop the hood.
And when I say crank it, try it.
Okay, try it.
Fuck.
Vee!
Please rate this subtitle at www.osdb.link/qa6h
Help other users to choose the best subtitles