Jump back, baby.
[SQUEAKING]
[GARGLING]
Someone needs to stop Clearway Law.
Public shouldn't leave reviews for lawyers.
[BELCHES]
WOMAN: Fritz, did you go down
and see the welfare people today?
FRITZ: Yeah. They told me
to report someplace tomorrow.
I got it written down
on a piece of paper, I think.
Listen, are you gonna go?
I don't know. Let's fuck.
Then will you go out
and look for a job like you said?
What? [LAUGHING] Did I say that?
Man, oh, man, am I stoned!
How is it a grown man
can spend so much time...
just dreaming about
what he's gonna do for his family?
For Christ's sakes!
Will you come down to Earth?
What we need is the basic staff of life!
Like grub!
I never saw anybody walking around
more stoned than you.
Always stoned!
Where do you get the money
to buy that grass?
Will you tell me?
You and your Acapulco Gold.
You know what that is?
That's shit!
Which is what you are!
You are shit, Fritz!
Here's something you don't know.
Harvey and I made it.
What do you think of that?
We made it, and he's better
in bed than you are.
You know why?
He's hung like a horse.
What about you? You're nothing.
in the living room.
-You're nothing
-in the bathroom.
You're nothing in bed.
You don't even change
the damn roller on the toilet paper.
I'm the one that uses that mostly.
And what about putting the seat down?
Why don't you ever do that?
Why don't you take
that chicken-shit grin off your face?
Fritz! You're a no-good!
How much can a person take?
And why don't you ever
put the goddamn seat down...
when you're through peeing?
You rotten putz, you!
That's all you do is sit around.
I never saw anything like it
in my entire life!
You know what
I would like to do to you?
I would like to take you
and shake you...
until all your teeth
fall right onto the floor...
and then you know what I'd do?
I'd stamp on them, all the teeth...
and I'd make them right into powder.
And then I'd sprinkle the powder
right over your head.
And then I would knock you
right in the goddamn face!
I'd like to pulverize you!
I'd take your nose...
and I'd put it across the room on the wall.
I'd like to knock you into next week sometimes!
This is it, Fritz.
I'm really sore.
Now, I'm really sore.
I am sick to death!
I'm gonna tell you one time and one time only...
so you better listen to me...
because if you don't listen to me now...
I ain't gonna say it again.
I'll go out and get myself a two by four...
and beat your fucking head in!
You are gonna pick up after yourself.
From now on, I'm through picking up after you.
And you will put the seat down
on that goddamn toilet!
I'm telling you one time
and one time only.
You're a no-good bum,
and I've had it with you, Fritz!
I have had it with you!
And let me tell you
something else.
I know you play around.
Don't try to lie to me.
You don't even have a guilty look on your face.
You really don't give a goddamn.
I know that
you're playing around.
Don't think I haven't seen you.
I get telephone calls
from girls.
They call me up.
God knows why they want you.
Don't they know how shitty you are in bed?!
[PASSES GAS]
[SNIFFING]
Hey, man, don't do that.
What? Do what?
You know what I'm talking about.
What the hell are you laying on me, man?
I ain't laying nothing on you, man.
It's what you laid on me.
No need to be crude.
God damn it, you freaking out or something?
Look, Juan, if we can just cash
this welfare check...
we can get us some Rip Bull
or maybe even some muscatel.
Kiss off, dude!
That's your problem.
You ain't got the guts
to admit when you're wrong.
You just passed gas at me, man,
and that's uncool.
Oh, wow.
Don't have the guts to confess
you're a goddamn coward.
You're just like my sister.
Well, you P.R.s are hypersensitive, you know?
I thought you and me were friends.
A little wig out,
I'm a religion now, huh?
A P.R., huh? Nice.
Hey, about your sister, Juan...
does she have big tits?
[CURSING IN SPANISH]
I wish you people would learn
to speak English.
Christ knows we were here first.
It's the only way I talk to a man
who has habits like a pig.
Man, don't be that way.
Let's get some wine
and go see your sister...
and maybe we can get it on.
Beats the hell out of
freezing our balls off, right?
No deal, man.
I can't trust you no more.
I can't let you fuck my sister, you know?
You got no class, man.
You wouldn't let me fuck your sister.
Why should I let you fuck mine?
Listen, your sister is some piece of ass.
I know, man. Yeah.
My sister?
Wow, man, I can't believe that.
Yeah, man, you better believe it.
She was a female creature of tender passion...
of simple earthen charm, you know?
Wow, dude, that's good.
Yeah, you could say that.
Juan, you better get back
in the phone booth again.
I feel a fart coming on.
-[GROANS]
-[LAUGHS]
[PASSES GAS]
[CURSING IN SPANISH]
[CRICKETS CHIRPING]
Check it out.
We done came all the way across town...
done caught busses and cars
and hitchhiked to get here...
then put on our best clothes...
so we can walk in this neighborhood...
so we can get in one of these white houses...
to rip off one of them $400 televisions...
one of them $300 watches...
one of them
Panasonic, rena-sonic...
exto-sonic, plesto-plastic stereos.
With the quadro-flex, modu-lextic...
medu-modula needles and shit...
Big-time shit, man.
I ain't never heard of nothing like that.
You ain't in this community, blood!
That's why we came here,
you know what I'm saying?
You don't know what you doing, man.
I also be doing this big-time
organizing and shit.
You ripping off washing machines
and toilet paper.
[LAUGHING] Unusual odd shit.
Now you know why we here.
OK, now...
we gonna crawl in this here window, all right?
You take the downstairs,
and I'll take the upstairs.
Why is it that I always got
to take the downstairs?
Because you don't like jumping
out of windows, man.
[PUERTO RICAN ACCENT] Shit!
Now, will you cut that out, Fritz?
ROBBER: Give me some skin!
Hey! [COUGHING]
The beauty of cannabis.
ROBBER: And then once we get inside,
get everything--
don't get no washing machines--
-[CREAK]
-then leave.
Somebody's home!
Doesn't it fill you with joy?
ROBBER: Is that cat smoking?
The unfettered exuberance, the lust for life?
It makes you...
Look how he's smoking weed.
-want to drop your phony inhibitions...
-ROBBER: Best dope in town, man.
and love your fellow man?
ROBBER: Look at that chick
with them titties!
Or brother, maybe.
Doesn't it? Huh?
ROBBER: She's Juan's sister.
Don't you kind of see things more clearly, huh?
[INHALES]
-[COUGHS]
-That's right.
-Take a good, long drag, sis.
-ROBBER: That's his sister!
Now breathe in the smoke. Deep.
It'll help clear your sinuses.
[BOTH GIGGLE]
Hey, I feel light-headed.
ROBBER:
That is Juan's sister, man!
He's going to the store!
[COUGHING, LAUGHING]
[LAUGHING]
¡Arriba!
[COUGHING, LAUGHING]
ROBBER: Looks like a feature film,
you know what I mean?
ROBBER: Right on.
[SIGHS]
[CLOCK CHIMING]
[MONKEY CRIES]
-[SIGHS]
-[INHALES]
Will it really expand my...
[INHALES] awareness?
Well, you know what they say...
[INHALES] "Take tea and see."
Doesn't clear my sinuses at all.
[GASPS] Ha ha.
Daddy says you're only good
for getting the papers.
Is that all you're good for, Fritz?
That's some kick, huh?
You know the most interesting thing
about smoking?
It causes excessive perspiration...
and a person has to take off all his clothes.
Otherwise, he can drown to death
in his own juices.
ROBBER: DO WHAT YOU CAN.
ROBBER: THAT'S THE NUT.
Now, this activity
is like artificial respiration.
Smoke some more of this shit.
Fuck them.
If I get up in this pad,
I got the downstairs--
-Hold it in.
-I'll knock it out.
You'd knock it out, you'd what?
I love my brother's friends.
Man, he ought to put a bag
over that ugly bitch's head.
Stick her head in the couch, man.
Before I stick my thing in her...
-Look at them fuck.
-Man, hold up.
Makes me kind of horny, man.
-Yeah.
-Let's rob.
Duck, man. There's a car coming up the driveway.
I bet it's her old man.
[GIGGLING] Fritz.
Is this good for the liver?
ROBBER: COME ON. LET'S WATCH
THIS SHIT GO DOWN.
-Oh, Fritz. That's good!
-ROBBER: Wow!
-Chita!
-ROBBER: That's the ugliest motherfucker.
Daddy!
ROBBER:
Look at that snaggle-toothed...
big, greasy, fucking nasty pig.
Gee, pops, maybe I should
go get the papers, huh?
Papers?! Why, you, you!
Little son of a bitch.
What do you want, pops,
News or the Times?
Pink commie bastard!
Shit.
I guess you killed him, right in the ass.
ROBBER: I guess we can't
rob this pad today, huh?
ROBBER:
We'll come back tomorrow.
My sister was once in psychoanalysis.
She says you're a boy who would fuck his mother.
And what have you done for Ralphie?
Other than to teach him how to masturbate?
And left-handed, no less.
[SCREECHES]
[YAWNING]
[WHEEZING COUGH]
[COUGHING]
[HACKING]
[SIREN]
[WHEEZING, COUGHING]
[HACKING COUGH]
[BELCHES]
[SIGHS]
[CLEARS THROAT]
You must be new around here.
I haven't seen your face before.
My old lady kicked me out of the house.
I've had this streak of bad luck lately...
and she's been making noise
I should go find work.
[COUGHING]
[SNORTS, GAGS]
What'd you say, something about work?
Everybody knows that's what kills a man.
YEAH. [HACKING COUGH]
Starts out with an eight-hour day...
forty hours a week...
and, hell, boy, before you know it...
you're married to some fine-ass woman
and buying a house. [COUGHS]
[COUGHING]
-[GULPING]
-I'll help you.
Ohh. [BELCHES]
Yeah, that's terrible.
Work is terrible.
What the hell do you get for it, anyway?
Jeez, I don't know.
It's just money is all.
It's evil.
I tell you, it's evil.
It all starts from having to work.
Now, if you don't have to work...
why, you don't get any money.
You know what I mean?
It's that simple.
Yeah. That's what
I try to tell my old lady.
She sent my ass down
to the welfare office again...
and those creeps started to hit on me...
about receiving public assistance
for over a year...
-and here was my last--
-[COUGHING]
-[GRUMBLES]
-Are you OK?
It's my last check and all...
and I had failed to find employment again.
It's just too much bullshit, so I split.
It doesn't pay to hit the big time.
No. [CLEARS THROAT] Yeah.
[VIOLENT COUGHING]
Oh, wow.
[SMACKS LIPS]
Well, you got any plans, son?
Oh, yeah.
I figured I'd settle down here.
Get away from all the zipper-heads uptown.
Not get involved
with all the extemporaneous bullshit.
And, hey, by the way, what's your name?
Oh, I'm God. [WHEEZING COUGH]
Wow, man, that is heavy.
You're really God, huh? No shit?
[COUGHING]
[SNORTS]
[GLASS SHATTERS]
-[SNORTS]
-You OK?
I've been God for about three
and a half years now.
A lot of responsibility, you know.
[GLASS SHATTERS]
I'll bet.
Also, I'm black belt karate.
No shit?
Wow, this really blows my mind.
Me, I'm standing here rapping with God.
Far out!
You want to be my assistant?
[LAUGHING] Well...
I might be forced to give up my job.
[SNORTS, GAGGING, SNORTS]
I can't keep busting my ass this here way.
Anyway, I've been into some heavy gear
in one of my lives.
I got nine of them, pal.
I got hung up with the weirdest dude one time...
you could ever imagine.
This guy I'm thinking of was really psycho...
you wouldn't believe it.
[COUGHING]
Jesus.
Wow, God, you really do some weird shit,
you know?
[GRUMBLING]
Make the fucking world in seven days--
try it sometime.
[FRITZ AND WOMEN
CHATTERING EXCITEDLY]
FRITZ: Work your vanilla!
[WOMAN LAUGHING]
[WOMAN SPEAKING GERMAN]
Oh, the Yanks are coming!
[PANTING]
[GERMAN ACCENT] And remember,
your fathers and mothers...
and all of your Fatherland will be watching you.
Envying in the great glory...
for which you have been selected...
you all have promised
to die for the Fuhrer.
Who wants to be next?
Ooh! Oh, Mama!
Mama, was Papa ever like this?
[SPEAKING GERMAN]
[GAS PASSES]
[BOMBS WHISTLING]
Mein Fuhrer, the bombs
have just killed your orderly!
Ah, another orderly gone.
Get me another one!
Order another orderly quickly!
Another orderly quickly!
Another orderly!
Another orderly for the Fuhrer!
Put up an "Out of Orderly" sign!
WOMAN: Harder!
I get excited! Good!
My Lenore!
My liebchen!
[CRYING]
Ohh! Hans! I mean, he was--ohh!
Hans, I'm sorry. I--
Stand aside!
Oh, he was so wonderful!
[LAUGHING] Oh, Hans!
I mean, he was--
My aching swastika!
I thought being a Nazi as all "Sieg, Sieg"...
and "Sieg Heil!"
This is for shit!
I better get my ass the fuck out of here.
War is hell!
[WOMAN LAUGHING] HANS! OH, GOD!
Mein Fuhrer, here are the candidates
for your orderly.
OFFICER: Heil Hitler!
MEN: Sieg heil!
FUHRER: That one!
I want that one!
Him! That's him!
[BOMB WHISTLING]
[EXPLOSION]
[PLANES FLYING]
Excuse me, Fuhrer.
I didn't mean to stare.
What is it? You see something missing maybe?
No, no! Everything's fine...
but you've only got one ball.
Everybody in the Third Reich
has to do without something!
I see.
When the Fuhrer is naked, everyone is naked!
Well, here I am, aren't I? Hi.
Imbecile. Imbecile.
Don't you know what is expected of you now?
What? I think you dropped something.
What? I dropped something?
I put the soap in your hand, you see...
and you seem to have let it go.
Dropped it, like...
almost like you weren't interested
in washing at all!
I was not conscious of this.
It is simple to see,
Mein Fuhrer.
You're real motivations are blocked here.
Blocked? What is blocked?
It's a new word.
It means what's inside can't get outside.
Some kind of Freudian horseshit.
Oh, inside, can't get out...
You're a nice boy.
[CLACK CLACK]
I'm going to make a confession.
Sometimes, I would like to be a ballet dancer.
Really? No kidding?
I often see myself in the opera.
[CHUCKLING] Oh, wow.
And the people are applauding me!
Well, sure they would.
♪ Lum dum duh diy diy ♪
♪ Diy diy diy diy diy ♪
♪ Dah dum dih diy diy ♪
♪ Diy dih diy dih diy ♪
♪ Dah duh dih diy diy ♪
There you go! You see?
That means this whole number you're doing--
this conquest of the world thing...
[LAUGHING] or whatever it is,
is just to get attention.
Interesting you should say that...
but I am washing, see, now?
So why did I drop the soap?
Well, that, my dear Herr Hitler...
is a question you must ask yourself...
when you wrestle with
the true identity, you know.
I mean, in the dawning of self-awareness...
between you and your pillow, man...
when after the labors of sleepless nights...
you gained the exalted heights
of the altar of truth!
You have insight.
When I see something
I want, I grab it.
Sure, why not?
Ja. Und my stomach doesn't stop
to ask my head if it's hungry.
No, that figures.
By the way, what is your name?
Fritz.
Well, Fritz, you say you once had three balls?
Yeah.
Would you like to try for one?
I don't--Sir!
Listen--OK, OK!
Now, look,
I'm gonna pick up the soap.
I am. Just wait.
I'm gonna bend over now. Just...
I'm gonna--
Hey, watch it, will ya?!
Mein Fuhrer, wait!
Oh, my God, wait!
[HUMPING]
FUHRER: Ich bin der fuhrer!
[PLANE FLYING]
[EXPLOSION]
[MEN CRYING]
FRITZ: Gee, Fuhrer,
now you got no balls.
Mein Fuhrer!
Gentlemen, we can no longer continue.
Ja. War is just a question of balls.
-Ja, balls.
-ALL: Balls.
Goebbels.
Goebbels, are you not...
my most loyal and truthful assistant?
Jawohl, Mein Fuhrer.
Und, did you not invent the slogan
which binds all us Nazis?
Jawohl, Mein Fuhrer.
And what is that slogan?
Death before dishonor.
What an asshole slogan.
-You can always change the slogan.
-[DING]
[DING]
[PINBALL MACHINE NOISES]
You must think of Fraulein Braun.
She needs you.
Ja, think of Eva.
How she would miss you, Adolf.
[CHUCKLES] That's right.
After all, who could take my place?
Sieg heil!
[OBJECT SHATTERS]
[VEHICLE APPROACHING]
I got that Nazi rat bastard...
right between the crack in his ass!
Now how do those sons of bitches
expect to win a war...
when they're out of goddamn uniform, huh?
-Ha ha!
-[GUNSHOT]
I don't have any time to do anything for myself!
I don't even have time
to get myself a new diaphragm!
If you hold it up to the light,
you can see little pinholes.
Fritz, I'm tired of plugging it up
with Chapstick!
Hey. Hey, hey, hey.
[CURSING IN ITALIAN]
Out of my shop.
I won't cash your check...
and there's no such thing
as a refund on those things...
just 'cause you say it don't fit quite right.
But it's never been used, Niki.
I'll even take a prorated refund.
It was used!
Well, only a little, a quickie.
And I bet I know who this was used on, too, huh?
OK, Niki, you're on.
Try to guess who.
Let's see now.
With your filthy taste...
let's see, it must be a fat one, right?
-Yeah, right. Go on.
-[CHUCKLES]
And I just bet she sweat a lot,
and she smell like a goat, huh?
[LAUGHING] Right.
And she's got bad breath, no teeth?
Yes! Go on!
You're getting warmer!
And she's got big, hairy...
goddamn moustache on the top lip!
FRITZ: Oh, you got me, Niki.
You got me nailed, man.
And I'll bet...
that fucking whore been with every guy
on this block, right?
-Right! Niki, you're a genius!
-[LAUGHING HYSTERICALLY]
[BOTH LAUGHING HYSTERICALLY]
Niki, you only left out one thing.
What did I leave out, Fritz?
You know what?
She's got the clap!
[BOTH LAUGHING HYSTERICALLY]
That's right!
How could I skip that?
That's a nice one.
She got to have the clap, right?
She has to.
-Hey, Fritz.
-Shit.
Fritz, I'll tell you something.
You're not so bad, you know?
Maybe I'll cash your check after all.
Hey, Fritz, tell me...
what's this fat whore pig's name, huh?
-What's the broad's name?
-Gina.
-Hey, Fritz.
-What?
That's a-my wife's name.
Gina is my wife's name.
She don't have the clap.
She does now.
Why, you-- [CURSING IN ITALIAN]
You fucking cat,
I rip your balls off!
Get the fuck out of my shop!
Fuck off! You fucking cat!
I kill you!
I fuck you in the ass!
Fritz, man, what's all this noise about, man?
I can hear all the way from the alley.
NIKI: Don't even come here!
FRITZ: Aw, nothing.
Niki can't take a joke.
He takes things too seriously.
It's hard not to around here.
Gets pretty fucking deadly sometimes.
I heard it was better years ago,
you know what I mean?
But, Lenny, things have always been,
more or less...
up-and-down situation.
This street wasn't always a shit-house,
let me tell ya.
And even as far back as the thirties...
there were those who gave and those that took.
Aw, Fritz, but what do I do
with this here thing?
You can have it.
I'm done with it anyway.
When I was back in the thirties...
I was one very sharp continental-type stud.
The only thing we have to fear is...
fear itself.
People must have faith.
Together...we cannot fail.
And it is up to you... to support...
and make it work.
WOMAN:
♪ When you're speakin'
In the last tense ♪
♪ And the things you say
Make no sense ♪
♪ To any other mother's son
But you ♪
♪ And when the past
Is ever present ♪
♪ And your prospects
Ain't too pleasant ♪
♪ There's only one thing left
For you to do ♪
WOMEN: ♪ You got to jump back ♪
♪ When your soul
Is out to riot ♪
♪ Do the jump back ♪
♪ You don't have to
Testify it ♪
♪ Get yourself on back ♪
♪ Back on
That righteous track ♪
♪ Do the jump back ♪
♪ Ooh, try it ♪
♪ Well, you sign up
For the new deal ♪
♪ But still it had
That old feel ♪
♪ You found that you were
Somehow incomplete ♪
♪ So you hunted
With delight ♪
♪ That was over one night ♪
♪ When they found out
What you learned ♪
♪ Down on the street ♪
♪ You got to jump back ♪
♪ When they find out
What you know ♪
♪ Do the jump back ♪
♪ Oh, pack it in and go ♪
♪ You better lose
Your self-control ♪
♪ But you'll never
Ever know ♪
♪ Till you jump back ♪
♪ Oh oh oh oh, yeah ♪
♪ You're a product
Of a dream ♪
♪ So you live it ♪
♪ But that dream
Ain't what it seem ♪
♪ Oh, now, is it? ♪
♪ Well, you went out
On a high stand ♪
♪ Black tie tied
And top hat ♪
♪ But now you say
You've given up that act ♪
♪ No more
Dog-eat-cat existence ♪
♪ No resistance ♪
♪ There's a better way to live
And that's a fact ♪
♪ You got to jump back ♪
♪ When your soul
Is out to riot ♪
♪ Do the jump back ♪
♪ You don't have to
Justify it ♪
♪ So get yourself
On back ♪
♪ Right back on that
Righteous track ♪
♪ Jump back ♪
♪ You just try it ♪
♪ Do the jump back ♪
♪ You got the right track ♪
Hey, putz!
Your idea of helping out
with the gas shortage...
was to stop eating pizza...
and bring home four of your hooker friends...
to sleep with us at night to stimulate heat.
FRITZ: Look, I don't know
how you can own a business...
and not be able to cash...
this miserable pittance
of a welfare check is all.
If I give you all my money...
I'll have nothing left to buy with.
Oh, Christ, then you are in luck, Morris.
Look at this.
Knowing of your love for the unusual...
I've brought you something
you won't be able to resist.
-I know it.
-Resist?
Believe me, I could resist.
Just look at it, Morris--
the design, the gentle contours.
Why, it's almost Louis Quinze
for Christ's sake.
It's disgusting,
It's the type of item that will sell so fast...
you'll be pleading for more
inside of a week, believe me.
[CHEWING PICKLES LOUDLY]
It's been used. I can tell.
What? Used?
By a little old lady.
A one-owner shitter-- and genteel.
That's gentile, you stupid bastard.
Don't get hosteel.
That's "hostile."
You're taking the wrong approach, Morris.
Now, some of my best friends are Jewish.
Do I look like the Chase Manhattan Bank?
You come in here with
out-of-money look in your face.
Look like you got hit in the head
with a foul pitch...
and you want to sell me this.
But with inflation,
the value of a dollar going down...
my expenses skyrocketing...
Why, even this week,
the price of a decent circumcision...
something I shudder to think about.
I agree with you there...
but what's that got to do with my toilet seat?
[MAN SPEAKING ON TV
INDISTINCTLY]
That's the point, my friend.
My old Seder used to say to me...
"Morris, take a pickle.
It's made for eating."
The thing you're holding is made for shitting.
It's simple logic.
You could even be a Rockefeller.
It's tough to find a good pickle.
Socioeconomically speaking,
-[BELCHES]
-you're absolutely correct, but--
Look, Fritz... [HICCUPS]
the pickles are beginning to get to me.
And these days,
a soft stool is too important to me...
for something to quibble,
so I'll make you a deal.
Tell you what I'm going to do.
You give me the seat,
I'll trade for you a bargain.
Where did you get this thing?
Questions--youth, all the time, questions.
Nowadays people don't know an opportunity...
when it smacks them upside of the face.
I think I've been screwed.
With that, you could be
the next man on the moon.
Fuck the moon.
I been further than that once.
That's no big deal.
I'd rather take a shit.
So would I. Give me the seat.
MAN ON TV: I'm going to hit you
on the top of the head.
This should cure you.
Here we go. I say heal!
Heal, Mr. Cobbs, heal!
Through the power vested in me
by God, Jesus Christ...
I'm going to heal you, Mr. Cobb.
ANNOUNCER: Hello, world.
This is the event mankind has been waiting for--
the first man launched to Mars.
MAN: Fritz, I got to tell you
something right out in front.
If it wouldn't be for this fucking cold...
I'd be going all the way to Mars with you.
39 million miles--a drop kick.
But the doc says
I can't fly with this cold.
It's bad for the ears.
He said something about me popping
a drum or something...
-I don't know.
-[SPRAYS BINACA]
-Jeez, I got to get some more Binaca.
Put that in my bring-ups, will you?
Fritz, you know how I hate to bother you...
when you're getting near the pad...
but we got to make a decision
on the Poli-Grip account.
I can see you with a package of five spots...
for the Japanese and Taiwan market.
Incidentally, the residuals will be unreal.
It's eight million yen
for every thirteen-week cycle...
and you don't have to declare it.
You know, there's a whole cult...
of denture-adhesive freaks out there...
just waiting for a leader.
Some of them still got their own teeth.
Am I bothering you with all this, Fritz?
My God, Fritz,
I got to get some air in here.
I feel myself slipping away.
Now, I know you're against charities...
and benefits and freebies...
but hear me out on this one, Fritzie.
There's a nationwide charity telethon
coming up...
the first of next month...
for the further development of all-vegetable...
organically-grown polyunsaturated
Preparation H--
with suntan oil.
Jerry Lewis is going to be there--everybody.
And before you shut me off,
I got to tell you...
the exposure will be sensational for you.
And we might even have a spin-off...
on a new movie that's coming out...
with Frankie Avalon and Annette Funicello...
called "Beach Ball Piles."
Well, Fritz, I see we arrived at the pad...
so this will give you
some things to think about...
on a 39-million mile trip.
And remember, Fritz, sweetheart,
I'd be with you all the way...
it wouldn't be for this fucking cold.
[SPRAYS BINACA]
Hot damn.
That chick wouldn't look bad...
holding up a Hershey's bar, would she?
With nuts.
Ah, freedom of the press.
MAN: Jeez,
I feel sorry for the poor slob.
I wouldn't make that trip
with him with six points.
Hey, Fritz, baby, want to talk to Walter?
Sure. Why not?
WALTER: Fritz, does being the first
to set foot on Mars--
golly--kind of give you goose bumps?
Ahem. Gentlemen,
I've been up and down...
the four corners of this big old world...
and I've seen it all, and I've done it all.
I've fought many a good man
and laid many a good woman.
And I've had riches, fame, and adventure, too.
Yes. I've stood eyeball-to-eyeball with death...
countless times and never, never once squinted.
Oh, I've tasted life to the fullest...
and still my tortured soul cries out--more!
More! Oh, shit!
God, can there be any more?
How do it feel, Fritz?
I mean,
Mars ain't around the corner.
FRITZ: You're so right.
Hey, would you like to discuss this in private?
Gee, you got a lovely pair of eyes.
In private?
Sure. Listen, doll...
I'd kind of like to give you a break.
You know, kind of help pay back...
for what my people did to your people.
Yeah? What kind of a break?
Well, you know, an exclusive-- an inside story.
Fritz, wait a second!
Wait! Come on, what about us?
REPORTER: What about a statement?
Give us a break, man, come on.
[PEOPLE TALKING ON RADIO]
FRITZ: UNH! AHH!
REPORTER: FRITZ!
[LAUGHS] Yeah.
Baby.
[BOTH MOANING]
ANNOUNCER: We interrupt this telecast
of the first flight to Mars...
for a message of real importance.
As chairman of the board
of the Golf Oil company...
with its 13,000 dealers from coast-to-coast...
I want to welcome you all
to this momentous event.
When you drive into one of our Golf stations...
say howdy to the man who polishes your window...
and we'll say howdy right back at you.
At this very minute...
you can look at one of our own
Golf refineries...
pumping away seven days a week,
twenty-four hours a day...
filling your tanks with gasoline.
We at Golf Oil are bringing you this telecast...
in appreciation of the millions
of happy Golf customers...
when they say, "Fill 'er up."
What's that I hear?
[RUMBLING]
MAN: Jeez, look at the money
they put in that rocket.
You could buy time on The Waltons...
for a year with that kind of bread.
[BOTH MOANING]
MAN: You know, I wonder
how you put a deal like that together.
That's fascinating.
[BOTH MOANING]
MAN: We have ignition.
FRITZ: Yahoo-hoo-hoo!
REPORTER: Me, too!
Baby!
-[LAUGHS]
-So unbelievable.
My brother-in-law would like a rocket like that.
[FRITZ AND REPORTER MOANING]
REPORTER: Shit.
MAN: That's fascinating.
Gee, look at that.
Well, there he goes.
When he gets back, we'll make millions.
MAN: Wow.
Jeez, I hope they got that explosion on tape.
It'd be perfect for our forest lawn spots.
MAN ON TV:
Mr. Cobb. Heal, Mr. Cobb.
Yeah. Heal.
Through the power vested in me
by God, Jesus Christ...
I'm going to heal you, Mr. Cobb.
[PERSON BELCHES]
[AIR WHINING OUT OF BALLOON]
[TARZAN YELLS]
[HORNS HONKING, FROGS CROAKING]
[BABY CRIES]
MAN: Let me make one thing very clear--
I am not a crook.
Why don't you climb up off your ass?
Remember I was telling you
you should get to be...
a contestant on Let's Make a Deal?
I'll tell you what.
You dress up like a frog.
You look good in green.
And wear a yarmulke.
I think he likes Jewish people.
[CAT MEOWS]
[SIGHS]
Man, am I hung up, strung out, and uptight.
[DUKE LAUGHS]
Hey. God damn it,
I know that laugh.
[DUKE LAUGHING]
Man, it couldn't be.
[LAUGHS]
Hey, man. You in a bag.
Hey, Duke, is it really you?
No shit.
But I thought you were dead.
I thought they got you.
[LAUGHS]
Fritz, you ain't changed a bit.
You still don't know where it's at.
[LAUGHS]
What are you doing down here, anyway?
I'm looking for the true meaning
of my existence, as usual.
I got tired of the pseudointellectuals...
and the super-hype bullshitters
running the world...
determining my destiny.
You dig it?
And crushing my creative juices?
Now lay the straight line on me.
My old lady kicked my ass out.
That's what I figured.
But you know, Duke...
it's going to be better for all of us, really.
No shit.
Ain't I heard that somewhere before?
That's no bullshit.
There's better days ahead,
I kid you not.
We brothers got some great times
rolling our way, man.
-Now you brothers, huh?
-Right on.
Shit. No telling how black we'll be...
by the time this little chat ends.
Take my word for it. I know.
Hey, Duke, you ever hear of New Jersey?
Sure.
You ever heard of Ray Charles?
Yeah. Hey, and I'll tell you...
you crows are finally going
to come into your own.
You wait and see.
DUKE: Jive sucker come into the ghetto,
talking some stuff.
Ought to cut the jive mother.
CROW: Twenty-five.
Ready, aim, fire!
-[GUNFIRE]
-Twenty-six.
Hey, man, your number's up.
Come on, let's get to this.
But--look, please, sir...
you got the wrong guy, see?
Don't push!
At least let me tell you
the way it happened, fella, huh?
[DING DING DING]
Go over to the White House
and pick up a package.
Yes, sir.
[BELL DINGS]
Mr. President.
You've got to do something.
Believe me, there's nothing to worry about.
Nothing to worry about?
This--what's his name...
Imaku.
Whatever--is suggesting...
that New Africa make a federation with Cuba...
China, Africa, and Northern Ireland.
I never did trust a nigger.
But you voted in favor
of giving them New Jersey.
The final solution to the schwartzen problem...
you said.
And we get rid of the Puerto Ricans...
and you can't get a decent shoeshine...
in the whole of America.
I haven't seen a decent football game
in ten years.
Honduras beat us in the Olympics.
You know what that means?
We have a whole country full of niggers--
angry niggers, right across the river
from New York.
They could fart and destroy Washington.
-[THUD]
-All we have to do...
is keep President
Supreme Jackson in office.
[KNOCK ON DOOR]
Come in.
Mr. President,
I'm from the messenger service.
It's about time.
Now, deliver this to President Supreme Jackson.
In New Jersey?
I mean, New Africa?
Well, that's where he is.
But I heard these crows
don't let whites in their country.
How long have you been...
with the Red Arrow delivery service?
Today's my first day.
I used to be on welfare.
[CRACK]
[OBJECT SHATTERS]
Go to the motor pool and get a car and a pass.
Yes, sir.
Remember, this is important...
to our national security, so don't fail.
I won't fail, sir.
Please. Stop kissing my hand.
-Yes, sir.
-And touching my palms.
-FRITZ: Hey.
-MECHANIC: Can I help you?
I want to see the man in charge.
I'm in charge here.
I came to get a car and a pass into New Africa.
OK, I'll get you a car
and a pass to Niggerville.
This is a rotary engine Mazda.
Them niggers will steal anything they can.
No sense in risking a new car to go over there.
We ain't got anybody to wash 'em up no more.
Here you go.
Thanks.
Come here.
If you're going to New Africa...
I got a wife and kid over there.
They had to go with their people...
when they gave the blacks
New Jersey.
-No shit?
-Could you kind of--
Well, there's a lot of blacks.
You were married to a colored woman?
Shit. That's ten years in the slammer.
Yeah. Look, I don't expect you
to look for 'em...
but if you should happen to see 'em...
will you tell 'em I--
tell 'em I said hi.
[STARTS ENGINE]
MECHANIC:
I wonder if they're still over there?
OK. Your pass is good. Go on.
Oh, hey, how do I find
President Supreme Jackson?
Wave a dollar bill.
Yeah. Thanks.
Yeah. Black is beautiful.
Like they say, huh?
[PARTS CLATTER]
[ENGINE BACKFIRING]
[FRITZ HUMS]
♪ I hears de gentle voices ♪
[LAUGHING]
Hey, man.
-Roscoe, dere, dere.
-What?
That broad, man.
That ugly broad.
Hey, man.
Ain't you going to say hello to your old lady?
-Watch out, now.
-That bitch is too ugly...
for you to say hello to in public.
Shoot. I'd go with her a lot quicker...
than I'd go with your mama.
Shoot. She's so ugly...
your daddy don't even want to go with her.
Shit! Look who's talking.
Shit, if ugliness was electricity...
your mama would be walking in a powerhouse.
Oh, man, dig that.
That's light shit.
Your mama look like ten miles
of bad road, nigger.
Your mama got a face...
that look like it been run over by a bus...
and everybody kept telling
how good she looking till you.
And then--so she's been jumping
in front of buses ever since.
Man, I don't want to hear that.
-Oh, hey, look at that.
-[BRAKES SQUEAL]
Boy, some pair of gazongas there.
That isn't bad. A little young.
But, then, what the hell.
These chicks know where it's at
by the time they're 11 anyway.
[PARTS CLATTERING,
ENGINE BACKFIRING]
[CAR RATTLING]
[PARTS CLATTERING]
[ENGINE DIES]
[TIRE SQUEALS]
[RUMBLES]
[PARTS CLATTER]
How do I get to the Black House?
You take the number twenty bus on the corner.
You do know what a corner is, don't you, honky?
MAN: UHH.
[MUTTERS]
Somebody help.
Help!
Hey, man. Come on, help me, man, please.
Oh, man. What's the matter?
Well, a gang, man.
They robbed--
-Oh, Jesus.
-Help me, man.
Hey, help!
There's a man hurt in the alley.
Help me, somebody!
-Where?
-Back here.
He hurt bad?
Look, man, there's a phone down the block.
Go and call an ambulance.
[LINE RINGING]
WOMAN: Hello?
Operator, give me the hospital.
Give you what?
A hospital--sick, doctor, pain, hurt, you know.
Just a minute, mister.
You looking for a Dr. Sax?
Information number 30-70.
Is that 13-17, or is that 30-70?
-You making fun of me?
-No, I just wanted to get--
Sound like you white. You white?
What's that got to do with anything?
Honky, what you doing talking
on a New African phone?
Trying to get a hospital.
You're going to need one
the way you making fun of people.
Look, all I want to know...
is if the number is 13-17 or 30-70 or what.
-You such a smart ass, you figure it out.
-[HANGS UP]
My opponent is accusing me
of dodging the issues.
Let me say this about that.
Issues is the only thing
I'm not dodging.
Hey, two more of the same.
What am I going to do, man?
I mean, I work.
I think I look good.
I'm still young.
You know, I might have about five children.
And when I saw Jimi Hendrix...
I'd never saw anybody play guitar, play like--
He took a guitar one time and took--
he had it round his neck, right?
And there was a girl in the audience...
that he was dedicating the song to...
and he took it, spun it around his neck, right?
He's got it on his neck, right?
Just going around.
Then he takes it...
throws it down between his legs
and jerks it off.
He jerks it off, man.
I couldn't believe it.
And then threw her right back around his--
and then started playing with his teeth.
WOMAN: That's right. That's him.
And then--after he played it with his teeth...
he dropped it down on the ground...
took some lighter fluid...
You see it on the album cover.
I decided that I just wanted to be a prostitute.
Oh, honey. Wait a minute, baby.
I just want to do my thing, baby.
They tell me I can get me some furs.
How you doing?
Hey, pal...
Nigger, you stepped on my shine!
What's wrong with you?
You better get the fuck outta my face.
-What you talking about?
-I'll cut you. Shoot you.
Man, nigger, step outside!
Listen, nigger, you better back off!
I'll cut you from here to tomorrow!
Back up? Ooh, that's right!
I'll cut you so goddamn fast
you won't bleed till tomorrow.
Too easy.
Have you got change for a dollar?
Well, now, looky here!
A real live white!
[LAUGHING]
Isn't anybody gonna break up that fight?
Them niggers don't fight, sucker.
Shit! They just roughin'.
What's a whitey doing in this joint?
-Here you go.
-FRITZ: Thanks. You got a phone?
It got ripped off.
There's one down the street.
Help! Somebody! Police!
[RATTLING]
I got five dollars say
you ain't gonna buy that number.
In fact,
I put my gold teeth on it...
you can't make that number
with a pencil and a sheet of--
Who goes there?
-Excuse me.
-Don't bother me. I'm hot.
Can you tell me where to find
President Supreme Jackson?
[LAUGHS] This jive motherfu--
He's right inside.
Go ahead.
You can't make that money.
Come on seven. Bet five.
[RATTLING]
Now what is it?
Message from the White House.
The honky prez.
-The White House?
-Gimme the message.
What does it say?
It says that we attempt an assassination...
and blame it on Imaku, man.
Attempt to assassinate who?
You, fool!
Don't worry, man.
We'll get an expert shot, man,
and all he'll do is wound you.
Wound me?
We got to make it look real.
Fuck that shit.
I ain't gonna let nobody shoot me.
The answer is no.
Man, I ain't gonna lose this election.
If I got to get shot you are!
[CLICK]
[CREAKING]
Not necessarily.
Fritz? General Jones wants to talk to you!
OK, thanks.
I'm from--
I know where the hell you from--
-Don't anybody move!
-What's this?
We found you was bugging our conference...
spying on the movements,
tapping the telephones...
and telling the papers
I use hair straightener!
[BOINGING]
How dare you.
-Where's Jackson?
-He's dead.
Don't you bullshit me!
I'm not.
Killed by an American spy.
What? I didn't kill anybody.
Why would they kill Jackson?
'Cause Jackson was a real brother.
Ain't gonna let this murder go unavenged!
The council has just declared war...
on the United States, and dig that!
[BRIDGE CREAKING]
[WHISTLING]
[CRACKLING]
[BOOM]
I thought you said we were going to lose
in two or three days.
It's been two weeks.
Where's all that war reparations money...
we was supposed to get?
All them PXs and black market cigarettes?
Now, give me a chance
to get my head together, man.
Now what is it?
The President of the United States.
[BEEP BEEP]
Mr. Speaker,
Mr. Vice President...
ladies and gentlemen, as Commander in Chief...
of all the United States military forces...
I surrender.
What? Surrender?
What the hell you mean, surrender?!
You better get back to fighting.
You folks ain't never lost a war.
-Shit, you can win!
-We getting them whiteys back?
Unconditional surrender.
MAN: That's your ass, Jones.
[GLASS SHATTERS]
For crimes against the Sovereign
Republic of New Africa...
and the assassination...
of our beloved
President Supreme Jackson...
you've been ordered executed this day.
[COUGHS] You got a last request?
Yes. Please don't shoot me.
Ready...aim...fire!
I bet you voted for Nixon!
Did you by any chance,
Mr. Smart Ass...
pop some of my birth control pills?
Oh, shit!
Ralphie just peed on my shoes!
[BELCHES]
[SIGHS] Christ,
is it refreshing to get away...
from the pressures of the street.
There's much to be said
for the advantages of isolation.
It allows one total freedom
to pick and choose...
without the forces of society to wear you down.
Take the example of the influence...
of our present-day culture.
It typifies humanity's lack
of personal concern for others.
[BELCH]
-[SEAGULLS CRYING]
-Hey, fuck you, you inconsiderate bastards!
You just sit there on your fat asses...
and dump on life indiscriminately.
I suppose I should learn to accept...
the miniscule distractions of life, though.
[COUGHS]
[TUBA BLOWING]
Oh, shit!
The sacred horn of Vishnu wakes you up.
Do wake up, please, young Caucasian...
'cause I've come to save your very soul.
What? You sure you want me?
It is not possible that I could be in error.
You see, my good book here,
it guides me as I wander...
through the vast cosmic universe
of my experience...
with astral flash and good vibes
as my bedfellows.
Wait a minute.
I can't get behind that really.
Aren't those the yellow pages?
-[BLOWING]
-FRITZ: Oh, man. Could you not do that?
Please to wash my feet.
Wash my feet, Caucasian one.
Especially the left one.
Only this morning,
I stepped in sacred cow shit.
Wow, man. Hold on now.
I'm not really into washing cow shit
off anybody's feet.
This is truly a bad omen.
I, Javral Ben Roderiga...
son of the most ample
Javral Ben Roderiga Sr...
have been truly affronted.
Look, I didn't mean to offend you, man.
Silence.
There is no need to explain.
[TUBA PLAYING]
Oh, yeah, this is nice.
Very nice.
The brass horn of Vishnu announces...
that I am the second of two sent from the East.
Two also were sent from the West.
No matter.
It was to cure those, those poor unfortunates...
afflicted with the leprosy.
Jeez, that's really a shame,
because I've seen...
a lot of disease down here,
but no leprosy--so far.
No leprosy? No running sores?
Nothing like that.
This is most disturbing news.
But chronic backache?
None of my friends have that, either,
I don't think.
Well, then perhaps the dreaded dandruff...
or the very heartbreak of psoriasis?
No. I'll tell you the truth.
I think you're a little late.
See, I think that went down a long time ago.
I could tell you a story, if you'd care to--
If you could possibly make it short...
because there is a strong possibility...
that I should be in Philadelphia.
[TUBA PLAYING]
Jesus, this stuff is dynamite.
The eyes of my own soul staring back at me.
God knows I've lived the best lives
I was capable of.
My minor infractions
of society's rules were only due--
Oh, please, Lucifer, don't take me!
I'm not ready! I'll change!
I'm already changing.
Look at me change.
Oh, my God, what a way to go.
Excuse me, certainly. Hello?
Yoo-hoo down there.
Excuse me.
Did anyone find an earring?
I dropped my earring in the trash.
You'd recognize it.
It opens on one side.
Kind of a jade color.
It's got a picture of Errol
Flynn and Alan Hale naked--
Oh, Jesus Christ!
Lucifer's a faggot!
Jesus Christ, my life is shit!
I had to get knocked up.
I could've had an abortion.
No. Mr. Good-Time Charlie over there.
"No," he says. "Have the baby.
"We'll get married.
I'll take care of you."
What'll you take care of?
It's a good thing we got Ralphie.
Otherwise, we don't even get welfare.
Will you tell me one thing
you ever did for my Ralphie?
Do you ever play with him?
Do you ever take him to the ballgame?
Do you ever take him fishing?
How about fishing?
Why don't you take your own son fishing?
You don't even change his kitty litter!
Did you know that Dr. Spock...
has stated very clearly in his book...
that fathers who are never there...
usually makes a fag kid?
Do you know what he does
most of the time around the house?
If he's not picking his nose, he's jerking off.
How's that gonna look
when he starts kindergarten?
Suck my dick, huh?
You get outta here!
Pack your things and get out!
I said get out, and I mean it!
While I'm still young enough...
to find a decent father for my child, you bum.
All you do is lay around.
Listen, I'm sick of cleaning up after you.
And don't think I don't know
that you fool around.
I know it.
You junkie, you hophead, you.
Are you kidding?
No, I'm not.
I'm sick of seeing you...
sitting around here doing nothing.
Get serious!
Don't come back here
until you're ready to shape up!
[SCRAPING]
Too much. I thought she was putting me on.
Hey, she actually did it.
That blows my mind.
Hey, I don't have to go
to the welfare office tomorrow.
Jesus! Wow!
♪ Had it good, had it bad
Had it any damn way I could ♪
Know what that is? That's shit!
♪ Made a friend, lost a few
But always knew where I stood ♪
You are shit!
♪ Made a deal, got a feel for
The way the whole deal fits ♪
♪ Had a ball, took a fall ♪
♪ Now I’m thinkin'
I'll call it quits ♪
♪ Wheels'll spin ♪
♪ I'm back again ♪
♪ I'm givin' in ♪
♪ Ever get the chance again ♪
♪ I'll do it right  ♪
♪ In my next life ♪
[LAUGHING]
Know what? Know what?
She's got the clap!
Some of my best friends...
When he gets back to Earth.
♪ Here we go ♪
♪ Had a change
Thought it strange ♪
♪ It'll always
Remain the same ♪
♪ Things appear
Ain't it weird ♪
♪ You're afraid of
What you can't name ♪
♪ Check the ins
Check the outs ♪
♪ Let it come
And let it go ♪
♪ Live it up, live it down
Live it any way that you know ♪
♪ Wheels'll spin ♪
♪ I'm back again ♪
♪ I'm givin' in ♪
♪ Ever get the chance again ♪
♪ I'll do it right ♪
♪ In my next life ♪
[LAUGHING]
This is about the worst life I ever had.
♪ Had it good, had it bad
Had it any damn way I could ♪
♪ made a friend, lost a few
But always knew where I stood ♪
♪ Made a deal, got a feel for
The way the whole thing fits ♪
♪ Had a ball, took a fall ♪
♪ Now I’m thinking
I'll call it quits ♪
♪ Wheels'll spin ♪
♪ I'm back again ♪
♪ I'm givin' in ♪
♪ Ever get the chance again ♪
♪ I'll do it right ♪
♪ In my next life ♪
♪ Had it good, had it bad
Had it any damn way I could ♪
♪ Made a friend, lost a few
But always knew where I stood ♪
♪ Made a deal, got a feel for
The way the whole thing fits ♪
♪ Had a ball, took a fall ♪
♪ Now I’m thinkin'
I'll call it quits ♪
♪ Wheels'll spin ♪
♪ I'm back again ♪
♪ I'm givin' in ♪
♪ Ever get the chance again ♪
♪ I'll do it right ♪
Watch Movies, TV Series and Live Sports
Signup Here -> WWW.ADMITME.APP