(GRUNTING)
ARI: In ancient times
there arose in the lands between
the Tigris and Euphrates rivers
a powerful kingdom
called Akkad.
(MEN SHOUTING)
(SCREAMING)
And for generations her elite warriors
called the Black Scorpions
held sway over
all the neighboring tribes.
Bound by their code of honor
to fight and die to the last man
rather than abandon
their master
they became prized as the personal
bodyguards of princes and emperors.
Most renowned among
the Black Scorpions was Ashur.
But as for
his own son Mathayus
Ashur refused to allow
the boy to compete
for the honor of joining
the Black Scorpions.
ASHUR: I must follow my faith and I
forbid you to go to the games tomorrow.
You think it's
all honor and glory.
Well it's not.
I've done some things
that were not noble.
I promise you
that my son.
ARI: But like
many boys his age
Mathayus paid no heed
to his father's warnings.
You 24 boys are here to show your skills
in the art of fighting.
Only 12 of you will be
chosen to move ahead
and train for six long years to become
the pinnacle of a warrior.
A Black Scorpion!
Ready!
(ALL GRUNT)
Advance to combat!
(ALL YELLING)
Show some mettle if you want
to be Scorpions.
Mercy is weakness!
(GRUNTING)
Layla?
Mathayus?
I thought your father...
I snuck out.
You're crazy.
I'm crazy?
I can fight
as well as any boy.
Oh really?
Prove it!
Hold!
Girls are forbidden
from the games.
(EXCLAIMING)
Leave her alone!
Little vermin!
Get him!
Get him back here!
Where do you think you're going?
You dare dishonor
the games by interfering?
Lay a hand on him
and you won't live to regret it.
Arm yourself.
I'm not in the mood
for killing today.
(YELLING)
Father!
Arrest them both!
And the girl.
HAMMURABI: Wait!
SARGON: King Hammurabi!
They make a mockery
of the ancient games and insult me
the commander
of your armies.
That may be Sargon.
But Ashur has earned himself
some forbearance.
I am in your debt
My Lord. As always.
And you may repay it
by sending your boy
to the Scorpions for training.
If he makes half the mercenary
his father was
he'll serve the nation well.
You will pay for this.
I promise.
ARI: The king's general Sargon
had always resented Ashur's fame.
And now his hatred
knew no bounds.
(ASHUR GRUNTING)
(ASHUR YELLS)
Father!
(ASHUR GROANING)
(INANNA SCREAMS)
(INANNA CRYING)
ARI: Though he had no proof
Mathayus knew in his heart
who had done
this to his father.
He vowed to master
the ways of the warrior.
TRAINER: You fight
like a woman.
ARI: Six years had passed.
Mathayus had left Nippur a boy
and he returned a man.
And as he would shortly learn
much had changed while he was gone.
(SHOUTING)
For these six years past you have seen
neither kinsman nor any friend
but blade
shield and shaft.
You have trained hard.
Some have fallen
by the wayside.
Those who
yet stand before me
represent the pinnacle of generations
of Akkadian fighting prowess
the Order of
the Black Scorpions.
Go forth proudly to wherever your king
may send you.
Fight nobly!
Bring gold to
our nation's coffers
and honor to
your family names!
Oh Mom!
Look at you.
You're a man now!
I barely recognized you.
NOAH: Mathayus! Mathayus!
Mathayus!
Noah!
(EXCLAIMS)
What do they
feed you rock stew?
I see you've grown too.
He eats Enki's portions
as well as his own.
Where is Enki?
Why didn't he come?
He ran away
from home last year.
He's left to
find his fortune.
He'll be back.
Well well look at the proud new
Black Scorpion.
I see you've come
to pay your respects Layla.
I can take you on
and don't you forget it.
(EXCLAIMS)
Does that sting?
Only if you
dare touch it.
OFFICIAL: All turn and hail
Sargon your king!
Present King Sargon!
I heard rumors.
You heard the truth.
Hammurabi's death was no accident.
Sargon killed him.
(HUSHING)
Such talk is dangerous.
MAN: Careful with your words.
Our top graduate Sire.
You look familiar.
Do I know you?
I think not Sire.
Ashur was his father.
Ah.
Your father was a skillful warrior
and a patriot.
I trust you will
honor his memory.
Send him to
the palace later.
I may have a special
assignment for him.
(MUSIC PLAYING)
(INDISTINCT CHATTERING)
(WOMAN LAUGHING)
(MAN GRUNTING)
SARGON: You call
yourself a fighter?
Get up!
You better show me
some skills.
Is that all you've got?
(MAN GRUNTING)
You're nothing.
(YELLING)
(BONES CRACKING)
(GROANING)
Don't just stand there.
Come to me.
There's no place for timidity now that
the scorpion rides on your shoulder.
You're wondering
about their tattoos.
One for each man
they've slain.
You'd like a few of your own
wouldn't you?
If they deserve
to die yes.
We all deserve to die.
The only question is in what manner
and how soon.
As a member of
my personal bodyguard
it'll be your job to insure that you
die long before I do.
Your personal bodyguard?
It's a great honor
Mathayus.
Beyond the skill and strength
I'm told you possess
the first requirement is an absolute and
unwavering loyalty to me
your king.
Show him what I mean.
Hail Sargon!
Are you capable
of such loyalty Mathayus?
I...
Yes
Sire.
Good.
Then riches and glory will be yours.
But Mathayus
betray me even once
and you will pray to the gods
for a quick death.
We'll talk again
in the morning.
GUARD: Pick one for the night.
Or two or three.
Don't wear yourself out.
CONCUBINE: Or three.
(CONCUBINE LAUGHING)
(GULPS)
I hear you're
quite the swordsman.
I'm not quite polished yet Sire but
I'm a quick learner I hope.
I like you Mathayus.
Bring in the prisoner.
He was overheard
slandering my name.
And the punishment is death.
Wait. But this is my...
I know.
You do the deed yourself
you prove your loyalty to me
beyond a shadow of a doubt.
I'll permit you
to make it quick.
Mathayus! I'm sorry.
Is this true?
Did you slander the king?
Mathayus! Please!
Answer me!
Are the charges true?
Yes.
Then you deserve
what's coming to you.
You've not only betrayed your king
but your family as well.
And you've disgraced
our father's name.
Whatever you do
don't flinch.
Run Noah!
I said run!
No!
Go.
We stand
and fight together.
Mathayus behind you!
You killed my father.
This is for him.
(YELLS)
Your father was a traitor.
As are his sons.
Turnabout's fair play.
(EXCLAIMS)
Let's go!
Out the window.
(GROANS)
SARGON: Kill them!
Noah come on!
GUARD: Come back! Stop!
(URGES HORSE)
(SPEAKING FOREIGN LANGUAGE)
MATHAYUS: Go! Go!
(URGES HORSE)
Hold on!
Noah what's wrong?
Just hold on.
We're almost safe.
Noah.
What's wrong?
Noah!
Hang on! Hang on!
(GROANS)
Noah.
(SCREAMS)
ARI: Now with his brother's blood
on his hands
vengeance had branded itself
in Mathayus' heart.
(SPEAKING FOREIGN LANGUAGE)
Shall we kill him now
or bring him back alive?
Neither. I have special plans
for this one.
(GROANS)
You idiot! Now I'm gonna stink of fish
for the next week.
What are you doing here?
(EXCLAIMS IN DISGUST)
And I hate mackerel.
Next time
I'll use tuna.
Layla why are you
following me around?
First of all
I am not following you around.
I'm escaping too.
My parents pledged my hand to that fat
sheep merchant Muktil.
We're due to be
married in a week.
(CHUCKLES) Congratulations.
You think it's funny.
Well I don't know who smells worse
him or his sheep.
Mathayus I just want
a life of adventure.
And battle.
Like a man.
There's one small problem.
You're not a man.
Thanks for noticing.
Hey!
I heard you tried
to kill Sargon.
Hey listen.
I will kill that bastard some day.
Everyone knows he makes sacrifices
to the dark gods
and they've given him
black magical powers.
You're gonna need
all the help you can get.
Layla that's nice but a girl would
only get in the way.
I'm not just a girl.
Look we're not kids anymore
playing games.
I see your Black Scorpion training
also included lessons
on how to become
an arrogant jerk.
Congratulations on passing
with flying colors.
Go home Layla.
Make the sheep merchant's life miserable.
Fine! If that's how you want it.
You're on your own.
Fine.
Ticket to Egypt please.
Ten pieces.
Ticket to Egypt for one.
Ten? That's pretty steep.
Plus one for insurance.
And I highly recommend it
because there are pirates
hostile natives
and hurricanes.
Just the ticket.
Piracy has already
started if you ask me.
Egypt. For one.
Ten pieces.
Pardon me.
Excuse me.
Don't push in!
What are you
talking about?
I left the line for 10 seconds
to relieve my bladder.
Liar. Greek.
Madam I would caution you
never to mix those two words together.
Cretin.
To the land of the pharaohs
my good man.
Ten pieces.
Ticket.
You are following me.
Admit it.
You know this may come
as a shock to you
but not everything
in the world happens because of you.
Then why are you
going to Egypt?
Because...
Everyone should go and see the pyramids
once in their lives.
Why are you going to Egypt?
Personal matters
which don't concern you.
Don't play coy with me.
You know I'll get it out of you anyway.
All right.
My father once fought for the pharaoh's
private guard and saved his life.
So I'm going to ask if in return
he'll let me borrow
the Spear of Osiris
to help me defeat Sargon.
The Pharaoh of Egypt
is going to lend one of the most
fabled weapons in history
to a 19-year-old kid
he's never even heard of?
I don't remember
asking your opinion.
Actually
I'm afraid she's right.
It wouldn't work.
But mainly for the simple reason
that the Spear of Osiris
is only effective
against Egyptian monsters.
Such as the winged scarab
sphinxes and cursed mummies.
And you know this how?
Let's just say
I'm well connected.
Really? And who
are you exactly?
Aristophanes of Naxos.
Not to be confused with the Aristophanes
from Corinth. That hack.
I speak 20 languages fluently
and another 20 passably.
So if you need
any translation services...
Yes yes. How did you learn
about the Spear of Osiris?
I am a poet and playwright by trade
and sometimes a musician.
And was most recently
court poet to the king of Elam.
Petty despot. May he rot in the
underworld for his lack of esthetic taste.
And learned of it from one of
his high priests.
But you are thinking
along the right path.
To defeat a man like Sargon
well-versed in the black arts
one would require
a potent weapon indeed.
Like?
Let's see.
There's the Hammer of Zeus.
No too unwieldy.
The Shield of Cronos.
That's completely discredited.
The Cloak of...
I've got it!
The Sword of Damocles!
The what?
Damocles. You know.
The one condemned to die
a thousand deaths
by the very hand of the sword that he used
to kill King Philpman.
(GROANS)
What do they teach you
in Akkadian schools these days?
Not to touch
other men's swords.
Well in any case
according to Book Five of
Herodotus' Histories
Damocles' infamous sword was transformed
by a lightning bolt from Zeus
into a wondrous weapon whose blade
could cut through anything.
Mortal or immortal.
And presented as a gift
to the Queen of the Underworld.
You're saying this sword
can cut through anything?
Oh please.
Anything.
And you know
where this sword is?
This has to be the most harebrained
scheme I've heard yet today
and that is saying plenty.
Oh and you
have a better idea.
Okay. I've decided.
We're gonna continue
on our journey to Knossos.
And you're gonna lead me
to the Sword of Damocles.
My friend such a journey would be
fraught with perils.
The Underworld is a grim and
dangerous place of condemned souls
suffering unspeakable...
How much do you want?
Exclusive rights to compose
an epic ode of your quest
and one hundred silver staters
for expenses.
Wait. A hundred?
For risking my life
it's a pittance.
A lady doesn't part
with her dowry that easily.
Here we go.
First of all
I'm coming along.
Wait. Forget it.
Second you will treat me with respect
and as your equal.
If not your superior.
LAYLA: Thirty-fifth you will launder my
undergarments daily in fresh rosewater.
Forty-seventh you will bathe and
rub my feet with olive oil once a day.
Don't push it.
Hey Greek.
Call me Ari my sweet.
In case you get any funny ideas
about losing us
or making off with my money
just remember this.
Akkadian women are just as handy with
a dagger as Akkadian men.
I'm sure that's not the only thing
you're handy at fair maiden
whose beauty makes even
goddesses blush with envy.
Hey save your flowery words
for your scribblings.
Focus on the task at hand
which is getting
us into that.
Alive.
Of course.
(WHISPERING) Perhaps Layla here might use
her feminine wiles
to distract the guards
whilst we slip past them.
This I have to see.
Hi boys.
Nice night isn't it?
GUARD: Concubines around back.
Nice.
She is quite the charmer
isn't she?
You should see her
in a bad mood.
Hmm.
LAYLA: Guys!
Come on let's go.
These keys
should get us into the palace.
But then we need
to find the labyrinth.
The portal to the Underworld
lies within the labyrinth.
Get down!
(GUARDS CHATTERING)
Let's go.
GUARD: Intruders
in the palace!
Stop them!
Intruders!
LAYLA: Hurry up.
Come on.
I'm in!
LAYLA: Come on!
Come on!
Ow! Watch your sword.
ARI: I think
I've found something.
I think it's a lever.
MATHAYUS: Hey
don't touch that.
(ALL SCREAMING)
Are you all right?
Yeah.
I'm fine too. Thank you.
Who are you people?
Why are you imprisoned here?
(SPEAKING FOREIGN LANGUAGE)
He says they are
captives from many lands.
All brought here
to be fed to the Minotaur.
The what?
What do I expect from people who write
on clay tablets?
The Minotaur.
A creature
half man half bull.
A crazed monster whose appetite must
be satisfied daily with human flesh.
King Minos believes that the Minotaur
protects the city
and as long as it lives
his reign will be secure
and the people will prosper.
And you were
going to tell us when?
(ROARING)
At the appropriate moment.
Speak up sooner next time.
We don't even know who this guy is.
Who will join me
in battling this monster?
(SPEAKING FOREIGN LANGUAGE)
(LAUGHING)
You'd rather
sit here in terror
and squeeze out a few more
wretched days of life
than die fighting honorably
for a chance at freedom?
My friend you are wasting your breath.
Most men are slaves to their fears.
Then it's the three of us.
(STAMMERS)
I would just
get in the way.
No doubt.
MATHAYUS: At least
she came strapped.
Nice.
This way.
MATHAYUS: Stay behind me.
LAYLA: As you wish.
I've never heard those words
from your mouth before.
You're not scared
are you?
(SCOFFS)
Don't be ridiculous.
You?
Please.
(ROARING)
(GASPS)
Did you hear that?
Yeah.
(ROARING)
(BOTH GASP)
Which way is it?
(RUMBLING)
Let's go this way.
Okay.
(GASPS)
That Akkadian
looked familiar to me.
Who was his father?
A famous mercenary
named Ashur.
I was afraid of that.
Men.
Illyrian honor calls.
Yeah I was afraid of that.
I feel like we're going in circles.
Weren't we just here?
MATHAYUS: What
the hell is this?
LAYLA: It smells like death.
(WHIMPERING)
(EXCLAIMING)
What?
(SPEAKING CANTONESE)
Stay back.
Here.
Where are you going?
Now I'm scared.
Let's go.
Now!
Shouldn't we
be following him?
He's out of his mind.
Or not.
(SNORTING)
(ROARING)
You've gotta be kidding me.
(SCREAMS)
(GRUNTING)
(EXCLAIMS)
(SCREAMS)
MATHAYUS: Layla!
(ROARING)
Ugly old slab of beef!
Your mother was a cow!
(YELLING)
(FLUTE PLAYING)
(GROANING)
(CHANTING IN FOREIGN LANGUAGE)
MATHAYUS: Don't worry.
It didn't go too deep.
A little higher up and you would
have been in trouble.
A little higher up and you might
be in trouble.
(SIGHS)
You'll be okay.
Wait here.
Your silence is praise enough.
That was you?
Music has charms
to soothe the savage beast.
Say that's good.
I'm sorry for your loss
but most grateful
for your help.
It was a debt
I owed your father.
We fought together in the war against
the Hittites.
And he saved my life.
Your debt is repaid then.
Damn right it is.
Let's go men.
Where we're going we could use
some brave fighters.
There's strength in numbers
and great riches to be had.
Where?
Tell him.
You tell him.
I'll tell him.
The Underworld.
Oh the Underworld.
There's a portal inside the center
of this labyrinth.
Well good luck to you.
No one has ever returned alive
from that place.
MATHAYUS: Gilgamesh did it.
Never heard of him.
So did Herodotus.
So he claims.
Do you know
what else he claims?
When he visited the Underworld
he saw with his own eyes
enough gold diamonds and rubies
to fill a thousand arenas.
He was literally crunching on a fortune
with every step.
But you veteran warriors wouldn't be
interested in such a hazardous journey
as that taken
by an old Greek historian.
And soon by a poet a young Akkadian lad
and a girl.
Greeks. Greeks.
(SPEAKING CANTONESE)
Okay.
Wait. Why is he coming?
Well I thought
we could use the extra body.
I told him the Underworld
was a shortcut back to China.
Now what?
ARI: The portal is
in here somewhere.
Where's the door?
LAYLA: What?
The door we just
came through!
These must mean something.
Look.
The entrance must
be here somewhere.
I don't understand it.
Here we go.
Yes! Yes! Yes!
What is it?
(READING IN FOREIGN LANGUAGE)
(RUMBLING)
(ALL EXCLAIMING)
POLLUX: What's happening?
Somebody tell me
what's going on?
MATHAYUS: Ari
ARI: Herodotus was right.
What's happening?
BALDO: Don't
say it again. Greek!
Step out into your faith.
ASHUR: Mathayus my son
always follow in your faith.
Faith my son.
That is your guide.
(CHUCKLES)
(LAYLA CHUCKLES)
(SCREAMING)
(GROANS)
Amazing what faith can do.
POLLUX: Nice one Akkadian!
How did you know?
I didn't.
Seems like nothing is
what it appears to be.
What's that?
Oh yes.
Herodotus says a living person can only
remain in the Underworld
for one hour before his or her life force
drains away
and he or she
turns to stone.
Well let's get moving.
(GROANS)
You okay?
Mmm-hmm.
(SPEAKING CANTONESE)
Yeah.
Nice place to visit but...
We're all gonna die here.
Impressive young one.
Now let's see
if he can get back alive.
Wait.
MATHAYUS: What's
happening Ari?
ARI: Bad omen.
Let's go.
(ALL EXCLAIMING)
This keeps getting
better and better.
What fresh hell is this?
ARI: We should get moving.
What in the name
of the gods was that?
Did you hear it?
MAN 1: You can't go back now.
MAN 2: I can
go guard the obelisk.
Ah...
One thing.
(ALL COUGHING)
Herodotus disguised himself
as a dead person like this.
As the Underworld
is forbidden to the living
I suggest
you do the same.
And if we're discovered?
Then we will be
dead people.
BALDO: What are we doing?
Dusty Greeks.
He must be stupid.
How do I look?
I think death becomes you.
(SIGHS)
MAN: Tell me
if you see any jewels.
Gold. Some silver.
Anything.
(WHIMPERING)
So it's vengeance for your father
you're after eh?
Good. Blood
should repay blood.
You knew him well?
We fought many a battle
shield by shield.
Burned and sacked cities.
Left the streets running red.
Aye. That was a swordsman.
(LOW MOANING)
POLLUX: What was that?
BALDO: I heard something.
POLLUX: I think I just
stepped in someone.
Buggers must have journeyed
here and run out of time.
POLLUX: Arm yourselves.
With all due respect I don't think we
should be stealing from the dead yet.
(EXCLAIMING)
Maybe it wasn't such
a bad idea after all eh?
Nice.
(ALL MOANING)
MATHAYUS: Father?
(GRUNTS)
(PANTING)
(STAMMERING) Don't look!
Keep moving.
Do not make eye contact.
Don't look them
in the eyes.
(SPEAKING EXCITEDLY
IN CANTONESE)
What's he going on about?
He seems dissatisfied
with the shortcut.
(SPEAKING CANTONESE)
(MUFFLED SCREAM)
I'll take care
of the loudmouth.
No you won't!
Save your blade
for chopping onions.
Hey! Save your tongue
for licking my boots Pollux.
Calm down! Calm down!
Can't you see the effect this
place is having on us all?
(CHUCKLES)
Later Akkadian.
Has anybody seen a single
wretched miserable ruby yet?
"Gold and diamonds and rubies so
your feet can crunch on them."
The only thing my feet have
been crunching on are corpses.
Patience my friend.
Ari are you sure
we're going the right way?
How close are we
to the sword?
Hard to say.
Say it anyway.
Well unfortunately Herodotus
wasn't exactly explicit.
So you don't know.
Well not exactly but...
So you lied to us.
Oh no no no no.
Appearances are deceiving.
For example there's this
game that we play in Greece.
You play by yourself.
The game keeps changing
getting harder as you continue.
And the longer you survive
and keep playing
the closer
you get to winning.
How are we doing
in the game?
I never played it.
Right.
(SPEAKING CANTONESE)
It's a bit like Mahjong.
Mahjong.
Double-talking Greeks.
Shifty-eyed Chinese.
Insane Akkadians. Dead
people! Damn Illyrian honor!
This better be
worth my while.
I can't believe
I find my fortune in hell.
Things are
looking up the Underworld.
PeARIs.
(GROWLING)
(SCREAMING)
Where is everyone?
Wait.
We have to go back.
There's no time.
You go then.
I'll wait here.
Okay let's move.
Like I was saying
the game gets easier.
Yeah I got it.
(MAN CHATTERING)
(LOW GROWL)
(EXCLAIMS)
What was that?
(INDISTINCT WHISPERING)
(LOW GROWL)
Who are you?
And by what devious means have
you violated my inner sanctum?
Her inner what?
Let me handle this.
My lady we are...
Actually I'm not sure how
we got here or where we are.
Because you see we...
LAYLA: Are humble traders
journeying to China.
Yes! This curious-looking
fellow's homeland
on a silk-seeking
expedition and...
And we must have
taken a wrong turn.
Silence!
On your knees.
My friends will have
their fun with you.
I prefer to stand.
But thanks anyway.
I am Astarte
goddess of both love and war.
You will not only kneel
you will grovel before me
like a wretched worm.
(GROWLING)
There's no reason
to get agitated.
We can handle this
like mature adults.
Listen.
And listen well.
I rule this land
at my pleasure.
And I could destroy you
with a wave of my hand.
Or if it pleased me
seduce you
with a single glance
into obeying
my every depraved
whim.
No please! Any woman can do as much by
cinching her bust and pouting her lips.
Are you a man or a woman?
I daresay you could not seduce a beggar
if you heaped gold coins
between your thighs.
Go up there and look for the
sword. I'll check down here.
If you didn't have a goddess's
powers to deceive men's eyes
they'd no doubt
run from you screaming.
Who wants a 5000-year-old
bag of bones?
(GROWLS SOFTLY)
You insolent little cur.
I don't need a goddess's
powers to tear you apart.
(GROWLING)
You will regret that!
We'll see who regrets what
you old cradle snatcher.
(GROWLS)
(MOANING)
I'll tear your face off.
Good then I won't
have to look at you.
LAYLA: Best you can do?
(SPEAKING HASTILY
IN CANTONESE)
(SPEAKING CANTONESE)
Where are you?
Come on you old cow!
That's it!
The Sword of Damocles.
(SPEAKING CANTONESE)
Slag!
Slut!
(GROWLS)
So you like to play.
What are you doing?
(EXCLAIMS)
It's not fair.
You said no magic!
I lied.
(EXCLAIMING)
Get ready for a long fall.
Wait My Lady.
It's not her fault
we're here. It's mine.
My arrogance
not hers.
I humbly beg your forgiveness
for intruding in your domain.
For your beauty
and grace are unequaled.
(EXCLAIMING)
Go on.
(BOTH EXCLAIMING)
If you'll accept my
apologies and let us leave
I swear on my word as an Akkadian
and we always keep our vows
that I will build you
a magnificent temple
in your honor
when I return home.
I have a thousand temples
already. They bore me.
But I must say
you do possess a rare
degree of physical appeal.
LAYLA: Don't listen to her!
Perhaps if you were
to stay by my side
as my consort
then I might be persuaded
to let the others go.
Except for that vermin.
Let me down!
It's so hot up here!
Mathayus! Mathayus!
You would stay young as long
as I decided to keep you.
With no duties save
to service my varied
and copious needs.
LAYLA: He'll never
agree to that!
He loves me!
Anyway what man would willingly
want to lay down with you?
(GRUNTS ANGRILY)
Lady Astarte
I would be a fool
to turn down your offer.
However I made a vow to Shamash
to avenge my father's murder.
And I'd rather be known
as a fool than a liar.
(LAUGHING)
LAYLA: You don't have
the guts to face me!
I knew your father.
And he means
nothing compared to me.
My father was a hero.
Scratch any hero Mathayus
and you will find
a monster lurking inside.
One kiss
and you're mine.
Forever.
For the love of Zeus!
Forget it.
You're not my type.
(SCREAMS)
ARI: Mathayus!
Mathayus!
Careful it's sharp.
(GROWLING)
Here you can keep this one.
Mathayus
we're almost out of time!
Run all you like Mathayus.
I'll have you soon enough.
Just as I took your father.
(ASTARTE LAUGHING SINISTERLY)
(SPEAKING CANTONESE)
ARI: Hurry
run the same way we came.
We don't have
much time. Run!
Aren't you
forgetting something?
Where's that treasure
you promised?
But it's not my fault
that Herodotus took a few...
You sacrificed my men
you slippery-tongued worm.
I'll skin you alive.
Look!
ARI: Quick! Run!
We haven't much time! Run!
Come on!
Come on! Let's go!
Hurry come on!
Hurry up!
Come on!
Yeah! Yeah!
LAYLA: Oh my God. Pollux!
We made it.
(SPEAKING CANTONESE)
(GROWLING)
Get off me!
You disgust me!
Lady Astarte
you honor me
with your presence.
It is not to honor you
that I'm here Sargon.
A young friend of yours paid a
surprise visit to me recently.
Apparently
he's thirsting for revenge
against you.
And he took something of mine
with great sentimental value.
A sword
which could wreak great havoc if
it's not returned to the Underworld
where it belongs.
I want it back.
And you shall have it
I assure you.
Especially
if you can increase my powers.
You're greedy Sargon.
I like that in a man.
(EXCLAIMING)
You shall have
all the powers you need.
But first
you must make me
the ultimate sacrifice.
ARI: Never were any mortals more
grateful to see the sun again
than the Akkadian
and his companions.
Even Fong content to take
the long way home to China
ceased his endless carping.
And Mathayus with the
invincible sword in his grasp
looked eagerly
to his reunion with Sargon.
Mathayus?
What I said back there to that
old battle ax of a goddess...
You know
about you being
in love with me.
Well I only said that
to try and distract her.
Cloud her judgment.
Stall for time.
That's what I thought.
Clever.
Yeah it was clever
wasn't it?
It was.
Do you think what the
goddess said was true?
Inside every hero lurks
the potential for a monster.
(ALL CLAMORING)
From this night forward the
goddess's protection will insure
that Akkad will be
great forever.
Tonight's celebration to Astarte
will be like none she has ever known.
My kingdom and powers
will know no boundaries.
Hail Sargon.
(FONG SPEAKING CANTONESE)
Fong says he's enjoyed our company
but he'll be heading back to China now
to return to the simple life of
being an acrobat for the emperor.
That's too bad.
We could use
another good man.
(SPEAKING CANTONESE)
Psst. Come here!
Come here!
Where's everyone going?
The king has told us
to go to the arena.
Everybody. Keep moving you little rats!
Something's not right.
You better go to the arena
while I go after Sargon.
I'll come with you.
I've never been a big fan
of command performances
and I suspect you'll
need the moral support.
(SPEAKING CANTONESE)
Don't get yourself killed.
Not even a good death.
Nor you.
Come on.
Shouldn't we discreetly
climb a wall or dig a tunnel.
No time.
Halt!
State your business!
I'm here for
Sargon's black blood.
Stand aside and I won't
have to spill yours.
Trust me you really
don't want to do this.
(YELLS)
Impossible!
What sorcery is this?
My quarrel is not with you
but with that demon Sargon.
Let them pass.
Step aside.
Gods be with you.
I'm with him.
I've never seen
such a weapon.
GUARD: Sit down now.
MAN: Goddess Astarte.
GUARD: Hurry up!
(SPEAKING CANTONESE)
Come on!
GUARD: Anywhere. Just go.
Wait here.
This is personal.
Where are you two going?
There's no seats this way.
Who's the shifty-eyed stranger?
(SPEAKING CANTONESE)
He's the entertainment
for the crowd.
To keep them
from becoming unruly.
King Sargon salutes you
citizens of Nippur.
Your great gift
insures the glory
and prosperity of Akkad...
Great gift?
...and the blessing
of the goddess Astarte.
I've got a bad
feeling about this.
And rejoice
in your new spirit.
(SCATTERED APPLAUSE)
Now.
(CROWD EXCLAIMING)
(CROWD MURMURING)
What's going on?
(SPEAKING CANTONESE)
Hmm?
MAN 1: Get away
from the walls.
MAN 2: Move! Open the gate.
MAN 3: Move out!
ASHUR: Mathayus.
Mathayus.
Father?
How can this be?
What magic is this?
No my son it is not
the magic that you think.
It is the wondrous power
and the miracle of the sword
that you hold that has
allowed us to meet again.
But I saw you.
I saw you in the Underworld.
A place you do not belong.
Prove to me
this is really you.
Remember
when you were
a very young boy
and sometimes
when you were frightened
I would put my arms around you
and whisper something in your ear
that only you and I
would ever know?
(SPEAKING FOREIGN LANGUAGE)
Remember?
Father?
You were a hero.
Why were you there?
We cannot escape our fate.
Scratch any hero
and a monster lurks beneath.
(GROANING)
Feeling smaller
without your special sword?
You're not the one to talk
hiding behind your trickery.
Father always said
you were a coward.
(GROANS)
(YELLS)
(CROWD CLAMORING)
Shoot that one!
(SPEAKING CANTONESE)
WOMAN: They're gonna
set us on fire!
(SPEAKING CANTONESE)
What?
Okay! Let's split up!
Okay.
We can't let
the arrows hit the oil.
You come to avenge your
father the great hero?
I fight for more
than vengeance now Sargon.
I fight for what
my father once believed in.
And I fight for what
you've corrupted.
Mark that down scribe.
Sounds like a good epitaph.
Ari throw me the sword.
The sword Greek.
MATHAYUS: Ari.
Jewels first.
Careful. It's sharp.
SARGON: That's right
you fool.
I planned every detail of your little
heroic journey into the Underworld.
This sword makes
my power supreme.
You can never
trust a Greek eh?
Nothing personal Mathayus.
But a fortune in jewels
and a good tale to tell...
What writer could resist that?
Write well of my exploits
scribe. Or I'll come for your head.
The king who became a god.
(BOTH YELLING)
What?
Mathayus!
Never trust a Greek!
And I'm a poet not a scribe you jackass.
Now Mathayus as a Black Scorpion
you owe your allegiance to your king.
You took a sacred oath.
(SPEAKING FOREIGN LANGUAGE)
And the darkness grows.
(GASPS)
LAYLA: Fong! Stop the arrow!
(CRUNCHING)
(CREATURE SCREECHING)
(YELLING)
(SCREECHING)
(HISSING)
(EXCLAIMS)
(GRUNTS)
(GRUNTING)
(GROANS)
(INDISTINCT WHISPERING)
Get them off the wall!
(SPEAKING CANTONESE)
GUARD: Release those arrows!
Fire!
Fong! We have to stop the
flames from reaching the walls.
LAYLA: Fong come on!
MAN: Stop the flames!
Put out the flames!
Use the sand!
(INDISTINCT WHISPERING
CONTINUES)
(EXCLAIMS)
MAN: Stop the flames
from reaching the walls!
Hurry Fong!
Don't let the flames
reach the walls!
(SCORPION SCREECHING)
(CLATTERING)
(SPEAKING CANTONESE)
Fong hurry get the wall!
We got to put it out!
(SPEAKING CANTONESE)
(LAUGHS) What?
(EXCLAIMS)
(GRUNTING)
(SCREECHES)
This is for my father.
(SHRIEKING)
MAN: Layla you saved us!
(GROWLING)
And so Mathayus why
should I show you any mercy?
You dared spurn me.
Not to mention
you stole my sword.
Because My Lady
you know you'll have me soon enough.
Yes.
I will.
INANNA: Oh Shamash
hear my plea.
For three days and nights my son has
slept the sleep of the living dead.
Bring him back to us
or take him please
I beg you.
(CHUCKLES)
What's that stench?
I would think I've earned a thank you.
Of course I never planned
on serving that wretch.
My words will tell your
story well my friend.
In time your exploits will be renowned.
If you'll just
let go.
Hey.
Welcome back.
HIGH PRIEST: Citizens of
Akkad I give you your new king.
Son of Hammurabi
Shalmaneser.
People of Akkad we have
passed through a very hard time.
But the sun is rising again.
Where is the Greek?
He said something about
Olympia and Neptune's Trident.
But he wanted you
to have this.
He said you'd understand.
What?
I think he'll do quite well.
Our land the people's
land will prosper again!
People of Akkad...
Should have been you.
No thanks.
Not my cup of tea.
And us?
We'll be fine.
It would have been nice to
live in a beautiful palace
with lots of servants
and fine linens.
I thought you wanted to be a warrior
roam the world
like a man.
Well I decided I didn't like battles
and killing as much as I thought I would.
SHALMANESER: That every man
may know right from wrong.
Do you?
ARI: But the truth
of the matter was
Mathayus did have a fondness
for battles and killing.
And though he loved Layla
the blood of a warrior
and the scorpion's dark venom
still coursed through his veins.
It would drive him out into the
wide world for further adventures
and further battles
until one day perhaps
he would return
to become the Scorpion King.
That is the subject
for another tale.