1
00:00:05,974 --> 00:00:15,974
Encoded By Deceit @ YIFY Torrents

2
00:01:02,896 --> 00:01:04,814
All right, that's it.

3
00:01:08,318 --> 00:01:10,027
One, two, three.

4
00:01:27,337 --> 00:01:29,172
Are you sure you're 18?

5
00:01:29,381 --> 00:01:30,840
Why, do I look older?

6
00:01:39,516 --> 00:01:40,808
Alberta Scrubb?

7
00:01:41,018 --> 00:01:45,021
That's a typographical error.
It's supposed to be Albert A. Scrubb.

8
00:01:45,189 --> 00:01:46,272
Edmund...

9
00:01:46,440 --> 00:01:48,483
you're supposed to be helping me
with the groceries.

10
00:01:53,614 --> 00:01:55,114
Better luck next time, eh, squirt?

11
00:02:02,122 --> 00:02:03,372
Squirt!

12
00:02:03,540 --> 00:02:05,792
He barely had two years on me.

13
00:02:05,959 --> 00:02:10,546
I'm a king! I've fought wars
and I've led armies.

14
00:02:10,714 --> 00:02:11,964
Not in this world.

15
00:02:12,132 --> 00:02:15,218
Yeah, instead I'm stuck here,
doing battle...

16
00:02:15,385 --> 00:02:17,678
with Eustace Clarence Scrubb.

17
00:02:17,846 --> 00:02:20,556
If anyone so deserved a name.

18
00:02:22,726 --> 00:02:23,935
What are you doing?

19
00:02:25,062 --> 00:02:25,895
Nothing.

20
00:02:26,939 --> 00:02:28,314
Come on then.

21
00:02:35,447 --> 00:02:38,491
Dear diary, it is now day 253...

22
00:02:38,659 --> 00:02:42,245
since my wretched cousins
Edmund and Lucy invaded our house.

23
00:02:42,412 --> 00:02:44,914
Not sure how much longer
I can cope living with them...

24
00:02:45,082 --> 00:02:47,250
having to share my things.

25
00:02:47,417 --> 00:02:51,045
If only one could treat relatives
like one treats insects...

26
00:02:51,213 --> 00:02:53,047
all my problems would be solved.

27
00:02:53,215 --> 00:02:56,759
I could simply put them in a jar
or pin them to my wall.

28
00:02:56,969 --> 00:02:59,929
I'm home. Hello!

29
00:03:00,097 --> 00:03:03,933
Note to self,
investigate legal ramifications...

30
00:03:04,101 --> 00:03:06,269
of impaling relatives.

31
00:03:09,565 --> 00:03:11,274
That concludes
the war news from the Western Front.

32
00:03:11,441 --> 00:03:13,818
- Hello, Uncle Harold.
- I tried to find some carrots...

33
00:03:13,986 --> 00:03:15,903
but all they had were turnips again.

34
00:03:16,071 --> 00:03:17,780
Shall I start making soup?

35
00:03:17,990 --> 00:03:19,907
Aunt Alberta's on her way home.

36
00:03:23,120 --> 00:03:24,078
Uncle Harold?

37
00:03:25,914 --> 00:03:27,957
Father. Edmund's making faces at you.

38
00:03:30,294 --> 00:03:31,419
Why, you little--

39
00:03:31,587 --> 00:03:32,795
Father, he's gonna hit me!

40
00:03:33,005 --> 00:03:34,046
Edmund, look!

41
00:03:34,464 --> 00:03:36,382
It's from Susan.

42
00:03:36,550 --> 00:03:37,884
I do wish you were here with us.

43
00:03:38,552 --> 00:03:42,138
It's been such an adventure,
but nothing like our times in Narnia.

44
00:03:43,015 --> 00:03:44,932
America is very exciting...

45
00:03:45,142 --> 00:03:48,728
except we never see Father.
He works so very hard.

46
00:03:48,896 --> 00:03:49,854
I was invited...

47
00:03:50,022 --> 00:03:53,274
"...to the British Consul's tea party
this week by a naval officer..."

48
00:03:53,483 --> 00:03:55,276
who happens to be very handsome.

49
00:03:55,652 --> 00:03:57,653
"I think he fancies me." Hmm.

50
00:03:58,447 --> 00:04:01,490
"It seems the Germans have made
the crossing difficult right now."

51
00:04:01,658 --> 00:04:02,825
Times are hard.

52
00:04:02,993 --> 00:04:06,245
"Mother hopes you both won't mind
another few months in Cambridge."

53
00:04:07,414 --> 00:04:08,748
Another few months?

54
00:04:08,916 --> 00:04:10,791
How will we survive?

55
00:04:10,959 --> 00:04:12,126
You're lucky...

56
00:04:12,336 --> 00:04:15,963
at least you've got your own room.
I'm stuck with mullet mouth.

57
00:04:16,131 --> 00:04:18,841
Susan and Peter
are the lucky ones.

58
00:04:19,009 --> 00:04:20,343
Off on adventures.

59
00:04:20,510 --> 00:04:23,429
Yeah, they're the eldest
and we're the youngest.

60
00:04:23,597 --> 00:04:25,640
We don't matter as much.

61
00:04:26,600 --> 00:04:28,351
Do you think I look anything like Susan?

62
00:04:30,520 --> 00:04:31,354
Lucy...

63
00:04:31,939 --> 00:04:34,106
have you seen this ship before?

64
00:04:34,274 --> 00:04:38,027
Yes. It's very Narnian-looking,
isn't it?

65
00:04:38,195 --> 00:04:39,695
Yeah.

66
00:04:39,863 --> 00:04:42,323
Just another reminder
that we're here and not there.

67
00:04:42,824 --> 00:04:45,701
There once were two orphans
Who wasted their time

68
00:04:46,662 --> 00:04:48,371
Believing in Narnian nursery rhymes

69
00:04:48,538 --> 00:04:50,206
- Please let me hit him.
- No!

70
00:04:50,374 --> 00:04:53,292
Don't you ever knock?
It's my house. I'll do as I please.

71
00:04:53,460 --> 00:04:54,460
You're just guests.

72
00:04:56,380 --> 00:04:58,798
What's so fascinating
about that picture anyway?

73
00:04:58,966 --> 00:05:00,174
It's hideous.

74
00:05:00,342 --> 00:05:01,884
You won't see it
from the other side of the door.

75
00:05:03,136 --> 00:05:05,304
Edmund, it looks like
the water is actually moving.

76
00:05:05,973 --> 00:05:06,847
What rubbish!

77
00:05:07,015 --> 00:05:08,224
See? That's what happens...

78
00:05:08,392 --> 00:05:11,060
when you read all those fanciful novels
and fairy tales of yours.

79
00:05:11,311 --> 00:05:13,229
There once was a boy called Eustace

80
00:05:13,397 --> 00:05:15,898
Who read books
Full of facts that were useless

81
00:05:16,358 --> 00:05:17,566
People who read fairy tales...

82
00:05:17,734 --> 00:05:20,403
are always the sort who become
a hideous burden to people like me...

83
00:05:21,029 --> 00:05:22,989
who read books
with real information.

84
00:05:23,198 --> 00:05:24,365
"Hideous burden"?

85
00:05:25,200 --> 00:05:27,994
I haven't seen you lift a finger
since we've been here.

86
00:05:29,579 --> 00:05:32,498
I have a mind to tell your father
you stole Aunt Alberta's sweets.

87
00:05:32,666 --> 00:05:34,083
- Liar!
- Oh, really?

88
00:05:34,251 --> 00:05:35,751
Edmund, the painting.

89
00:05:35,919 --> 00:05:38,671
I found them under your bed,
and you know what?

90
00:05:38,839 --> 00:05:40,256
I licked every one of them.

91
00:05:40,424 --> 00:05:42,925
Ugh! I'm infected with you!

92
00:05:47,431 --> 00:05:48,764
What's going on here?

93
00:05:48,932 --> 00:05:51,017
- Lucy, do you think--?
- It's some kind of trick!

94
00:05:51,184 --> 00:05:52,601
Stop it or I'll tell mother.

95
00:05:52,769 --> 00:05:55,354
Mother!

96
00:05:58,025 --> 00:05:59,650
I'll just smash the rotten thing.

97
00:06:00,110 --> 00:06:01,944
No, Eustace! No!

98
00:06:02,112 --> 00:06:03,237
We can't stop it!

99
00:06:03,405 --> 00:06:04,488
Get off me! Get off!

100
00:06:04,656 --> 00:06:06,532
Let go of it, Eustace! Put it down!

101
00:06:06,700 --> 00:06:08,617
- Get off it!
- Let go!

102
00:06:36,146 --> 00:06:37,313
Edmund!

103
00:06:38,732 --> 00:06:39,648
Edmund!

104
00:06:39,816 --> 00:06:41,692
What's happening?

105
00:06:42,110 --> 00:06:43,569
Where are we?

106
00:06:45,822 --> 00:06:47,198
Eustace, swim!

107
00:06:47,824 --> 00:06:49,116
What's going on?

108
00:06:49,284 --> 00:06:50,618
Eustace, come on!

109
00:06:50,786 --> 00:06:52,078
Come on, move!

110
00:06:52,245 --> 00:06:54,413
Keep swimming!

111
00:06:56,666 --> 00:06:58,125
Edmund!

112
00:07:02,964 --> 00:07:05,925
It's all right. I've got you.

113
00:07:06,843 --> 00:07:07,927
Caspian!

114
00:07:08,095 --> 00:07:09,553
Lucy.

115
00:07:09,721 --> 00:07:11,013
Edmund, it's Caspian!

116
00:07:11,181 --> 00:07:13,682
It's all right, boys. You're safe now.

117
00:07:13,850 --> 00:07:14,850
Are we in Narnia?

118
00:07:15,018 --> 00:07:16,644
Yes, you're in Narnia.

119
00:07:16,812 --> 00:07:18,020
I don't want to go!

120
00:07:18,188 --> 00:07:22,441
I want to go back to England!
I'm going back to England!

121
00:07:22,859 --> 00:07:24,151
Hold on.

122
00:07:43,964 --> 00:07:45,548
That was thrilling!

123
00:07:45,715 --> 00:07:47,716
How in the world did you end up here?

124
00:07:47,884 --> 00:07:49,301
I have no idea.

125
00:07:49,469 --> 00:07:50,761
Caspian.

126
00:07:52,139 --> 00:07:53,139
Edmund.

127
00:07:53,306 --> 00:07:54,348
It's great to see you.

128
00:07:54,516 --> 00:07:56,684
Great to see you.
Didn't you call for us?

129
00:07:56,852 --> 00:07:59,562
No. Not this time.

130
00:07:59,729 --> 00:08:01,981
Well, whatever the case,
I'm just glad to be here.

131
00:08:03,733 --> 00:08:06,819
- Now calm down, sir.
- Get that thing off me!

132
00:08:06,987 --> 00:08:08,154
Get that thing off me!

133
00:08:11,324 --> 00:08:12,575
Reepicheep!

134
00:08:14,202 --> 00:08:16,245
Oh. Your Majesties.

135
00:08:16,413 --> 00:08:18,414
Hello, Reep. What a pleasure.

136
00:08:18,582 --> 00:08:20,374
The pleasure is all mine, sir.

137
00:08:20,542 --> 00:08:23,752
But first, what to do
about this hysterical interloper?

138
00:08:25,255 --> 00:08:26,547
That giant rat thing...

139
00:08:26,715 --> 00:08:27,923
just tried to claw my face off!

140
00:08:28,091 --> 00:08:29,425
I was merely trying...

141
00:08:29,593 --> 00:08:31,010
to expel the water...

142
00:08:31,178 --> 00:08:32,178
from your lungs, sir.

143
00:08:32,345 --> 00:08:35,764
It talked! Did you see?
Did anyone just hear that? It just talked!

144
00:08:35,932 --> 00:08:38,601
He always talks.
It's getting him to shut up that's the trick.

145
00:08:38,768 --> 00:08:41,187
The moment there is nothing to be said,
Your Highness...

146
00:08:41,354 --> 00:08:43,898
I promise you, I will not say it.

147
00:08:44,065 --> 00:08:47,443
I don't know what kind of prank this is,
but I want to wake up right now!

148
00:08:47,903 --> 00:08:49,778
Perhaps we could throw him back?

149
00:08:51,781 --> 00:08:52,656
Edmund!

150
00:08:54,534 --> 00:08:57,494
I demand to know,
just where in the blazes am I?

151
00:08:57,662 --> 00:08:59,121
You're on the Dawn Treader...

152
00:08:59,289 --> 00:09:01,957
the finest ship in Narnia's navy.

153
00:09:07,631 --> 00:09:08,964
Was it something I said?

154
00:09:10,133 --> 00:09:11,133
See to him, will you?

155
00:09:11,343 --> 00:09:12,927
Your Majesty.

156
00:09:15,931 --> 00:09:16,972
Men...

157
00:09:18,975 --> 00:09:20,809
behold our castaways...

158
00:09:22,270 --> 00:09:26,106
Edmund the Just
and Lucy the Valiant...

159
00:09:26,274 --> 00:09:29,276
high King and Queen of Narnia.

160
00:09:58,306 --> 00:09:59,515
Aslan.

161
00:10:06,815 --> 00:10:07,940
Look...

162
00:10:08,108 --> 00:10:10,192
Susan's bow and arrows.

163
00:10:10,360 --> 00:10:11,151
Lucy.

164
00:10:13,196 --> 00:10:14,947
My healing cordial...

165
00:10:15,282 --> 00:10:16,699
and dagger.

166
00:10:16,866 --> 00:10:18,200
Oh, may I?

167
00:10:18,410 --> 00:10:20,035
Of course, they're yours.

168
00:10:20,203 --> 00:10:21,287
Peter's sword.

169
00:10:21,454 --> 00:10:22,538
Yes.

170
00:10:23,456 --> 00:10:25,666
I looked after it as promised.

171
00:10:26,876 --> 00:10:29,044
Here, hold it if you wish.

172
00:10:29,212 --> 00:10:31,005
No, no, it's yours.

173
00:10:31,464 --> 00:10:33,048
Peter gave it to you.

174
00:10:34,301 --> 00:10:37,011
I did save this for you though.

175
00:10:42,517 --> 00:10:43,726
Thanks.

176
00:10:45,729 --> 00:10:48,689
Since you left, the Giants
of the North surrendered unconditionally...

177
00:10:48,857 --> 00:10:52,026
then we defeated the Calormen armies
at the Great Desert.

178
00:10:52,193 --> 00:10:53,902
There is peace across all of Narnia.

179
00:10:54,070 --> 00:10:55,070
Peace?

180
00:10:55,238 --> 00:10:56,488
In just three years.

181
00:10:57,073 --> 00:10:59,700
And have you found yourself a queen
in those three years?

182
00:11:00,577 --> 00:11:03,537
No. Not one to compare with your sister.

183
00:11:03,705 --> 00:11:05,581
- Hang on.
- If there are no wars to fight...

184
00:11:05,749 --> 00:11:09,043
and no one is in trouble,
then why are we here?

185
00:11:09,210 --> 00:11:11,920
It's a good question.
I've been asking myself the same thing.

186
00:11:12,422 --> 00:11:13,756
So where are we sailing to?

187
00:11:14,341 --> 00:11:16,258
Before I took back the throne
from my uncle...

188
00:11:16,426 --> 00:11:20,262
he tried to kill my father's closest friends
and most loyal supporters.

189
00:11:20,680 --> 00:11:22,389
The seven lords of Telmar.

190
00:11:27,062 --> 00:11:28,354
They fled to the Lone islands.

191
00:11:30,065 --> 00:11:31,398
No one has heard from them since.

192
00:11:33,526 --> 00:11:35,569
So you think something
has happened to them?

193
00:11:35,737 --> 00:11:38,947
Well, if it has, it's my duty to find out.

194
00:11:40,784 --> 00:11:43,619
Well, what's east of the Lone Islands?

195
00:11:43,787 --> 00:11:45,120
Uncharted waters.

196
00:11:45,997 --> 00:11:48,457
Things you can barely imagine.

197
00:11:48,625 --> 00:11:50,959
Tales of sea serpents and worse.

198
00:11:53,421 --> 00:11:54,630
Sea serpents?

199
00:11:54,798 --> 00:11:55,964
All right, Captain...

200
00:11:56,132 --> 00:11:58,133
that's enough of your tall tales.

201
00:12:09,145 --> 00:12:11,605
Where sky and water meet

202
00:12:11,773 --> 00:12:14,233
Where the waves grow ever sweet

203
00:12:14,401 --> 00:12:18,320
Doubt not, you Reepicheep

204
00:12:19,072 --> 00:12:21,657
To find all that you seek

205
00:12:21,825 --> 00:12:24,660
There is the Utter East
Doubt not--

206
00:12:24,828 --> 00:12:26,829
- That's pretty.
- Oh!

207
00:12:26,996 --> 00:12:28,664
Thank you.

208
00:12:29,040 --> 00:12:32,167
A dryad sung it to me
when I was just a mouseling.

209
00:12:32,335 --> 00:12:35,838
I can't divine the meaning,
but I've never forgotten the words.

210
00:12:36,005 --> 00:12:38,132
What do you think is past
the Lone islands, Reep?

211
00:12:38,508 --> 00:12:42,428
Well, I've been told the furthest east
one can sail is to the end of the world.

212
00:12:42,595 --> 00:12:43,846
Asian's country.

213
00:12:44,264 --> 00:12:46,140
Do you really believe
there's such a place?

214
00:12:46,683 --> 00:12:49,017
Well, we have nothing, if not belief.

215
00:12:52,188 --> 00:12:54,440
Do you think you could
actually sail there?

216
00:12:54,607 --> 00:12:57,025
Well, there is only one way
of finding that out.

217
00:12:57,527 --> 00:13:00,112
I can only hope I will one day
earn the right to see it.

218
00:13:01,489 --> 00:13:03,449
Your Majesty.

219
00:13:40,904 --> 00:13:42,321
Come on.

220
00:14:02,759 --> 00:14:05,010
You've grown stronger, my friend.

221
00:14:05,178 --> 00:14:07,012
Seems I have.

222
00:14:07,931 --> 00:14:10,933
All right, back to work.

223
00:14:12,602 --> 00:14:14,686
- Your Highness.
- Thank you.

224
00:14:18,608 --> 00:14:19,566
Edmund...

225
00:14:19,734 --> 00:14:21,109
do you think if we keep sailing...

226
00:14:21,277 --> 00:14:22,444
to the end of the world...

227
00:14:22,612 --> 00:14:25,948
we'll just... tip off the edge?

228
00:14:26,157 --> 00:14:29,284
Don't worry, Lu,
we're a long way from there.

229
00:14:29,452 --> 00:14:32,162
I see you're still talking nonsense,
the two of you.

230
00:14:33,373 --> 00:14:34,498
Are you feeling better?

231
00:14:34,666 --> 00:14:38,085
Yes, no thanks to you.
It's lucky I have an iron constitution.

232
00:14:38,253 --> 00:14:39,920
As effervescent as ever, I see.

233
00:14:40,380 --> 00:14:41,421
Find your sea legs?

234
00:14:41,589 --> 00:14:44,132
Never lost them.
Simply dealing with the shock of things.

235
00:14:44,968 --> 00:14:48,804
Mother says I have an acute disposition,
due to my intelligence.

236
00:14:49,264 --> 00:14:51,431
I don't think he has
a cute anything.

237
00:14:51,599 --> 00:14:54,434
I'll have you all know,
as soon as we find civilization...

238
00:14:54,602 --> 00:14:57,437
I'm contacting the British Consul.
Have you all arrested for kidnapping.

239
00:14:57,605 --> 00:14:58,480
Kidnapping, is it?

240
00:14:58,648 --> 00:14:59,731
That's funny.

241
00:15:00,275 --> 00:15:01,483
I thought we saved your life.

242
00:15:01,651 --> 00:15:02,985
You held me against my will!

243
00:15:03,152 --> 00:15:03,902
Ha!

244
00:15:04,070 --> 00:15:04,820
Did I?

245
00:15:04,988 --> 00:15:07,447
In, what I must say,
are the most unhygienic quarters.

246
00:15:07,615 --> 00:15:08,907
It's like a zoo down there!

247
00:15:09,075 --> 00:15:10,742
He's quite the complainer, isn't he?

248
00:15:10,910 --> 00:15:12,327
He's just warming up.

249
00:15:12,662 --> 00:15:14,246
Land ho!

250
00:15:36,352 --> 00:15:40,022
- The Lone Islands.
- The port of Narrowhaven.

251
00:15:40,189 --> 00:15:43,984
Strange, not a Narnian flag in sight.

252
00:15:44,986 --> 00:15:47,237
But the Lone Islands
have always been Narnia's.

253
00:15:50,199 --> 00:15:51,700
Seems suspicious.

254
00:15:53,828 --> 00:15:55,329
I say we prepare a landing party.

255
00:15:56,205 --> 00:15:57,664
Drinian?

256
00:15:58,207 --> 00:16:00,042
Forgive me, Your Majesty...

257
00:16:00,209 --> 00:16:03,837
but the chain of command starts
with King Caspian on this ship.

258
00:16:05,214 --> 00:16:06,048
Right.

259
00:16:06,215 --> 00:16:07,549
We'll use longboats.

260
00:16:07,717 --> 00:16:09,384
Drinian, pick some men
and come ashore.

261
00:16:09,552 --> 00:16:11,094
Aye.
Tavros.

262
00:16:12,555 --> 00:16:17,392
Man the longboats, furl the sail
and prepare to drop anchor.

263
00:16:31,407 --> 00:16:34,910
- Onward!
- The thrill of the unknown lies ahead.

264
00:16:35,745 --> 00:16:37,412
Couldn't this have waited
till the morning?

265
00:16:38,247 --> 00:16:41,083
There is no honor in turning away
from adventure, lad.

266
00:16:41,250 --> 00:16:42,626
Listen.

267
00:16:43,503 --> 00:16:45,921
Where is everyone?

268
00:16:46,089 --> 00:16:47,589
Come on, jelly legs.

269
00:16:47,757 --> 00:16:50,676
I'm capable of doing it myself. Oof!

270
00:16:52,387 --> 00:16:54,221
And you're certain
he's related by blood?

271
00:17:18,538 --> 00:17:21,373
Reepicheep, stay here with Drinian's men
and secure the place.

272
00:17:22,291 --> 00:17:23,625
We'll head on.

273
00:17:23,793 --> 00:17:26,920
If we don't come back by dawn,
send a party.

274
00:17:27,088 --> 00:17:28,839
Yes, Your Majesty.

275
00:17:43,354 --> 00:17:45,897
Yeah, looks like nobody is in.
Do you think we should head back?

276
00:17:48,693 --> 00:17:51,611
Do you want to come here and guard...
something?

277
00:17:52,613 --> 00:17:53,822
Ah, yes.

278
00:17:54,949 --> 00:17:55,949
Good idea, cousin.

279
00:17:56,659 --> 00:17:59,327
Very, uh... logical.

280
00:18:09,172 --> 00:18:11,173
I've got it. I've got it. Don't worry.

281
00:18:31,527 --> 00:18:34,029
Uh, I'm ready to go when you are.

282
00:18:43,498 --> 00:18:45,457
Who are all these people?

283
00:18:45,625 --> 00:18:48,376
Why have they been crossed out?

284
00:18:48,878 --> 00:18:52,047
It looks like some kind of fee.

285
00:18:52,215 --> 00:18:53,507
Slave traders.

286
00:18:58,137 --> 00:18:59,721
Look out!

287
00:19:15,404 --> 00:19:20,075
Unless you want to hear this one
squeal like a girl again...

288
00:19:20,743 --> 00:19:22,160
I'd say you should...

289
00:19:22,328 --> 00:19:23,078
drop your weapons.

290
00:19:23,246 --> 00:19:24,996
Like a girl?
Now!

291
00:19:26,749 --> 00:19:27,958
Put it down.

292
00:19:28,876 --> 00:19:30,085
Eustace.

293
00:19:30,670 --> 00:19:32,003
Put them in irons.

294
00:19:32,171 --> 00:19:33,588
Come on. Come here, you.

295
00:19:34,173 --> 00:19:34,840
Ah!

296
00:19:35,007 --> 00:19:35,924
Get your hands off me!

297
00:19:36,092 --> 00:19:37,843
Let's take these two to market.

298
00:19:38,010 --> 00:19:38,760
Let go!

299
00:19:38,970 --> 00:19:40,428
Send those two to the dungeons.

300
00:19:40,596 --> 00:19:42,264
Listen to me, you insolent fool!

301
00:19:42,431 --> 00:19:43,723
I am your king!

302
00:19:45,726 --> 00:19:47,185
You're gonna pay for that.

303
00:19:47,353 --> 00:19:48,895
Actually...

304
00:19:49,689 --> 00:19:51,523
someone else is going to pay...

305
00:19:53,818 --> 00:19:55,902
for all of you.

306
00:19:56,070 --> 00:19:58,113
- No! Edmund! Edmund!
- Lucy!

307
00:19:58,614 --> 00:20:00,866
No! Edmund!

308
00:20:09,917 --> 00:20:11,459
You all right?

309
00:20:13,004 --> 00:20:14,045
Yeah.

310
00:20:17,967 --> 00:20:19,342
It's hopeless.

311
00:20:20,803 --> 00:20:22,512
You'll never get out.

312
00:20:24,223 --> 00:20:25,724
Who's there?

313
00:20:25,933 --> 00:20:28,476
Nobody. Just a voice...

314
00:20:28,644 --> 00:20:30,312
in my head.

315
00:20:40,865 --> 00:20:41,865
Lord Bern?

316
00:20:45,369 --> 00:20:49,873
Perhaps once, but I'm no longer
deserving of that title.

317
00:20:51,792 --> 00:20:52,959
Is he one of the seven?

318
00:21:00,843 --> 00:21:01,843
Your face...

319
00:21:03,262 --> 00:21:05,513
You remind me of a king
I once loved well.

320
00:21:06,349 --> 00:21:07,515
That man was my father.

321
00:21:09,018 --> 00:21:10,894
Oh, my lord.

322
00:21:11,062 --> 00:21:13,438
- Please forgive me.
- No, please.

323
00:21:13,773 --> 00:21:14,940
Please.

324
00:21:16,567 --> 00:21:17,359
No!

325
00:21:18,152 --> 00:21:19,569
No!

326
00:21:19,862 --> 00:21:20,654
Helaine!

327
00:21:20,821 --> 00:21:21,696
- Mummy!
- No!

328
00:21:22,782 --> 00:21:24,824
Helaine!

329
00:21:26,494 --> 00:21:27,869
- Mummy!
- Please!

330
00:21:30,498 --> 00:21:31,331
Mummy!

331
00:21:31,874 --> 00:21:33,208
Get back!

332
00:21:33,918 --> 00:21:36,336
- Mummy!
- Stay with Daddy!

333
00:21:36,504 --> 00:21:38,880
Don't worry! I'll find you!

334
00:21:39,298 --> 00:21:40,799
Mummy!

335
00:21:51,811 --> 00:21:52,894
No!

336
00:21:53,229 --> 00:21:54,604
Where are they taking them?

337
00:21:55,231 --> 00:21:56,606
Keep watching.

338
00:22:26,262 --> 00:22:27,595
What happened?

339
00:22:27,763 --> 00:22:29,931
It's a sacrifice.

340
00:22:30,266 --> 00:22:31,599
Where did they go?

341
00:22:32,143 --> 00:22:33,393
No one knows.

342
00:22:34,103 --> 00:22:37,647
The mist was first seen
in the east.

343
00:22:37,982 --> 00:22:41,443
Reports of fishermen and sailors
disappearing out at sea.

344
00:22:41,777 --> 00:22:44,029
We lords made a pact...

345
00:22:44,196 --> 00:22:46,781
to find the source of the mist
to destroy it.

346
00:22:47,283 --> 00:22:48,742
They each set sail...

347
00:22:49,910 --> 00:22:52,037
but none came back.

348
00:22:56,584 --> 00:22:59,961
You see, if they don't sell you
to the slave traders...

349
00:23:00,129 --> 00:23:01,880
you're likely to be fed to the mist.

350
00:23:02,048 --> 00:23:03,298
We have to find Lucy...

351
00:23:05,134 --> 00:23:06,301
before it's too late.

352
00:23:06,469 --> 00:23:08,303
- I bid 60.
- I bid 80.

353
00:23:08,471 --> 00:23:09,971
100 for the little lady.

354
00:23:10,139 --> 00:23:11,598
120.

355
00:23:11,766 --> 00:23:12,640
150.

356
00:23:13,684 --> 00:23:14,642
Any more bids?

357
00:23:18,773 --> 00:23:19,939
Sold!

358
00:23:20,274 --> 00:23:21,316
Ah!

359
00:23:21,484 --> 00:23:23,193
Come on, move.

360
00:23:23,402 --> 00:23:24,194
Move!

361
00:23:24,403 --> 00:23:25,320
And now...

362
00:23:25,488 --> 00:23:26,654
for this...

363
00:23:26,822 --> 00:23:28,323
fine specimen...

364
00:23:28,616 --> 00:23:30,992
who'll kick off the bidding?

365
00:23:31,285 --> 00:23:33,161
Come on now...

366
00:23:33,496 --> 00:23:36,539
he may not look like much
but he's strong.

367
00:23:36,707 --> 00:23:37,999
Yeah, he's strong, all right.

368
00:23:38,167 --> 00:23:40,543
Smells like the rear end of a Minotaur!

369
00:23:41,337 --> 00:23:43,338
That is an outrageous lie!

370
00:23:43,964 --> 00:23:46,758
I won the school hygiene award
two years running.

371
00:23:48,177 --> 00:23:50,428
Come on, someone make a bid!

372
00:23:50,596 --> 00:23:52,514
I'll take them off your hands.

373
00:23:52,681 --> 00:23:54,557
I'll take them all off your hands!

374
00:23:54,725 --> 00:23:55,809
For Narnia!

375
00:23:56,477 --> 00:23:57,519
Narnia!

376
00:24:00,523 --> 00:24:03,358
Guards! Guards! Move yourselves!

377
00:24:18,874 --> 00:24:20,542
Thanks, Reep. I knew you'd come.

378
00:24:20,709 --> 00:24:21,876
Your Highness. Ha!

379
00:24:29,218 --> 00:24:30,218
Get the keys!

380
00:24:38,477 --> 00:24:39,769
Keys!

381
00:25:15,764 --> 00:25:19,100
Oh, you're a boat in a magical land.
Can't you row yourself?

382
00:25:38,787 --> 00:25:41,122
Oh, God. I hope that wasn't
the British Consul.

383
00:25:43,042 --> 00:25:44,667
Your Majesty. Your Majesty!

384
00:25:44,835 --> 00:25:45,752
Hold it!

385
00:25:45,961 --> 00:25:48,004
My wife was taken
just this morning.

386
00:25:48,172 --> 00:25:49,130
It's all right, Drinian.

387
00:25:49,298 --> 00:25:50,798
I beg you, take me with you.

388
00:25:50,966 --> 00:25:51,966
Gael!

389
00:25:52,134 --> 00:25:54,928
I want to come.
No, Gael, stay with your aunt.

390
00:25:55,095 --> 00:25:58,681
I'm a fine sailor.
Been on the seas my whole life.

391
00:25:58,849 --> 00:26:00,225
Of course, you must.

392
00:26:00,392 --> 00:26:01,935
Thank you.
But, Daddy!

393
00:26:02,102 --> 00:26:03,478
Have I ever
not come back?

394
00:26:05,648 --> 00:26:07,649
Now be good.

395
00:26:12,696 --> 00:26:14,155
My king.

396
00:26:14,657 --> 00:26:16,157
My king.

397
00:26:20,412 --> 00:26:25,166
This was given to me by your father.
I hid it safely in a cave all these years.

398
00:26:25,584 --> 00:26:26,876
That's an old
Narnian sword.

399
00:26:27,086 --> 00:26:28,836
It's from your Golden Age.

400
00:26:29,004 --> 00:26:33,841
There are seven such swords,
gifts from Aslan to protect Narnia.

401
00:26:35,010 --> 00:26:37,637
Your father
entrusted them to us.

402
00:26:38,347 --> 00:26:40,139
Here, take it.

403
00:26:44,019 --> 00:26:45,603
And may it protect you.

404
00:26:55,239 --> 00:26:56,322
Thank you, my lord.

405
00:26:57,408 --> 00:26:59,200
And we shall find your lost citizens.

406
00:27:03,539 --> 00:27:04,706
Edmund.

407
00:27:21,140 --> 00:27:24,892
Dear diary, there has been
an extraordinary turn of events.

408
00:27:25,060 --> 00:27:26,686
I've been abducted by my cousins...

409
00:27:26,854 --> 00:27:30,773
and set adrift in uncharted waters
in some ridiculous-looking boat.

410
00:27:30,941 --> 00:27:34,902
What's worse is I share quarters
with an obnoxious mouse thing.

411
00:27:35,070 --> 00:27:38,197
And I thought bunking with
my cousin was bad enough.

412
00:27:38,365 --> 00:27:40,908
So far, every person I've met
in this strange place...

413
00:27:41,535 --> 00:27:44,120
suffers from the most florid delusions.

414
00:27:44,747 --> 00:27:48,249
Chasing green mists
and looking for lost lords.

415
00:27:48,792 --> 00:27:50,168
I can only assume that this is...

416
00:27:50,336 --> 00:27:52,462
the result of poor diet.

417
00:27:52,921 --> 00:27:54,672
Or they're all just barking mad.

418
00:27:56,925 --> 00:27:59,218
Cousin Edmund is no exception.

419
00:27:59,386 --> 00:28:02,388
He spends every spare second
rubbing that tin sword of his...

420
00:28:02,556 --> 00:28:04,098
like it's some magic lantern.

421
00:28:04,266 --> 00:28:05,892
Poor fool clearly needs a hobby.

422
00:28:06,060 --> 00:28:09,103
It's going to be magnificent.
Do they come in a smaller size?

423
00:28:10,606 --> 00:28:11,606
Peeving marmot!

424
00:28:12,107 --> 00:28:14,901
He's even more deluded than my cousin.

425
00:28:18,781 --> 00:28:21,449
In England, we have mouse traps
for that sort of thing.

426
00:28:23,702 --> 00:28:26,746
Speaking of food, you don't know
where I could get any, do you?

427
00:28:27,331 --> 00:28:30,041
Uh, why are you talking to that bird?

428
00:28:31,251 --> 00:28:32,960
I just naturally assumed you can--

429
00:28:34,421 --> 00:28:36,881
He's talking to birds!

430
00:28:37,049 --> 00:28:38,466
He's mad as a loon,
that one.

431
00:28:38,634 --> 00:28:39,550
Yeah!

432
00:28:41,220 --> 00:28:43,638
Shoo! Go on, get off!

433
00:29:07,496 --> 00:29:09,622
Are you aware...

434
00:29:09,790 --> 00:29:13,167
that stealing rations
is a capital offense at sea?

435
00:29:13,502 --> 00:29:16,045
Up here.

436
00:29:16,630 --> 00:29:17,839
Oh, you.

437
00:29:18,715 --> 00:29:20,508
Men have been keelhauled for less.

438
00:29:20,676 --> 00:29:21,509
For what?

439
00:29:21,677 --> 00:29:22,677
For treason...

440
00:29:22,845 --> 00:29:24,846
and sneakiness
and general nuisancery.

441
00:29:25,013 --> 00:29:27,974
Look, just hand over the orange
and we'll let the matter pass.

442
00:29:28,142 --> 00:29:29,559
I don't know
what you're talking about.

443
00:29:29,810 --> 00:29:31,352
Allow me to cla--

444
00:29:31,520 --> 00:29:33,020
Look, I've had quite enough of you.

445
00:29:33,188 --> 00:29:35,690
Unhand the tail.

446
00:29:36,024 --> 00:29:38,151
The great Aslan himself
gave me this tail.

447
00:29:38,318 --> 00:29:38,943
No one...

448
00:29:39,111 --> 00:29:41,654
repeat, no one touches the tail.

449
00:29:42,030 --> 00:29:42,822
Period.

450
00:29:42,990 --> 00:29:44,115
Exclamation mark.

451
00:29:44,283 --> 00:29:45,241
Sorry.

452
00:29:45,492 --> 00:29:47,326
Now, I will have the orange...

453
00:29:47,494 --> 00:29:49,370
then I will have satisfaction.

454
00:29:49,538 --> 00:29:51,330
Please, I'm a pacifist.

455
00:29:51,498 --> 00:29:52,373
En garde!

456
00:29:58,046 --> 00:29:59,672
Watch it!
Sorry.

457
00:30:03,844 --> 00:30:05,094
Trying to run away?

458
00:30:05,345 --> 00:30:06,888
We're on a boat, you know.

459
00:30:07,055 --> 00:30:08,723
Look, can't we just discuss this?

460
00:30:09,516 --> 00:30:10,808
That was for stealing...

461
00:30:10,976 --> 00:30:12,226
that was for lying...

462
00:30:12,561 --> 00:30:15,354
and that was for good measure.

463
00:30:17,232 --> 00:30:20,234
That's the spirit!
We have ourselves a duel.

464
00:30:20,402 --> 00:30:21,777
Catch.

465
00:30:22,196 --> 00:30:23,696
Now, come on.

466
00:30:23,864 --> 00:30:25,364
Take your best shot.

467
00:30:25,532 --> 00:30:27,366
Is that it? Come on, boy.

468
00:30:27,993 --> 00:30:29,243
Focus! Focus!

469
00:30:30,078 --> 00:30:31,746
Yes! Ha!

470
00:30:32,414 --> 00:30:36,209
Stop flapping your wings
like a drunken pelican! Poise.

471
00:30:36,502 --> 00:30:37,335
Keep your blade up.

472
00:30:37,503 --> 00:30:38,419
Up, up! That's it.

473
00:30:38,587 --> 00:30:39,253
Now...

474
00:30:43,926 --> 00:30:45,218
Ha-ha-ha! Yah!

475
00:30:45,719 --> 00:30:46,677
Yoo-hoo!

476
00:30:46,845 --> 00:30:48,095
Over here.

477
00:30:48,263 --> 00:30:49,931
Now, lunge with your foot.

478
00:30:50,599 --> 00:30:51,933
Not your left, your right.

479
00:30:52,142 --> 00:30:54,936
Got it? Come on.
Be nimble! Be nimble!

480
00:30:55,103 --> 00:30:56,854
It's a dance, boy, a dance.

481
00:30:57,022 --> 00:30:58,773
Come on now, again and again.

482
00:30:58,941 --> 00:31:00,274
That's right, that's right.

483
00:31:01,944 --> 00:31:03,277
Oh, no!

484
00:31:10,285 --> 00:31:11,327
And that...

485
00:31:12,246 --> 00:31:13,287
is that.

486
00:31:19,086 --> 00:31:20,336
Look.

487
00:31:22,589 --> 00:31:23,756
Gael?

488
00:31:24,424 --> 00:31:26,425
What are you doing here?

489
00:31:33,058 --> 00:31:34,350
Here.

490
00:31:44,653 --> 00:31:46,153
Looks like we have an extra...

491
00:31:46,321 --> 00:31:47,822
crew member.

492
00:31:55,664 --> 00:31:56,664
Welcome aboard.

493
00:31:56,873 --> 00:31:58,040
Your Majesty.

494
00:31:58,208 --> 00:31:59,292
Call me Lucy.

495
00:31:59,626 --> 00:32:00,668
Come on.

496
00:32:01,336 --> 00:32:02,962
Come on, look lively.

497
00:32:03,213 --> 00:32:04,589
Back to work.

498
00:32:06,675 --> 00:32:08,009
Good match.

499
00:32:08,385 --> 00:32:10,094
I'll make a swordsman of you yet.

500
00:32:12,222 --> 00:32:16,058
Yes, well, if the playing field
were a little more even...

501
00:32:16,226 --> 00:32:18,019
it would've been
an entirely different result.

502
00:32:18,186 --> 00:32:20,521
Heh-heh-heh. Indeed.

503
00:32:32,868 --> 00:32:34,869
It looks uninhabited.

504
00:32:35,037 --> 00:32:38,706
But if the lords followed the mist east,
they would have stopped here.

505
00:32:38,874 --> 00:32:40,875
Could be a trap.

506
00:32:41,835 --> 00:32:43,669
Or it could hold some answers.

507
00:32:44,212 --> 00:32:45,838
Caspian?

508
00:32:47,966 --> 00:32:51,093
We'll spend the night on shore.
Scour the island in the morning.

509
00:32:51,261 --> 00:32:52,553
Aye, your Majesty.

510
00:33:12,199 --> 00:33:14,575
Seems they've brought a pig.

511
00:33:18,664 --> 00:33:20,873
This one, it's female.

512
00:33:23,460 --> 00:33:25,878
So is this one.

513
00:33:26,922 --> 00:33:29,965
This one reads.

514
00:33:30,425 --> 00:33:31,592
Let's take her.

515
00:34:07,087 --> 00:34:09,130
There is no escape.

516
00:34:09,339 --> 00:34:10,965
- Well put.
- Scary.

517
00:34:11,133 --> 00:34:12,591
- Yeah.
- What are you?

518
00:34:12,759 --> 00:34:15,052
We are terrifying invisible beasts.

519
00:34:15,220 --> 00:34:18,305
If you could see us,
you would be really intimidated.

520
00:34:18,640 --> 00:34:21,934
You forgot to mention
that we are very large.

521
00:34:22,102 --> 00:34:23,561
- Well, what do you want?
- You.

522
00:34:24,312 --> 00:34:25,646
You'll do what we ask.

523
00:34:25,814 --> 00:34:27,314
- She will.
- Very clear.

524
00:34:27,482 --> 00:34:29,316
- Well put.
- Yeah.

525
00:34:30,360 --> 00:34:31,193
Or what?

526
00:34:31,361 --> 00:34:32,445
Or death.

527
00:34:32,612 --> 00:34:34,113
Death? Death? Death?

528
00:34:34,281 --> 00:34:37,491
Death. Death. Death.

529
00:34:39,119 --> 00:34:42,496
Well, I wouldn't be much use
to you dead, would I?

530
00:34:42,664 --> 00:34:43,998
I hadn't thought of that.

531
00:34:44,166 --> 00:34:45,291
No, you hadn't.

532
00:34:45,459 --> 00:34:46,709
Fair point.

533
00:34:46,877 --> 00:34:50,463
All right,
then we'll just kill your friends.

534
00:34:50,630 --> 00:34:51,839
Ooh.

535
00:34:52,007 --> 00:34:53,466
Good idea.

536
00:34:53,633 --> 00:34:55,718
What do you want with me?

537
00:34:55,886 --> 00:34:58,179
You will enter the house...

538
00:34:58,346 --> 00:34:59,805
of The Oppressor.

539
00:35:00,515 --> 00:35:01,724
What house?

540
00:35:01,892 --> 00:35:03,517
This one.

541
00:35:10,025 --> 00:35:13,652
Upstairs, you'll find
The Book of incantations.

542
00:35:13,820 --> 00:35:17,364
Recite the spell
that makes the unseen seen.

543
00:35:17,532 --> 00:35:19,241
Well put, Chief. Well put.

544
00:35:19,409 --> 00:35:20,534
Yeah.

545
00:35:20,702 --> 00:35:22,036
Yeah.

546
00:35:23,371 --> 00:35:25,372
Well, go on. We haven't got all day.

547
00:35:25,540 --> 00:35:27,208
Remember what will happen
to your friends.

548
00:35:27,417 --> 00:35:29,001
You've been warned.

549
00:35:29,169 --> 00:35:30,503
Yeah. Yeah.

550
00:35:30,670 --> 00:35:32,004
- Yeah.
- Right.

551
00:35:32,214 --> 00:35:33,339
Right.

552
00:35:33,507 --> 00:35:34,507
Yeah.

553
00:35:34,674 --> 00:35:36,175
Why don't you do it yourselves?

554
00:35:36,885 --> 00:35:38,385
We can't read.

555
00:35:38,553 --> 00:35:41,639
Can't write either, as a matter of fact.

556
00:35:41,807 --> 00:35:43,098
Or add.

557
00:35:43,308 --> 00:35:44,725
Yeah.

558
00:35:45,393 --> 00:35:48,062
Why didn't you just say so?

559
00:35:48,313 --> 00:35:49,897
Beware The Oppressor.

560
00:35:50,065 --> 00:35:51,732
He's very oppressive.

561
00:35:52,567 --> 00:35:55,152
"What makes the unseen seen," got it?

562
00:35:55,320 --> 00:35:56,362
Don't forget.

563
00:35:56,530 --> 00:35:59,073
- Don't forget that.
- Yeah.

564
00:36:10,585 --> 00:36:11,710
Ed.

565
00:36:12,838 --> 00:36:13,963
Ed, wake up.

566
00:36:14,548 --> 00:36:16,215
Wake up, look.

567
00:36:24,933 --> 00:36:26,433
Where's Lucy?

568
00:36:26,601 --> 00:36:28,060
Lucy?

569
00:36:28,228 --> 00:36:29,144
Lucy!

570
00:36:29,354 --> 00:36:30,938
Everybody up!

571
00:36:31,147 --> 00:36:31,981
Get up.

572
00:36:32,232 --> 00:36:33,107
Get up, I said!

573
00:36:35,610 --> 00:36:36,777
This way!

574
00:36:36,945 --> 00:36:38,112
Move, you blackguards.

575
00:37:41,176 --> 00:37:44,803
"With these words
Your tongue must sew

576
00:37:44,971 --> 00:37:48,682
For all around there to be snow"

577
00:38:38,483 --> 00:38:40,025
"An infallible spell"

578
00:38:40,193 --> 00:38:41,735
To make you she

579
00:38:41,903 --> 00:38:43,821
"The beauty you've always wanted to be"

580
00:38:54,916 --> 00:38:56,917
Susan, what's going...

581
00:38:58,086 --> 00:38:59,753
...on?

582
00:39:04,259 --> 00:39:06,260
I'm beautiful.

583
00:39:18,273 --> 00:39:19,440
No, wait!

584
00:39:21,401 --> 00:39:23,402
"Make me she, whom I'd agree..."

585
00:39:32,579 --> 00:39:33,954
Lucy!

586
00:39:34,789 --> 00:39:36,165
Lucy.

587
00:39:36,332 --> 00:39:40,544
Aslan?

588
00:39:55,643 --> 00:39:57,978
"A spell to make the unseen seen."

589
00:39:59,647 --> 00:40:02,566
"Like the 'p' in psychology"

590
00:40:02,734 --> 00:40:04,860
The 'h' in psychiatry

591
00:40:05,070 --> 00:40:08,280
Invisible ink
And the truth in theology

592
00:40:08,448 --> 00:40:09,782
Caspian, Lucy's dagger.

593
00:40:15,163 --> 00:40:17,956
Stop right there or perish.

594
00:40:23,213 --> 00:40:25,964
The spell is complete

595
00:40:26,132 --> 00:40:28,842
"Now all is visible"

596
00:40:51,157 --> 00:40:53,492
- What sort of creatures are you?
- Big ones...

597
00:40:53,660 --> 00:40:55,911
with the head of a tiger
and the body of a...

598
00:40:56,371 --> 00:40:58,038
Different tiger.

599
00:40:58,331 --> 00:41:00,165
You don't want to mess with us.

600
00:41:00,500 --> 00:41:01,500
Or what?

601
00:41:01,668 --> 00:41:04,169
Or I'll claw you to death.

602
00:41:05,046 --> 00:41:08,882
And I'll ram my tusks right through you.

603
00:41:09,050 --> 00:41:10,717
And I'll gnash you with my teeth.

604
00:41:10,885 --> 00:41:13,720
And I'll bite you with my fangs. Grrr!

605
00:41:13,888 --> 00:41:16,223
You mean squash us
with your fat bellies?

606
00:41:16,391 --> 00:41:17,432
Yes!

607
00:41:17,725 --> 00:41:18,725
Fat bellies?

608
00:41:18,893 --> 00:41:19,852
Tickle us with your toes?

609
00:41:23,189 --> 00:41:25,941
What have you done with my sister,
you little pip-squeak?

610
00:41:26,651 --> 00:41:27,860
Now, calm down.

611
00:41:28,027 --> 00:41:29,027
Where is she?

612
00:41:29,195 --> 00:41:31,405
- You better tell him.
- Go on, Chief, tell him.

613
00:41:31,573 --> 00:41:32,698
In the mansion.

614
00:41:32,866 --> 00:41:33,866
What mansion?

615
00:41:43,084 --> 00:41:44,543
Oh.

616
00:41:44,711 --> 00:41:46,253
That mansion.

617
00:41:46,713 --> 00:41:49,089
I'm really getting tired
of you all leaving me behi--

618
00:41:49,257 --> 00:41:51,842
- It's the pig!
- The pig has come back.

619
00:41:52,302 --> 00:41:54,094
This place just gets
weirder and weirder.

620
00:41:54,262 --> 00:41:56,263
- Weird?
- Him calling us weird?

621
00:41:57,599 --> 00:42:01,310
- The Oppressor!
- The Oppressor! The Oppressor!

622
00:42:02,270 --> 00:42:03,270
Lucy.

623
00:42:04,189 --> 00:42:05,397
Your Majesty.

624
00:42:06,107 --> 00:42:08,317
Caspian and Edmund.

625
00:42:08,484 --> 00:42:11,403
This is Coriakin. It's his island.

626
00:42:11,571 --> 00:42:13,113
That's what he thinks.

627
00:42:13,281 --> 00:42:14,823
You have wronged us, magician.

628
00:42:15,408 --> 00:42:17,284
I have not wronged you.

629
00:42:17,452 --> 00:42:19,995
I made you invisible
for your own protection.

630
00:42:20,205 --> 00:42:21,121
Protection?

631
00:42:21,289 --> 00:42:23,081
- That's oppressive!
- Oppressor!

632
00:42:23,249 --> 00:42:24,958
I have not oppressed you.

633
00:42:25,126 --> 00:42:27,461
But you could've, if you'd wanted to.

634
00:42:27,754 --> 00:42:28,754
Begone.

635
00:42:29,297 --> 00:42:31,298
It's a spell!

636
00:42:31,633 --> 00:42:33,091
What was that?

637
00:42:33,468 --> 00:42:34,343
Lint.

638
00:42:34,844 --> 00:42:36,094
But don't tell them.

639
00:42:39,265 --> 00:42:40,474
What were those things?

640
00:42:40,642 --> 00:42:42,351
Dufflepuds.

641
00:42:42,769 --> 00:42:44,519
Right, of course. Silly me.

642
00:42:47,482 --> 00:42:51,109
What did you mean when you said you
made them invisible for their own good?

643
00:42:51,277 --> 00:42:53,946
It seemed the easiest way
to protect them...

644
00:42:54,155 --> 00:42:56,198
from the evil.

645
00:42:56,824 --> 00:42:58,825
You mean the mist?

646
00:42:59,619 --> 00:43:02,496
I mean what lies
behind the mist.

647
00:43:21,015 --> 00:43:22,516
That's quite beautiful.

648
00:43:30,942 --> 00:43:34,486
I mean, for a make-believe map
of a make-believe world.

649
00:43:34,654 --> 00:43:36,113
There is the source of your troubles.

650
00:43:37,740 --> 00:43:39,157
Dark island.

651
00:43:40,493 --> 00:43:42,911
A place where evil lurks.

652
00:43:44,956 --> 00:43:49,876
It can take any form. It can make
your darkest dreams come true.

653
00:43:51,713 --> 00:43:53,797
It seeks to corrupt all goodness...

654
00:43:55,383 --> 00:43:57,676
to steal the light from this world.

655
00:43:58,052 --> 00:43:59,219
How do we stop it?

656
00:43:59,887 --> 00:44:02,681
You must break its spell.

657
00:44:02,849 --> 00:44:06,727
That sword you carry...
there are six others.

658
00:44:06,894 --> 00:44:08,478
Have you seen them?
Yes.

659
00:44:08,646 --> 00:44:11,064
The six lords,
they passed through here?

660
00:44:11,316 --> 00:44:12,649
Indeed.

661
00:44:12,817 --> 00:44:13,900
Where were they headed?

662
00:44:14,068 --> 00:44:15,986
Where I sent them.

663
00:44:19,324 --> 00:44:20,991
To break the spell...

664
00:44:22,327 --> 00:44:24,578
you must follow the Blue Star...

665
00:44:25,663 --> 00:44:27,998
to Ramandu's Island.

666
00:44:28,166 --> 00:44:32,419
There, the seven swords
must be laid at Asian's table.

667
00:44:32,587 --> 00:44:35,255
Only then can their true
magical power be released.

668
00:44:38,426 --> 00:44:39,760
But beware...

669
00:44:39,927 --> 00:44:42,971
you are all about to be tested.

670
00:44:43,139 --> 00:44:44,431
Tested?

671
00:44:46,434 --> 00:44:51,271
Until you lay down the seventh sword,
evil has the upper hand.

672
00:44:52,607 --> 00:44:53,940
It will do everything...

673
00:44:54,108 --> 00:44:55,776
in its power...

674
00:44:55,943 --> 00:44:58,195
to tempt you.

675
00:45:03,451 --> 00:45:04,868
Be strong.

676
00:45:06,871 --> 00:45:09,873
Don't fall to temptation.

677
00:45:10,583 --> 00:45:13,585
To defeat
the darkness out there...

678
00:45:13,753 --> 00:45:15,962
you must defeat the darkness
inside yourself.

679
00:45:46,160 --> 00:45:48,495
For reasons beyond my comprehension...

680
00:45:48,663 --> 00:45:50,997
we've taken the advice
of a senile old coot...

681
00:45:51,165 --> 00:45:55,293
who doesn't possess a razor
and dawdles around in a dressing gown.

682
00:45:55,461 --> 00:46:00,465
So we're back in this tub
and lost in a tempest. Brilliant!

683
00:46:00,633 --> 00:46:02,509
Hold!

684
00:46:03,636 --> 00:46:05,595
Three spokes to starboard.

685
00:46:05,763 --> 00:46:07,013
Aye-aye, sir.

686
00:46:07,181 --> 00:46:08,265
More pails here.

687
00:46:08,433 --> 00:46:10,016
Pass it down!

688
00:46:10,184 --> 00:46:11,852
Heave!

689
00:46:12,603 --> 00:46:16,982
Fourteen days of being tossed like
a pancake and not the slightest sign of land.

690
00:46:21,654 --> 00:46:24,531
The only consolation is,
everyone is finally...

691
00:46:24,699 --> 00:46:25,782
as miserable as I am.

692
00:46:28,703 --> 00:46:31,621
Except for that show-off talking rat.

693
00:46:31,789 --> 00:46:36,209
He's one of those annoying
glass-is-always-half-full types.

694
00:46:39,505 --> 00:46:42,299
So we're stuck here...

695
00:46:43,384 --> 00:46:48,221
at half-rations, with food and water
for two more weeks, maximum.

696
00:46:49,056 --> 00:46:52,058
This is your last chance to turn back,
Your Majesties.

697
00:46:53,060 --> 00:46:56,188
There's no guarantee we'll spot
the Blue Star anytime soon.

698
00:46:56,355 --> 00:46:57,564
Not in this storm.

699
00:46:58,399 --> 00:47:01,568
Needle in a haystack, trying
to find this Ramandu place.

700
00:47:01,736 --> 00:47:04,237
We could sail right past it
and off the edge of the world.

701
00:47:04,405 --> 00:47:06,239
Or get eaten by a sea serpent.

702
00:47:08,701 --> 00:47:11,244
I'm just saying the men
are getting nervous.

703
00:47:11,996 --> 00:47:14,581
These are strange seas
we're sailing...

704
00:47:14,749 --> 00:47:17,375
the likes of which
I've never seen before.

705
00:47:17,543 --> 00:47:20,921
Then perhaps, Captain, you would like
to be the one to explain to Mr. Rhince...

706
00:47:21,088 --> 00:47:23,089
that we're abandoning
the search for his family.

707
00:47:26,260 --> 00:47:28,053
I'll get back to it.

708
00:47:31,015 --> 00:47:32,432
Just a word of warning.

709
00:47:34,352 --> 00:47:38,104
The sea can play nasty tricks
on the crew's mind.

710
00:47:38,689 --> 00:47:40,273
Very nasty.

711
00:48:12,640 --> 00:48:14,474
Trensform my reflection

712
00:48:14,642 --> 00:48:18,979
Cast into perfection
Lashes, lips and complexion

713
00:48:19,146 --> 00:48:20,272
Make me she

714
00:48:20,439 --> 00:48:24,776
Whom I'd agree
Holds more beauty over me

715
00:49:31,010 --> 00:49:32,552
Ladies and gentlemen...

716
00:49:32,720 --> 00:49:34,387
Miss Pevensie.

717
00:49:37,433 --> 00:49:39,893
She's quite a looker. Swell.

718
00:49:40,144 --> 00:49:40,977
Edmund!

719
00:49:41,145 --> 00:49:42,687
You look beautiful, sister.

720
00:49:42,897 --> 00:49:44,064
As always.

721
00:49:44,231 --> 00:49:46,024
Peter!

722
00:49:46,359 --> 00:49:48,485
Excuse me, miss,
can I get a photo?

723
00:49:48,653 --> 00:49:50,403
Mother's going to love this.

724
00:49:50,571 --> 00:49:52,405
All her children in one picture.

725
00:49:52,573 --> 00:49:53,740
Smile.

726
00:49:53,908 --> 00:49:57,661
Hang on, where am I?
I mean, where's Lucy?

727
00:49:57,828 --> 00:50:00,163
Lucy? Who's Lucy?

728
00:50:00,998 --> 00:50:02,832
Susan, what's wrong?

729
00:50:03,084 --> 00:50:05,543
Come on now, miss.
Nice big smile.

730
00:50:05,711 --> 00:50:08,380
Edmund, I'm not sure about all this.
I think I want to go back.

731
00:50:08,547 --> 00:50:09,506
Go back where?

732
00:50:09,674 --> 00:50:11,007
To Narnia.

733
00:50:11,175 --> 00:50:13,218
What on earth is Narnia?

734
00:50:13,386 --> 00:50:15,428
What's going on?
Stop this!

735
00:50:23,229 --> 00:50:24,437
Lucy.

736
00:50:25,856 --> 00:50:27,232
Aslan?

737
00:50:31,028 --> 00:50:33,446
What have you done, child?

738
00:50:34,532 --> 00:50:35,865
I don't know.

739
00:50:36,784 --> 00:50:38,326
That was awful.

740
00:50:38,953 --> 00:50:41,121
But you chose it, Lucy.

741
00:50:42,373 --> 00:50:45,125
I didn't mean to choose
all of that.

742
00:50:45,292 --> 00:50:48,461
I just wanted to be beautiful
like Susan.

743
00:50:49,255 --> 00:50:51,256
That's all.

744
00:50:51,757 --> 00:50:55,885
You wished yourself away,
and with it much more.

745
00:50:56,053 --> 00:50:59,931
Your brothers and sister wouldn't
know Narnia without you, Lucy.

746
00:51:00,099 --> 00:51:03,476
You discovered it first,
remember?

747
00:51:05,229 --> 00:51:07,188
I'm so sorry.

748
00:51:07,982 --> 00:51:10,775
You doubt your value.

749
00:51:10,943 --> 00:51:13,778
Don't run from who you are.

750
00:51:15,823 --> 00:51:17,240
Aslan!

751
00:52:08,042 --> 00:52:11,127
Father! Father...

752
00:52:13,047 --> 00:52:15,465
Edmund. Edmund.

753
00:52:18,052 --> 00:52:21,721
Come with me. Join me.

754
00:52:24,892 --> 00:52:26,142
Edmund.

755
00:52:30,314 --> 00:52:32,315
Oh, Lucy.

756
00:52:34,735 --> 00:52:36,194
I can't sleep.

757
00:52:37,029 --> 00:52:38,279
Let me guess.

758
00:52:38,781 --> 00:52:40,240
Bad dreams.

759
00:52:41,659 --> 00:52:44,160
So either we're all going mad...

760
00:52:45,412 --> 00:52:48,581
or something is
playing with our minds.

761
00:53:09,436 --> 00:53:11,604
I doubt the lords stopped here,
my liege.

762
00:53:11,772 --> 00:53:13,731
There's no sign of anything living.

763
00:53:13,899 --> 00:53:14,732
Right.

764
00:53:14,900 --> 00:53:18,152
Well, once we get ashore, take your men
and search for food and water.

765
00:53:18,320 --> 00:53:20,029
The three of us will look for clues.

766
00:53:20,197 --> 00:53:21,698
Hang on,
you mean the four of us.

767
00:53:24,326 --> 00:53:26,703
Come on, please don't
send me back to the rat.

768
00:53:26,871 --> 00:53:28,538
I heard that.

769
00:53:30,374 --> 00:53:31,291
Big ears.

770
00:53:31,542 --> 00:53:33,209
I heard that too.

771
00:53:39,216 --> 00:53:40,925
Go on, unload it all.

772
00:53:51,145 --> 00:53:53,479
Look, we're not
the first ones on this island.

773
00:53:53,647 --> 00:53:54,606
The lords?

774
00:53:55,149 --> 00:53:57,150
Could be.

775
00:54:01,572 --> 00:54:03,281
What do you think could be down there?

776
00:54:04,742 --> 00:54:06,576
Let's find out.

777
00:54:42,696 --> 00:54:44,280
What's that?

778
00:54:44,448 --> 00:54:45,657
I don't know.

779
00:54:45,824 --> 00:54:48,201
Looks like some sort of gold statue.

780
00:55:07,471 --> 00:55:08,554
Ah!

781
00:55:19,441 --> 00:55:21,526
He must have fallen in.

782
00:55:22,569 --> 00:55:23,653
Poor man.

783
00:55:24,196 --> 00:55:25,613
You mean, "poor lord."

784
00:55:25,781 --> 00:55:27,031
The crest of Lord Restimar.

785
00:55:27,282 --> 00:55:28,366
And his sword.

786
00:55:28,534 --> 00:55:29,575
We need it.

787
00:55:32,913 --> 00:55:34,247
Be careful.

788
00:55:38,877 --> 00:55:40,837
Your sword hasn't turned to gold.

789
00:55:41,005 --> 00:55:42,338
Both the swords are magical.

790
00:55:43,966 --> 00:55:45,383
Here.

791
00:55:48,262 --> 00:55:49,887
He mustn't have known
what hit him.

792
00:55:50,931 --> 00:55:51,931
Maybe.

793
00:55:53,267 --> 00:55:55,601
Or maybe he was
onto something.

794
00:55:56,770 --> 00:55:58,104
What are you talking about?

795
00:56:18,042 --> 00:56:19,459
What are you staring at?

796
00:56:21,503 --> 00:56:24,505
Whoever has access to this pool...

797
00:56:25,257 --> 00:56:27,759
could be the most powerful
person in the world.

798
00:56:31,638 --> 00:56:35,141
Lucy, we'd be so rich.

799
00:56:35,309 --> 00:56:37,226
No one could tell us what to do...

800
00:56:37,394 --> 00:56:39,062
or who to live with.

801
00:56:39,229 --> 00:56:41,564
You can't take anything
out of Narnia, Edmund.

802
00:56:41,815 --> 00:56:43,399
Says who?

803
00:56:44,276 --> 00:56:45,443
I do.

804
00:56:52,993 --> 00:56:54,827
I'm not your subject.

805
00:56:55,412 --> 00:56:57,163
You've been waiting for this,
haven't you?

806
00:56:57,331 --> 00:56:59,290
To challenge me?
You doubt my leadership?

807
00:56:59,458 --> 00:57:00,917
You doubt yourself.

808
00:57:01,085 --> 00:57:01,793
You're a child!

809
00:57:01,960 --> 00:57:03,252
And you're a spineless sap!

810
00:57:03,420 --> 00:57:04,170
Edmund.

811
00:57:04,338 --> 00:57:06,130
I'm tired of playing second fiddle.

812
00:57:06,298 --> 00:57:08,674
First it was Peter and now it's you!

813
00:57:09,009 --> 00:57:11,135
You know I'm braver than both of you.

814
00:57:11,345 --> 00:57:13,346
Why do you get Peter's sword?

815
00:57:13,764 --> 00:57:17,141
I deserve a kingdom of my own.
I deserve to rule!

816
00:57:17,309 --> 00:57:19,644
If you think you're so brave,
prove it!

817
00:57:20,062 --> 00:57:21,354
Ah!

818
00:57:22,481 --> 00:57:23,439
No!

819
00:57:24,024 --> 00:57:25,775
Stop it!

820
00:57:25,943 --> 00:57:27,026
Both of you!

821
00:57:28,862 --> 00:57:30,696
Look at yourselves.

822
00:57:30,864 --> 00:57:32,490
Can't you see what's happening?

823
00:57:33,784 --> 00:57:35,159
This place has tempted you.

824
00:57:36,078 --> 00:57:37,995
It's bewitching you.

825
00:57:38,705 --> 00:57:40,581
This is exactly what Coriakin
was talking about.

826
00:57:42,209 --> 00:57:44,377
Let's just get out of here.

827
00:58:07,609 --> 00:58:12,572
Oh, yes, follow the imaginary Blue Star
to the island of Ramandoodoo.

828
00:58:13,699 --> 00:58:17,410
Lay the seven steak knives
at the table of a talking lion.

829
00:58:18,495 --> 00:58:19,912
Ninnies!

830
00:58:30,799 --> 00:58:31,591
What is that?

831
00:58:46,231 --> 00:58:48,232
I must be dead.

832
00:59:10,964 --> 00:59:11,964
Ah!

833
00:59:14,927 --> 00:59:16,928
You're definitely dead.

834
00:59:23,060 --> 00:59:25,436
Won't be needing that then,
will you?

835
00:59:40,994 --> 00:59:42,286
Finally...

836
00:59:42,704 --> 00:59:44,956
a favorable turn of events.

837
00:59:54,174 --> 00:59:55,174
What food did you find?

838
00:59:58,011 --> 00:59:59,637
It's volcanic, Your Majesty.

839
00:59:59,846 --> 01:00:01,389
Not much grows.

840
01:00:02,432 --> 01:00:03,933
Where's Eustace?

841
01:00:05,352 --> 01:00:08,771
I believe he's out,
not helping us load the boats.

842
01:00:08,939 --> 01:00:10,106
Eustace!

843
01:00:11,108 --> 01:00:12,483
Eustace!

844
01:00:15,862 --> 01:00:17,530
Edmund, I've got a bad feeling.

845
01:00:18,365 --> 01:00:19,615
I'll go find him.

846
01:00:20,367 --> 01:00:21,367
I'll come with you.

847
01:00:31,670 --> 01:00:33,629
Eustace!

848
01:00:34,798 --> 01:00:36,882
Eustace!

849
01:00:41,555 --> 01:00:43,556
Treasure.

850
01:00:45,225 --> 01:00:46,642
Trouble.

851
01:00:56,069 --> 01:00:57,445
Eustace.

852
01:01:02,117 --> 01:01:03,034
No!

853
01:01:08,915 --> 01:01:10,583
Oh, cousin.

854
01:01:12,502 --> 01:01:13,794
I'm sorry.

855
01:01:13,962 --> 01:01:15,463
He was just a boy.

856
01:01:17,924 --> 01:01:19,925
I never should have left him.

857
01:01:24,139 --> 01:01:25,723
What could have happened
to him?

858
01:01:26,641 --> 01:01:31,437
In this place? Anything.
And he wasn't the first.

859
01:01:35,025 --> 01:01:37,151
It's Lord Octesian.

860
01:01:39,946 --> 01:01:41,030
We should find his...

861
01:01:43,450 --> 01:01:45,201
...sword.

862
01:02:03,804 --> 01:02:04,887
What was that?

863
01:02:09,518 --> 01:02:10,893
Is it the volcano?

864
01:02:12,604 --> 01:02:15,898
Oh, no. That's no volcano.

865
01:02:16,233 --> 01:02:17,608
All hands on deck there!

866
01:02:22,406 --> 01:02:25,074
Archers, arm yourselves!

867
01:02:29,913 --> 01:02:31,539
Here, here!

868
01:02:31,706 --> 01:02:33,290
Take one and pass them on.

869
01:02:43,677 --> 01:02:45,177
Take your positions...

870
01:02:45,345 --> 01:02:46,679
and wait for my command.

871
01:02:54,646 --> 01:02:56,021
What's it doing?

872
01:02:56,648 --> 01:02:57,648
Fire!

873
01:02:58,024 --> 01:02:58,774
Fire.

874
01:02:58,942 --> 01:02:59,942
Fire.

875
01:03:02,320 --> 01:03:04,113
He'll break the mast.

876
01:03:09,453 --> 01:03:10,536
Right!

877
01:03:12,247 --> 01:03:13,998
Hold your positions!

878
01:03:16,585 --> 01:03:18,169
- Fire!
- Fire!

879
01:03:24,551 --> 01:03:26,177
Take that!

880
01:03:46,781 --> 01:03:47,573
Edmund!

881
01:03:47,782 --> 01:03:48,991
Ed!

882
01:03:53,413 --> 01:03:54,538
Edmund!

883
01:03:54,706 --> 01:03:58,417
Lucy! Lucy!

884
01:04:23,360 --> 01:04:25,361
You have got to be joking.

885
01:04:35,956 --> 01:04:38,040
He must have been tempted
by the treasure.

886
01:04:39,334 --> 01:04:41,126
Anyone knows a dragon's
treasure is enchanted.

887
01:04:43,046 --> 01:04:44,630
Well, anyone from here.

888
01:05:00,480 --> 01:05:03,274
Is there any way to change him back?
Not that I know of.

889
01:05:07,279 --> 01:05:08,904
Aunt Alberta will not be pleased.

890
01:05:10,365 --> 01:05:13,909
Sorry about the hand, old boy.
I can be a little overzealous at times.

891
01:05:15,829 --> 01:05:17,371
The boats are ready, Sire.

892
01:05:17,539 --> 01:05:18,706
We can't leave him alone.

893
01:05:18,873 --> 01:05:21,500
We can't bring him on board,
Your Majesty.

894
01:05:21,668 --> 01:05:23,586
Drinian, you and the others
take one boat back.

895
01:05:23,753 --> 01:05:25,504
The rest of us will
stay here till morning...

896
01:05:26,089 --> 01:05:27,172
and work out what to do.

897
01:05:27,340 --> 01:05:29,675
But you've no provisions,
and no means...

898
01:05:29,843 --> 01:05:31,260
of staying warm, Your Majesty.

899
01:05:35,473 --> 01:05:36,599
You were saying?

900
01:05:45,400 --> 01:05:48,193
I've never seen these
constellations before.

901
01:05:49,029 --> 01:05:51,030
Me neither.

902
01:05:52,365 --> 01:05:54,617
We're a long way from home.

903
01:05:54,784 --> 01:05:58,829
When I was a boy I used to imagine
sailing to the end of the world...

904
01:06:00,248 --> 01:06:02,249
finding my father there.

905
01:06:05,211 --> 01:06:07,212
Maybe you will.

906
01:06:20,852 --> 01:06:22,770
I miss my mummy.

907
01:06:27,275 --> 01:06:29,735
I miss mine too.

908
01:06:29,903 --> 01:06:31,945
Don't worry, you'll see her again.

909
01:06:32,113 --> 01:06:33,322
How do you know?

910
01:06:33,531 --> 01:06:36,742
You just have to have faith
about these things.

911
01:06:36,910 --> 01:06:38,410
Aslan will help us.

912
01:06:45,752 --> 01:06:48,545
But Aslan couldn't stop her
from being taken.

913
01:06:49,297 --> 01:06:51,507
We'll find her. I promise.

914
01:06:53,677 --> 01:06:55,260
Somehow.

915
01:07:11,986 --> 01:07:13,320
Hmm.

916
01:07:21,705 --> 01:07:22,788
Trouble sleeping?

917
01:07:24,666 --> 01:07:26,291
Now, now.

918
01:07:26,459 --> 01:07:28,919
All is not as lost as it seems.

919
01:07:30,004 --> 01:07:32,297
I'll stay up with you if you wish...

920
01:07:32,465 --> 01:07:34,466
keep you company.

921
01:07:35,552 --> 01:07:38,470
I'll wager you didn't even believe
in dragons this morning.

922
01:07:40,515 --> 01:07:41,515
Yes.

923
01:07:42,517 --> 01:07:43,976
You know...

924
01:07:44,144 --> 01:07:49,148
extraordinary things only happen
to extraordinary people.

925
01:07:50,358 --> 01:07:52,484
Maybe it's a sign...

926
01:07:52,652 --> 01:07:55,654
that you've got
an extraordinary destiny.

927
01:07:56,531 --> 01:08:00,617
Something greater than
you could have imagined.

928
01:08:03,329 --> 01:08:06,457
I could tell you one or two
of my adventures if you like...

929
01:08:06,624 --> 01:08:09,251
just to pass the time.

930
01:08:09,461 --> 01:08:13,005
Believe it or not, you're not
the first dragon I've encountered.

931
01:08:13,173 --> 01:08:15,758
Many years ago,
too many than I care to mention...

932
01:08:15,925 --> 01:08:17,509
I was with a band of pirates.

933
01:08:17,719 --> 01:08:20,679
I met another dragon,
much fiercer than you...

934
01:08:31,441 --> 01:08:32,357
Lucy!

935
01:08:32,525 --> 01:08:34,860
Lucy, wake up!

936
01:08:35,570 --> 01:08:36,361
Look!

937
01:08:38,823 --> 01:08:40,866
The Blue Star!

938
01:08:41,034 --> 01:08:41,950
Everybody!

939
01:08:42,118 --> 01:08:43,327
What? What is it?

940
01:08:43,495 --> 01:08:45,370
Everybody, wake up!

941
01:08:45,538 --> 01:08:46,789
It's the Blue Star!

942
01:08:46,998 --> 01:08:49,666
Come on, old boy, wake up.

943
01:09:26,162 --> 01:09:27,329
Pull!

944
01:09:28,289 --> 01:09:30,249
Mind your strokes there, lads.

945
01:09:30,416 --> 01:09:31,583
Pull!

946
01:09:33,711 --> 01:09:35,629
The wind has left us.

947
01:09:35,797 --> 01:09:38,590
So how do we get to
Ramandu's Island now then?

948
01:09:39,634 --> 01:09:42,803
My guess is something
doesn't want us to get there.

949
01:09:44,264 --> 01:09:45,430
Pull!

950
01:09:46,599 --> 01:09:47,766
All together.

951
01:09:47,934 --> 01:09:51,728
If I get any hungrier,
I'm gonna eat that dragon!

952
01:09:52,939 --> 01:09:56,817
Don't worry, Eustace,
they'll have to deal with me first.

953
01:09:57,443 --> 01:09:58,193
Ah! Careful!

954
01:09:58,361 --> 01:10:01,613
If we don't find land by tonight,
they may well eat that dragon.

955
01:10:06,870 --> 01:10:08,662
What did we hit?

956
01:10:12,709 --> 01:10:14,626
Eustace, that's brilliant.

957
01:10:22,468 --> 01:10:24,136
Onward, ho!

958
01:10:45,909 --> 01:10:49,786
We can't be sure the other lords
even made it to Ramandu's Island.

959
01:11:00,840 --> 01:11:02,090
You got us there!

960
01:11:02,258 --> 01:11:05,260
What did I tell you, Eustace?
Extraordinary! Ha-ha-ha!

961
01:11:05,428 --> 01:11:07,179
Extraordinary!

962
01:12:00,191 --> 01:12:01,775
Mmm. Food.

963
01:12:01,985 --> 01:12:03,068
Wait.

964
01:12:03,236 --> 01:12:04,277
Huh?

965
01:12:39,689 --> 01:12:40,772
Lord Revilian.

966
01:12:46,237 --> 01:12:47,237
Lord Mavramorn.

967
01:12:52,201 --> 01:12:54,202
Lord Argoz.

968
01:13:02,128 --> 01:13:03,712
He's breathing.

969
01:13:09,802 --> 01:13:11,261
So are they.

970
01:13:14,223 --> 01:13:15,474
They're under a spell.

971
01:13:17,518 --> 01:13:18,435
It's the food!

972
01:13:18,603 --> 01:13:19,770
Huh?

973
01:13:21,397 --> 01:13:22,314
Hey.

974
01:13:22,482 --> 01:13:24,691
It's the stone knife.

975
01:13:24,859 --> 01:13:25,901
This is Asian's table.

976
01:13:26,986 --> 01:13:27,819
Their swords.

977
01:13:37,497 --> 01:13:38,580
On the table.

978
01:13:48,424 --> 01:13:49,591
That's six.

979
01:13:51,594 --> 01:13:53,595
Still missing one.

980
01:13:57,975 --> 01:13:59,184
Look!

981
01:14:26,003 --> 01:14:27,337
Travelers of Narnia...

982
01:14:28,214 --> 01:14:29,589
welcome.

983
01:14:31,592 --> 01:14:33,593
Arise.

984
01:14:35,847 --> 01:14:37,347
Are you not hungry?

985
01:14:37,890 --> 01:14:38,890
Who are you?

986
01:14:39,225 --> 01:14:43,270
I'm Liliandil,
daughter of Ramandu.

987
01:14:43,437 --> 01:14:45,021
I am your guide.

988
01:14:49,068 --> 01:14:50,068
You're a star?

989
01:14:57,994 --> 01:14:59,327
You are most beautiful.

990
01:15:00,246 --> 01:15:03,248
If it is a distraction for you,
I can change form.

991
01:15:03,416 --> 01:15:04,708
No!
No!

992
01:15:06,252 --> 01:15:07,419
Please.

993
01:15:09,380 --> 01:15:11,047
The food is for you.

994
01:15:12,633 --> 01:15:16,761
There is enough for all
who are welcome at Asian's table.

995
01:15:16,929 --> 01:15:17,762
Always.

996
01:15:17,930 --> 01:15:20,223
Help yourselves.

997
01:15:21,058 --> 01:15:22,100
Wait.

998
01:15:22,852 --> 01:15:23,810
What happened to them?

999
01:15:25,271 --> 01:15:28,690
These poor men were half-mad
by the time they reached our shores.

1000
01:15:29,192 --> 01:15:31,109
They were threatening violence
upon each other.

1001
01:15:31,485 --> 01:15:34,446
Violence is forbidden
at the table of Aslan.

1002
01:15:34,864 --> 01:15:36,364
So they were sent to sleep.

1003
01:15:37,074 --> 01:15:38,575
Will they ever wake?

1004
01:15:39,493 --> 01:15:41,286
When all is put right.

1005
01:15:41,454 --> 01:15:42,954
Come...

1006
01:15:43,122 --> 01:15:44,539
there is little time.

1007
01:16:01,474 --> 01:16:04,893
The magician, Coriakin,
told you of Dark island?

1008
01:16:05,811 --> 01:16:06,811
Yes.

1009
01:16:12,193 --> 01:16:15,070
Before long,
the evil will be unstoppable.

1010
01:16:15,321 --> 01:16:18,823
Coriakin said to break its spell,
we lay the seven swords at Asian's table.

1011
01:16:19,825 --> 01:16:21,785
He speaks the truth.

1012
01:16:21,953 --> 01:16:23,536
But we only found six.

1013
01:16:23,704 --> 01:16:25,956
Do you know where the seventh is?

1014
01:16:26,832 --> 01:16:28,166
In there.

1015
01:16:28,626 --> 01:16:31,503
You will need great courage.

1016
01:16:37,843 --> 01:16:38,969
Now, waste no time.

1017
01:16:42,390 --> 01:16:43,765
I hope we meet again.

1018
01:16:46,602 --> 01:16:47,686
Goodbye.

1019
01:17:13,796 --> 01:17:16,715
So, what do you think is in there?

1020
01:17:17,341 --> 01:17:19,551
Our worst nightmares.

1021
01:17:19,719 --> 01:17:21,803
Our darkest wishes.

1022
01:17:22,555 --> 01:17:24,723
Pure evil.

1023
01:17:27,643 --> 01:17:30,228
Tavros, unlock the armory.

1024
01:17:30,396 --> 01:17:31,438
My lord.

1025
01:17:31,605 --> 01:17:34,232
Archers, prepare yourselves.

1026
01:17:34,400 --> 01:17:35,400
Aye, Captain.

1027
01:17:35,568 --> 01:17:37,152
Light the lanterns.

1028
01:17:38,112 --> 01:17:39,696
Let's get ready.

1029
01:17:45,328 --> 01:17:49,122
When I grow up,
I want to be just like you.

1030
01:17:56,672 --> 01:17:58,173
When you grow up...

1031
01:18:00,176 --> 01:18:04,220
you should be just like you.

1032
01:18:12,396 --> 01:18:15,732
In case we don't get through
whatever this is...

1033
01:18:17,443 --> 01:18:20,028
I want you to know
I think of you as my brother, Ed.

1034
01:18:20,654 --> 01:18:21,696
Me too.

1035
01:18:27,203 --> 01:18:29,204
You gave up your sword.

1036
01:18:29,747 --> 01:18:31,081
It wasn't mine to keep.

1037
01:18:35,544 --> 01:18:37,253
Use this.

1038
01:18:38,339 --> 01:18:39,214
But it's...

1039
01:18:39,382 --> 01:18:40,924
Peter would want you to have it.

1040
01:18:50,643 --> 01:18:52,811
There it is, my friend.

1041
01:18:53,604 --> 01:18:55,647
Our battle awaits.

1042
01:18:56,273 --> 01:18:57,482
Eustace, no!

1043
01:18:58,067 --> 01:18:58,983
Halt!

1044
01:18:59,151 --> 01:19:00,985
Eustace, stop! Stop!

1045
01:19:03,155 --> 01:19:05,740
I will not accept surrender.

1046
01:19:05,908 --> 01:19:08,743
A noble warrior does not run from fear.

1047
01:19:08,911 --> 01:19:12,122
Look at me! Look at me
when I'm talking to you!

1048
01:19:14,125 --> 01:19:15,792
I am a mouse.

1049
01:19:15,960 --> 01:19:18,169
You, you're a dragon.

1050
01:19:18,754 --> 01:19:22,507
You've got skin like chain mail,
you breathe fire.

1051
01:19:22,716 --> 01:19:25,552
Come on, let's meet our destiny.

1052
01:19:32,518 --> 01:19:35,061
No matter what happens here...

1053
01:19:35,229 --> 01:19:38,022
every soul who stands before me
has earned their place...

1054
01:19:38,274 --> 01:19:40,150
on the crew of the Dawn Treader.

1055
01:19:40,860 --> 01:19:43,445
Together we have traveled far.

1056
01:19:43,612 --> 01:19:45,196
Together we have faced adversity.

1057
01:19:45,364 --> 01:19:47,365
Together we can do it again.

1058
01:19:49,368 --> 01:19:52,203
So now is not the time
to fall to fear's temptations.

1059
01:19:52,371 --> 01:19:54,789
Be strong. Never give in.

1060
01:19:56,709 --> 01:19:58,042
Our world...

1061
01:19:58,252 --> 01:20:00,211
our Narnian lives, depend on it.

1062
01:20:01,380 --> 01:20:03,298
Think of the lost souls
we're here to save.

1063
01:20:07,970 --> 01:20:09,971
Think of Aslan.

1064
01:20:11,223 --> 01:20:12,974
Think of Narnia.

1065
01:20:13,142 --> 01:20:15,810
- For Narnia!
- For Narnia!

1066
01:20:17,313 --> 01:20:18,229
For Narnia!

1067
01:21:15,204 --> 01:21:15,995
Helaine.

1068
01:21:27,299 --> 01:21:29,467
I can't see a thing.

1069
01:21:29,635 --> 01:21:32,095
This fog's too thick.

1070
01:21:37,810 --> 01:21:40,937
You are
a great disappointment to me.

1071
01:21:41,105 --> 01:21:46,067
You call yourself my son,
then act like a king.

1072
01:21:49,613 --> 01:21:52,991
Edmund, come with me.

1073
01:21:54,493 --> 01:21:56,494
Be my king.

1074
01:21:57,955 --> 01:21:59,998
I'll let you rule.

1075
01:22:00,165 --> 01:22:01,416
Go away.

1076
01:22:01,584 --> 01:22:03,668
You're dead.

1077
01:22:03,836 --> 01:22:06,504
You can never kill me.

1078
01:22:06,672 --> 01:22:11,009
I'll always be alive in your mind,
silly boy.

1079
01:22:11,176 --> 01:22:12,427
No!

1080
01:22:12,636 --> 01:22:13,386
Edmund?

1081
01:22:15,389 --> 01:22:17,015
Are you all right?

1082
01:22:18,100 --> 01:22:19,350
Yeah.

1083
01:22:28,611 --> 01:22:31,529
Keep away!

1084
01:22:32,531 --> 01:22:34,991
Keep away!

1085
01:22:35,618 --> 01:22:36,659
Who's there?

1086
01:22:36,827 --> 01:22:38,703
We do not fear you.

1087
01:22:38,871 --> 01:22:41,039
Nor I you.

1088
01:22:50,132 --> 01:22:51,799
Keep away!

1089
01:22:51,967 --> 01:22:52,967
We will not leave.

1090
01:22:53,927 --> 01:22:56,179
You will not defeat me.

1091
01:22:56,388 --> 01:22:57,221
Caspian.

1092
01:22:57,514 --> 01:22:58,848
Caspian, his sword.

1093
01:23:01,560 --> 01:23:02,810
Lord Rhoop!

1094
01:23:04,897 --> 01:23:07,398
You do not own me!

1095
01:23:08,067 --> 01:23:09,317
Stand down.

1096
01:23:09,485 --> 01:23:10,902
Let's get him on board, quickly.

1097
01:23:11,070 --> 01:23:12,695
- Help him up.
- Ready, sir.

1098
01:23:20,996 --> 01:23:22,413
Be calm, my lord.

1099
01:23:22,581 --> 01:23:24,540
Off me, demon!

1100
01:23:24,708 --> 01:23:25,875
No, my lord.

1101
01:23:26,043 --> 01:23:27,585
We are not here to hurt you.

1102
01:23:27,920 --> 01:23:30,713
I am your king, Caspian.

1103
01:23:32,049 --> 01:23:33,675
Caspian?

1104
01:23:37,012 --> 01:23:38,471
My lord?

1105
01:23:39,765 --> 01:23:43,017
You should not have come.
There's no way out of here.

1106
01:23:43,185 --> 01:23:44,185
Quickly...

1107
01:23:44,395 --> 01:23:46,771
turn this ship about, before it's too late.

1108
01:23:47,022 --> 01:23:48,147
We have the sword. Let's go!

1109
01:23:48,691 --> 01:23:49,982
Let's turn her about, Drinian.

1110
01:23:50,150 --> 01:23:51,609
Aye-aye, Your Majesty.

1111
01:23:51,777 --> 01:23:52,777
Do not think.

1112
01:23:54,071 --> 01:23:55,780
Do not let it know your fears...

1113
01:23:56,031 --> 01:23:57,949
or it will become them.

1114
01:24:00,119 --> 01:24:01,452
Oh, no.

1115
01:24:01,745 --> 01:24:04,622
Edmund,
what did you just think of?

1116
01:24:04,790 --> 01:24:06,249
Oh, I'm sorry.

1117
01:24:21,306 --> 01:24:22,473
Look!

1118
01:24:22,641 --> 01:24:24,058
What is that?

1119
01:24:25,144 --> 01:24:27,103
It's too late. It's too late!

1120
01:24:30,899 --> 01:24:32,900
It's gone under the boat!

1121
01:24:33,068 --> 01:24:33,818
Gael!

1122
01:24:43,454 --> 01:24:44,495
Come here!

1123
01:24:44,663 --> 01:24:45,621
Run!

1124
01:24:46,749 --> 01:24:50,168
Don't let me down.
No fear. No retreat.

1125
01:24:50,335 --> 01:24:52,295
Hold fast!

1126
01:25:00,637 --> 01:25:01,846
For Narnia!

1127
01:25:02,014 --> 01:25:04,515
Take that and that!

1128
01:25:05,058 --> 01:25:06,642
Yah!

1129
01:25:06,810 --> 01:25:08,811
Eustace, hang on.

1130
01:25:37,549 --> 01:25:38,800
Out, creature!

1131
01:25:39,009 --> 01:25:40,885
No! The sword! The sword!

1132
01:25:41,136 --> 01:25:42,220
Eustace!

1133
01:25:43,680 --> 01:25:45,097
No! Come back!

1134
01:25:45,307 --> 01:25:47,183
We're all doomed! Doomed!

1135
01:25:47,351 --> 01:25:49,393
- Turn this ship about!
- Stop him!

1136
01:25:49,561 --> 01:25:51,687
Someone stop him!

1137
01:25:58,529 --> 01:25:59,695
Now, crew...

1138
01:25:59,905 --> 01:26:01,739
to your rowing positions.

1139
01:26:02,324 --> 01:26:04,325
Oars at double speed!

1140
01:26:04,493 --> 01:26:06,911
Aslan, please help us.

1141
01:26:14,169 --> 01:26:15,586
Pull!

1142
01:26:16,755 --> 01:26:17,630
Pull!

1143
01:26:36,775 --> 01:26:38,609
Pull!
Put your back into it!

1144
01:26:38,777 --> 01:26:40,027
Pull!

1145
01:26:42,573 --> 01:26:45,199
Gael, come on! This way!

1146
01:27:00,966 --> 01:27:04,260
Now you must stay here until
someone comes and gets you. Okay?

1147
01:27:09,308 --> 01:27:11,142
Ed! Ed.

1148
01:27:11,310 --> 01:27:14,395
We'll ram the serpent.
Smash him on the rocks.

1149
01:27:14,563 --> 01:27:17,398
Steer her to port.
I'll keep it on the prow.

1150
01:27:19,610 --> 01:27:20,776
Look out!

1151
01:27:24,489 --> 01:27:26,991
Forward!
Come on! Pull!

1152
01:27:34,166 --> 01:27:36,125
Try and kill me! Come on!

1153
01:27:36,293 --> 01:27:37,335
Come on, I'm here!

1154
01:27:41,340 --> 01:27:42,673
No!
Edmund!

1155
01:27:56,021 --> 01:27:57,355
Archers...

1156
01:27:57,522 --> 01:27:59,023
ready yourselves.

1157
01:28:01,693 --> 01:28:02,818
I'm still here!

1158
01:28:10,285 --> 01:28:11,369
Brace yourselves!

1159
01:29:26,111 --> 01:29:27,319
Move!

1160
01:29:42,544 --> 01:29:43,836
We can beat this.

1161
01:30:01,897 --> 01:30:03,481
We have to get it closer.

1162
01:30:03,648 --> 01:30:04,899
All hands to the main deck.

1163
01:30:05,609 --> 01:30:06,984
Ready the harpoons.

1164
01:30:11,990 --> 01:30:14,575
I want everybody up here!

1165
01:30:18,663 --> 01:30:19,663
Ready?

1166
01:30:19,873 --> 01:30:21,165
Aye, sir!

1167
01:30:21,333 --> 01:30:22,166
Now!

1168
01:30:28,423 --> 01:30:29,673
Pull its head down!

1169
01:30:51,863 --> 01:30:52,863
Heave!

1170
01:31:01,873 --> 01:31:03,332
Edmund.

1171
01:31:09,047 --> 01:31:10,881
What are you trying to prove,
Edmund?

1172
01:31:12,050 --> 01:31:13,467
That you're a man?

1173
01:31:19,266 --> 01:31:21,058
Edmund!

1174
01:31:23,603 --> 01:31:25,229
Do it!

1175
01:31:25,814 --> 01:31:27,148
I can make you that.

1176
01:31:27,315 --> 01:31:29,066
I can make you my king.

1177
01:31:31,862 --> 01:31:33,737
Just take my hand.

1178
01:31:47,419 --> 01:31:48,919
Just give in.

1179
01:31:58,221 --> 01:31:59,180
Do it!

1180
01:32:00,849 --> 01:32:02,516
Come on!

1181
01:32:05,604 --> 01:32:07,605
No!

1182
01:32:40,513 --> 01:32:42,556
The spell...

1183
01:32:42,724 --> 01:32:43,933
it's lifting.

1184
01:32:47,604 --> 01:32:48,646
Edmund!

1185
01:32:50,732 --> 01:32:52,483
Caspian!

1186
01:32:53,109 --> 01:32:54,526
Look!

1187
01:33:22,555 --> 01:33:24,848
Narnians! Narnians!

1188
01:33:40,782 --> 01:33:42,032
Mummy!

1189
01:33:42,200 --> 01:33:43,200
Helaine!

1190
01:33:52,335 --> 01:33:53,669
Rhince!

1191
01:33:53,837 --> 01:33:54,712
Gael!

1192
01:33:54,879 --> 01:33:56,839
Mummy!

1193
01:33:57,007 --> 01:33:58,215
Mummy.

1194
01:34:00,051 --> 01:34:01,885
Oh, Mummy.

1195
01:34:07,976 --> 01:34:10,894
Let's have them on board!
Clear the decks.

1196
01:34:13,398 --> 01:34:15,149
We did it.

1197
01:34:15,317 --> 01:34:17,109
I knew we would.

1198
01:34:17,319 --> 01:34:19,194
It wasn't just us,
though.

1199
01:34:20,155 --> 01:34:21,238
You mean...

1200
01:34:21,406 --> 01:34:24,158
Hey! Hey, I'm down here, Lucy.

1201
01:34:24,367 --> 01:34:25,576
Over here!

1202
01:34:25,744 --> 01:34:27,995
Hey, Lucy. I'm in the water. Lucy!

1203
01:34:28,163 --> 01:34:28,996
Eustace.

1204
01:34:29,497 --> 01:34:30,831
I'm a boy again.

1205
01:34:31,541 --> 01:34:32,666
I'm a boy.

1206
01:34:32,876 --> 01:34:35,002
Eustace! I see your wings...

1207
01:34:35,170 --> 01:34:36,420
have been clipped. Ha, ha!

1208
01:34:39,591 --> 01:34:41,425
Where sky and water meet

1209
01:34:41,593 --> 01:34:44,053
Where the waves grow ever sweet

1210
01:34:44,637 --> 01:34:45,512
It is sweet.

1211
01:34:46,181 --> 01:34:47,097
It's sweet!

1212
01:34:49,768 --> 01:34:52,519
Look! Look!

1213
01:34:58,943 --> 01:35:01,153
Asian's country.

1214
01:35:01,363 --> 01:35:03,530
We must be close.

1215
01:35:03,740 --> 01:35:05,866
Well,
we've come this far.

1216
01:35:18,338 --> 01:35:22,549
So, what was it like
when Aslan changed you back?

1217
01:35:22,759 --> 01:35:27,054
No matter how hard I tried,
I just couldn't do it myself.

1218
01:35:27,389 --> 01:35:28,680
Then he came towards me.

1219
01:35:28,848 --> 01:35:33,060
It sort of hurt, but it was a good pain.

1220
01:35:33,228 --> 01:35:36,980
You know, like when you pull a thorn
from your foot.

1221
01:35:37,649 --> 01:35:39,650
Being a dragon wasn't all bad.

1222
01:35:39,818 --> 01:35:43,987
I mean, I think I was a better dragon
than I was a boy, really.

1223
01:35:44,197 --> 01:35:46,115
I'm so sorry for being such a sop.

1224
01:35:46,658 --> 01:35:48,742
It's okay, Eustace.

1225
01:35:48,910 --> 01:35:51,662
You were a pretty good dragon.

1226
01:35:54,833 --> 01:35:58,627
My friends,
we have arrived.

1227
01:36:35,707 --> 01:36:37,040
Aslan.

1228
01:36:37,959 --> 01:36:40,878
Welcome, children.
You have done well.

1229
01:36:41,045 --> 01:36:43,046
Very well indeed.

1230
01:36:43,214 --> 01:36:47,468
You have come far,
and now your journey is at its end.

1231
01:36:48,136 --> 01:36:49,553
Is this your country?

1232
01:36:49,721 --> 01:36:52,139
No, my country lies beyond.

1233
01:36:55,852 --> 01:36:57,227
Is my father in your country?

1234
01:36:57,729 --> 01:37:00,564
You can only find that out
for yourself, my son.

1235
01:37:01,441 --> 01:37:04,067
But you should know
that if you continue...

1236
01:37:04,235 --> 01:37:06,570
there is no return.

1237
01:37:38,478 --> 01:37:41,355
- You're not going?
- I can't imagine my father...

1238
01:37:41,523 --> 01:37:44,858
would be very proud
that I gave up what he died for.

1239
01:37:47,028 --> 01:37:49,112
I spent too long wanting
what was taken from me...

1240
01:37:49,280 --> 01:37:51,198
and not what was given.

1241
01:37:52,158 --> 01:37:54,451
I was given a kingdom.

1242
01:37:55,328 --> 01:37:56,995
A people.

1243
01:38:02,961 --> 01:38:04,962
I promise to be a better king.

1244
01:38:05,338 --> 01:38:07,297
You already are.

1245
01:38:08,508 --> 01:38:09,883
Children.

1246
01:38:11,010 --> 01:38:13,637
I think perhaps it's time
we went home actually, Lu.

1247
01:38:16,224 --> 01:38:18,100
But I thought you loved it here.

1248
01:38:18,476 --> 01:38:19,726
I do.

1249
01:38:19,936 --> 01:38:22,771
But I love home
and our family as well.

1250
01:38:25,942 --> 01:38:27,943
They need us.

1251
01:38:35,660 --> 01:38:37,661
Your Eminence...

1252
01:38:37,829 --> 01:38:41,456
ever since I can remember,
I have dreamt of seeing your country.

1253
01:38:41,958 --> 01:38:45,002
I've had many great adventures
in this world...

1254
01:38:45,169 --> 01:38:47,671
but nothing has dampened
that yearning.

1255
01:38:48,256 --> 01:38:50,048
I know I am hardly worthy...

1256
01:38:50,216 --> 01:38:54,344
but with your permission,
I would lay down my sword...

1257
01:38:54,512 --> 01:38:58,807
for the joy of seeing your country
with my own eyes.

1258
01:39:02,353 --> 01:39:06,690
My country was made for
noble hearts such as yours...

1259
01:39:06,858 --> 01:39:09,401
no matter how small their bearers be.

1260
01:39:10,028 --> 01:39:11,194
Your Majesty.

1261
01:39:11,362 --> 01:39:13,030
No one could be more deserving.

1262
01:39:13,197 --> 01:39:14,615
Well, I--
It's true.

1263
01:39:28,212 --> 01:39:30,213
May I?

1264
01:39:30,423 --> 01:39:33,717
Well, I suppose.
Just this--

1265
01:39:39,557 --> 01:39:41,516
Goodbye, Lucy.

1266
01:39:56,658 --> 01:39:58,575
Don't cry.

1267
01:39:58,743 --> 01:40:01,036
I don't understand.

1268
01:40:03,247 --> 01:40:06,583
Will I not see you again? Ever?

1269
01:40:06,834 --> 01:40:11,338
What a magnificent puzzle you are,
and a true hero.

1270
01:40:11,547 --> 01:40:15,133
It has been my honor to fight
beside such a brave warrior...

1271
01:40:15,301 --> 01:40:17,052
and a great friend.

1272
01:40:29,273 --> 01:40:31,441
I won't be needing this.

1273
01:40:59,220 --> 01:41:00,971
This is our last time here,
isn't it?

1274
01:41:01,139 --> 01:41:02,097
Yes.

1275
01:41:02,640 --> 01:41:06,101
You have grown up,
my dear one.

1276
01:41:06,310 --> 01:41:08,478
Just like Peter and Susan.

1277
01:41:08,646 --> 01:41:11,273
Will you visit us in our world?

1278
01:41:11,441 --> 01:41:14,818
I shall be watching you,
always.

1279
01:41:16,821 --> 01:41:18,196
How?

1280
01:41:18,656 --> 01:41:21,742
In your world, I have another name.

1281
01:41:21,993 --> 01:41:24,327
You must learn to know me by it.

1282
01:41:24,829 --> 01:41:27,748
That was the very reason
you were brought to Narnia.

1283
01:41:27,915 --> 01:41:30,751
That by knowing me here for a little...

1284
01:41:30,918 --> 01:41:33,879
you may know me better there.

1285
01:41:34,046 --> 01:41:35,672
Will we meet again?

1286
01:41:36,174 --> 01:41:40,343
Mm. Yes, dear one. One day.

1287
01:41:55,359 --> 01:41:58,236
You're the closest thing
I have to family.

1288
01:42:00,031 --> 01:42:02,449
And that includes you,
Eustace.

1289
01:42:04,076 --> 01:42:05,494
Thank you.

1290
01:42:34,065 --> 01:42:35,232
Will I come back?

1291
01:42:35,399 --> 01:42:38,485
Narnia may yet have need of you.

1292
01:43:35,501 --> 01:43:37,294
Eustace?

1293
01:43:38,004 --> 01:43:38,795
Eustace...

1294
01:43:40,339 --> 01:43:41,965
what are you doing up there?

1295
01:43:42,675 --> 01:43:43,884
Jill Pole's...

1296
01:43:44,051 --> 01:43:45,635
dropped in for a visit.

1297
01:43:56,397 --> 01:43:59,774
We spoke often of Narnia
in the days that followed.

1298
01:44:02,153 --> 01:44:05,822
And when my cousins left,
after the war ended...

1299
01:44:07,491 --> 01:44:10,243
I missed them with all my heart...

1300
01:44:12,288 --> 01:44:14,664
as I know all Narnians will miss them...

1301
01:44:15,791 --> 01:44:18,335
till the end of time.

1302
01:45:20,731 --> 01:45:27,153
There's a place out there for us

1303
01:45:27,947 --> 01:45:31,783
More than just a prayer

1304
01:45:31,951 --> 01:45:35,328
Or anything you've ever dreamed of

1305
01:45:35,496 --> 01:45:40,750
So when you feel like giving up

1306
01:45:40,918 --> 01:45:44,087
'Cause you don't fit in down here

1307
01:45:44,255 --> 01:45:46,631
Fear is crashing in

1308
01:45:46,799 --> 01:45:50,593
Close your eyes and take my hand, yeah

1309
01:45:50,761 --> 01:45:57,600
We can be the kings and queens
Of anything if we believe

1310
01:45:57,768 --> 01:46:03,398
It's written in the stars that shine above

1311
01:46:04,734 --> 01:46:08,319
A world where you and I belong

1312
01:46:08,487 --> 01:46:11,990
Where faith and love will keep us strong

1313
01:46:12,158 --> 01:46:17,704
Exactly who we are is just enough

1314
01:46:17,872 --> 01:46:20,472
There's a place for us

1315
01:46:33,304 --> 01:46:40,143
When the water meets the sky

1316
01:46:40,644 --> 01:46:44,314
Where your heart is free

1317
01:46:44,815 --> 01:46:47,734
And hope comes back to life

1318
01:46:47,902 --> 01:46:51,780
When these broken hands

1319
01:46:51,947 --> 01:46:55,450
Are whole again

1320
01:46:55,618 --> 01:46:59,412
Well, we'll find
What we've been waiting for

1321
01:46:59,580 --> 01:47:03,208
We were made for so much more

1322
01:47:03,375 --> 01:47:10,006
We can be the kings and queens
Of anything if we believe

1323
01:47:10,174 --> 01:47:16,096
It's written in the stars that shine above

1324
01:47:17,515 --> 01:47:20,892
A world where you and I belong

1325
01:47:21,060 --> 01:47:24,771
Where faith and love will keep us strong

1326
01:47:24,939 --> 01:47:30,485
Exactly who we are is just enough

1327
01:47:30,653 --> 01:47:33,253
There's a place for us

1328
01:47:46,460 --> 01:47:50,463
So hold on

1329
01:47:50,631 --> 01:47:52,231
Hold on

1330
01:47:56,053 --> 01:48:01,933
There's a place for us

1331
01:48:03,394 --> 01:48:10,066
We can be the kings and queens
Of anything if we believe

1332
01:48:10,234 --> 01:48:17,240
It's written in the stars that shine above

1333
01:48:17,408 --> 01:48:20,994
A world where you and I belong

1334
01:48:21,162 --> 01:48:24,581
Where faith and love will keep us strong

1335
01:48:24,748 --> 01:48:30,920
Exactly who we are is just enough

1336
01:48:31,255 --> 01:48:37,760
Yeah, exactly who we are is just enough

1337
01:48:37,928 --> 01:48:45,602
There's a place for us