-== [ www.OpenSubtitles.com ] ==-
During the
human wars many people died,
if it was the Ukranians creating
a virus to wipe out Russia
or the U.S. Setting off
nuclear weapons to Iraq
very few humans survived.
After the wars, governments
fell and civilians took over,
creating their own leaders.
Only 10 countries remained
and divided up the world.
Those countries were
collectively known as sectors.
The U.S. Sector grew
to be the biggest
and most powerful of them all.
But humans are not the only
ones who walk this planet.
Deviants are also living
throughout the sectors,
hidden and trying to stay alive.
I am one of them and
like many others I fight
against those who want to rid
the planet of the gifted ones.
It began with the civil
battles where humans
would control our
powers with UV charges.
Each year humans capture
and torture Deviants.
They then force them to
fight and kill each other
to find their vanquisher.
The one that would
represent their Sector
at the main tournament
Dominion's Battle.
Dominion's Battle,
an event created
by madman Dominion Harvey.
He runs and operates
The Immortal Wars,
a television show aired
to the entire world.
This fight is held by the
U.S. and it has become
the world's biggest
entertainment corporation.
Humans wait all
year for this day.
These are dark days and
the darkest of them all
is when the world will
watch us fight to the death.
That's not the one.
Bag her up, let's take her.
Hey.
You are a vanquisher?
Can you make sure the
guards have these things
fully charged at all times.
I still don't know
why we use these things.
What are you, brain dead?
These UV rays are the only
thing keeping your ass alive.
Without these we'd
lose all control.
Little obsessive,
don't you think?
Did you develop a
soft spot for the skags?
You're old, Costa,
and you're weak.
Maybe that's why you've
been making all those
little mistakes in the field.
Like I said, that
was out of my control.
Yeah, but it was still
your team though, wasn't it?
I can't wait to see what Dominion
has to say about all this.
Considering you're number
one on his shit list now.
Sir, they're asking for you.
Have fun.
Move.
What is this place?
Well it looks like
a jail, doesn't it?
Now move, skag.
No, you've got
to tell me what's...
You wanna try again?
This is your home now.
You better get real comfy, skag.
Sir.
What is it?
You requested my presence.
Sir, I apologize for my mistake.
Would you like a drink?
No, I'm fine thank you.
So what happened today?
It was a small
mistake, my guys they...
Ah ah, get one thing straight.
These are my guys.
They didn't secure the Deviant
correctly and it escaped.
So a group of highly
trained guards made a mistake
that gave my Deviant
the chance to escape.
A mistake that
risked everything.
My Sector, my network my show.
Sir I apologize.
Son, how long have you
been fighting for us?
Since I was valid.
Which is?
Six years.
You know mistakes
can never happen.
There's no time for them.
Yes sir and I promise it
will never happen again.
It will never happen again.
Guards, can you please
take the trash out.
What trash?
Did you hear?
Costa expired this morning.
How?
They said he shot
himself right in the head.
That's bullshit.
They got him for
what his team did.
You serious?
Yeah, you think there's
time for mistakes?
No but hey that just give
us a chance to move up.
I'm okay with that.
Right.
Hey you think the
game's gonna be as brutal
this year as last year?
They can all kill each
other for all I care.
As long as they're
not on our streets.
What's wrong with you?
How did a girl like
you make it this far?
It's not my choice to
be here, they forced me.
We all were.
So tell me your story.
How'd you end up here?
There is no story, I
wasn't supposed to be here.
I'm tired of fighting.
But I will do what I
have to do to survive.
I just want to be free and
live the life I have left.
Yeah me too.
L talk to me.
We're good.
How good?
We're broadcasting
to all Sectors.
Russia, Africa, Mexico
each one's ready for us.
That's why I love you.
Now time to greet
our special guests.
What will you do when
we're in front of the world?
I won't fight you.
When the time comes I will
fight you and I will win.
You think you
can beat Nyx Moros?
You ask as if it's
going to be hard.
She is a monster, a murderer.
She killed her own brother
for this sick game.
The god of Deserts and storms.
I told you, you can't win.
I'm stronger than you.
No you're wrong.
I'm stronger.
But I couldn't
hurt my own family.
You see that's the
difference between you and I.
When we were forced
into this, this game,
I put to side the fact
that you were my brother,
and I made you my enemy.
This is the end,
you ready to die?
We both know this
isn't the end of me.
Give them what they want.
Seth was one of the strongest
deviants known to man.
Nothing will stop her
from killing anyone
who gets in her way.
Maybe this will.
This place is
surrounded by UV lines.
We can't use any of our
powers, they control it all.
So tell me about yourself.
We are going to be
here for a while,
might as well know a little
bit about my next victim.
I'm just messing around.
Well, I was seven when
my family found out.
Found out what?
What I am.
They grew hatred towards me,
so I ran away and started over.
I then began to fight for
those who needed help.
But then when I found out
what I was capable of I got...
You okay?
So what's your name?
Olive, Olive Summerlin.
No, I meant what
do they call you?
What do they call you?
Oh uh, Trikalypse.
Cool.
You?
Iro.
Cool.
How about something to eat?
Maybe, skag.
I said maybe, skag.
Maybe you oughta come
into this cell, huh?
You know what?
That sounds like a good idea.
Really?
- Come on.
- You know what they say.
Once you go black,
they never come back.
Maybe next time princess.
I want something to eat!
What does that do?
It scans the body, it records
strength, power, health.
It's how they know who to pair
us up with for each fight.
How do you know all this?
I knew I would
be here some day.
I looked into everything.
I did my research
and prepared myself.
Step forward skag.
She thought that
you were me, huh?
Step forward
for evaluation!
Hey I'm sorry, I
didn't hear you there.
You can try to keep us in here,
but it ain't gonna
work, you know why?
There's a revolution
coming, brother.
I'm gonna make sure your
black ass dies first.
I'd love to see that.
You will see that.
See if you can
get your power off
before I put two hollow
points between your eyes.
Gentlemen, for years the
world has been divided.
Rich and poor, strong and weak.
And the question is which
category do you fall into?
As we witnessed, the
last year of the feathers
the Phoenix rose to be the
Victor and as we all know
this is the age of the snake.
Every 365 days we work hard
and prepare for today's events.
The day our people come together
and watch how we're making
the world a better place.
Now it's time to reveal
which serpent will represent
your sector at the table.
France we'll begin with you.
The Black Mumba.
Very Confident I
see, great choice.
Mexico.
The Blood Python.
The River Jack.
The Siamese palm viper.
The Canebrake.
The Nightingale adder.
The Copperhead.
The Blue krait.
Russia.
The Emerald boa.
The King Cobra.
Who will be
victorious this year?
Blackout, Germany,
skilled assassin.
Developed super human Senses
and environmental radar.
Bloodshed, England,
ability to drain
and absorb energy from others.
Atmo, Australia,
ability to manipulate
the elements of the earth.
Sin, Africa, super strength,
ability to generate
the dark force and summon her
children from the underworld.
Karly and The Tank, Russia.
Karly, ability to
scan the future
and telepathically
communicate with her partner.
What a child.
The Tank generates
superhuman strength.
Aiolos, Ukraine,
Olympic Martial Artist,
ability to generate
extreme speed and strength.
The Charge, France,
ability to generate
and expel electricity.
Iro, Mexico, ability to
manipulate and control fire.
Dekay, India, skilled assassin,
ability of breath and touch
generating the dark force.
Very interesting.
Trikalypse, United States,
telekinesis, superstrength
and durability, telepathy,
ability to absorb powers
with body contact.
I take it we have all
selected our battle grounds?
The time for entry is now,
please proceed to
cell block four.
They say she's a god.
They say Nyx Moros
is an Egyptian god.
How else do you think she
was able to kill Seth?
Looks good.
I take it this
is for the show.
We are the stars.
So what happens next?
Well now that they
have scanned us.
They are going to ranks
us one through 10.
That will then determine
who we fight first.
Then what happens after that?
Right now we are all going to
be visited by 10 individuals.
The ones who brought us here.
Then they will
register us for entry.
Then it begins.
We will be hit by the
shrill three times.
We will be to weak to stand.
And then we'll be announced
to the world of who we are
and what we can do.
Then the final 24 hours of
our lives begin to count down.
Get me the hell out of here!
Haven't you noticed
you're surrounded by steel?
You could have escaped
by now if you wanted to.
But no, here you are caged.
Why is that?
Nowhere to go,
nothing to return to.
Let's get something
perfectly straight right now.
This is your life now.
You have nowhere else to go.
This is not my life, this
was a diversion, a distraction.
All I have to do
now is just sit back
and watch it crumble around you.
Better yet, I'll listen to
the distraction carry on.
I am done fighting for you.
Game over!
You've clearly lost your mind.
Dominion didn't come.
You're registered
automatically.
You actually think
he'll come down here?
What are they
going to do to him?
They're taking him
down to cell block one.
What's in cell block one?
Cell block one is no
cell block its more like
the sewers chambers.
A dark hall that
not even a speck
of sunlight will ever shine.
Its said that Dominion throws
any deviant that does not obey
his laws and for those who
cannot take captivity well.
They are only fed medications
that slowly kill them.
They say some of
them are also used
for genetic experimentations.
Leo.
Who is he?
Our replacement.
He replaces us if any one of us
does not make it
to registration.
Think of it as him
being on standby.
They announced him months
before the civil battles.
And we are locked in.
We are locked and ready to go.
Gentlemen, it
is now show time.
May the strongest win.
Okay we are in, In 54...
Hello citizens of the world.
It Is that time
of the age again.
The time all our hard
work and dedication
will be put to the test.
In years past we have witnessed
some heartfelt moments.
- Hey it's starting, come on.
- We have watched some of
the greatest succeed
and some fail.
But this year it will
be one for the books.
In my hand I have the list
of the Immortal Wars VQ's.
Now I don't know about you,
but I am beyond excited
for this year's selections.
I've even heard that this year
one of the strongest Deviants
ever recorded in history.
Now let us begin.
First up we have The Charge
with a rank of a five.
Next we have Atmo
ranked at a six.
England's Leo ranked
with a number seven.
Karly and The Tank ranked
together at a seven.
Sin is also a seven.
Iro ranked at an eight.
Aiolos with a rank of an eight.
Blackout ranked at an eight.
Dekay ranked at a nine.
And finally last but not least,
Trikalypse ranked at a 10.
Now I know this has never
happened before in the ages
of the Immortal Wars, but
this is history in the making.
So on behalf of the city of
Lambent, let the battles begin.
My moneys on the US.
No India's got it,
she looks ruthless.
$100 down for the US
make it the third round.
This years going
to a good year, huh?
Yes it is.
Wait she was right.
Weakest versus strongest.
Eliminate the weak
so the strong have to
fight against each other.
It will make for a great show.
How do you know all this?
Like I said I did my research.
Research gives you
only so much information,
you know everything.
When you said that you
knew you would be here,
you actually meant you wanted
to be here, am I right?
You're right, I
chose to be here.
My mother was killed
five years ago
at the 10th age Immortal Wars.
She didn't make it
past the second round.
She was in contact
with my father
through one of
Dominion's slaves.
But Dominion found
out and had her killed
as well as my father soon after.
But not before he
told me everything.
That's why I'm here.
Dominion will pay
for what he has done
and nothing's gonna stop me.
That's not the
job for one person.
It's bigger than you, it's
bigger than both of us.
It's not one man that
needs to be stopped,
it's the whole government.
We've been forced to
forget what peace is.
Then what do we do?
We play, we fight,
and we survive.
But we don't entertain.
Five man.
Oy, what makes you
so special huh?
How about you come in
here and I can show you.
I mean it, let me show you.
Tempting, however
let's bring our romance
to the battlefield.
Hi, what's your name?
I'm Karly, this is The Tank.
How is our leading lady doing?
Well since you
asked quite excited.
I was able to get a
glimpse of the top 10.
I hope you weren't
disappointed.
No, so when I win the
final round what happens?
You will receive your awards.
Which are?
Power, freedom.
Then lets get
this thing started.
Well citizens it is time.
Please stop what you
are doing and join us
in this new age of
the Immortal Wars.
Our representatives
have been matched
and first up we have
Leo Versus Black.
Now this will Germany's
strongest fighter
since about two years ago.
They have had some rough times.
England, on the other
hand, has dominated.
However, they have had to
remove their primary fighter
due to medical reasons.
Leo has been selected
to fill those shoes.
Okay lets bring up the lights.
Environment bring up the sound.
Easy, easy, easy, nice and slow.
And, go.
So are you ready?
Are you?
A great way to start the show.
Good one.
How was that?
You shouldn't have done that.
Now that's the
way to start a show!
Who will be next?
Stay tuned after
this quick break.
Tank I don't want to die.
This is wrong.
How do we even have a
chance against each other
if they make us so
weak before each fight.
Before each fight
they're going to
inject us with UV Charges.
It's a small dose but enough
to spike up our energy,
powers, strength.
The next couple of fights
are going to go by fast.
They're gonna save
the strongest for last
and get rid of the weak first.
Then it will be us
against each other.
Who's next?
The kid.
They say you're a nine, huh?
I've seen better.
Watch this.
You really need
to be working more
on your fighting skills.
Like that?
Yeah, like that.
Watch this.
Is this what you
wanted to see, huh?
Is this what you wanted to see?
Tighter Tank, squeeze tighter.
Please don't make me do this.
For being a 10 you're
really are not that strong.
Please.
I don't want to fight her!
But I will for freedom.
And so will I.
Yikes.
She got him.
I'm sorry.
Tank!
Tank, get up.
Please get up.
Well that was a
very rough round.
But that is what
this game is about.
The display of
strength and power.
I gotta say did you all
see that coming from Iro?
It's like she couldn't
take the beating anymore
and just snapped!
Well now is the time
to get more drinks,
serve yourself up
with some more grub,
pay for your losses and
collect on your winnings,
because we have the
quarter finals coming
right after these messages.
We will be right back with
some more Immortal Wars.
I killed her kids.
I Killed three children.
Make me live.
Yes sir.
You're in.
Hello representatives
this is Dominion Harvey.
I wanted to congratulate
you all for making it
to the next round.
And take the time
to share something.
The one thing we all
have in common is death,
the only difference
is how it happens.
Your lives are not yours
anymore, they belong to me.
Do what you were born
to do fight, kill, die
and your passing
will be one of honor.
Now, If you withstand my
wishes, I promise you agony
in the lights that you never
could envision conceivable.
Thank you.
What do we do
now, he's on to us?
We continue to play his game.
Gentlemen that was a pretty
entertaining round wasn't it?
Russia what happened?
I was rooting for you.
I thought I made
it clear to you all
you had to have entered
your strongest fighter.
All I see here is a group
of scared creatures,
Lets see if the
final five can make
the next round more superior.
If not there will be some
extreme changes to come.
Are you with me?
Good.
How many times have
I told you not to do that?
Just play like
normal kids, okay?
What are they doing?
I don't know.
2, 3, it's even now.
What do you mean?
Well, now that
they took Blackout,
there's an even
number of fighters.
You're right.
What are they up to?
So, how's everything looking?
We did have some interference
from an unknown signal
but I took care of it,
other than that we are good.
All perished deviants
have been transferred
to cell block two
and we're just about
ready for the quarter finals.
Great.
What environments
do we have left?
Let's see, Death
Lands, Forest of Ice,
and the streets of Lambent.
This round should be good.
What if they make
us fight each other?
They won't.
They're going to put
me against Dekay.
We are both the strongest.
He's a business man, he'll
put us together last.
He knows we're friends,
it'll make good TV.
And when that time
comes we strike.
Okay, you've got this.
You got this, Olive.
No, me, take me!
I'm fighting her!
Iro!
Take me!
Olive.
This is all out
of our control.
I can't fight.
You're going to have to.
No don't make
me give them that.
I won't fight you!
You think I want to die?
Huh?
I don't stand a
chance against you!
I am walking into my own grave
when I go into that
battle ground with you!
Nice shots.
Nice try, now it's my turn.
You're a tough one aren't you?
You have no idea.
You actually thought you
could beat me, didn't you?
Tell me, how were you
going to defeat Nyx
if even I am to much for you?
I never wanted Nyx.
Tell me.
If not Nyx, then who?
Dominion.
But if you get in my
way I'll kill you too.
That's it.
Taste your power.
What did you do to her?
What we are here for?
Crazy bitch.
What I did I did to
be free and now I'm
just one steps ahead of you.
I suggest you do
the same, survive.
Because I can't wait to
have the chance to kill you.
Now that is what
I'm talking about!
That was amazing.
Dekay has no remorse
she's a killer.
I want to fight her.
Well, well now we still
have two more fights.
You make sure you
win this one got it?
I'm not fighting you.
Oh really?
Is that right?
You know they won't let
you just walk out of here.
You have to fight.
I will not.
Did you hear that?
I will not fight anymore!
Did she just do that?
Take care of this.
I told you I don't
want to fight any more.
There you go.
Why are you smiling?
Please, don't do this.
Win, you have to survive.
Make Dominion pay.
Please.
You got this.
You're forcing me to do this.
Do it.
What is she doing?
Cut it, cut it now.
It looks like she checked
if he was still alive.
Is what she did not allowed?
What she did made us look bad.
What she did shows the world
she is good and she cares.
The purpose of these
games are to show
that you are all to blame for
what happened to this planet
and that you are all the enemy.
That last round
was pretty good.
A bit sad at times,
but overall good.
I bet Harvey has
a boot up his ass.
What do you mean.
What that girl Trikalypse did.
I don't think he's
happy about that.
She really made him look bad.
Thank you.
Wait, hold on, is this correct?
Those are the orders.
What is it?
Can you bring up the
sound from the last fight?
Yes sir.
What exactly are
you looking for?
They were talking
through out the fight.
I want to know what was said.
Okay here it is.
Win, you have to
survive, make Dominion pay.
Please.
You got this.
Make me pay, huh?
Don't worry, I won't hurt you.
I know you won't.
Well, well, well look at us.
The last two standing.
Dekay don't talk.
Come on, after all
we've been through
I am glad it is just us left.
This should be good.
This is exciting.
And why is that?
Because the entire world
is going to watch me win
and witness the
death of Trikalypse.
Why?
Why are you doing this?
Why are you giving them a show?
- We are all the same.
- No.
I am something more.
I am something bigger
and more powerful.
Let me show you.
I almost had you.
Your poor little Iro
didn't have it so easy.
Stop this.
You're giving them
what they want.
Isn't that the point?
To give them a show.
It's not going to
happen, stop trying.
Oh bitch, you haven't
even seen me try.
Can't you see the world
needs some one like me.
Someone who can win.
Attention fighters,
there has been a change
to your orders.
Three fighters
must battle it out
for the last available spot.
Here we go.
Our viewers are jumping
up by the thousands sir.
Excellent.
He's here to kill us.
No shit.
No this is different.
They did something to
him, he's a puppet.
Once he's dead, we will
finish what we started.
They're controlling you!
You can fight this.
Just kill me.
I'm sorry.
Can't you see, its
not how strong you are,
it's about how you
use your power.
There I win!
Nyx Moros where are you?
This is my show.
What's going on here?
Geeze, sir, I uh...
Did she win?
Yeah, yeah she did.
I've been rooting for
her the whole time.
You watch this?
Yeah, who doesn't?
Send me in.
Prepare for the final battle.
Oh and can you have a
round of those drinks
for our guests in the
executive chamber?
Yes sir.
Thank you.
Come on, what is this?
Aw! She did put
up a good fight.
That's it! Push it.
Give it all you got.
I'm going to kill you.
Jankins?
What the hell are you doing?
It's sad that
you don't see it.
That power you have pointing
at me this very second.
What gives us the right
to have it more than them?
What makes us any different?
You're right.
Let's settle this like humans.
Enough, we have to save what
little humanity we have left.
No, there's the different
between me and you, pretty boy.
You'll never have what
it takes to survive.
And it begins.
Please rate this subtitle at www.osdb.link/748qw
Help other users to choose the best subtitles