I have to get home.
- Mama's gonna kill me.
- No.
You are staying with me tonight.
Roman wants us there
at nine in the morning.
Raya we've been over this.
It's just a few months
working in a hotel.
Yes, but...
You want to work at
Copyshack like your mother?
He said it was both
of us or nothing!
No.
Fuck your mom!
- I'm sorry.
- It's 1:30 in the morning.
You don't understand!
Luba wanted me to...
If her mother lets her do
whatever she wants...
go live there.
You graduated.
You're an adult now.
Do what you want.
Raya?
Big smile.
Good.
What will you say at border?
I am Natalya...
I am Natalya Verbova.
I am going to Budapest
to buy carpets for reselling.
Raya...
Hello.
I'm working...
Out. Out.
Out.
Smile!
Hi, Kathy.
You're in a hurry.
Where's the fire?
Sorry.
- Hi, Mare.
- Hi.
Transfer come through?
No.
You'll find something, hon.
Yes.
- Hi, boys.
- Hi.
Why don't you guys go
inside and help your mom, okay?
All right?
Marie asked me to bring this.
Erin around?
- It's nice to see you too, Kath.
- Yes, right.
You can't hold this
against me.
I gave you plenty of
warning on this.
It's not my fault you're
married to that job of yours.
Plenty of warning?
You just sprung this on me.
Look, I'm not going to
do this in front of Erin, okay.
Where is she? Erin?
And actually I'm not
married to my job.
I happen to like it.
I don't see why that has
to make me a bad mother.
Well, it's not my fault the
judge didn't see it that way, Kath.
Thanks, Kyle. Thank
you for bringing that up.
Look, I told you, you're welcome
to come down to Dalton...
It's really simple for me, you know,
I've just got to clear my mortgage...
find a transfer, you know,
really a piece of cake.
Hey, sweetie, how's it
going? Come here.
- Come here.
- No, Kyle, it's fragile.
- How am I supposed to know?
- Hi, Marie. How's it going?
- I brought the camping gear.
- Thank you.
- Why don't you label them...
- Marie scares me.
I'll tell you a secret.
She scares me too.
Don't tell anyone.
You okay?
Tell me.
When are you coming?
Sweetie, I'm having a really
hard time finding a transfer.
It might take awhile. But
I'm trying really hard.
I'm going to make it
happen, okay?
I don't understand.
There's got to be something.
- I mean I have the experience...
- Kathy.
- I took extra forensic courses.
- Kathy!
You've done
everything right.
- This is just how the cards fell.
- Yes, story of my fucking life.
Look, there's something
I heard about.
Yes.
I didn't think it would
work for you...
what with you trying
to get closer to your kid.
It's incredible money.
A hundred grand tax-free
for six months' work.
Come on, is it legal?
What is this?
It's the contractor that
the government uses to provide...
peacekeepers in Bosnia.
Bosnia.
You see the bullet
marks? Eye level!
They just... Kicked out
with the store. All the store.
Hey, man.
You gotta watch your back.
You come here today as
a beacon of hope.
As representatives of
our highest aspirations.
You've been hired by
Democra Security...
to represent the US...
as monitors for the
United Nations.
In the next few months...
you will protect the rule of Law
where lawlessness is run rampant.
The 1995 Dayton Peace
Accords ended this war...
dictating that an international
police task force...
you, would smooth the
transition from war to peace.
During your training you
will see that peace...
is harder won than war.
That every morning's hope is
haunted by yesterday's nightmare.
As representatives of
the United Nations...
we stake our highest
values, even our lives...
on the belief that we
can rebuild.
We must renew and we will
witness the rebirth of this country.
- Yeah!
It'll settle down.
Hey, honey.
- You been here before?
- This is my second mission.
You came straight from
the Academy?
No, I'm not a cop. I work
in administration.
You only need
a high school diploma...
and to be over 21 to get in.
What about you?
What brought you here?
I heard the food was
really great.
I thought the war was over.
De-mining.
- You okay?
- Yes.
I'm great.
I'm serious. He couldn't
move off the mine...
for eight days and eight nights.
So he's demanding time
and a half for nights.
Best part is that now,
sue me! How about that?
You still seeing the little guy?
Kathy, meet Fred Murray.
- Hi.
- Pleasure.
Hi, guys. We got a match.
High stakes tournament
situation. US versus Holland.
- Come on, let's go.
- Oh yes...
- Yes!
- Come on!
- Let's go, let's go.
- Come on, yes!
I knew it!
You suck at pinball and
you suck at football.
- Who do you think invented pinball?
- Can you play?
- Can I play! Hold this.
- Okay. Alright.
- She's having the last one.
- The last one.
You know what?
You got to pull it, alright?
Yes, she knows, okay.
She knows.
- Okay, come on.
- Just watch this.
- Damn it!
- Okay. Here we go!
Yes! Yes!
Here we go, here we go!
Shit!
Sorry, guys. I don't
know what happened.
Who's not going to buy
the drinks?
I don't know what
happened there.
I would love some whisky and...
- Don't use...
- Shit!
Sorry, you can't use both flippers
at the same time, otherwise...
- Flippers?
- Yes, these are called flippers.
Well, this is the way I was taught.
- With a man behind you?
- Girls.
See, bam bam.
Bam bam, because it
has to bounce off.
This move still get you laid?
Well, in Holland it does.
I'm really out of practice.
Gentlemen.
So where do we sign
to say we came?
You sign...
Well, I think you have to
sign at the end of the session.
No. Why?
No, no, no.
Yep. It says right here, "UN mandate
requires you to sign at the end"...
Yes, but this paper is no
good. The new policy is...
Leave her alone.
They try it out with everyone.
You sign them in,
they bugger off.
- I'm McVeigh. You're Kathy?
- Yeah.
Welcome to paradise.
Follow me.
Okay, gentlemen. If you have
nothing better to do today...
I would like you to start
investigating two new stabbings.
Four new shootings...
and a wee man with
a broken leg...
who can barely remember his name.
First one. In here.
Gather around.
Kathy...
why don't you take
this, please?
Facial contusions from
repeated beatings with fist.
Lacerations on the eye caused
by the edge of an iron.
Left arm was the first entry
point of a large kitchen knife.
Okay, Mama, I'm Just
going to lift this up.
It's all right.
- Who did this?
- Looks like the husband.
Okay, that's the case.
Who's taking it and
what's their first step?
- I will take it.
- Very good.
All right. Calm down.
What is he saying?
Say woman is Muslim...
and she deserved it.
Alright, alright!
That's enough. Stop it!
Hands off.
Moving on. Next case.
Go. Everyone outside.
Kathy, you too.
Excuse me. What do
you mean moving on?
Who's going to investigate
and make an arrest?
This is a felony assault.
Okay, let me ask you something.
Can you tell a Serb
from a Croat or a Bosniak?
Because I can. Racial hatred
started a war in this country.
And as much as I'd like to be...
we aren't here as investigators,
we monitor. That's it.
Sometimes stepping
back is part of the job.
Zlata has been in the hospital
eight times because of her husband.
Each time she tried
to make complaint...
my bosses send her home.
They laugh at her. They
laugh at women in Bosnia.
They laughed at
my mother even.
And they do not prosecute
domestic violence.
Yesterday you wanted to help.
Now you can show me
how to do this.
So this is the hospital report.
You have no police reports.
Well, what you need to do
is investigate this...
as if it were a felony assault.
So if you go back to the hospital...
and get every single doctor
who treated her to testify...
well, then you might have a chance.
But you'll have to...
Cross reference every
injury with other cases...
where courts ruled
felony assault.
If our courts rule that stabbing
a man in a bar is criminal...
then the same should apply
to a woman in her home.
I have considered the evidence...
and rule in favour
in Zlata Sehik.
- H el I o.
Don't mind him.
He's a complete wimp.
Well, you've been
stirring things up.
Ms. Rees, if I over-stepped protocol
with the Zlata Sehick case I'm...
Would you call me
Madeleine?
You've just done in two months...
what we failed to do
in four years. Sit down.
- Do you want some tea?
- Yes, please.
Viko Mezovic did a great job...
but you've just facilitated the first
conviction for domestic violence...
since the end of
the war in Bosnia.
Well, it was very basic...
Thank you.
Basic police work.
It's just my job.
You can't imagine how that makes
you stand out around here.
The IPTF have a
Gender Affairs Office here.
And the current head left...
and I think you're
the right person to take over.
Well...
Are you up for it?
- Hello.
- Hi, Sweetie.
Did you get the stuff I sent?
- Did dad say you're not coming back?
- No.
Of course I'm coming back.
- Are you sure?
- Yes.
- For Labour Day?
- Well, I...
Because my friends
are renting a boat and...
But I have to stay longer...
because they've asked me
to be the head of a department.
Oh, well...
You know what?
I'm making a lot of money...
so I can move nearer dad and
I can see you all the time.
That's cool. Hold on!
Sorry, I've got to go, Mom.
- I have a game.
- Okay.
- I love you. Bye.
- Bye.
- Kathy?
- Yes.
Nick Kaufman, Contingent Commander.
- Good to meet you.
- Great to meet you.
- How are you?
- Can I give you a hand?
- I'm fine. This way?
- Yeah.
Good having another
American in the mix.
Some people get pissed off,
saying we're taking over.
Makes my life easier.
Especially when it's a good-looking
woman reporting to me.
I don't mean to burst your bubble
but I report to Madeleine Rees.
It's a joint appointment.
And she's Human Rights.
But you're Democra.
So ultimately you're all mine
at the end of the day.
No, you can't. Don't, don't.
Please don't.
Just don't touch. Just step
away from the table, please.
I've had my eyes on this
table for a long time.
This one is mine, lady.
- This is your table?
- This is my table.
I'm sorry to tell you
but this is my table.
I have a new job over at HQ
with a lot of fancy diplomats...
and for someone
in my position this...
- Would have this table?
- Yes.
I feel very strongly about it.
- You don't care about my feelings?
- I don't care about your feelings.
- So you're just going to take it?
- I'll tell you what.
If you buy me dinner you can
have the damn table.
- Come on! Let's go.
- Okay, let's go.
I was married twice.
Like, two times?
- Two times.
- That's twice.
Yes, once and then again and
I messed it up both times.
- What about you?
- Well, technically I'm still married.
But it is...
it's complicated right now...
because we are in the middle of...
what I would call an ending.
But you're married.
Right. But we are in
the process of...
- Kids?
- Yes, we have two.
- Two?
- Boys.
It isn't that complicated
but it is.
If I slept with you,
I'm going straight to hell.
You are.
Let's get drunk first.
I'm sorry!
Stop fighting, okay?
- Put it down.
- Stay here, please.
Total goat fuck!
Musical apartments!
Just hold the people back!
What do you need me to do?
The Muslim women are supposed
to get their old apartments back.
Serbs took them during the war.
Serbs don't want to leave!
And a lot of places got sold to
third-party Croats or God knows what!
And everyone's pissed.
And I figured it's a
bunch of widows...
- so your Gender Office can handle it.
- Okay.
- Bolkovac?
- Yes.
They need you. Come on.
- Murray, can you deal with it?
- I'll take this then. Great!
She was talking but
I couldn't understand.
She's not local.
Hey.
Hey?
All right.
I'm not going to touch you.
What is it? Are you in pain?
Oh God, this girl is seriously ill.
Could you call a medic?
Somebody call an ambulance!
Raya, are you okay?
- She was further back in the woods.
- It's me, Irka. Wake up!
They make raid!
They abuse the girls.
Okay, calm down.
Take a breath.
Nine girls there.
- Help them!
- Where?
- Florida Bar.
- Florida Bar?
- What is Florida Bar?
- It's one of the bars in the hills.
Raya!
I can take them to
the Zenica Shelter.
That's where we usually
take these girls.
Usually!?
Where is the bar?
How do I get there?
What's happening here?
What's going on here?
- IPTF told us to come.
- Really?
That's interesting.
Since when do you listen to us?
Well, where are they?
I don't see any monitors.
Lady, what do you want?
I got called to come here to take
the girls to Zenica so I'm here.
What's Zenica?
What's it?
Mothersuckers. I don't pay you
fucking Smurfs no more.
Pay? Pay?
What's he talking about?
What does he mean, pay?
- What did he say?
- I don't know.
I am Bosniak and he is Croat and
I don't understand Croat!
Bullshit! I know you
understand him.
Smart lady.
- What's in Zenica?
- It's a woman's shelter.
You know, the whores
get a good meal.
They can talk about problems.
It's like a vacation for them.
Very funny.
Oh my God.
Jesus Christ.
Quickly! Over here.
- Is this the Zenica Shelter?
- Yes.
We have to be careful.
Sometimes they watch.
- Who watch?
- Traffickers.
- Traffickers?
- Yes. Human trafficking.
These girls were
abducted and sold.
They are told they must
work off their debt.
And then they'll be let go.
But they never are.
Since the end of the war...
sex trafficking has spread
like cancer.
- Why since the end of the war?
- Half our men are dead.
So...
who are these girls
brought in for?
This is our volunteer nurse.
She says Raya has bad infection.
The nurse found objects inside her.
Excuse me?
Coins.
Like you saw, they're
not prostitutes.
They are slaves, treated
like dogs.
Do you have a doctor here?
We don't have doctor.
Try the Global
Displacement Agency.
If they keep them or not,
I don't know.
Wait, please. There
were other girls?
The ones who were
from the Florida Bar.
The police brought them
here about an hour ago.
Here? No police came.
Are you sure?
These girls never arrived.
I'm looking for Laura Levi.
Okay. We'll see you later.
Okay?
I'm Kathy Bolkovac. I'm the new
Head of Gender Affairs.
I heard. Congratulations.
I'm Laura Levi.
What nationalities are
we dealing with here?
I presume these two women
want to be repatriated?
I don't know.
Actually, I brought them here because
they need medical attention.
We'll get them to the medical centre.
As soon as we get clearance,
we'll know where we stand.
Clearance? What does that mean?
Look, I'll do whatever
I can to help...
but I have to determine
if they'll cooperate...
with their repatriation program.
That's the only way
I can let them stay here.
It's not me, it's policy.
I see, policy. Okay. One more thing
I just wanted to ask you.
The other girls from
the raid were supposed to go...
to the Zenica Shelter
but they never arrived.
Really? Why don't you check
the IPTF message boards?
Listen, half the time
these raids are for show.
I'm sure the owner has paid off
whoever he had to by now.
Your missing girls are
probably back at the bar.
Excuse me now.
- Murray, mind if I join you?
- Yes, have a seat.
- Not eating?
- No, I just have a quick question.
You know the raid you
ordered last night?
Local police said they were
taking the girls to Zenica...
but they never showed up.
Fucking mess! It's the locals
dragging us into their turf war.
Some cop from another
canton calls in a fake tip...
about a prostitution bust.
But the bar is legit and
the girls just waitresses. So...
Waitresses?
It doesn't hurt to be
thorough, though, right?
Yes, right.
Thing is I found padlocked rooms,
young women's passports...
and there was a lot of
US currency...
Where are we going,
Columbo?
I don't know, but something
fucked up is going on.
Honey, it's like I say,
this is Bosnia.
These people specialize
in fucked up.
And speaking of which...
we've got another re-housing goatfuck
in Gorazde, so catch you later.
See you later, guys.
Let's go.
Should have seen this place.
There were pictures all over
the walls of guys with those girls.
And almost every
single guy in there is ours.
I saw one of your guys there.
- You saw one of my guys there?
- Yes, he was wearing your flag.
You want to ask me something?
I guess I do.
Okay, listen...
I've heard about these places.
I know they exist.
I know my guys go up
there once in awhile.
I figured for strippers or sex.
I don't know, I haven't been there.
I know nothing about any girls
being locked up. What the fuck?
Okay.
I'm sorry.
At home...
I worked in a Precinct
where there were 25 guys.
And I knew them really well,
I knew every one of them.
I know their families.
I know everything about them...
and I trust them completely.
I was dumb enough to think...
I'd be joining some
elite police officers here.
But I don't know who
these people are.
Three, two, one, clear.
Kaufman!
- Is it okay for me to be here?
- Sure. Just wait there.
What's up? You finally come
and see me in action.
I live to see you in action.
This is for you.
I think Fred Murray's taking
payoffs from brothels.
And it's not prostitution.
The girls were trafficked.
The problem is, who investigates,
how to charge him?
All the international personnel
have immunity.
They can't be Prosecuted.
But this is good work, Bolkavac.
I think it might even deserve
a dinner out with yours truly.
Don't think I've earned that.
Girls, how are you doing?
Did you get some rest?
I went to the Florida Bar...
and I saw the room in the back and
I know what's been happening to you.
Good for you. Can we go now?
What happened to the girls?
Did you see my friend Luba?
Is she safe?
No.
The police took
the girls back to the bar.
But we can still help
your friend.
I believe the bar was raided
because Tanjo, the owner...
was refusing to pay
this man money.
Is that true?
Look, I know you're
scared to talk but...
if you can tell me that
this is the man then...
Then what?
You put him in jail?
No, he has diplomatic
immunity.
That means he's protected
by the UN.
But Tanjo can go to jail.
He can go to jail.
And if you both say
in a court...
that Tanjo has been taking
payoffs from this man...
then his name will go on record...
and the UN has to do
something.
They can't knowingly have one
of their men involved in rape...
kidnapping and torture.
How do you do this
if you work for the UN?
I'm an American police officer.
It doesn't matter who I work for...
I wouldn't let anybody
get away with this.
So if we go to court you promise
you can stop these men?
I can't promise I can stop
all these men. I promise...
If you cannot promise then
why do we agree?
There is too much danger
to go speak in a court, even this...
to say anything to you.
How do I know this is safe?
You're a smart girl.
I have a daughter.
She was taken away from me and...
I can't change that.
But maybe I can change
what happens to you.
- Will we be safe?
- Yes.
Do you promise?
I promise.
Hello.
I'm calling from the Global
Displacement Agency in Sarajevo.
Do you have a daughter
named Raysa?
- Yes. Yes.
- We have her here.
If everything checks out...
we will send her home
in a few days.
- I'll come there now.
- I'm sorry, we can't afford...
I'll pay for it.
Just tell me where to go.
Roman will be home soon.
Roman seems to be doing well.
Milk?
I need to borrow money.
They found Raya in Sarajevo.
I want to go and get her.
I don't need much.
Does he still hit you?
You know I hate to ask.
But she's my daughter...
and your niece. Please.
I will get you the money.
But you have to go.
Roman will be home soon.
He won't give it to me
if he knows it's for you.
You need an armored security
vehicle for two teenage girls?
- What the hell did they do?
- None of your business.
Okay, well, it's tough today.
They sent most of
our convoy up to Tesla.
- Found some war criminal.
- Shit!
I can push for end
of the week.
Never mind. Don't worry about it.
But I'll put it through.
You never know, right?
- Is Viko around?
- Viko, your girlfriend is here.
Come on, let's go.
The van just sits here.
It's no problem.
It is not armored like you want
but it's heavy like tank.
So it's okay.
They don't build them like this.
So we go straight to the safe house.
Here's the address. after they
make statement in court, yes?
I made the call, so it's okay.
Where is Irka?
- I need to have a word with you.
- Okay. Hey, Raya.
There was a problem.
During repatriation procedures
we realized Irka had no passport.
Okay, so we get her one.
Where is she?
You don't understand.
She was trafficked from Grozny.
Her parents were killed in Chechnya
and she has no documentation.
No embassy will recognize her.
She's a girl without a country.
Okay, you're not answering
my question. Where is Irka?
We handed her over to
the police a few hours ago.
How could you do that?
Viko, take Raya.
- So you meet us when you're done?
- Yes.
- Come on. Let's go.
- Raya, I'll see you soon, okay?
- It's okay.
- How could you do that?
I couldn't keep her. She
didn't have the paperwork.
- This is bullshit!
- Every case needs to be justified.
I know what you think
but it's an uninformed opinion.
- We have a system that works here.
- Really, for who?
Sorry, I look for Laura Levinia?
That's me.
Hey.
You know where they took her?
The police take them to the border.
Once they've crossed, there is one
less trafficking victim in Bosnia.
Take the 761 to Visegrad.
Hey, I'm looking for a girl.
The police dropped
her here a few hours ago.
Could you check the border logs?
She's 15 years old, no passport.
Okay. Lady, I know
what you look for.
Those girls do not go
through border.
They go through there.
To Serbia, if they survive.
Jesus.
Irka!
Leave me alone!
Go home!
Irka, please wait.
You promised.
Irka!
Stop doing that!
Please.
Just let me die.
I'm sorry. Irka, I'm sorry.
No.
It's okay.
Alright, alright.
It's okay. It will be over soon...
then you go home
with your mother, okay?
Where's the other girl?
She's not here. Let's go.
We'll do whatever
we can to get Raya back.
I'm truly very sorry.
What will they do to her?
I want to show you what happens
when you talk to the devil.
Now. Bring her in.
Bring her in.
Watch. Make sure
they are watching.
Open your eyes.
Watch! Watch!
Take a good look.
Look at your fucking friend no w.
What happened?
The car must have
been following us.
Do you know who they were?
No.
Nobody at my station
knew where I was going.
Did you tell anybody at IPTF?
Madeleine, I need to see you.
This is Peter Ward.
Hello.
Peter's an old friend,
Internal Affairs.
So, Kathy, have you had
any report on Raya?
None.
Kathy, from now on I want you to run
your investigation alongside Peter.
The best way to find Raya...
is to continue your investigation
into Fred Murray.
You handed in a vehicle
request to IPTF.
Yes.
Well, the traffickers obviously knew
where you'd be, so there's a leak.
I know that cops don't like
to work with Internal Affairs...
but considering what just
happened, it's our only way.
Well, I don't know how
to move forward.
I've lost two witnesses.
Raya, and Irka won't testify
now, she's too terrified.
Do you think Fred Murray is only
getting payoffs from one bar?
No.
So there could be other girls willing
to testify against Fred Murray.
It's possible.
Well, if you can get any of these
girls to testify in court then...
well, there'd be something quite
substantial to work with.
Agreed?
Thank you.
I don't want to put any of you
in a dangerous position...
and ask you to speak out
against your traffickers.
I just want to know if you
recognize this man.
Maybe give them some time.
I'll let you know...
if anyone says anything.
Okay.
Milena, would you show them
this photograph, too?
Just maybe someone has
heard something about her.
You look for this girl?
She is okay?
No. No, she's not.
Do you know her?
No.
But I know him.
He comes in the same group...
every month to take
money from Ivan.
- He came in a group?
- Yes.
I want to show you some
other photographs.
If you could tell me if any
of these people were in the group.
That is Paolo.
He liked pain.
He liked weird things.
He wanted me to like too...
This made my price go down.
I know then...
it will take me two more years
to pay my debt.
He buys girls for other men
and puts them in apartments.
Soldiers pay money to own
girls for themselves.
Check it out, three grand
and she's all mine.
Luc got one for 25 hundred.
Turn around, let me see your ass.
Take off your bra.
When we come through
checkpoint he drives the van.
- What?
- Him. He was the d river.
This man drove you in a van...
across the border...
into Bosnia?
Yes.
We stop at border.
See man in blue like you.
I thank God. I think
we have our saviour.
Then he jumps in
and drives the van.
Madeleine, they're
bringing them in.
IPTF are actually trafficking girls
and bringing them across the border.
And it's not just IPTF.
This involves all kinds
of internationals...
from military officers
to diplomats.
I thought I was only
going after one guy.
I had no idea what
I'd be handing over.
Get this off to Peter
as quickly as you can.
Are you sure you want
to go ahead with this...
because you know there'll be
no going back after?
Yes, ma'am.
Right.
You work in two hours.
You sleep on whichever
mattresses are free.
They bring us food in the morning.
You have to eat it all,
or you get fined.
Come sit down.
Don't let them see you like this.
Okay?
What is your name?
Raya Kochan.
I've nearly paid my debt.
Then I can go home.
- It's all bullshit.
- No.
He sent a girl back
three months ago.
I was here.
What is your name?
She is Luba.
Luba Pallch.
I'm afraid we can't keep
you here any longer.
I'll let you know
if I hear anything.
We'll do anything we
can to get Raya back.
- Kathryn Bolkovac?
- Yes.
You're wanted
in Human Resources.
- Now?
- Yes, now.
- Sorry to keep you waiting there.
- No problem.
John Blakely.
Kathy Bolkovac.
Nice to meet you.
Have a seat.
- So you keeping busy?
- Yes.
Your superiors, they tell me
that you're working hard.
I enjoy my work.
You're dedicated, thorough.
Thank you.
Tough stuff, though, your area.
Stressful.
Do you ever worry about burnout?
No. Never.
You must miss your daughter.
It's unusual, isn't it, that a judge
would award custody to the father?
I would imagine there's almost
some kind of a stigma around that?
What did you want
to talk to me about?
I'm sorry. I just wondered.
Because we award
special paid leave to folks...
who work in stressful departments.
You know, parents especially,
we really encourage it.
And you'd have some time
to hang out with your daughter.
Nice little jaunt around
Europe, see the sights.
I'm going to have
to think about it.
You're not the maternal type?
Bitch.
Who the fuck do you think you are?
Go home before you get...
We're watching you...
You'd do better to shut
your mouth, you fucking...
Kathy, we need to meet.
It's important.
And be careful. Make sure
you're not followed.
Kathy, we need to meet.
It's important. And be careful.
Make sure you're not followed.
Fuck!
The world and its mother
knows about my investigation.
I know.
- Would you like something to drink?
- No.
- Do you mind if...
- Go ahead.
Kathy, Internal Affairs is
shutting down all your cases.
Why?
All of your files look like this.
Jesus.
I've been completely
steam-rolled.
They've sent Fred Murray
home on some kind of leave.
And top level military
commanders...
are walking into my office
and pulling your files.
I've never seen I.A.
Over-ridden like this before.
Over-ridden by who?
I don't know.
I mean, I can't be sure.
It's the State Department.
Or Democra.
You do know what
they stand to lose if this...
I guess not.
Their contract in Bosnia
is worth millions.
Globally, just this year alone...
billions of dollars
in US government contracts.
And now you come along
with this scandal...
I don't want a scandal.
I'm just doing my job.
I know, but it doesn't matter.
Nobody cares about you.
I'll get you the rest of
your files back from I.A.
You get them out of here,
take them public.
Or this will never see
the light of day.
- I can't leave these girls.
- You're not helping them here.
And, frankly, you're not safe
to walk around.
It's completely exposed you.
Kathy, accidents do happen.
A car blows a tire, a mine explodes.
We don't have to report
civilian deaths.
I'll get you the rest of these...
and you get yourself the hell
out of here as soon as you can.
Trust me. This is
the right thing to do.
I was so stupid. I mean I thought
I could work inside the system.
Like I knew what the fuck
I was doing.
Like I knew how to play ball
with all these fancy diplomats.
I don't know. What would you do?
I have to go home.
My wife got a lawyer.
I have to go home for the kids.
I'm so sorry.
But I'm worried about you.
Don't be.
I don't want...
I don't want to leave you
in the middle of all this. And...
I don't want this to be the end.
Please be careful.
What is it?
- We have to get out of here...
- Don't...
You'll get us in trouble.
Go.
I want to take you home.
- Ivan!?
- Come.
How much do you want me to pay
for these girls, to take home?
- You want to take them home?
- Yes!
It's ten times normal.
It's three thousand each.
Sorry, not this one, she's trouble.
I'm sorry, sir.
So just this one?
You bring the girl back, I give
you the deposit back, okay?
Okay.
Come on. I'll get you a drink.
Sign at the bottom, please.
- Yes?
- It's Viko.
- I can't talk right now, Viko.
- I think I know where Raya is.
Okay.
We have a bit of a problem.
What kind of problem?
Where's the girl?
All right. All right.
There you go, Raya.
- What did she say?
- Names of girls. Raya.
Raya!?
Raya is there?
All right. Calm down, you're okay.
- We go to Oasis?
- Yes!
- And IPTF?
- Fuck protocol.
We just raid the bar.
Here.
- You trust these guys?
- Yes, I do.
- They're going to listen to you?
- Out!
You sure?
I do trust them. Let's go.
Hello?
We need to bring the owner out here.
We arrest him outside.
I don't want him
threatening the girls. Go!
Here we go, go! Go!
We have a warrant
to search these premises.
Ivan Bladzic has been arrested
for human trafficking.
Get out of here.
You don't have to be afraid
of Ivan. He can't hurt you.
We're going to get you somewhere
safe and help get you home.
Raya. Raya. Come on.
These girls work here.
They have all documents,
passports.
- And you can fuck off!
- Really?
Fakes. Bad ones.
And you, too, fuck off.
And you, too, fuck you!
Okay, Viko, get the blankets
out of the van...
and get these girls out of here.
Okay, girls, come on.
You're safe. Just come.
All right, come.
Let's go.
Don't be afraid, we can all
go now. Raya, come on.
It's going to be okay. All right?
Now. Come on, Raya.
Let's just...
Come on, what's the matter?
What?
What's the matter?
What's...
What the fuck are you
doing here?
- We got a call about this raid.
- From who?
Get out.
Get out! Come on, get out.
Get out! Out!
Get out right now!
- Get your hands off me.
- Fuck!
Don't look at these guys.
Don't be afraid of these guys.
Just say you want to go
and I can walk you...
Raya, I can walk you out
of here, right now.
You just have to say you
want to go, that's all.
Don't look at him.
Look at me. I want you
to look at me.
You are safe.
Listen to me, don't look at him.
Out of here!
Just get out! Fuck!
Okay, Raya, just look at me.
Look at me. Please.
Okay. Just say yes.
Just say yes.
It's all you have to do.
Raya, please. Just say
you want to go.
No.
Just say you want to go.
Fuck! What the fuck is
the matter with you?
Don't you know anything!
We are supposed
to protect these people.
- You're a crazy bitch!
- We are supposed...
to protect these people.
- I know this girl.
- I know you do.
I know this girl.
I can't leave her here.
Let's go. Come on, Raya.
Let's go.
- I can't leave her here.
- Look at me! Kathy!
We cannot force them.
Nothing will hold up in court.
Please, understand. They will be
brought down here, punished.
You want blood on your hands?
- You fuck!
- Get the fuck out of here!
You piece of shit. You fuck!
What the fuck is the matter
with you people?
What is the matter with you?
My husband arranged
for me a job.
But his friend
bought me for $2,000.
With renewed funding from...
USAID the Global
Displacement Agency...
continues to be a pioneer at
international counter-trafficking.
My sister arranged for my papers.
Her boyfriend did this for
12 other girls.
Mostly traffickers prey
on those they know...
banking on the fact that
the girl will trust them.
Traffickers can be fathers,
brothers, sisters, aunts, uncles...
I wanted to tell you.
It's how you pay for this.
Roman, he does...
How could you...
sell your own blood?
You swine.
- Where is she?
- I don't know.
Where is she?
She is no longer your sister.
Stay away from me.
Where's Raya? Where's
the little bitch?
She's in the back.
I didn't say anything.
Please...
Are you sure you want to see?
Excuse me.
Would you please cover her up?
Could you find a blanket, please?
Could you cover her up?
I am a police officer
obligated to report crimes.
I have taken statements from
women describing their physical...
psychological...
and emotional torture.
On arriving in Bosnia,
these women are sold...
and forced to provide
sexual services.
Their clientele consists of SPOR...
IPTF, local police...
and international employees.
Worse, they have become
in olved in the trade itself.
It is time each and
every one of you realize...
this is a serious organized crime...
with enormous profits.
We are peacekeepers who came
to protect the innocent...
but now prey upon them
in the worst ways possible.
We may be accused of thinking with
our heart instead of our heads...
but we will have our humanity.
Good morning.
I have to ask you to
surrender your ID.
What?
What's going on?
You've been ordered out
of this mission.
You can't be serious.
I'll need the ID.
- Thank you. Guys...
- Come on.
Why do you want to get rid of her?
Madeleine, I have to protect this
organization and so should you.
The UN is too fragile, too important.
That's what immunity is for.
Immunity not impunity.
The United Nations was formed
from the ashes of Auschwitz.
The United States led the way and
it's a point of honour with me...
that the UN is not
remembered for raping...
the very people we must protect.
Those girls are whores of war.
It happens.
I will not dictate for morality.
So what are we dictating for?
I'll go to Washington. I'll go to
the State Department if I must.
Democra isn't even based out of the
States, it's based out of England.
It's a private corporation.
We work in the real world.
Thank you so much.
Really helpful.
I had to send that e-mail.
They killed Raya.
- They shot her in the head.
- I know.
She wanted to testify and
they made an example of her.
I'm responsible for this.
No, dear, you're not.
I promised her I would
protect her.
Oh God, I can't stop
thinking about her mother.
How do we tell people
what's happening here?
Democra is registered in
the UK, in Britain.
So you are entitled
to appeal your dismissal.
We've got to get those files out
of the mission right away.
Because you're a whistleblower,
so the press will want to know.
I handed in my ID
and my keys.
Shit!
I don't know how
to get in there.
We'll have to find a way.
Zoe. Zoe!
What are you doing here?
I need to get something
out of my office.
I was wondering if you
could get me a set of keys.
Kathy, I can't.
It's too risky.
I would lose my job.
I wish I could help, I really do.
I'm sorry. I'm just not like you.
- You scared me.
- Sorry, I didn't recognize the coat.
We don't have much time.
I can't go up there with you.
You understand, right?
Yes.
Alright, now make
certain you get everything.
And that includes any files you
didn't send to I.A. or to me.
Yes.
If anybody's going to believe this,
the press needs to see it all.
Okay, I'll meet you
in the atrium, right.
Okay.
You're an asshole.
You really didn't think you were
going to get away with this, did you?
Those look right to you?
Yes, it's all here.
You're trespassing.
So what? What are you going
to do, fire me again?
You going to arrest me?
I have diplomatic immunity.
Isn't that what you all rely
on around here?
You had immunity. You don't
have a UN ID any more.
You're a civilian now.
You're on your own.
I'm sure the State Department
will be happy to hear...
- from me when I get back.
- Where do you think this comes from?
The State Department
owns your contract.
They don't want you here.
Democra wants you out.
You talk to whoever you want.
They're not listening.
You're finished.
Did you get what you need?
The State Department
owns your contract.
They don't want you here.
Democra wants you out.
You talk to whoever you want.
They're not listening.
That's good.
As soon as you get to London
take this right to the BBC, okay?
- Thank you, Peter.
- Go.
I can categorically state
not one United Nations officer...
has been involved in
the trafficking of a single woman.
You believe all these victims'
claims to be false?
Well, I don't want to make
accusations against those girls.
But I will assert over and over again,
I run a Zero Tolerance program...
for that type of activity.
Now we've just set up a full
taskforce dedicated to abolishing...
all sex trafficking
in the region.
Thank you.
We spoke to Bill Hynes, the senior
UN official in Bosnia at the time.
I saw that interview.
And as you watched it,
what did you think?
I think Mr. Hynes knows
that he made a false statement.
So you're accusing
him of lying?
Yes. Absolutely.
We have considered
Democra's explanation...
as to why they
dismissed Ms. Bolkovac...
and there is no doubt
whatsoever...
that the real reason
for her dismissal...
was that she made
a protected disclosure...
and accordingly
was dismissed unfairly.
You smuggled files that belonged
to the UN out of the mission.
Don't you think that was a rather
reckless thing to do?
Those young women had put themselves
at great risk by confiding in me.
And I led them to believe
that they would receive justice...
but we let them down.
So the least I can do is
let them be heard.
Given everything
you've been through...
would you do it again?
Yes.
Yes, I would.
No doubt about it.