-== [ www.OpenSubtitles.com ] ==-
Attention please.
TWA flight number
820 from Hong Kong
has landed one half
hour ahead of schedule.
Passengers are
deplaning at Gate 3.
Announcing the departure
of Pan Am flight number
538 leaving for New York.
Passengers please
proceed to gate 4.
Thank you.
Japan Airlines flight number 18
has just arrived at gate 20.
Thank you.
Mommy!
Go right on in!
May I help you?
Eggs.
There.
Announcing the arrival of
BEA flight number 704.
Thank you.
Waiter?
Tang Lung?
Miss Chen Ching Hua?
Yes.
Why not waiting for me at the
exit gate but running around?
The plane arrived early.
I was hungry so I went
and grabbed a bite.
How is my uncle in Hong Kong?
He's a bit unwell,
so I came instead.
He wrote me about you but
didn't go into details.
How can you help me?
Please don't stand on ceremony.
I'll personally help you.
Personally help me?
You know my problem?
That you must tell
me in details later.
But first, now please tell
me where the toilet is?
Precious horse (BMW)?
Wild horse (Mustang)?
A flying horse?
Dad died last month and
left me this restaurant.
Uncle Wang and the others
have helped out a lot.
Business wasn't bad
in the beginning.
Then a huge syndicate
stepped in.
They're interested in our land
and wanted me to
sell the restaurant.
There's no sale without
mutual agreement.
If you refuse, what can they do?
In theory, you're right, but
they won't listen to reason.
They'll do anything
for getting my land.
They hired some young thugs to
watch the place day and night.
If a customer comes in they
simply drive him away.
What am I to do?
Why not report it to the police?
They disappear when
the police come.
We can't ask the police for
round-the-clock protection.
Business has gone down badly and
I still have to pay my workers.
How can I go on
meeting the expenses?
The thugs have become worse lately
demanding an immediate answer.
So I wrote to my uncle for help.
I thought he'd send
a lawyer, but...
You are welcome.
I told you not to worry.
I am here to help.
Don't worry, Miss Chen.
It's nothing, I can
take care of them.
Look up there!
That's their headquarters.
Please sit down.
I rent this place.
It's more convenient living here
because all the men
live at the restaurant.
There's always a spare room.
If any of the workers get
sick, they can come here.
It is crowded in the restaurant.
You can stay here
for the time being.
You're my uncle's friend,
so please feel at home.
Let me know if you
need anything.
May I use your toilet?
It's over there.
Chinese New Year is coming up.
Everyone in Hong Kong is
happy and celebrating.
Do they celebrate it in Rome?
I haven't been back to Hong
Kong for more than 1 O years.
I think it's changed a lot.
I may be a stranger
when I am back.
Oh, yes.
How's the restaurant
business there now?
I live in the New Territories
and seldom go out of town.
I practice martial
arts every day.
Restaurants haven't
changed much.
Take a seat.
Here's the key.
Our telephone number and
address are all on it.
The restaurant is nearby.
If you get lost just show
that card to a taxi driver
and any taxi driver
will bring you back.
Taxi? It's too expensive here.
Are there public light buses?
Do you need some money?
No, I brought some with me.
Better put it in a bank,
it's safer that way.
No, it's safer to
carry it by myself.
Much safer than
carry it by others.
I won't argue. How
much did you bring?
Not much.
Really, not much.
I still say it's
safer in the bank.
Come on!
Miss Chen! How are you?
This is Mr. Tang.
He wants to deposit some money.
Ah, my friend!
How much do you have?
Take it out now.
This way.
How much you want to
change into our currency?
How much local money
will you change?
Only $20.
Lately the exchange
rate has been bad.
There $20 will do.
That was the bank manager
not a pickpocket.
You must be more polite.
Not everyone you
meet is a villain.
Not everyone you meet
is a pickpocket.
Besides, I know
that bank manager.
Foreigners are warm and passionate.
They also quite friendly.
When people smile, smile back.
That's politeness.
When someone puts an
arm on your shoulder
it's a sign of friendship.
You should react the same way.
Remember my words and no
need to be so uptight!
Sit down.
Make yourself at home.
Ah Lung.
You must be Ah Lung!
Welcome to Rome.
I'm Ah Kun from Miss
Chen's restaurant.
Brother Kun!
Miss Chen has returned to the
restaurant after a long wait.
She asked me to take you there.
By the way, where
were you just now?
Let's g0!
Uncle Wang, Ah Lung is coming.
Ah Lung, this is Uncle Wang.
Uncle Wang.
Have a seat!
- Ah Kun, make some tea.
- OK.
It must have been a long
and tedious flight.
How do you like it here so far?
I'm certainly not
used to things yet.
Doesn't matter, you
will, as time goes on.
It's been a long time
since I was back home.
How are things in Hong Kong?
Hong Kong? I live in
the New Territories
and I seldom go out of town.
Have some tea.
Come, have some tea.
Why there is no customer coming
to such a big restaurant?
Ah Lung, with those
thugs around,
who'd dare come here?
Ah Lung, there are more
workers training out back.
Let's go meet them.
There's no business so they
spend their time exercising.
Come on!
Before Mr. Chen passed
away, they learned karate
to handle the villains.
Why didn't you take it up?
I'm not interested in
foreign martial arts.
It doesn't matter what style
if you can use your
body well without limit
even in the midst
of violent movement
to honestly express oneself.
I prefer Chinese boxing.
Do you know Chinese boxing?
Yes!
Really?
Let's take a breather.
Come here.
This is Tang Lung.
Introduce yourselves.
My name is Tony!
Jimmy!
Thomas!
Robert!
I've no English name.
Call me Ah Quan.
Brother Quan.
Come on...
He looks like a coach.
Have you learned any boxing?
Ah Lung came from
Hong Kong to help us.
He's an Chinese boxing expert.
I'm just a novice.
Chinese boxing? I understand
it's like dancing.
But it sadly lacks power?
You lack power when you haven't
mastered the fundamentals.
Right, how then do
you develop power?
By uniting the waist
with the stance.
Will you demonstrate how to unite
the waist with the stance?
I'm afraid I'll hurt someone.
What are you afraid of?
They're wearing
protective padding.
They won't get hurt.
We've guests coming.
Change the clothes
and get to work.
Hurry!
Come on, let's go.
Change the clothes
and get cracking!
Brother Kun, where's the toilet?
Over there. It's
labeled in English.
Get the hell out of here.
Now.
Come on!
Get out!
Why?
That's why!
What's your decision?
Uncle Wang!
Come quick, they're here again!
Stop it!
All right!
If you don't send
a reply tonight,
don't blame us for
getting rough.
Please help us out, Mr. Ho,
put in a good word for us.
Give us a few more
days to think it over.
You've been delaying
a long time.
Are you not selling?
Why do you fight?
You fight.
Don't fight please! We'll
only wreck our own things.
Remember, you must
send a reply tonight.
Let's g0!
Sorry!
Be careful next time.
You don't even know
a word of English.
Why did my uncle send you here?
Ah Lung, they're young
and headstrong.
Don't blame them, everything
will be all right.
Lucky that they
weren't armed today.
In broad daylight?
They wouldn't dare
use a gun in public.
If Uncle Wang hadn't
stopped them,
I'd have used karate on them!
You can talk!
What good is your karate?
It's still better
than Chinese boxing.
People shove you out of the way.
And you even apologized!
Sit down, please!
May I help you?
May you help me?
Sure!
I'd like some Chinese spareribs.
Chinese spareribs?
You mean to tell me
you don't know what
Chinese spareribs are?
Well, let me show you!
What are you doing?
You know what we are
doing, don't they, fellas?
You all should have
left this restaurant!
Brother Kun, get Uncle
Wang out here to help.
You two come to help.
Stay calm. Don't
wreck our place.
It's no use.
You want to step outside?
Sure!
Good!
Ah Lung, you?
Jimmy! Jimmy.
Jimmy!
Chinese boxing?
Damn! They know nothing!
They think this is
Chinese boxing.
If I knew Chinese boxing, I'd
give them a good taste of it!
I'll go!
Tell him this is Chinese boxing.
Hey! Chinese boxer!
The Gold Dragon Fist No.4.
"Little Dragon Asking
for Direction."
"Big Dragon whipping its tail!"
Ah Lung, bravo!
Magnificent!
Excellent!
Don't be overjoyed.
There'll be more
trouble after this.
With Ah Lung's skills,
those men dare not
think twice now.
You don't understand.
Powerful outsiders can hardly
afford to neglect local bullies.
This is their territory.
We are under their control.
We must be careful.
Let's be more patient.
More patience! Man,
our Dragon is here!
You'd be wise to heed my advice.
Is that so?
Calm down, everyone.
Ah Lung, it's late,
you must be tired.
Let's turn in.
Want some supper?
No, I must get up
early for training.
Go to bed early.
I hear it's easy
to buy a gun here?
Yes, any local citizen
can get a license.
What are you doing?
Making darts.
Darts?
What is it?
What to do?
Want to eat?
You can eat if you're
as good as Ah Lung.
Better go practice your karate!
Is it for Brother Lung? Why
didn't you say so earlier?
Brother Lung?
Brother Lung...
Good morning, Brother Lung!
Brother Lung, I made
this especially for you.
Eat it while it's hot.
Your kung fu is terrific.
Who was your teacher
in Hong Kong?
Look at this! "Little Dragon
Asking for Direction."
"Big Dragon whipping its tail."
With that, all the
enemies are down!
You said Chinese
boxing lacks power.
I was only kidding.
Brother Lung, you were
too fast yesterday.
We couldn't see clearly.
Will you show us again?
Please show us.
Go on then!
OK, come on.
Brother Lung, come on.
Everyone says you're
fast and powerful.
I didn't see it last night.
You said power can be generated
by uniting the waist
with the stance.
How about a demonstration?
Be quiet and let's watch, okay?
Let's watch together.
So, shut up!
Step back!
Are you all right?
Everything all right?
Fantastic!
Brother Lung, will
you be my teacher?
Will you be my teacher?
You said practicing
martial arts is useless.
So why are you doing it now?
I never liked karate.
But this is Chinese boxing.
Can you dig it?
We'll give up karate.
Let's learn from Brother Lung.
Right!
Customers! Come quick!
Corning...
Change your clothes!
Brother Lung, oh no, my teacher.
I am going to take
care of the customers.
We'll talk later.
Miss Chen, is there
anything for me to do?
Watch out for those villains.
They may come again.
My boss wants to see you!
What did he say?
He wants us to see his boss.
Shut up! Now move!
See you tomorrow.
All of you are good for nothing!
You! Didn't you have a gun?
What I like, I get,
and I want that restaurant.
Yes, boss! Yes, boss!
Haven't you wasted enough time?
But I always do my best.
Then how come you failed?
I found out that they are helped
by a man called Tang Lung.
A man? Only one man?
But this man knows
Chinese kung fu.
Kung m?
Good morning, sit down.
Eat please.
It's hard to find this in
Rome how does it taste?
It's not as good
as in Hong Kong.
I cooked it.
It's all right.
And you?
Want some more?
I'll take you around Rome later.
Wait!
Go on!
Move, move, come on!
Where's the man from Hong Kong?
Tell him to come out.
Where is he? Talk!
I don't know.
You'd better talk!
All right. He'll be back soon.
Where is he now?
These are Rome's famous
relics of the past.
Over there it is... what is it?
Our slum is full
of these wrecks.
Please.
This garden...
A king built the
garden for his queen.
It took a lot of time and money.
They must have been
really in love.
Are you married?
How do you like the palace?
Such a big place is a waste.
In Hong Kong, I would build a
skyscraper and collect rent.
We'd better return
to the restaurant.
Close the door.
You better cool it, baby.
Bring him down!
Chinese kung fu?
The boss means well.
We all come out for a living.
He appreciates talent
and he knows you're strong.
Oh, what rippling muscle!
We don't want to harm you.
Here's a ticket
back to Hong Kong.
Better to stay out of trouble.
All right! Take him out,
but be careful with
the gun in public.
Yes, boss. Come on, let's go.
Go see if anybody's around.
Put your hands down.
Put your hands down!
Listen! Listen! Boss,
that bastard got away!
Go! Get him, but no gun!
Get him!
Let's get him!
Let me get him.
Get him.
Get him!
Mama mia!
No need to like this.
Miss Chen, quit
while you're ahead.
You'd better say yes.
We intended well.
We're offering you a good deal.
What do you think?
Hello!
Tell him.
We don't want any more trouble,
or else I will retaliate.
He told us not to come and
cause any more trouble.
Move them out.
Hurry up and pick up everybody.
Ah Lung, hold it,
those are customers.
Welcome!
Come in please.
Serve our guest properly.
Tang Lung must leave
Rome before 12pm,
otherwise a gunman for him.
See? I told you to be patient.
You should bear the
responsibility for this.
What should we do now?
We'll fight to the end.
This is no joke.
I know, but...
I know how you feel,
but we must think of Ah Lung.
They'll do what they say.
You mean...
Keep him under cover for awhile.
Tomorrow is Lunar New Year's Day.
If there's trouble then...
I don't know if he'll agree?
I know he's stubborn.
You must persuade him.
Without him, we'll be forced
to sell the restaurant.
We'll have to see.
We may have to cooperate.
But we mustn't sell the place.
Let me decide.
All right.
Better go and talk to Ah Lung.
Is your restaurant
open tomorrow?
Good.
We'll go to the
countryside and practice.
Remind Ah Kun to bring
the protective padding.
Firecrackers?
It's banned in Hong Kong. There
must be Chinese living nearby.
You must leave Rome for awhile.
Leave Rome?
Don't misunderstand. We
don't want you to go.
Especially me, but
you must leave.
Do you understand me?
I don't understand.
Ah Lung, why won't you...
Are you afraid of fire crackers?
I'll take you to the airport.
- Why?
- Those men want you...
My duty is to help you.
I know, but you must leave.
They intend to kill you!
Kill me? Who?
Time's up. Let's go!
It's too noisy. I'll
close the window.
Stay here, don't move about.
Miss Chen!
Hello! May I help you?
Hello? Hello? Hello?
Hello?
Three five.
Hello, what was that Sir,
can you please repeat that?
Hello? Hello? Hello?
Miss Chen, don't waste time.
Here's the agreement of sale.
Sign it.
No!
Why be so stubborn?
The boss has been nice to you.
If this knife crosses your face,
you'll look ugly.
Agree and sign.
So don't make our boss mad.
I won't sign!
It's for your own good.
No matter whether
you sign or not.
We'll get the restaurant
sooner or later.
Tang Lung will soon be here.
Tang Lung? You think
he will come?
Tell you, he go to hell already.
Be careful!
The mastermind is over there.
You're crazy!
- Let me tell you...
- He doesn't understand Chinese.
I think of a wonderful way
to handle that Tang Lung.
Which is called, do unto others
as you would have
them do unto you.
Well, among my friends,
there is one Japanese
martial artist
and one European martial artist.
They are both strong,
but the problem is that they're
from different styles.
I'm afraid they might not
cooperate with each other.
Money will buy cooperation.
If money is not a problem,
then I suggest we must
call America for Colt.
Is this Colt good?
Is Colt good? He
is America's best!
You better pray that you
don't fail this time.
He will beat Tang Lung.
I'm willing to bet
my life on it.
Operator!
I'd like to call America.
Yes, A-me-ri-ca!
Happy New Year!
Here you are... thank you...
Thank you, Uncle Wang...
I didn't expect traditional
lucky money abroad.
Uncle Wang gives us
lucky money yearly.
This is my best New Year ever.
First, we successfully
defended our restaurant.
And second, we have
Brother Lung with us,
who's also our teacher.
Third, we finally
beat the hoodlums.
Good day today.
Let's enjoy the new year
and skip the violence.
Here comes Ching Hua.
Happy New Year!
Come, this is for you.
Thank you, Uncle Wang.
Ah Lung, a cable for you.
It's from my Uncle.
He wants you to go
somewhere to help someone.
Don't be like that I'll be back.
I won't leave until the
whole thing is settled.
Happy New Year! Beautiful
decorations indeed.
What a warm gathering.
What do you want?
I came to bring greetings.
It was our fault.
I must apologize.
We must all be friends.
Our boss would like to see Mr.
Tang.
Have a talk in person.
Would he do us the honor?
Wonderful, this is
good beginning.
Business will be good this year.
Tell your boss we'll be there.
Meet in the Empress Restaurant
tomorrow morning. Bye-bye.
Oh, no. Please! Please, stop it.
Both of you.
- Damn it!
- Oh. Oh, no.
Please! Listen to me.
Oh, please.
We are friends.
Tang Lung is our enemy.
Please wait for our boss
to come back to decide
which one of you will take
care of that Chinaman, OK?
Stop!
Sensei!
Bob's my student.
He will be the one who will
personally take care of Tang Lung.
Yes, boss!
Who can do karate better
than the Japanese?
Now that we have decided.
- Is everything arranged?
- Yes, boss!
First of all,
I'll meet them at the Empress
Restaurant early tomorrow morning.
You're here. Sit down.
Sorry our boss couldn't
make it today.
What's going on?
Sorry, something urgent came up.
My car's outside. I will
drive you to meet him.
What? We're to go to him?
Never mind. Take us there!
Right! I like straight-talkers.
Let's g0!
Where is he?
He's gone.
Forget it. He won't get away.
It's a trick. Be
careful everyone!
Leave it to me, Teacher!
The three of us can handle him.
I'll go first.
You? Tang Lung?
Tang Lung.
Are you Tang Lung?
Leave it, he's
already surrendered.
Ah Lung, we're lucky this time,
not to have fallen
into their trap.
Tang Lung, come if you dare!
Ah Lung, don't let him get away.
Tony and Jimmy can
take the Japanese.
Tony, are you all right?
I'm hurting all over.
Uncle Wang, why...
Don't blame me. If you
must, blame it on Ah Lung.
Yes, Ah Lung got you
into this mess.
He should not have
get in my way.
You... what do you mean?
What do I mean?
Working men have no future.
I have worked hard for half
my life but I own nothing.
My wife and children are
waiting in Hong Kong.
If the restaurant
cooperates with them,
they'll pay me a big reward.
Then I can return to Hong
Kong, and enjoy luxury.
You should understand
my difficulties!
Tang Lung, you've got guts.
Tang Lung, the man you
just saw will kill you.
Tang Lung, you're at
the end of your road.
You're at Death's door.
Ho!
Mr. Wang, we've failed.
Hold it!
We've been tricked.
Tony and Jimmy... look!
Don't get emotional, please!
Listen to me, Mr. Tang.
Boss...
All right. Hands up!
Don't move.
Okay. Let's go.
Now that it's over, I must go.
I'll see you off.
No, Ah Quan has a
car waiting for me.
Take good care.
In this world of
guns and knives,
Tang Lung is respected
wherever he goes!
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org