Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org
- Beautiful spot, right?
- Amazing.
- You know what formed all this stuff, right?
- No.
Volcanoes, earthquakes, storms. Violent shit.
Did you know that there's
an entire city beneath the canyon?
Did you know that?
Isn't it amazing how fast kids grow up?
One day they're in diapers and next they're
debating you on politics and music.
What? Andrew is debating you
on politics and music?
- I'm impressed.
- I'm using the word "debate" very loosely.
Here we go, ladies.
Time to strap on a feedbag.
Yeah, chow time.
And every good meal needs a little booze.
Bronn?
I'm sorry. No, I'm sorry.
No, no, no. It's okay.
I got a soda around here somewhere.
God bless you.
I don't know how you can do it.
I mean, I need the booze,
if only to deal with this one.
Hey! Hey.
You know, you're gonna have to do
a lot of sucking up after that comment.
Sucking up? Magic fingers on the footsies?
- Foot massage. Come on, babe.
- That's fine. Not now.
Come on! Come on!
Gary, come on!
One foot massage before we eat. Come on!
- Gary, come on!
- Come here!
Hey! Where the hell you going?
Just going up the trail. I can see
where it ends from right here.
Did you ask Steph and Michael
if they want to join ya?
I'll go.
Keep an eye on him, okay?
You don't have to say it every time.
My turn?
Hey, no running, okay?
You twist an ankle out here
and we don't find ya,
you're gonna have to drink your own piss
and survive inside an animal carcass.
Gary!
What? Like Bear Grylls, honey,
that badass on TV.
What is wrong with men that
they're obsessed with this crappy show?
Really? I mean, that show
gave us our mad skills.
Yeah, I mean, we're, kind of,
the American version
- of Man vs. Wild.
- Yeah.
We stayed in hotel rooms
for most of the vacation.
We were camping for, like, four nights?
- Three?
- Sure. I know that.
- Two and a half?
Two and a half.
Doesn't matter.
Look. If we ever were stranded,
say, near the wilderness...
We would handle it.
- Yeah. Boom.
- Oh!
Whose turn is it?
- You.
- You distracted us.
Bet there's all kinds of creepy
old shit in this place.
The only shit in this place
is spilling out of your mouth.
Whoa!
Hey, Mikey, do you know
how hardcore your sister is?
Guess not, huh?
Hey, he's smarter than you.
He just sees different, that's all.
What's he see then?
Nobody really knows, but he's on a whole
different level to the rest of us.
Meaning what?
For one thing, he's not afraid
of the things that scare most kids.
Let's find out.
- Don't be a jerk, Andrew.
- It's okay.
Hey, Mikey. Mikey.
Did you know the Indians
that used to live around here
thought this place was haunted?
Legend says, that the guardians
of their spirit world
lived in the rocks and the trees,
and that one day they're gonna
come back into our world.
And when they do, it means
the whole world's gonna end.
Really?
Yeah.
They're right behind you!
Guess that didn't work out, moron.
Look, I didn't mean anything by it.
Mikey knows that.
Here. You've had your eye on this all day.
You can have it.
Hey, there's some kind of
lookout up here. Come on.
- Come on, Mikey.
- No.
Mikey.
All right, just stay put, okay?
Don't move.
Gary!
- What's up?
- There you are.
Where'd you go, guys?
- We were just...
- I was looking for this guy.
I was lost.
He was lost. I found him.
Mikey! Mikey!
Uh, Mikey. Just a minute, buddy.
What?
Oh, my God. What is up with that dog lately?
Michael!
Uh...
- Honey, not now, okay?
- No? Really?
- Yeah.
- I wanna talk to you.
Yeah.
Don't go.
Kids are up.
Mikey.
Hey, I told you not to leave
the tap running in the kitchen.
Mikey?
Hey, come on. Let's get some breakfast.
Jenny did it.
Jenny? Who's Jenny?
She's my new friend.
Oh, that's nice. Where's Jenny?
In the wall.
Well, maybe Jenny's hungry, too. Come on.
Steph.
You in there?
Mom! What the hell?
Did you burn something in the kitchen?
Close the frickin' door!
Jesus H.!
Mikey, I told you not to do this.
What is that smell? Putrid.
Hey, buddy, do me a favor
and listen to Mommy today, okay?
Hey, family.
Hey.
- Breakfast, Stephanie.
- Later.
No bags on the table, Mikey. Remember?
- No, no, no, no.
- Okay. Okay.
That's like his new thing.
He's very attached.
Okay. No one's gonna touch your backpack.
Okay, buddy?
Ugh!
Babe, what's that smell?
I don't know. I think it's the trash.
Can you take it on your way out?
Yup. I'm late as it is, but okay.
- Maybe open a window, okay?
- Okay.
See you later. Gotta go.
- Gotta go. Gotta go.
- Love you.
Go. Go. Go. Gotta go.
Gotta go.
Go.
Just you and me again, Mikey, huh?
Five, six,
seven, eight,
nine,
ten. Hmm.
If I were Mikey,
where would I hide?
Boo!
Mikey.
Michael, you trying
to give me a heart attack?
What is it? "Bon Voyage"?
Well, no one's going anywhere,
but you can have one. Come on.
Okay, two balloons, then. Come on.
Come on, mister greedy pants.
Michael!
What the hell are you doing up here?
You scared me half to death.
How did you get up here?
Jenny showed me a way.
Jenny...
When I meet this Jenny,
I'm gonna have a word with her.
Now, come on.
Don't forget our safety in the...
Sweetie, come on.
Let's just get out of here. Come on.
These are the new offices.
The old offices,
you would not have enjoyed that.
Now the only other important
person you need to meet...
Well, not as important as me,
but I want you to meet Peter Taylor.
He's one of our top designers
and a great guy. You're gonna like him.
- I know you're doing...
- Peter!
All right, I gotta call you right back, okay?
Peter, say hello to Sammy.
New member of the team.
She can help you on the Foster project.
Hi.
She's a graduate, so she can
help you with whatever you need.
Design and drafting and project coordination,
CAD rendering, whatever you need.
All right, you guys talk.
Welcome to the firm.
Thank you, Mr. Taylor.
It's a pleasure to meet you, finally.
Sorry, I'm a huge fan of your work.
You came to my college last year and did
some lectures on modern design theory.
- Very fascinating.
- Thank you.
I'm just thrilled to know that anybody
actually attended one of my lectures.
- Hey. How was your day?
- It was fine.
Hey.
You're late again.
Hardly see you these days.
Yeah. I'm just super busy at work.
I told you, this project is like
the biggest thing we've ever done.
It's killing me.
Yeah. Well, can you put the vegetables on?
I've got a pile of work to do here myself.
Yeah, I'll do whatever you want
as soon as I get back from a run.
Well, don't bother then.
I'll do it. It's just a quick jog
around the block.
Twenty minutes max, okay?
What is up with that dog?
Yeah, she...
She's... She's not like that. She doesn't...
She... I don't know. She doesn't enjoy it.
Mmm-mmm.
I don't know. My birthday?
Yeah, look, I would if I could,
but I told you how things are right now.
It's just nuts with work and, um...
Yeah, I can't get out.
Tell me about it. All right.
Michael, were you in the bathroom just now?
Come on, answer me!
Stop hiding in this stupid place!
Michael, if you don't answer me,
I'm gonna mess up all your stuff.
One, two...
I wasn't in your bathroom.
Jenny was in your bathroom!
There is no Jenny!
- There is a Jenny!
- Don't you get it?
You freakin' made her up!
I didn't make her up!
Stephanie! Get out of here
and go to your room now!
- One...
- You okay?
Two,
three...
One, two...
Get the hell out.
Hey, watch it.
I thought you were asleep.
The light's on.
That's usually a hint I'm not.
Why do you provoke him, Steph?
Why do I get blamed
for everything in this family?
Honey, you know that's not true.
It is. You and Mom,
we never talk about anything.
We never talk about him. We never
talk about how he affects all of us.
We do. We do. We talk about...
No, you and Mom just ignore it.
We never talk about the creepy stuff he does.
It's getting creepier and creepier
and you just let him get away with it.
- Sweetie, here's the thing...
- I've got to study.
I've got to study.
Michael.
Hey, sweetie, what're you doing?
I kept hearing weird noises last night.
Freaked myself out, so I came in here.
What kind of noises?
Can you tell Michael to stay out of my room?
He keeps leaving dirty hand marks everywhere.
Hey, big guy.
Something's bugging you, huh?
Hey, Jeff. I was just seeing
what was up with your dog.
What you got,
a new cat over there or something?
No, Jeff, we don't have a new cat.
We don't have a bird or a fish or a gerbil.
We have no pets.
Maybe it's time to take yours to the vet?
Yeah, let me, uh, get right on that, huh?
Asshole.
Hey.
Get out! Get out!
What the hell? Shoo! Get out of here!
Get out! Get out! Get out!
I'm trying to help! I'm trying to help!
I'm trying to help you!
Peter!
I hate you!
- Hey! Hey! Hey! Whoa! Whoa! Whoa!
- I hate you!
- She's sick!
- You're a bitch!
She's sick!
She's so sick!
I hate you! Evil, bitch!
No!
She eats and then she comes
in here and she throws it up.
She's so sick.
Honey...
I'm sorry, Dad.
I know. It's okay. Come here, come here.
- I'm sorry, Dad.
- No, no, no.
Can I go for my driving test soon?
A promise is a promise in this family, right?
You know your mom and me
are not the enemy, right?
We just want you to get healthy
and happy and strong.
Get through this crap
and put it all behind you.
We only want you better, sweetheart.
Okay.
Look at you! Look how you've grown.
- Say hi.
- TV, TV, TV, TV, TV, TV.
- Okay.
- Okay!
Hiya, honey.
All right, well. Thanks for taking him
on such short notice, Mom.
Stephanie is not feeling so hot
so we just need to spend
a little bit of time with her, alone.
Okay, but any time, darling. You know that.
- All right. Well, I gotta go.
- Okay.
So, I'll see you tonight.
All right, don't worry.
- Thanks, Mom!
- Okay.
- Bye!
- Bye.
Okay, mister.
How about peanut butter and jelly?
I think it's time that we went and watched
your favorite television show.
Okay? I'm just gonna finish up in here.
And Keensy can keep you company.
Keensy! What's gotten into you?
Uh...
Michael, maybe you just better
leave him alone today, honey.
Mikey!
Bronny, where's your mom?
She's upstairs in observation.
- Mr. Taylor, I'm Dr. Jones.
- What happened?
Your wife's mother, she said that
somehow a snake got into the house.
A...
By the time the paramedics
got there, it was gone.
But she was obviously distressed, so we
gave her something to calm her down.
She said that she was hearing
strange noises in the room with him,
but when she got there he was alone.
Um, Mr. Taylor,
your son was trying to kill her cat.
No. No, no, no. That's not right.
He would never do that.
Hey, how you doing, buddy? Okay?
Just let me know if you have any questions.
- Okay. Thank you.
- We're in the hospital.
The hospital.
If I were Mikey,
where would I hide?
Oh, Michael!
Michael! Hey!
- Peter!
- Get down from there!
Sweetie, getting...
This has gone far enough. He's got to learn.
- Mikey!
- Look, getting angry doesn't help.
He's got to learn. Come on!
Sweetie, nobody got hurt.
This time.
Calm down. You're scaring him.
He's scaring me. Look, I...
I can handle the counting.
I can handle the forts in the living room.
The damn toys, I never get tired
of stepping on them.
But I draw the line at starting fires.
He's getting dangerous.
Why can't you see that?
Sweet... I'm not...
Mikey.
What? Come on, guys.
Hello?
Sammy. Hey, it's Pete.
- Hey!
- I'm really, uh, sorry to call you so late.
Oh, that's fine. No problem.
Is everything okay?
Yeah, yeah. I was just running through this
latest round of designs that just came in.
They're an absolute mess
and I think I'm gonna need some
one-on-one help to make this deadline.
I was just wondering if there's any chance
at all that you would be willing
to work late for a couple of nights
or maybe even over the weekend?
Yeah. Whatever I can do to help you.
Great, see you tomorrow.
Open fire!
Honey, uh, I'll tell you it's lucky
you caught it when you did
because the damage is mostly superficial.
I can just paint over it when I get the time.
I can fix it.
You know I'm very good with my hands.
I'm being serious, Peter.
How do you think he did it?
I don't know. It's just an accident, I guess.
He's playing around,
suddenly the room's on fire.
That's not what I mean.
How did he get the matches
in the first place?
They're in the cupboard
above the refrigerator.
Uh... Maybe we left them out.
I don't know. Stephanie?
Okay. Wait, wait. Hang on.
Hang on. I'm listening.
What I'm trying to say is do you think this
has something to do with us as parents?
Hold on. Please. Let's not start
blaming ourselves. All right?
Kids are affected by the problems
and emotions of their parents.
You heard Dr. Mitchell.
Right, and the very,
very expensive specialist
is never wrong about these things.
You're not hearing me, Peter.
What I'm trying to say is...
Yeah?
I think there's something else in the house.
Hold on. Please. Let's not start...
I mean, how do you explain the matches?
How do you explain the smells?
How do you explain the weird noises?
It's not ghosts, honey.
It's just Michael's autism
manifesting itself in a new way.
Stop being a jerk and listen.
Stephanie said she heard something, too.
Peter, maybe there is something here.
And I don't know.
Maybe it's some kind of karma.
Karma? Karma for what?
Bad things that we've done?
Come on, honey. You don't
really believe that crap? Do ya?
Will you please, please open your eyes
for once?
Wait, Bronny. Bronny.
Bronny.
The Anasazi were an ancient culture
that lived in the Colorado Plateau.
No one knows why they
built their fortified cities.
But we do know that their entire
civilization ended suddenly
when they abandoned their homes.
Some have speculated that the nature
spirits worshipped by the Anasazi
became destructive demons when the community
ceased to maintain their sacred laws.
These beings appeared in the form
of a coyote, snake,
crow, buffalo and wolf.
They terrorized the population.
Often appearing to children
before taking them away forever.
Knock, knock.
Oh, no! Don't do it to me. No, no more.
These are ready for you to review.
I will have the rest later tonight.
Is it always like this?
Yes. Actually, this is the average
level of panic and confusion
that makes this place so great.
Um...
Maybe, when this project is done,
you and I could get some coffee
and talk about what the rest
of the year is going to look like.
Maybe I can take some work off your plate?
Maybe we can even get a drink or...
Yeah, I appreciate that, Sammy.
But I think maybe it would be better
if we just catch up
at the regular staff meetings.
Uh, that way nobody is gonna
miss any of our brilliant ideas.
Yeah. Yeah. Yes. Yeah. Okay.
They terrorized the population.
Often appearing to children
before taking them away forever.
This event was known...
- What do you think you're doing?
- Oh, shit.
Jesus Christ. What is up with you?
You're, like, a little edgy these days.
Really? I'm fine.
To be honest with you, chief, uh,
judging from your work, you're not.
Your whole team is down 10%.
So, my question is, what's the deal?
Simon, you gotta trust me, okay?
Now that you know how tricky this one is
and we will catch up
in the homestretch like always.
I promise you, no problem.
Mmm. Well, listen...
That is why you are the man around here.
Give me something. You got stellar capacity.
You've always had stellar capacity.
- I'm gonna see you for dinner, right?
- Yup.
All right, baby.
Hey, can you stay here a sec, hon?
Looks like a hell of a party.
Okay, you know to call me if there's
any problems with Michael.
Yeah, I know.
You can just call me, anyway. You know that.
Yeah, I know that.
I'm serious. No. You don't need it.
I like it. Thanks.
- You're beautiful because you...
- We gotta go, we gotta go.
Sweetie, can I just stay and you go?
Just call them and tell them I'm sick.
We cannot reschedule them.
You know what he's like. Let's just go.
We'll get it over with
and come right back. Okay?
Bye.
Are you sure you're gonna be okay?
Yes. I'm sure. I am sure.
- Where's my dress?
- What's wrong with that?
Simon will love it.
You sure we can't split it?
Hey, put your money away.
- You'll pay for it later.
- It's on us.
I did reach. You saw me reach, right?
Next time you bet your ass it's on you.
Bronny, I need to tell you about this
fascinating lecture I went to the other day...
Saw this guy on the Internet.
This is what he does.
- This guy on the Internet...
- Honey, can I talk?
He charges women whose husbands have
too much money to stare at them.
- That's what they do.
- No. Seriously?
Yeah, right? I told you
they stare at women. They go...
- "Okay, here's $1,000."
- Yeah, that's all he does.
So, who spoke at this event?
Oh, this amazing woman.
She's a psychic and a spiritual healer.
Her lecture was on ancient Hopi prophecy.
Do you know anything about...
That's funny you mention prophecy.
I just had a prophecy.
Oh, hold on a second.
In this prophecy,
Petey and I go to the bar
and we drink more alcohol.
And look, it's coming true!
Okay.
Side conference.
Tell me what's going on
with your little special project.
"Special project"?
Sammy.
I'm not... I'm afraid that project
is going to die in R&D.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no. I gave it to you.
I teed it up perfectly. Are you kidding me?
I put it right in your hands
and you kick it out of bounds like that.
I used to look up to you.
You used to be my hero.
- Why?
- People change.
You're breakin' my heart, Fredo.
Breakin' my heart.
It was about her cleansing ceremonies
that she would perform.
- We're back.
- And... Hi, guys.
And you know, our son was sick
a few years back and she...
Okay, sweetie.
What?
Well, it's interesting, actually, Simon.
Stephanie's been having issues
and Michael's been acting strangely,
even for Michael and...
I'm thinking we should probably
hit the road, right?
I think it's got something
to do with our house.
Let's talk about this later, shall we? Okay.
With the house?
You got goblins and fairies
up in the attic? What do you got?
These guys aren't interested
in our little soap opera.
Thank you so much for dinner.
Honey, I think we probably should hit it.
Okay. Let's go.
- Yeah, thanks. This was amazing.
- Yeah.
- What are you so angry about?
- What do you think?
I embarrassed you in front of Simon?
He's disgusting with Wendy.
He bulldozes through every conversation
as if it just doesn't matter
if he's not the one talking.
Honestly, he is unbearable.
- That may be true.
- It is true.
But he's my unbearable boss
who is now going to tell
the entire goddamn office
that my wife can't get
through a single dinner
without bringing up
our personal family problems.
Thanks for dragging me along.
Steph, where's Michael?
Mikey?
Mikey. Honey.
Sweetie, I told you not to play
in here until we clean it up.
Sweetie, don't put your hands in this, honey.
You're leaving marks all over the house.
Hey.
Open up, buddy. There you go.
I think he's gonna be okay for a night.
I'll just take him to the doctor
in the morning.
You okay, big Mike?
Whatcha thinking about, sweetie?
The blue star.
It's close now.
What are you talking about?
His shirt's all dirty.
Can you take him upstairs and change him?
Let's get changed.
I told you we shouldn't
have left them here alone.
Yeah, I know. I know. You were right.
You're absolutely right.
Peter.
One, two, three.
One, one, one, one.
Two, two...
One, two, three, four...
One, two, three, four.
One, two, three...
One, two, three.
Mikey.
One, one...
Who are you talking to, honey?
The Sky People.
They want us to come and live with them now.
Our time here is over.
The Sky People...
Where are they?
They're right behind you.
No!
- Stephanie!
Oh, my God. Stay with her!
Stephie! Oh, my God!
Are you okay?
Jeff! Your dog just attacked my daughter!
Unbelievable.
They said they have to wait
for somebody to become available
before they could even admit her,
maybe 20 minutes.
All the doors were locked.
Front and back. I locked them.
Well, then, somebody must have the key.
That's the only explanation.
I'll get the locks changed tomorrow
and I'll look at the rest of the doors
and windows while we're at it.
I don't know...
We're gonna be all right.
Peter, Mikey was in her room.
Jeff, look...
Crow.
Wolf.
Snake.
Buffalo.
Coyote.
I know it's been rough between us,
but we do need to talk.
Things have gotten a little screwed up
around here for all of us.
"A little screwed up."
You didn't notice
when Stephanie's moods changed
and her weight dropped,
and your son's behavior
went spiraling out of control,
but now you want to talk.
Hmm.
So I don't notice things.
Okay.
And that's not what you think.
Really?
How can that possibly not be what I think?
Yeah, fuck you, Peter!
You don't understand anything.
My God.
What's happening to us?
Why did you do it, Peter?
Were you bored with me?
Did you just not want
your life with us anymore?
Jesus, you're bringing this up now?
The affair didn't mean anything.
And it's not who I am anymore.
Well, I'm still who I am.
And it meant something to me.
Well, like I said, I'm sorry.
Yeah.
Sometimes being sorry isn't enough.
- Petey!
- Shit.
What're you doing here?
I didn't see you in the office.
What are you, a ninja these days?
Just sneaking in to grab
some work to finish at home.
Listen, um...
I'm gonna need to...
I'm gonna need some time off.
'Cause things have just
gotten worse with the kids,
and I just... I just got to take care of it.
Yeah, okay. Okay.
Sure. Listen.
Uh...
You know the other night
I was giving Wendy a lot of crap
about all that airy-fairy
stuff that she's into,
but, um, the truth is,
years back, our little guy was,
like, three or four and he got sick.
He got, like, sick.
Like we thought we were
going to lose him, sick.
So we took him to all kinds of doctors
and specialists and nobody knew anything.
Nothing helped.
So, a friend of our friend...
He tells us about this healer.
That's what she does. She heals.
She's like wind spirits and water spirits...
Believe me, if I told you the crazy shit
she was telling us about, you'd laugh.
She tells us what to do, and we do it.
Everything she says, we do it to the letter.
We do what she says.
A week later, he's better.
There's like life in his eyes again,
and then four weeks later,
he's playing baseball.
So, is that a miracle?
I don't know what you call it.
Tell Bronny to call Wendy.
She'll tell her more about it.
But you've got to call this woman,
I'm telling ya.
Sometimes the answer you're looking for is
gonna come from someplace you're not looking.
Anyway, you get back, all right?
I need you, hombre.
Need you in there. Call her.
They terrorized the population.
Often appearing to children
before taking them away forever.
This event was known as the darkness,
and began with an infestation
of these shadow-like beings.
They would then torment
their victims until madness
or painful death followed.
As a desperate last resort,
the Anasazi priests trapped
the demons inside the ritual stones
they used to communicate with the beings.
They then hid them deep within the caves
that surrounded their homes.
If the stones were removed,
the demons would be freed.
Leading to the darkness descending once more.
Ancient writings revealed that
this curse could only be lifted
by returning the stones to
their original resting place.
And only by one among them who had no fear.
There have been many cases of people
who claimed to have located these stones
dying mysteriously.
Once happy friends
and families turned on each other,
and random accidents brought
death and disaster.
Here you go. Have a great night.
Okay. Thanks, you too.
Jenny?
Hey! Who's up there?
Jenny, is that you?
Oh, my God.
What the hell is that?
Stephanie, come on.
Okay, it's okay.
Sit right here.
No, no, no, no! Dad, don't leave me!
It's okay. I'm gonna get you.
It's okay. I'm gonna be right back.
Mikey! Mikey! Open the door!
Michael, come on. Open the door!
Come on, open the goddamn door!
Michael, open the door!
Peter!
Hi.
I'd like a room, please.
Sure.
Well, it's a weeknight so you're in luck.
But the only room available
is the presidential suite.
- We'll take it.
- Sure.
Any bags, sir?
What are you looking for?
They have one in every
hotel room I've ever stayed in.
A Bible?
Huh?
I'm so tired. I think I'm going to pass out.
They took Bibles out of most
hotel rooms a while ago.
Oh, yeah? Why?
I don't know.
Apparently some people
felt it was discriminatory
to have just one religion represented.
Jesus.
Not anymore.
You know, I was thinking
about us the other day.
I was thinking about how we first met.
I admired you so much.
And when I saw you, it was just...
It still is...
Just love.
We deserve a happy ending, Peter.
I forgive you.
Hey, you know we could beat this together.
Do you like it?
Hi, Bronn. Yeah, come in. Come in.
To be honest, I've never
experienced anything like this,
so I'm just not quite sure how to deal.
That's just it. I mean, few people do.
Some people don't even believe,
but I can tell you
everything changes pretty fast when
someone has a firsthand encounter.
I, uh, have Teresa's number.
Look, I know you're upset, but don't worry.
Just give her a call.
She's very good.
The world is filled with things
that we simply can't explain, Bronn.
It's just easier for most people
to focus on the things we can.
But it doesn't make them any less real.
Whose truck is that, Dad?
Someone to help, buddy.
Hi.
Honey.
So this is Teresa
- and this is her granddaughter, Gloria.
- Hi.
- Nice to meet you.
Steph, can you take Mikey,
and just keep an eye on him as we...
- Yeah. Okay.
- Just give us a minute. Thanks.
My grandmother's English is not
100% so I'll help out, okay?
Is there anything new or strange
someone has brought into the house?
Uh...
No, no, I don't... I don't think so.
Maybe you've been somewhere recently?
Somewhere you've never been before?
We went camping a few months ago.
Canyon De Chelly. Grand Canyon.
Hiking. That kind of thing.
It's a very important area.
It's the home of the Anasazi.
The people the Navajo Indians
call the ancient ones.
It's said they communed
with very powerful spirits.
Throwers and Forest Dwellers
and Shadow Creatures.
And they had rituals
to keep the ancient demons
trapped in another dimension.
A place called the third world.
Yeah, yeah. I read something about that.
That is why the Anasazi kept
their rituals hidden
so no one could open the doorways
and let these beings cross into our world.
So you're saying that's real?
Hmm.
There are five demons
that were mostly feared.
But their name cannot be spoken.
It's known that they manifest
physically as a crow,
a coyote, a snake,
a buffalo or a wolf.
That's not their true form.
If all five spirits appear,
it will be disastrous.
What do they want?
They bring out the darkness within people,
so their victims destroy themselves
or destroy each other.
What is she saying?
She says we must hurry.
They won't stop until
they get what they want.
We'll begin by performing
a clearing of the house.
Closing any portals
and banishing any dark spirits.
Dark forces exist everywhere.
Do you believe in any higher power?
Not really.
Now would be a good time to start.
Aren't you going to need that?
She's sensing older things at work here.
And the God you might be familiar
with cannot help you now.
Stay close.
Stay put.
Wait here. We'll deal with it.
Oh, my God. Are you okay?
What's going on?
Spirits will try to prevent us from clearing
the house and keeping them out.
No, Daddy!
Peter!
Are you okay?
They're getting stronger.
Mom, was that you?
I'm right here.
Something brushed...
They won't hurt us.
They're going to set us free.
Michael! No!
You okay?
Quickly, Grandmother.
No!
Oh, my God. Teresa, are you okay?
Is she okay?
- Where's Mikey? Mikey!
- What's happening?
Mikey.
Mikey! Mikey!
Mikey, open up!
Mikey!
Peter? Mikey?
Peter! Peter!
Peter!
Take me.
Mikey. Come here. Come here.
Come here. Come here, buddy.
Quick. Come on. Come on.
You get outta here. Don't look back.
Peter! Peter!
Dad!
I'm not afraid, Dad!
No!
- Dad!
- Peter!
Peter!
Look at me.
Are you okay?
It's all right. It's all right.
It's over.
We're okay.
Sweetie, are you okay? And you, are you okay?
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today