Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
Is it ready?
Hey, that's a great punch.
Fear no good. So emotion...
Breathing.
Breakdown, breakdown.
Okay.
I can make it work for a while...
...but you need...
Okay. Okay.
No, no, no. Shut that off.
Turn it off!
Watch out!
Okay.
Martina.
No, wait. Oh, that's not right.
You see that? You see that?
Our ticket out of here.
Damn it.
Here's something
a bit more interesting.
It's possible gamma sickness.
Milwaukee.
A man drank
one of those guarana sodas.
Guess it had a little more kick
than he was looking for.
Where was it bottled?
Porto Verde, Brazil.
Get our agency people looking
for a white man at that bottling plant.
Tell them no contact.
If he even sees them, he's gone.
I got you what I could.
Short notice, but they're all quality.
And I pulled you an ace.
Emil Blonsky.
Born in Russia, raised in England...
...and on loan to SOCOM
from the Royal Marines.
I know you're cashing some chips
for this, Joe.
Glad I could help.
Just make it good.
This is the target and the location.
Snatch and grab, live capture.
Have your dart clips and suppression
ordinance, live fire is for backup only.
We got local out there,
but we want it tight and quiet.
Is he a fighter?
Your target is a fugitive
from the U.S. Government...
...and stole military secrets.
He is also implicated
in the deaths...
...of two scientists, a military officer,
an Idaho state trooper...
...and possibly two Canadian hunters,
so don't wait to see if he's a fighter.
Trank him...
...and bring him back.
Oh, come on.
Gentlemen.
Here we go.
Get rid of the damn dog.
Take him.
Target's on the move.
Where is he?
- He's on the ground.
- Let's go.
Go.
Move, move.
Thank you.
Go, go, go!
Go, go!
Stay on him!
Do not lose him.
Get around behind him.
Target moving past
Mobile Unit 090.
Oh, no.
You gotta be kidding me.
Where is he?
Target acquired.
Let's go.
My computer.
Give me that. No.
Not so tough now, huh?
Try those fancy moves again.
Come on.
Stop. Please.
Me angry...
...very bad.
You very angry?
I very angry.
Oh, no.
You don't understand. Something
really bad is about to happen here.
Yeah. Very bad.
Anybody else seeing this?
We got a bogey. Please advise.
That is the target!
Use every trank you've got.
Do it now.
Go wide. Go wide.
Go wide. Move.
No.
Behind him. Get behind him.
Move! Move!
Get him!
Get him! Get him!
Leave me alone.
No! No!
I knew something was different
before I got the shot off.
Had it on him when he bolted.
Is that a girlfriend?
She helps him maybe?
She is no longer a factor.
We closed that door to him
a long time ago. He's alone.
He wants to be alone.
Let's see
if he's been talking to anybody.
Forgive me, sir.
Doesn't anybody want to talk about
what went down in there, because...?
He didn't lose us.
And he was not alone, sir.
We had him,
and then something hit us.
Something... Something big hit us.
It threw a forklift truck
like it was a softball.
It was the most powerful thing
I've ever seen.
Well, it's gone.
Well, if Banner knows what it is...
...l'm gonna track him down,
put my foot on his throat and...
That was Banner.
It...
...was Banner.
You have to explain
that statement, sir.
No, I don't.
You've done a good job.
Pack up
and get our men on the plane.
We're going home.
Can you help me?
I don't speak Portuguese.
What? Where...?
Where am I?
Guatemala.
I'm going to the next town.
Will you help me?
Get in.
Here, put this on.
Where are you going?
Home.
I've run into bad situations
on crap missions before.
I've seen good men go down...
...because someone didn't let us know
what we were walking into.
I've moved on
because that's what we do.
I mean, that's the job.
But this...
This is a whole new level of weird.
I don't feel inclined
to step away from it.
So if you're taking another
crack at him, I want in.
And with respect,
you should be looking for a team...
...that's prepped and ready to fight
because if that thing shows up again...
...you'll have a lot of professional
tough guys pissing in their pants...
...sir.
Oh, yeah.
Let me emphasise
what I'm about to share with you...
...is tremendously sensitive
both to me personally and the Army.
You're aware that we've got an infantry
weapons development programme...
...while in WWll,
they initiated a subprogramme...
...for biotech force enhancement.
A super soldier.
Yes.
An oversimplification, but yes.
And I dusted it off.
Got them doing serious work again.
Bold work.
Across the hall,
they're trying to arm you better.
We're trying to make you better.
Banner's work was very early phase.
It wasn't even weapons application.
He thought he was working
on radiation resistance.
I would never have told him
what the project really was.
But he was so sure
of what he was onto...
...that he tested it on himself.
And something went very wrong.
Or it went very right.
As far as I'm concerned, that man's
whole body is property of the U.S. Army.
You said he wasn't working
on weapons, right?
- No.
- But you were, weren't you?
You were trying other things.
One serum we developed...
...it was very promising.
- So why did he run?
He's a scientist.
He is not one of us.
Blonsky, how old are you?
Forty-five?
- Thirty-nine.
- It takes a toll, doesn't it?
Yes, it does.
So get out of the trenches.
You should be a colonel now
with your record.
No, I'm a fighter.
I'll be one for as long as I can.
If I could take what I know now,
put it in the body I had 10 years ago...
...that would be someone
I wouldn't wanna fight.
I could probably arrange
something like that.
Take care, kids.
Stan, I give you my word.
Whatever you've heard about me,
it's not true.
I know it. I always knew it.
And you know
how I felt about you two.
- Have you talked to her?
- No.
She doesn't know that I'm here.
She's with somebody?
He's a head shrink.
They say he's one of the best.
But a really nice guy.
Good, that's good.
Bruce.
- What can I do to help you?
- I could use a bed for a few nights.
You can have
the spare room upstairs.
That'd be so great.
There is... There's one other thing.
Excuse me. Pardon me.
Coming through.
Hey, pal, I got a delivery on 5.
I don't think
there's anybody up here.
Oh, man, I'm gonna catch hell
if I don't collect.
You gotta let me try.
I tell you what.
I got an extra medium.
Take it on the house.
- You are the man.
- God bless you, partner.
Oh, boy.
Okay.
We're pretty well closed here, folks,
I'm sorry.
Oh, come on, Stan, it's Friday night.
Oh, kids.
- I got nothing but marinara now.
- I gotta have a Mr. Pink, please.
She worked through dinner again,
of course.
Stan?
I go...
So, yes, I mean, where were you?
I can't...
I don't know where you were, Cecil.
Then he goes,
"Not where you've been at."
I felt... Oh, my God, I just felt so awful.
Bruce.
Betty?
What's going on?
Betty.
Just tell me if I saw
what I think I saw.
I don't know what to say.
Please, just tell me the truth.
Oh, God. Thank God.
I want you to come with me now.
Please, come with me.
Please.
It's our data.
That got in there
before they carted it all away.
I hoped somewhere that
it might tell us something someday.
- Does the general know you have this?
- No, I don't think so.
I haven't spoken to him
in a couple of years.
- You have to be sure.
- Bruce.
I don't understand why we can't just
go in there together and talk to him.
He told me what he wanted to do.
He wants it out of me.
He wants to dissect it
so that he can replicate it.
He wants to make it a weapon.
- Hi.
- I thought you might wanna...
- Thanks.
Listen, I should leave early.
As early as I can.
Really?
You can't stay at all?
I want to,
but it's not just safe for me to be here.
If I could borrow some cash...
- Of course.
- I need to take a bus.
Well, at least let me walk you
to the station.
Okay.
- You have everything you need?
- Yeah.
- Good night.
I hope you get some rest.
We're giving you
a very low dose only.
I need you sharp out there
and disciplined.
First sign of any side effect...
...we stop and you're off team
until you straighten out.
- Agreed?
- Agreed.
You'll get two separate infusions.
One into the deep muscle...
...one into the bone-marrow centres.
Bone ones are gonna hurt.
One, two, three, four,
five, six, seven, eight.
One, two, three, four...
Is everything okay?
I think so.
- Come here.
- What?
I just wanna do this.
- It's better like that.
- Yeah.
- It's too tight, huh?
- Yeah, a little.
Okay.
What?
They're here.
Betty, look at me, look at me.
You have to go far away from me.
Don't argue with me, just go, go.
We'd have had snipers on target
in three more minutes.
I wanna know who jumped the gun.
He's heading 270.
Move it.
Blonsky, not yet.
Sir.
Look alive,
this could get interesting.
Stop.
I got him.
I know you're in there.
General, please.
- Sir.
- Dad!
Dad, please don't do this.
You can't see this clearly.
- Now, get inside.
- There he is.
Target is in the overpass.
We have a visual.
Do not engage.
Repeat, do not engage.
He's lock ed in.
- Put two canisters in there with him.
- Fire.
Get her back here.
Now she'll see.
Alpha Team.
Let him have all of it.
Light him up.
Come on, light him up.
Where are the.50 cals?
Move your asses.
Fall back.
Oh, my God.
- Blonsky, now you're up.
- Yes, sir.
Cover me.
Remember me?
My God, he's doing it.
Move him toward the cannons.
Move.
- All good.
- Do it, now.
- Please, please, please, no, please.
- Get her back.
You're killing him! Stop!
Get off of me!
Where's the gunship?
- Is that it?
- Blonsky, pull back now.
Pull back.
Is that all you got?
- Fall back.
- Let's go, let's go.
- Find cover.
- Move back, get down.
- Move it.
Betty!
- Move it, move it, move it.
- Take cover.
Fire, goddamn it.
Bruce.
Stop firing!
No!
You did the right thing, calling me.
I need to know where they're going.
She's in danger
as long as she's with him.
From who? He protected her.
You almost killed her.
I give you my word, her safety
is my main concern at this point.
You know, it's a point
of professional pride with me...
...that I can always tell
when somebody's lying.
And you are.
I don't know where he's going.
- I know she'll help him if she can.
- Then she's aiding a fugitive.
And I can't help either one of them.
I used to wonder
why she never talked about you.
Now I know.
Where does she meet these guys?
Bruce?
It's okay, it's okay.
Come here. Come this way.
Watch your head.
We're okay.
It's okay.
It's just the rain.
Will he ever walk again?
Most of the bones in his body
look like crushed gravel right now.
I will say this for him.
He's got a heart like a machine.
Never seen anything like it
outside of a racehorse.
Here.
Bruce?
Oh, hi.
- Are you okay?
- Yeah. Yeah, actually I feel a lot better.
- Good.
- I just had to get my data back.
- You ate it?
- Well, you know...
...the circumstances called for
a little improvisation.
Okay, so they didn't have a great
selection but I got you a few options.
First things first.
Oh, you're kidding me.
- What?
- No.
- They were the stretchiest pair.
- I'll take my chances.
Rumours continue to swirl
about a violent clash...
... between forces of the U.S. Military
and an unknown adversary...
... on the campus of Culver University
earlier today.
Sophomores Jack McGee and Jim
Wilson witnessed some of the battle.
It was so big.
- It was lik e this huge, lik e, hulk.
- Yeah.
McGee, who happens to be
a reporter for the campus paper...
... captured this on his cell phone.
Further search for the mysterious hulk
was postponed...
... by powerful thunderstorms in
the Smoky Mountain National Forest.
Take short back there, okay?
I have done this before, you know.
I don't know how you've done this
on your own for all this time.
With clippers, usually.
Wait, wait, wait.
- What?
- We can't do this.
- It's okay, I want to.
- No.
No.
I can't.
I can't get too excited.
Not even a little excited?
It's okay.
Sir, it's Blonsky.
Has anyone found out
if he has next of kin or family?
You can ask him yourself.
Sir?
Good to see you
back on your feet, soldier.
Thank you, sir.
How do you feel?
Pissed off and ready for round three.
Basically, we can't use any of this,
because they can track all of it.
Well, my lip gloss,
can they track that?
- No, you can take your lip gloss.
- Thank you.
Well, I need my glasses.
Well, you can take your glasses
and your watch, okay?
We can use most of it, we just
can't use the credit cards, ID or phone.
- Don't even turn that on.
- Okay.
And we'll take the cash, obviously.
How are we gonna get
where we need to go...
...on $40 and no credit cards?
- Well, we could sell this.
- No.
No, that's the only thing you have
left from her. No.
Well, we'll have to try
and get it back.
Federals are already monitoring...
...phones, plastic,
and Dr. Ross' web account.
And local P.D.
Have been placed on alert.
They'll pop up somewhere, and
when they do it comes straight to us.
They're not gonna just pop up.
He made it 5 years and got across
borders without making any mistakes.
He's not gonna use a credit card.
If he was trying to escape,
he'd be long gone.
He's not trying to escape,
he's looking for help.
That's how we're gonna get him.
We know what they're after.
He's been talking to somebody. You'll
have copies of the correspondence.
Aliases Mr. Green and Mr. Blue...
... have been added to
the S.H.I.E.L.D. Operations database.
If he comes up for air,
we'll be waiting.
If he mak es a peep we'll hear him.
And when he slips up,
we'll be ready.
Smile.
What is it like?
When it happens,
what do you experience?
Do you remember those experiments
we volunteered for at Harvard?
Those induced hallucinations?
It's a lot like that.
It's a thousand times amplified.
It's like someone's poured
a litre of acid into my brain.
- Do you remember anything?
- Just fragments, images.
There's too much noise,
I can never derive anything out of it.
- But then it's still you inside it.
- No, it's not.
I don't know.
In the cave, I really felt like
it knew me.
Maybe your mind is in there.
It's just overcharged
and can't process what's happening.
I don't wanna control it.
I wanna get rid of it.
- You ready?
- Let's even the playing field a little.
Gentlemen?
Bruce, wake up.
There's something going on.
We gotta go, walk toward the back.
Just don't move too fast.
All right, come.
It is a long way uptown. I think
the subway is probably quickest.
Me in a metal tube,
deep underground...
...with hundreds of people
in the most aggressive city?
Right, let's get a cab.
Come on, now. Let's go.
You're too slow,
you drive like a woman.
- Very nice, you see her?
- Oh, my God.
She's very pretty.
Look out, you goat.
Breathe, breathe, breathe.
Are you out of your mind?
What is wrong with you?
What's the matter, baby?
You don't like a good ride?
Asshole!
I know a few techniques could help
you manage that anger very effectively.
You, zip it.
- We're walking.
- Okay.
Excuse me, Dr. Sterns.
- Yes?
- I'm sorry to bother you.
I'm Elizabeth Ross.
Dr. Ross.
I have someone
who'd like to meet you.
Okay.
It's Mr. Blue, isn't it?
Mr. Green?
I've gotta tell you, I've been wondering
if you were even real.
And if you were,
what would it look like?
A person with that much power
lurking in him.
Nothing could have
surprised me more...
...than this unassuming man
shaking my hand.
But look, we're not strolling in the park
for a picnic here.
Even if everything goes perfectly,
if we induce an episode...
...if we get the dosage exactly right,
is that gonna be a lasting cure?
Or just some antidote
to suppress that specific flare-up?
I don't know.
What I'm saying is...
...that if we overshoot this
by even the smallest integer...
...we're dealing with concentrations
with extraordinary levels of toxicity...
- You mean it could kill him?
- Kill him, yeah.
I should say so.
You should know
there's a flipside to this too.
If we miss on the low side,
if we induce me...
...and it fails, this will be
very dangerous for you.
Look, I've always been
more curious than cautious.
And that's served me pretty well.
So are we gonna do this?
How are you feeling, man?
Like a monster.
Okay, on the table.
These will protect you
from yourself...
...if you have a strong reaction.
You can tell me later
if you thought it was strong.
Oh, come on.
Stupid graduate students.
Okay. You. You. You.
This will be a somewhat
novel sensation.
We have begun.
The dialysis machine will mix
the antidote with your blood.
So the antidote will only take hold
once we've achieved the full reaction.
Just relax.
Okay, we are comprehensive.
Here we go.
All right, we set to pop?
I'd take your hands off him.
Oh, my God.
Wait, wait, there's more. Wait.
- No. Hang on.
- Wait.
Now do it.
Do it!
Bruce, Bruce, look at me.
Stay with me. The antidote. Now.
Sterns, do it now.
Bruce, look at me. Look in my eyes.
Please look in my eyes.
You've gotta be kidding.
- Bruce.
- Oh, my God.
Bruce? Bruce, can you hear me?
Bruce.
It's okay, you're okay.
You're okay.
You did it.
- He's fine, this is fantastic.
- It's over.
- Hi.
That was the most extraordinary thing
I have seen in my entire life.
Okay, you know what? Stop, please.
We need to talk about
what happened in there.
Absolutely, okay.
The gamma pulse
came from the amygdala.
I think Dr. Ross' primer lets the cells
absorb the energy temporarily...
...and then it abates.
That's why you didn't die
of radiation sickness years ago.
Now, maybe we've neutralised
those cells permanently...
...or maybe we just suppressed
that event.
I'm inclined to think the latter,
it's hard to know.
Because none of our test subjects
ever survived.
Wait. What did you just say?
- They weren't getting the primer.
- No, no, test subjects?
What test subjects?
Come with me.
- What's the activity level?
- Snipers are covering Alpha Sector.
We started on rats and mice,
but it just completely fried them...
... we had to go bigger.
We still don't know
which is more toxic.
- The gamma or your blood.
- What do you mean, my blood?
Bruce, this is all you.
You didn't send me
much to work with...
...so I had to concentrate it
and make more.
With a little more trial and error,
there's no end to what we can do.
This is potentially Olympian.
This gamma technology
has limitless applications.
We'll unlock hundreds of cures.
We will make humans
impervious to disease.
No, no, we've gotta destroy it.
- Wait, what?
- All of it, tonight.
We're gonna incinerate it.
Is this the whole supply?
We could get the Nobel for this.
You don't understand the power
of this thing.
It is too dangerous,
it cannot be controlled.
At your discretion, shooter.
Yeah, but this is Promethean fire.
No shot.
Blonsky is going in.
Blonsky, stand down.
My daughter's in there.
- We have the antidote now.
- They don't want the antidote.
They wanna make it a weapon.
If we let it go,
we will never get it back.
You have no idea
how powerful this thing is.
I hate the government
as much as anyone.
But you're being a little paranoid,
don't you think?
Bruce, Bruce.
Get out.
Where is it? Come on, where is it?
Show him to me.
Blonsky.
Miss, take this.
If you took it from me, I'm gonna put
you in a hole for the rest of your life.
Betty.
I will never forgive
what you have done to him.
- He's a fugitive.
- You made him a fugitive.
To cover your failures
and to protect your career.
Don't ever speak to me
as your daughter again.
It's only because you're my daughter
that you're not in handcuffs too.
Are you telling me
you can make more like him?
No, not yet,
I've sorted out a few pieces...
...but it's not like I can put together
the same Humpty Dumpty.
If that's what you're asking.
He was a freak accident.
The goal is to do it better.
So Banner is the only...
Now, she's an annoying bitch.
Why are you always hitting people?
Now, what possibly could I have done
to deserve such aggression?
It's not what you've done,
it's what you're gonna do.
I want what you got
out of Banner, I want that.
You look like you've got a little
something in you already, don't you?
I want more.
You've seen what he becomes, right?
I have.
And it's beautiful.
Godlike.
I want that.
Need that. Give me that.
I don't know what you've got
inside you already.
The mixture
could be an abomination.
I didn't say I was unwilling.
I just need informed consent.
And you've given it.
This is what I was trying to explain.
I don't know
what you've been ladling into yourself.
But clearly it worked.
Let's assume you don't understand
a word I'm saying...
...but if you'll just get back
on the table...
...I can fix this.
Shoot it!
No!
Delta 4 to leader.
They still got two of our guys.
Two of our guys...
...Blonsky and the major,
are still inside.
Come on, move, move, move.
It's over there!
- What is that thing?
- Shoot it!
Okay, all right. You, you drive.
Let's go. Move, move.
Delta 4 to leader.
Something big
just went off down here.
General, you should hear this.
The hulk is in the street.
I repeat, the hulk is in the street.
That's impossible.
You get ahold of yourself.
You get it together.
What is your position?
121 st Street,
heading north on Broadway.
Turn us around.
We're going back.
Why are we going back?
Damn it, give me eyes down there.
Yes, sir.
What the hell was that?
Go, go, go.
No.
One of yours?
Oh, my God.
What have you done?
Fire! Fire!
You think a rifle's gonna hurt that?
Come on.
Sweet.
Get out of there, soldier.
Stand back!
Give me a real fight.
No, no, no!
Sir?
Tell them to bring everything
they've got and head for Harlem.
It has to be me.
- You have to take me back there.
- What are you saying?
You think you can control...
No, no, not control it,
but, I don't know, maybe aim it.
And what if you can't?
We made this thing.
All of us.
Please.
- Land us near it.
- No, no.
No, keep us high.
Open the back door.
Bruce. Bruce, stop.
Stop. What are you doing?
Think about this.
You don't even know
if you'll change.
You don't have to do this, please.
This is insane.
Betty, I've gotta try.
I'm sorry.
Oh, shit.
Get her in here.
Come on, miss.
There. Betty.
Hulk.
Come on.
Is that all you've got?
Use that thing, soldier.
Give him some help.
Which one?
Help the green one, damn it.
Which one do you think?
Cut the other one in half.
Ross.
Keep it on him.
I gotta put it down.
Hang on.
Dad.
Are you hurt? Let me help you.
I'm all right. Just find a way out.
You don't deserve this power.
Now watch her die.
Look out!
General.
Any last words?
Hulk...
...smash!
Stop!
It's okay.
Betty.
Reload.
The smell of stale beer and defeat.
You know,
I hate to say I told you so.
But that super soldier programme
was put on ice for a reason.
I've always felt that hardware
was much more reliable.
Stark.
General.
You always wear such nice suits.
Touch.
I hear you have an unusual problem.
You should talk.
You should listen.
What if I told you
we're putting a team together?
Who's we?
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org