1
00:00:38,247 --> 00:00:39,956
NARRATOR: Five thousand years ago,

2
00:00:40,040 --> 00:00:43,209
a fierce warrior known as the Scorpion King

3
00:00:43,293 --> 00:00:45,378
led a great army on a campaign

4
00:00:45,462 --> 00:00:47,588
to conquer the known world.

5
00:00:56,056 --> 00:00:57,724
(ALL SHOUTING)

6
00:01:06,567 --> 00:01:09,110
(SPEAKING IN
ANCIENT EGYPTIAN LANGUAGE)

7
00:02:08,754 --> 00:02:13,466
NARRATOR: After a vicious campaign
which lasted seven long years,

8
00:02:13,550 --> 00:02:16,594
the Scorpion King and his army
were defeated

9
00:02:16,678 --> 00:02:20,348
and driven deep into the sacred desert
of Ahm Shere.

10
00:02:33,529 --> 00:02:35,363
(BIRD SCREECHING)

11
00:02:42,830 --> 00:02:47,083
One by one, they slowly perished
under the scorching sun

12
00:02:49,503 --> 00:02:53,172
until only the great warrior himself
was left alive.

13
00:03:00,305 --> 00:03:02,014
Near death,

14
00:03:02,099 --> 00:03:06,227
the Scorpion King made a pact
with the dark god Anubis

15
00:03:06,854 --> 00:03:08,980
that if Anubis would spare his life

16
00:03:09,064 --> 00:03:11,440
and let him conquer his enemies,

17
00:03:11,817 --> 00:03:13,943
he would give him his soul.

18
00:03:21,869 --> 00:03:25,788
Anubis accepted his offer
and spared his life.

19
00:03:45,809 --> 00:03:47,143
(YELLING)

20
00:03:53,317 --> 00:03:56,777
Anubis gave the Scorpion King
command of his army,

21
00:03:56,862 --> 00:03:57,862
(GROWLING)

22
00:03:58,572 --> 00:04:03,534
and like an evil flood,
they washed away all that lay before them.

23
00:04:04,912 --> 00:04:06,579
(PEOPLE SCREAMING)

24
00:04:14,338 --> 00:04:18,215
When his task was done,
Anubis forced the Scorpion King

25
00:04:18,300 --> 00:04:20,509
to serve him for all time.

26
00:04:20,719 --> 00:04:22,094
(GRUNTS)

27
00:04:27,351 --> 00:04:31,604
His army was returned to the sands
from whence they came,

28
00:04:31,688 --> 00:04:32,939
(GROWLING)

29
00:04:36,068 --> 00:04:39,195
where they wait, silently,

30
00:04:39,279 --> 00:04:41,447
to be awakened once again.

31
00:05:03,762 --> 00:05:05,388
(MICE SQUEAKING)

32
00:05:10,852 --> 00:05:12,645
(GUN COCKING)

33
00:06:05,824 --> 00:06:07,158
(SNARLING)

34
00:06:18,211 --> 00:06:19,378
Alex?

35
00:06:20,797 --> 00:06:23,466
What were you thinking,
a mummy had come back to life?

36
00:06:23,550 --> 00:06:25,342
I'll tell you a story sometime.

37
00:06:25,427 --> 00:06:26,385
What are you doing down here?

38
00:06:26,470 --> 00:06:27,887
I told you to wait for us up in the temple.

39
00:06:27,971 --> 00:06:28,971
-But, Dad, I saw...
-No "buts."

40
00:06:29,056 --> 00:06:30,097
It's dangerous down here, Alex.

41
00:06:30,182 --> 00:06:32,850
-But I saw your tattoo.
-You saw what?

42
00:06:32,934 --> 00:06:35,978
On a wall by the entrance.
There's a cartouche just like it.

43
00:06:36,063 --> 00:06:40,357
With the pyramid and the eye
and the two kings and everything.

44
00:06:40,734 --> 00:06:42,735
-Really?
-Yeah.

45
00:06:42,819 --> 00:06:45,738
Okay, well, I'll be up to take a look
at that in a minute.

46
00:06:45,822 --> 00:06:47,573
In the meantime,
I want you to wait for us up there.

47
00:06:47,657 --> 00:06:48,741
But... But...

48
00:06:48,825 --> 00:06:52,244
No, pick up your stuff,
and I'll see you up in the temple. Go.

49
00:06:53,789 --> 00:06:57,083
-Go on.
-And... And what shall I do?

50
00:06:57,167 --> 00:06:59,627
I don't know. Surprise me.

51
00:07:00,087 --> 00:07:02,421
-Build a better mousetrap.
-Okay.

52
00:07:02,506 --> 00:07:05,341
While your mother goes
and desecrates another tomb.

53
00:07:12,682 --> 00:07:14,767
(HISSING)

54
00:07:19,314 --> 00:07:20,689
Go away.

55
00:07:23,652 --> 00:07:26,570
-Those are poisonous, you know.
-Only if they bite you.

56
00:07:26,655 --> 00:07:29,240
-What was all that about?
-Oh, nothing.

57
00:07:29,324 --> 00:07:31,951
Alex wanted to show me something.

58
00:07:32,035 --> 00:07:33,994
I swear,

59
00:07:34,079 --> 00:07:36,580
the kid gets more
and more like you every day.

60
00:07:36,665 --> 00:07:41,043
What, you mean more attractive,
sweet and devilishly charming?

61
00:07:41,128 --> 00:07:43,379
No, he's driving me crazy.

62
00:07:43,839 --> 00:07:45,589
Now, where were we?

63
00:07:46,633 --> 00:07:48,342
Hammer and chisel.

64
00:07:53,306 --> 00:07:56,767
-All right, all right! Let's do it your way.
-Thank you.

65
00:08:00,021 --> 00:08:01,730
(THUDDING)

66
00:08:15,662 --> 00:08:21,041
Ever since I had that dream,
this place is all I can think about.

67
00:08:21,126 --> 00:08:25,421
Ever since you had that dream,
I haven't had a decent night of sleep.

68
00:08:25,922 --> 00:08:28,424
EVELYN: I feel like I've been here before.

69
00:08:28,758 --> 00:08:32,511
-I know I've been here before.
-Evy, nobody's been here before.

70
00:08:32,596 --> 00:08:35,848
Not in at least 3,000 years.
Except for these guys.

71
00:08:41,104 --> 00:08:43,647
Then how do I seem to know exactly
where I'm going?

72
00:08:58,413 --> 00:08:59,663
MAN: Let's go.

73
00:09:16,348 --> 00:09:18,140
(VOICES ECHOING)

74
00:09:33,823 --> 00:09:37,243
Knock, knock. Anybody home?

75
00:09:40,330 --> 00:09:43,499
You two check out that stuff,
see if it's there.

76
00:09:43,750 --> 00:09:46,001
I'll sort out the O'Connells.

77
00:11:19,179 --> 00:11:22,222
You know, if you move that fast enough,
you can almost write your name.

78
00:11:22,307 --> 00:11:24,099
I just had a vision.

79
00:11:24,601 --> 00:11:28,687
It was...
It was like my dream, but it was real.

80
00:11:28,772 --> 00:11:31,190
It was like l was actually here
in ancient times.

81
00:11:31,274 --> 00:11:35,778
Well, if you actually were here,
could you show me how to open this thing?

82
00:11:36,446 --> 00:11:37,780
Hold this.

83
00:11:53,046 --> 00:11:56,924
-All right, now you're starting to scare me.
-Now I'm starting to scare myself.

84
00:11:57,801 --> 00:12:00,719
What is this?
Look at the state of this rubbish.

85
00:12:00,804 --> 00:12:04,598
Those Egyptians never had a clue.
It's all chintz and stuff.

86
00:12:05,141 --> 00:12:06,517
Look at that.

87
00:12:06,601 --> 00:12:10,729
Cheap pottery, this. Ancient rubbish.

88
00:12:10,939 --> 00:12:12,147
(Screaming)

89
00:12:13,483 --> 00:12:19,196
-Jacques, something's hit me head!
-Shut up, Spivey. This place is cursed.

90
00:12:22,158 --> 00:12:24,410
We do not want to wake the gods.

91
00:12:46,516 --> 00:12:49,143
EVELYN: That's the emblem
of the Scorpion King.

92
00:12:49,227 --> 00:12:51,395
He's supposed to be pure myth.

93
00:12:51,479 --> 00:12:54,148
No... No trace of him
has ever been found before.

94
00:12:54,232 --> 00:12:57,192
No artifacts, no archival evidence.

95
00:12:57,485 --> 00:12:59,194
Maybe they didn't want anybody to find him.

96
00:12:59,279 --> 00:13:00,279
Let's open this.

97
00:13:00,363 --> 00:13:03,115
Evy, l don't have
a real good feeling about this.

98
00:13:03,199 --> 00:13:06,535
It's only a chest.
No harm ever came from opening a chest.

99
00:13:06,619 --> 00:13:09,037
Right, and no harm ever came
from reading a book.

100
00:13:09,122 --> 00:13:11,707
-Remember how that went?
-We can't stop now.

101
00:13:11,791 --> 00:13:14,418
Just remember,
l was the voice of reason here.

102
00:13:14,502 --> 00:13:15,586
For once.

103
00:13:15,670 --> 00:13:19,965
Rubbish. Rubbish. Dreck. Chintz.

104
00:13:20,383 --> 00:13:22,509
Only half of this...

105
00:13:25,346 --> 00:13:26,930
God, that hurt!

106
00:13:46,409 --> 00:13:49,828
Hon? Let's do it your way.

107
00:14:07,889 --> 00:14:10,057
The bracelet of Anubis.

108
00:14:18,316 --> 00:14:20,275
I'll take care of this.

109
00:14:23,363 --> 00:14:24,988
(Rumbling)

110
00:14:26,741 --> 00:14:28,325
Oh, my God.

111
00:14:29,452 --> 00:14:31,453
It's a bit late for that!

112
00:14:31,704 --> 00:14:34,665
-Put it in your rucksack.
-l got a better idea. Let's leave it here.

113
00:14:34,749 --> 00:14:37,209
-l think it's a bit late for that!
-What's it say?

114
00:14:37,293 --> 00:14:42,631
"He who disturbs this bracelet
shall drink from the Nile."

115
00:14:42,715 --> 00:14:44,299
That doesn't sound too bad.

116
00:14:45,802 --> 00:14:47,386
(Screaming)

117
00:15:02,652 --> 00:15:06,947
Jacques's gonna make a nice fillet
out of you, my son.

118
00:15:08,408 --> 00:15:11,326
-Oh, please. Please.
-Spivey! Jacques!

119
00:15:11,661 --> 00:15:14,830
-Let's get the hell out of here!
-Come on!

120
00:15:20,920 --> 00:15:22,671
Come on!

121
00:15:32,515 --> 00:15:34,016
(GRUNTS)

122
00:15:41,691 --> 00:15:43,442
(BOTH Screaming)

123
00:15:44,986 --> 00:15:46,528
(Grunting)

124
00:16:07,258 --> 00:16:08,383
Whoa.

125
00:16:16,309 --> 00:16:17,768
This is bad, Evy!

126
00:16:17,852 --> 00:16:20,312
-We've had bad before!
-This is worse!

127
00:16:57,475 --> 00:16:59,101
(BOTH Coughing)

128
00:16:59,435 --> 00:17:03,522
Mom, Dad, l can explain everything.

129
00:17:31,217 --> 00:17:34,136
The Book of the Dead gives life.

130
00:17:34,721 --> 00:17:37,097
And The Book of the Living

131
00:17:39,267 --> 00:17:41,393
takes life away.

132
00:17:41,769 --> 00:17:44,062
l thought that was my job.

133
00:17:46,649 --> 00:17:48,400
We're getting close.

134
00:18:18,181 --> 00:18:19,931
Did you acquire it?

135
00:18:20,016 --> 00:18:22,309
(Rumbling)

136
00:19:00,223 --> 00:19:02,307
(Skittering)

137
00:19:02,391 --> 00:19:04,810
(PEOPLE Screaming)

138
00:19:26,165 --> 00:19:27,666
(Screaming)

139
00:19:31,212 --> 00:19:33,463
We're getting very close.

140
00:19:38,761 --> 00:19:40,220
(Skittering)

141
00:19:48,229 --> 00:19:49,855
We've found him.

142
00:19:52,149 --> 00:19:54,609
We've found him! We've found him!

143
00:20:11,836 --> 00:20:14,212
Step aside here. Out of the way!

144
00:20:19,468 --> 00:20:23,305
Imhotep. It's him. It's Imhotep.

145
00:20:27,935 --> 00:20:29,102
Now we must raise those that serve him.

146
00:20:29,186 --> 00:20:30,228
(MAN 1 Speaking Arabic)

147
00:20:30,313 --> 00:20:31,438
Get out of my way.

148
00:20:31,522 --> 00:20:35,233
Get out of my way,
or I'm gonna shoot you in the face.

149
00:20:35,318 --> 00:20:37,861
He means it. He shot someone before.

150
00:20:37,945 --> 00:20:42,616
-Give it to me.
-The opportunity passed us by.

151
00:20:43,534 --> 00:20:45,327
We need that bracelet.

152
00:20:45,411 --> 00:20:47,996
And we need it before it opens.

153
00:20:52,001 --> 00:20:53,501
Enough.

154
00:20:55,755 --> 00:21:00,759
My dear Hafez,
l told you l should have handled it.

155
00:21:00,843 --> 00:21:05,138
l did not want your past history
to cloud the issue.

156
00:21:05,222 --> 00:21:07,849
We know where it is. We'll take care of it.

157
00:21:07,934 --> 00:21:10,101
No, we'll take care of it.

158
00:21:10,645 --> 00:21:13,438
l have a different chore for you now.

159
00:21:13,522 --> 00:21:17,442
-Where is the bracelet?
-It's on its way to merry old London.

160
00:21:18,986 --> 00:21:21,404
Then London is where we must go.

161
00:21:39,090 --> 00:21:44,094
l think the bracelet is some sort of guide
to the lost oasis of Ahm Shere.

162
00:21:44,178 --> 00:21:48,640
Evy, l know what you're thinking,
and the answer is no.

163
00:21:48,724 --> 00:21:50,809
We just got home.

164
00:21:50,893 --> 00:21:53,937
That's the beauty of it.
We're already packed.

165
00:21:54,271 --> 00:21:57,649
Why don't you just give me
one good reason?

166
00:21:57,733 --> 00:22:02,404
It's just an oasis, darling.

167
00:22:03,906 --> 00:22:07,742
A beautiful, exciting,

168
00:22:08,661 --> 00:22:10,578
romantic

169
00:22:12,707 --> 00:22:14,624

oasis.

170
00:22:15,042 --> 00:22:19,087
The kind with the white, sandy beach
and the palm trees

171
00:22:19,171 --> 00:22:22,048
and the cool, clear, blue water and...

172
00:22:22,591 --> 00:22:26,594
We could have some of those big drinks
with the little umbrellas.

173
00:22:26,846 --> 00:22:28,888
-Sounds good.
-Sounds too good.

174
00:22:28,973 --> 00:22:30,223
What's the catch?

175
00:22:30,307 --> 00:22:32,642
Supposedly it's the resting place
of Anubis’s army.

176
00:22:32,727 --> 00:22:35,353
See? l knew there's a catch.
There's always a catch.

177
00:22:35,438 --> 00:22:39,858
And let me guess. It was commanded
by that Scorpion King guy?

178
00:22:39,942 --> 00:22:42,193
Yes, but he only awakens
once every 5,000 years.

179
00:22:42,278 --> 00:22:44,029
Right. And if someone doesn't kill him,

180
00:22:44,113 --> 00:22:46,573
-he's gonna wipe out the world.
-How did you know?

181
00:22:46,657 --> 00:22:48,700
l didn't. But that's always the story.

182
00:22:48,784 --> 00:22:50,618
The last known expedition to actually

183
00:22:50,703 --> 00:22:53,830
reach Ahm Shere was sent by Ramses IV

184
00:22:53,914 --> 00:22:55,707
over 3,000 years ago.

185
00:22:55,791 --> 00:22:58,501
-He sent over a thousand men.
-And none of them was ever seen again.

186
00:22:58,586 --> 00:22:59,669
-How did you know?
-l didn't.

187
00:22:59,754 --> 00:23:01,004
But that's always the story.

188
00:23:01,088 --> 00:23:03,089
-Did l mention there was a pyramid of gold?
-Twice.

189
00:23:03,174 --> 00:23:05,550
Alexander the Great
sent troops in search of it.

190
00:23:05,634 --> 00:23:07,302
-Hooray for him.
-So did Caesar.

191
00:23:07,386 --> 00:23:09,471
-Yeah, look what happened to his career.
-And Napoleon.

192
00:23:09,555 --> 00:23:12,849
But we're smarter than him. And taller, too.

193
00:23:12,933 --> 00:23:16,686
-Exactly. That's why we're gonna find it.
-Because we're taller?

194
00:23:17,855 --> 00:23:20,815
-That's why I love you.
-Nice try.

195
00:23:41,796 --> 00:23:43,088
ALEX: Mom!

196
00:23:43,589 --> 00:23:45,298
What do l do with this chest?

197
00:23:45,382 --> 00:23:47,592
This sucker weighs a goddang ton.

198
00:23:47,676 --> 00:23:49,761
Alex, watch your language!

199
00:23:49,845 --> 00:23:51,679
Rather weighty, this.

200
00:23:55,768 --> 00:23:56,935
(CLICKING)

201
00:23:57,019 --> 00:23:58,353
Huh?

202
00:24:01,315 --> 00:24:05,193
Evy, that first weird dream of yours
was exactly six weeks ago, right?

203
00:24:05,277 --> 00:24:08,446
l think so, yes.
But what's that got to do with anything?

204
00:24:08,989 --> 00:24:12,492
It just happens to coincide
with Egyptian New Year.

205
00:24:13,160 --> 00:24:16,287
Oh. That's right. What a coincidence.

206
00:24:17,790 --> 00:24:22,210
Maybe. All I'm saying is, let's be cautious.

207
00:24:27,007 --> 00:24:28,466
Oh!

208
00:24:31,011 --> 00:24:34,681
lf anything happened to you,
l would never forgive myself.

209
00:24:40,896 --> 00:24:42,355
(Snarling)

210
00:24:54,785 --> 00:24:57,495
You and Alex are the only thing
that matter to me.

211
00:24:57,580 --> 00:24:59,038
Well,

212
00:25:00,249 --> 00:25:03,751
the Bembridge scholars
have been begging me

213
00:25:03,836 --> 00:25:05,879
to run the British Museum.

214
00:25:14,555 --> 00:25:16,556
Wh... Whoa.

215
00:25:24,023 --> 00:25:26,107
Cripes, how do you get this thing off?

216
00:25:26,192 --> 00:25:28,234
Have l kissed you today?

217
00:25:36,785 --> 00:25:39,704
l hate it when you do that.

218
00:25:39,788 --> 00:25:42,749
-Why?
-Makes me feel like agreeing to anything.

219
00:25:42,833 --> 00:25:44,292
Anything?

220
00:25:50,466 --> 00:25:52,675
Those knickers are not mine.

221
00:25:53,969 --> 00:25:55,637
Jonathan.

222
00:25:55,721 --> 00:25:58,306
Hey, Alex, behave yourself for five minutes.

223
00:25:58,891 --> 00:26:00,308
You betcha.

224
00:26:09,318 --> 00:26:12,070
-Happy to be home?
-Couldn't be happier.

225
00:26:12,905 --> 00:26:15,240
It's the year of the scorpion.

226
00:26:15,324 --> 00:26:17,492
-Neat!
-Thought you might like that.

227
00:26:18,077 --> 00:26:21,663
So then l killed the mummy
and all his minions and stole his scepter.

228
00:26:21,747 --> 00:26:25,625
-Oh, you're so brave.
-And rich. Did l mention rich?

229
00:26:25,709 --> 00:26:27,835
What do you think I'm doing here?

230
00:26:30,381 --> 00:26:32,173
Sorry. We must be in the wrong house.

231
00:26:32,258 --> 00:26:34,926
-You said this was your house.
-No, l didn't.

232
00:26:35,010 --> 00:26:36,678
Call me!

233
00:26:37,680 --> 00:26:40,181
-You're not Sheila's husband, are you?
-No.

234
00:26:40,557 --> 00:26:43,726
Look, if you work for Johnny,
l was gonna pay him back on Tuesday.

235
00:26:43,811 --> 00:26:45,853
l don't know any Johnny.

236
00:26:45,938 --> 00:26:48,273
We are looking for the bracelet of Anubis.

237
00:26:48,357 --> 00:26:51,693
Oh, good for you. Good thing to have,
the old bracelet of Anubis.

238
00:26:51,777 --> 00:26:53,319
Where is it?

239
00:26:53,404 --> 00:26:55,947
You're looking here for the bracelet. l see.

240
00:26:56,031 --> 00:26:58,032
l have no idea what you're talking about.

241
00:26:58,117 --> 00:27:01,286
Mr. O'Connell, you try my patience.

242
00:27:01,370 --> 00:27:04,580
Mr. O'Connell? No, hold on a minute.
You've got the wrong...

243
00:27:04,665 --> 00:27:06,833
That bracelet. Now l remember.

244
00:27:06,917 --> 00:27:10,586
-l lost it in a card game.
-For your sake, l hope not.

245
00:27:14,550 --> 00:27:16,050
It can't be.

246
00:27:17,094 --> 00:27:18,761
ANCK-SU-NAMUN: Hello.

247
00:27:21,890 --> 00:27:23,308
Hello.

248
00:27:24,059 --> 00:27:27,770
-Where's your wife?
-My wife? Oh, you mean Evy.

249
00:27:27,855 --> 00:27:31,357
l think she went off to Baden-Baden
or Tibet or something.

250
00:27:31,442 --> 00:27:32,900
The girl's a free spirit.

251
00:27:32,985 --> 00:27:35,320
Did l mention l was single now?

252
00:27:41,076 --> 00:27:43,995
Egyptian asps are quite poisonous.

253
00:27:44,997 --> 00:27:46,497
It's downstairs. There's a safe.

254
00:27:46,582 --> 00:27:51,127
The combination is 320-58...

255
00:27:51,211 --> 00:27:53,338
393-something.

256
00:27:53,422 --> 00:27:56,632
It's in a safe downstairs.
l told you. l told you!

257
00:27:56,717 --> 00:27:57,884
And your point is?

258
00:27:57,968 --> 00:28:00,219
My point is,
l told you so you wouldn't kill me.

259
00:28:00,304 --> 00:28:02,805
When did we make that arrangement?

260
00:28:10,230 --> 00:28:11,481
Hello.

261
00:28:13,275 --> 00:28:15,568
Jonathan, l thought l said
no more wild parties.

262
00:28:15,652 --> 00:28:17,945
Well, when you're popular...

263
00:28:18,030 --> 00:28:21,407
Alex, I'm serious.
lf you've lost that key, you're grounded.

264
00:28:21,492 --> 00:28:24,452
l haven't lost it. l just can't find it.
There's a difference.

265
00:28:24,536 --> 00:28:27,330
Well, you'd better start finding it then.

266
00:28:27,414 --> 00:28:29,749
l will, Mom. There's nothing to worry about.

267
00:28:29,833 --> 00:28:31,334
Good evening.

268
00:28:34,296 --> 00:28:37,840
Who are you? What are you doing here?

269
00:28:37,925 --> 00:28:40,593
I'm looking for the chest, of course.

270
00:28:42,554 --> 00:28:44,263
Give it to me now.

271
00:28:47,101 --> 00:28:50,019
Get out of my house.

272
00:28:50,104 --> 00:28:52,313
Whoa, Mom. Maybe not the best idea.

273
00:28:52,398 --> 00:28:54,148
Alex, get back there.

274
00:28:57,444 --> 00:28:59,946
Definitely not the best idea.

275
00:29:00,030 --> 00:29:01,781
l think it's time to yell for Dad now.

276
00:29:01,865 --> 00:29:05,493
-Now l will kill you and take it anyway.
-ARDETH: l think not.

277
00:29:07,663 --> 00:29:10,623
Ardeth, what are you doing here?

278
00:29:10,707 --> 00:29:12,750
Perhaps explanations are best kept for later.

279
00:29:12,835 --> 00:29:14,419
Ardeth Bay.

280
00:29:14,920 --> 00:29:16,170
Lock-Nah.

281
00:29:17,423 --> 00:29:18,548
Knowing my brother-in-law,

282
00:29:18,632 --> 00:29:20,633
he probably deserves
whatever you're about to do to him,

283
00:29:20,717 --> 00:29:24,804
but this is my house, l have certain rules
about snakes and dismemberment.

284
00:29:28,517 --> 00:29:29,809
Shoot him!

285
00:29:34,523 --> 00:29:35,773
(Groaning)

286
00:29:36,358 --> 00:29:38,568
(Speaking Arabic)

287
00:29:58,422 --> 00:30:01,757
Whoa, Mom! When did you learn to do that?

288
00:30:01,842 --> 00:30:03,384
l have no idea.

289
00:30:08,724 --> 00:30:10,141
That l learned from your father.

290
00:30:12,519 --> 00:30:14,937
-I'll take that.
-Whoa!

291
00:30:23,947 --> 00:30:26,866
Not bad for a Medjai.

292
00:30:33,749 --> 00:30:34,957
Let go!

293
00:30:44,426 --> 00:30:47,428
-What's in the chest?
-The bracelet of Anubis!

294
00:31:01,860 --> 00:31:05,655
They must not get the bracelet!
Get it and get out of here!

295
00:31:12,162 --> 00:31:13,704
Mom, look out!

296
00:31:14,456 --> 00:31:15,873
Evelyn!

297
00:31:20,420 --> 00:31:21,504
Mom!

298
00:31:27,928 --> 00:31:31,597
Jonathan!

299
00:31:34,977 --> 00:31:36,852
What'd you do this time?

300
00:31:36,937 --> 00:31:39,105
l haven't done anything to anybody!

301
00:31:39,189 --> 00:31:40,856
(GUN FIRING)

302
00:31:41,400 --> 00:31:42,650
-Lately.
-Come on!

303
00:32:04,298 --> 00:32:05,423
Rick!

304
00:32:06,466 --> 00:32:08,426
-Evelyn!
-Look out, Rick!

305
00:32:18,812 --> 00:32:20,730
Dad! Dad!

306
00:32:21,648 --> 00:32:23,232
-Are you all right?
-Yeah.

307
00:32:23,317 --> 00:32:24,775
Yeah? Okay.

308
00:32:26,486 --> 00:32:27,862
O'Connell.

309
00:32:29,197 --> 00:32:32,325
What are you doing here?
No, scratch that. l don't care.

310
00:32:32,409 --> 00:32:34,285
Who are those guys?
Where are they taking my wife?

311
00:32:34,369 --> 00:32:37,079
My friend, I'm not sure,

312
00:32:37,164 --> 00:32:41,042
but wherever this man is,
your wife will surely be.

313
00:32:42,878 --> 00:32:44,629
Hey, l know him.

314
00:32:44,713 --> 00:32:47,590
He's the curator.
He works at the British Museum.

315
00:32:47,674 --> 00:32:49,467
-Are you sure?
-Believe him.

316
00:32:49,551 --> 00:32:52,261
He spends more time there than at home.

317
00:32:54,514 --> 00:32:57,058
You're here, the bad guys are here,
Evy's been kidnapped.

318
00:32:57,142 --> 00:32:59,101
-Let me guess.
-Yes, they once again removed

319
00:32:59,186 --> 00:33:00,311
the creature from his grave.

320
00:33:00,395 --> 00:33:01,437
l don't mean to point fingers,

321
00:33:01,521 --> 00:33:03,773
but isn't it your job to make sure
that doesn't happen?

322
00:33:03,857 --> 00:33:05,483
That woman who was with him,
she knows things

323
00:33:05,567 --> 00:33:07,443
that no living person could possibly know.

324
00:33:07,527 --> 00:33:09,695
She knew exactly
where the creature was buried.

325
00:33:09,780 --> 00:33:12,948
We were hoping she would lead us
to the bracelet. She obviously did.

326
00:33:13,033 --> 00:33:14,492
And now they have it.

327
00:33:14,576 --> 00:33:17,036
l wouldn't get too nervous just yet.

328
00:33:19,247 --> 00:33:20,331
Is that gold?

329
00:33:20,415 --> 00:33:22,500
When l stuck it on,
l saw the pyramids at Giza.

330
00:33:22,584 --> 00:33:25,419
Then, whoosh!
Straight across the desert to Karnak.

331
00:33:25,504 --> 00:33:27,338
By putting this on,
you have started a chain reaction

332
00:33:27,422 --> 00:33:29,715
that could bring the next apocalypse.

333
00:33:30,092 --> 00:33:34,178
You, lighten up.
You, big trouble. You, get in the car.

334
00:33:40,268 --> 00:33:42,019
l am sorry if l alarmed your son,

335
00:33:42,104 --> 00:33:45,106
but you must understand,
now that the bracelet is on his wrist,

336
00:33:45,190 --> 00:33:47,650
we have only seven days before
the Scorpion King awakens.

337
00:33:47,734 --> 00:33:49,276
We? What we?

338
00:33:49,361 --> 00:33:51,821
lf he is not killed,
he will raise the Army of Anubis.

339
00:33:51,905 --> 00:33:54,782
-l take it that's not a good thing.
-Oh, he'll wipe out the world.

340
00:33:54,866 --> 00:33:56,909
The old "wipe out the world" ploy.

341
00:34:01,373 --> 00:34:03,457
Whomever can kill the Scorpion King

342
00:34:03,542 --> 00:34:05,418
can send his army back to the Underworld

343
00:34:05,502 --> 00:34:08,212
or use it to destroy mankind
and rule the Earth.

344
00:34:08,296 --> 00:34:09,797
That's why they dug up Imhotep.

345
00:34:09,881 --> 00:34:12,216
He's the only guy tough enough
to take out the Scorpion King.

346
00:34:12,300 --> 00:34:13,509
That is their plan.

347
00:34:26,148 --> 00:34:29,692
Alex, I've got a big job for you.
Stay here and protect the car.

348
00:34:29,776 --> 00:34:32,361
-l can do that.
-Protect the car?

349
00:34:32,446 --> 00:34:35,239
Just because I'm a kid
doesn't mean I'm stupid.

350
00:34:35,323 --> 00:34:37,783
-l know.
-Dad!

351
00:34:38,577 --> 00:34:41,912
lf you see anyone come out screaming,
it's just me.

352
00:34:41,997 --> 00:34:45,708
-Maybe you should stay here and watch him.
-Yes, now you're talking.

353
00:34:49,921 --> 00:34:53,174
-You want the shotgun?
-No, l prefer the Thompson.

354
00:34:59,848 --> 00:35:01,474
lf l were to say to you,

355
00:35:01,558 --> 00:35:05,686
I'm a stranger traveling from the east,
seeking that which is lost...

356
00:35:05,771 --> 00:35:08,522
Then l would reply that l am a stranger
traveling from the west.

357
00:35:08,607 --> 00:35:12,026
-It is l whom you seek. How...
-Then it is true.

358
00:35:12,110 --> 00:35:14,528
-You have the sacred mark.
-What, that?

359
00:35:14,613 --> 00:35:17,072
No, that got slapped on me
in an orphanage in Cairo.

360
00:35:17,157 --> 00:35:22,536
That mark means you're a protector of man,
a warrior for God, a Medjai.

361
00:35:22,621 --> 00:35:24,705
Sorry. You've got the wrong guy.

362
00:35:27,918 --> 00:35:30,836
(PEOPLE Chanting)

363
00:35:59,866 --> 00:36:02,993
(HAFEZ Chanting
IN Ancient Egyptian LANGUAGE)

364
00:36:09,793 --> 00:36:11,210
Mr. Hafez.

365
00:36:16,299 --> 00:36:17,925
They found him.

366
00:36:39,281 --> 00:36:41,866
(THUNDER Rumbling)

367
00:36:50,125 --> 00:36:53,544
Rise up!

368
00:37:00,802 --> 00:37:03,178
(Roaring)

369
00:37:18,069 --> 00:37:21,572
(HAFEZ Chanting
IN Ancient Egyptian LANGUAGE)

370
00:37:41,676 --> 00:37:43,010
(Growling)

371
00:37:53,313 --> 00:37:54,563
Imhotep.

372
00:37:54,648 --> 00:37:55,648
(Speaking Ancient Egyptian)

373
00:37:55,732 --> 00:37:57,191
What year is it?

374
00:37:57,359 --> 00:38:02,696
My Lord, it is the Year of the Scorpion.

375
00:38:02,906 --> 00:38:03,948
Truly?!

376
00:38:04,032 --> 00:38:05,032
Yes!

377
00:38:05,450 --> 00:38:07,117
(Laughing)

378
00:38:07,202 --> 00:38:08,744
(DOOR Opening)

379
00:38:30,725 --> 00:38:32,643
Do not be frightened.

380
00:38:32,727 --> 00:38:33,978
l am not afraid.

381
00:38:34,062 --> 00:38:35,145
(Speaking Ancient Egyptian)

382
00:38:35,230 --> 00:38:38,607
l am Anck-su-namun reincarnated.

383
00:38:39,651 --> 00:38:42,903
Only in body.

384
00:38:43,071 --> 00:38:44,697
But soon...

385
00:38:44,906 --> 00:38:50,911
l shall bring your soul back
from the Underworld...

386
00:38:51,079 --> 00:38:55,582
...and our love shall once again be whole.

387
00:39:03,842 --> 00:39:09,555
You know, a couple of years ago
this would've seemed really strange to me.

388
00:39:15,395 --> 00:39:17,855
Lord Imhotep will be much pleased.

389
00:39:27,532 --> 00:39:29,116
Where is it?

390
00:39:29,617 --> 00:39:31,827
Where is the bracelet?

391
00:39:32,912 --> 00:39:34,329
l think l know.

392
00:39:35,749 --> 00:39:39,543
At the very top of the gold pyramid,
there was a huge diamond.

393
00:39:39,627 --> 00:39:40,711
Huge? How huge?

394
00:39:40,795 --> 00:39:46,133
It was so big, it would reflect the sun
and wink at distant travelers,

395
00:39:46,217 --> 00:39:48,594
beckoning them to their deaths.

396
00:39:49,929 --> 00:39:50,971
(Speaking Ancient Egyptian)

397
00:39:51,056 --> 00:39:52,973
l have a gift for you.

398
00:39:53,266 --> 00:39:54,308
Her!

399
00:39:57,479 --> 00:40:02,066
l knew it would please you to watch her die.

400
00:40:09,532 --> 00:40:11,825
Get... No! Get off!

401
00:40:15,163 --> 00:40:16,371
Oh, my God.

402
00:40:16,664 --> 00:40:18,582
The Underworld awaits you.

403
00:40:18,708 --> 00:40:22,002
You wait! I'll put you in your grave again!

404
00:40:22,087 --> 00:40:25,339
Our thinking was,
not if we put you in your grave first.

405
00:40:27,008 --> 00:40:28,092
Burn her!

406
00:40:28,176 --> 00:40:29,718
You bast...

407
00:40:30,095 --> 00:40:31,678
(Screaming)

408
00:40:33,431 --> 00:40:34,640
Rick!

409
00:40:34,891 --> 00:40:36,517
(GUNS FIRING)

410
00:40:44,025 --> 00:40:46,527
-Open it! Open it!
-I'm trying, I'm trying!

411
00:40:49,322 --> 00:40:50,531
Meela!

412
00:41:07,382 --> 00:41:09,800
ALEX: Hurry up!
JONATHAN: Come on, come on,

413
00:41:11,052 --> 00:41:13,720
-You broke it, you broke it, you broke it!
-Be quiet, Alex!

414
00:41:13,805 --> 00:41:16,014
lf there's gonna be hysterics,
they'll come from me!

415
00:41:22,689 --> 00:41:23,689
YOU! !

416
00:42:00,602 --> 00:42:02,186
Go, go, go, go!

417
00:42:02,270 --> 00:42:03,937
Collect your bones!

418
00:42:04,105 --> 00:42:05,939
Gather your limbs!

419
00:42:06,149 --> 00:42:08,817
Shake the earth from your flesh!

420
00:42:09,944 --> 00:42:11,778
Your Master is here!

421
00:42:17,368 --> 00:42:20,245
Oh, no. Not these guys again.

422
00:42:20,622 --> 00:42:22,581
DESTROY THEM!!

423
00:42:23,082 --> 00:42:25,000
(Growling)

424
00:42:29,839 --> 00:42:32,090
What are we gonna do?
What are we gonna do?

425
00:42:32,175 --> 00:42:35,052
You're asking me? I'm only eight years old!

426
00:42:42,602 --> 00:42:46,438
Honey, what you doing?
These guys don't use doors.

427
00:42:49,025 --> 00:42:51,109
Where the hell's Jonathan?

428
00:42:56,658 --> 00:42:58,408
-Alex!
-What's the matter with my car?

429
00:42:58,493 --> 00:43:00,994
l was forced to find an alternative
means of transportation.

430
00:43:01,079 --> 00:43:03,413
-A double-decker bus?
-It was his idea!

431
00:43:03,498 --> 00:43:04,748
-Was not!
-Was too!

432
00:43:04,832 --> 00:43:05,791
Just go!

433
00:43:05,875 --> 00:43:07,209
-It was too!
-Was not!

434
00:43:07,293 --> 00:43:08,585
Oh, jeez.

435
00:43:22,475 --> 00:43:24,935
No, no! Not my car!

436
00:43:29,357 --> 00:43:31,942
Oh, l hate mummies.

437
00:43:32,026 --> 00:43:34,861
-Glad to see me now?
-Just like old times, huh?

438
00:43:54,465 --> 00:43:55,632
Right.

439
00:44:14,569 --> 00:44:39,760
(Snarling)

440
00:44:41,304 --> 00:44:42,512
(SCREAMS)

441
00:44:55,693 --> 00:44:57,027
(Snarling)

442
00:45:14,462 --> 00:45:17,714
Turn! Turn! Turn! Turn! Turn!

443
00:45:19,759 --> 00:45:21,134
(Yelling)

444
00:45:28,142 --> 00:45:29,601
(Growling)

445
00:45:34,273 --> 00:45:36,650
No! Get out of the way!

446
00:45:57,755 --> 00:45:59,214
(Snarling)

447
00:46:05,763 --> 00:46:07,305
ALEX: Look out!

448
00:46:13,688 --> 00:46:14,813
(Growling)

449
00:46:27,243 --> 00:46:28,535
(Grunting)

450
00:46:33,166 --> 00:46:35,750
(GLASS Shattering)

451
00:46:35,835 --> 00:46:37,210
Whoa!

452
00:47:10,411 --> 00:47:12,913
-Great driving, Uncle Jon.
-Yeah.

453
00:47:19,962 --> 00:47:24,591
-You all right?
-This was my first bus ride.

454
00:47:31,933 --> 00:47:33,433
What would l do without you?

455
00:47:33,518 --> 00:47:37,604
-Are all librarians this much trouble?
-Oh, jeez, get a room.

456
00:47:50,618 --> 00:47:52,452
-Let me go!
-Alex!

457
00:47:52,537 --> 00:47:54,246
-Silence!
-ALEX: Stop!

458
00:47:54,330 --> 00:47:56,873
-Go!
-Stop!

459
00:48:01,128 --> 00:48:03,255
(BELL Ringling)

460
00:48:29,657 --> 00:48:31,032
Alex.

461
00:48:38,958 --> 00:48:40,000
(Speaking Ancient Egyptian)

462
00:48:40,084 --> 00:48:41,376
l shall now go to Ahm Shere

463
00:48:41,460 --> 00:48:43,837
and kill the Scorpion King.

464
00:48:44,088 --> 00:48:47,173
And with his Army we shall rule the world...

465
00:48:47,383 --> 00:48:49,843
...together.

466
00:48:50,136 --> 00:48:51,845
My Lord...

467
00:48:52,179 --> 00:48:53,972
...there is something you must know.

468
00:48:54,056 --> 00:48:56,057
They have the Scepter of Osiris.

469
00:48:56,142 --> 00:48:58,101
l have seen it.

470
00:48:58,686 --> 00:49:01,354
By the time we reach Ahm Shere,

471
00:49:01,564 --> 00:49:03,857
my powers will have regenerated.

472
00:49:04,025 --> 00:49:09,529
And l will have no need for the Scepter.

473
00:49:41,437 --> 00:49:44,606
Please, do not fear for your son, my friends.

474
00:49:44,690 --> 00:49:48,360
They cannot hurt him,
for he wears the bracelet of Anubis.

475
00:49:48,527 --> 00:49:49,861
Alex is wearing the bracelet?

476
00:49:49,945 --> 00:49:53,448
When he put it on, he said he saw
the pyramids at Giza, the temple at Karnak.

477
00:49:53,532 --> 00:49:58,161
And when they reach Karnak, the bracelet
will show him the next step of the journey.

478
00:49:58,245 --> 00:49:59,621
Well, if we don't get to Karnak before them,

479
00:49:59,705 --> 00:50:02,332
we won't have any idea
where to look for him next.

480
00:50:02,416 --> 00:50:06,294
Seems to me like we need a magic carpet.

481
00:50:06,587 --> 00:50:08,755
(TRAIN Whistle Blowing)

482
00:50:25,439 --> 00:50:28,024
When Lord Imhotep
last encountered the O’Connells,

483
00:50:28,109 --> 00:50:31,194
they sent his immortal soul
to the Underworld.

484
00:50:31,821 --> 00:50:35,365
As powerful as he will become,
he is still vulnerable.

485
00:50:35,449 --> 00:50:39,119
Only with the Army of Anubis
will he be invincible.

486
00:50:40,287 --> 00:50:42,288
He will need your help.

487
00:50:44,375 --> 00:50:45,959
(Speaking Ancient Egyptian)

488
00:50:46,043 --> 00:50:47,961
Keep this with you always.

489
00:50:49,130 --> 00:50:50,338
Hey!

490
00:50:50,423 --> 00:50:52,215
The Book of the Dead!

491
00:50:52,299 --> 00:50:54,592
What a bright little child.

492
00:50:56,220 --> 00:50:58,763
Your mother must be missing you terribly.

493
00:50:58,848 --> 00:51:01,558
lf you wish to see her again,
you'd better behave.

494
00:51:01,642 --> 00:51:04,060
Lady, l don't behave for my parents.

495
00:51:04,145 --> 00:51:05,895
What makes you think
I'm going to do it for you?

496
00:51:05,980 --> 00:51:07,105
Silence!

497
00:51:07,189 --> 00:51:11,317
Because your parents wouldn't slip
poisonous snakes into your bed

498
00:51:11,819 --> 00:51:13,862
while you were sleeping.

499
00:51:14,572 --> 00:51:16,865
Lord Imhotep wishes to meet the boy.

500
00:51:17,742 --> 00:51:20,577
Now we shall see how brave you are.

501
00:51:21,579 --> 00:51:24,622
Hey! Watch the suit! Hey!

502
00:51:25,332 --> 00:51:26,916
Me fingers!

503
00:51:28,335 --> 00:51:29,502
Nice.

504
00:51:33,215 --> 00:51:34,758
Very nice.

505
00:51:34,842 --> 00:51:39,012
-Did you acquire what we asked?
-Oh, we acquired it, all right.

506
00:51:39,346 --> 00:51:40,764
You know what?

507
00:51:40,848 --> 00:51:44,809
We had to kill two of those guards
at the mausoleum to acquire it.

508
00:51:44,894 --> 00:51:46,936
This chest is cursed.

509
00:51:49,023 --> 00:51:55,278
It says there is one, the undead,
who will kill all those who open this chest.

510
00:51:55,362 --> 00:51:57,197
Yes, yes, and the creature
will suck them dry,

511
00:51:57,281 --> 00:51:59,032
then become whole again.

512
00:51:59,533 --> 00:52:00,950
We've all heard this story before.

513
00:52:01,035 --> 00:52:04,954
Yeah, but l heard the yanks
who found it nine years ago all died.

514
00:52:05,039 --> 00:52:06,956
Horrible deaths, they were.

515
00:52:07,416 --> 00:52:09,876
-So, with that in mind...
-We want ten.

516
00:52:09,960 --> 00:52:10,960
Quiet!

517
00:52:11,045 --> 00:52:12,128
(Speaking Ancient Egyptian)

518
00:52:12,213 --> 00:52:14,047
This chest must never be opened.

519
00:52:14,715 --> 00:52:16,466
The agreement was for five.

520
00:52:16,550 --> 00:52:19,260
Yeah, well, we want ten,
or we'll take it elsewhere.

521
00:52:19,345 --> 00:52:21,971
-lf you...
-Ten will be just fine.

522
00:52:22,056 --> 00:52:23,807
Follow me, gentlemen.

523
00:52:25,768 --> 00:52:27,060
Get in.

524
00:52:42,701 --> 00:52:43,660
(Speaking Ancient Egyptian)

525
00:52:43,744 --> 00:52:46,120
l know you can understand me little one.

526
00:52:46,205 --> 00:52:48,748
So you must listen carefully because...

527
00:52:48,833 --> 00:52:51,751
It is you who are the chosen one,

528
00:52:51,836 --> 00:52:54,671
you who will take me to Ahm Shere.

529
00:52:54,755 --> 00:52:59,592
What if l don't? What if l get a little...lost?

530
00:52:59,677 --> 00:53:01,886
(Laughing)

531
00:53:01,971 --> 00:53:04,556
You have strength, little one.

532
00:53:04,640 --> 00:53:06,808
You are your father's son.

533
00:53:06,892 --> 00:53:09,352
But l know something you don't.

534
00:53:09,436 --> 00:53:14,399
This bracelet is a gift and a curse.

535
00:53:15,025 --> 00:53:20,530
The sands of time
have already begun to pour against you.

536
00:53:24,285 --> 00:53:26,369
Yeah, yeah. l already heard this part.

537
00:53:26,453 --> 00:53:28,037
From the minute l put the bracelet on,

538
00:53:28,122 --> 00:53:30,915
seven days do l have before
the Scorpion King wakes up.

539
00:53:31,000 --> 00:53:33,626
Did you also hear that
if you do not enter the pyramid

540
00:53:33,711 --> 00:53:36,212
before the sun strikes it
on that very morning

541
00:53:36,297 --> 00:53:39,340
that the bracelet
will suck the life out of you?

542
00:53:40,301 --> 00:53:41,968
That part l missed.

543
00:53:42,052 --> 00:53:45,054
Hey, wait a minute.
That means I’ve only got five days left.

544
00:53:45,139 --> 00:53:49,517
Then l believe it will be best
if we do not get lost. Don't you?

545
00:53:49,602 --> 00:53:52,812
My dad is going to kick your ass.

546
00:54:00,446 --> 00:54:02,488
l do not think so.

547
00:54:06,827 --> 00:54:10,914
In here, gentlemen,
you shall receive your just rewards.

548
00:54:10,998 --> 00:54:12,916
No tricks now, woman.

549
00:54:13,292 --> 00:54:15,668
We're not giving up this chest
till we're satisfied.

550
00:54:15,753 --> 00:54:19,631
Oh, don't worry.
There is much satisfaction to be had.

551
00:54:28,098 --> 00:54:29,891
What's going on?

552
00:54:34,605 --> 00:54:38,232
This place is cursed.

553
00:54:38,317 --> 00:54:42,070
-What is it with you and curses?
-He ain't happy without a curse.

554
00:54:42,154 --> 00:54:46,324
-This is cursed. That is cursed.
-Give it a rest, will you!

555
00:54:46,784 --> 00:54:48,743
(ALL Screaming)

556
00:54:49,870 --> 00:54:51,204
Christ!

557
00:54:59,964 --> 00:55:03,132
He wants you to open the chest!
Open the chest!

558
00:55:03,842 --> 00:55:05,468
No!

559
00:55:26,699 --> 00:55:29,617
Where'd he go? Where'd he go?

560
00:55:33,831 --> 00:55:35,623
(ALL Screaming)

561
00:55:48,971 --> 00:55:50,930
Spivey!

562
00:56:18,792 --> 00:56:22,253
-This is the magic carpet?
-He'll be fine. He's a professional.

563
00:56:25,174 --> 00:56:26,716
Izzy!

564
00:56:26,967 --> 00:56:29,135
(Mumbling)

565
00:56:29,845 --> 00:56:30,887
(DOOR Locking)

566
00:56:30,971 --> 00:56:32,096
Hey!

567
00:56:32,181 --> 00:56:35,058
-He definitely remembers you.
-He's a little shy.

568
00:56:35,142 --> 00:56:37,894
-Jonathan, get our bags.
-Oh, my hands are full.

569
00:56:37,978 --> 00:56:40,855
-Now.
-Right. I'll get the bags.

570
00:56:40,939 --> 00:56:43,066
I'll deal with the flight details.

571
00:56:43,150 --> 00:56:47,028
-Honey, you're not a subtle man.
-We don't have time for subtle.

572
00:56:49,490 --> 00:56:51,783
-Izzy, come here.
-Oh, no, no.

573
00:56:53,077 --> 00:56:55,828
-Doesn't look happy to see you.
-Never turned me down yet.

574
00:56:55,913 --> 00:56:57,914
Whatever it is, whatever you need,
l don't care.

575
00:56:57,998 --> 00:57:00,833
Forget it, O'Connell.
Every time l hook up with you, l get shot!

576
00:57:00,918 --> 00:57:04,712
Last time, l got shot in the ass.
I'm in mourning for my ass.

577
00:57:04,797 --> 00:57:07,882
-Remember that bank job in Marrakesh?
-Bank job?

578
00:57:08,008 --> 00:57:11,219
-It's not like it sounds.
-It's exactly how it sounds.

579
00:57:11,303 --> 00:57:13,596
I'm flying high, hiding in the sun.

580
00:57:13,680 --> 00:57:16,599
The white boy here flags me down,
so l fly in low for the pickup.

581
00:57:16,683 --> 00:57:18,726
The next thing you know, l get shot!

582
00:57:18,811 --> 00:57:21,187
I'm lying in the middle of the road
with my spleen hanging out,

583
00:57:21,271 --> 00:57:24,232
and l see him waltzing up
with some belly dancer girl.

584
00:57:24,316 --> 00:57:27,944
Belly dancer girl?
Izzy, l think you and l should talk.

585
00:57:28,028 --> 00:57:30,279
-As long as l don't get shot.
-Quit your whining.

586
00:57:30,364 --> 00:57:32,740
You're gonna get paid this time.

587
00:57:34,660 --> 00:57:36,244
IZZY: O'Connell, have you looked
around here any? Huh?

588
00:57:36,328 --> 00:57:40,123
What do l need money for?
What the hell am l gonna spend it on?

589
00:57:40,207 --> 00:57:42,750
I'm gonna keep this short.
My little boy is out there.

590
00:57:42,835 --> 00:57:45,920
I'm gonna do whatever it takes
to get him back.

591
00:57:52,803 --> 00:57:54,470
O'Connell, if you give me
that gold stick there,

592
00:57:54,555 --> 00:57:57,932
you can shave my head,
wax my legs and use me for a surfboard.

593
00:57:58,892 --> 00:58:01,018
Didn't we do that in Tripoli?

594
00:58:01,103 --> 00:58:04,605
Say, by the way,
when did you lose your eye?

595
00:58:04,690 --> 00:58:06,816
Oh. l didn't.

596
00:58:06,900 --> 00:58:09,402
l just thought it made me
look more dashing.

597
00:58:10,571 --> 00:58:12,905
Come on. Get to work.

598
00:58:13,824 --> 00:58:17,368
-You're not exactly catching me at my best.
-Oh, I'm sure l am.

599
00:58:25,169 --> 00:58:28,171
l knew it. I'm gonna get shot.

600
00:58:29,256 --> 00:58:32,884
These are the commanders
of the 1 2 tribes of the Medjai.

601
00:58:33,427 --> 00:58:34,677
Horus!

602
00:58:40,142 --> 00:58:43,561
-Pet bird.
-My best and most clever friend.

603
00:58:43,979 --> 00:58:48,441
He will let the commanders know
of our progress so that they may follow.

604
00:58:49,776 --> 00:58:52,111
(Speaking Arabic)

605
00:59:05,209 --> 00:59:07,501
lf the Army of Anubis arises,

606
00:59:08,337 --> 00:59:10,963
they will do all they can to stop it.

607
00:59:11,298 --> 00:59:15,968
-Rick, are you sure Izzy's reliable?
-Yeah, yeah, he's reliable-ish.

608
00:59:20,891 --> 00:59:23,893
-Isn't she beautiful?
-It's a balloon.

609
00:59:23,977 --> 00:59:27,438
-Oh! It's a dirigible.
-Where's your airplane?

610
00:59:27,522 --> 00:59:30,608
-Airplanes are a thing of the past.
-Izzy, you were right.

611
00:59:30,692 --> 00:59:32,401
-l was?	
-Yeah. You're gonna get shot.

612
00:59:32,486 --> 00:59:35,988
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
She's faster than she looks.

613
00:59:36,073 --> 00:59:38,407
And she's quiet. Real quiet.

614
00:59:38,492 --> 00:59:42,078
Perfect for sneaking up on people,
which is a very good thing.

615
00:59:42,162 --> 00:59:44,247
Unless, of course, we go with your approach

616
00:59:44,331 --> 00:59:49,085
barging in face-first, guns blazing,
and getting your friends shot in the ass!

617
00:59:50,587 --> 00:59:53,339
Why can't you people
ever keep your feet on the ground?

618
01:00:39,970 --> 01:00:43,889
O'Connell does not want to believe,
but he flies like Horus towards his destiny.

619
01:00:43,974 --> 01:00:47,852
Yes, yes, very interesting.
Tell me some more about this gold pyramid.

620
01:00:47,936 --> 01:00:50,604
Well, it is written
that since the time of the Scorpion King,

621
01:00:50,689 --> 01:00:53,733
no man who has laid eyes upon it
has ever returned to tell the tale.

622
01:00:53,817 --> 01:00:56,569
Where is all this stuff written? Hello.

623
01:00:58,530 --> 01:00:59,739
Got it.

624
01:01:05,412 --> 01:01:07,079
Pretty nice, eh?

625
01:01:07,456 --> 01:01:09,498
This is all l have left in the world.

626
01:01:09,583 --> 01:01:11,751
The rest of my fortune was lost

627
01:01:11,835 --> 01:01:14,378
to some rather unscrupulous characters,
actually.

628
01:01:14,463 --> 01:01:17,840
But if the curator reacted to it
the way you say, it must be very important.

629
01:01:17,924 --> 01:01:20,343
lf l were you, l would keep it close.

630
01:01:20,427 --> 01:01:23,429
My friend, the gods couldn't take this away
from me.

631
01:01:23,513 --> 01:01:26,057
-Hey! That's mine!
-No, it's not!

632
01:01:27,851 --> 01:01:29,935
Keep your hands off of it.

633
01:01:37,778 --> 01:01:38,819
Hey.

634
01:01:39,905 --> 01:01:41,781
l want him back, Rick.

635
01:01:42,699 --> 01:01:45,326
-l want him in my arms.
-l know.

636
01:01:48,163 --> 01:01:49,955
We taught him well.

637
01:01:51,166 --> 01:01:53,000
He's smarter than you

638
01:01:54,336 --> 01:01:56,087
and he's tougher than me.

639
01:01:56,171 --> 01:02:00,758
-l love him so much. l just can't...
-l know. We both do, and Alex knows that.

640
01:02:02,677 --> 01:02:06,097
-I'll get him back, Evy. l promise.
-l know you will.

641
01:02:33,500 --> 01:02:34,834
-ALEX: Are we there yet?
-No.

642
01:02:34,918 --> 01:02:47,012
-Are we there yet?
-No.

643
01:02:48,014 --> 01:02:49,849
Whoa! That was amazing!

644
01:02:49,933 --> 01:02:52,726
-Perfect aim.
-What are you talking about?

645
01:02:54,229 --> 01:02:55,521
l missed.

646
01:03:03,947 --> 01:03:05,614
l have to go to the bathroom.

647
01:03:37,063 --> 01:03:38,606
Make it quick.

648
01:03:45,864 --> 01:03:47,114
Hurry up.

649
01:03:50,660 --> 01:03:53,162
-Hey, reading material.
-Now!

650
01:03:57,959 --> 01:04:00,503
l can't go when someone's watching.

651
01:04:03,006 --> 01:04:04,590
l don't trust you. You'll look.

652
01:04:11,389 --> 01:04:13,641
(Grunting)

653
01:04:14,309 --> 01:04:15,518
Damn!

654
01:04:19,689 --> 01:04:23,776
Oh, my God! Doesn't anyone around here
know how to flush a toilet?

655
01:04:42,671 --> 01:04:45,130
(WHEELs Screeching)

656
01:04:56,434 --> 01:04:57,434
(Speaking Ancient Egyptian)

657
01:04:57,519 --> 01:04:58,519
The boy.

658
01:05:24,379 --> 01:05:25,629
Karnak.

659
01:05:38,184 --> 01:05:39,226
Huh?

660
01:06:06,546 --> 01:06:09,590
lf a man does not embrace his past,
he has no future.

661
01:06:09,674 --> 01:06:13,427
Look, even if

662
01:06:13,970 --> 01:06:17,681
l was some sort of sacred Medjai,
what good does that do me now?

663
01:06:17,766 --> 01:06:19,892
It is the missing piece of your heart.

664
01:06:20,101 --> 01:06:23,687
lf you embrace it, if you accept it,
you can do anything.

665
01:06:24,105 --> 01:06:25,939
Sounds great. Listen.

666
01:06:26,399 --> 01:06:29,360
What can we expect
from our old friend Imhotep?

667
01:06:29,444 --> 01:06:31,487
His powers are returning.

668
01:06:31,571 --> 01:06:32,655
By the time he reaches Ahm Shere,

669
01:06:32,739 --> 01:06:34,782
even the Scorpion King
won't be able to stop him.

670
01:06:49,297 --> 01:06:50,339
(Imhotep Speaking
Ancient Egyptian)

671
01:06:50,423 --> 01:06:53,634
It is time to remind you of who you are...

672
01:06:56,137 --> 01:06:59,431
...and of who we are together.

673
01:06:59,641 --> 01:07:02,893
For our love is true love,

674
01:07:03,061 --> 01:07:06,230
an eternal love,

675
01:07:06,481 --> 01:07:08,107
our souls mated...

676
01:07:08,358 --> 01:07:09,983
together as one...

677
01:07:10,652 --> 01:07:12,611
...forever.

678
01:07:23,790 --> 01:07:25,666
(MAN Speaking
Ancient Egyptian)

679
01:07:56,740 --> 01:07:57,740
(Speaking Ancient Egyptian)

680
01:07:57,824 --> 01:07:58,949
Put your mask on!

681
01:07:59,242 --> 01:08:01,160
Let's not scar that pretty face.

682
01:09:10,855 --> 01:09:14,024
You are learning quickly, Nefertiti.

683
01:09:14,317 --> 01:09:16,193
I'll have to watch my back.

684
01:09:16,611 --> 01:09:20,948
Yes... and I'll watch mine.

685
01:09:22,742 --> 01:09:23,992
(Speaking Ancient Egyptian)

686
01:09:24,077 --> 01:09:25,077
Bravo! Bravo!

687
01:09:26,788 --> 01:09:31,166
Who better to protect
the Bracelet of Anubis...

688
01:09:32,210 --> 01:09:34,461
than my lovely daughter, Nefertiti.

689
01:09:34,796 --> 01:09:37,923
And who better to protect me,

690
01:09:38,132 --> 01:09:39,758
than my future wife, Anck-su-namun.

691
01:09:44,347 --> 01:09:46,807
Well done, daughter.

692
01:10:51,664 --> 01:10:52,706
(Speaking Ancient Egyptian)

693
01:10:52,790 --> 01:10:53,790
The Pharaoh!

694
01:10:56,002 --> 01:10:57,753
PHARAOH: Anck-su-namun!

695
01:11:10,516 --> 01:11:11,767
Imhotep!

696
01:11:12,018 --> 01:11:12,976
(Speaking Ancient Egyptian)

697
01:11:13,061 --> 01:11:14,061
Medjai!

698
01:11:14,479 --> 01:11:16,396
My father needs you!

699
01:11:23,696 --> 01:11:25,530
(Screaming)

700
01:11:25,865 --> 01:11:26,990
Evy!

701
01:11:29,285 --> 01:11:30,702
(BOTH Grunting)

702
01:11:39,212 --> 01:11:41,713
-Go! Save yourself!
-NO!

703
01:11:41,798 --> 01:11:43,674
Only you can resurrect me!

704
01:11:45,760 --> 01:11:47,094
l won't leave you!

705
01:11:47,220 --> 01:11:48,845
Get away from me!

706
01:11:50,723 --> 01:11:51,807
Anck-su-namun!

707
01:11:51,891 --> 01:11:53,141
Imhotep!

708
01:11:55,395 --> 01:11:58,563
My body is no longer his temple!

709
01:12:25,091 --> 01:12:27,592
-Imhotep.
-Anck-su-namun.

710
01:12:35,393 --> 01:12:37,561
Evy, l know
you haven't exactly been yourself lately

711
01:12:37,645 --> 01:12:39,229
with all these dreams and visions...

712
01:12:39,313 --> 01:12:41,857
No, no,
they're memories from my previous life.

713
01:12:41,941 --> 01:12:44,818
Honestly, I'm not losing my mind.
It all makes perfect sense now.

714
01:12:44,944 --> 01:12:46,778
And that's the reason
why we found the bracelet?

715
01:12:46,863 --> 01:12:48,822
Exactly. l was its protector.

716
01:12:48,906 --> 01:12:50,407
Now do you believe, my friend?

717
01:12:50,491 --> 01:12:52,701
Clearly, you were destined to protect
this woman.

718
01:12:52,785 --> 01:12:56,204
Right. She's a reincarnated princess,
and I'm a warrior for God.

719
01:12:56,289 --> 01:13:00,500
And your son leads the way to Ahm Shere.
Three sides of the pyramid.

720
01:13:00,626 --> 01:13:03,295
This was all preordained
thousands of years ago.

721
01:13:03,379 --> 01:13:05,005
And how does the story end?

722
01:13:05,089 --> 01:13:08,175
Only the journey's written,
not the destination.

723
01:13:08,259 --> 01:13:11,219
-Convenient.
-How else do you explain Evy's visions?

724
01:13:11,304 --> 01:13:13,889
That it is your son who wears the bracelet?

725
01:13:13,973 --> 01:13:16,600
-How do you explain your mark?
-Coincidence.

726
01:13:16,768 --> 01:13:21,188
My friend, there is a fine line between
coincidence and fate.

727
01:13:41,417 --> 01:13:43,502
Don't even think about it!

728
01:13:47,256 --> 01:13:49,174
Hold on there, partner.

729
01:13:52,553 --> 01:13:54,346
When the time comes,

730
01:13:55,348 --> 01:13:57,724
l shall truly enjoy killing you.

731
01:13:59,685 --> 01:14:01,478
But until that time,

732
01:14:02,438 --> 01:14:04,981
you better be a little nicer to me.

733
01:14:05,316 --> 01:14:07,192
Now, where's my water?

734
01:14:11,197 --> 01:14:12,405
No ice?

735
01:14:15,034 --> 01:14:16,785
(Speaking
Ancient Egyptian)

736
01:14:17,829 --> 01:14:19,871
Make sure he doesn't move!

737
01:14:50,153 --> 01:14:52,404
They've gone. We've lost them.

738
01:15:08,713 --> 01:15:09,796
Rick!

739
01:15:19,015 --> 01:15:20,807
Alex left us his tie,

740
01:15:21,434 --> 01:15:24,811
and he made us a little sand castle.

741
01:15:25,688 --> 01:15:27,731
It's the Temple Island of Philae.

742
01:15:27,815 --> 01:15:29,691
-They've gone to Philae.
-That-a-boy, Alex.

743
01:15:29,775 --> 01:15:31,067
Come on!

744
01:15:42,788 --> 01:15:45,123
The great temple of Abu Simbel.

745
01:16:48,020 --> 01:16:50,939
(Speaking Arabic)

746
01:17:12,545 --> 01:17:14,879
That's the Blue Nile down there.

747
01:17:15,006 --> 01:17:16,464
We must be out of Egypt by now.

748
01:17:16,549 --> 01:17:20,010
In ancient times, all this still belonged
to the upper kingdom.

749
01:17:20,428 --> 01:17:22,637
The oasis must be around here somewhere.

750
01:17:22,722 --> 01:17:25,640
RICK: Don't worry, Evy, we'll find him.
He's a smart kid.

751
01:17:25,725 --> 01:17:27,600
He'll leave us a sign.

752
01:17:32,815 --> 01:17:34,607
Surprised to see me?

753
01:17:35,276 --> 01:17:37,235
Leaving bread crumbs, huh? Huh?

754
01:17:37,528 --> 01:17:38,528
(Speaking Ancient Egyptian)

755
01:17:38,612 --> 01:17:39,654
Lock-Nah!

756
01:17:39,739 --> 01:17:42,324
Put the boy down.

757
01:17:46,412 --> 01:17:50,081
l hope your parents enjoyed their journey.

758
01:18:31,749 --> 01:18:34,209
We're in trouble!

759
01:18:35,211 --> 01:18:36,336
Whoa!

760
01:18:39,548 --> 01:18:41,049
(Growling)

761
01:18:46,514 --> 01:18:47,931
Horus, fly!

762
01:18:50,726 --> 01:18:54,813
Izzy, come hard right! Starboard! Starboard!

763
01:18:54,897 --> 01:18:56,606
(Grunting)

764
01:19:37,982 --> 01:19:40,733
Was there a little something
you forgot to mention?

765
01:19:45,489 --> 01:19:46,698
People?

766
01:19:54,540 --> 01:19:56,624
(Birds Twittering)

767
01:19:58,878 --> 01:20:01,212
(MONKEYS Chattering)

768
01:20:05,885 --> 01:20:07,218
Ahm Shere.

769
01:20:18,230 --> 01:20:19,439
Right.

770
01:20:19,523 --> 01:20:21,691
(Rumbling)

771
01:20:26,572 --> 01:20:27,906
He's back!

772
01:20:27,990 --> 01:20:29,324
(Growling)

773
01:20:31,243 --> 01:20:32,535
Hang on!

774
01:20:46,342 --> 01:20:48,218
Well, that's not good.

775
01:20:49,762 --> 01:20:51,012
RICK: Hang on!

776
01:20:58,604 --> 01:20:59,687
Mom?

777
01:21:00,773 --> 01:21:01,856
Dad?

778
01:21:11,784 --> 01:21:13,284
RICK: We're gonna go get my son.

779
01:21:13,369 --> 01:21:14,994
Then we're gonna wanna
get out of here fast,

780
01:21:15,079 --> 01:21:17,789
-so make this work, Izzy.
-No, no, you don't understand, goddamn it.

781
01:21:17,873 --> 01:21:20,583
This thing was filled with gas.
Not hot air... Gas.

782
01:21:20,668 --> 01:21:22,252
l need gas to get this thing off the ground.

783
01:21:22,336 --> 01:21:24,337
Where am l gonna get gas
from around here? Huh?

784
01:21:24,421 --> 01:21:27,090
Bananas? Mangos? Tarzan's ass?

785
01:21:27,174 --> 01:21:29,300
Well, maybe l could finagle it to take hot air.

786
01:21:29,385 --> 01:21:33,221
But do you know how many cubic meters
I'd need? It's too big!

787
01:21:33,681 --> 01:21:37,642
lf anybody can fill this thing up with hot air,
Izzy, it's you.

788
01:21:44,108 --> 01:21:45,650
Come to Daddy.

789
01:21:47,486 --> 01:21:48,903
(Whistling)

790
01:21:48,988 --> 01:21:50,154
Horus!

791
01:21:58,956 --> 01:22:02,667
JONATHAN: So, Rick, what's the plan?
RICK: Let's find some higher ground.

792
01:22:07,631 --> 01:22:10,508
(HORUS CHIRPING)

793
01:22:19,685 --> 01:22:21,185
(GUN FIRES)

794
01:22:21,979 --> 01:22:23,187
Horus!

795
01:22:29,778 --> 01:22:31,404
-l must go.
-Where?

796
01:22:31,488 --> 01:22:32,989
l must let the commanders know
where we are.

797
01:22:33,073 --> 01:22:34,949
-You can't go.
-lf the Army of Anubis arises...

798
01:22:35,034 --> 01:22:37,493
l need you to help me find my son.

799
01:22:42,875 --> 01:22:45,418
-Then first, l shall help you.
-Thank you.

800
01:23:24,416 --> 01:23:26,751
Look. Roman legionnaires.

801
01:23:29,296 --> 01:23:33,091
And here. Turn-of-the-century French.
Napoleon's troops.

802
01:23:33,175 --> 01:23:35,760
What in the name of Anubis did this?

803
01:23:43,727 --> 01:23:45,978
(Growling)

804
01:23:56,782 --> 01:23:58,616
-You hear that?
-What?

805
01:23:59,993 --> 01:24:01,285
Nothing.

806
01:24:02,246 --> 01:24:03,996
Absolutely nothing.

807
01:24:05,958 --> 01:24:07,500
My word!

808
01:24:11,171 --> 01:24:13,256
l say, chaps, look at this.

809
01:24:13,340 --> 01:24:16,843
Shrunken heads.
I’d love to know how they do that.

810
01:24:20,180 --> 01:24:21,681
Just curious.

811
01:24:27,312 --> 01:24:28,813
You any good with that?

812
01:24:29,106 --> 01:24:32,066
Three times Fox and Hound's
grand champion, I'll have you know.

813
01:24:32,151 --> 01:24:35,653
-You any good with that?
-You'll know soon enough.

814
01:24:36,697 --> 01:24:40,491
Because the only way to kill
an Anubis warrior is by taking off its head.

815
01:24:41,660 --> 01:24:43,411
I'll remember that.

816
01:24:48,167 --> 01:24:50,585
Evy, try to remember to...

817
01:24:52,254 --> 01:24:55,006
Just keep it tight in the shoulder and

818
01:24:56,925 --> 01:24:59,719
lead the target a little bit, and then...

819
01:25:00,846 --> 01:25:03,347
And squeeze the trigger. Don't pull it.

820
01:25:05,184 --> 01:25:06,684
l won't miss.

821
01:25:31,627 --> 01:25:34,003
(Snarling)

822
01:25:46,475 --> 01:25:48,559
-Pyramid.
-The pyramid.

823
01:25:49,311 --> 01:25:51,437
Cripes, I'm in trouble now.

824
01:25:51,814 --> 01:25:53,022
Now may l kill him?

825
01:25:53,774 --> 01:25:54,774
(Speaking Ancient Egyptian)

826
01:25:54,858 --> 01:25:55,858
My Lord...

827
01:25:55,943 --> 01:25:59,070
Now there is no need for the boy.

828
01:25:59,321 --> 01:26:01,072
Yes, but we need the bracelet.

829
01:26:01,240 --> 01:26:03,407
It will unlock the Army of Anubis.

830
01:26:03,617 --> 01:26:04,659
The bracelet?

831
01:26:04,743 --> 01:26:06,369
The bracelet is the key?!

832
01:26:06,453 --> 01:26:08,913
-Retrieve that bracelet.
-With pleasure.

833
01:26:21,927 --> 01:26:22,927
(Speaking Ancient Egyptian)

834
01:26:23,011 --> 01:26:24,011
What is it?

835
01:26:26,974 --> 01:26:28,850
(THUNDER Rumbling)

836
01:26:35,232 --> 01:26:37,942
Something is coming.

837
01:26:51,498 --> 01:26:52,623
(Speaking Ancient Egyptian)

838
01:26:52,708 --> 01:26:53,958
Fan out! Eyes open! Guns up!

839
01:26:58,881 --> 01:27:00,464
-Jonathan?
-Yes?

840
01:27:01,091 --> 01:27:03,843
That's my husband and my son down there.

841
01:27:04,177 --> 01:27:05,720
Make me proud.

842
01:27:06,722 --> 01:27:08,639
Today's that day, Evy.

843
01:27:10,225 --> 01:27:14,145
Do not fear. They cannot harm me.

844
01:27:15,272 --> 01:27:16,689
(MAN Shouting IN Arabic)

845
01:27:16,773 --> 01:27:18,357
Where's the boy?

846
01:28:22,881 --> 01:28:24,006
(Snarling)

847
01:28:24,091 --> 01:28:25,591
(Screaming)

848
01:28:25,926 --> 01:28:27,426
(Shuddering)

849
01:28:27,552 --> 01:28:29,095
(Snarling)

850
01:28:37,020 --> 01:28:38,562
The black book!

851
01:28:43,610 --> 01:28:44,902
Let's go!

852
01:28:45,946 --> 01:28:48,322
(PEOPLE Yelling)

853
01:29:14,558 --> 01:29:16,100
There you are!

854
01:29:16,184 --> 01:29:18,019
(GUNS FIRING)

855
01:29:18,687 --> 01:29:22,231
-The time has come, my little friend.
-Let go!

856
01:29:40,167 --> 01:29:42,710
-Dad!
-Alex!

857
01:29:44,129 --> 01:29:45,379
Alex...

858
01:29:52,804 --> 01:29:53,846
Dad!

859
01:30:03,356 --> 01:30:06,192
Time to remove that bracelet, my good son.

860
01:30:06,318 --> 01:30:07,443
Dad!

861
01:30:16,745 --> 01:30:19,288
-Dad, behind you!
-Whoa!

862
01:30:25,045 --> 01:30:26,712
(Yelling)

863
01:30:35,388 --> 01:30:37,098
(MEN Grunting)

864
01:30:49,277 --> 01:30:50,820
(Snarling)

865
01:31:28,984 --> 01:31:30,568
(GUN FIRES)

866
01:31:42,497 --> 01:31:44,832
-Let's go.
-Thank God for that.

867
01:31:52,007 --> 01:31:55,926
The two of you must sacrifice yourselves
for me.

868
01:31:56,970 --> 01:31:59,346
You shall be rewarded in heaven!

869
01:32:05,437 --> 01:32:06,937
(Snarling)

870
01:32:14,529 --> 01:32:15,946
-Mom!
-Alex!

871
01:32:17,240 --> 01:32:18,324
Hey, nice shootin', Tex.

872
01:32:18,408 --> 01:32:20,534
What were those creepy little pygmy things?

873
01:32:20,619 --> 01:32:22,828
-Just the local natives.
-Are you sure?

874
01:32:22,913 --> 01:32:24,163
I'm sure. It was nothin'.

875
01:32:24,247 --> 01:32:26,207
Come on, Mom! Come on! Come on, Dad!

876
01:32:26,291 --> 01:32:29,627
We have to get to the pyramid.
l have to get the bracelet off now!

877
01:32:29,711 --> 01:32:31,712
Oh, leave it on, Alex. Looks good on you.

878
01:32:31,796 --> 01:32:33,797
No, you guys! You don't understand!

879
01:32:33,882 --> 01:32:35,549
He told me the bracelet will kill me

880
01:32:35,634 --> 01:32:38,510
if l don't get inside the pyramid
before the sun hits it!

881
01:32:38,595 --> 01:32:41,138
-Today!
-Oh, my God.

882
01:32:41,348 --> 01:32:43,390
(CREATURES Screeching)

883
01:32:44,851 --> 01:32:46,268
Time to go!

884
01:32:47,479 --> 01:32:49,438
l thought you said it was nothing!

885
01:32:55,195 --> 01:32:56,779
(Screeching)

886
01:33:02,285 --> 01:33:03,953
Where's Jonathan?

887
01:33:13,838 --> 01:33:15,589
Look! There's a burial ground!

888
01:33:15,674 --> 01:33:17,216
We're safe! We're safe!

889
01:33:17,300 --> 01:33:19,343
See those sacred stones?
They'll never cross those.

890
01:33:19,427 --> 01:33:22,179
-You are sure?
-Yes, of course I'm sure!

891
01:33:27,394 --> 01:33:29,270
(Screaming)

892
01:33:37,445 --> 01:33:39,154
Sorry. My mistake.

893
01:33:47,664 --> 01:33:50,624
JONATHAN: Wait for me!
EVELYN: Hurry up, Jonathan!

894
01:33:51,876 --> 01:33:54,420
Wait for me! What's that for?

895
01:33:54,587 --> 01:33:57,089
Ah, nothin'. Just a little something
in case of an emergency.

896
01:33:58,133 --> 01:33:59,758
(Screeching)

897
01:34:15,191 --> 01:34:16,317
Rick.

898
01:34:20,113 --> 01:34:21,697
Let's go, Alex!

899
01:34:30,832 --> 01:34:34,251
Run! Come on, Alex, faster! Come on!

900
01:34:34,669 --> 01:34:37,921
-Come on!
-Dad! The bracelet!

901
01:34:38,089 --> 01:34:40,049
Run! Come on!

902
01:35:03,073 --> 01:35:05,574
You know, it's not

903
01:35:06,076 --> 01:35:08,077
easy being a dad.

904
01:35:09,496 --> 01:35:12,164
Yeah, but you do it really good.

905
01:35:13,500 --> 01:35:14,750
Thanks.

906
01:35:33,812 --> 01:35:36,313
They made it. Thank God.

907
01:35:37,440 --> 01:35:39,316
Oh, yes. Great.

908
01:35:39,984 --> 01:35:41,318
Fabulous.

909
01:35:42,278 --> 01:35:43,612
(GROANS)

910
01:35:44,906 --> 01:35:45,989
No!

911
01:35:58,837 --> 01:36:01,463
Evy!

912
01:36:06,886 --> 01:36:08,929
-Jonathan! Jonathan!
-Mom!

913
01:36:10,223 --> 01:36:13,142
-You're going to be all right. Isn't she, Dad?
-She'll be fine.

914
01:36:13,226 --> 01:36:15,936
-She's going to be all right.
-Just get him... Take him. Take...

915
01:36:16,020 --> 01:36:17,980
Mommy's fine. It's okay.

916
01:36:19,232 --> 01:36:21,191
-Where... Evy...
-Your mother's gonna be fine, okay?

917
01:36:21,276 --> 01:36:22,901
Oh, my God!

918
01:36:23,695 --> 01:36:26,405
You're real strong.
You're gonna make it. You're gonna make it.

919
01:36:26,489 --> 01:36:27,865
You're fine.

920
01:36:28,450 --> 01:36:31,869
What do l do? What do l do, Evy?

921
01:36:32,579 --> 01:36:35,539
-What do l do?
-Take care of Alex.

922
01:36:37,709 --> 01:36:41,044
No. Sweetheart, no.

923
01:36:43,381 --> 01:36:44,798
l love you.

924
01:36:46,384 --> 01:36:49,636
No, don't... No. No!

925
01:36:50,930 --> 01:36:52,514
Evy? Evy?

926
01:36:53,808 --> 01:36:57,853
RICK: No. No. Evy!

927
01:37:02,317 --> 01:37:04,067
Come back, Evy.

928
01:37:06,196 --> 01:37:08,113
Evy, come back.

929
01:37:09,240 --> 01:37:10,616
Come back.

930
01:37:58,831 --> 01:38:01,041
(BOTH Screaming)

931
01:38:21,271 --> 01:38:22,271
(Speaking Ancient Egyptian)

932
01:38:22,355 --> 01:38:23,397
The great god Anubis...

933
01:38:23,481 --> 01:38:25,983
...has taken my powers.

934
01:38:26,651 --> 01:38:29,987
It seems he wishes me to fight...

935
01:38:30,154 --> 01:38:31,863
...as a mortal.

936
01:38:36,035 --> 01:38:37,411
Stay here.

937
01:38:48,673 --> 01:38:50,007
(GASPS)

938
01:38:51,175 --> 01:38:53,635
(Skittering)

939
01:39:29,505 --> 01:39:30,631
Whoa!

940
01:40:05,667 --> 01:40:06,667
(Speaking Arabic)

941
01:40:06,751 --> 01:40:07,751
So it begins.

942
01:40:12,256 --> 01:40:14,800
Try to think of it like this, Alex.

943
01:40:15,134 --> 01:40:17,386
She's gone to a better place.

944
01:40:17,553 --> 01:40:19,429
You know, like it says in the good book.

945
01:40:19,514 --> 01:40:21,139
-The book.
-What?

946
01:40:21,224 --> 01:40:22,349
That's it.

947
01:40:22,433 --> 01:40:25,185
-That's it. Come on, Uncle Jon!
-That's what?

948
01:40:25,269 --> 01:40:27,062
-Come on! Come on! That's it! The book!
-What?

949
01:40:27,146 --> 01:40:28,939
(Grunting)

950
01:40:36,531 --> 01:40:40,450
You're too late, O'Connell.
l have released the Army of Anubis.

951
01:40:41,244 --> 01:40:45,455
Lord Imhotep shall soon kill
the Scorpion King and take command.

952
01:40:46,541 --> 01:40:48,458
Not after l get through with him.

953
01:40:49,377 --> 01:40:51,253
(Screaming)

954
01:41:07,520 --> 01:41:08,562
(Speaking Ancient Egyptian)

955
01:41:08,646 --> 01:41:10,313
l must face the Scorpion King alone.

956
01:41:10,398 --> 01:41:11,565
No. You must not.

957
01:41:11,733 --> 01:41:13,692
Without your powers he will kill you.

958
01:41:13,901 --> 01:41:14,985
Nothing can stop us.

959
01:41:15,111 --> 01:41:16,903
It is our destiny!

960
01:41:16,988 --> 01:41:18,113
Niy!

961
01:41:19,782 --> 01:41:21,992
l don't want to lose you again.

962
01:41:26,497 --> 01:41:29,124
Niy! Niy!

963
01:41:29,834 --> 01:41:31,251
You realize, of course,

964
01:41:31,335 --> 01:41:35,088
that this can only be done by someone
who can actually read ancient Egyptian.

965
01:41:35,173 --> 01:41:38,133
l don't know about you, but I'm a tad rusty.

966
01:41:39,218 --> 01:41:40,594
Now where?

967
01:41:40,720 --> 01:41:43,054
-We go right.
-How do you know?

968
01:41:44,056 --> 01:41:46,016
"Kasheesh Osirian Nye."

969
01:41:46,559 --> 01:41:49,603
Basically, "This way to the Scorpion King."

970
01:41:51,147 --> 01:41:52,689
Mum taught me.

971
01:41:55,985 --> 01:41:57,819
This just might work.

972
01:42:22,595 --> 01:42:24,387
(Growling)

973
01:42:28,893 --> 01:42:31,228
It's time someone taught you a lesson,
wench. Come on.

974
01:42:40,196 --> 01:42:42,072
This is for my sister.

975
01:42:44,909 --> 01:42:46,576
(GONG RINGING)

976
01:43:08,057 --> 01:43:21,570
(Grunting)

977
01:43:33,457 --> 01:43:34,583
(Speaking Ancient Egyptian)

978
01:43:34,667 --> 01:43:36,918
So you wish to kill me?

979
01:43:37,003 --> 01:43:38,962
And then you would kill him...

980
01:43:40,214 --> 01:43:42,716
...and send his Army back
to the Underworld.

981
01:43:44,051 --> 01:43:46,887
This l cannot allow.

982
01:44:07,074 --> 01:44:08,658
(Growling)

983
01:44:14,540 --> 01:44:17,125
(Yelling)

984
01:44:31,515 --> 01:44:33,433
Is that all you've got?

985
01:44:40,650 --> 01:44:43,068
(Shouting)

986
01:44:43,152 --> 01:44:45,028
(ALL Yelling)

987
01:45:25,361 --> 01:45:26,903
Hurry up, Alex!

988
01:45:27,154 --> 01:45:31,658
"Hootash naraba oos Veesloo.

989
01:45:32,159 --> 01:45:35,203
"Ahm kum Ra. Ahm kum Dei."

990
01:46:18,122 --> 01:46:21,374
"Efday Shokran... Efday Shokran..."

991
01:46:21,459 --> 01:46:24,294
Uncle Jon, l don't know
what this last symbol is!

992
01:46:24,462 --> 01:46:27,881
-What's it look like?
-It's a bird! A stork!

993
01:46:30,551 --> 01:46:32,969
l know that one! l know that one!

994
01:46:33,596 --> 01:46:35,221
Then what is it?

995
01:46:37,516 --> 01:46:38,933
Ahmenophus!

996
01:46:39,977 --> 01:46:43,271
That's it! "Efday Shokran Ahmenophus!"

997
01:47:24,396 --> 01:47:27,357
Why don't you pick on somebody
your own size?

998
01:47:27,691 --> 01:47:30,443
-Oh, my God. Evy!
-Take Alex.

999
01:47:30,528 --> 01:47:32,362
-Go and help Rick.
-But Mom...

1000
01:47:32,446 --> 01:47:33,613
No "buts," Alex.

1001
01:47:33,697 --> 01:47:35,907
-Come on, Alex.
-But... But...

1002
01:47:37,743 --> 01:47:39,452
I'll be just fine.

1003
01:47:39,703 --> 01:47:41,663
We did it, Uncle Jon! We did it!

1004
01:47:41,747 --> 01:47:43,748
Right, partner. Now, let's go help your dad.

1005
01:48:37,887 --> 01:48:38,928
(Speaking Ancient Egyptian)

1006
01:48:39,013 --> 01:48:42,307
l am your servant!

1007
01:48:44,935 --> 01:48:46,186
We shall see.

1008
01:48:49,481 --> 01:48:52,192
But he was sent to kill you!

1009
01:48:52,276 --> 01:48:53,443
(Growling)

1010
01:49:20,304 --> 01:49:21,638
Nefertiti.

1011
01:49:22,973 --> 01:49:24,140
Anck-su-namun.

1012
01:49:24,391 --> 01:49:25,391
(Speaking Ancient Egyptian)

1013
01:49:25,476 --> 01:49:26,476
Good.

1014
01:49:41,617 --> 01:49:43,701
You have remembered the old ways.

1015
01:49:46,205 --> 01:49:48,248
That's a little something new!

1016
01:50:01,262 --> 01:50:02,720
(SHIVERING)

1017
01:50:06,517 --> 01:50:08,142
(Growling)

1018
01:50:17,027 --> 01:50:18,319
My lord!

1019
01:50:20,489 --> 01:50:22,282
Save me! Save me!

1020
01:50:22,533 --> 01:50:23,658
Why?

1021
01:50:40,592 --> 01:50:42,593
(ALL Cheering)

1022
01:51:18,589 --> 01:51:19,547
(Speaking Arabic)

1023
01:51:19,631 --> 01:51:20,757
God help us.

1024
01:51:47,868 --> 01:51:49,869
Okay, now I'm a believer.

1025
01:51:50,871 --> 01:51:51,996
Rick!

1026
01:51:54,041 --> 01:51:55,666
-Jonathan!
-Dad!

1027
01:51:56,126 --> 01:51:57,293
It's a spear!

1028
01:51:57,378 --> 01:52:00,046
The gold stick thing... It's a... It's a spear!

1029
01:52:00,130 --> 01:52:03,007
Really? Doesn't look like a spear!

1030
01:52:03,092 --> 01:52:06,219
No! That's because it opens up into one!

1031
01:52:06,303 --> 01:52:08,304
-Yes? And?
-Jonathan!

1032
01:52:08,389 --> 01:52:11,557
It opens up into a spear!

1033
01:52:11,642 --> 01:52:13,643
(Roaring)

1034
01:52:17,022 --> 01:52:18,689
(Screaming)

1035
01:52:40,254 --> 01:52:41,295
(Speaking Arabic)

1036
01:52:41,380 --> 01:52:42,505
'Til Death!

1037
01:52:42,756 --> 01:52:44,841
(ALL Shouting)

1038
01:52:57,980 --> 01:53:00,898
-Rick!
-Evy?

1039
01:53:07,448 --> 01:53:09,907
-Twist it!
-Pull! l tried it! Push!

1040
01:53:12,411 --> 01:53:13,578
The Spear of Osiris!

1041
01:53:13,871 --> 01:53:15,496
Jonathan, quick!

1042
01:53:29,470 --> 01:53:32,597
Jonathan, throw it! Kill the Scorpion King!

1043
01:53:32,681 --> 01:53:34,765
Send his army back to the Underworld!

1044
01:53:35,392 --> 01:53:37,727
Step aside, Alex. I'm a professional.

1045
01:53:48,405 --> 01:53:50,072
(Snarling)

1046
01:53:52,910 --> 01:53:54,952
The Army of Anubis shall now be MINE!

1047
01:53:57,581 --> 01:53:58,748
Rick!

1048
01:54:06,673 --> 01:54:28,986
No!

1049
01:54:30,322 --> 01:54:31,781
(Growling)

1050
01:54:34,243 --> 01:54:35,743
Niy!

1051
01:54:41,708 --> 01:54:45,127
Go to hell, and take your friends with you!

1052
01:54:46,922 --> 01:54:48,506
(Growling)

1053
01:55:07,985 --> 01:55:10,111
(ALL Cheering)

1054
01:55:59,202 --> 01:56:00,536
(GRUNTS)

1055
01:56:01,663 --> 01:56:02,705
Dad!

1056
01:56:20,724 --> 01:56:23,893
Evy, no! Get out of here!

1057
01:56:24,227 --> 01:56:26,062
Just get out of here!

1058
01:56:26,855 --> 01:56:27,938
No!

1059
01:56:32,402 --> 01:56:33,527
Mom!

1060
01:56:46,917 --> 01:56:48,042
Hang on, Rick!

1061
01:56:51,922 --> 01:56:53,547
(SCREAMS)

1062
01:56:58,512 --> 01:57:00,054
Anck-su-namun!

1063
01:57:00,847 --> 01:57:03,766
HELP ME!

1064
01:57:04,726 --> 01:57:07,812
-No!
-Anck-su-namun!

1065
01:57:12,234 --> 01:57:13,776
Anck-su-namun.

1066
01:57:30,252 --> 01:57:31,752
(Growling)

1067
01:57:35,674 --> 01:57:37,466
(Rumbling)

1068
01:57:38,468 --> 01:57:39,969
(GRUNTS)

1069
01:57:45,016 --> 01:57:46,767
(SCREAMS)

1070
01:57:48,812 --> 01:57:50,855
(Screaming)

1071
01:57:57,821 --> 01:57:58,988
Whoa!

1072
01:58:03,869 --> 01:58:05,327
Let's go up!

1073
01:58:24,890 --> 01:58:27,099
This whole damn place
is gonna get sucked up!

1074
01:58:27,184 --> 01:58:28,851
Let's move up! Go!

1075
01:58:42,199 --> 01:58:44,366
JONATHAN: Go, Alex! Come on! Come on!

1076
01:58:54,920 --> 01:58:56,712
Rick, we're trapped!

1077
01:59:04,221 --> 01:59:05,346
IZZY: Hey!

1078
01:59:08,600 --> 01:59:11,477
-Izzy!
-Come on! Get your butts moving!

1079
01:59:11,561 --> 01:59:13,771
Hurry up! Hurry up! l haven't got all day!

1080
01:59:18,193 --> 01:59:19,819
RICK: Go! You're next!

1081
01:59:26,034 --> 01:59:27,159
(GRUNTS)

1082
01:59:27,661 --> 01:59:29,161
RICK: Jonathan! Hold on!

1083
01:59:29,246 --> 01:59:32,373
-Pull him up! Pull him up!
-Pull up! Pull me up!

1084
01:59:34,835 --> 01:59:38,420
Wait! Wait! Let me down! Let me down!

1085
01:59:38,505 --> 01:59:41,924
-It's not worth your life, you idiot!
-Yes, it is! Yes, it is!

1086
01:59:44,636 --> 01:59:45,845
Right.

1087
01:59:51,852 --> 01:59:53,018
(Yelling)

1088
01:59:53,103 --> 01:59:55,938
Pull me up! Pull me up!

1089
02:00:10,954 --> 02:00:13,622
-Whoo! Whoo!
-Okay.

1090
02:00:14,124 --> 02:00:16,667
Yeah! O'Connell.

1091
02:00:16,751 --> 02:00:19,253
-You almost got me killed!
-At least you didn't get shot.

1092
02:00:20,297 --> 02:00:22,756
Izzy! Thank you!

1093
02:00:23,758 --> 02:00:25,134
Thank you!

1094
02:00:26,011 --> 02:00:27,344
Yes!

1095
02:00:29,097 --> 02:00:31,640
O'Connell, who the hell
you been messin' with this time?

1096
02:00:31,725 --> 02:00:33,475
Huh? Oh, you know, the usual.

1097
02:00:33,560 --> 02:00:35,769
Mummies, pygmies,

1098
02:00:36,479 --> 02:00:37,813
big bugs.

1099
02:00:47,824 --> 02:00:49,783
(Speaking Arabic)

1100
02:00:58,293 --> 02:01:00,336
(HORSE NEIGHING)

1101
02:01:07,052 --> 02:01:09,511
l thought l almost lost you there.

1102
02:01:10,013 --> 02:01:11,972
For a moment there, you did.

1103
02:01:13,266 --> 02:01:15,684
Would you like to know
what heaven looks like?

1104
02:01:17,145 --> 02:01:18,312
Later.

1105
02:01:22,317 --> 02:01:24,109
BOTH: Oh, please!

1106
02:01:24,444 --> 02:01:26,904
-That's half mine, you know.
-What?

1107
02:01:26,988 --> 02:01:29,365
-That's half mine.
-l have no idea what you're talking about.

1108
02:01:29,449 --> 02:01:32,534
What? You took my gold stick!
l know you took my gold stick!

1109
02:01:32,619 --> 02:01:36,789
l swear on the head of my wife,
l have no idea what you're talking about.

1110
02:01:36,873 --> 02:01:38,874
IZZY: You haven't... You ain't got a wife!

1111
02:01:38,959 --> 02:01:41,502
JONATHAN: l don't have
your gold stick either!

1112
02:04:22,497 --> 02:04:24,039
Forever

1113
02:04:32,132 --> 02:04:35,676
Forever may not be long enough

1114
02:04:35,760 --> 02:04:37,886
For my love

1115
02:04:41,558 --> 02:04:46,395
l have a will but I'm lost inside your time

1116
02:04:50,191 --> 02:04:53,819
lf you could would you come with me

1117
02:04:53,903 --> 02:04:56,780
To the other side

1118
02:04:58,950 --> 02:05:11,295
Forever may not be long enough

1119
02:05:11,379 --> 02:05:14,590
For this life

1120
02:05:15,592 --> 02:05:39,781
Forever

1121
02:05:43,536 --> 02:05:46,705
Forever may not be long enough

1122
02:05:46,789 --> 02:05:49,124
For you to know

1123
02:05:52,378 --> 02:05:55,714
Just how far l traveled
Just how far

1124
02:05:55,798 --> 02:05:58,508
l will go

1125
02:06:01,429 --> 02:06:04,264
Open your heart and everything

1126
02:06:04,349 --> 02:06:07,184
Will be all right

1127
02:06:10,271 --> 02:06:13,482
Open your heart, baby
Leave with me

1128
02:06:13,566 --> 02:06:17,527
Don't be afraid

1129
02:06:18,071 --> 02:06:33,669
Forever

1130
02:06:45,807 --> 02:06:48,976
Forever may not be long enough

1131
02:06:49,060 --> 02:06:51,061
For our love

1132
02:06:53,606 --> 02:07:09,830
Forever

1133
02:07:12,709 --> 02:07:24,469
Forever may not be long enough

1134
02:07:24,554 --> 02:07:27,389
It might be long enough