[CARNIVAL MUSIC PLAYING
OVER SPEAKERS]
[SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY]
[LOST BOYS WHOOPING]
[ALL SHOUTING]
MAN 1:
Come on.
MAN 2: Come on, man.
Come on, let him through. Come on.
Come on, hold him back, man,
hold him back, man. Back off, man.
I told you to stay off the boardwalk.
[CAROUSEL BELL RINGS
AND MUSIC STOPS]
[DAVID CHUCKLES]
Okay, boys, let's go.
You too, off the boardwalk.
[CAROUSEL BELL RINGS
AND MUSIC RESUMES]
[LOST BOY CHUCKLES]
[HIGH-PITCHED SCREECHING]
[YELLING]
[LOST BOYS WHOOPING
AND LAUGHING]
[GUARD SCREAMING]
[EASY-LISTENING MUSIC
PLAYING ON CAR RADIO]
SAM: Keep going.
LUCY: Hey, I like that song.
[MAN SPEAKING IN SPANISH ON RADIO]
SAM:
Keep going, Mom.
[CLASSICAL MUSIC PLAYING ON RADIO]
LUCY: Oh, how about this?
MICHAEL: Hang on.
MAN 1 [ON RADIO]:
I don't see any bogeymen or nasty guys.
[COUNTRY MUSIC PLAYING ON RADIO]
MICHAEL: Pretty cool, Mom, you know.
You wanna switch the dial?
[BLUES MUSIC PLAYING ON RADIO]
SAM: Oh, this jams.
MICHAEL: Quite right.
LUCY:
Gosh, you guys are rough.
MAN 2: His pain, discomfort, manipulation--
SAM: No, no.
[THE RASCALS' "GROOVIN"'
PLAYING ON RADIO]
MICHAEL:
No.
-Oh!
BOTH: Keep going.
Oh, wait, wait, wait. That's from my era.
[SINGING "GROOVIN"']
BOTH: Keep going.
-Keep going, okay.
[ECHO AND THE BUNNYMEN'S "PEOPLE
ARE STRANGE" PLAYING ON RADIO]
LUCY:
Hey, we're almost there.
Mom, what's that smell?
-Ah, that's the ocean air.
SAM: It smells like someone died.
LUCY:
Aw, honey.
Look, guys, I know the last year
hasn't been easy...
...but I think you're really gonna like
living in Santa Carla.
[PEOPLE CHEERING]
[INAUDIBLE DIALOGUE]
SAM: Mom, there's an amusement park
right on the beach.
Sam, tell those kids
to get something to eat.
-Is there any jobs around here?
-Nothing legal.
[ALL SCREAMING]
[PEOPLE SCREAMING]
[CHEERING]
[ALL SCREAMING]
[BRAKES SQUEAL]
Come on, Nanook.
[BARKS]
Dad? Dad?
-Looks like he's dead.
-No, he's just a deep sleeper.
lf he's dead, can we go back to Phoenix?
Playing dead.
And from what I heard,
doing a damn good job of it too.
Dad. Oh, Dad.
[GRANDPA CHUCKLING]
[DOOR CLOSES]
[FOOTSTEPS]
MICHAEL: This is a pretty cool place.
SAM: For The Texas Chain Saw Massacre.
MICHAEL:
Come on, Sam, give Mom a break.
SAM:
What's wrong with this picture?
There's no TV. Have you seen a TV?
I haven't seen a TV, Mike.
You know what it means
when there's no TV? No MTV.
Sammy, we're flat broke.
[NANOOK BARKING]
[HORSES WHINNYING]
Lucy, you're the only woman
I ever knew...
...who didn't improve her situation
by getting divorced.
Yeah, I know.
But a big legal battle wasn't gonna improve
anybody's situation.
You know, Dad,
we've all been through enough. You know.
Anyway, I was raised better than that.
Hey, ouch! My hair.
[LAUGHING]
SAM: Mom. Mom, you've gotta help me.
LUCY: Soon.
Hey, guys, no running in the house.
Talk about
The Texas Chain Saw Massacre.
GRANDPA:
Rules.
We've got some rules around here.
Second shelf is mine.
That's where I keep my root beers
and my double-thick Oreo cookies.
Nobody touches the second shelf but me.
Now, there's another rule around here,
and I want you to pay close attention.
Don't touch anything.
Everything is exactly
where I want it to be.
Hey, Grandpa, is it true that Santa Carla's
the murder capital of the world?
Well, there are some bad elements
around here.
Wait, let me get this straight.
Are you telling me we moved
to the murder capital of the world?
-Are you serious, Grandpa?
GRANDPA: Well, let me put it this way.
lf all the corpses buried around here
were to stand up all at once...
...we'd have
one hell of a population problem.
Great, Dad.
Now, on Wednesdays,
when the mailman brings the TV Guide...
...sometimes the address label
is curled up just a little like that.
Now, you'll be tempted to tear it off.
Don't.
You'll only wind up ripping the cover,
and I don't like that.
-And stay out of here.
-Wait, wait.
-You have a TV?
-No.
I just like to read the TV Guide.
Read the TV Guide, you don't need a TV.
[HIGH-PITCHED SCREECHING]
[LOST BOYS WHISPERING]
[ROCK MUSIC PLAYING IN DISTANCE]
[PEOPLE SCREAMING AND CHEERING]
[BAND PLAYING ROCK MUSIC]
[SINGING "I STILL BELIEVE"]
BOY:
Mom. Mom.
I can't find my mom.
What's the matter?
Are you lost?
[GROWLING]
Let's go in here and we can ask, okay?
Excuse me, I wonder if you could help us.
This boy is lost and we're wondering
if his mother might be in here.
MAX:
I don't really know.
-Well, if--
-Terry.
-I was so worried.
LUCY: Great.
-Don't run off like that.
-There you are.
MOTHER: Thank you.
-Thank you.
Bye, Terry.
Hey, we only come here
to watch one thing.
-Well done.
-No, thanks.
Well, on second thought....
I told you not to come in here anymore.
Wild kids.
Oh, they're just young.
We were that age, too, once.
Only they dress better. Bye-bye.
You have a generous nature.
I like that in a person.
-My name's Max.
-I'm Lucy.
-How are you?
-Hello.
-That's my dog, Thorn.
-Hi, Thorn.
Say hello, Thorn.
Well, how may I help you this evening?
We have it all. The best selection
of videotapes in Santa Carla.
No. Actually, I'm not looking for a tape.
What I need is....
-A job?
-Is a job.
Yeah. I look that needy, huh?
[CARNIVAL MUSIC
PLAYING OVER SPEAKERS]
SAM: So where are we going?
MICHAEL: Nowhere.
SAM: So, what's our rush?
You're chasing that girl, aren't you?
Come on, come on, admit it.
You're chasing her.
I'm at the mercy of your sex glands.
Sam, don't you have something better to do
than follow me around all night?
Yeah.
Actually, I do.
[INXS & JIMMY BARNES' "LAYING DOWN
THE LAW" PLAYING OVER SPEAKERS]
Got a problem, guys?
Just scoping your civilian wardrobe.
Pretty cool, huh?
For a fashion victim.
Listen, if you're looking
for the diet frozen-yogurt bar...
...it went out of business last summer.
Actually, I'm looking for
a Batman, Number 14.
-That's a very serious book, man.
-Only five in existence.
Four, actually.
I'm always looking out
for the other three.
Look. You can't put the Superman
Number 77s with the 200s.
They haven't even discovered
red kryptonite yet.
And you can't put the Number 98s
with the 300s.
Lori Lemaris hasn't even been introduced.
Where the hell are you from? Krypton?
Phoenix, actually.
But lucky me, we moved...
...here.
[SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY]
Take this.
-I don't like horror comics.
-You'll like this one, Mr. Phoenix.
It could save your life.
-Hey!
ALAN: Come back here!
EDGAR: Hey, let's go!
Hey, wait a minute! Come back here!
[ENGINES REVVING]
Come on, she stiffed you. Ha.
[SHELLY LAUGHING]
[GREG GROWLING]
[HIGH-PITCHED SCREECHING]
-What was that?
-What was what?
-I thought I heard something.
-Forget it.
[BOTH SCREAMING]
-Well, how do you like that baby, huh?
SAM: It's a beauty.
-Come on, let's get in.
-All right.
Hey, can I drive it on the way back?
Fat chance.
Nobody drives this baby but me.
[ENGINE STARTS]
Yeah.
You gotta let it warm up a little.
Hear that sound?
Just like a baby pussycat.
-Okay, let's go to town.
-All right.
[ENGINE STOPS]
[DOOR OPENS]
[DOOR CLOSES]
Are we having fun, or what?
-I thought we were going to town.
-That's as close to town as I like to get.
What a weirdo, man.
MAN 1:
It means you gotta bounce, man.
MAN 2: Did you see that?
Where did he come from?
Oh, he turned green.
ALAN: Notice anything unusual
about Santa Carla yet?
No, it's a pretty cool place.
-lf you're a Martian.
-Or a vampire.
Are you guys sniffing old newsprint
or something?
You think you really know
what's happening around here?
Well, I'll tell you something.
You don't know shit, buddy.
Yeah. You think we just work
in a comic-book store for our folks, huh?
-Actually, I thought it was a bakery.
-This is just our cover.
We're dedicated to a higher purpose.
We're fighters for truth, justice
and the American way.
Right.
Hey, man. Read this.
I told you I don't like horror comics.
Think of it more as a survival manual.
There's our number on the back.
And pray you never need to call us.
I'll pray...
...I never need to call you.
Sure.
[PEOPLE SCREAMING]
It looks great. Definitely.
Enjoy it, for sure.
-Thanks.
-Night.
BARKER:
Step right up, folks....
MICHAEL:
Excuse me.
All right, it won't hurt. It won't.
It's a rip-off.
MICHAEL:
Hi.
lf you want your ear pierced, I'll do it.
What's your name?
-Star.
-Oh, your folks too, huh?
-What do you mean?
-Ex-hippies.
I came this close to being called
Moonbeam or Moonchild.
Or something like that.
But Star's great. I like Star.
STAR:
Me too.
-I'm Michael.
-Michael. Michael's great. I like Michael.
-Wanna get something to eat?
-Okay.
Where are you going, Star?
For a ride. This is Michael.
-Let's go.
-Star.
You know where Hudson's Bluff is,
overlooking the point?
I can't beat your bike.
You don't have to beat me, Michael.
You just have to try and keep up.
We're going for a ride.
[CHEERING AND WHOOPING]
[LAUGHING]
[YELLS]
Whoo!
Come on!
Come on, Michael!
[PANTING]
-What the hell are you doing?
STAR: No!
Just you. Come on.
Just you.
Come on. Just you.
How far are you willing to go, Michael?
[LAUGHING AND WHOOPING]
PAUL: Hit the rock box, buddy.
STAR: Yeah.
[WAVES CRASHING]
Not bad, huh?
This was the hottest resort in Santa Carla
about 85 years ago.
Too bad they built it on the fault.
In 1906...
...when the big one hit San Francisco...
...the ground opened up
and this place took a header...
...right into the crack.
So now it's ours.
So check it out, Mikey.
[ALL LAUGHING]
Marko.
Food.
That's what I love about this place.
You ask, and then you get.
-Thank you.
-Yeah.
Appetizer.
You'll like it here, Michael.
LUCY:
Ten o'clock. Lights out.
-Did you brush your teeth?
-Uh-huh.
Okay, night-night, sweetheart.
-Mom?
-Uh-huh?
Oh.
Sorry.
You know, I can never sleep
with the closet door open either.
Not even a crack.
Sam, this is a terrible thing to admit,
but I think that...
...one of the reasons
I divorced your father...
...was because he never believed
in the closet monster.
[GRANDPA LAUGHING]
LUCY: Dad. Dad, you shouldn't
sneak up on people like that.
Brought you something
to dress up your room with, Sam.
How do you like that?
-Thanks, Grandpa.
-Dad, really. You shouldn't have.
Yeah. Lots more where he comes from.
-Good night, Sam.
SAM: Good night, Grandpa.
-Lights, Sam.
-As soon as I finish this comic, okay?
-Okay. Night-night, honey.
-Good night, Mom.
[DOOR CLOSES]
You're history, buddy.
Feeding time. Come and get it, boys.
PAUL: All right. Food time.
DWAYNE: All right.
Chinese. Good choice.
Over here, bud.
Guests first.
No. No, thanks.
You don't like rice?
Tell me, Michael, how could
a billion Chinese people be wrong?
[ALL SNICKERING]
Come on.
How are those maggots?
[ALL CHUCKLING]
Maggots, Michael.
You're eating maggots.
How do they taste?
[ALL LAUGHING]
Leave him alone.
DWAYNE:
Pretty sad. Pretty sad.
DAVID:
Sorry about that.
No hard feelings, huh?
No.
Why don't you try some noodles?
-They're worms.
-What do you mean, they're worms?
Don't eat--
They're only noodles, Michael.
PAUL:
Nice worms.
STAR: That's enough.
PAUL: Chill out, girl.
[WHISPERS]
Drink some of this, Michael.
Be one of us.
[CHANTING]
Michael, Michael.
-Don't. You don't have to, Michael.
PAUL: Take a chance.
-Michael. Take a chance.
-Michael.
[CHANTING]
Michael, Michael.
-Michael, Michael, Michael.
-It's blood.
-Yeah, sure. Blood.
PAUL: Michael, drink it.
Bravo.
[ALL CHEERING]
Give me a ride, Marko.
ALL [CHANTING]:
Michael, Michael, Michael....
You're one of us, bud.
Let the good times roll.
[ALL WHOOPING AND CHEERING]
Michael.
Michael. Michael.
[LAUGHS]
Perfect timing.
What's going on?
DAVID:
Michael wants to know what's going on.
[ALL CHUCKLING]
DAVID:
Marko?
What's going on?
I don't know. What's going on, Paul?
-Wait a minute, who wants to know?
-Michael wants to know.
I think we should let Michael know
what's going on.
PAUL:
Yeah.
Marko.
Good night, Michael. Bombs away.
Bottoms up, man. Whoa!
Come with us, Michael.
[ALL CHEERING AND LAUGHING]
Hey, Michael.
DAVID:
Michael Emerson!
Come on down!
MARKO: Come on, Michael.
PAUL: Come on.
DWAYNE: Hey, Michael.
PAUL: Way to go, Michael.
PAUL:
Welcome aboard, Michael.
-Fun, huh?
PAUL: How do you like it?
[TRAIN HORN BLARING]
Hold on!
Jesus Christ!
Yeah.
-Jesus Christ!
-Don't be scared, Michael.
[MARKO YELLS]
[YELLS]
Michael, you're one of us. Let go!
And do what?
You are one of us, Michael.
[MOUTHS]
What?
David!
MARKO: Michael, let go.
PAUL: Michael, let go.
DAVID:
Michael.
[LOST BOYS WHOOPING
AND SHOUTING]
DAVID:
Michael. Michael.
[GRUNTING]
[DAVID CHUCKLES]
[SCREAMING]
Mike, wake up.
It's Mom.
-Mom's home?
-No, on the phone, Mike.
-What time is it?
-It's 2:00.
Give me those sunglasses.
You need your sunglasses
to talk on the phone?
Are you freebasing?
Inquiring minds wanna know.
Ooh.
-Hello?
LUCY: Michael, are you still in bed?
No. I'm up.
Michael, would you do me a favor?
Max asked me to go to dinner with him
after work tonight.
-Would you stay home with Sam?
-Sam is old enough to stay by himself.
I don't need a babysitter, Mike.
Michael, you come home
in the middle of the night...
...you sleep all day.
I work all day. Sam is always alone.
It's been a long time
since somebody asked me to go to dinner.
I'd like to go. Okay?
Okay, Mom.
Thanks, honey. It's a real favor. Bye-bye.
[WIND CHIMES TINKLING]
Hey, anything around here
that might pass for an aftershave?
How about some Windex, Grandpa?
Yeah, yeah, let me try some of that.
Yeah.
You have a big date tonight?
Ah, ha-ha-ha.
Just going to drop by some
of my handiwork to the Widow Johnson.
What did you stuff for her? Mr. Johnson?
Yeah, well, I'll see you two guys later.
That wasn't funny, Mike.
[HORN HONKS
"LA CUCARACHA" OFF-KEY]
I'm gonna make you a sandwich.
Don't bother.
Lose the earring, Michael.
It's not you. It's definitely not you.
Piss off.
All you do is give attitude lately.
You watching too much Dynasty, bud?
What the hell...?
[HIGH-PITCHED SCREECHING]
[BARKING]
[LOST BOYS WHOOPING]
DAVID:
Michael, Michael.
[DAVID LAUGHING]
Michael, Michael, Michael....
No, Mike.
Mike, don't open the door. Mike!
Mike, don't.
What's going on, Mike?
Go take your bath.
[GRUNTING]
[COUGHS]
[CLARENCE "FROGMAN" HENRY'S
"AIN'T GOT NO HOME" PLAYING ON RADIO]
[SAM SINGING]
[MICHAEL PANTING]
[NANOOK BARKING]
[BANGING AND GROWLING]
[BANGING AND GROWLING STOP]
Mike?
Michael, are you there?
Nanook?
[MICHAEL GROANS]
SAM:
Michael?
Mike, what happened?
-Nanook.
-What about Nanook?
What did you do to my dog, asshole?
Nothing. I didn't hurt him.
He bit me. This is my blood.
Why did he bite you, Mike?
What did you do to him?
He was protecting you.
Look at your reflection in the mirror.
You're a creature of the night, Michael.
Just like out of a comic book.
You're a vampire, Michael.
My own brother,
a goddamn shit-sucking vampire.
You wait till Mom finds out, buddy.
Sammy, wait. Sam!
SAM: Stay back.
MICHAEL: Just let me talk--
Wait a minute. Sam!
[POUNDING ON DOOR]
Get away from me, Mike!
MICHAEL:
Sammy. Sammy, open the door.
You did the right thing by calling us.
Does your brother sleep a lot?
Yeah, all day.
ALAN: Does the sunlight freak him out?
-He wears sunglasses in the house.
EDGAR:
Bad breath? Long fingernails?
Yeah, his fingernails are a bit longer.
He always had bad breath, though.
He's a vampire, all right.
EDGAR:
All right, here's what you do.
Get yourself a good, sharp stake
and drive it right through his heart.
I can't do that. He's my brother.
ALAN:
Okay, we'll come over and do it for you.
-No.
-You better get yourself a garlic T-shirt.
Or it's your funeral.
[DIAL TONE HUMMING]
[MICHAEL GRUNTING]
[GLASS BREAKS]
[PHONE RINGS]
-Hello.
-Sam, is everything all right?
Mom, I think we have to have
a long talk about something.
Help!
LUCY: What's going on there?
SAM: Mom?
-Sam, I'm starting to get worried.
-Mom-- Uh-oh.
What's that noise? That's not Michael.
Why is he screaming like that?
-Now, we should stay calm.
-Calm? Calm about what?
-Nothing, nothing.
-Listen, just who's making that noise?
I can't talk about it on the phone.
It's Michael.
Don't listen to him, Mom.
He doesn't know what he's saying.
SAM: Ah!
-Shut up, Sam.
Mom! Help! He's coming to get me!
Oh, my God!
-Mom!
-Sam!
-He's gonna kill me!
-Honey, I'm coming.
SAM: No! No! Tell him to get away!
No! No! Mom!
Open up!
Stay back! Stay back!
Sammy, help me! Open up!
Help me! Sammy, open the window!
-You're a vampire! I knew it!
-I am not!
So, what are you, the Flying Nun?
I'm your brother, Sammy. Help me!
Sammy, open up!
Please.
Thank you, Sam.
We've gotta stick together, Sam.
We've gotta stick together, bro.
-What about Mom?
-Just don't tell her anything.
I don't know, Mike.
It's not like getting a D in school.
We're gonna work this out. I'm gonna
work this out. Trust me, okay?
LUCY: Sam.
-Okay.
Sam! Sam!
Sam. Sam, are you all right?
You had me scared to death.
I'm okay. I was reading a horror comic
and I thought I saw someone...
...out my window,
but I guess I got carried away.
You got carried away by a comic book?
It was a scary comic, Mom. I'm sorry.
You know, I've just about had it
with the both of you.
You know that?
What is this mess?
You spill milk all over
and don't even bother to clean it up?
SAM:
I didn't spill it.
I can't believe you people.
The refrigerator door's wide open.
Are you trying to refrigerate
the whole neighborhood?
You know, it's not fair.
I would like to have a personal life too.
-Where's Michael?
SAM: He went to bed early, Mom.
[HORN HONKS
"LA CUCARACHA" OFF-KEY]
Mom? Can I sleep in here
with you tonight?
In here? Are you sure you're all right?
I'm fine.
It was a real scary comic, that's all.
-Do you mind?
-No, I don't mind.
-Have you been eating pizza?
-No. Why?
Whew! You smell like garlic.
[WHIMPERING]
[GROWLING]
Who's there?
[DOG WHIMPERS]
Hello, Thorn.
Is that you, Thorn?
Is that you making all that noise?
[THORN BARKING]
[MOTORCYCLES APPROACHING]
[LOST BOYS WHOOPING]
Star.
[WAVES CRASHING]
[GLASS BREAKS]
I'm over here, Michael.
-What's happening to me, Star?
-Michael.
-Oh, Michael.
Michael, I can't tell you.
I don't know how to help you.
What's happening?
I can't. I can't.
[LOST BOYS LAUGHING
AND WHOOPING]
[LAUGHING AND WHOOPING STOPS]
Hi.
Hey, aren't we friends anymore?
-Sure.
-"Sure."
Does that mean we are, or...?
-We are.
Well, then let's act like friends.
Let's talk.
Michael, take off your glasses.
Michael, look at me.
-lf there's a girl--
-I'm tired, Mom.
-We could talk about--
-I'm tired.
We could talk about anything
you want to talk about.
I have more serious things on my mind
than girls and school. Things that--
Things I wouldn't understand?
[DOOR OPENS]
[DOOR CLOSES]
GRANDPA:
Eh....
Looks like I wasn't the only one
who got lucky last night.
[GRANDPA CHUCKLES]
SAM:
Did you take care of everything, Michael?
What's the wine for?
LUCY: My apology to Max
for running out on him last night...
...which, young man,
you should be making.
SAM:
Mom.
Honey, I better bring this up to the house
or somebody's just gonna take it.
SAM:
All right, I'll be here.
Hi, Thorn.
[BARKING]
Oh!
Sam. Sam.
Stop. Sam!
-Help, Sam!
-Mom!
God, no! Sam! Help, Sam!
No! No!
Sam, no!
SAM:
Mom!
Oh, my God!
Honey, get in the car. Get in the car.
Then dog started chasing my mom like the
Hounds of Hell in Vampires Everywhere.
We've been aware of some serious vampire
activity in this town for a long time.
Santa Carla has become a haven
for the undead.
As a matter of fact,
we're almost certain...
...that ghouls and werewolves
occupy high positions at City Hall.
Kill your brother. You'll feel better.
Look, guys,
my brother is not a bloodsucker.
Look, it says here
that if you kill the head vampire...
...all half-vampires will return to normal.
Guys, if my brother's a vampire,
believe me, he's only half.
Does your brother know
who the head vampire is?
No, I don't think so.
Then you'll have to kill him.
And if you don't...
...then we will.
This all started when my mom
went to work at Max's video store.
Max never comes in till after it's dark.
The dog who chased my mom
this morning was his.
And listen to this: "Vampires require
a daytime protector, a guardian...
...to watch over them as they sleep.
Fierce dogs, the Hounds of Hell,
are often employed for this purpose."
No shit.
Yeah? Well, what happens
if my mom is dating the head vampire?
You guys could nail him
and save Santa Carla.
Truth, justice,
the American way triumphs.
Thanks to you two.
We'll check out Max.
Sam.
Hey! Smells good. When do we eat?
I told Max 8:00.
Max? Are we gonna
have company again?
Again? Dad, you haven't had company
in this house...
...since Mom died eight years ago.
Right. Now we're gonna have
company again.
Michael, Max is coming to dinner.
I'd like you to meet him.
I can't, I have plans.
Michael.
You know, things are gonna change
around this house when school starts.
Hey.
How you doing?
You must be Michael, right?
And you must be Max.
Right. How are you?
Well, you're the man of the house...
...and I'm not coming in
until you invite me.
You're invited.
Thanks very much.
-Hello.
-Oh, hi. I didn't hear you come in.
Is it all right for the guest to see the food
before dinner?
You're thinking of the groom
not seeing the bride before the wedding.
Oh, yeah, I always get those confused.
-Thorn sends his apologies.
-Oh, well, tell him I'm walking again.
[BOTH LAUGHING]
He promises to behave if you come back.
Oh, well, that's so sweet.
SAM:
Mom?
These are my dinner guests.
Edgar and Alan, the Frog brothers.
Oh, I didn't know
you were having guests.
Mom, if we're in your way, we can go
eat some peanut butter in the kitchen.
No, there's plenty for everybody.
Max, this is my son Sam,
and Edgar and Alan Frog?
BOTH:
Mm-hm.
-Lucy, this looks terrific.
-I hope it tastes good.
Mmm. It tastes wonderful.
Mmm! Boy, somebody around here
has bad breath.
[NANOOK PANTING]
[NANOOK WHIMPERS]
Nanook, would you quit breathing on me?
Nanook, get upstairs. Go on.
You want some Parmesan cheese
on that?
Yeah, Sam. Thank you very much.
-Sam grated the cheese himself. My son.
MAX: Ah.
Another budding chef in the family.
[COUGHING]
Are you all right?
No. It's not cheese, it's garlic.
-You hate garlic, don't you?
-No, I like garlic. It's just a little much.
It's raw garlic.
Garlic? How did that happen?
Guys, he likes garlic.
LUCY:
Sorry.
Here. Quick, drink some water.
-Hey, wait a minute!
LUCY: Oh!
Sam, what's the matter with you?
-Does it burn?
-Burn? What are you, nuts?
It's freezing.
LUCY: Oh, look at your suit, Max.
And your pants.
-I'm so sorry. Gosh.
MAX: It's all right.
LUCY: Now what?
SAM: Must be a circuit breaker, Mom.
EDGAR: He's not glowing.
-I know. Hit the lights.
-Ah!
-Oh!
Sam, what has gotten into you tonight?
I think I know what's going on here.
-You do?
MAX: Yeah.
I know what you're thinking, Sam,
but you're wrong.
-I am?
-Yeah.
I'm not trying to replace your father.
Or steal your mother away from you.
I would just like to be your friend,
that's all.
Good night, Lucy.
-Thanks a lot.
-I'm sorry, Mom.
LUCY: Max, I'm so sorry. I mean,
nothing like this has ever happened.
Major mistake.
Our batting average isn't terrific, is it?
0 for 2.
You were so sweet to him just now.
I don't know what got into him.
He's not like that.
Well, kids Sam's age need discipline,
otherwise they run all over you.
He doesn't run over me.
Protecting mother.
Listen, let's try it once more.
Dinner, my house, tomorrow night.
-I'm cooking.
-Okay.
LUCY:
Bye.
[CARNIVAL MUSIC
PLAYING OVER SPEAKERS]
MARKO:
Hey, whoa!
Where is she?
[DAVID CHUCKLES]
Take it easy, Michael.
Where's Star, David?
Michael, if you ever
wanna see Star again...
...you better come with us now.
[RUN-D.M.C.'S "WALK THIS WAY"
PLAYING ON STEREO]
[LAUGHING AND CHATTERING]
[SURF NAZIS SINGING
"WALK THIS WAY"]
-Michael, over here.
PAUL: Go on, Michael.
You don't wanna miss this.
[DAVID LAUGHS]
DAVID:
Initiation's over, Michael.
Time to join the club.
[GROWLS]
[LOST BOYS LAUGHING]
Hi, Michael.
[HIGH-PITCHED SCREECHING]
[SURF NAZIS SCREAMING]
DAVID:
Michael.
-Michael.
-No!
[SCREAMS]
[DAVID CHUCKLES]
So.
Now you know what we are.
Now you know what you are.
You'll never grow old, Michael...
...and you'll never die.
But you must feed.
[LOST BOYS LAUGHING]
[CREAKING]
Ah! Ah!
I wish Grandpa would stop giving me
these stupid things.
-Ah!
-It's okay.
I know who I am now, Sam.
Don't kill me, Mike.
I'm basically a good kid,
so just don't kill me.
I can help you.
Just tell me who the head vampire is.
I thought it was Max, but I was wrong.
Just work with me, and I can help you.
You'll be okay.
STAR:
Michael. Michael.
It's that girl. Is she one of them?
-I have to talk to you. Can I come up?
-No.
You shut the window and lock your door.
[WIND HOWLS]
She's one of them!
And don't tell me it doesn't make her
a bad person, Mike.
You know where David took me tonight,
don't you, Star?
-Who's David?
-Yes, and it's my fault.
lf you hadn't met me,
if I hadn't liked you....
I tried to warn you.
It was that night in the cave, wasn't it?
That wasn't wine they gave me to drink.
It was blood.
That was David's blood.
You drank someone's blood?
Are you crazy?
I'm just like David now, Star.
No, you're not.
You're like Laddie and me.
-We're not one of them--
-Until you make your first kill.
Why didn't you kill me last night?
You were supposed to be my first.
That's what David wanted.
-But I couldn't, Michael.
-Why?
-Because you care so much about me?
-Yes, I do.
What are you doing here?
What do you want from me?
I wanted to tell you
that it's not too late for you.
But for me it gets harder and harder
to resist.
I'm weak.
Why did you come here tonight, Star?
I was hoping you'd help Laddie and me.
[CHUCKLING]
[WIND HOWLS]
Star!
Don't kill anybody
until we get back to you.
MICHAEL: What are you doing?
-I've got connections.
[BICYCLE BELL RINGS]
Okay. Where's Nosferatu?
-Who?
-The Prince of Darkness.
-The night crawler. The bloodsucker.
-El Vampiro.
Mike, they're here!
[TIRES SCREECHING]
Hey, Grandpa,
is it okay if we borrow your car?
Weapons check.
-I don't want you going down there.
-I'm going.
This isn't a comic book, Sammy.
These guys are brutal killers.
So are the Frog brothers.
EDGAR:
Check me.
Who would you rather go down there
with you? Them or me?
lf something happens, I'm not gonna
have the strength to protect you.
Well, this time I'll protect you, bud.
Even though you're a vampire,
you're still my brother.
Listen, just so you know...
...if you try to stop us
or vamp out in any way...
...then I'll stake you
without even thinking twice about it.
Chill out, Edgar.
Yeah. Come on.
Where did you say you met these guys?
EDGAR: Holy shit.
ALAN: Vampire hotel.
Here's one.
Come on, let's stake her, man.
Don't you touch her!
You stay away from her!
EDGAR: Come on.
Vampires have such rotten tempers.
Star.
The rest of them have gotta be around here
someplace. Let's find them.
-There must be something in the corner.
MICHAEL: Star.
EDGAR: Look up there, man.
You gotta look everywhere.
-I'm taking you out of here.
-No, take Laddie first. Please.
I feel a draft.
I think there's something up here.
EDGAR: Let's check it out, Sam.
ALAN: Come on.
EDGAR:
Let's go.
I'll be right back, Mike!
I hope.
EDGAR: Come on, Sam, let's go!
Move, Alan! Move!
[FLIES BUZZING]
ALAN:
Ah. Ugh. Ugh.
-Flies.
EDGAR: We're on the right trail.
Flies and the undead go together,
like bullets and guns.
Come on.
[SNIFFING]
What's that smell?
Vampires, my friend. Vampires.
[ALL COUGHING]
EDGAR:
Come on.
SAM:
It's freezing in here. Ah!
It looks like a dead end.
Let's head back.
They must have hidden the coffins
around here someplace.
SAM:
There's nothing here. Let's go, guys.
-Jesus!
-Aah!
[SAM YELLING]
I thought they were supposed to be
in coffins.
That's what this cave is.
It's one giant coffin.
Right now
they're at their most vulnerable.
ALAN:
Easy pickings.
Remember, you have to kill the leader.
EDGAR:
We don't know which one the leader is.
I guess we'll just have to kill them all.
Let's start with the little one.
First come, first staked.
What was that, a little vampire humor?
It wasn't funny.
Oh, my God.
No! Don't even.
Good night, bloodsucker.
SAM:
No!
[SCREAMING]
[ALL SCREAMING]
You're dead meat!
ALAN:
Let's get out of here! Let's go!
[ROARING]
SAM: Go! Get out of here!
Run! Go! Fast! Come on!
[SAM SCREAMING]
EDGAR:
Grab him! Get him into the light!
EDGAR: Get him into the sun!
Get him into the sunlight!
[SCREAMING]
Tonight.
SAM:
Mike, start the car!
Mike! Mike! Start the car.
Mike. Mike.
-We blew it, man. We lost it.
-Shut up.
We unraveled in the face of the enemy.
They pulled a mind-scramble on us.
-They opened their eyes and talked.
-I'll drive.
-We don't ride with vampires.
-Fine. Stay here.
-We do now.
-Yeah.
[ENGINE STARTS]
EDGAR:
Come on! Sam, let's get out of here.
Burn rubber.
[ALL SCREAMING]
[TIRES SCREECH]
Christ!
Burn rubber does not mean warp speed.
[NANOOK BARKING]
Cool it, Nanook.
-Your dog knows a flesh-eater.
-Take him outside, Sam.
Come on, Nanook.
Michael.
Do you know the rule
about filling up the car with gas...
...when you take it without asking?
No, Grandpa.
Well, now you do.
-We definitely blew Plan A.
-Time to activate Plan B.
SAM: What's Plan B?
-We don't have one.
We only have two and a half hours.
SAM:
Why?
The sun will go down.
They'll be looking for us.
Mom.
This is--
What are you doing with the bike?
I gotta tell you something.
It's real important. Shh.
-Santa Carla is crawling with vampires.
-Excuse me.
Mom, I'm serious.
Listen, Edgar staked one.
It was screaming and fizzing.
Look, there's evidence on my sweater.
-Mom, you gotta tell someone.
LUCY: Come on, honey.
-You gotta tell someone.
-This isn't funny.
I'm not kidding.
They're coming as soon as it gets dark.
Stop it. Right now. Just stop it.
-Mom--
-No, not another word.
I don't believe you're doing this.
I'm gonna see Max
and you're trying to ruin it.
No, I'm not.
There's nothing wrong with Max.
Why don't you want me to see--?
I'm not talking about Max, all right?
To hell with Max.
I'll deal with you later, young man.
-Mom.
-No.
SAM:
Guys, we're on our own.
Good. That's just the way we like it.
[BICYCLE BELL RINGS]
[SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY]
Grandpa?
The Widow Johnson called. She said
to pick her up at 7 instead of 8, okay?
We got a date tonight?
I guess so. She said not to be late.
Well, I better get cleaned up, then.
[HORN HONKS
"LA CUCARACHA" OFF-KEY]
EDGAR:
Go, let's go, come on.
Die, Mr. Vampire.
Go, come on, come on. Let's move.
They'll be coming for Laddie and me,
won't they?
They'll be coming for all of us.
-Laddie, wake up.
LADDIE: Hm?
[PEOPLE SCREAMING]
[YELLS]
[HIGH-PITCHED SCREECHING]
MAX: It's okay? Thank you.
LUCY: Oh, it's delicious.
[BARKING]
Oh!
Thorn, stop that.
[THORN GROWLING]
[LUCY LAUGHS]
What's the matter, Lucy?
Oh, just old memories coming back.
No, seriously.
Why are you so jumpy tonight?
No, well, it's something Sam--
He came into the store, and--
You know, it was just a kid's imagination,
I'm sure, but...
...he seemed so sincere, but--
-It's insane.
-Tell me. I promise not to laugh. Honest.
[NANOOK WHIMPERING]
EDGAR:
I think I should warn you all.
When a vampire buys it,
it's never a pretty sight.
No two bloodsuckers
go out the same way.
Some yell and scream. Some go quietly.
Some explode. Some implode.
But all will try to take you with them.
[HIGH-PITCHED SCREECHING]
[BARKING]
-Nanook. I left him outside.
EDGAR: Don't go out there. Stop him.
MICHAEL:
Sam!
EDGAR: Sam, stop. Sam, come back.
ALAN: No, wait.
-Sam. Come back.
-Sam.
Sam, you're in danger, man.
SAM:
Nanook.
Come on.
STAR: Michael!
ALAN: Come on, come back!
STAR: No.
ALAN: Come on back.
EDGAR: Michael, get back, man.
-Mike.
STAR:
Hurry! Michael, hurry!
Hurry, Michael.
Michael, they're coming!
Come on, hurry!
[HIGH-PITCHED SCREECHING]
Hurry up, man!
[ALL SHOUTING]
Come on, come on.
They're coming now!
Take them upstairs!
Go. Come on, move it, move it.
[DWAYNE YELLS]
[LAUGHING]
-I say we terminate them right now.
-Laddie, run!
-Hey!
ALAN: Aah!
[PAUL LAUGHS]
You're mine!
-You killed Marko!
-Yeah. You're next.
No. You're next.
Garlic don't work, boys.
Try the holy water, dead breath!
[SCREAMING]
[BOTH SCREAMING]
[NANOOK BARKING]
[SCREAMING]
[ROARS]
[BOTH SCREAMING]
Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
Mike. Mike.
Mike. Mike. Mike, wake up.
[SAM SCREAMING]
[DWAYNE LAUGHING]
[SCREAMS]
[DWAYNE GROANING]
[CHUCKLING]
-You missed, sucker.
-Only once, pal.
[SCREECHING]
[INXS & JIMMY BARNES' "GOOD TIMES"
PLAYING ON STEREO]
[SCREAMING]
[MUSIC STOPS]
Death by stereo.
Come on.
[WATER RUNNING]
What the hell?
Come on.
[YELLS]
[LAUGHING]
[HIGH-PITCHED SCREECHING]
[ALAN YELLS]
-Hey, hey, shh. It's me, it's me.
-Are you okay?
I nailed one of them
with a bow and arrow.
All right, Sam-o.
We trashed the one
that looks like Twisted Sister.
We totally annihilated
his night-stalking ass.
Well, Nanook helped a little.
SAM:
All right, Nanook.
EDGAR: Death to all vampires.
Maximum body count.
We are awesome monster-bashers.
-The meanest.
-The baddest.
[ALL SCREAMING]
[GROWLING]
Holy shit! It's the attack of Eddie Munster.
Get him.
Stop! Get away from him.
You just stay away from him.
He's just a little boy.
[GROWLING]
[DAVID YELLS]
[DAVID LAUGHS]
You afraid to face me, David?
Huh?
Come on.
DAVID:
I tried to make you immortal.
You tried to make me a killer!
[DAVID LAUGHING]
You are a killer.
[HISSES]
[BOTH GRUNTING]
My turn.
[HIGH-PITCHED SCREECHING]
Stop fighting me, Michael.
I don't want to kill you.
Join us.
Never.
It's too late. My blood is in your veins.
So is mine!
[BOTH YELLING]
[SCREAMING]
No!
Michael!
[GASPS]
SAM:
Mike!
MICHAEL: Don't let them see me like this.
-Michael.
Yeah.
MICHAEL:
Get away, Sam.
-Mike, what's wrong?
MICHAEL: I said, get away!
What's the big deal?
You destroyed the head vampire.
-It's all over.
MICHAEL: Nothing's changed.
He's right. I don't feel any different.
Then there's still one more.
LUCY:
Sam? Michael?
I'll handle Mom. Come on, go.
Don't let her see the bodies.
-Sam? Michael?
SAM: Mom?
-What is going on?
-What's happened?
-We have to have a heavy conversation.
-Where's Michael?
-What happened to your face?
-I think I can explain what's going on.
Remember the food fight Michael and I
got into last year?
EDGAR: This has nothing to do with
the food fight. I think I should cover this.
SAM: I think you should sit down.
LUCY: What happened to your face?
[FOOTSTEPS]
I don't want to hear another word from you
until I talk to Michael.
MAX:
I'm sorry, Lucy.
This is all my fault.
David and my boys misbehaved.
I told you, boys need a mother.
Max, what are you talking about?
I knew it. You're the head vampire.
Sam, don't start this again.
You're the secret
that David was protecting.
Mm-hm.
-Who's this?
-But you passed the test.
Don't ever invite a vampire
into your house, you silly boy.
It renders you powerless.
-Did you know that?
-Of course. Everyone knows that.
Has everyone gone crazy here?
What's the matter with all of you?
It was you I was after all along, Lucy.
What?
I knew that if I could get Sam and Michael
into the family...
...there's no way you could say no.
Where's Michael?
It was all going to be so perfect, Lucy.
[SCREAMING IN DISTANCE]
Just like one big happy family.
Your boys...
...and my boys.
Great. The bloodsucking Brady Bunch.
But I still want you, Lucy.
[ALL SCREAM]
[STAR GASPS]
I haven't changed my mind about that.
I didn't invite you this time, Max.
Michael.
[LAUGHS]
LUCY:
Michael, no!
[BOTH YELLING]
[LUCY SCREAMS]
Michael.
[YELLS]
[ALL YELLING]
-Don't you touch my mother.
-Sam, don't!
SAM:
Ah! Ow.
Damn it.
Don't fight, Lucy.
It's so much better if you don't fight.
Mom! Mom, don't!
Mom. Don't do it, Mom.
Mom, don't do it.
-Sam--
SAM: Mom, no.
-Mom, no! Mom!
LUCY: Sam!
SAM:
Mom!
[HORN HONKS
"LA CUCARACHA" OFF-KEY]
[CHOKING AND GROANING]
[MAX SCREAMING]
[ALL COUGHING]
[MAX GROWLING]
[GROWLING STOPS]
Jesus.
LUCY: Are you okay?
-Yeah. Yeah.
-Yeah, right.
-Yeah. We kicked their ass, man.
It's over.
Star! Star!
Laddie.
[NANOOK BARKING]
Is everybody okay?
Oh, Michael.
STAR: Are you okay?
LADDIE: Yes.
-Oh, Michael.
STAR: I was so scared.
LUCY:
Oh, my boys.
How much do you think
we should charge them for this?
Dad.
Dad?
Dad, are you all right?
The one thing about living in Santa Carla
I never could stomach:
All the damn vampires.
[REFRIGERATOR DOOR CLOSES]
[ENGLISH SDH]