Subtitles by explosiveskull
www.OpenSubtitles.org
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
Oh! I'm surprised you answered.
Am I interrupting something?
Hey, are you on an airplane?
Yeah. I'm coming home.
Babe. Why?
That trip was expensive.
Yeah. Trust me. I know it
was expensive.
But it's not really a honeymoon
when you're not there.
Yeah. I know. But I told you
I was going to meet you
in Sao Paulo in a
couple days, right?
Yeah. That was three days ago.
I'm sorry. Work's taking
longer than expected.
Look. I'm just calling you to let you know
that I'm coming home tonight. And you're
probably going to be busy,
so you don't have to worry about
- picking me up at the airport.
- Don't do that, Okay? You know that hurts.
Really?
So you hurting my feelings,
hurts you?
Miss, I'm not going
to tell you again-
- All large electronic devices must be turned off. Now.
- Donna. Come on.
Don't hang up. You said never
hang up angry.
Can I borrow your phone?
I hate to ask, but
my battery just died.
- Yeah. Sure. It's no problem. It happens to me all the time.
- Thanks.
You have such a
pretty wife, Benjy.
- I'm sorry. I don't think we actually ever met.
- No. We haven't met.
Don't worry.
Okay. So how do you
know who I am?
I know everyone who created the
code for Genesis 7.
- No. I'm sorry, you've got the wrong guy.
- Stay.
I don't want to have
to hurt you or Donna.
Who are you?
Today you'll make one
of two choices.
Either you give me the code for Genesis
7 and I'll give you ten million dollars
in a Swiss bank account and a one
way first-class ticket to Dubai.
You'll leave tonight and
start a new life.
Or if you don't give me the code to Genesis
7, and your wife dies in 45 minutes.
- Maybe less.
- Okay.
No, no, no. I get it.
I get it. This is all Donna's
idea of a sick joke.
- You know to get back to me...
- Yeah. You would think it's all about you, wouldn't you?
You're an Aries, right?
- Okay. I'm done. Give me my phone.
- That's not...
- I said give me my phone!
- I said keep your voice down if you want to keep your wife safe.
First off, Donna's not even
here. She's on a plane.
She's in the sky and the plane is set to
explode if you don't do everything I say.
He can't help you.
- But Homeland Security can. Let's just give them a call.
- Okay. Stop.
Look. You had me concerned at
first. Congratulations.
Well done. But-
I don't even have the code.
Okay. The code is at GioTech. And today's
a Sunday. Which means I can't even come in.
Yeah. It should be pretty
easy to get me in.
So why me? Huh? I mean, I'm only one of the
four project managers who worked on the code.
Three. Actually.
Your colleague Cliff with the wife and kid?
I went to him first.
Yeah.
He didn't choose wisely.
It could have been an accident.
They won't think that it's
an accident.
They won't think that Donna's
death is an accident.
When they investigate the
wreckage of that plane,
they will discover that all of
the evidence leads to you.
And they will even have a motive since
the two of you weren't getting along.
If you want my code, that's
between you and me.
But do not bring my wife
into this.
Oh, she's already in it.
La Vida Airlines Flight 12-24 is up in the
air going from Sao Paulo to Los Angeles.
Whether is stays up in the air,
it's up to you.
What do you even want
the code for?
You don't get to ask questions.
What's it gonna be,
Benjy? Make up your mind.
So-Cal Approach, this is La Vida
12-24 requesting timing for landing.
We've been circling for
almost an hour.
If I didn't know better, I
think you are having a
secret initiation rites
for a new captain.
La Vida
12-24, this is So-Cal Approach.
No hazing going on around here. You are
currently number twelve for approach.
La Vida 12-24.
What's you fuel situation?
We're around fifteen
thousand kilos.
Another hour of this...
stuff...
we'll fall like a brick.
Stand by
for priority clearance.
Roger, So-Cal Approach.
Thanks.
I'm impressed.
With my looks?
You made it through the entire
flight without cussing once.
I gotta watch my big mouth.
It's part of the reason
I'm stuck in this right seat.
Sir. Would you mind
taking a seat.
Miss, have a seat. Power down
your large electronics.
We're about to go in for landing.
I know it's been a frustrating flight.
I know you're tired. Please take your
seats. Fasten your seat belt, please.
Turn your phones off.
I appreciate that. Thank you so much.
Would you mind taking a seat
for me, please? Thank you.
there, please for me.
And you as well.
Buckle up.
Thank you.
If you can take a seat,
that would be great. Thank you.
Hey Miss, do you mind taking a
seat and buckle up? Thank you.
And if you wouldn't mind, please.
I'd appreciate that. Thank you.
Ladies and gentlemen, if I may
please have your attention.
I know it's been a long flight but
if you could please take a seats
as we've been cleared for
descent. Thank you.
Stewardess!
Yes.
That lavatory is foul.
I'm glad I don't have to go.
I'm kidding. If you'll just stay seated,
I'll get it cleaned up right away, okay?
Sir, if you'll kindly
take your seat.
I have 50-yard line seats at the Texas-UCLA
football game down at the Rose Bowl.
I'm so jealous.
I went to UCLA.
I've got money on Texas.
The game starts in five minutes.
Well, we'll be on the ground
soon, okay?
- Sir, if you will take you seat.
- Yeah, yeah.
Don't touch.
Yes.
We got a man down, officer.
God. No wonder with
all this circling we've been doing.
How are you feeling?
You okay?
Okay. We'll be
landing soon.
How are you feeling?
I'm on the ride of my life.
Excuse me.
I don't mind switching with her. Being by
the wings might help alleviate the nausea.
Are you sure? We'll be
landing soon.
We've been landing for an hour.
It's fine.
That's very sweet of you. If we
weren't descending I'd buy you a drink.
Come on, ma'am. You'll feel
better up here.
Alright. Just take a seat
right there for me. Okay. Right this way.
- Oh my God.
- Where's my twenty dollars?
Hi.
Thank you so much for
spotting me last night.
Yeah. I've never seen anyone
cry at a blackjack table.
I'm a sore loser.
Mm-hmm.
I though you weren't leaving
until next week?
Yeah, well, it's not that fun
spending your honeymoon alone, so.
I don't think it's
supposed to be.
I hope that-
I hope that you don't think that
last night I was trying...
Don't. Don't worry.
Women with wedding rings
aren't my thing.
Besides, I have a sugar mama
I'm not about to cheat on.
- Oh! Okay.
- I was just trying to keep you out of much trouble as possible.
Oh, God. What kind of trouble
are we talking about?
You got really drunk
playing craps.
Security got mad.
I took you to your room.
And left.
I'm so sorry. This is really humiliating.
I never do anything like this.
- Kurt.
- Kurt. Right. I'm Donna.
And your husband is Benjy.
Wow. I do not shut up when I'm
taking tequila shots apparently.
They were actually Jäger shots.
Oh, please stop.
This is horrible.
Well, sometimes it's easier to talk
to a stranger than it is to a friend.
For what it's worth, I don't
really consider you a stranger.
You saw me vomit.
To friendship.
God. What a zoo.
I should have never agreed to switch
days with Donald.
Donald switches schedules faster
than he switches boyfriends.
Hey, I thought we were
out of soda.
We are now.
Cheers.
La Vida 12-24, descend and
maintain twelve thousand.
Expect vectors for
ILS seven left in four minutes.
So-Cal Approach, La Vida 12-24
leaving flight level 2-0-0
for twelve thousand expect
vectors in four.
Ladies and gentlemen, we've been
cleared for final descent to LAX.
Currently at LAX the weather is
98 degrees with winds of 12 knots.
We enjoyed having you on board.
Thank you for your patience.
Expecting a bumpy approach into LAX,
so keep those seat belts fastened.
Want to do the honors?
You know it's what I live for.
Ladies and gentlemen,
as we're starting our descent to
LAX, please make sure that
your seat backs and tray tables are
on their full and upright position.
Also, turn off all large electronic
devices and make sure your phones
are in airplane mode until we
touch down. Thank you.
So your husband.
You love the guy?
Yeah. Yeah I do.
That's why I have to
divorce him.
One down, 19 to go. Let's move that
traffic before wind picks up again.
Nancy talked me into having
dinner with her later.
The drama queen who works
for Columbia?
Come with. I'll buy.
No way. We're going back to the hotel
and I'm going to have a long hot bath.
With the new captain?
You've been checking him out ever
since pre-board in Sao Paulo.
- Have not.
- Have too.
Hey if you don't want him, I'll gladly...
Does no one follow
rules anymore?
Everyone, this is a friendly
reminder that all phones and
electronic devices should be
turned off at this time.
Thank you.
I don't think that's a phone.
- Alexis, sit back down.
- I'm fine. I'm fine.
What?
- What did you find?
- Shh.
Play me for the captain.
Alexis, what is
that thing?
- Alexis, what is it?
- No, no. Shh.
Captain, don't land that plane.
Captain!
Alexis.
Captain, you have to hear this.
We're all going to get really
hurt if you land this plane.
Can't distract the captain when
he's trying to land.
- You know how may FAA regulations you broke?
- If there's a credible threat,
I can enter the flight deck under-
CAPTAIN: Quiet! Both of you.
Alexis, what is this?
Good afternoon,
Captain. If you land the plane, you die.
Before departing Sao Paulo, an
overriding mechanism
was attached to your plane's
stabilizer system.
Once the aircraft descends past
1,500 feet above ground level,
its guidance systems will be
programmed to malfunction.
This will also jam the transponder radar,
making you undetectable to other aircraft.
If the plane rises above 1,500
feet or falls below 500 feet,
ASL, the stabilizer system will
fail, severing the hydraulic lines
and making the craft
completely uncontrollable.
This will cause the plane to
break apart in mid-air,
killing everyone on board and
others on the ground.
If anyone gets off the plane,
I'll destroy it.
If anyone tries to get on the
plane, I'll destroy it.
I'm controlling the device
remotely with limited range.
If you fly out of a 20 mile
radius of LAX,
the device will lose my signal
and short-circuit the system.
I will disable the system
remotely once I get what I want.
What's the altitude?
- We just crossed 3,000 feet.
- You gotta pull up.
Captain?
So-Cal Approach, this is La Vida
12-24. We have a possible terrorist threat.
Possible?
We're below 2.500 feet.
Requesting clearance
to go around.
La Vida 12-24, please elaborate.
A flight attendant received a recording outlining
a detailed threat if we attempt to land.
Who gave the flight attendant
this recording?
We're 2,000 feet! Do something.
- Captain?
- Alexis, who gave it to you?
It was in the cart. Anyone could
have put it there. 1,800 feet!
So-Cal Approach, we once again
request permission-
By the time they give us
permission we could all be dead.
JC, what the hell are you doing?
La Vida 12-24, you do not
have clear airspace.
Traffic - two contacts. One in your
three o'clock ascending into your path.
The other in your five. Maintain
your current altitude.
Prepare for collision.
Oh my God! We're going to hit.
Alexis, get out of here and get
yourself strapped down.
La Vida 12-24, what are your
intentions, over?
Do it now.
- Sir, sit down!
- Hey!
Alert! We have a runaway aircraft
and a possible terrorist situation.
La Vida 12-24, make two-eighty heading
one-ninety and enter the transponder code
for your situation if you
are unable to speak.
Hey!
Everyone. Everyone take your brace
position. Heads down or heads forward.
Heads down or heads forward.
Get everybody away from...
Fly the plane.
Standard recovery.
Preventing yaw nose down.
Keep the nose down. Stabilize.
Come on.
Captain, we're almost at
1,500 feet.
That's the threshold the
terrorist warned us not to cross.
We stayed above the threshold.
Good thing I was
able to lift us up on time.
Now we got some time to figure
out what this thing really is.
Captain, why do you still
look so tense?
That's why.
We're losing systems
left and right.
La Vida 12-24, come in.
- La Vida 12-24...
- La Vida 12-24, we've veered 1,200.
La Vida 12-24,
not seeing your transponder.
Please go to one-two-one
point five.
One-two-one point five,
roger.
So-Cal, La Vida 12-24 on
one-two-one point five.
La Vida 12-24,
what's your current position?
So-Cal Approach, this is
La Vida 12-24.
All navigation and avionics have
failed except the com.
We don't know exactly
where we are.
But we have reason to believe
that the terrorist threat is real.
Have you made your
decision yet, Benjy?
Alright.
Wait!
Okay. I'll do it.
I'm in.
You got me.
I've finished my initial
interrogation, sir.
And in conclusion?
- Undecided.
- Undecided. Really?
Do you still think that
he's a threat to national security?
The boy's name is John Rogers,
who's on the no-fly list and
he's wanted in seven states.
And what is John Rogers
wanted for?
Armed robbery, physical
assault, arson, and kidnapping.
And you think little Johnny
here is responsible for all that?
Well, his name is on the list.
May I?
Ah.
It is indeed.
I think we can probably
release him.
Thank you, officer.
Thank you very much.
Well, come with me,
please.
This is why no one trusts
us anymore.
Yes, sir.
Wasting my time and yours confiscating
extra large tubes of toothpaste and
interrogating women
breastfeeding their babies.
Meanwhile, those who may
actually do us harm
are invited to our planes
with open arms.
- I give up.
- Yes, sir.
I mean, no, sir.
Obviously, don't.
Please.
- Agent Coleman?
- Who's asking?
My name is Belflor, sir. You're
needed in the traffic control.
What for? Two kids kissing on
the tarmac again?
We have a Rogue Baron.
In the red.
Let's go.
ATC is now under the authority
of Homeland Security.
Ground all outbound flights.
Divert incoming traffic to
Las Vegas and San Diego.
Los Angeles is now under
a red terror alert.
Santa Monica and Catalina
airports are calling in
the smaller planes
currently in the air,
but many are still out there.
It will take time.
Lots of recreational pilots in
the sky. It's Sunday, after all.
I don't care if it's Christmas and Santa's
test driving new reindeer. Bring them in.
- Will do.
- Does El Segundo have a bird?
Negative. The nearest F-18
is in San Diego.
But they're prepping for launch
and they should be within
Los Angeles air space
in twenty minutes.
We'll blow that plane out of the
sky before I let it crash into the
Federal Building or whatever
they have planned.
This is not going to be the West
Coast's version of 9/11.
The captain said they received a
terrorist threat onboard
the aircraft from a
recording device.
Michaels, has the airport or any
other plane received a similar threat?
There has been no reported activity
on any terrorist watch lists.
Who told you that, TSA? Those guys
have less sense than God gave Iraq.
I printed out the plane's
manifest.
There's 67 passengers, 2 pilots,
and 3 crew members.
Ouch. Times are no bueno for
La Vida Airlines.
- I need a complete background check on every soul on board.
- Yes, sir.
Can I speak to the Captain?
He's on radio now.
What's his name?
Khalib Safir.
(QUIETLY)
He's Middle Eastern.
Really? so am I.
You are?
No.
But if I was, would you
trust me any less?
No, sir.
Thank you.
La Vida 12-24.
Captain Safir,
this is Agent Coleman with
Homeland Security.
I hear you're having quite
the Sunday drive up there today.
I'd take a cruise in my '65
Corvette any day over this.
As soon as we get you home,
I'll let you take me for a spin.
Deal.
La Vida 12-24, we are clearing
the air space from Santa Monica to Malibu.
What's your current altitude?
So-Cal Approach, we are flying
a steady 1,000 feet.
Get down some more.
There are some cumulous clouds coming in.
Those combined with the Santa Ana winds
are gonna get too much for you up there.
- Copy that. Lowering altitude.
- That's not a good idea.
We can handle the air.
So-Cal Approach, per your instruction, we
are descending down to a steady 750 feet.
- Copy that.
- But... Captain?
If we were in different seats,
you would make the call.
But you're not.
Even if I know what
you're doing is wrong?
I'm just as capable as you.
JC. This is my plane.
Right.
Your plane.
Just stay above 500
feet in case the threat is real.
In case? Someone's managing to
jam our radar going in and out,
you still think
this threat isn't real?
Approach is just doing
their job, boys.
Can you play me that recording?
We need to record it for analysis
so we know what we're dealing with.
Will do. You're sure the air
ahead is clear?
Just stay along the beach. Don't head
out more than a mile towards the ocean.
There's some bad wind shear coming off of the
Pacific that you can't fly above right now.
We can't track anything.
Did we hit something?
We're okay. Just some
major turbulence.
- Why haven't we landed?
- We will.
You keep saying that but it
never happens.
Matthew!
No, no, no.
Oh my God. Oh my God.
Tilt his head up.
Oh my God. No, no,
no, no, no, no.
- What happened?
- You hit your head. You may have a concussion.
Is there a first aid kit and
some towels to wipe up the blood?
Yeah.
Are we on the ground?
No. No. No,
we haven't landed.
- My God. Why didn't I stay in Brazil?
- Here.
Frankie!
Help!
Hold this.
Careful. Careful. Careful.
- Careful. Careful. His ribs maybe broken.
- Alexis, help me!
Set him down!
We have to make sure he's as
comfortable as possible.
Okay. Over there!
No, he's going to roll off.
There's empty room in coach.
- Okay. I'm going to help you, ready?
- Yeah.
One. Two. Three.
Right here. It's going
to be okay. Okay?
Just hang on there.
Captain. Straight ahead.
Which way do we turn?
So-Cal Approach, I thought you
said this airspace was clear.
It is. What
do you see?
If they crash, there will be
less civilian casualties.
Except the lives on board.
A plane that size can't sustain airspeed
at that low altitude over the ocean.
If they fly against the heavy Pacific wind
currents, they hit too much shear. See?
I recommend that they stay over
the land if you want to keep them
at an altitude between
500 to 1,500 feet.
Is that really worth the risk?
To the people on that
plane it is.
Until otherwise, we're doing
everything we can to keep them alive.
- Coleman, if that plane...
- Michales.
Right now you're being as useful
as a pogo stick in quick sand.
I need you to be a knight,
not a ninny.
- Now help me find out what we're up against.
- Yes, sir.
La Vida 12-24, head
east at 120 degrees.
So-Cal, this is La Vida
12-24. On course now.
We need some help up in here!
Ladies and gentlemen, is there
anyone on board with medical training?
I can help with the basics.
I used to be an EMT.
Thank God. In my book that
qualifies you to do heart surgery.
- We need ice packs for him and the others.
- Okay.
- I got these.
- Thanks. Let me know if I can help in anyway.
Okay.
Hold on to this right here.
I don't think it's broken.
Just tilt your head back.
Then why does it feel like my face
is my balls and I just got kicked.
You're still bleeding a lot.
That's why.
Everyone, if you or someone beside you
is injured, please raise your hand.
Dammit, Khalib, I told you not
to fly at such a low altitude.
This discussion can wait.
Yeah, if we had discussed this in the first
place, we wouldn't--JC. You're not helping.
This plane would have crashed if
you didn't have my help.
Flight crew, I need an attendant
to report to the deck immediately.
What's wrong?
I'm going to help you calm down.
I don't need to calm down.
Come in.
- Yes, captain.
- Sit in the cockpit while
- JC steps out for a moment.
- I'm not stepping out.
- Step outside and drink some water.
- I'm not thirsty.
I need you to lower your level of stress.
You're no good to me angry.
You think this is angry?
Step outside and
cool down. Now.
Ladies and gentlemen, we are
experiencing technical
difficulties which are currently
being remedied.
I hope to have further updates
and information for you soon.
In the meantime, please
cooperate with the flight crew
and remain seated while we
handle the situation.
Thank you.
Wait. You're coming with me?
How am I supposed to get
you past security?
Yeah. I guess I can
sneak you in.
I don't sneak.
Hey Benjy. You forget
it's Sunday?
You know me. Just-
Work. Work. Work.
If only you'd been this dedicated
to your studies back at A&M.
I taught Benjy his first coding
course in college.
He'll never forgiven me for
giving him a B.
You teach at Texas A&M?
Benjy's one of our most
successful graduates.
Good thing you got that academics down.
'Cause UCLA is whipping your butt right now.
Careful. Those are fighting
words. And I've got claws.
What kind of ID would you like to see?
Driver's license, passport, Texas alumni card?
Driver's license, please.
Keep that A&M card away from me.
Not a Texas fan?
Not until you walked
in the door.
Okay, then.
Andy, thank you so much.
And we're just gonna be up in my
office, in case anything comes up.
Yeah. Sure.
Goodbye.
So-Cal to La
Vida 12-24. What is your position?
- May I respond?
- Please.
So-Cal, This is La Vida 12-24.
We're at an altitude of 900 feet.
We're coming up on
Pasadena at 240 degrees.
La Vida 12-24 stay on course and
wait for our direction.
We're going to turn you
back out to LAX.
You better have good words and not bad
breath in that mouth of yours, Michaels.
We got two verifiable hits on
the maintenance crew in Brazil.
Do you know what type of device
they put on the plane?
Well, right now we're working
with Sao Paulo authorities to get
- them in for questioning.
- I need to know what's on that plane now.
Are they still in a
secure pattern?
Taking it minute by
minute by minute.
We need to stop their roller coaster ride
long enough for the crew to search the plane.
Any luck with the recordings?
The feds say it could take weeks
to analyze and track the source.
If that device doesn't kill
them, an empty gas tank will.
How many kilos they got left?
Enough to keep them going
another fifty minutes.
Maybe.
But if they fly too low, they'll
burn right...
Screw me.
- What is it?
- How did I miss this?
- More aircrafts?
- La Vida 12-24, this is So-Cal.
Immediate twenty degrees south.
Away from the hills. I want as
much unblocked air as possible.
Flight team, prepare for
turbulence.
Strap in. We're in for
some chop.
Wouldn't it be better just to
take our chances and jump?
Quick. Quick.
Get to your seat now.
You're good.
You actually care.
I'm just doing what anybody
else would do.
Not anybody.
This wind is working against us.
- More power?
- Yeah.
Wait, that's too much.
Jesus, what's going on
out there?
Who's broadcasting that
aerial shot?
Is that coming from a
news chopper?
Didn't we issue a no-fly zone?
We did. All news stations
agreed to it.
Well somebody lied.
Jesus.
Power to the left.
Just a touch.
- Increasing the left engine to
stabilize. - We're either going
to fly into the city or this baby's
gonna drop. On my count. One, two, three!
Let's get some altitude.
Keep it controlled.
Turbulence around these
buildings is absurd.
My bag!
Leave it, Kurt!
- Leave it!
- Souvenirs.
La Vida 12-24. Now stable at
one thousand.
Men, you're doing a hell of
a job up there.
- Much better job than what we're doing for them down here.
- Sir. We're dealing with
a terrorist who hasn't told us who they
are, what they want, or how we'll even
know if they finally get it. Alright.
This is far from textbook.
If we are going to win this game we
need to find out what all the pieces are.
Captain, I need you to find out what's
been on that plane so we can get rid of it.
Come in.
Captain, it's getting messy out there.
Everyone keeps asking questions.
I don't know what to tell them.
Tell them what they need to know.
That a mechanical failure is...
That's a lie.
It's a lie but it will keep them
calm and in their seats.
You need to take mine.
What?
Where are you going?
Find out what this lunatic
put on the plane.
JC, you're in charge.
No, captain-
I don't think-You should
stay and I'll go, okay?
This is my plane.
I gotta find out what's
going on with it.
Okay. Then I'll come with you.
You know it's regulation to always
have two crew members in pit.
But captain, I don't think
that's a good idea.
Alexis, you heard the captain.
Respect his wishes.
Ladies and gentlemen,
I thank you for your cooperation
with the crew as we deal with
this unexpected minor
mechanical issue.
Mechanical issue?
I promise
we will resolve the issue
as soon as we can. And you
have my guarantee that
the crew and I will do everything we
can to get you on the ground safely.
And while we fix this issue,
please remain seated silently.
And request assistance from the crew only
when absolutely necessary. Thank you.
Hey. Hey.
Excuse me?
Excuse me? Do you
need some help?
I worked the war in Iraq and was
on the bomb-disposal team.
Before that I was a mechanic on
some B-52s in Louisiana.
I'm good with planes.
- Well this isn't a military plane.
- Right. Right. Right.
But I may be able of some assistance.
You know? Just in case.
I'd hate to think I could have
helped and I didn't.
Okay. I'll consider it.
Thanks.
What can I say, Nurse Nightingale?
You've inspired me to help my fellow man.
I see some very
nice work here.
And I see some very
sloppy work here.
This isn't easy. Okay?
- The code is divided into three different quant...
- Shhh!
You can transfer it onto this.
What do you want this
code for anyway?
Not your concern.
Well, since if the Genesis 7 gets in the
wrong hands it can literally end the world.
No matter. I'll still get my
100 million.
This is about cash?
You are doing all this
over some cash?
It's shocking what people will do for even
one percent of the kind of stash I rank in.
Oh. Benjly.
Look, it's your wife.
It's Donna?
- Come on-
- Work.
I'm okay. I'm not hurt.
I shouldn't have left the
way I did. I'm sorry.
Okay. Could I please
respond to her?
Just give me the code and you
can do anything you want.
Come on, you-God! At least give me
the chance to tell her that I love her.
Benjy? Is that you?
Amy?
What's wrong?
Cliff is dead.
And his family.
Amy.
How were they killed?
They were on their way to Santa
Barbara when their boat exploded.
- A bad fuel line or...
- Ooh.
I'm so sorry for your loss.
Who are you?
I'm Donna's friend.
Benjy and I were getting brunch
when he heard the news.
He's just here downloading somethings
so that he can work remotely.
What are you guys
downloading anyway?
It's actually just the
Mackenzie crap.
- That's not do for another month though.
- Yeah.
Benjy, you work too much.
Yeah.
I realize that. Now.
Well, you know, I just came to pick up
some of Cliff's things for his mom. So.
- Hurry up and get out of here.
- Okay.
You'll be alright.
Yes. Benjy.
Hurry up.
She seems like a nice girl.
It's no wonder that she was on the
team also who created Genesis 7.
Hmm.
I wonder if she would be interested
in cooperating with me if you mess up.
What's this for?
To keep me from getting fried when
handling the computer equipment.
I don't know what they may have
done down there.
Make sure this stays grounded.
So did you find out
what's malfunctioning?
It'll be okay.
JC? Open the door.
JC?
Did you find anything?
I took some pictures. Whatever is planted on there,
looks like it's using the plane
to charge its own.
JC? Open this door.
Open the door.
La Vida 12-24 this is Coleman.
Any luck with that jamming device?
That's a negative.
What did Captain Safir find?
Still searching the bay.
He left me in charge of
the flight deck.
JC, are you crazy?
The only reason why you and
everyone else on this plane
are still alive because of the
decisions I've made, not Khalib.
If it weren't for my quick thinking,
he would have tried to land this plane.
- He was just trying to do the right thing.
- But I did the right thing. Me.
As long as he's not on this
cockpit, I'm in charge.
Just those gnarly Santa Ana
winds acting up.
Dropping down a bit should
take care of it.
See?
Things are better already.
Why don't they just land?
Hey.
Why don't you tell us what's
really wrong or land the plane?
- What's the pro...
- Sir. Please go back to your seat.
Uh-oh.
The rats are about to
overtake the kitchen.
I want to know why the
captain is locked out of
- his own flight deck.
- Sir, this is official business.
- Please have...
- Don't. Don't bully me, buddy.
- I'm not bullying anyone.
- My wife's hurt.
And this plane has destroyed city
property and everyone's scared as hell.
- Like the captain has said, it is a mechanical issue.
- Bull.
I have a right to know.
Sir, please.
Go back to your seat.
Unless you want to explain to your beer-bellied
friends why a flight attendant from
West Hollywood broke your arm, I suggest
you go back to your seat and not hit me.
Now sir, please have a seat
and let the captain continue
his explanation.
I won't have violence
on my flight.
Just got a little congested.
That's all.
I won't hurt anyone.
Good.
Because we're in enough
trouble as it is.
You all deserve to know we
received a terrorist threat.
This plane will crash if
we try to land.
And why aren't you
flying the plane?
The terrorist is in there, isn't he?
He's one of the pilots.
My copilot and I just had a
misunderstanding, that is all.
What, he locked you out
of the cockpit?
What did you do to the
bottom of the plane?
I saw him go down there.
I saw him.
I have a feeling I know who the
terrorist on this plane is.
It isn't the first time someone
like you has put a flight at risk.
- Someone like me?
- Yeah, someone like you.
I knew as soon as I got on
board this plane and saw
what you looked like, this
flight was in trouble.
- This is getting out of control.
- Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
- Where are you going?
- I'm going to go do something. - KURT: Up there?
- Yeah. I'm going to take my chances.
- You'll just make it worse.
I'm American. Just like you.
Nah, man.
You ain't nothing like me.
- You ain't nothing...
- Hey Texas!
Knock it off.
You want to hit him, you're
going to have to hit me first.
- You're protecting him?
- I'm protecting all of us. Now sit down,
put your seat belt on, and
listen to our Captain.
- But-
- SHUT UP!
Everyone into your seats.
Now!
Just a little navigation error.
Diverting power from the main generator to
the battery to get the elevator back online.
- The captain should be in here.
- Hey. Hey.
You may be willing to put your
life in his hands, but I'm not.
You can't fly this alone.
I've got this. Alright. I've just got to lean
into the pivot to correct it like I did before.
Sir.
We have visual of the 757
heading into the Hollywood Hills.
- We are in position to shoot down the wing...
- Jesus Christ,
What is happening on that plane?
La Vida 12-24, this is Coleman.
You have ten seconds to redirect
your flight pattern or we are
taking invasive action.
We can correct it.
Turn 50 degrees to the left
and increase the throttle
when I say mark. Ready?
Uh. Yeah.
Three. Two. One. Mark.
JC, we'll discuss what happened
when we are on the ground.
And right now that's my number
one priority, getting home.
But I need your
cooperation.
No grudges.
No ulterior motive.
Otherwise whoever is behind this
has already won,
and these passengers will die
because you and I can't get along.
Khalib, I-
We'll discuss this when we land.
Sir, this is now a domestic terrorist
attack on United States soil.
The President has been informed and wants your
feedback whether or not to shoot it down.
Now, I would be remiss if I didn't tell
you that our estimates calculate minimal
civilian casualties if we
take action now.
Seventy two people.
That seems minimal.
It may be our only option.
Michaels.
Yes, sir.
How fast can you get me
on that plane?
I
mean, come on, really Kelly.
Do you even know what honest
hard working Americans are on board?
I mean, sources insist this
isn't a hostage situation but a mechanical...
- Let me call her.
- So this isn't a terrorist situation...
Come on. At
least let me text her back.
Listen.
I can't have her think
that I don't care.
Look. I need her to know that I
should have gone with her.
And I know that now.
...to protect us, and our entire country
- could be destroyed. I blame the President.
- Absolutely.
It's always his fault.
I mean, not the one coming in.
You remember
the plane that disappeared?
What are you doing?
They didn't have
enough peanuts.
They didn't have enough
peanuts. Alright. Back to you guys.
I will enter through
the cargo hold.
At your low altitude, there should
be no danger of pressurization loss.
It will just be windy as hell.
The doors will depart at the rate
of sixty knots on the ground.
How many of you are
coming on board?
Two. Myself and
a specialists gonna try and rewire the
circuitry to the stabilizer
system.
You know how to disable it?
My team analyzed the
photos captain Safir sent.
I'm not gonna lie. This is
going to be trickier than
trying to get a mule to
mate with a sheepdog.
When should we open the doors?
In two minutes our plane
should be aligned with yours.
Open a hatch and we'll
zip line over.
You need to slow to a
speed of 150 to 175.
That's too low. We'll burn right
through our fuel reserves.
Guys, we shouldn't be doing this.
The instructions were very clear-
no outside interference.
In about twenty minutes,
we'll have no more fuel and no plane.
Okay. Fine. I'll go down
and guide them in.
- I'll be right behind you.
- With that eye? No way.
Don't get too comfortable.
I'll be right back.
I can go by myself.
I'd love to pin all of our hopes
and dreams on you,
but I only have one pin left.
I'm all out of dreams.
Are you guys sure there's not another way?
We are breaking the rules.
Stop talking and start
walking.
Just try to keep it steady
and don't dump me out.
Although I wouldn't blame
you if you did.
We're in position!
Open the doors!
You got your seat belt on?
Yeah.
Tight?
I think so.
Make sure.
PTSD?
Huh?
Post traumatic stress disorder.
You're showing the symptoms.
- Is that obvious, huh?
- Do you have something you take for it?
- Do you need me to get your bag?
- No. No no no no no no. Just-
Just hold my hand.
That works best.
Do I have adequate
coverage to get a clean purchase?
The wall is clear!
Aim high so you
miss the baggage!
Move over! Both of you!
The hook is secure!
Come on! Let me call Donna!
You know she can call
off the rescue.
What do you want?
I obeyed all your rules.
Look! The transfer is
almost done.
Then you'll get paid.
I don't want to get paid.
I just want my wife!
Line is secure! I'm coming over!
Stop climbing!
It's not me.
The plane's climbing
on it's own.
Oh my God!
We broke the rules!
They warned us it was going to
happen, but we didn't listen.
- The planes have to be parallel for me to get over!
- It's not me.
You're going to
snap the line!
No! Not until they're in!
Everybody turn away! Don't look!
Deploying our landing gear to create
some drag and slow our ascent.
Why won't it stop?
Well?
Well, what? It didn't work.
Khalib, you okay?
How much damage did the
plane take from our hit?
The circuitry in both wings is so damaged.
We could short out any second.
There's only 800 pounds
of fuel left.
Do we have enough
for another shot?
No. Is LAX clear?
It's totally evacuated.
Escort us to the airport.
That way the casualties on the ground
will be minimized when this plays out.
And there's a chance some
of us will survive.
This is not over.
This is La Vida 12-24 setting
a course for LAX.
Make sure Alexis is okay.
And prepare the passengers.
Here's your damn code,
okay? Now just-
let the plane land.
What? What is it?
Is there something wrong?
You can't make it land?
Kurt, is there anybody that you want to
text or message? You can use my phone.
No, no, no. I got my own phone.
Thanks.
I can fix this.
I know I can.
Sit down.
Why won't you let me help?
You can help by having a seat and
letting the professionals handle this.
Whoa.
Alexis needs help.
Whoa. Whoa.
Sit down.
- Oh my God! Are you okay?
- Don't...
Don't ask me how I feel.
I'm not okay.
I told them. I told them
that this would happen.
But they didn't listen.
Why doesn't anyone ever
listen to me?
- Sir, I absolutely cannot. Now, sit down.
- Just give me ten seconds
to check it out.
What do you have to lose? Let me
get down there and take a look.
If you don't sit down
right now...
What could be more threatening than
me being on this plane right now?
What's the problem?
Oh. There's not a problem.
I'm just offering
a solution.
- Alexis, this...
- Oh. No, no, no.
What can you do?
Let me look what's going on in
the Avionics Bay.
I used to dismantle all
kinds of crap in Iraq
and I bet my life what's down
there is very similar.
Now, it maybe too complicated. I don't
know. But at least let me give it a shot.
Whoa, whoa, whoa. What do
you plan on doing with that?
I can either try to save the
plane or open a can of beans.
- Which do you prefer?
- Hurry up! It's this way.
- We can't have passengers in the restricted area.
- I'll be his escort.
We need captain's
approval.
Matthew, get off it already!
I just saw JC die in
front of me.
I tried to save him and I failed.
Now this man is offering to help us.
And you're saying he can't
because it's against FAA protocol?
Do you see anyone else
here offering to help?
I didn't think so.
Move!
I'm just trying to do
the right thing.
I know.
No, you don't. Because if we do
survive this, I'm fired.
Good news.
I think I can help.
Aah! Dammit!
There's too much internal
electrical damage.
What do you mean?
It means we're screwed.
- Where's Alexis?
- Get back to your seat.
Where's Alexis?
Get away from him!
Donna, that doesn't
belong to you.
Donna, what are
you doing?
Both of you. Back
to your seats.
There's a reason you were so
concerned with this bag.
You knew it was your way out if
something went wrong.
That's standard military issue.
Is that what this is?
Oh my God.
You're the terrorist.
Sir. Step back and have a seat
on the jump seat.
If I was a terrorist, then why
would I try to dismantle the device?
Sir. I suggest you don't say
another word until we land
the plane and the proper
authorities are involved.
But she stole from me!
Sir, sit down, okay?
And we can sort this all out.
Why?
So I can be the fall guy?
Matthew, quick, get the
extension cord so we can strap him down.
He's dangerous.
He can't be trusted.
Bitch!
Bullrush me and I'll slit
her fucking throat.
Let her go, man.
Don't do this.
Everybody out.
Now.
Now!
You.
You stay.
Come with me.
Come on.
That's good.
Come on. Stop.
- Open it.
- What?
At this altitude we don't have
to worry about pressurization.
Don't you think I
thought of that?
Now be a good girl. Turn around
and help me put that parachute on.
I didn't know you were
a dancer.
Come on.
You know about teamwork.
You're married, right?
Help me.
Middle strap.
Not bad.
How's that door coming?
Now Donna!
Hold on to me, tight!
You're coming with me!
Didn't you know?
- You're the ransom.
- You're not taking her!
Flight crew to flight deck.
Who opened the
emergency door?
And what got sucked into
the engine?
I think it was the terrorist
who put the device on the plane.
And also the only man that
could save us.
This was found in
his belongings.
Some kind of signal box.
Radar jamming
equipment.
I was sitting next to the
terrorist this whole time.
I held his hand.
Oh my God! What's wrong now?
We have only seven minutes left.
So, we can land the plane?
Not with those devices
still attached.
Those devices. They're rigged to
make us crash, right?
Yes! We've been over this.
So we just have to find a way
to crash this plane first.
You want to do what?
That overriding device isn't as
complicated as it appears.
Pull up the photos
I took earlier.
Looking at
them right now.
The overriding equipment is
powered by the aircraft
just like the equipment
on the plane.
The call lights, the water
heaters, USB ports.
Zoom in on the
right side of the first photo I took.
Look at the wires
that are attached.
They feed directly into a unit that
looks like a compressor of some kind.
Exactly.
Which means its only getting its power
by the aircraft and its generators.
Not the battery or the
back-up. If the device loses its
power source, it will go dead
and no longer able to carry out
the malfunction to cutting
the hydraulic lines.
Right now I'm only running on
a few pounds of fuel and one engine.
With my fuel gone, I will lose power
and have to initiate a glided landing.
But the motor from the right engine
will still be powering the generator,
which means the device
will be active and
initiate a malfunction once
I fall below 500 feet.
But if I no longer had that
engine to power the generators...
Then there would be no aircraft
power for the device to feed off of.
Is there anyway for you
to cut the engine?
No.
But you can.
I need the F-18 that's been
tailing us to shoot out the engine.
Prepare the cabin.
We're going home.
Why isn't it landing?
Thank you for your services.
Here's your payment as agreed.
What?
May I have my code, please?
Not until my wife is
safely on the ground.
Unforeseen errors have occurred. Now I
suggest you take this money and leave. Now.
Once they finish sifting through
the debris from that plane,
they're going to find out that
the code that cause the
malfunction was created by
B. Samuels of GioTech.
How?
While you were transferring
data onto my drive,
it was also transferring data
onto your system.
- My wife is still in the sky. The deal was she'd be on the...
- You can buy another one
with all the money that I'm giving you.
Now give me my drive.
Give me my drive.
Fine.
I'll take the deal.
May I?
Women in Dubai, huh?
You think they'll go for
a guy like me?
Give me my drive.
So this is ten million dollars
in a Swiss Bank Account.
How do I possibly know that
this is any good?
It activates with a simple code online. Which
I will give you once you give me my drive.
No.
You first.
Shall we?
Go ahead and boot this us.
And we can be...
Tell me how to save my wife!
I'm sorry.
She was dead before
we even started.
I'm sorry.
So-Cal Approach, I have
visual on LAX tarmac.
Will begin descent for an emergency
landing on Runway 2-5 left.
Roger that,
La Vida 12-24. How's your fuel?
Still a few drops to run on.
Khalib, do you know
what you're doing?
No. Do you?
The ammunition the F-18 carries is
about the size of a coke bottle.
Should only take a few rounds
to blow out the engine.
We've assured the pilot
is one of the finest Top Guns in the nation.
Targeting system is top-notch.
This could go downhill fast.
Everybody to the backside of the
plane. Come on. Let's go. Okay.
It wasn't a full flight so
there's plenty of space.
Away from the engines.
Where's Alexis?
So-Cal Approach, once we've lost
power, I'll switch to my cell
phone so we can still
communicate.
Confirmed.
Flight crew. Please prepare for
emergency landing.
Okay. Fasten your seat belts.
Strap yourselves in. Heads down. Knees up.
Heads down. Knees up.
Alexis!
I'll go get her.
Please. Please sit beside me.
If we're going to die, I want my
daughter to think I wasn't alone.
Target confirmed.
Will commence fire in fifteen seconds.
Alexis?
Alexis, where are you?
So-Cal Approach, I'm on glide
and on course.
- Alexis!
- Yeah. I'm back here.
- What are you doing?
- Donna, I'm so scared.
I know. Me too.
But we have to sit down.
10, 9, 8, 7, 6...
I don't know how I'm
going to do this.
Just don't think about it.
Come on. Come on.
Will you help me?
- Yeah.
- Okay. I can count on you to cooperate?
Yeah. What do you need me to do?
Alexis.
Don't scream.
Fire!
It was never supposed
to go there.
We arranged to blow up
your hotel in Brazil,
but you shot that plan to hell when
you decided to leave early.
Now that you see how easy it
is for me to kill you,
let's discuss what will
keep you alive.
- The code for Genesis 7.
- The code is Benjy's. It's not mine!
But you're married,
right?
Fifty-fifty, huh?
So it's technically yours.
Donna! Donna!
Is that you?
- Donna, are you still on the plane?
- Benjy! Oh, Benjy!
Do you have the code
for Genesis 7?
Yeah. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Who wants it?
I should have never hesitated.
I know that now, okay?
All I want is you.
I know.
I know you do.
Tell him. Now.
Donna.
Listen, I love you.
I love you too, Benjy.
I couldn't bare to live
without you.
I know that now.
And that's why you have
to forgive me.
For what?
I'm going to let you save me.
Hold on tight!
What happened to Alexis?
It was her.
The terrorist was her.
Captain Khalib.
Agent Coleman.
You took your time.
Congratulations.
Sir.
I'm ashamed of my behavior
and I owe you an apology.
But I was right.
You're not like me.
You're better.
That's kind of you to say.
God. I need a drink before I see the brat.
Who has a good martini?
One of my favorite places
in Echo Park.
Well, come on.
I'll buy it for you.
You mean, you're going to
buy me a drink?
Oh no, honey.
After what we've been through,
- I'm going to buy you the whole damn bar.
- Come on.
Mmm.
Benjy!
I love you more than
everything.
You did it.
We did.
So, what do you want to
do now?
Start over.
Hey. Hey.
Listen.
I owe you a real honeymoon,
okay? I do. Together.
Just you and me. We can go anywhere
you want. Alright? Just tell me.
We can fly out tonight
if you want.
Let's just drive please.
Are you Hans Fensen?
Yeah.
Today you're going to
make one of two choices.
Subtitles by explosiveskull
www.OpenSubtitles.org
-== [ www.OpenSubtitles.org ] ==-