Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
Open this door right now.
Open this door.
Mary, get back.
No, Mary. No.
- No.
- No!
Don't...
don't play with fate boy.
Nothing good will come.
I know you more into cars, Jake,
but look at that right there.
That's a dang
Rembrandt right there.
- See?
- Oh yeah.
That's beautiful, Catfish.
Yeah.
Not really into guns, man.
More of a lover, not a fighter.
There you go.
That's the trouble with you.
Thinking you gel to choose.
Hey.
Where is Cobb?
I think he's fixing a forklift.
You hand checked that truck to
Iberia this morning, right?
Yeah. Gill, it's in the computer.
Don't want to hear about
anymore short loads.
Look, Mr. Gillespie, I got these
two loads that I'm trying to get
ready for freight, and then I got two
more that I'm trying to prep, man.
Jake, when I promoted
you to shift supervisor,
it's 'cause you said you could
handle the extra responsibility.
Now, if you can't, tell me.
'Cause it's my ass on the line.
Not yours.
Gill, we're good.
Hey.
It's my ass on the line, not yours.
That guy promoted me just to shovel
more of his work on me, ya know?
Just another day of
missing visiting hours.
That's all that means.
How is that red hot
mama of yours anyway?
That's gross.
When you talk about my
mom like that, it's weird.
You know, man, she got
another round of chemo,
and she'll be okay.
You bet she is.
She's gonna pull through.
All right, let's
quit farting around.
Back to work.
Yeah, I certainly
do apologize, sir.
No, no. Of course, we
appreciate your business.
This is just what we
call simple human error.
Thank you.
Mr. Gillespie, a moment please.
Check that out.
Hey, man, what's goin' on in there?
I heard another truck
come up short.
I'd say it's about curtains
for Gillespie this time.
I should say something.
I got to go do something.
I tell you what you do.
Call your ex.
- Olivia?
- Call Olivia, man.
Have her put in a
word with the hubby.
Maybe save Gillespie a job.
Go on, do it.
Man, it's been three years.
I know.
You and her, you're special.
Kevin's wife, man?
She can't save someone's job.
That's the stupidest idea.
All right.
Well, you asked.
- Hey, sorry to interrupt guys.
- Not a good time.
Mr. Gillespie, I just
need you to sign off...
Mr. Gillespie is no longer with us.
Put your paperwork on my desk.
No, Kevin.
Is this necessary?
At the office, it's Mr. Weese.
Go back to work.
- You know...
- It's not a good time, Jake!
Damn you, Kevin.
Way to make the tough
call there, boss man.
Excuse me, Anthony?
Hard working old man like that.
Hey, what the hell?
Let's get rid of 'em.
Somebody got to take the fall.
The buck got to stop somewhere.
Not with you.
Is this funny to you?
Well, it's not like
ha, ha funny, no.
How about joining 'em?
Would that be funny?
How about you try that?
I'll go right to corporate.
Who I'm sure would love to hear about
your erratic behavior, frequent cat naps.
You push a button on a large machine,
and you hardly do that well.
So don't act like you're so special
that anyone would miss
you if you were gone.
They won't.
So, back to work.
There you go, man.
Pretty much done.
Come on.
Need a ride?
No, man. I'm good.
All right. But I won't
be offering forever now.
I'm all right, man.
Walking helps me, you
know, clear my head.
I don't know how you do
it walking all the time.
All right, man.
See ya later, Catfish.
Get a couple more shotgun
bumper stickers.
Later, boy.
Hey, who's sweet stang
is that outside?
Do I look like a valet to you?
- I saved you a seat.
- Hey, what's up boss?
Two beers.
You still drinking beer?
Hey, man, does a frog scratch
his ass before he farts?
- Here's to the life, huh?
- Yeah. Carry on.
Hey, grandpa.
Hey, hey, hey.
Watch out you.
Might have to take
you over my knee.
That'll be interesting.
Teach him some manners.
Honey, I tried.
You failed, but I
do crave discipline.
Maybe you should take
me over your knee.
Maybe.
She likes me.
Yeah, you think she
likes the old ones, huh?
No. Not the older ones,
the classy ones.
Hey, speaking of which, did
you see that GT out in the yard?
Oh, hell yeah.
Did you see that GT out there?
I'm sorry to break up the party.
Gander yonder right there.
Old man over there.
Yeah, thanks for bringing
the bad news, Catfish.
Always good to see ya.
I didn't know he was
gonna be here tonight.
Don't let it bring you down.
You didn't fire him.
That son of a bitch Kevin did.
That's gonna come back on him.
You know what goes
around comes around.
It's called karma, boy.
It just seems like
there's guys out there
that they can't even
fail if they try.
Uh-oh. Hey, Judy, bring
two of these, will ya?
Gonna need 'em.
We box bolts and
straps for a living.
That's what we do.
We take bolts and straps,
and we put 'em in a box.
Like, what kid wants to do
that when they grow up?
You gonna do other things.
You're still young.
Still young.
You know what, what do I have
to look forward to, Cobb?
I got my mom.
She's dying of cancer.
Then my brother...
he's calling me all the time
asking me to help him
pay these bills,
and I can't afford a car to walk...
I'm walking all around town
trying to get where I'm going.
I got the scum bucket of a boss
married to my ex-girlfriend.
It's like ever since I left
that girl, man, it's just like
the first domino in this
long line of bad decisions.
Things work out.
Like I say, you're still young.
Are you listening to me?
Yeah, I'm listening to you, man.
Why don't you listen
to me for a minute.
Hey, look at this.
You know what that is?
That's a court order.
Let me tell you a story.
The old man fall in love,
yeah with a younger girl.
I thought she loved me too.
We had a kid together.
I mean, I'm thinking wedding bells,
white picket fences, whew!
I guess she wasn't
thinking that way because
this is what love looks like, man.
That's a court order.
That says that I cannot come
within 500 yards of my own son.
My own son!
I mean, she can rot in hell,
but I would like to see my boy
now and again.
Yeah, you got problems, huh?
I tell you something
about the courts.
They gonna side with the woman
every time, don't matter if
she's a woman of your dreams or a
frigid cold, vindictive bitch.
Anyway, we all got problems, Jake.
Hey man.
I'm sorry about that.
I didn't know you had a kid.
That's all right.
Don't matter.
All I'm saying is we
all get dealt cards.
It's how you play 'em and man,
play yours better
than I played mine.
Hey, thanks man.
Hey, I'm a be right
back, all right?
Yeah. I'm gonna go
get some air myself.
Ow!
Hit me like that.
Hey, Gill.
Look man, I'm sorry about the
way things went down today.
It's not so bad, kid.
Don't worry about it.
Hell, he give me a
second chance at life.
And after all, a man my age
should have no problem
finding another job.
Well, with the job market being
in such good shape and all...
as am I.
Plus with my generous
severance package,
future's looking
pretty damn bright.
I guess I should be
thanking you, Jake.
That what you come over here for?
So as I could thank ya?
Yeah, I was just... sorry.
Hey boy, brought you
something to ease the pain.
I hope you noticed that
I tried to stick up for
you back there today.
Yeah, but Weese has had
a bean up his butt
about me from the start.
What is that?
It's just some ugly old thing
my daddy give me as a boy.
I should've got rid of
it a long time ago.
- It's a monkey's paw.
- What?
Monkey's paw.
My dad said it'll do
magic if you want it to.
Hey, monkey magic?
Some kind of hoodoo?
I never would've taken
you as an obeah, man.
A little too pale.
Tell you honestly, I'm
not sure what it is.
But I tell you this, my daddy
said it could take hold of
a man's life, move
the pieces around.
Just gets passed on from
one person to the next
bending a man's fate
to his own will,
giving him whatever he wants.
How?
How does it work?
Three bones.
Three good wishes that
only his owner can ask.
You ever see 'em actually
work... the wishes?
Of course.
I wished for eternal good looks.
Go ahead.
Give it a shot.
All right.
Won't be too hard.
I wish for that
bitching GT outside.
All right.
Felt good.
You guys feel that?
It's my turn.
No.
It's his now.
Won't work for no one else until
he finishes his three bones.
I can't.
It's yours.
It's, you know, from
your dad and all.
No.
It's yours now.
Just an old trinket anyhow.
Doing me a favor getting
that thing out of my sight.
Consider it a peace treaty.
No hard feelings.
No hard feelings, boy.
Hey!
Still here.
Man, she is pretty.
Whose is that?
Look at that.
Whoa.
Come on, man. Let's go.
I'm getting tired.
How about that?
Damn!
Damn, Jake!
Keys are in it.
Look for yourself!
Whoa, how about that?
That thing works!
Come on, man.
You know that's a coincidence.
Maybe.
Man, come on, baby!
Car's not in the driveway.
I don't think she's home.
Exactly what was the plan here?
What do you figure you gonna
drive up and sweep her off her
feet, drive off into the
sunset just the three of us?
You ready to go?
I'm ready to go.
No, no.
Hold on.
Just so it shouldn't
be a total loss.
Cobb, what are you doing?
Just stay in the car, Jake.
Don't get your panties in a twist.
- Get back in the car!
- That's all right.
I'm just gonna...
I'm gonna leave a message
on the little car right now.
This is our boss' house!
Seriously, stop!
Don't do that.
Don't ever do that.
Come on, man.
Look, we got to go, all right?
All right, but don't forget.
You mess with the Cobb,
you get the corn.
Huh?
Nasty drunk, you know that?
Uh-oh.
What's going on, Jake?
Hey, Olivia.
Kevin's not home.
A little late for stopping
by don't ya think?
Is it?
Sorry.
I don't have my phone on me.
- You drunk?
- No. You know Tony?
He works at the factory.
Hi Tony.
Who's car?
That's mine.
- You have a car now?
- Yeah.
I wished for it.
Okay.
Hey, Olivia...
What part of this
don't you understand?
Where is Kevin at
this time of night?
Shouldn't he be home?
He's prepping for the
fundraiser at St. Luke's.
But I just drove by there,
and they're all closed up,
so I will be expecting
him back shortly.
Why are you looking for him?
I'm...
here for you.
Yeah, that's one thing
you've never been.
That's really mean
and really not nice.
I'm married, Jake.
Too little, too late.
Says who?
Me.
Go on. Go home
before Kevin gets home
and fires your ass.
Night, Tony.
Hey.
Gosh, she's really pretty.
She's kind of a fetching
girl, ain't she?
See the way she look at you?
I think you got a shot.
You think you got a shot with her?
What are you doing with that knife, Cobb?
Just gonna twist his titties, that's all.
Just gonna break his
chops a little.
Yeah, it didn't seem like you
were breaking chops, man.
What did it look like?
I don't know.
Looks like you were
losing your mind a
little bit, that's what.
Hey man, I'm not the one making
wishes on a monkey's paw, am I?
- Maybe I am...
- I'm sorry about that.
Watch it!
Cobb.
Hey.
- Dude, help me.
- What's that?
Hey, buddy.
Cobb?
I'm gonna call for help.
Hey, man.
I wish you weren't dead.
Help!
Oh my lord.
911 operator. What's
your emergency?
Hell on earth, sister.
I need an ambulance fast
as you can, all right?
Where you located?
I'm a ways out on
I-10 near Mettery.
Stay calm. Go ahead and
tell me what happened.
I didn't see a damn thing.
I don't know.
I just... I was driving along
on the road and then I just
stopped, and I saw him
and I think this fella's dead.
I don't know.
You need to come now!
Yes!
I told you!
I don't know what's going on.
Am I still dead?
Take hold of a man's life,
bending a man's fate,
giving him whatever he wants.
I got three brothers.
As we speak, one's locked up.
One's an MP.
One's a minor league
hockey forward.
My ex, we used to call him Bailey,
so you see I've had my fair
share of patching up noggins
over the years.
Still say you ought to go to the
hospital, but no one listens to me.
I don't feel nothing.
Tough stuff, huh?
Press it.
Poor thing.
Been through a trauma.
Your beard is all white.
I always did have a thing
for the old fellers.
Who's Abby?
Real nice.
Hey, Jamie.
Because I brought someone home.
It's not that interesting.
Okay, and I'm freaking
bored, all right?
Turns out, there wasn't much
to work with it anyway.
I'll call you back.
I think you should go home,
send you on back to
that Abby of yours.
Hey! Where you going with that?
That's my hoodie.
- Hey!
- Good morning, detective.
Good morning to you.
How you doing today?
- Very good, sir.
- Good.
Can I help you with something, sir?
Hey, son.
Let's you and me go fishing.
You've got about two minutes!
Response time around
here is pretty good!
You are not invited!
What'd you do to your face?
You know, actually I don't care!
Yes, hello? I need police, please.
- Look at you.
- Restraining order violation.
Growing up! Getting big!
You stay away from him!
You get off of my property now!
Take this.
Go and get in the car.
Huh?
No, ma'am.
He's not my husband.
Yes, he's driving away.
I'll stay on the phone with you.
Look, I'm just trying to
find my friend, all right?
C-O-B-B.
He's not in the ER.
Jake, boy.
You see Cobb?
I ain't seen him.
All right. Thank you.
I checked outside, where he
usually likes to kick a couple,
but I don't know.
Look, what do I look
like his mother, Catfish?
I'm sure he's fine.
All right.
Is it a crime that I asked?
You said that you
were working late.
This is not a suitable
time or the place.
No. I want to know.
Where were you?
I told you.
You're running around town...
Olivia!
Not now, Jake.
Is there something I can do?
Yeah, give me a do over.
This whole thing all of it.
Could you do that?
That's what I thought.
- Need a lift?
- No, I'm good.
That's it, right there.
Last straw, boy.
No more.
If a boy don't want to do nothing
the hard way, the hard way you do?
See you, Catfish.
Enjoy your weekend.
Jake.
Surprise.
I thought you were dead.
I believe I was.
That's impossible.
It's the paw, Jake.
Three wishes.
First the car, then me.
You wished this on me, didn't ya?
Didn't ya?
- No.
- Yeah, you did.
Cobb, no.
I didn't.
I want that third wish.
Gillespie said there's no wish.
It's the paw.
It's trash.
It's a trinket.
It's Olivia, isn't it?
What are you talking about?
Jake, you don't got to waste
that third wish on her.
You gonna get her
back without wishing.
I promise you.
I'll see you later...
alligator.
I hope you don't mind
the change of setting.
I don't mind, baby.
It's cozy.
Hello!
Cobb?
What the hell are you doing here?
Overtime?
No, no, no, no, no.
Cobb!
Cobb, untie me right now!
Cobb, get me out of here!
Cobb!
I pushed the button
on a large machine,
and I hardly do that too
good, but you know what?
I do it just good enough.
No, no, no.
Wait, wait, wait.
Listen to me!
Cobb!
Oh, stop acting like
you so special!
Ain't nobody gonna miss
you when you're gone!
No, no, wait, wait.
Listen to me.
Cobb, just listen to me, please.
Hey, Charlie.
Yeah, I know man.
I'm on my way.
Are you sure you're
all right there, Jake?
No, I'm fine.
You know, just some late
nights... a couple of...
a little bit of trouble at work.
That's all.
- There you go, baby.
- Thanks, Sandy.
It's not a layoff is it?
We can still carry
most of mom's bill,
but I'll still need some
help like we talked about.
Yeah. We're good.
It's not layoffs.
How's mom doing by the way?
You'd know if you
went and visited her.
Come on, Charlie.
Betty's doing fine, Jake.
I'm going to visit her.
All right?
When?
Yeah, you better get that.
Honey.
Babe.
- Hey.
- Hey, Jake.
Sorry to bother you.
I didn't know who else to call.
Are you all right?
Kevin didn't come home last night.
You didn't have to come
all the way down here.
You sounded pretty shaken up.
He has stayed out before,
but not this long.
Well, I'm sure he's
just cooling off.
To tell you the truth, it's the
cooling off that's the problem.
Me and him...
You and him what?
I don't even know anymore.
I need to get back to this.
Hey, let me buy you
a cup of coffee.
I know it's hard for
you to believe,
but he was really good to me
when we first started out.
He listened.
Sorry.
What were you saying?
Of course, he listened.
He was your AA sponsor.
He used to be present.
He wasn't afraid of the future,
and I needed that after you.
I wasn't afraid of the future.
No. You just never
even thought about it.
It's worse.
I got an idea.
Come on.
Come with me.
It's gonna be fun.
Afraid of the future, huh?
I knew you'd sit with me as
soon as I saw you walking there.
I'm sure you did.
Palms or cards?
What's your pleasure?
Cards.
I beg your pardon?
You have willingly entered
into the combination
of that what is dark.
Now you sit responsible
for the man with no soul.
He's upon your life.
You make him so he makes you.
You got your wish...
Olivia.
What did you do?
Now it's my turn.
There is no wish.
The car was already there,
Cobb, and you're not dead.
I want it, Jake.
I don't have it.
I mean, I went looking
for it, and I can't find it.
I'm sorry.
I can't help you.
My mom's cancer...
I'm helping my brother...
my brother is asking me
to help her pay her bills.
I don't know what broke inside you,
but something's broken, man.
I get it.
Man, I don't owe you a damn thing.
Yeah, you do.
How are we doing, Ms. Betty?
Better than Custer,
worst than I'd like.
My youngest supposed to visit
today, but we'll just see.
That sounds nice.
We'll be back to check
on you in a little bit.
Jake?
I'm a friend of your son.
He asked me to come by.
I'm sorry.
What for, doll?
I'm gonna put my hands
over your face now.
It's all right.
I been there.
Not so bad.
Jake?
Sandy, hey, where is she?
What happened?
It was something with her heart.
They're not quite sure.
Where's Charlie?
He's on his way back
from Baton Rouge.
I'm so sorry.
Can I see her?
They're not letting anybody in.
Where is she?
What'd they do with her?
- What'd they do with her?
- Jake!
Don't go crazy.
It was just her time!
Yeah.
Condolences.
What did you do?
Come see me.
We'll talk.
Where?
Cobb!
Was it you?
I did it for you, Jake.
That'll do.
You are one selfish
son of a bitch, Jake!
You got what you want.
Got your girl back.
Your mom is in peace.
It's my turn now!
- What do you want?
- I want my boy.
I want him to love me!
I want you to wish my
son back into my life!
I don't have it.
You better find it!
No.
Then what are you on?
I'm not on anything.
Okay.
So some old grump gives
you this... what was it?
- A paw,
- A paw?
Which is where now?
I threw it away.
A paw?
Says you get three wishes.
You wished for a car,
which you then steal?
- It's hard to explain.
- I'm doing all right, I think!
You steal it.
You wreck it.
Your buddy from work is chunked
in the brains, but you wish him
back to life, maybe, and now
he's threatening people you know
if you don't give
him your last wish!
And also you're not on drugs.
Did I leave anything out?
Yeah.
Sarcasm, Charlie.
Hell, yes, sarcasm!
I just lost my mother.
It sounds crazy.
Yeah.
Yeah, it does, Jake.
Guys, you need to call the police.
I know.
I think you guys need
to get out of town
until all this blows
over just for a bit.
JJ, what have you done?
Hey, we could take a few
days off up at the cabin.
Might be good for you, for
us after your mom and all.
Okay?
Okay.
Whatever you say.
Mr. Tilton?
Detective Margolis.
So, this man you say is
making threats against you.
When did you see him last?
This morning.
He assaulted me.
Got some bruises I see.
He also murdered my mother.
Yeah, about that, I spoke with
the attending over at Charity,
and they're saying heart failure.
When was the last time
you saw Kevin Weese?
What does this have
to do with anything?
You know he's dead?
Somebody crushed him in one
of your industrial presses
over at the supply
warehouse where you and he
and this Mr. Cobb all work.
Tony Cobb.
He did this, man.
You got to believe me.
How long have you been seeing
the late Mr. Weese's wife?
Where are you getting
your information?
- An anonymous tip.
- Tony Cobb.
You haven't denied it yet.
Tony Cobb is behind all this.
I remember you.
You were here the other morning.
You looked like you needed
someone to talk to.
What's on your mind?
Am I under arrest?
No.
No, not yet.
But if you leave town, that
could be a big problem.
You knew, didn't you?
What this thing did.
I knew it was bad luck.
I figured you deserved some.
Did you ever use it?
I never had the guts.
My daddy did, though.
We used to own 30 acres of land
just past the point there.
My dad and mom, my brother and me.
My brother hated it here
so he joined the Corp
as soon as he hit 18.
Mom wasn't happy about it, but
she loved him something fierce.
My daddy was so pissed off
so he rented out my brother's room
to make sure he never come home.
One night, a wanderer, weird
fella, he passes through port
and needs a place to stay and he
can't pay so he shows my daddy
a collection of trinkets
to barter with,
and among 'em was this
one little monkey's paw.
He tells him wish
on it three times,
give a man whatever he desires.
As a joke, my daddy wishes it
to help pay off his mortgage.
Didn't think nothing of it.
Traveler spends the night,
is gone before sun come
up the next morning.
Days later, we got word
my brother died in combat.
But then we get his
life insurance policy,
the exact price of the
mortgage to the penny.
My family was never
the same after that.
What happened with the
other two wishes?
Let's just say my mom
would've done anything to see
my brother's face again.
Don't play with fate, boy.
It did something to Cobb.
I don't know what.
He's different.
Psychotic.
Soulless?
Yeah.
I should've got rid of
that damn thing years ago.
Look, if I have this monkey's
paw and it works, right?
Well, then I can just
wish all this undone.
It'll give you what you ask for
but not the way you want it.
It takes from what's there
and spits it back darker.
Poison.
Don't bring anymore
misery upon yourself.
Don't look like it gone well
judging by the look back there.
Let's get out of here.
Feel better?
Mississippi?
Jackson, which was named
after Andrew Jackson.
Right. Nevada?
Carson City.
Hold on, baby.
Stay right here.
Are you Abby?
He came by here...
his face seemed different.
I don't know.
What happened to him?
Something bad.
Whatever it is, I feel responsible.
No. No.
You didn't make him what he is.
You see, Tony was always a bad egg.
I guess that's how I got in trouble
with him in the first place.
I liked bad eggs.
Now, I'm paying for it.
So what are you gonna do now?
I don't know.
That's what I'm
trying to figure out.
I should've listened.
No.
No!
Margolis.
The witness described
an older dude.
Big son of a bitch, about 6'2,
drives an old model 4 by 4.
Sounds familiar.
Think it might be that
Tony Cobb character, sir?
The warehouse is the connection.
I don't see Jake Tilton as this
mad ripper type, and the Weese
widow, she doesn't have
the physical strength.
So Cobb, he's our best bet.
Look, I'm gonna go track her down.
See if you can land eyes on Tilton.
Right. I'm on it.
You okay?
Yeah, sure.
Good 'cause I'm not.
Let's go.
Now the so-called police call
this a throw down piece.
Got a file number, got no paper.
You can have it if you need it,
just keep my name all the way out.
It's for self-defense
if that matters.
Sure.
I need to borrow your truck.
Yeah, yeah.
Been some bad, creepy blow
around here the last few day.
Boss Kevin, poor Gillie.
Gillespie?
Ya didn't hear?
Early tonight out by
the trailer of his.
Somebody done burn up
his car real good.
Worse for your health than smoking.
Yeah.
Thanks, Catfish.
I owe you one.
Jake, boy, so much for
lover, not a fighter, huh?
My brother may be a screw up,
but my woman is an absolute rock.
Just get the gas.
Look at this jerk.
I've seen that truck.
This can't be happening.
Charlie, hey. What's up?
- What does he drive?
- What?
Cobb. His car, what is it?
He drives an old car.
He got behind on his payments, and he
doesn't even have it anymore. Why?
Okay.
It's not him.
Never mind.
We're on our way to the cabin.
We thought it was him.
It's just some jackass
tailgating in a busted 4 by 4.
Oh!
Charlie!
Oh God!
There's a man following us.
He intends to harm us.
We need the authorities out here!
Well, I reckon I'm the
authorities around here, fella.
The real police!
Aggravation I do not need!
Hey!
Are you insane?
I'm gonna get fired!
You got to be out
of your damn mind!
Drunk driver, you almost... oh.
Almost?
I'm just gonna...
I'm just gonna go, all right?
Sandy.
Sandy!
- Charlie, what are you doing?
- This ends now.
Charlie!
- Run!
- No!
Sandy!
Jake!
Jake, I don't know what he's doing.
Stay back you son of a bitch!
Oh my God!
No! Please! No!
No!
Help.
I'll see you at Abby's house.
Be there.
Where are you?
I thought you might be here.
I want my lawyer.
I'm not taking you in,
not like that anyway.
So what then?
Have you spoken to Mr. Tilton?
No, but he didn't do it.
You weren't so sure the other day.
I am now.
It wasn't him.
Well, I believe you.
Do you know someone
named Anthony Cobb?
Oh, God.
Look, I want to take you to a
safe location, somewhere we can
keep our eyes on you, protect you.
- What about Jake?
- Him, too.
It's going to be all right.
Why is all this happening?
It's hard to say, but the awful
truth is bad things happen
all the time,
especially around here.
I just want to...
I just want to make sure
nothing happens to you
if you come with me, all right?
Okay.
Let me get my stuff.
All right.
No!
Hey!
Yeah, I'm talking to you!
What the hell is that?
You just put that lady
in the trash can, man.
I don't care where you're from.
That's bad manners.
So, here's what's gonna happen.
Once you let her out of that
trash can what you are gonna do,
my friend, I'm gonna teach
you a thing or two about
proper etiquette with the ladies.
Let's rock.
Let's roll.
Oh no!
No!
Is somebody there?
Hey, are you all right?
- Yeah.
- Where's Cobb?
He's inside.
I heard him and screaming.
He killed a cop, Jake.
Yeah, something bad
happened to him.
I don't really know
how to explain it.
What is that?
It's what started it.
Now, I'm gonna end it.
Abby.
You asked me to be
here, and here I am.
Please don't do anything.
Listen, just let her go.
Let her go.
My son!
Okay.
Is this what you want?
I brought it.
You want your wish,
but Tony, it ruins things, man.
It takes what you want,
and it ruins it just
like it ruined you.
You were right at the bar the
other night when you told me
that I didn't appreciate anything.
I was taking it all for granted.
My job. My family.
My friend.
Look around.
This is all my fault.
This isn't on anyone else.
This is on me, man.
My Son!
Okay.
No.
I wish my friend,
Tony Cobb...
had his soul back.
No!
Go inside!
Fast!
Tony, let me in!
Tony!
Open the door!
Open this door right now!
No!
Please don't!
Tony, don't. No.
This isn't you.
This is not you.
Abby.
I just want to take my boy fishing.
I am so...
so sorry.
Come on.
Stay with me, Jake.
Jake.
Where am I?
Everything's gonna
be all right, sir.
Take over a man's life.
The paw.
Where's the paw?
Sir, it's a part of your life.
No. You're not listening.
Where's the paw?
Sir, calm down.
No, no.
No!
Where's the paw?
You buckled up?
Yep.
Please rate this subtitle at www.osdb.link/352gk
Help other users to choose the best subtitles