Ghost Two, this is Echo One.
ETA, four minutes. Repeat, four minutes.
Intel confirmed. Nine hostiles, three marines.
Ghost Two, you are not to engage.
Alpha team is on its way.
No time.
- You guys ready to go home?
- Yeah.
- How do we get around them?
- We don't.
We go through 'em.
Ten hut! Look sharp, Marine.
As you were, gentlemen.
Triton.
Sir?
Outside. Ten minutes.
Yes, sir.
We've approached this from every angle.
The judge advocate's done hearing your case.
- What about an appeal?
- They're not accepting more appeals.
Bottom line is, you disobeyed a direct order.
You're being discharged.
You served your unit, your corps
and your country with honor, son.
Walk away with dignity.
Colonel,
I'm a marine.
One of the best. Remember that.
On behalf of a grateful nation
and the United States Marine Corps,
I thank you for your loyal service.
Thank you.
You're home.
- Are you all right?
- Yeah.
Yeah. I just...
I can't believe you're here.
You know, the hardest thing
about you leaving was not knowing.
You know?
Not knowing where you were,
not knowing if you're coming home,
not knowing if I'm gonna get that phone call
saying that you wouldn't be.
You married a marine, Kate.
I know it's not gonna be easy for you, John.
We'll figure it out together.
I'm home now, and I'm not going anywhere.
Good.
And speaking of that, are you sure
about starting this job tomorrow?
I think there's so many other things
you could be doing.
If I sat around here all day, I'd go insane.
I just want you to be happy, John.
I am happy.
- Come on.
- Where are we going?
To make me happy.
- I'll be right back.
- You got it, man.
- What?
You know, Scarface. Come on.
- Do it again.
- OK. You got it, man.
Wow. That's horrible.
- How you doing?
- Fine, sir.
Excuse me.
Everybody, down.
Everybody, on the ground now!
Ladies and gentlemen,
keep your heads down and your mouths shut.
I don't wanna see any eye contact.
I have severe intimacy issues and a gun,
so do yourselves a favor and don't look up.
What I want is on the other side of this door.
But that's gonna be tricky because...
it's bulletproof.
Here's how we're gonna do it.
Hi. Can I borrow you for a second?
- How you doing in there, sport?
- Oh, God, please!
Don't look at him. He can't help you.
Please! I have children!
I don't think he cares.
Please!
Fill it.
Get down.
Thank you.
Rome.
You gotta hit me. It's gotta look real.
For the cops.
That's real.
Well, the cops are coming.
I'd love to stay and chat, but I can't.
I apologize for that little outburst of anger.
That's really more for dramatic purposes
than anything else.
I hope that what I've done here today hasn't
forced you to have a negative opinion of me
or how you think I feel about the great state
of South Carolina, because I love it here.
I do.
I love the people.
Enjoy the rest of your day.
What? Too much?
OK.
We know how they got in here.
Once they're in,
they don't bother with any small stuff.
They just go right for the vault
with 12 million in diamonds in it -
the same diamonds that were delivered
just 24 hours ago.
What are the odds of that?
How did our guys know
they were gonna get so lucky today?
We could ask our friend on the floor
over there. I bet he knows.
I don't care.
Do you understand what I'm saying?
Really? See if you can understand this.
Is this what you do all day?
I had a Game Boy, but they took it.
Come on, man. This is a greatjob.
Good benefits, great money.
A couple, two, three years,
they move you to management.
- How long have you been working here?
- Nine years.
How come you're not in management?
Security.
We'll be right there.
Psycho ex-boyfriend on 12.
Rick, have you lost your mind?
This is my job.
Really? It doesn't look like a whorehouse.
Where's all the other whores?
Where's your pimp? You were with him.
That's why you didn't answer your phone.
Sir, could you please come with us?
Don't mess with me, pork chop.
You're causing a scene.
This is a scene? Wait till I tell Daddy
about the little whore he raised!
- Sir, I'm going to have to ask you to come...
- Ask me what?
Take a seat, flattop. I'll get to you in a second.
Now, listen to me...
Get your hands off me!
Why are you so angry?
You got the Drake.
Dude, let me call you back later.
Because I am trapped in an elevator
with a couple ofjackasses, that's why.
We kindly ask you to leave the premises, sir.
Thanks.
Seriously, just spitballing here.
You know, tell me if I'm close.
Right out of high school,
straight into the military,
realized you'd never be
all you thought you could be
and that's how you ended up as a rent-a-cop.
Tell me I'm wrong.
Whoa, whoa!
Wait a minute, wait a minute.
- The genie just tried to hit me!
- He shouldn't have done that.
You shouldn't have done that.
But he missed, and you're fine.
We deal with people like this every day
and sometimes you just gotta let things go.
Yeah? Well, you better
tell your boyfriend to back off.
Unfortunately for the genie,
this is not one of those times.
It's on now.
You really messed up. Somewhere, somehow,
somebody just got all this on video.
By the time you go to sleep tonight,
I'm gonna own this building.
And tomorrow...
don't be late,
'cause when you clock in,
you're fired!
Johnny.
A toast - to your first and last day on the job.
Yeah. About that...
Dude, I told you. Don't worry about it.
It's not the first time I've been suspended.
That's not it.
John, you'll find anotherjob.
You got all that training.
Training. Covert reconnaissance.
Close-quarter hand-to-hand combat.
Demolition. Not a high call in the workplace
for skills like that, Joe.
OK, but you're a smart guy.
You can do whatever you want.
You don't get it. It's not about work.
It's not about ajob.
Being a marine meant everything to me.
Now I go and get fired
from some bullshit security job.
Sorry.
I don't know what to do.
Look.
I'm not gonna try and pretend
I know what you're going through,
'cause I don't.
And your time as a marine,
yeah, it's over, and that sucks, man.
But your life's not over.
I mean, it's changing,
but you've got to learn to change with it.
Sometimes... sometimes it's good
to just take a step back
and see what you still have.
You know,
I think I'm gonna go home and see my wife.
Yeah. She's hot.
What happened today?
We made a lot of money.
In the vault. With the kid.
That kid showed that
he couldn't keep his mouth shut.
And Morgan? Blowing up that cop car?
He went a little overboard.
But in all fairness to Morgan,
I was firing an automatic weapon
at those cops.
Dead cops, all those witnesses...
Doesn't that pose a potential problem for us?
So does a prison term.
Bottom line is, we got away clean.
What's the matter, Angela?
Don't you trust me anymore?
Look at me.
That kid knew my name.
That's dangerous for all of us.
Baby, is there anything in these eyes
that makes you think I could ever hurt you?
- What?
- Forget what you did to our guy in the vault.
You killed two cops today
and that's a problem.
- Don't start with me.
- You arrogant bastard. You've lost control.
That's where you're wrong, my friend.
You see,
- I've gained control.
- Is that right?
You bet your ass that's right.
What's the matter with you, Rome?
Have you lost your mind?
- Have you forgotten who you're talking to?
- I know exactly who I'm talking to.
You see, I have the diamonds,
therefore I have the power.
You have no idea the level of hell
I can bring down on you.
Yeah, but you won't.
Not if you want to see these diamonds.
Tomorrow. Noon.
I get my diamonds, you get your money.
Listen.
About what happened at work today...
I'm not telling anybody.
Cool.
- Hi, baby.
- Hey.
- How was work?
- Fine.
Well?
What? What happened?
- Talk to me.
- Nothing.
Stuff.
They're hired to protect us.
But who will protect us from them?
Security guards out of control, tonight at 11.
Stuff. Like you throwing
a guy out of a window.
Yeah.
I thought my days of worrying about you
were over. What happened?
This isn't me.
You jumped into work
the minute you got back.
Kate, what was I supposed to do?
Come home, sit around?
- That's not me. I can't do that.
- I know you can't.
- What if we just took off?
- What?
Yeah. Just left.
Gone. Do something crazy. We'll get up
in the morning, we'll go somewhere.
- Where?
- I don't know where. Anywhere.
It doesn't matter. That's not the point.
I just... I've been thinking a lot about it.
- You have?
- Yeah.
What do you think? Just me and you.
I really wanna do this.
Come on. Say yes.
Say yes. John, say yes.
- Come on!
- OK, OK, yes, yes.
Hey, man, you're Lincoln Kennedy.
What are you doing here?
- I don't know what you're talking about, man.
- Come on, 72, I know it's you.
Husky Hall of Fame,
three consecutive Pro Bowls.
Man, you even started in a Super Bowl.
You didn't win,
but you started.
Come on, man. I know it's you.
Morgan.
Thanks, L.K.
Let's take a walk.
- Rock candy?
- Man, you know I hate rock candy.
Oh, that's right, because of that one time.
Yeah.
Let's walk it off. How'd you like
that Benz I hooked you up with?
Liked it? Shit. 24-valve V-8,
4MATIC all-wheel drive.
- What's not to like?
- If you liked that, you're gonna love this.
- What's it gonna be, a Mustang?
- Nah.
- A Jag?
- Better.
- Come on, man, tell me. What is it?
- Right there.
- Man, that's a minivan.
- Rome said inconspicuous.
Yeah, but how you gonna send a brother out
in a minivan?
Man, I'm a criminal, not a soccer mom.
Come on, big guy. CD, DVD. If you want, I'll
even have Johnny throw some spinners on it.
- Fuck you!
- Or not.
Maybe I'm not making myself clear.
You see, I am a black man.
- Yeah, I got that.
- OK. And that is a minivan.
Right.
Black men don't drive minivans, Frank.
They do now.
Morgan, the five of you
are never gonna fit in one of those.
Take the van. Nobody pays attention.
You guys can just disappear.
What do you say?
Keys are in it. Knock yourself out.
Mount Cedar.
I used to go to camp there.
God, I haven't thought about that
in a long time.
But the mountains are hours away.
Are you sure you don't wanna
just stop at the beach?
I think I've seen enough sand.
Besides, you're not the only one
with childhood memories of the mountains.
You never told me
that you went to Mount Cedar.
It wasn't Mount Cedar. Further up.
So, are you gonna tell me where?
It was just a place that my dad
used to take us when we were kids.
What did you guys do up there? Was it fun?
It was all right.
- Dad liked it.
- Why?
I guess it's 'cause he knew
it was far enough away
where nobody could hear
me and my brothers scream.
We gotta get some gas.
- You want anything?
- A Diet Coke.
OK.
- Nice butt.
- What?
Oh, man.
How you doing?
Cadillac man, huh?
Yeah.
What happens there, stays there.
What?
The Vegas sticker.
Oh, yeah. It's my brother's car.
He lives in Vegas.
You visit him much?
- Couple of times a year.
- Me too.
My mom lives there.
I just love it there, you know?
Especially downtown.
You ever go to the Olympus?
Not since they tore it down last year.
Oh, man.
Don't move.
Great.
Take the truck!
Come here! Bring her! Come here!
- Damn!
- John!
- Shut up!
- Get off of me! John!
- Where the hell did she come from?
- Do we kill her?
- No. We might need a hostage.
Get up!
John!
Morgan! Get in the truck.
Come out here.
Come on. Hang in there.
Keep pressure on that.
I'm gonna call for help.
Highway patrol, this is John Triton.
You have officers down at Manze's Gas.
Multiple assailants. Four men, one woman,
headed southbound in a black Navigator.
They have a hostage. It's my wife.
Kate Triton.
Married to John Triton.
Sergeant John Triton.
She married a marine.
What'd you marry him for? Benefits?
Settle down. Settle down.
You gotta be kidding me.
Cops.
That ain't the cops.
I hate cops.
And rock candy.
- Shoot him.
- No!
- Would somebody shoot this guy?
- What does it look like we're doing?
Missing.
Hey, slow down!
Hey!
Whoa!
No, no, no, no!
This guy's like the Terminator.
You murdering sons of bitches!
Shut her up and get her out of here.
You murderers!
Now, Angie, baby, I know you got a hair
trigger, but I said shut her up, not kill her.
We might need an insurance policy.
Get a rope and tie her up.
Put your hands together.
Front axle's history.
We're not going anywhere in this thing.
Now, you figured that out
all by yourself, huh?
Actually, I did, yeah.
- But, hey, you know what else I figured out?
- What's that?
That you're a trigger-happy nutjob
who belongs in a cage.
All right. We are monumentally screwed here
and the last thing I need is you two bickering
like a couple of little girls.
So as of right now, it's over. Are we clear?
Because if we're not, I give you my word,
I will absolutely shoot you myself.
What do we do now?
The way I see it, we got two options.
A - we stand here and try to kill each other,
but then no one gets paid
and someone gets dead,
or - B - we get out of the swamp,
make our drop and collect our dough.
And maybe it's just the greed talking,
but I'm sticking with B.
Yeah, well, I say we move,
'cause every cop in the state heard that blast.
We'll follow the swamp downstream.
- Through there?
- Yeah, through there.
The trees will give us cover from the air.
The swamp will slow down the cops.
- What shall we do with our insurance policy?
- Go to hell.
Angie, why'd you do that?
Now Morgan's gotta carry her.
Morgan's got...? Morgan's gotta do what?
- Watch out for crocodiles.
- What's the matter with you?
Ain't no crocodiles in South Carolina.
- Detective Van Buren.
- Sir.
- What have we got?
- Well, we got one deceased officer here
and another found seriously wounded there.
The guy who called in?
Is a John Triton. He's an ex-marine.
He's for real.
His description of the perps sounds like
the crew that hit the diamond store yesterday.
- Are the roadblocks up?
- Yes, sir.
Choppers and search teams are on their way.
So, what else do we know about these guys?
- They're sloppy.
- Unit Four, come in.
- Go ahead.
- We got a report of a multiple car accident
and shots fired five miles south of you.
The highway patrol car from your location
was involved. Check and advise.
I'm en route.
Detective Van Buren, Homicide.
I'm gonna assume you're John Triton.
They took my wife.
- That's a matter for law enforcement now.
- Listen.
I've seen them kill three people.
My wife will not be number four.
I can't give you permission to pursue.
I'm not asking for it.
You know, this whole area's tidal.
The way the water level changes, these guys
are going to be impossible to track.
- I can handle it.
- Triton.
I've seen what these guys can do.
You better hurry.
Get the chains out. I want this river dragged.
Are we in the air yet?
If you and I are gonna be friends,
you need to learn some manners.
Bitch.
- Man, the hell with this!
- You got a problem, brother?
My problem is walking through this dirty-ass
swamp with the entire county looking for us
because somebody decided
that killing cops was a good idea.
Genius, that somebody's you.
- You're the one that killed the cops.
- Yeah. Both of 'em.
So now we wanna start
playing the blame game, huh?
Always wanna blame the black man.
Somebody steals a car, the black man did it.
House gets robbed, black man.
Cop car gets blown up by an Israeli
single-shot shoulder-fired rocket launcher,
- guess who?
- The black man.
That's right, Vescera.
- The black man!
- Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, Morgan!
You are one crazy son of a bitch.
I like that. I do.
But no one's gonna get killed here
until I give the go-ahead, and I didn't give it.
- What was that?
- The go-ahead.
- Why Vescera?
- We might need a crazy son of a bitch.
- I thought you said there were no crocodiles.
- Those are alligators.
- You think they're hungry?
- Not anymore.
- What have you got?
- Nothing yet.
There's no way anybody
could have lived through this.
- Keep me informed.
- Yes, sir.
- Yeah.
- Where are you?
- How you doing?
- How am I doing?
Not so good, huh? Well, you know
that triple homicide I was just involved in?
- The one all over the news?
- Yeah, right. That's the one. I know, bad.
Anyways, I think I can now add kidnapping
to my litany of atrocities.
I know I can. She's standing there
in front of me right now.
- Why are you telling me all this?
- Why am I telling you this?
Because in the middle of blowing up the gas
station, killing the marine and kidnapping,
I had a great idea. In fact, it's such a great idea
that I even came up with a name for it.
It's called "You're Out."
Which basically means you get nothing.
No split, no diamonds, no payoff, no nothing.
- We had a plan, Rome.
- I know we had a plan, but plans change.
At least, for one of us, they do.
Now, listen. If you think for one second...
- You wouldn't get away with this without me.
- Can you hold on?
Yeah. This is he.
I'm calling to let you know
your order's been approved.
Yeah. Now, does that include all the premium
channels and the sports package?
Sure does.
All right. The air show's over.
Let's get the hell outta here.
Go on.
That's a creepy-ass snake.
Slimy and scaly.
It's terrifying, all these animals and bugs.
I hate this, man. I'm not built for this stuff.
- What's wrong with you?
- What's wrong with me? Think about it.
How many brothers you see in Deliverance?
The answer is zero.
You know why?
Because brothers don't camp.
Why does everything always have
to be racial with you, Morgan?
Why do you feel the need
to confine us to these labels?
Why can't we just be people?
- What do you think, Kate?
- I think you're psychotic.
Now, how can you say that?
You don't even know me.
That's very judgmental.
Is she looking at me?
I'm gonna be totally honest here.
I thought that you and I, you know,
we could've had a future, you know,
if it wasn't for...
What?
You're insane.
Maybe.
Good talk.
- Cops.
- Get the truck loaded.
Hold it right there, cop.
I'm not a cop.
I'm just looking for some people.
Boy, I will end you.
I told you, I'm not a cop.
Wait here. And somebody shut her up.
- What have you got?
- Nothing.
All right.
- Van Buren here.
- Sir, come in.
- What's going on in the south fork?
- Nothing. We're headed for the marina.
I want every shack
on that riverbank searched.
- Find them.
- Copy that.
What'd you find?
There's a lodge up there.
It's swarming with cops.
What do you want to do now?
We'll let the cops leave
and then we'll cross the river.
Take these. Get 'em loaded.
We gotta move.
What the hell are you doing out here, cop?
You guys got it all wrong.
Save your lies, boy.
If I was a cop, I'd have a badge, a gun.
I don't. I'm just out here trying...
Just trying to what?
I got choppers buzzing around here,
and I got you sneaking up our asses,
and you're not a cop?
Right.
You're right. I'm a cop.
They're tracking my GPS right now.
GPS? I told you to search him!
- I did!
- Find it!
Where's the goddamn bug, cop?
- What are you doing, man?
- No contact points, no alarm.
It's a freaking shack.
Get in there.
Something die in here?
I don't know, but it smells like baked ass.
Morgan, see if you can go find a generator.
- Why me?
- Why not?
What if there's some guy
with a hockey mask and a hatchet?
Or a group of country ass-crackers
craving some man love?
Lt'll be fun, like summer camp.
Yeah, but brothers don't camp.
Yeah, well, actually I did go to camp once.
I was 13 years old.
And there was this camp counselor.
Cool honky.
Timothy.
Tim.
Or, as he liked to be called, Johnny Whiplash.
Well, tell us, Morgan.
What did this Johnny Whiplash have to offer?
Well, first he offered friendship.
Then some rock candy.
Then he offered me something
that I never should have accepted.
Wow.
Well, good luck with all that.
Now go find the generator.
What we talked about...
ain't leaving this room, right?
No. No.
Now, go find the goddamn generator.
Cool.
- Hello.
- Hey. It's me.
- Hold on. Frank.
- What?
It's Rome.
- So, how's my Cadillac?
- Plan A's screwed.
- No shit. You're all over the news.
- We're switching to plan B.
- Well, what the hell is plan B?
- I don't know what plan B is.
- I'm making this up as I go.
- Great.
- You know Rita's down by the marina?
- Yeah.
- I want you to leave a car there for me.
- I need some time. Give me till tomorrow.
No, as soon as you can.
Looks like we're going to Phoenix.
What are you looking at?
Why so sad?
Don't like your new friends?
You're pathetic.
How so?
You're like his little puppet.
So, what's the plan?
Where are we going?
What, no faith?
I have faith.
I just need to know if I'm still in the loop.
There's this guy in Phoenix.
I figure since we did 100% of the work,
why not keep 100%% of the diamonds?
- Can he move 'em?
- That he can, my friend.
That he can.
You grew up on the water, right? Louisiana?
- Miami.
- Yeah, whatever.
See if you can go get
that boat started out there.
Hey, Bennett.
Check on Morgan. See what he's up to.
Morgan.
- How many are left?
- There's two upstairs.
- You wait here.
- I'm not waiting anywhere.
You don't know what you're walking into.
It's a matter of time before they realize
these two aren't coming back.
I gotta do something and I gotta do it now.
OK.
Playtime's over.
- There's a crazy son of a bitch.
- Where is she?
This just gets better and better.
Put it down.
All right.
Easy, big guy.
He's still got something I need.
I don't care what you do to him.
I just want my wife.
He's not gonna do anything to me.
Not until he finds out
what happened to those stolen diamonds.
'Cause that's what he's after.
His cut.
Isn't that right, Officer?
Now, why don't you just take a second
and let that sink in there, champ?
Where are they, Rome?
- Where's what?
- Give me my damn diamonds!
Whoa! Calm down, V.B.
I know our last deal didn't work out too well,
but I'm willing to make a new one.
You see, I tried to kill this guy twice today
and he just won't die.
Maybe I'm having an off day. I don't know.
But if you shoot him right now,
I'm willing to split the diamonds with you.
What do you say?
- There's our ride. Let's go.
- Go where? What happened?
- Her marine showed up, that's what.
- He's still alive?
Let's go.
Oh, no. You're not putting me in there.
You're not putting me in there!
Out of the water. Get out of the water now!
Turn around.
Put your hands above your head.
- Turn around.
- I'm John Triton.
Shut up! Down on your knees.
Place your hands behind your head.
- I called you. They have my wife.
- Shut up, boy!
You're under arrest. You have the right
to remain silent. I suggest you use it.
You're dead, boy!
Son of a bitch!
Look at that.
You don't mind if I keep this one, do you?
I'm sure we can work something out.
Work something out?
Wait a minute, baby.
I gotta drive. Baby, I can't do this.
Say yes.
Baby, I gotta drive. Yes.
Yes.
What's the matter, baby?
Don't you trust me anymore?
Unit Four, this is Command. Over.
We gotta get rid of this car.
- Any suggestions?
- Van Buren?
Yeah.
I got one.
- Hi.
- Hey, girl.
- Nice truck.
- Wanna go for a ride?
Base to River Unit. We have a positive
identification on your trucker.
Last logged in driving a grey semi.
A vehicle matching that description
was just seen five miles north of Rita's Marina
heading southbound on Route 16.
- So, what's the plan?
- We'll pick up our clean car
and then we're home free.
Get that bitch off me.
I don't see the car.
Let's check the other line.
What the hell was that?
John!
Gotta go, babe!
Say hello to your wife!
Come on. Come on.
No, Kate. Come on, come on, come on.
Wake up!
Come on.
Come on. Wake up!
Wake up!
That's it. Come on. That's it.
We should've gone to the beach.