Created and Encoded by --  Bokutox -- of  www.YIFY-TORRENTS.com. The Best 720p/1080p/3d movies with the lowest file size on the internet. World of Warcraft - Outland PVP (EU) - Torporr (name)
(PIANO PLAYING CHRISTMAS SONG)
(INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS)
Ho-ho-ho! Merry Christmas!
Hey, guys.
- Merry Christmas.
- Thanks.
- Hey!
- (MUSIC ENDS)
MR. WHITTLE: Ladies and gentlemen,
can I have your attention?
This has been our best year ever
thanks to Do-it-All-For-You-Dolly.
(GUESTS CHEERING)
And I think we should give
a special thanks to the people
responsible for our
record-breaking sales,
our Midwest marketing
and distribution team,
- Scott Calvin and Susan Perry!
- MAN: Yeah!
- (ALL CHEERING)
- Let's hear it for 'em! Come on!
Susan, darling, come on up here.
Aren't they adorable?
Say a few words.
Thank you very much.
This was really a team effort.
I would just want to thank every one
of you individually...
But we don't have time for that, do we?
(ALL LAUGHING)
In all seriousness, here at B&R Toys,
we're not just about making
a profit in quality toys.
We're also about families. But our
families aren't here with us right now.
Which is probably why Johnson's
secretary is sitting in his lap.
(CHUCKLING) You guys
have a great party. Have a great year.
Drive safe. Thanks very much.
(ALL APPLAUDING)
Aren't they wonderful?
(ANSWERING MACHINE BEEPS)
SCOTT: Laura, I was hoping to
catch you before you'd left your house.
I ran real late today.
You wouldn't believe the traffic out here.
- (HORN HONKING)
- Yeah, same to you!
And that's not very ladylike!
(CHUCKLES) Anyway, I'll try to get
to my house as soon as I can.
Oh. There's the problem right there.
Three car pileup.
I'm really gonna be late.
(SINGING)
Hark, carol bells, sweet silver bells
All seem to sing, throw cares away
Christmas is here bringing good cheer
To young and old, meek and the bold
Ding dong and dong, balance in song
Ring joyful ring, all caroling
One seems to hear
Words of good cheer
From everywhere, filling the air
Oh, how they pound, raising the sound
Go hand in hand, calling in the town
Gaily they ring while people sing
Songs of good cheer
Christmas is here
Merry, merry, merry, merry Christmas
On we will sing, dawn with a hymn
Angel will come to every home
Hark, carol bells, sweet silver bells
All seem to sing, throw cares away
One seems to hear
Words of good cheer
From everywhere, filling the air
Oh, how they pound, raising the sound
Go hand in hand, calling in the town
Gaily they ring while people sing
Songs of good cheer
Christmas is here
Merry, merry, merry, merry Christmas
On we will sing, dawn with a hymn
Angel will come to every home
Ding dong ding
Dong
(SIGHS)
LAURA: All right, let's go.
- Bye, Charlie.
- CHARLIE: Bye, Neal.
Oh! Sorry I'm late. Hi.
- Hi.
- Did you want to come in for a minute?
- Neal's waiting in the car, so...
- Why doesn't he come in?
'Cause, Daddy, he says you'll just
end up saying something snotty.
Not necessarily. Could be rude
or sarcastic. Whatever it takes.
See? I gotta go.
Come on, come on. Christmas Eve.
Just a minute.
Watch those steps.
They're real slippery.
(LAURA GRUNTS)
SCOTT: Told ya.
- So...
- Well...
(LAURA CLEARS THROAT)
SCOTT: You going to your mom's
for dinner?
Actually, we're gonna be with
Neal's family.
Ah! Christmas at the pound.
(IMITATING DOG HOWLING)
(IMITATING CAT HISSING)
(IMITATING CAT MEOWING)
There aren't that many
presents over there.
- That's because Santa isn't here yet.
- Neal doesn't believe in Santa.
- Well, Neal's head comes to a point.
- (CAR HORN HONKING)
- He's smart. He's a doctor.
- He's not a doctor, he's a psychiatrist.
Take your coat off.
You're sticking around, aren't ya?
(CONTINUES HONKING)
I'll be right there. Just a sec.
- I just want to...
- Did that jerk tell Charlie
there was no Santa Claus?
What? No. Oh, Charlie came home
from school the other day in tears
because some big kid told him
there was no such thing as Santa.
And, you know Neal.
Well, he sat him down and...
SCOTT: And told him
there was a Santa Claus.
Well, all he said was that Santa
was more like a feeling.
You know, more like a state of mind
than a person.
Kind of like Neal.
And who gave you permission
to tell Charlie there's no Santa Claus?
I think if we're going to destroy our
son's illusions, I should be a part of it.
Yeah, but you're never around,
- are you, Scott?
- Oh, please.
LAURA: Listen,
all we are trying to do is give
Charlie a firm grasp on reality.
That's a good idea.
You don't want kids running around
using their imaginations.
Oh, yeah.
That's from the guy responsible
- for the Do-It-All-For-You-Dolly.
- Leave her out of this.
(SINGING) "Don't you burp me
Don't you change me, I'm the dolly..."
Why do you guys always have to fight?
We're not fighting.
It's your mom singing.
It sounds a lot like fighting, doesn't it?
Cats, even.
(IMITATING CAT YOWLING)
The trouble is, Neal and your mom,
they don't believe in Santa
because they were real naughty.
Which is why they'll probably get
lumps of coal in their stockings.
I don't know. It seems kind of babyish
to believe in that kind of stuff.
What are you talking about?
I believe in Santa Claus. I'm not a baby.
- Well...
- Maybe it's time you left.
We don't want to keep
Dr. Pinhead waiting.
LAURA: Come here.
Do I gotta stay?
LAURA: Listen, you and your daddy
are gonna have
a great Christmas, okay?
- Will you pick me up tomorrow?
- Of course.
- Early?
- Yes.
We're talking sunup, you're here?
(LAURA CHUCKLING)
You'll be fine. Merry Christmas, Charlie.
I love you.
I love you, too, Mom.
- You be a good boy, okay?
- Bye, Mom.
(DOOR OPENS)
Four hours?
(DOOR CLOSES)
(CHRISTMAS SONG PLAYING)
I'm dreaming
Of a white Christmas
WOMAN ON TV:
Your Christmas will be perfect...
with its own built-in turkey timer.
Where those treetops glisten
MAN ON TV:
And now, we return you
to the most cherished
of Christmas stories,
Miracle on 34th Street, starring...
(FIRE EXTINGUISHER BLASTING)
(SIGHS)
Ah.
That is exactly why you want
a high-quality fire extinguisher
right in the kitchen.
Those flames were really big, Dad.
Well, turkey's funny that way.
Dad!
It's done!
(BRAKES SQUEALING)
You like osso buco, Charlie?
- They're closed.
- You know, Neal's a real good cook.
SCOTT: Yeah, and you should
see him walk on water.
CHARLIE: You don't like him
very much, do you, Dad?
Charlie, yeah. I was joking, okay?
I'm sorry. I was just kidding around.
I like him a lot... Yeah, sure, I like him.
You know, there...
There's just something about him
that makes me wanna...
Lash out irrationally.
Where did you hear that?
From Neal. I learn a lot from him.
He listens to me.
Yeah. Then he charges you for it.
(EXHALES)
I'm dreaming
Of a white Christmas
All right. Denny's. It's always open.
I don't wanna eat here.
What're you talking about?
Everybody likes Denny's.
It's an American institution.
(SPEAKING JAPANESE)
(CROWD CONVERSING
IN JAPANESE)
- Are you with Hatsutashi?
- No.
- Dad burned the turkey.
- Oh, yeah. This way. Come on.
- Right over there.
- Thank you.
(CLEARS THROAT)
- WAITRESS: Here we go.
- Burn the turkey?
(CHUCKLES)
WAITRESS: Coffee?
No, thank you, Judy.
(CHUCKLING)
What do you say we start out
with cold glasses
of delicious seasonal favorite eggnog?
- I don't like eggnog.
- We're out.
- Coffee. Decaf.
- Mmm-hmm.
- I'll have chocolate milk, please.
- WAITRESS: We're out.
Plain milk's fine.
Okay.
At least we know they got hot apple pie.
- We did.
- Mmm-hmm.
This is nice.
SCOTT: "And Mama in her kerchief
and I in my cap
"had just settled down
for a long winter's nap.
"When out on the lawn
there arose such a clatter,
"I sprang from my bed
to see what was the matter.
"Away to the window I flew like a flash.
"With a miniature sleigh and St. Nick...
"And Prancer and Dancer...
"...and to all a good night."
CHARLIE: What's that?
- What's what?
- "A Rose Suchak ladder"?
It's not a ladder.
I said, "Arose such a clatter."
- It means, "Came a big noise."
- What?
Charlie, "arose" is a word
that means "it came,"
and "clatter" is a big noise.
Now please, go to sleep.
Shut your eyes.
How do reindeer fly?
They don't have any wings.
- Fairy dust.
- That's from Peter Pan, Dad.
- Horns.
- Antlers.
Whatever. Their antlers give them...
You know, there's a slipstream effect.
The air goes... They move...
They're weightless.
But if Santa's so fat, how did
he get down the chimneys?
He sucks it in like Grandpa.
What about people
who don't have fireplaces?
How does he get into their house?
Charlie, sometimes believing
in something means you...
Means you just believe in it.
Santa uses reindeer to fly because
that's how he has to get around.
But you do believe in Santa, right, Dad?
Of course I believe in Santa.
Now please, go to sleep.
Dad?
What is it, Charlie?
Maybe you better leave some cookies
and milk out, just in case, okay?
Great. I'll just go preheat the oven.
CHARLIE: And don't forget
the fire extinguisher.
Good night, Charlie.
(SIGHS)
(BELLS JINGLING)
(JET ENGINE WHOOSHING)
(CHIMING)
- SANTA: (FAINTLY) Ho!
- (THUDDING)
Settle down there.
(DOG BARKING)
(STOMPING)
(QUIETLY) Dad! Dad!
(SNORTING)
- What?
- I heard a clatter!
What, Charlie?
- (CLATTERING)
- There! A clatter.
- Charlie, what're you talking about?
- You know, "It came a big noise"?
- It's coming from outside!
- Charlie, it's just the wind or something.
- Come on, let's go back to bed.
- (THUDDING)
- Somebody's on the roof.
- Maybe it's Santa.
Not now, Charlie. I want you to sit here,
and I want you to stay right there.
- Charlie, do you know how to call 911?
- Sure. 911.
Yeah, great. Stay there.
Hey, you!
Oops! Whoa!
Whoa, whoa!
Whoa!
(SANTA SHOUTING)
(THUD)
Whoo-hoo!
- (BELLS JINGLING)
- Hey, buddy.
All right. You should just stay still.
Perfect.
You got him!
Charlie, stay where you are. Charlie,
would you listen to me? Stay up there!
It is Santa! You killed him.
Did not! It is not Santa.
Well, he was.
He's got some ID on him, I bet.
Fella, if you can hear me, I'm just
looking for your identification.
Once I figure out who you are,
I'll give you a lift back to the mall.
"If something should happen to me,
put on my suit.
"The reindeer will know what to do."
Yeah, right.
(BELLS CHIMING)
Whoa.
Dad!
SCOTT: Hey.
CHARLIE: He disappeared!
Whoa.
He's naked somewhere.
You gonna put on the suit
like the card said?
- Are you?
- No. No.
Come on, Dad. I wanna go, too.
Stop it, Charlie.
We're not going anywhere.
You never do what I wanna do!
Would you please be quiet for a minute
so I can figure this out?
(SIGHS)
Reindeer up on the roof.
Santa suit laying on the ground.
Guy fell. Not my fault.
Reindeer on the roof.
That is hard to explain.
It's the ladder.
(GROANS)
Where the hell'd this come from?
Look here, Dad.
"The Rose Suchak Ladder Company."
Huh?
"Out by the roof
there's a Rose Suchak ladder."
- Just like the poem.
- Just like the poem?
Charlie, come on down from there.
Charlie, get down from there!
Dad! You gotta see this!
SCOTT: Don't touch anything.
CHARLIE: It's great!
I'm just gonna call the police.
I'll carry this stuff up there.
Let them deal with it, okay?
(SOFT MOANING)
(LAUGHING)
Whoa.
This guy was huge.
- Dad, isn't this neat?
- (MOANING CONTINUES)
Charlie. Charlie!
Stay away from those things.
They're reindeer.
You don't know where they've been.
They all look like they've got
key lime disease.
(FARTS)
(EXCLAIMS IN DISGUST)
Easy, Rudolph.
(GRUNTING)
Excuse me. Comet.
Dad! Check out Santa's sleigh!
There's no such thing as Santa's sleigh.
Sure there is.
You said you believed in Santa.
- Right?
- I did? I do!
What about the reindeer?
These are Santa's reindeer,
aren't they?
I hope not.
These are
a gift.
Probably from the cable company.
We're getting the Disney Channel now.
Merry Christmas.
- Now, hop out of there, please.
- I don't wanna go.
Listen, Charlie, I'm not kidding.
(SHOUTING) Let's go!
(GROANING)
Yeah, let's go!
(CHARLIE SHOUTING GLEEFULLY)
(SCREAMING)
Charlie!
Hold on, Charlie! (SCREAMING)
CHARLIE: Whoa!
Giddyap, Comet! Whoa, let's go!
Dad, climb up here.
(GRUNTING)
There we go.
So, if we go straight
on this road and we hit I-94...
(SCOTT SCREAMING)
(SCOTT GRUNTS)
Well, we made good time.
Now what do we do?
- Get the bag of toys!
- And do what?
- Go down the chimney.
- Down the chimney!
You want me to take the toys
down the chimney
into a strange house in my underwear?
No. You got to put the suit on first.
You know what we're gonna do,
is we're gonna get out of here
because this whole thing is stupid.
How come everything
I want to do is stupid?
I didn't say that.
(SOFT GRUNT)
Freezing my nubs off out here, and you
want me to get into a Santa costume.
This is great. A Santa costume.
Oh, this thing.
You never know where it's been.
A thousand malls.
Well, I hope you're happy, Comet.
Hope you're happy. But most of all,
I hope the guy that lives here is a tailor!
Nice coat.
Well, how do I look? Nice?
- You forgot the sash.
- You're right.
This completes the ensemble.
All right. Got my boots.
Now I've got the suit on. How am I
supposed to know what to leave?
Maybe there's a list.
A list. How silly of me.
Of course there's a list.
(PANICKED SHOUTING)
Careful, Dad!
- I'm okay, I'm okay, I'm okay!
- Look! You're flying!
It's okay, I'm used to it.
I lived through the '60s.
Whoa, whoa, whoa! (GROANING)
(SCREAMING)
(GRUNTING)
(GROANING)
(LIGHT THUDDING)
(GROWLING)
Nice teeth.
(BARKING)
- MAN: Who's down there?
- (ALARM BLARING)
(WHIMPERING)
It's the holidays. Come on, come on.
(CONTINUES BARKING)
(GUNSHOT)
Hey, Charles!
Need a little help down here!
- (SCOTT GRUNTS)
- (CHIMNEY BELCHES)
Whoa!
How'd you do that?
What'd it feel like, Dad?
It felt like America's Most Wanted!
Now pull me in, quick!
We gotta get outta here.
(GRUNTING)
Thanks. We gotta go home.
How do you start this thing?
- (LOUD RUMBLING)
- Just like that!
(HOUSE ALARM CONTINUES)
Whoa.
This could be a really long night.
- (REINDEER GRUNTING)
- Do it again, Dad.
Please?
I can't. That thing's empty.
(GRUNTING)
There's nothing in the bag.
(GROWLING)
Even if there was,
didn't you notice there's no chimney?
Where there's no chimney,
there's no fireplace.
(CONTINUES GROWLING)
Are you growling at me?
(GRUNTS)
Look, Comet, like I said,
there is nothing left...
That's so weird, because I know when
I did that... No, no, no, no, no!
Hold it! There's no chimney here!
Can you hear me?
No chimney, all right?
Looking good, Dad!
You have got to be kidding!
Come on! Look at the size of this thing!
(GROANING)
(GRUNTING)
(GULPING)
(GROANING)
Weird! Ow.
(GROANS)
(SIGHING)
- Santa?
- Scott Calvin.
How come your clothes are so baggy?
Because Santa is watching
his saturated fats.
- How come you don't have a beard?
- Because I shaved!
Do you want this doll or not?
Go back to sleep.
(ORNAMENT BREAKING)
You're supposed to drink the milk.
Look, I am lactose intolerant.
And I am just about this close to taking
all those presents back up the chimney.
(MOCKING TONE)
"Supposed to drink the milk"!
Shut your eyes!
Oh!
CHARLIE: How do you get in
without a fireplace?
SCOTT: I don't know.
- One just kind of appeared.
- CHARLIE: Awesome!
(SCOTT CHUCKLING)
(SIGHS)
(GRUNTING) Oh, boy!
(GLASS SHATTERING)
(CRASHING)
Charlie, look at the clouds over here.
Aren't they pretty?
Charlie!
- (CHARLIE GIGGLING)
- (DOG BARKING)
Yah!
All right. Morning, fellas.
Morning, sport. We're done, Comet.
Ho-ho-ho.
Back to the house.
Merry Christmas to all
and to all a good night.
When I wake up,
I'm getting a CAT scan!
(REINDEER BLEATING)
CHARLIE: Is this okay, Dad?
No, it's not okay!
Hey, does this look like
home to you guys?
No, no! No, no, no, no!
Hey, hey! Where you going?
Come back here!
Oh.
(GRUNTING)
(FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING)
In the silence of the night
When the snow...
Hey, hey! Hey, buddy!
You, sir! Hey!
You can see a magic light
And hear the ring of Christmas bells
Can you hear me?
Though the night seems long and dark
It is the earth...
- What's that?
- I don't know.
I think it's the North Pole.
That's the North Pole?
Hey, buddy, we need some help.
Hello! What are you doing?
So close your eyes and come with me
The Christmas bells
will bring you home
(BLEATING)
ELF: Hey, look!
Here comes the new Santa!
And now with song we fill the night
While magic dances in the light
To wish you now and all the year
The joy that comes
with Christmas cheer
Sit back.
Hear our voices fill the air
To drive the winter's cold away
And so our hearts with all will share
The love that comes
with Christmas day
The Christmas bells
will bring you home
(INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS)
(REINDEER GULPING)
- Where are all the grownups?
- This is so cool!
Stay here.
Hey, kid, kid.
Kid, who's in charge here?
(CHUCKLING) You are.
And I'm not a kid.
I've pointy shoes that are
older than you. I'm an elf.
You guys, or you girls.
Who gives the orders?
Who's your boss?
- You are.
- No, no, no.
- Who's the head elf?
- You are!
Hey! Who's causing
all the trouble around here?
- He is.
- She is.
Excuse me, are we on a coffee break?
- We don't drink coffee.
- Then I guess the break is over.
Back to work. Thanks.
Take it easy on her, will ya?
Who are you?
I'm Bernard. Nice to meet ya, Santa.
I'm not Santa! I've had a rough night.
There's been dogs barking,
guns going off.
Look, my back's killing me.
Have you ever tried to shove
a sea kayak down a chimney?
I'm tired of this small talk.
Hmm.
The other Santa disappeared, right?
Wait a minute. Hey!
I know where this is going.
It wasn't my fault. The other guy fell.
It was an accident.
I've got homeowner's insurance
and a good attorney.
Not as good as my wife's,
but let's not open up that wound.
Hold it a minute.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
How did you know the other guy
was gone?
- Can I get you a drink?
- No, I don't want a drink.
I'm thirsty, and hungry, too.
Charlie, I thought I told you
to stay in the sleigh.
Who's this?
This is my son, Charlie.
I'm sorry. Charlie, this is...
(STAMMERING)
- Bernard.
- Hi, Bernard.
- Hiya, sport.
Hey, Dad, he called me "sport"
- just like you.
- Wonderful.
Hey, you know what?
I got something for you.
Okay, now hold out
your hand, all right?
Now, be very careful.
This is very old, just like me.
Shake it up, Charlie.
(BELLS JINGLING)
Wow.
Why don't you hold onto it for me
for a while? It might come in handy.
Thanks. Thanks a lot.
I promise I'll take real good care of it.
Make sure you do.
I will.
Hey, Dad, look!
Fabulous ball. Hey, Barabbas.
- Bernard!
- Bernard.
Can we take a direct flight
back to reality
or do we have to change planes
in Denver?
Larry, take Charlie here
and get him some chow.
No, Larry, don't do that. Charlie!
He'll be okay. Follow me,
you'll want to get out of those clothes.
I... No, look, Barnaby,
I just want to go home.
(TOYS CLANGING)
(TRAIN WHISTLE BLOWING)
Look, I am not Santa Claus!
Ah.
Did you or did you not read the card?
- Yeah, I read the card.
- Then you're the new Santa.
In putting on the hat and jacket,
you accepted the contract.
What contract?
The card in the Santa suit.
You said you read it, right?
So when you put on the suit,
you fell subject to the Santa Clause.
- Here.
- The Santa Claus?
You mean the guy that fell off my roof?
No, no, no. Not Santa Claus the person,
Santa Clause the clause.
What?
Look, you're a businessman, right?
- Yeah.
- Okay.
A clause,
as in the last line of a contract.
You got the card?
Okay, look. (EXHALES DEEPLY)
The Santa Clause, "In putting on
this suit and entering the sleigh,
"the wearer waives any and all
rights to any previous identity,
"real or implied,
"and fully accepts the duties
and responsibilities
"of Santa Claus in perpetuity
"until such time that wearer
becomes unable to do so
- "by either accident or design."
- What does that mean?
It means you put on the suit,
you're the big guy.
That's ridiculous.
I didn't put on a suit just to...
Try to understand this!
ELVES: Ooh.
Let me explain something to you, okay?
Toys have to be delivered.
I'm not gonna do it.
It's not my job. I'm just an elf.
It's Santa's job, but Santa
fell off a roof, your roof.
You read the card, you put on the suit.
That clearly falls under
the Santa Clause.
- Now you're Santa, okay?
- A question.
- What?
- When can I get outta here?
Dad, you gotta see this place!
You leave tomorrow morning.
You have 11 months
to get your affairs in order,
and you're due back here
Thanksgiving.
I'm not coming back here
on Thanksgiving.
I'll ship the list to your house.
- What list?
- Come on, now. The list.
(SINGING) He's making a list
Checking it twice
ELVES: Gonna find out
who's naughty or nice
Ugh. Look, you put a "P" next
to the kids who are nice
and a "C" next to the naughty ones.
"P" and "C"?
Yeah! "P" for present,
"C" for coal, right, Bernard?
Right!
Wait a minute!
How do I know who's good and bad?
- You'll know.
- What if I don't wanna do this?
- Don't even kid about a thing like that!
- Why not?
What if I don't buy into this
Santa Claus thing?
What if I choose not to believe it?
(SILENCE)
Then there would be millions of
disappointed children around the world.
You see, children hold the spirit
of Christmas within their hearts.
You wouldn't want to be responsible
for killing the spirit of Christmas,
now, would you, Santa?
Judy will take you to your room. Get out
of the suit, it needs to be cleaned.
- And taken in.
- Then get some sleep.
We've got a lot of work to do
and only a year in which to do it.
(TRAIN WHISTLE BLOWING)
- Judy.
- Santa.
- Scott Calvin.
- Follow me.
I'll just take the next train.
- Dad, come on!
- Charlie!
Come on, Dad!
Charlie, wait up!
(PUPPETS CACKLING)
- That's funny. I like that.
- I like that, too. But I don't like...
(TOOTING)
Wow.
- (THUDDING)
- (GROANS)
Can I get you anything?
The kitchen's always open.
How about a stiff drink?
JUDY: You should get some sleep.
Here are your pajamas.
I'll be right back.
PUNCH PUPPET:
Look, Judy. Look over there.
(PUPPETS CONTINUE INDISTINCTLY)
Look over there. I know.
Look over there. There's a canoe.
Yeah, it's true.
(JUDY PUPPET SCREAMS)
Look, there's an emu!
- ELF: Look at him!
- Shoo!
(ELVES GIGGLING)
- JUDY: Santa?
- Scott Calvin.
- I brought you some cocoa.
- No, thanks.
My own recipe.
Took me 1,200 years to get it right.
- 1,200 years?
- That's right.
You know, I must say,
you look pretty good for your age.
Thanks, but I'm seeing someone
in wrapping.
(GULPS)
(WHISPERING) Okay.
Mmm.
Hmm.
This is good.
This is really good.
Not too hot, extra chocolate,
shaken, not stirred.
You look distressed.
Distressed? I'm way past distressed.
- Why's that?
- I'm talking to an elf!
And I stopped believing
in Santa Claus a long time ago.
That's not surprising.
Most grownups can't believe in magic.
It just sort of grows out of them.
Look, you're a nice little elf.
- Thanks.
- But this is a dream.
I mean, this is fabulous. Is that a polar
bear directing traffic down there?
(BEAR GROWLS)
(CHUCKLING)
I see it, but I don't believe it.
- (LAUGHS) You're missing the point.
- What is the point?
Seeing isn't believing,
believing is seeing.
Kids don't have to see this place
to know that it's here.
They just know.
Well, you should get some rest.
Good night, sir.
CHARLIE: Dad!
Dad!
Wake up, sleepy!
Come on, get up!
- Dad!
- SCOTT: Mmm.
- (GRUNTS)
- Dad!
- (GROANS)
- (RAPID FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING)
- Come on, Dad, come on!
- (GROANING)
- See all the neat toys!
- Stop shaking me, Charlie.
- Come on, get up, get up!
- Okay.
- Come on, it's Christmas morning.
- Great! Go make some coffee.
- Come on, Dad, let's go!
SCOTT: Okay.
(SOFT GROANING)
(SNIFFS)
(BELLS JINGLING)
(YAWNS)
(EXHALES)
- Are you okay, Dad?
- Yeah. Just fine, just fine.
Are you having a heart attack?
I know CPR.
No, I was just...
- S.C.
- Yeah, Santa Claus.
Hey. Same initials as your name, Dad.
Scott Calvin.
- (DOORBELL RINGS)
- What?
LAURA: Oh, Charlie!
Merry Christmas, honey.
- Did you have a good time?
- Great time! The best!
Great. Scott, nice P.J.s. Very festive.
- Where'd you get them?
- I don't know.
Judy gave them to you.
- Judy. Really.
- Who?
- Up at the North Pole.
- Ah. One of Santa's little helpers.
Last night, Dad and me
went with the flying reindeer.
It was really neat, Mom. Dad was Santa,
and Larry showed me the workshop.
You know,
where they make all the toys?
Gee, thanks for
- keeping his feet on the ground.
- You bet.
Honey, you go wait in the car
for a minute. I'll be right there.
Merry Christmas.
Bye, Dad. Thanks for
a great night at the North Pole.
- (BOTH CHUCKLING)
- (DOOR OPENS)
(DOOR CLOSES)
So...
- What have you been telling him?
- Nothing.
It's just... I had this
really strange dream
and I must've told him all about it.
Wait.
- Charlie.
- Scott.
- Hi, Dad.
- Nice jammies.
Thanks. About what you said
in the house...
- Who showed you the workshop?
- The elf.
- How'd I get the pajamas?
- I told you. Judy.
SCOTT: Oh, wait, wait.
Judy was the name of the waitress
at the restaurant last night.
- Some waitress gave you pajamas?
- What's this all about?
Dad took me to the North Pole,
and Larry showed me the workshop.
- The North Pole!
- Yeah. Dad's the new Santa.
The regular Santa fell off the roof
and Dad put on the suit.
Charlie, we'll discuss this at home.
(BOTH CHUCKLE)
The clause. The Santa Clause.
(CAR DOOR CLOSES)
- (ENGINE STARTS)
- It's just a dream.
Stuff like that doesn't happen.
It was a dream. Come on!
I don't even wear pajamas.
Normally I sleep naked. Buck naked! Ha!
Morning, Mrs. McGloin.
Mary Catherine.
MRS. McGLOIN:
Eyes front, Mary Catherine!
Sometimes boxer shorts. You know.
(CHUCKLES)
So, remember, kids,
there is nothing more painful
than third degree burns.
Well, thank you, Fireman O'Hara.
And I think the whole class
will join me in saying
sorry about your partner.
(SIGHS)
Well, perhaps this is a good time
to bring up the psychiatrist.
Charlie, would you like
to introduce your...
(STAMMERING)
Dr. Miller! (CHUCKLES)
Can I ask Dad to go first?
Well, if that's how you feel, Charlie.
That's how he feels, Neal. Come on.
Nice sweater, buddy.
This is my dad, Scott Calvin.
He's got a really neat job.
- Thank you, Charlie.
- My dad is Santa Claus.
(CHILDREN LAUGHING)
Oh, boy. (LAUGHS)
I think what he means is,
I'm like Santa Claus.
We're both giving, we're both jolly,
and we both work very hard
one day a year. (CHUCKLES)
- Oh, boy!
- That's not what I mean, Dad.
Look, on Christmas Eve,
my dad pushed Santa off the roof.
- No, Charlie.
- Santa disappeared
- and my dad took his place.
- SCOTT: Charlie!
Then I went with him
to deliver all the presents.
Then the reindeer flew us to
the North Pole where the head elf
- Bernard gave me this.
- Charlie...
Look, I work for a toy company.
I deliver toys all over the country.
So, in a way, I'm like Santa Claus.
- Yes, sweetheart?
- Do you make the toys?
No, stupid, the elves do!
Bobby, we don't say "stupid,"
and we don't say "elves."
They're "little people."
No, but they really are elves.
- Whatever, honey.
- Which one's your favorite reindeer?
- Comet.
- I don't have a favorite.
So, let me get this straight, Santa.
You mean, when I grow up,
if I wanna be Santa Claus,
all I gotta do is push you off a roof?
SCOTT: He said that it was
the best Christmas he ever had?
LAURA: Oh, big surprise!
It's just nice to hear it from him.
Is that a problem with you?
All right. So?
May I speak, please? I am a doctor.
(WHISPERING) No, he's not.
He's a psychiatrist.
Please. Go ahead, Dr. Miller.
I guess we know
who's the teacher's pet.
Scott! Oh, grow up.
The reason we're here is that
this is far more serious
than a boy believing or not believing
in Santa Claus.
That's right, because Charlie thinks
that this whole thing actually happened.
Scott, what was the last thing
you and Charlie did
before you went to bed Christmas Eve?
We shared a bowl of sugar,
did some shots of brown liquor,
played with my shotguns,
field dressed a cat,
looked for women.
I read him a book!
- What book?
- Hollywood Wives.
The Night Before Christmas, folks.
Come on!
And did you go to the North Pole?
This is ridiculous.
I don't have time for this.
Ridiculous
or not, Scott, for Charlie,
this isn't some dream, it is real.
You need to sit down with Charlie.
Explain to him you are not Santa Claus.
CHARLIE: They're like the bears
at the North Pole, Dad.
SCOTT: Charlie, I already told you,
we did not go to the North Pole.
- That was a dream.
- You're in denial, Dad.
Denial! You don't even know
what that means.
Well, you are. I know what happened.
How do you know that? How?
You don't have any proof.
- Proof?
- Why can't we both
think of it as just a great dream
and forget about it?
What about this?
Remember all the neat stuff inside?
Charlie, this is a toy.
We used to make things like this
at work, but no one bought 'em.
Here. I don't want
to talk about this anymore.
I know who you are, Dad.
You'll figure it out soon enough.
There are a lot of kids that believe
in you. You can't let them down.
Charlie, you're wrong.
(REINDEER MOANING)
(GIGGLING)
What's so funny?
Nothing.
(CHRISTMAS SONG PLAYING)
He sees you when you're sleeping
- He knows when you're awake
- (CHARLIE GIGGLING)
He knows if you've been bad or good
Rollin'. Keep those reindeer rollin'
Okay! You better watch out
You better not cry
Come on, Dancer. Come on, Prancer.
- Santa Claus is coming to town
- Whoa.
We can't stop.
(IN SQUEAKY VOICE)
But I have to go to the bathroom!
I told you, should've gone
before we left the North Pole.
And rummy tum-tums
CHARLIE: Whoa.
Right here. Turn over here.
Curly-haired dolls that toddle and coo
Elephant spokes and kiddie cars, too
Where is he?
Well, he could be in his room
jumping up and down on his bed,
wearing a red hat and galoshes.
I don't care what Neal's doing.
Where's Charlie?
(LAUGHS) Oh, I see, I see.
Well, if you can't be father of the year,
why not be Father Christmas, huh?
NEAL: Charlie, it's just not logical.
How can one man, in one night,
visit all the children of the world?
Not everyone celebrates Christmas.
And I think there's some sort
of time continuum
that breaks down once
Santa's in his sleigh.
What about fireplaces?
A lot of people don't have them.
How does Santa visit those people?
He turns into Jell-O and... (SLURPING)
The fireplace kind of appears
and he goes through it like this.
What about the reindeer?
Have you ever seen a reindeer fly?
- Yes.
- Well, I haven't.
(DOOR OPENS)
- Have you ever seen $1 million?
- No.
(DOOR CLOSES)
Just because you haven't seen it
doesn't mean it doesn't exist.
Hi, Neal. Howdy, sport.
- Hi, Dad.
- You wanna take a walk?
- I wanna talk to you.
- Sure. I'll get my coat.
Okay, hustle up.
Scott? Can I have a minute?
Sure.
I think Charlie
is conflicted at the moment.
Wow. Really?
(WHISTLES) Boy. Hmm.
Appreciate your analysis, I really do.
Boy, you got more important things
to worry about, you know.
Like, where are you gonna get
more sweaters
after the circus pulls out of town?
(INHALES DEEPLY)
Scott! I mean, you're not listening.
- We are very concerned about this.
- Concerned about what?
(STAMMERING) This...
If Charlie spending time with you
is the best thing for him.
(CLICKS TONGUE)
You were right about
the sweater, okay?
Do you think by next year
I'll be big enough to drive the sleigh
all by myself?
No!
- But I've been practicing.
- No, that's not what I'm talking about.
Charlie, hold on a second. We've got
to talk about this Santa Claus thing.
Charlie, there is no...
No what, Dad?
There's no reason why we have to
tell anybody about the North Pole.
Why not?
Well, sometimes some things,
big things,
should remain unsaid,
like between two people...
- Oh, you mean like a secret.
- Yes. Like a secret. Let's keep it secret.
How come?
Because of Mom and Neal.
Not just because of them.
There's school.
Everybody thinks...
No, it's not important what they think.
It...
How does five bucks sound to ya?
This is something I really want you
to do for me, sport.
I want to keep this secret.
Will ya do that, please?
- Okay, Dad.
- All right.
Great.
You don't have to worry about
the Santa Claus thing anymore.
So when do I get the five bucks?
MAN ON RADIO: 15 in the morning.
It's gonna be a beautiful day.
(RADIO CONTINUES INDISTINCTLY)
Spend the day with me, Larry B.
(FARTING)
(SIGHING) Oof!
(YAWNING)
(SCREAMS)
Huh?
(GROANS)
Something's wrong with the mirror.
(CHUCKLING)
(MUMBLING)
What?
Something's wrong with the scale!
(SCREAMS)
(ELEVATOR DINGS)
Excuse me, excuse me.
I'll have a field green salad and...
Oh, my God.
MAN: What the...
WOMAN: What? Scott?
(SIGHING) Calvin?
(CHUCKLING)
Sorry, the dry cleaner
in my neighborhood went up in smoke,
some big chemical fire.
All my clothes, poof, gone.
God. Your... Your weight.
What happened?
Bee sting. Evidently, I'm allergic.
Almost killed me. But the guy
at the emergency room says
the swelling will go down.
I hope. So, did I miss anything?
No, we were just about to order lunch.
Great! I'm starving.
I'll have a salad and ice tea
and dressing on the side.
Pasta and tomatoes and very
light on the oil. Can you do that?
And I'll have a Caesar. No dressing.
And one of those homemade cookies,
the warm chocolate chip. No nuts.
And a little slice of cheesecake,
crme brle,
and hot fudge sundae, extra hot fudge.
On the side.
- Anything to drink?
- Ice-cold milk.
Stung by a bee, Scott?
A big bee.
(SPOON CLATTERING)
Finished?
Okay, now, remember.
This is just a storyboard.
But here is our
preliminary Total Tank TV spot.
Okay, now, we've got Santa.
He's up in the North Pole.
He's getting ready for Christmas!
Oh, no.
- Problem?
- It's just a little thing. The elves.
- What about the elves?
- They look so funny.
They're supposed to look funny.
They're elves.
SCOTT: Just my opinion.
Can't they look a little younger
with silver specks on their cheeks?
Can we continue here?
Okay, now this year,
Santa's not going out in a sleigh.
This time he's going Total Tank!
Wait a minute! No way! No way Santa's
going anywhere without his sleigh.
He would if he's trying
to sell the Total Tank.
Well, isn't that a pretty picture?
Santa rolling down the block
in a panzer.
Well, kids, I certainly hope
you've been good this year.
'Cause it looks like Santa just
took out the Pearson home.
- Incoming!
- WOMAN: Oh, please.
And another thing.
What about the reindeer?
Reindeer and Santa.
Santa and reindeer.
It's kind of a package deal.
- Calvin.
- You don't believe in Santa, do you?
Calvin, can we get back
to the presentation?
I'm not done yet.
Since we've opened this box, have any
of you tried to build the Total Tank?
It's got 10,000 parts,
and even if you do get it together,
it breaks 10 minutes later.
Then you got to spend more money
to buy more parts.
- I thought that was the whole point.
- No, no, no, no.
What we got to do is develop a basic,
simple, inexpensive toy
that will nurture
a child's creative thinking.
- Calvin...
- Here, try the brown ones.
Can I see you outside a minute?
I don't know what's happening to you.
You're starting to look like
the Pillsbury Doughboy.
- You're falling apart.
- I know! I know.
I don't know what came over me.
Just get some help.
You should see a doctor, a shrink.
A dietitian, anything.
Just get some help.
(PANTING)
(CHUCKLING)
- Okay, Scott. The time is up.
- Whew!
- Get over here and check your pulse.
- All right.
Okay? Hmm.
Ah.
Well, nuts. I...
Oh, no, your pulse is great.
I don't know, Scott.
You're as healthy as a horse.
Yeah. Clydesdale.
Okay, look. So, what?
You put on a little weight.
A little weight?
Does this look like a little weight to you?
Weight can fluctuate from year to year.
Fluctuate? You make it sound like
I'm retaining water.
I've gained 45 pounds in a week!
Pete, what's happening to me?
- What's your diet like?
- Milk and cookies.
- Really?
- But I don't finish all the milk.
Well, then, there is your problem.
Just try to cut back on the sweets.
Anything else?
Yeah. How fast does hair grow?
Facial hair?
What?
I shave in the morning
and in the afternoon, I look like this.
Well, it could be a hormonal imbalance.
- That would explain the mood swings.
- Mood swings?
Look at my hair. It's turning gray.
It's middle age, buddy. It happens.
And with that body,
you should be thankful you have hair.
Look, if it bothers you,
you can dye it, and you should diet!
(BOTH LAUGHING)
Just kidding.
Okay, up with the shirt.
Let's take a listen to the old ticker.
(LAUGHING) Whoa.
- Okay.
- Ooh. That's cold.
Ah.
(HEART BEATING TWICE)
(HEART BEATING THREE TIMES)
(HEART BEATING RHYTHMICALLY)
(ALL SHOUTING)
Get it!
What?
I want some ballet slippers.
- CHARLIE: Hi, Mom.
- Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
- Hold on now.
- Wait a minute. Wait, I'm not done.
Fax me. Hi, hey. This probably
looks pretty odd, doesn't it?
These kids lined up all by themselves.
Scott, I think it's safe to say
you're taking this Santa thing
to an unhealthy level.
Here's my card. Call me.
Scott, I really have to tell you
that this is beginning to scare me.
I never in my wildest...
Well, no, okay, maybe my wildest...
But certainly never
in my normal dreams...
But then this is Scott
we're talking about.
Laura, the point.
I never thought you would stoop
to changing your physical appearance
in order to make Charlie like you.
Do you have any concept of how
dangerous this is to a little boy?
- Whoa, whoa. "How dangerous"?
- Mom, what's the matter?
- Come on, Charlie. We're going home.
- But we just started.
You let him stay. I'll go.
If you don't get your act together, Scott,
so help me...
MAN: Watch it, folks.
- Mom!
- I will just...
(DOOR BELL RINGING)
- Hi, there.
- Hi. I got a delivery for S.C.
- You S. C?
- Scott Calvin, that's me.
Sign here, please.
(CHUCKLES) All right.
- Thanks. I'll get your packages.
- Packages?
- Yeah. There's quite a few of them.
- That's great.
I'll leave the door open.
Just leave them inside here.
Will do.
(WHISTLING)
It's the list!
"Armand Assante"?
Yo!
(ENGINE STARTING)
Hold it! Hold... Oh! Hold it!
You! You! Take that... Come on!
Come on!
- (HORN HONKING)
- Stay away from the truck.
What am I supposed to do with all
these packages, guys? Come on!
(GROANS)
You know, I knew it. I knew that
something was going on. I just...
What I can't believe is that he would
go behind our backs all this time,
confusing Charlie again just...
I... What are we supposed to do?
Well, there's one obvious alternative.
Okay.
- Annie, nice.
- Beep!
- Johnny, naughty.
- Johnny, wait up!
Gary, nice. (CHUCKLING)
Veronica, very nice.
In your dreams, sleigh boy.
Hmm?
(SIGHING)
I'm in big trouble. Mmm-hmm.
Thank you.
(PHONE RINGING)
WOMAN: Judge Wayland's office.
Charlie, do you mind if
I talk to you for a minute?
It's okay, honey. Come on.
We won't be long.
Are we doing the right thing, Neal?
- Something needs to shake Scott.
- Yeah, but...
But to take away his visitation rights.
- Honey, the man is delusional.
- Okay, okay.
So maybe I'm having second thoughts,
kind of. I just...
I mean, what was so bad about
Charlie believing in Santa?
Well, he's a little old.
Oh, come on, Laura.
Don't you remember when you stopped
believing in Santa Claus?
I was Charlie's age, I guess.
I wrote Santa a letter
every week that year.
Well, okay. You know, maybe...
Maybe not every week.
But...
Boy, I really wanted
a Mystery Date Game.
Do you remember those?
No. Of course you don't.
You know, no one does.
I don't even think
they make them anymore, but...
Well, anyway...
Christmas morning came and...
Oh, I got dozens of presents.
I got everything.
Except Mystery Date.
I was three, and it was
an Oscar Mayer wienie whistle.
Christmas came. No wienie whistle.
And that's when I stopped believing.
You were three?
Yeah.
Oh, Neal.
Where's Charlie?
- I want to talk to him.
- He's with the judge.
Dad!
(GRUNTING)
It's all okay. I told the judge everything
about you and the North Pole.
After reviewing all of your testimonies,
I've come to a very difficult decision.
I'm sorry to do this in light
of the holiday season.
But in the best interest of the child,
I'm granting the petition
of Dr. And Mrs. Miller.
(CHARLIE SOBBING)
Mr. Calvin, as of today, all of your
visitation rights are suspended,
pending a hearing
after the first of the year.
(SIGHS)
(DOOR BELL RINGING)
- Hey, Neal.
- Scott?
You're not supposed to be here.
Don't make me beat you up, Neal.
Oh, would Santa really
beat someone up?
- I'm this close.
- So you still believe you're Santa?
I don't know.
CHARLIE: What do you mean
you don't know?
Of course you are, Dad.
How can you say that?
- Think of all those kids.
- The only kid I'm thinking about is you.
Dad, I'm fine. You can't let them down.
- They all believe in you.
- Charlie, listen.
You listen!
You think you know who he is.
- You don't!
- Charlie.
Honey, listen. You're confused.
- I know exactly who he is.
- Charlie! He's not Santa.
He is, too, Santa.
We went to the North Pole together.
I saw it. The elves are real old
even though they look like me.
Bernard called me sport,
'cause he knew everything. Right, Dad?
Remember!
Thank you, Charlie. Thank you.
(WHISPERING) I love you, Dad.
Could you guys leave us
alone for a minute?
I mean, so I can say
goodbye to him properly?
Sure.
So! You saw the ball come to life.
You bet I did.
Well, Charlie, I guess I better go.
- I'll get my stuff.
- Wait, sport. Wait, wait.
I think it's a much better idea
if you stayed here with your mom.
I want to be with you, Dad.
(CHUCKLING)
Boy, I love hearing you say that.
You mean I can go?
(CHIMES JINGLING)
BERNARD: Boy, this bird is dry.
Haven't you people
heard about basting?
Bernard!
Hiya, sport.
Bernard, can I go?
Please, can I go, Bernard?
It's okay with me.
Charlie, if...
Charlie?
Scott!
Charlie!
(WIND HOWLING)
This is our perpetrator!
Scott Calvin, 38 years old.
Believes himself to be Santa Claus.
Ladies and gentlemen, this one
is not going to be easy to find.
Won't the bright red suit
and beard give him away?
(ALL SNICKERING)
Charlie's got some great ideas
on how to keep you safe.
Santa, this is Quintin,
head of research and development.
- Quintin, good to meet ya.
- Hello, Santa.
Charlie and I have
put our heads together.
I think we've got a few surprises for you.
This is some of the best stuff that's
come out of the workshop since the ball.
Fabulous. What happens
if I fall off the roof?
Is this the most
current photo you have?
(PHONE RINGING)
Hold on.
(CLEARING THROAT) Hello?
- CHARLIE ON PHONE: Mom!
- Oh, Charlie. Oh, my God.
Honey, how are you? Where are you?
- Are you okay?
- I'm fine. We're up at the North Pole.
- Charlie, are you sure you're okay?
- I'm terrific.
I'm helping the elves
build a new sleigh.
We're trying for a vertical takeoff.
Well, gotta go.
- The elves need me.
- No. Charlie, wait.
- No. Don't hang up. Charlie, don't...
- See you at Christmas.
(DISCONNECTS CALL)
BERNARD: Fireplaces will
no longer be a problem.
It's a new fabric.
Completely flame retardant.
It's light, yet durable.
And you can wear the jumpsuit
under your coat and pants.
But what do I do if I fall off a roof?
We'll cordon off a three-block radius
around Dr. Miller's house.
Calvin is to be apprehended unharmed.
And remember, he'll probably
be dressed like Santa Claus.
(ROCK SONG PLAYING)
(TIRES SCREECHING)
(SIRENS WAILING)
Give it your best shot
What you got is oh, so sweet
(SIREN WAILING)
- Freeze!
- What?
I need a routine, gimme all your loving
Not even my suit. It's a rental.
Gimme all your loving
Don't let up until we're through
"From Comet, to Santa."
Did you make the card?
(GRUNTING)
It's a nice rope.
Just in case I fall off the roof?
(GRUNTING)
Comet, this means a lot to me.
Thanks, buddy.
If I blow my top
Will you let it go to your head?
Gimme all your loving
All right, let's go!
- You ready to go, sport?
- You betcha, Dad.
Now Dasher, now Dancer!
Now Prancer and Vixen!
On Comet, on Cupid!
On Donner and Blitzen!
Hah!
CHARLIE: Bye! Bye, Quintin!
Bye, Peewee!
Merry Christmas!
Hyah!
- (GRUNTS)
- CHARLIE: Whoa.
Take your time.
Turn to your right. Hello!
No.
Charlie, stay in your seat.
I gotta show you this.
Radar-jamming jingle bells,
snow screen,
DC-10 alert and air freshener.
- Wow!
- And most important of all,
- your hat.
- My hat?
It's lined with a two-way radio.
Microphone's in here.
It connects you directly to Judy.
- Wait a minute. What's this?
- Oh, that's a CD.
- Compact disc.
- No. Cookie/cocoa dispenser.
The cocoa comes out nice and hot.
And out pops a cookie.
How could I have done this
without ya, Charlie?
- You couldn't.
- (CHUCKLES)
(CHIMES JINGLING)
(SHUSHING)
You're fatter this year.
Thank you very much.
You've grown, too.
And you were a very good girl this year,
but I want you to
go back to sleep, okay?
(GULPING)
(SMACKING LIPS)
(GAGGING)
- I think the milk's a little sour.
- It's soy milk.
Huh?
You said you were lactose intolerant.
I did say that, didn't I?
Thanks for remembering.
Go to sleep.
(CHIMES JINGLING)
Merry Christmas, Sara.
Merry Christmas, Santa.
CHARLIE: Look, there's Mom
and Neal's street.
- Can we go there next?
- Sure.
I made something for them
at the workshop.
(SCOTT HUMMING)
(HUMMING CONTINUES)
Freeze!
Oh! (LAUGHS)
You officers really gave me a start.
- Merry Christmas, guys.
- Not for you, fat boy.
"Fat boy"? Guys.
Uh-uh-uh. Nice and easy now.
Guys, guys. I got a lot of work to do.
This is a big mistake.
You got to watch the suit, too.
This is so old. It's an antique, you know.
- Where's the boy?
- He's in the sleigh.
We got Calvin. We're bringing him out.
CHARLIE OVER MICROPHONE:
Santa, are you okay? Over, over.
(GRUNTING)
- Watch your head.
- Santa? Are you all right?
- Santa?
- It'll be okay, kids.
Let him go! Let Santa go!
(SIREN WAILING)
NEAL: Honey, I'm sure Charlie's fine.
We've got a problem. Santa was
at the Millers, but he's not responding.
Well, time to deploy E.L.F.S.
(BELL TOLLING)
Let's go!
(BELLS CHIMING)
Go, go, go, go!
(WATCH BEEPING)
(WHOOSHING)
Look, I know you're Scott Calvin.
You know you're Scott Calvin.
So let's make this simple.
I say, name. You say, Scott Calvin.
- Name?
- Kriss Kringle.
- Sinterklaas.
- Name?
- Pre Nol.
Babbo Natale. Pelz-Nicole.
Topo Gigio. (LAUGHS)
Okay, Calvin. Maybe a couple of hours
in the tank'll change your mind.
(SLURPING)
(WATCHES BEEPING)
- Charlie?
- Yeah?
Don't worry. We're the good guys.
Come on. Let's go save Santa.
We can't.
The police are watching this place.
Yeah, they probably are.
But you see, we weren't figuring
on walking out the front door.
We find that we can get around
a lot faster if we fly.
Now grab hold of my hand.
And hang on tight.
- And Charlie?
- Yeah?
Don't ever try this
without elf supervision.
(LAUGHING)
(DOOR CREAKING)
We're looking for Santa Claus.
Go home, kids. Visiting hours are over.
We're not kids, and we're not visiting.
- We're here to bust out my dad.
- You're the Calvin boy.
Who are these other kids?
We're your worst nightmare.
Elves with attitude.
(LAUGHING)
Shouldn't have had that donut.
Untie me! I mean it!
Untie... (MUFFLED YELLING)
- Charlie!
- Are you okay, Dad?
I am now.
(WHISTLING)
How'd you do that?
Tinsel. Not just for decoration.
Hey, excuse me.
Can I get some of that tinsel?
(DOOR OPENING)
CHARLIE: Mom?
Mom!
Neal? I'm home!
Charlie?
- Charlie? Oh, my God, Charlie!
- Charlie.
Sweetheart. Oh, God.
Come here, come here.
Oh, my boy. Oh, sweetheart.
My boy, you're home!
I missed you so much. How are you?
- I'm fine, Mom.
- LAURA: Are you okay? Look at me.
- Charlie, I missed you, honey.
- Mom, I'm fine. It's okay.
(SIREN WAILING)
- LAURA: I was so worried.
- Mom, put me down.
- Stop kissing me.
- I don't have a lot of time.
Did you leave the gifts
I made under the tree?
- You bet I did.
- We better go.
- No, Charlie. No, no, no.
- No! Wait, Charlie.
It's okay, Laura.
Actually, I...
I think it's a much better idea
that you stay here
with your mom and Neal.
- Really?
- But, Dad...
No buts, Charlie. I can't be selfish.
I can't be with ya all the time.
We're a family.
You, me, your mom...
And Neal.
And they need to be with ya, too.
I miss you too much.
(SOBBING)
Come here a minute.
(CHIMES JINGLING)
Listen to me.
Come on, listen.
There's a lot of kids out there.
Okay? Millions of kids.
They all believe in me.
They're counting on me, Charlie.
I'm not gonna let 'em down.
I got a lot of work to do.
So I can't be selfish either.
You gave me a wonderful gift.
Listen, a wonderful gift.
You believed in me
when nobody else did.
You helped make me Santa.
Selfish? Come on.
You're the least selfish person I know.
I love you, Santa Claus.
(SOBBING)
I love you, son.
(SHUSHING)
It's okay. Okay. It's okay. (SHUSHING)
Laura, what do you think?
Christmas Eve
you guys spend with Charlie?
Oh, my God.
It's you.
It really is you.
You really are
Santa Claus.
- Pretty cool, huh?
- Oh, my God.
And your parents thought
I'd never amount to anything.
(CHUCKLING)
Wait. Don't go yet.
I have something for you.
It's Santa.
- Scott.
- Neal.
Santa?
It's okay, Neal.
(GRUNTS)
Here.
It's... Well, it's...
It's my Christmas present for you.
It's the custody papers.
And I want you to come
and see Charlie as often as you can.
SCOTT: You can count on it.
Thanks, Laura.
Merry Christmas.
What's all this boo-hooing going
on here? Hey, how ya doing?
It's nothing, Bernard.
I'm just saying goodbye to Charlie.
What goodbye?
You still got the glass ball, right?
Yeah.
Well, all you got to do is shake it
whenever you want to see your dad.
Really?
BERNARD:
He can come back to see you
anytime, day or night.
Hey, have I ever steered ya wrong?
Nice sweater.
Hey, did we make this?
Laura. He's sucking us
into his delusions.
Look at the elaborate
measures he's taken.
Neal, relax.
I'll explain it to you later.
Where'd he go?
(SIRENS WAILING)
Go, go, go, go!
Team one!
Okay, stand back, folks.
Give us some room.
- Here you go, sir.
- Thanks.
Return to your homes!
Stay off the street!
Come on, folks. Let us do our job here.
Excuse me, excuse me. Hi!
You know, you don't
have to send anybody...
- Hey! Hey!
- Oh, my gosh!
That's my ex-husband
and he's already up the chimney.
Chief, look up there.
(CROWD GASPING)
BOY: Santa Claus!
Santa.
MAN: Look!
GIRL: What is it?
Oh, wow!
Up there. Do you see it?
Hey, do you see it?
- Goodbye, Charlie.
- Bye, Dad!
Merry Christmas to all!
And to all a good night!
I'm sorry, Charlie.
That's okay, Neal.
You were just denying your inner child.
(LAUGHING)
You're gonna make a great psychiatrist
one day, kid.
No, I think I'm going to go
into the family business.
Look out below!
NEAL: My wienie whistle.
(BLOWING WHISTLE)
(ELVES LAUGHING)
- Bye!
- Merry Christmas!
(ELVES LAUGHING)
(DOOR OPENING)
LAURA: Charlie? Time to come inside.
CHARLIE: Mom,
this stupid ball's not working.
Shoot.
- Hey, sport!
- Dad!
You miss me already?
I've been gone, what? Ten minutes?
Give me a break.
I was on my way to Cleveland.
Come here and give me a hug.
(GRUNTS)
- Do you want to go for a quick ride?
- Yeah!
- Of course, it's up to your mom.
- Please, Mom.
Go on. Get out of here.
All right. Hold on.
- On our way.
- Bye, Mom!
Just a quick one.
And...
Not over any oceans, Scott.
- Bye, Mom! Bye!
- Scott.
Scott!
Santa!
(CHRISTMAS SONG PLAYING)
All the brightly colored paper
Lies around the Christmas tree
While mothers shake their heads
And pack the decorations carefully
All the little children know that
Monday's just another day
They feel a little sad to think
That Santa's gone away
But Christmas will return
And joyful hearts like candles burn
With love for all the little ones
In countries far and near
And if we live and learn
To show the world our real concern
Then Christmas will return, yeah
Every year
Yeah
Take a little Christmas spirit
With you into each new year
Make a little Christmas spirit
Last till Easter Sunday's here
Take it with you through the summer
Till the autumn leaves arrive
In the bitter cold of winter
The spark is still alive
Christmas will return
And joyful hearts like candles burn
With love for all the little ones
In countries far and near
And if we live and learn
To show the world our real concern
Then Christmas will return
Every year
Christmas will return
So much
Love for the little ones
Oh, they can live and learn
Yeah
Take it with you through the summer
Till the autumn leaves arrive
In the bitter cold of winter
See the spark is still alive
Oh, oh, Christmas will return
Joyful hearts like candles burn
With love for all the little ones
In counties far and near
If we live and learn
To show the world our real concern
Christmas will return
Every year