Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org
(ROCK MUSIC PLAYING ON CAR STEREO)
(VEHICLE APPROACHING)
(MUSIC STOPS)
Jane!
Jane, it's me! Open up.
Did you tell anyone?
Did I...
About the name. The name?
Yeah, I told Rick.
He thought it was funny. (CHUCKLES)
Just Rick and nobody else?
No.
Why, what's the matter?
Larry, what's wrong?
I'm sorry.
You have no idea how sorry I am.
Larry, you're scaring me.
What are you doing?
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
- (GUNSHOT)
- (DOG BARKING)
(PANTING)
(GASPING)
(WHIMPERS)
Rick!
Ricky!
(RICK BREATHING HEAVILY)
(SOBBING)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
Rick, the name!
RICK: (SOBBING) Janey!
Did you tell anyone? Anyone!
Larry, please, please! I...
Rick, he's coming!
The name!
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
Giselle. I told Giselle!
(RICK GROANING)
(GUNSHOT)
I'm going to stop you!
(PANTING)
(LARRY SOBS)
Giselle!
(GISELLE SCREAMS)
- ANNA: Larry...
- GISELLE: Mom!
Who did you tell?
GISELLE: He killed them!
LARRY: Don't think it.
- ANNA: Mom, come on!
- LARRY: Don't say it.
Don't think it. Don't say it.
Giselle! Did you say the name?
Don't say it.
Who did you say the name to, Giselle?
GISELLE: (SCREAMS)
What the hell are you...
- Larry!
- (GUNSHOT)
(TRAIN HORN BLOWING)
JOHN: What's up, playboy?
- How's it going?
- Good.
(GRUNTS) Today is a good day.
- You got the key?
- No, it's under the mat.
Oh! Come on.
ELLIOT: It's only 20 minutes.
This is the first time he's rented the place.
The guy says it's fantastic.
JOHN: What else would he say,
"It's a dog house"?
ELLIOT: No, I'm trying to convince her, let's go.
Come on, man, work with me.
- Sash?
- SASHA: Yeah. I'm up for it.
(DOOR CREAKING)
It's a little creepy. Right?
Nah, it's just cold.
Heat's off.
I've got to piss like a race horse.
Cute.
Dude, this place is sweet, bro.
Hey.
Right?
We could put the desk over there.
We could put the bed here.
Well, maybe if there was a bed.
I know, the landlord said
it was fully furnished.
JOHN: Yo, El, come and check
this out, man. This is crazy.
Come on down.
Yo, El, come in here, man.
See, you can't get this
in the dorms, right?
Now, that's classic.
John, you really think Sasha
wants to see that, or that?
You got the whole upstairs
to make girly, okay?
- I've definitely seen bigger.
- See? You're awesome.
Bro, she's awesome, man.
SASHA: Oh, yeah, you guys must've
been hilarious when you were young.
"Must've been"? Are.
- Tier 1.
- (BOTH CHUCKLING)
Hey, he made me look smart,
and I made him look ugly.
ELLIOT: But after the crash,
he took care of me.
Talk shit about my
boy's folks, you're done.
Okay, when the Tier 1s are both ready
to cook and clean and help me
do this place up right.
'Cause I'm not going
to be your guys' maid.
Of course not. I told him. Right?
Well, I never cooked you
my butter pasta-nette.
(CHUCKLES) That is not a thing.
- That's 'cause I invented it.
- Okay.
And I clean, too.
I promise.
Yo, what does this do?
Yeah, you cook.
JOHN: Yes, I cook, okay? I don't bake.
(EXHALES)
ELLIOT: Found the furniture.
I've heard about you and all the girls.
And that's exactly why we need
to get out of the dorms.
This is perfect.
Whoa. Easy.
You all right?
Yeah, thanks.
So, it looks like
the landlord wasn't lying.
- Wow.
- (JOHN CHUCKLES)
Damn, son.
Hey, I like this.
(ELECTRICITY CRACKLING)
(THUD)
Ow. Fuck.
So?
Don't you want to?
Well, yeah, yeah. I do. Now I know you...
Yo, all the dishes in here, they're white.
Just saying.
He touches everything.
It's up to you, Bear.
I can't afford it without him.
I know you can, but I don't...
Elliot. Elliot.
- Yeah?
- We're doing it. Obviously.
- (CHUCKLES) Yeah.
I see she approves, huh?
(JOHN GRUNTING)
- Hey, you need a hand?
- No, I got this.
- Okay, don't break yourself.
- Better than going to the gym, right?
(DISTANT BANG)
(BANGING CONTINUES)
- Hey, Elliot?
- Yeah?
- Hey, did you hear that banging?
- Yeah.
(BANGING)
The radiators sound worse.
ELLIOT: Okay, Bear, here it is.
Rilke says, "Coins symbolize
the wonder and terror of fortune.
"Do you land face up
or face down in the dirt?
"What home will you be born into?
"With whom will you fall in love?
"Fortune is truly like a coin
tossed by the hand of God."
I'm wiped.
Hmm.
Thanks for finding me that quote.
You wanna watch something stupid?
Mmm-hmm.
Just us, yeah.
I'm gonna brush my teeth.
Hey, what's on the bed?
(CHUCKLES SOFTLY)
(READING) "You look like
a model from the '70s.
"The personal pilot of
a James Bond villain.
"A 19-year-old koala bear person."
(CHUCKLES)
"If any of them were true,
I wouldn't have you.
"But they're not, and I do.
"Amazingly.
"Bullshit aside,
I never thought I would meet,
"let alone be with, anyone like you.
"With so much love,
"Your Knight, Beau, Casanova
and new roommate, Elliot.
"No animals were harmed
in the making of this card!"
(CHUCKLES)
(CLATTERING)
Hey, Elliot, that's not funny!
Elliot?
Hey.
What's wrong?
Hey!
What's up, man?
- Oh, Little brother!
- How's it going?
Look at this place. Fantastic.
- Hi, darling.
- Hey.
Hi, Uncle Elliot!
- Hey, Niece Alice!
- Hey, hey.
- Hey, there.
- Hey.
Sorry we're so early,
your brother's pathological.
It's called being prompt and professional.
- Virgil's awesome.
- Thank you.
Oh, hey, I almost forgot.
Here's your housewarming present.
You going to help me drink it?
(GIGGLES) No!
(ALL CHUCKLE)
Look at this.
- (ALL CHEERING)
- (MUSIC PLAYING)
So, a house off-campus with
John Henry and a live-in girlfriend.
You ready for this?
She's the one, Virgil.
She did all this herself.
That's great, it's just,
you know... Be smart.
Be a student, man.
It's the last time to have
no responsibilities. Enjoy it.
I don't want that. I want what you have.
An amazing wife, an amazing daughter.
VIRGIL: Well, just don't rush it.
That's all out there waiting for you.
Believe me, what I have is great. It is.
But I missed out on all this.
I mean, what a college edu-ma-cation
could have done for me.
You have a scholarship, man.
You should be upstairs studying right now.
Jesus. It's a good
thing you're not jealous.
It is good.
(SONG PLAYING)
JOHN: Come on, man,
you got this. You got this!
Come on, come on, come on. Come on.
All right, all right.
(BOTH CHEERING)
Baby!
JOHN: Bam! Thank you! Thank you!
(DOOR CREAKING)
(COIN CLATTERS)
ELLIOT: An oldy-old gold coin, huh?
Yeah, I put it back on the little table
next to the bed.
I didn't want to keep it.
It's 'cause you're the best, most honest,
smartest, cutest, heaviest,
oldest person here.
I'm not the heaviest, or the oldest.
Dad's the oldest and he's the heaviest.
What?
She ratted me out.
Here.
Head-bump.
Fist-bump.
That's John's room, we're upstairs.
VIRGIL: All right, we're out of here.
Buddy, great party.
Be good.
ELLIOT: Bye, guys. Bye, Alice.
Kim? She's in my Lit class.
Girls who wear hats inside
are crazy, you know that, right?
She's going to do a psychic
cleansing after everyone leaves.
- Cool, can I leave, too?
- No.
She's just gonna burn some sage,
and you are going to be nice.
Maybe you need a hat.
It's a twist-off.
Oh, thank you.
John, do you think this house is creepy?
- Mmm.
- Yup.
I don't, but I'm not a girl.
And I think you should get dressed,
'cause we're playing baseball.
Why do jocks always have
to play games, even at a party?
"Don't think it. Don't say it.
"Don't say it. Don't think it."
Miss Sasha steps up to the plate.
She's going long! She's going long!
Okay, all right, all right. You got this?
All right.
- Oh! Yes!
- (SASHA CHUCKLES)
- Oh, you all right?
- Yeah. (CHUCKLING)
You're drunk.
So, you thought
there were sounds and what?
- "Bad vibrations"?
- Yeah.
And now if they're gone,
then what's the big deal?
We burned all that bad shit away, right?
That's tight.
You're actually psychic?
Sensitive, my mother says.
Oh, "Sensitive," huh?
So, what, your mom locked you under
the stairs when you were a kid?
You shoot knives at her.
Yeah. No.
But I could find stuff.
I always knew when people were
coming over to the house.
You know what I'm thinking?
Yes. I might just do that.
Damn, you are psychic.
Sensitive there, for sure.
- Elliot...
- It's okay, Sasha.
People have doubted me my whole life.
Elliot, you can go ahead
and live a sheltered, shallow,
physical existence.
Well, a non-physical existence
would be kind of tough.
What Aristotle is trying to say is...
Well, he needs proof.
Yeah, is that crazy?
Okay, let's just take some deep breaths.
Okay.
So, if nothing happens,
I should believe, 'cause it means
you got rid of the spirit.
- Elliot, come on.
- What?
We all know you don't believe
in this stuff, okay?
But can you just please let her do it?
Right. Sorry. No being rational.
I give over. I do.
Yo, El, just loosen up
the grip a little bit,
I'm trying to concentrate on my breathing.
Are you ready, ladies?
Okay, let's do this thing. Come on.
Now, I have no ego about it,
but I do know this stuff.
Okay, cool. Well, what do you know?
Okay.
I know your parents died in a crash.
Dude...
He didn't tell me.
They did.
Bro, I didn't say anything. Swear.
I would never tell anyone that.
They're worried about you, though.
All right, I'm sorry I laughed at you
before, but that's not funny.
I'm not being funny, Elliot.
This is just what I'm getting.
Okay, how did they die?
What kind of accident was it?
Your brother will do anything
in his power to protect you now.
But they worry that
he's taking on too much.
All right. So, you talked
to my brother tonight.
Sasha, your...
Your grandmother has some
biscuits or rolls or something.
Gam's Rolls?
Come on, everybody's grandma
bakes biscuits.
Yeah. He's not wrong about that.
This is... This is... You know what?
You want to blindfold me, too?
Just hang on.
I'll take you up on that, though.
I'm all down for the blindfolding,
- whatever you got...
- Of course.
Okay, what'd I hide? Where'd I hide it?
- Oh, come on. That's crazy.
- Elliot...
Shh.
You know what? I...
I don't like this.
Yeah, I don't want to do this anymore.
Maybe this was a bad idea.
ELLIOT: Nah, come on.
You're a good faker, I admit it.
You put the keys in a pot on the stove.
Did you?
You heard.
You were listening for it, weren't you?
Well, I didn't hear that, did you?
No.
- Something's coming.
- SASHA: What?
They're saying,
"Don't...
"Don't think it.
"Don't say it.
"Don't say it. Don't think it.
"Don't say it! Don't think it!
Don't say it! Don't think it!
"Don't say it! Don't think it!"
Don't say or think what?
The Bye Bye Man.
(SASHA SCREAMS)
JOHN: Jesus! What the fuck?
Kim! Oh, my God.
Hey...
- What happened, Kim?
- Kim?
Are you all right?
(STEAM BLOWING)
(GASPS)
- Sorry.
- What are you doing?
Nothing. Nothing. Sorry.
(COUGHING)
Are you sick?
Good night. Love you.
I love you, John.
What?
Hey. You're joking, right?
Sasha, you're kidding, right?
(WOMAN SCREAMS)
What?
What the hell is that?
KIM: Come on!
John, let's go!
JOHN: Look, I'm trying...
(KIM GRUNTS AND PANTS)
- KIM: Like this?
- (JOHN MOANING)
(DISTANT SNARLING)
(SNARLING CONTINUES)
Hey.
Shh.
- What are you doing?
- Do you hear that?
What the hell is that?
You ready?
Thanks for being nice to me last night.
That was pretty crazy.
It was. Definitely.
You want to go inside?
My roommate's car isn't here.
We could try again.
These things happen, right?
Actually, not to me, they don't.
Yeah.
Actually, not to me, either.
A guy not finishing up,
I've never had that happen before.
Come on.
I'm hungry.
Jesus.
What?
Nothing.
Nothing, okay?
Kim, I need to go.
Now.
Fuck.
Dude, check this out.
They were already there, right?
No.
It was Colin or one of
those douches from last night.
No, listen, I heard it.
I heard something after
the party outside, scratching.
What do you mean, you heard something?
(SASHA COUGHING)
Morning.
See, you are clean and beautiful.
That's nice.
What was that?
- John, you drive Kim home?
- Yeah.
And now I gotta wash her off.
The girl's gross, man. Total pig.
Come on, man, that's not cool.
Don't say that.
JOHN: Oh, sure, yeah,
it's easy for you to say.
Your girlfriend is perfect.
(COUGHING)
Oh, God.
You okay?
I don't know, maybe I shouldn't be
playing baseball in the cold.
That's the problem
with being an alcoholic.
Oh, shut up, I didn't
even drink that much.
Maybe that was the mistake.
I'll make you some tea.
(SIGHS)
Come on.
Fuck him.
(SHOWER RUNNING)
Bear, you went away there for a second.
I did?
Yeah. Where'd you go?
God, you're shivering.
I was just thinking.
About John?
(HUMMING)
(COUGHING)
(EXHALES DEEPLY)
VIRGIL: (ON PHONE)
No, little brother, it's cool.
You can call me any time, you know that.
Are you really taking on too much?
Are you worried about protecting me?
What is going on?
Is it Sasha?
Yeah, she's been really sick and scared.
And John's been acting weird.
You guys seemed like you were great.
Were we? You saw them dancing together.
Talk to me, buddy, what's going on?
(DISTANT SNARLING)
Elliot?
What?
You wanna go get lunch
tomorrow or something,
we'll talk about this then?
You know what, listen, I gotta go.
There's something I gotta...
I gotta deal with something.
- El...
- (LINE DISCONNECTS)
Guys?
Guys, what are you doing up there?
(SNARLING CONTINUES)
(DOOR CREAKS)
(SNARLING)
Hello? Anyone down there?
Hello?
(SNARLING)
(SCREECHING)
Hello?
(COIN CLATTERING)
Guys! Help!
(WHIMPERING)
No!
Guys!
What are you doing, Elliot?
- You were here the whole time?
- Yes.
That's bullshit.
But we were, Elliot.
You didn't answer me.
- We didn't hear you!
- What were you doing?
Studying, talking...
- You didn't hear me? You didn't hear me?
- We weren't doing anything.
Elliot, for the last time, bro,
we wouldn't do that to you!
Why are you lying to me?
- We're not!
- Jesus Christ.
Then what just happened, huh?
And there were sounds... I mean, come on!
I told you there was something happening.
Now do you believe me?
Hey, don't worry, okay?
What are you doing? Don't do that.
- Don't do what?
- Don't...
- Elliot...
- No, no, no. Don't touch her.
- What?
- Don't touch her!
You are a crazy paranoid, bro!
(ELLIOT SIGHS)
Yeah, you're a little warm.
Okay, so you weren't with John.
Am I hearing things? Am I seeing things?
Tonight you thought the house
was empty when we were here.
You went away, Elliot.
I kind of went away, too.
What?
SASHA: I sat down to study...
I don't remember doing any of that.
It's like now that I know his name,
he's coming for me.
And the more I try to get rid of it,
the bigger it gets.
It's horrible.
Hey, babe.
Bye Bye Man's not real.
It's just something that's in our heads.
That's real.
Ideas are real.
If it's not,
then, Elliot, we're all losing
our minds at the same time.
And what are the chances of that?
(SNARLING)
(TRAIN HORN BLOWING)
(COIN CLATTERING)
(DISTANT THUD)
- What the hell is that?
- What is it?
What...
Elliot, there's nothing here.
So, you're not going to be late, right?
No, I'll meet you at 2:00 sharp,
right where we parked.
I'm going to find out how real
this thing is. The name...
You're going to talk to the landlord
about the furniture?
And the house.
Maybe he can find somewhere else.
You're feeling better, though?
I guess.
It's hard to be scared
in the middle of the day.
I'm going to take care of you.
(COUGHING)
Oh, my God.
You're shivering.
I'm going to figure this out, I promise.
I'll see you at 2:00.
I love you.
"Register Archive. Dead File 69. Redmon."
MRS. WATKINS: Here, put these on.
- ELLIOT: Really?
- MRS. WATKINS: Yeah.
They're originals and we don't want
your sweaty palms messing up
the documents in the box.
Now, the dead file has dead articles,
material that got
killed before going to press,
but still saved for posterity.
And it was written by Redmon.
- Thanks.
- Mmm-hmm.
(COUGHING)
(CASH REGISTER RINGING)
MR. DAIZY: Thank you, Dennis.
- Mr. Daizy?
- Yes, how are you doing?
Not so great, actually.
Uh, me and my friends
are renting your place
out in Sun Prairie. 37 Oakdale.
Oh, yeah, the two handsome guys.
Are you with them?
You have a weird house, Mr. Daizy.
Really, it's awful.
Well, I'm sorry that you feel that way,
but they did sign a lease.
(SNEEZES AND COUGHS)
Bless you.
Sorry.
- You okay?
- It's really cold in here.
It's a hothouse.
It's actually not cold at all, honey.
Maybe you should be home in bed?
Look, Mr. Daizy.
There was an old nightstand
in the basement.
And it has this writing inside it.
Where did it come from?
A nightstand?
COOPER: Let's begin by
considering this wall...
Now, we can all agree that the sentence...
- Sorry.
- Yeah, have a seat.
Now, we can all agree that this sentence,
"This is a wall," is a truth claim.
This wall is real. I see it, you see it.
We can touch it.
Likewise, if I were to brush
a few atoms from this wall,
it would still be here.
It would still be here before us.
It would still be "the wall."
But what if I continued
to slowly brush the atoms,
one by one, away from this wall?
Well, at first,
you'd say it's still a wall.
I brush a few more,
well, it's still a wall.
But what if I remove every single atom
from this wall except for one?
And you've seen me brush
every single atom from this wall
except for that one atom,
and I point to it, and I say,
"There, that's what's left."
That's the wall.
Now, is it?
Is that the wall?
What the...
- (STUDENTS LAUGHING)
- All right, John?
Welcome back.
Language and reality
inform each other as we construct...
ELLIOT: Okay, I'm looking up
The Bye Bye Man, right?
There's nothing online, so I type in,
"Don't say it, don't think it,"
and it led me here,
the dead archives and Redmon.
Here's what was in his folder.
I think you write it and repeat it
to try and keep from saying...
The Bye Bye Man.
Okay, but why is that in the dead files?
"October 18, 1969, byline, Larry Redmon.
"Deerfield, Iowa.
"A teenager, accused of murdering
"his own family and four other youths.
"When asked by this reporter why he
would do such a thing, he replied,
"'The Bye Bye Man made me do it."'
It's an article about
a kid who went crazy.
But it was never published.
And Larry Redmon, the writer...
He was pretty infamous locally.
After he killed this piece
about the kid in Deerfield,
Larry Redmon took a shotgun
and murdered eight friends
and family members
right here in Madison.
- Don't say it. Don't think it.
- ANNA: Mom!
- Mom!
Don't say it.
Mom, shut the door!
Giselle! Who did you tell?
No one! We didn't tell anyone, Larry!
(GUNSHOT)
Mommy!
Stop!
We didn't tell anyone!
I swear we didn't say anything!
Get back! Please!
(GUNSHOT)
Maybe he got inspired by
what he was writing about.
(GUN CLICKS)
(PANTING)
(GRUNTS)
(SNARLING)
(GROWLING)
(BREATHING DEEPLY)
You won't win.
I won't let you.
(GULPING)
(ELECTRICITY CRACKLING)
(GAGGING)
(GURGLING)
There are no other mentions
of these cases anywhere else.
It's like someone redacted the whole story,
so no one else could read it.
Why would anyone do that?
Well, obviously he was bat-shit crazy.
But, if you remove all references
to something in the past,
that past no longer exists.
Even the idea of it is gone.
Maybe somebody wanted to make this
Bye Bye Man disappear permanently.
And you've got the
last record of it right there.
I'll be back.
Good, I have time.
Don't write it either, idiot.
(ELECTRICITY CRACKLING)
What are you doing, boy?
Are you out of your mind?
I, um...
- What is wrong with you, Elliot, huh?
- What the...
I'm sorry, I need to go. I'm late.
Elliot!
(PANTING)
Oh, my God.
Sasha!
Hey, John!
Hey.
(DOORBELL BUZZING)
Hello.
Kim, it's Elliot.
Elliot... God, I was just
thinking about you guys.
- You wanna come up?
- Listen. Listen.
Um, what are you doing?
You mean, right now? Or since the party?
- Isn't that why you're here?
- Kim, can you come down?
I want to do another séance.
Right now, with all
four of us, at the house.
Listen, you were right.
I was wrong.
Sure.
I'll be down in a sec.
ELLIOT: The Bye Bye Man doesn't exist
anywhere else that I could find.
You don't have to look for him, Elliot.
He's found us.
You can't help thinking about him.
And the more you think about him,
the closer he gets.
You see things that aren't there.
You don't see things that are there.
Or hear things.
- Like a coin rolling.
- Yeah.
Like a train.
Some people catch it and it spreads.
Some go crazy sooner,
but they all die in the end.
The word spreads
and he comes to you with...
With that thing.
I told Katie.
I didn't want to.
What can you do with
cancer but cut it out?
You have to stop it before it
spreads and every cell dies.
This could spread everywhere
if we don't cut it out.
Did you tell anyone?
Ms. Watkins, the librarian.
We have to get to her, too.
What do you mean, you have to get to her?
KIM: Stop!
Oh, my God!
Stop! Elliot, stop!
Let me help you!
(BELL CLANGING)
Kim! Wait!
Kim!
Kim! Kim!
No!
We have to help them!
- What do you see?
- It's a family!
It's in your head!
No, Kim! There's a train, a real train!
No!
Kim! Move! It's in your head!
Kim! No!
(BELL CLANGING)
(SIRENS WAILING)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
(INDISTINCT RADIO CHATTER)
Elliot, what happened?
Kim, she's dead.
Shit. Jesus.
- Oh, my God.
- It was him. He killed her.
You were right,
he's trying to get inside us.
He got in her. He's going to
drive us crazy and he's going to kill us.
- You mean the...
- Yeah.
He's why I was late to get you.
He's why you're feeling sick.
Have you said the name to anyone?
The name... No. No.
Have you?
No, I haven't said...
Good. Don't. We can't say
the name to anyone else, ever.
You going to tell me what to do now?
Swear you won't say the name
so we don't spread it.
- No...
- SASHA: John, please.
Please.
- Bro, swear it.
- You just need to cut this shit.
You swear!
- Swear!
- No.
- Elliot, stop it!
- Swear!
- What's wrong with you, Elliot?
- What's wrong with you?
- Elliot, stop it!
- Hey, guys!
- Hey, break it up!
I said break it up right now!
Back up.
- He got to you, didn't he?
- No one got to me, all right?
Admit it. He's making you feel angry.
- He's making you sick.
- JOHN: Yeah?
He's making you crazy.
You on something?
No, I'm upset.
We're just having a little argument.
You call that a "little argument"?
John, please.
Please don't say it.
Don't say what?
- Sasha?
- I won't.
J, you can't.
This name of some stupid shit
Elliot thinks is dangerous.
Yes. I was talking about Kim.
There was a hammer in her bag.
It was covered with blood.
Oh, my God.
Train's engineer said
that you were chasing Kim,
with the hammer.
He said she was crying for help,
and that she jumped out of your car
to get away from you.
Jesus Christ. Elliot?
That's not what happened.
No? They found Kim's roommate,
Katie Williams.
She was killed by a hammer, too, but...
You knew that, didn't you?
I... Sasha, no! I was at the library.
He made me lose track of time. You have...
SHAW: Sasha?
Do you want to talk to me here?
You want to tell me what's going on?
Don't say it. Don't
think it. You were right!
Quiet.
Sasha, what doesn't he want you to say?
- Yeah, Sash.
- You! Shut it!
(CLICKS TONGUE)
ELLIOT: It just happened, John.
You see that? It's him.
No.
Sasha.
What? What is it?
Blood.
Blood?
Where?
What do you see? He makes you see things.
- (RETCHING)
- Fuck.
- Oh, my God.
- Hey! Hey! Hey!
Back away. I need you over here.
- She's fine. Stay back.
- (COUGHING)
Wait, there he is!
Hey!
(BARKING)
Hey, bud. Somethin' wrong?
- I'm sorry. I thought...
- What?
Hey, are you all right?
Wait! Wait! Sasha!
He's gonna take her home
and she's going to lie down for a bit.
I'm her boyfriend. She needs me.
Maybe. Maybe later.
But right now,
you're going to come with me.
We're going to talk a little bit.
Did you say the name to anyone?
She didn't, man.
Neither of us did.
(SASHA COUGHING)
JOHN: It's gonna be all right.
(SOFTLY) Don't say it. Don't think it.
Don't say it. Don't think it.
Don't think it. Don't think it.
(SIGHS)
Good news for you. Maybe.
Kim Hines wrote a suicide note,
taking responsibility for her roommate
and for the deaths of you
and the other two living at your house.
So, I guess she was
planning on killing you, too.
Is that what happened, Elliot?
You found out and you chased her?
I don't think that's murder.
Don't think it. Don't say it. Don't think it.
You want to write it?
No.
You're going to tell me, you know that.
I hope not.
Why did you chase Kim?
I told you, I was trying to help her.
So you chased her into a train?
What are you doing?
You could lose everything.
Your scholarship, that pretty girl.
You are a smart kid.
Talk to me and I can help you.
Otherwise, it'll be out of my hands
and you'll be wishing that you had.
You might find yourself wishing I hadn't.
Well, you let me worry about that.
You really want to know?
You really think the truth,
honesty, is the best policy?
- I do.
- Always?
When wouldn't it be?
You have kids?
Maybe.
You have kids.
Don't think it. Don't say it.
What if you saw
the worst crime scene ever?
A mass murder at a school.
With dead bodies and brains and students
and sneakers with blood on them.
And you go home, and your kids say,
"Tell us about your day, Mommy."
You could be honest.
You could tell the truth.
You could describe every
awful nightmare thing you saw,
and what was burned into your head
would be burned into their heads forever.
Or...
You could hug them tight,
and spare them your honest truth.
What would you do?
I'd hug them.
Please don't make me say it.
I haven't hurt anyone.
But I'm afraid of
putting this into your head.
All I have to do is talk to you,
and you and your kids...
You're all dead.
Hey! Elliot!
Your friend died?
What the hell is going on, man?
Thanks for coming to
get me, but I gotta go.
Was it Sasha and John...
Hey, talk to me. Let me help you.
Whatever is going on,
there's nothing you can do, okay?
I literally can't tell you.
I'm not going to let it
happen to you, Virgil.
Especially not you.
What are you talking about?
You've got a family. Go take care of them.
Elliot, hey! You are my family. Elliot!
- (ENGINE STARTS)
- Shit!
(JOHN AND SASHA MOANING)
JOHN: Fuck!
JOHN: Yeah!
Oh, my God.
What are you doing, Elliot?
What's... What's wrong with you, Elliot?
(GROANS)
What the...
I'm so sorry.
(PHONE RINGING)
MRS. WATKINS: Elliot?
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
- Hi, Ms. Watkins.
- Hi. Elliot?
I've been having
some really strange thoughts
about that Bye Bye Man since we talked.
Ms. Watkins...
Ms. Watkins, you can't
talk to anyone about it.
Well, maybe I can
come over to your house later.
I'm so sorry.
I'm sorry, too.
Believe me, but I've just been
having the most vivid thoughts. I...
Elliot?
Redmon...
Larry Redmon.
The writer.
It was his nightstand.
Ms. Watkins.
Okay, maybe I'll see you later,
maybe I'll have a fix for this.
- I gotta go. Thanks.
- Oh, you're welcome...
I'll be there soon.
He almost got us, man.
Oh, fuck! I almost killed you with a bat,
but, fuck, he's not going to get us.
He's not going to get us.
I'll figure this out.
I'm really sorry, but...
I'm sorry, I can't call an ambulance,
'cause you're gonna say it.
You will. You will.
'Cause I messed you up.
I'll be back as soon as I can.
I'm taking this.
You found her and now
I'm going to go talk to her.
I love you.
And don't touch him.
(ROCK MUSIC PLAYING ON CAR STEREO)
(SINGING) Bye-bye, happiness
Hello, loneliness
I think I'm gonna cry
Bye-bye, love
Bye-bye, sweet caress
Hello, emptiness
I feel like I'm gonna die
Bye-bye, my love, goodbye
(MUSIC STOPS)
Hello?
Mrs. Redmon?
- Leave.
- (GASPS)
Ms. Redmon?
I said, leave! Are you deaf,
or just defective?
Ms. Redmon, did your husband write
for The Register a long time ago?
You're too young to remember that.
Ms. Redmon. You're still alive.
I know your husband
killed a lot of people.
But I don't think he was crazy.
I need your help, whatever you remember.
There's a train, gold coins...
A hound...
He came to Larry.
(SIGHS) With the hound.
What Larry told me gave me nightmares.
I made him stop.
I understand.
But I need you to tell me
everything Larry said.
Please.
Larry was on a story of a teenager
who killed his family.
Poked around like a good nosy
reporter and heard rumors...
Whispers about an evil,
some kind of a reaper
that drove the teenager mad.
Larry had to go nosing around
and writing it down.
And then it came to Larry, too,
this nightmare, this name
we must not think or say.
But just three days
after Larry got back from Iowa,
I came home from work.
October 20th, 1969.
The day my life went turn-turn-turn...
LARRY: Don't say it. Don't think it.
Don't say it.
Don't think it. Don't say it.
Don't think it.
Don't say it. Don't think it.
Oh, my God.
Don't say it.
Larry... Oh, my God.
(YOUNG MS. REDMON GASPS)
I was just doing my job.
That's what I do. I track down the story.
And that's what I was doing.
See...
Once you know his name,
you can't escape him.
You see, he gets in your head and...
He makes you do horrible things.
Okay. Okay. (SHUSHING)
What horrible things?
Who makes you do this?
What are you talking about?
Let's get you to bed, okay, sweetheart?
Listen. Listen, I didn't know
if he was alive or dead.
And then the hound...
That's how you know he's coming.
When you see the hound
and you hear the coins,
that's when you know he's close by.
- You understand?
- No, I... (STAMMERS)
MS. REDMON: Larry...
I don't know what's happened,
but I'm trying...
He listens for his name.
Anyone could say it. It could be you.
Or it could be me.
And it's just dumb luck
like the flip of a coin.
And I heard the name
and I told Janey the name.
"Don't think it. Don't say it."
What does this mean? What did you write?
I don't understand.
He makes you see things.
And he makes you do things.
Who knows how many good people
he's made do horrible things like this.
No! Oh, God, no! Please.
Please, don't.
Please put it down.
You think it's me?
You think I did this?
This is what happens.
They say people snap.
They say people go crazy.
No, it's him.
It's him that's doing it!
(SHUSHING) Just put it...
Put it down. Okay?
No.
I love you.
MS. REDMON:
But in the end, Larry was a hero.
You tell people that.
Larry erased him, you see.
He did away with everyone who'd
heard it before they could pass it on.
But not you.
You're here.
How did you survive all this time?
- Survive?
- Yes.
How did you beat it?
I didn't beat it.
I never knew it.
What?
If my husband had told me the name,
he'd have had to kill me with the rest.
My husband controlled himself.
Your fucking husband wrote the name
in the nightstand you sold and I read it.
He typed it in a dead article
and I read that, too!
Don't you say it!
Your husband spared you and he got me.
He's in me now. He's in my friends.
- You want my help?
- Yes.
Here.
Kill all of the ones you told first
and then kill yourself.
It's the only way.
No! There has to be another way.
"Don't say it.
Don't think it." It's a clue.
- Look.
- (TRAIN HORN BLARING)
Oh, my God. He's coming!
What are you talking about?
You didn't bring him here.
- Don't you see it?
- See what?
The light... Hear the name...
He's in your head.
He makes us see things, hear things,
tricks to make us afraid.
He makes us afraid. Then he grows.
The more scared we are,
the more real he gets.
We make him real with our fear.
We make him more powerful.
Yeah, we give him the power
and he gets closer and he hears us
when we think of him.
But maybe, if we're not afraid,
we take his power.
Maybe, if we're not afraid, he's nothing!
How could you figure it out
and my Larry not?
(SCREAMS)
Help me!
Shoot me!
(SCREAMING)
Shoot me now!
(CONTINUES SCREAMING)
No, no! It's not real!
No, it's not real.
Help me!
I have you now, don't I?
Come on, try another trick.
Come on, try it!
Where are you?
Oh, my God.
Sasha!
(LINE RINGING)
Pick up.
Sasha?
VOICEMAIL: Hey. It's Sasha.
Leave a message...
You better not fuckin' hurt her!
Thanks.
- (VOICEMAIL BEEPS)
- Sasha. I'm coming.
I know it's hard, but don't be afraid.
And don't believe anything you see.
- (THUDS)
- Whoa, what the...
What?
No, you're not real.
Not real!
Ha! I knew it!
(BRAKES SCREECHING)
Okay. Tricks.
You want to play tricks?
Okay. I'm ready.
(EXHALES)
Elliot!
John!
Where are you guys?
Elliot?
Sasha!
Elliot!
Sasha?
I'm in here.
Oh, God.
(SIGHS)
You look like hell.
Jesus.
There you are.
Elliot... Thank God. You're back.
I'm not...
Oh, my God.
Hey, what's the matter?
Elliot, what are you doing?
Shit.
Get away.
Hey, come on, it's all going to be okay.
We're going to be okay. I feel better.
Get away!
Elliot! It's me!
What the hell?
Elliot, I don't understand.
What are you doing?
Help!
Elliot! Come on.
Come here, John.
- Please, Elliot!
- Help!
I don't understand. Please. (SOBBING)
No.
- Come on.
- No!
Please.
Stop. Elliot, please stop!
Will you just stop?
Get away from me!
Get away!
(WHIMPERS)
Guys!
Sasha, John, it's a trick. It's not real.
Listen to me!
(SASHA SCREAMING)
Sasha, John. Listen to me, it's not real.
(SCREAMING)
John, no!
Elliot! Shoot! Shoot!
No!
(GASPING)
(ELLIOT SOBBING)
(SNARLING)
(TRAIN HORN BLARING)
Go ahead. Kill me.
You win.
(GASPS)
No.
You leave them alone!
(DOORBELL RINGING)
Come on, guys. It's freezing out here.
Hey, man. Anybody home?
I've got Alice here.
She's here to cheer you up, buddy.
- Elliot!
- No!
VIRGIL: Hey! Anybody home?
Guys, come on! We know you're in there.
I hear something. Hello!
Open the door, you guys.
We're turning into popsicles out here.
- Go away!
- Elliot?
Go away!
No, no. We're not going anywhere, Elliot.
Uncle, open up!
Please, get her out of here.
Both of you, you need to go!
Elliot, open the goddamn door
or I'm calling the police.
Good. Do it!
Honey, why don't you go wait in the truck?
No! Daddy, I got to pee!
Go to the truck, please.
Open the door, man, come on.
Go. Go.
- Elliot!
- Bye... Bye...
(SNARLING)
No!
Elliot, what the hell is going on?
Virgil, please, get her out of here.
Uncle Elliot!
Okay, Peanut, I need you
to listen to me, okay?
I need you to go to the truck.
No, Daddy, I got to go!
Go someplace close where I can
see ya, and be quick, okay?
Outside?
No one is going to see you,
baby. It's okay.
Go. Go. Go.
Elliot. Elliot, what is going on in there?
ELLIOT: Don't think it. Don't say it.
Don't think it. Don't say it.
VIRGIL: Elliot, what are you saying? What?
I have to do this. I'm not crazy.
Let me help you.
No, you can't. But I
can help you, if you go!
But I'm not going to let you catch it!
Bye... Don't say it! Don't think it!
- What? Don't say what?
- Just go!
(SCREAMS)
Jesus Christ, what was that?
Elliot, what was that?
(GASPING)
(HOUND SNARLING)
The Bye Bye Man. Bye Bye...
Bye Bye? What is that? Bye Bye?
What is it, what are you saying?
Bye Bye what?
What is that? Elliot? Bye Bye what?
I love you so much.
(GUNSHOT)
Elliot!
(TRAIN HORN BLARING)
(FIRE CRACKLING)
Alice.
Alice? Alice!
Alice?
Where are you, baby?
Alice!
(OBJECTS CLATTERING)
Alice? Alice?
Honey?
Alice?
Alice!
Honey! Come here!
I was cold!
Oh, I know, honey,
but you scared me so much!
Oh, no! Look!
Uncle Elliot!
It's okay.
The fire can't hurt him anymore.
POLICE CAPTAIN:
So, this boy ran a librarian over,
mutilated and murdered her children,
and then killed his roommates and himself
and you had him in custody today,
but you let him go?
Yes. But this is not some creepy kid
pulling a Columbine, okay?
I talked to him.
Something is going on here. I can feel it.
(INDISTINCT RADIO CHATTER)
(ENGINE STARTS)
I wanted to say goodbye.
I know, baby. Me, too.
At least he gave me the coins.
What are you talking about?
He must've left them
out there for me to find.
Left them out where, honey?
In the little table.
Outside, next to the trash cans.
Well, was there
anything else in this table?
No.
Just some writing.
Writing?
What did this writing say?
Daddy. You know I can't read in the dark.
What do you think I am? A flashlight?
(CHUCKLES)
We got one alive!
WOMAN: Get me a tool, a line and morphine!
Wait, wait! He's trying to say something!
Hey, I'm listening, go ahead.
FIREFIGHTER: It won't matter.
It does matter.
Okay, take your time.
It's okay. I'm here.
And I want to know.
Please. Please tell me.
Bye Bye Man...
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today