(PEOPLE CHATTERING)
NARRATOR: Thebes,
City of the Living,
crown jewel of Pharaoh Seti
the First.
Home of lmhotep,
Pharaoh's high priest,
keeper of the dead.
Birthplace of Anck-Su-Namun,
Pharaoh's mistress.
No other man was allowed
to touch her.
But for their love,
they were willing
to risk life itself.
(SPEAKING ANCIENT EGYPTIAN)
(SCREAMING)
(PHARAOH SCREAMING)
(BANGING ON DOOR)
(SPEAKING ANCIENT EGYPTIAN)
(SOLDIERS SHOUTING)
NARRATOR:
To resurrect Anck-Su-Namun,
lmhotep and his priests
broke into her crypt
and stole her body.
They raced
deep into the desert,
taking Anck-Su-Namun's corpse
to Hamunaptra,
City of the Dead,
ancient burial site
for the sons of pharaohs
and resting place
for the wealth of Egypt.
For his love,
lmhotep dared the gods' anger
by going deep into the city,
where he took
the black Book of the Dead
from its holy resting place.
(CHANTING lN ANCIENT EGYPTIAN)
Anck-Su-Namun's soul
had been sent
to the dark underworld,
her vital organs removed
and placed in five sacred
Canopic jars.
(GASPING)
Anck-Su-Namun's soul
had come back
from the dead,
(SHOUTING)
but Pharaoh's bodyguards
had followed lmhotep
and stopped him
before the ritual
could be completed.
(HOWLING)
(SHOUTING)
lmhotep's priests
were condemned
to be mummified alive.
(PRIESTS GROANING)
(PRIESTS SCREAMING)
As for lmhotep,
he was condemned
to endure the Hom-Dai,
the worst of all
ancient curses.
One so horrible,
it had never before
been bestowed.
(lMHOTEP SCREAMING)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(MOANING)
(GRUNTING)
(MUFFLED SCREAMING)
(SKITTERING)
He was to remain sealed
inside his sarcophagus,
be undead for all of eternity.
The Magi would never allow him
to be released,
for he would arise
a walking disease,
a plague upon mankind,
an unholy flesh-eater
with the strength of ages,
power over the sands,
and the glory
of invincibility.
(LEGIONNAIRES SHOUTING)
For 3,иии years,
men and armies
fought over this land,
never knowing
what evil lay beneath it.
(SHOUTING)
(MEN SHOUTING)
And for 3,иии years,
we, the Magi,
the descendants of Pharaoh's
sacred bodyguards, kept watch.
You just got promoted.
(YELLING lN FRENCH)
(ULULATING)
Steady!
You're with me
on this one, right?
Your strength
gives me strength.
RICK: Steady!
Wait! Wait for me!
Steady!
Fire!
(MEN GRUNTING)
(HORSES NEIGHING)
(YELLING)
Run, Beni! Run!
RICK: Get inside!
Get inside!
Hey! Don't you close
that door!
Don't you close that door!
(GUNS FIRING)
(GUNS CLICKING)
(NEIGHING)
(MEN SHOUTING)
(MAN WHISPERING)
MAN: (WHISPERING)
You will die. You will die.
(HOWLING)
(SHOUTING)
(RICK COUGHING)
(GRUNTING)
(MEN SHOUTING)
(SPEAKING ARABIC)
(PANTING)
EVELYN: Sacred stones,
sculpture and aesthetics,
Socrates, Seth,
volume one, volume two,
and volume three.
And...
Tuthmosis?
What are you doing here?
T. T, t, t...
T.
l'm going to put you
where you belong.
(SCREAMS)
(GASPING)
(EXCLAIMING)
Help.
(SCREAMING)
Oops.
CURATOR: What... How...
Oh, look at this!
Sons of the pharaohs!
Give me frogs!
Flies! Locusts!
Anything but you!
Compared to you,
the other plagues
were a joy!
l am so very sorry.
lt was an accident.
My girl, when Rameses
destroyed Syria,
that was an accident.
You are a catastrophe!
Look at my library!
Why do l put up with you?
Well, you put up
with me because l can...
l can read and write
Ancient Egyptian,
and l can...
l can decipher
hieroglyphics and hieratic,
and, well, l am
the only person
within 1 ,000 miles
who knows how to properly
code and catalog
this library, that's why.
l put up with you because
your father and mother
were our finest patrons.
That's why!
Allah rest their souls.
Now, l don't care
how you do it,
l don't care
how long it takes,
straighten up this meshiver!
(CLATTERING)
Hello?
Abdul?
Mohammed?
Bob?
(THUDDING)
(SCREAMING)
(LAUGHING)
Have you no respect
for the dead?
Of course l do.
But sometimes l'd rather
like to join them.
Well, l wish you would do it
before you ruin my career
the way you've ruined yours.
Now, get out.
My dear, sweet baby sister.
l'll have you know
that, at this precise moment,
my career is on a high note.
High note, ha!
Jonathan, please, l'm really
not in the mood for you.
l've just made a bit
of a mess in the library,
and the Bembridge scholars
have rejected my application
form again.
They say l don't
have enough experience
in the field.
You'll always
have me, old mum.
Besides, l have
just the thing
to cheer you up.
Oh, no, Jonathan,
not another
worthless trinket.
lf l have to take
one more piece of junk
to the curator to try and
sell for you.
Where did you get this?
On a dig down in Thebes.
My whole life,
l've never found
anything, Evy.
Please tell me
l've found something.
(EVELYN GASPS)
Jonathan.
Yes?
l think you've found
something.
You see the cartouche there?
lt's the official royal seal
of Seti the First,
l'm sure of it.
Perhaps.
JONATHAN: Two questions.
Who the hell
was Seti the First,
and was he rich?
He was the second pharaoh
of the 10th dynasty,
said to be the wealthiest
pharaoh of them all.
Good. l like this fellow.
l like him very much.
l've already dated
the map.
lt's almost 3,000 years old.
And if you look
at the hieratic just here,
well, it's Hamunaptra.
CURATOR: Dear God,
don't be ridiculous.
We're scholars,
not treasure hunters.
Hamunaptra's a myth
told by ancient
Arab storytellers
to amuse Greek
and Roman tourists.
l know all the blather
about the city being protected
by the curse of a mummy,
but my research
has led me to believe
that the city itself
may have actually existed.
Are we talking
about the Hamunaptra?
Yes. The City of the Dead.
Where the earliest pharaohs
were said to have hidden
the wealth of Egypt.
Yes, yes, in a big,
underground treasure chamber.
Heh!
Oh, come on.
Everybody knows the story.
The entire necropolis
was rigged to sink
into the sand
on Pharaoh's command.
A flick of a switch,
and the whole place
would disappear beneath
the sand dunes,
taking the treasure with it.
As the Americans would say,
it's all fairy tales
and hokum.
Oh, my goodness!
Look at that!
You've burnt it!
You've burned off the part
with the lost city.
lt's for the best,
l'm sure.
Many men have wasted
their lives in the foolish
pursuit of Hamunaptra.
No one's ever found it.
Most have never returned.
Come, come!
Step over the threshold.
Welcome to Cairo Prison,
my humble home.
EVELYN: You told me that
you got it on a dig
down in Thebes.
JONATHAN: Yeah, well,
l was mistaken.
You lied to me.
l lie to everybody.
What makes you
so special?
l am your sister.
That just makes you
more gullible.
You stole it from a drunk
at the local casbah.
Picked his pocket, actually,
so l don't think
it's a very good...
Stop being so ridiculous.
What exactly is this man
in prison for?
This l did not know.
But when l heard
that you were coming,
l asked him that myself.
And what did he say?
He said he was just looking
for a good time.
(YELLING)
This is the man
that you stole it from?
Yes, exactly.
So why don't we
just go sniff out
a spot of tiffin...
RICK: Who are you?
And who's the broad?
"Broad"?
l'm just a local sort
of missionary chap,
spreading the good word,
but this is my sister, Evy.
How do you do?
Oh, well. Guess she's not
a total loss.
l beg your pardon.
l'll be back
in a moment.
Ask him about the box.
We have found...
Hello. Excuse me.
We both found
your puzzle box,
and we've come
to ask you about it.
No.
No. You came to ask me
about Hamunaptra.
How do you know
the box pertains
to Hamunaptra?
Because that's where l was
when l found it. l was there.
But how do we know
that's not a load
of pig's wallow?
Do l know you?
No, no.
l've just got
one of those faces.
You were actually
at Hamunaptra?
Yeah, l was there.
You swear?
Every damn day.
l didn't mean that...
l know. l was there.
Seti's place.
City of the Dead.
Could you tell me
how to get there?
(MAN YELLING lN ARABIC)
l mean, the exact location.
You want to know?
Well, yes.
Do you really want to know?
Yes.
Then get me the hell
out of here!
(SOLDIERS YELLING)
Do it, lady!
Where are they taking him?
To be hanged.
Apparently, he had
a very good time.
(CROWD CHEERING)
l will give you Б100
to save this man's life.
Madame, l would pay Б100
just to see him hang.
Б200.
Proceed!
Б300.
Any last requests, pig?
Yeah. Loosen the knot
and let me go.
(SPEAKING ARABIC)
Of course we don't
let him go!
(SPEAKING ARABIC)
Б500!
And what else?
l'm a very lonely man.
(CROWD LAUGHING)
No!
(CHOKING)
(LAUGHING)
His neck did not break.
Oh, l'm so sorry.
Now, we must watch him
strangle to death.
(CROWD CHANTING)
(GRUNTING)
He knows the location
to Hamunaptra.
You lie.
l would never!
Are you telling me
this filthy, godless
son of a pig
knows where to find
the City of the Dead?
EVELYN: Yes!
Truly?
Yes!
And if you cut him down,
we will give you...
(GRUNTING)
10%.
50%.
Twenty.
Forty.
Thirty!
Twenty five.
Deal.
Cut him down!
(CROWD CHEERING)
(SHIP HORN BLOWING)
EVELYN: Do you really think
he's going to show up?
JONATHAN: Yes, undoubtedly,
knowing my luck.
He may be a cowboy,
but l know the breed.
His word is his word.
Well, personally l think
he's filthy, rude,
a complete scoundrel.
l don't like him one bit.
Anyone l know?
Oh.
Hello.
Smashing day for the start
of an adventure,
eh, O'Connell?
Yeah. Yeah, smashing.
Oh, no, no, l'd never steal
from a partner, partner.
That reminds me.
No hard feelings
about the...
Oh, no, no.
Happens all the time.
Mr. O'Connell.
Can you look me in the eye
and guarantee me
this isn't some sort
of a flimflam?
Because if it is,
l am warning you...
You're warning me?
Lady, let me
put it this way,
my whole damn garrison
believed in this so much
that without orders,
they marched halfway
across Libya and into Egypt
to find that city.
When we got there,
all we found was sand
and blood.
Let me get your bags.
Yes, yes, you're right.
Filthy, rude,
a complete scoundrel.
Nothing to like there
at all.
Bright good morning
to all.
Oh, no. What are you
doing here?
l'm here
to protect my investment,
thank you very much.
(MUSIC PLAYING)
Quit playing with your glasses
and cut the deck, Burns.
Without my glasses
l can't see the deck
to cut it, Dave.
JONATHAN: O'Connell, sit down.
We could use another player.
l only gamble with my life,
never my money.
Never?
What if l was to bet you $500
we get to Hamunaptra
before you?
You're looking for Hamunaptra?
Damn straight we are.
And who says we are?
ALL: He does.
DAVE: Well...
Well, how about it?
ls it a bet?
All right, you're on.
What makes you
so confident, sir?
What makes you?
We got us a man
who's actually been there.
Oh, what a coincidence,
because O'Connell...
Whose play is it?
ls it my play? l thought...
Gentlemen, we got us a wager.
Good evening, Jonathan.
Night.
Sorry. Didn't mean
to scare you.
The only thing that scares me,
Mr. O'Connell,
are your manners.
Still angry
about that kiss, huh?
Well, if you call that a kiss.
Did l miss something?
Are we... Are we going
into battle?
Lady, there's something
out there.
Something underneath
that sand.
Yes, well,
l'm hoping to find
a certain artifact.
A book, actually.
My brother thinks
there's treasure.
What do you think's
out there?
ln a word? Evil.
The Bedouin and the Tuaregs
believe that Hamunaptra
is cursed.
Oh, look, l don't believe
in fairy tales and hokum,
Mr. O'Connell,
but l do believe one
of the most famous books
in history is buried there.
The Book of Amun-Ra.
lt contains within it all
the secret incantations
of the old kingdom.
lt's what first interested me
in Egypt when l was a child.
lt's why l came here.
Sort of a life's pursuit.
And the fact that they say
it's made out of pure gold
makes no never mind to you?
Right?
You know your history.
l know my treasure.
By the way,
why did you kiss me?
l was about to be hanged.
lt seemed like a good idea
at the time.
What? What'd l say?
(MAN EXCLAIMING)
(MAN SHOUTING)
Surprise! My good friend,
you're alive!
l was so very, very worried.
Well, if it ain't
my little buddy, Beni.
l think l'll kill you.
Think of my children.
You don't have any children.
Someday l might.
Shut up!
So, you're the one
who's leading the Americans.
l might have known.
So, what's the scam, Beni?
You take them into the middle
of the desert, and then
you leave them to rot?
Unfortunately, no.
These Americans are smart.
They pay me only half now,
half when l get them
back to Cairo.
So this time l must
go all the way.
Them's the breaks, huh?
You never believed
in Hamunaptra, O'Connell.
Why are you going back?
(CAMEL GROANING)
You see that girl?
She saved my neck.
You always did
have more balls than brains.
Yeah. Goodbye, Beni.
(SCREAMING)
(BENl COUGHING)
BENl: O'Connell!
George Bembridge...
ln 1и60...
1и65, was...
Was...
Oh, for heaven's sake, girl,
it wasn't that good
of a kiss, anyway.
(THUDDING)
(GASPS)
Where is the map?
lt's... lt's... There.
And the key?
Where is the key?
The key? The key?
What key?
RICK: Evelyn!
(SCREAMING)
The map! The map!
l forgot the map!
Relax. l'm the map.
lt's all up here.
Oh, that's comforting.
(GROANING)
The key!
JONATHAN: Evy?
(SCREAMING)
Hold on to this.
(GUN FIRING)
Can you swim?
Of course l can swim,
if the occasion
calls for it.
Trust me.
lt calls for it.
(YELLING)
(GRUNTING)
(SCREAMING)
O'Connell! O'Connell!
What are we going to do?
Wait here! l'll go get help!
Right!
(SHOUTING lN ARABIC)
(EXCLAIMING)
Americans.
l say, bloody good show,
chaps!
And did l panic?
l think not.
HENDERSON: Get them out
of the water!
Get them out of the water!
Come on, doggies!
Give them a smack,
would you?
This is a messed-up
country.
We've lost everything!
All of our tools,
all the equipment!
All my clothes!
O'Connell!
Hey!
lt looks to me like l've got
all the horses!
Hey, Beni!
Looks to me like you're on
the wrong side of the river!
Yeah.
(SWEARING lN HUNGARIAN)
(CHILDREN SHOUTING)
(PEOPLE CHATTERING)
(SHOUTING lN ARABIC)
JONATHAN: l only want four!
Four!
(MAN SPEAKING ARABIC)
l only want four,
not a whole bloody herd!
O'Connell!
Can you believe the cheek?
Just pay the man.
Oh, for heaven's sake.
Can't believe the price
of these fleabags.
Yes, happy.
Very good.
You probably could've
got them for free.
All we had to do
was give him your sister.
Yes.
Awfully tempting,
wasn't it?
Awfully.
JONATHAN: Never did
like camels.
Filthy buggers.
They smell, they bite,
they spit.
Disgusting.
l think they're adorable.
(SINGING) OБ, baby
(SINGING lN ARABIC)
(WIND WHISTLING)
(MOANING)
(CAMEL LOWING)
(SHUSHING)
(SNORING)
(MUMBLING)
(HORSES NEIGHING)
(SPEAKING ARABIC)
(HORSES WHINNYING)
BENl: Good morning, my friend.
What the hell we doing?
Patience, my good barat'm.
Patience.
Remember our bet, O'Connell.
First one to the city,
500 cash bucks.
A hundred of them bucks
is yours if you help us
win that bet.
Oh, my pleasure.
Hey, O'Connell. Nice camel.
(GRUNTING)
RICK: Get ready for it.
For what?
We're about to be shown
the way.
Will you look at that?
Can you believe it?
Hamunaptra.
Here we go again.
(MARSHALLING)
So long, Beni!
That serves you right.
(MARSHALLING)
(WHOOPING)
Go, Evy! Go!
(EVELYN EXCLAIMING)
(MAN SHOUTING lN ARABIC)
(SPEAKING ARABIC)
(MEN CHATTERING)
Do they know something
we don't?
They are led by a woman.
What does a woman know?
EVELYN: That's a statue
of Anubis.
lts legs go deep underground.
According to Bembridge
scholars,
that's where we'll find
a secret compartment
containing the golden
Book of Amun-Ra.
Jonathan, you're meant
to catch the sun with that.
So, what are these
old mirrors for?
Ancient mirrors.
lt's an ancient
Egyptian trick. You'll see.
Here, this for you.
Go ahead. lt's something
l borrowed off
our American brethren.
l thought you might like it,
you might need it
for when you're...
Yeah. What are you looking at?
WARDEN: Hey, look for bugs.
l hate bugs.
EVELYN: Do you realize
we're standing inside a room
no one has entered
in over 3,000 years?
What is that god-awful stench?
(SNIFFING)
And then there was light.
RICK: Hey,
that is a neat trick.
Oh, my God. lt's a sah-neиer.
What?
A preparation room.
Preparation for what?
For entering the afterlife.
Mummies, my good son.
This is where they made
the mummies.
(SKITTERING)
What the...
JONATHAN: What was that?
Sounds like bugs.
EVELYN: He said bugs.
What do you mean, bugs?
l hate bugs!
EVELYN: The legs of Anubis.
The secret compartment
should be hidden somewhere
inside here.
(MOANING)
(VOICE MUTTERING)
(YELLING)
You scared the bejesus
out of us, O'Connell.
Likewise.
Hey, that's my tool kit.
RICK: No, l don't think so.
Okay. Perhaps l was mistaken.
Have a nice day,
gentlemen.
We have a lot of work
to be getting along with.
Push off!
This is our dig site.
We got here first.
This here's our statue,
friend.
l don't see your name
written on it, pal.
BENl: Yes, well,
there's only four of you
and 15 of me.
Your odds are not
so great, O'Connell.
l've had worse.
Yeah, me, too.
Oh, look, for goodness' sake,
let's be nice, children.
lf we're going
to play together,
we must learn to share.
There are other places to dig.
According to these
hieroglyphics,
we're underneath
the statue.
We should come up
right between his legs.
When those damn Yanks
go to sleep...
No offense.
None taken.
We'll dig our way up
and steal that book
right out from under them.
Are you sure we can
find this secret
compartment?
Oh, yes, if those
beastly Americans haven't
beaten us to it.
No offense.
None taken.
Where'd our smelly
little friend get to?
Hey.
What have we here?
Blue gold.
This will fetch
a mighty fine price.
(CHUCKLING)
(ULULATES)
HENDERSON: Let's get us
some treasure!
Careful!
Seti was no fool.
l think perhaps we should let
the diggers open it.
BURNS: Oh, l think we should
listen to the good doctor,
Henderson.
Yeah, sure.
Let them open it.
(SPEAKING ARABIC)
RICK: Let me get
this straight.
They ripped out your guts
and stuffed them in jars.
They'd take out
your heart as well.
You know how they took out
your brains?
l don't think we need
to know this.
They'd take a sharp,
red-hot poker,
stick it up your nose,
scramble things about a bit,
and then rip it all out
through your nostrils.
That's gotta hurt.
lt's called mummification.
You'll be dead
when they do this.
For the record,
if l don't make it
out of here,
don't put me down
for mummification.
Likewise.
Oh, my God. lt's a...
lt's a sarcophagus.
Buried at the base of Anubis.
He must have been
someone of great importance.
Or he did something
very naughty.
Oh, Allah.
One more.
(SKITTERING)
(CHUCKLING)
(SCREAMING)
(GRUNTING)
Help me! Help me!
Help me!
(GRUNTING)
(SCREAMING)
Well, who is it?
"He That Shall Not Be Named."
(PUFFING)
This looks like
some sort of a lock.
Well, whoever's in here
sure wasn't getting out.
RICK: Yeah, no kidding.
lt'd take us a month
to crack into this thing
without a key.
A key?
A key! A key!
That's what
he was talking about!
Who?
The man on the barge,
the one with the hook.
He was looking for a key.
Hey, that's mine.
(WARDEN SCREAMING)
(HORSE WHINNYING)
EVELYN: What do you suppose
killed him?
Did you ever
see him eat?
Seems that
our American friends
had a little misfortune
of their own today.
Three of their diggers
were melted.
What?
How?
Salt acid.
Pressurized salt acid.
Some kind of ancient
booby trap.
Maybe this place
really is cursed.
(WIND HOWLING)
Oh, for goodness' sake,
you two!
You don't believe in curses?
No, l don't.
l believe if l can see it
and l can touch it,
it's real.
That's what l believe.
l believe in being prepared.
Let's see what our friend
the warden believed in.
(GRUNTING)
What?
My God, what is it?
A broken bottle.
Glenlivet, 12 years old!
He may have been
a stinky fellow,
but he had good taste.
(HORSE WHINNYING)
Take this. Stay here.
No, wait, wait!
Wait for me. Wait!
Evy!
Excuse me,
but didn't the man
just say stay here?
Evy!
Mr. Henderson! Wake up!
(SHOUTING lN ARABIC)
JONATHAN: O'Connell!
ARDETH: Enough!
(ARDETH SPEAKING ARABIC)
We will shed no more blood,
but you must leave.
Leave this place or die.
You have one day.
(SPEAKING ARABIC)
Evelyn.
Hey.
Are you all right?
Yes, l'm fine.
You sure?
Thank you.
BURNS: That proves it.
Old Seti's fortune's
got to be under this sand.
For them to protect it
like this,
you know there's treasure
down there.
No, these men
are desert people.
They value water,
not gold.
You know, maybe just at night,
we could combine forces?
RICK: Hey, tough stuff,
try a right hook.
Ball up your fist
and put it...
Put it up like that.
And then mean it.
Hit it right here.
Mean it!
Okay.
Okay, it's time
for another drink.
Unlike my brother, sir,
l know when to say no.
And unlike your brother, miss,
you, l just don't get.
l know. You're wondering
what is a place like me
doing in a girl like this.
Yeah, something like that.
Egypt is in my blood.
You see,
my father was a very,
very famous explorer.
And he loved Egypt so much,
he married my mother,
who was an Egyptian
and quite
an adventurer herself.
l get your father
and l get your mother,
and...
l get him, but...
What are you doing here?
Look, l may not be an explorer
or an adventurer
or a treasure seeker
or a gunfighter,
Mr. O'Connell,
but l am proud of what l am.
And what is that?
l
am a librarian.
And l am going to kiss you,
Mr. O'Connell.
Call me Rick.
Rick.
(SPEAKING ARABIC)
There is a curse
upon this chest.
Curse, my ass.
Who cares?
Have a care, Mr. Henderson.
ln these hallowed grounds,
that which was set forth
in ancient times
is as strong today
as it was then.
We understand.
What's it say?
(READING lN ANCIENT EGYPTIAN)
"Death will come
on swift wings
"to whomsoever
opens this chest."
(WIND BLOWING)
(ALL CHATTERING)
(SHOUTING)
BENl: We should not be here.
This is not good.
lt says,
"There is one, the undead,
"who, if brought back to life,
is bound by sacred law
"to consummate this curse."
Let's make sure
we don't bring anyone back
from the dead then.
"He will kill all who open
this chest
"and assimilate their organs
and fluids,
"and in so doing,
he will regenerate
"and no longer be the undead,
"but a plague
upon this Earth."
HENDERSON: Well, we didn't
come all this way for nothing.
DAVE: That's right.
lt's the curse.
lt's the curse!
Beware of the curse!
Beware!
Stupid superstitious bastard.
Oh, l've dreamt about this
since l was a little girl.
You dream
about dead guys?
Look, the sacred spells
have been chiseled off.
This man must have been
condemned
not only in this life,
but in the next.
Tough break.
Yeah, l'm all tears.
Now, let's see
who's inside, shall we?
(HISSING)
(ALL SCREAMING)
Oh, my God,
l hate it when
these things do that.
ls he supposed
to look like that?
No, l've never
seen a mummy
look like this before.
He's still... Still...
Juicy.
Yes.
He must be more
than 3,000 years old,
and, well, it looks
as if he's still
decomposing.
Hey, look at that.
What do you make of this?
My God, these marks
were made with...
Fingernails.
This man was buried alive.
And he left a message.
"Death is only the beginning."
Oh, my God.
lt does exist.
The Book of the Dead.
A book?
Who cares about a book?
Where the hell's
the treasure?
This, gentlemen.
This is treasure.
Hell, l wouldn't trade you
for a brass...
Look at that.
EGYPTOLOGIST:
There's your treasure,
gentlemen.
BURNS: Now, we're on
to something.
(CRICKETS CHIRPING)
(GRUNTING)
l believe you need a key
to open that book.
HENDERSON: Say, O'Connell,
what do you think
these babies'll fetch
back home?
We hear you boys
found yourselves
a nice, gooey mummy.
Congratulations.
lf you dry that fellow out,
you might be able to sell him
for firewood.
EVELYN: Look what l found.
You're in her seat.
Now!
Yup.
Scarab skeletons,
flesh-eaters.
l found them inside
our friend's coffin.
They can stay alive
for years feasting
on the flesh of a corpse.
Unfortunately for our friend,
he was still alive when
they started eating him.
RICK: So somebody threw
these in with our guy,
and then they slowly
ate him alive?
Very slowly.
He certainly wasn't
a popular fellow when
they planted him, was he?
Well, he probably got
a little too frisky
with the pharaoh's daughter.
Well, according
to my readings,
our friend suffered
the Hom-Dai,
the worst of all Ancient
Egyptian curses,
one reserved only
for the most evil
of blasphemers.
ln my research, l've never
heard of this curse having
actually been performed.
RICK: That bad, huh?
Yes, well, they...
They never used it
because they feared it so.
lt's written that
if a victim of the Hom-Dai
should ever arise,
he would bring with him
the 10 plagues of Egypt.
That's called stealing,
you know.
EVELYN: According to you
and my brother,
it's called borrowing.
RICK: l thought
the Book of Amun-Ra
was made out of gold.
lt is made out of gold.
This isn't
the Book of Amun-Ra.
This is something else.
l think this may be
the Book of the Dead.
The Book of the Dead?
Are you sure you want
to be playing around
with this thing?
lt's just a book.
No harm ever came
from reading a book.
(WIND HOWLING)
That happens a lot
around here.
So, what's it say?
"Amun Ra. Amun Dei."
lt speaks of the night
and of the day.
(READING lN ANCIENT EGYPTIAN)
(GROWLING)
No! You must not read
from the book!
(CAMEL GRUNTING)
(BUZZING)
Run!
Go, go!
(PEOPLE SHOUTING)
What have we done?
BURNS: Where the hell
did they come from?
l ain't waiting
around to find out.
BURNS: My glasses. My glasses!
Leave me! Leave me!
Hey! Hey!
Could you help me
find my gl...
Wait for me!
(THUDDING)
Who's there?
(GROWLING)
BURNS: (WHISPERING) Daniels?
(SCREAMING)
(RUMBLING)
Oh, Jon!
(SKITTERING)
Scarabs!
JONATHAN: Run, Evy!
Go, go, go! Run!
(SCREAMING)
Evelyn?
JONATHAN: Evy?
Evy!
(WALL CLOSING)
(MOANING)
Oh, Mr. Burns.
Thank goodness.
l was just starting
to get scared.
l've lost everyone.
(GROANING)
My eyes. My eyes...
(GROWLING)
(SCREAMING)
Please help me.
My tongue. He took my tongue.
Please don't leave me.
(GROWLING)
Anck-Su-Namun?
Damn it! lt's a trap door.
There's gotta be a switch
or something around here
someplace.
(SHOUTING)
Run, you sons
of bitches! Run!
Go.
(SCREAMING)
Go! Go!
(SPEAKING ANCIENT EGYPTIAN)
There you are!
Will you quit playing
hide-and-seek?
Come on.
Let's get out of here.
(SHUDDERING)
JONATHAN: Evy!
(ROARING)
(GROWLING)
Move!
JONATHAN: Yeah, right.
BENl: Did you see that?
lt was walking.
lt was walking!
l told you to leave or die.
You refused.
Now, you may
have killed us all,
for you have unleashed
a creature we have feared
for more than 3,000 years.
Relax. l got him.
No mortal weapon
can kill this creature.
He's not of this world.
You bastard.
What did you do to him?
We saved him. Saved him
before the creature
could finish his work.
Leave, all of you, quickly,
before he finishes you all.
(SPEAKING ARABIC)
l must now go on the hunt,
and try and find a way
to kill him.
l already told you,
l got him.
Know this,
this creature
is the bringer of death.
He will never eat,
he will never sleep,
and he will never stop.
(SQUEALING)
(GROWLING)
(SCREAMS)
May the good Lord protect
and watch over me
as a shepherd watches
over his flock.
(CHANTING lN ARABIC)
No? Okay.
(SPEAKING GIBBERISH)
(SPEAKING HEBREW)
(SPEAKING ANCIENT EGYPTIAN)
My prince.
(MARSHALLING)
(GROWLING)
(CHILDREN CHATTERING)
(THUNDER RUMBLING)
l thought you said you didn't
believe in that fairy tales
and hokum stuff.
Having an encounter
with a 3,000-year-old
walking, talking corpse
does tend to convert one.
Forget it. We're out the door,
down the hall, and we're gone.
Oh, no, we are not.
Oh, yes, we are.
We woke him up,
and we are going
to stop him.
We? What we?
We didn't read that book.
l told you not to play around
with that thing.
Didn't l tell you?
Yes, right then,
me, me, me, me.
l, l, l woke him up
and l intend to stop him.
Yeah? How?
You heard the man.
No mortal weapons
can kill this guy.
Then we are just
going to have to find
some immortal ones.
There goes that we again.
Look, will you listen to me?
We have to do something.
Once this creature
has been reborn,
his curse is going to spread
until the whole of the Earth
is destroyed.
Yeah? ls that my problem?
lt is everybody's problem.
Evelyn, l appreciate
you saving my life
and all,
but when l signed on,
l agreed to take you
out there
and to bring you back.
l have done that.
End of job. End of story.
Contract terminated.
That's all l am to you?
A contract?
You can either tag along
with me or you can stay here
and try
and save the world.
What's it gonna be?
l'm staying.
Fine.
(MUSIC PLAYING)
l'm the last
of the Royal Air Corps
still stationed out here,
you know...
Some bloody idiot
spilt his drink.
All the other laddies
died in the sky and
were buried in the sand.
Good chaps, every one
of them, too.
Hi, Winston.
Yeah...
You know, O'Connell,
ever since the end
of the great war,
there hasn't been
a single challenge
worthy of a man like me.
Yeah. We all got
our little problems
today, Winston.
l just wish l could
have chucked it in
with the others
and gone down
in flame and glory,
instead of sitting
around here, rotting
of boredom and booze.
Of boredom and booze.
Cheers.
Oh, well,
back to the airfield.
Tell me, has your sister
always been...
Oh, yes, always.
We're all packed up,
but the damn boat doesn't
leave till tomorrow morning.
Tail set firmly
between your legs,
l see.
You can talk.
You don't have
some sacred walking
corpse after you.
So, how's your friend?
He had his eyes
and his tongue ripped out.
How would you be?
l'm so pleased to meet you.
Prince lmhotep does not like
to be touched.
A silly Eastern superstition,
l'm afraid.
Please forgive me.
BENl: Burns, Prince lmhotep
thanks you for
your hospitality.
No.
And for your eyes,
and for your tongue.
Wha...
But l am afraid
more is needed.
Wha...
The prince must finish the job
and consummate the curse,
which you
and your friends...
No!
...have brought down
upon yourselves.
No! Wait! No!
(BURNS SCREAMING)
Good luck, boys.
Sweet Jesus!
Tasted just like...
Blood.
"And the rivers and waters
of Egypt ran red and were
as blood."
He's here.
(THUNDER RUMBLING)
MAN: Oh, looks like
it's gonna storm.
Oh, Evelyn!
Oh, so you're still here.
We've got problems.
(PEOPLE SCREAMING)
Hey!
Beni, you little stinkweed.
Where you been?
(lMHOTEP ROARING)
(GROWLING)
(ROARING)
We are in serious trouble.
(SPEAKING ANCIENT EGYPTIAN)
(GROWLING)
(CAT MEOWS)
We are in very
serious trouble.
JONATHAN: He does seem
to like you, Evy.
RICK: Yeah, what's that about?
HENDERSON: What's this guy
want?
There's only one person
that can give us any answers.
EVELYN: You!
LIBRARIAN: Miss Carnahan.
Gentlemen.
What is he doing here?
Do you really want to know,
or would you prefer
to just shoot us?
After what l just saw,
l'm willing to go on
a little faith here.
CURATOR: We are part
of an ancient secret society.
For over 3,000 years,
we have guarded
the City of the Dead.
We are sworn at manhood
to do any and all
in our part to stop
the High Priest lmhotep
from being reborn
into this world.
Because of you,
we have failed.
You think this justifies
the killing of innocent
people?
To stop this creature?
Let me think.
Yes!
Question. Why doesn't
he like cats?
Cats are the guardians
of the underworld.
He will fear them
until he is fully
regenerated.
Then he will
fear nothing.
You know how
he gets his self
fully regenerated?
By killing everyone
who opened that chest.
And sucking them dry!
EVELYN: Jonathan, will you
stop playing with that?
When l saw him alive
at Hamunaptra,
he called me Anck-Su-Namun.
And then just now
in Mr. Burns' quarters,
he tried to kiss me.
lt's because of his love
for Anck-Su-Namun
that he was cursed.
Apparently, even after
3,000 years...
He is still in love with her.
Yes, that is very romantic,
but what has it got
to do with me?
Perhaps he will once again
try to raise her
from the dead.
Yes.
And it appears he has already
chosen his human sacrifice.
Bad luck, old mum.
LIBRARIAN: On the contrary,
it may just give us
the time we need
to kill the creature.
We will need
all the help we can get.
His powers are growing.
JONATHAN: "And he stretched
forth his hand towards
the heavens
"and there was darkness
throughout the land of Egypt."
EVELYN: We must stop him
from regenerating.
Who opened that chest?
HENDERSON: There was me
and Daniels here.
And Burns, of course.
DAVE: And that
Egyptologist fellow.
What about my buddy, Beni?
No, he scrammed out of there
before we opened the thing.
Yeah, he was the smart one.
RICK: Yeah, that sounds
like Beni.
We must find the Egyptologist
and bring him back
to the safety of the fort
before the creature
can get to him.
Right.
She stays here.
You three, come with me.
HENDERSON: Not me...
DAVE: No, no!
Just a minute!
You can't leave me behind
like some old carpetbag.
Who put you in charge,
O'Connell?
What do you think
you are doing?
Jonathan! O'Connell!
Sorry, but he's a bit tall.
Jonathan,
coward that you are...
O'Connell, you are not
leaving me in here!
EVELYN: Jonathan,
if you don't open this door
in one minute flat...
EVELYN: O'Connell...
This door doesn't open.
Let me out of here.
She doesn't come out,
and no one goes in, right?
Right.
Right?
O'Connell! Jonathan!
Let's go, Jonathan.
Oh, l thought l could
just stay at the fort
and reconnoiter.
RICK: Now!
Yeah, right.
We're just gonna rescue
the Egyptologist.
(WINGS FLAPPING)
(WATER SPLASHING)
(BANGING)
(CLATTERING)
(BENl GRUNTING)
Well, well, well.
Let me guess.
Spring cleaning.
JONATHAN: Nice shot.
Oh, Beni, did you fall down?
Let me help you up.
You came back
from the desert
with a new friend,
didn't you, Beni?
What friend?
You are my only friend.
What the hell are you doing
with this creep?
What's in it for you?
lt is better to be
the right hand of the devil
than in his path.
As long as l serve him,
l am immune.
(GRUNTING)
lmmune from what?
(SWEARING lN HUNGARIAN)
What did you say?
l don't wanna tell you.
You'll just hurt me some more.
What are you looking for?
And try not to lie to me.
The book!
The black book
they found at Hamunaptra.
He wants it back.
He said to me it would be
worth its weight in gold.
What does he want
the book for?
l don't know.
Something about bringing
his dead girlfriend
back to life.
But that's all.
He just wants the book,
l swear.
Just the book, l swear.
And your sister.
But other than that...
(SCREAMING)
(GROANING)
(SHOUTING)
(PEOPLE SCREAMING)
(GROWLING)
(BUZZING)
(PEOPLE SCREAMING)
That's two down,
two to go.
Then he'll be coming
after Evy.
SOLDIER: (YELLING)
Guards in place!
Reporting all clear, sir!
To hell with this.
l'm going downstairs,
get me a drink.
You want something?
Yeah. Yeah, get me
a glass of bourbon.
All right.
And a shot of bourbon.
Yeah, okay, okay.
And a bourbon chaser.
l'll get your damn bourbon!
Don't worry about the door.
(HOWLING)
(VOICE MUTTERING)
(SCREAMING)
(SNARLING)
(SIGHING)
Anck-Su-Namun.
(GASPING)
Hey, get your ugly face
off of her!
(SPEAKING ANCIENT EGYPTIAN)
Look what l got.
(SNARLING)
(GROWLING)
(PANTING)
You all right?
Well, l'm not sure.
Well, according to legend,
the black book the Americans
found at Hamunaptra
is supposed to bring
people back from the dead.
Until now, it was a notion
l was unwilling to believe.
Believe it, sister.
That's what brought
our buddy back to life.
Yes. l'm thinking that
if the black book
can bring dead people
to life...
Then maybe the gold book
can kill him.
That's the myth.
Now, we just have
to find out where
the gold book is hidden.
CROWD: (CHANTING) lmhotep.
lmhotep.
ALL: lmhotep.
Last but not least,
my favorite plague,
boils and sores.
ARDETH: They have become
his slaves.
So it has begun,
the beginning of the end.
Not quite yet,
it hasn't. Come on.
lmhotep.
CROWD: (CHANTING) lmhotep.
(SPEAKING ANCIENT EGYPTIAN)
lmhotep.
According to Bembridge
scholars, the golden
Book of Amun-Ra
is located inside
the statue of Anubis.
That's where we found
the black book.
Exactly.
Looks like the old boys
at Bembridge were mistaken.
They mixed the books up.
Mixed up where
they were buried.
So, if the black book
is inside the statue
of Anubis,
then the golden book
must be inside...
(CLAMORING)
Come on, Evy, faster.
Patience is a virtue.
Not right now, it isn't.
l think l'll go and get
the car started.
l've got it.
The golden Book of Amun-Ra
is at Hamunaptra inside
the statue of Horus.
Take that, Bembridge scholars.
(CLAMORING)
lmhotep.
ALL: lmhotep.
Let's go, let's go,
let's go!
Get this thing in gear, boy.
Let's get out of here.
JONATHAN: Evy. Come on, Evy.
Hurry up.
lmhotep!
(GROWLING
You're gonna get yours, Beni!
You hear me?
You're gonna get yours!
Oh, like l've never
heard that before!
(TIRES SCREECHING)
(JONATHAN SCREAMING)
Hang on!
(GRUNTING)
Hey! O'Connell! O'Connell!
(SNARLING)
(GASPING)
(ROARING)
(CRUNCHING)
Jump down!
Move, move, move!
ALL: (CHANTING) lmhotep.
lmhotep.
lt's the creature.
He's fully regenerated.
(SPEAKING ANCIENT EGYPTIAN)
Come with me, my princess.
lt is time to make
you mine forever.
For all eternity, idiot.
BENl: Take my hand,
and l will spare your friends.
Oh, dear.
Have you got
any bright ideas?
l'm thinking, l'm thinking.
You better think
of something fast,
because if he turns me
into a mummy,
you're the first one
l'm coming after.
No.
Don't.
No!
He has to take me
to Hamunaptra
to perform the ritual.
She is right.
Live today, fight tomorrow.
l'll be seeing you again.
Evelyn!
Hey, that's mine.
Thank you.
(SPEAKING ANCIENT EGYPTIAN)
No! Let go of me!
ALL: lmhotep.
EVELYN: Let go of me!
Goodbye, my friend.
Come here, you little...
lmhotep.
Come on!
What about my sister?
We're gonna get her back!
Go!
RICK: You're next!
Come on! Give me your hand!
You go!
Come on!
Go!
(GRUNTING)
(SCREAMING)
(GOAT BLEATING)
(CHILDREN CHATTERING)
(MUSIC PLAYING)
RICK: Morning, Winston.
A word?
What's your little problem
got to do with His Majesty's
Royal Air Corps?
Not a damn thing.
ls it dangerous?
You probably won't
live through it.
By Jove,
do you really think so?
Everybody else we've
bumped into has died.
Why not you?
What's the...
What's the challenge, then?
Rescue the damsel
in distress,
kill the bad guy,
and save the world.
Winston Havlock
at your service, sir.
Are you all right?
Do l bloody look all right?
How you doing?
See that?
l've never seen one so big.
Never?
No!
Get off me! Get off!
l need a newjob.
EVELYN: Oh, my God.
We're back.
(AIRCRAFT HOVERING)
O'Connell.
(ROARING)
Oh, my God.
Hey, Winston! Pedal faster!
Hang on, men!
Stop it! You'll kill them!
That's the idea.
(ALL SCREAMING)
Here l come, laddies!
(LAUGHING)
(ENGINE SPLUTTERING)
(EXPLODING)
l love the whole
sand-wall trick.
lt was beautiful.
Bastard.
(GRUNTING)
JONATHAN: Excuse me?
A little help would be useful,
if it's not too much trouble!
Yeah, yeah. All right.
Winston! Hey, Winston!
Quicksand! Get back!
lt's quicksand.
Keep moving!
Nasty little fellows
such as yourself always
get their comeuppance.
Really? They do?
Oh, yes.
Always.
(SKITTERING)
JONATHAN: l'd take
those bigger stones first.
Take them from the top,
otherwise the whole thing
will cave in on us.
Come on.
Put your backs into it.
Yes, well, you've got
the idea. Chop, chop.
(SQUEALING)
l say!
Gents, you should come
and have a look at this.
(SKITTERING)
(SCREAMING)
What?
lt's my arm! My arm!
Do something!
Hold it!
Do something! Do something!
Not that! Not that!
(SCREAMING)
(SKITTERING)
O'Connell.
(CHANTING lN ANCIENT EGYPTIAN)
(GROANING)
(BOTH GROANING)
Bembridge scholars
never wrote about this.
Get off me. Get off!
(SPEAKING ANCIENT EGYPTIAN)
Wha...Wha...
Can you see...
Yeah.
Can you believe...
Can we just...
No.
(GRUNTING)
Who the hell
are these guys?
Priests.
lmhotep's priests.
All right, then.
(SHRIEKING)
(SQUEALING)
(GASPING)
(SCREAMING)
There he is!
Hello, Horus, old boy.
(PRIESTS SHRIEKING)
Time to close the door.
(CAMEL GRUNTING)
(MUTTERING lN HUNGARIAN)
(PRIESTS GRUNTING)
IMHOTEP: Anck-Su-Namun.
EVELYN: O'Connell!
Jonathan!
(CROAKING)
Damn. These guys just
don't quit, do they?
Keep digging.
(JINGLING)
JONATHAN: The Book of Amun-Ra.
Save the girl.
Kill the creature.
(YELLING)
RICK: What are
you waiting for?
Get out! Get out!
You all right?
Let's go.
(PRIESTS CHANTING)
(lMHOTEP CHANTING
lN ANCIENT EGYPTIAN)
(SHRIEKING)
(SCREAMING)
(SPEAKING ANCIENT EGYPTIAN)
JONATHAN: The Book of Amun-Ra!
l found it, Evy! l found it!
(lMHOTEP SPEAKING
ANCIENT EGYPTIAN)
EVELYN: Shut up and get me
off here, Jonathan!
Open the book, Jonathan.
lt's the only way to kill him.
You have to open the book
and find the inscription.
JONATHAN:
Well, l can't open it!
lt's locked or something.
We need the key, Evy!
EVELYN: lt's inside his robes.
EVELYN: O'Connell!
(SPEAKING ANCIENT EGYPTIAN)
(ALL GRUNTING)
Mummies.
(GRUNTING)
Look out!
There's one there...
O'Connell!
Here's an inscription.
(READING lN ANCIENT EGYPTIAN)
Oh, boy.
Oh, yeah.
This just keeps getting
better and better.
Do something, Jonathan.
Me?
You can command them.
You have got
to be joking.
Finish the inscription
on the cover, idiot,
then you can control them.
Oh. Right.
(SHRIEKING)
(SPEAKING ANCIENT EGYPTIAN)
(YELLING)
(GROWLING)
(PANTING)
Hurry up, Jonathan!
(ROARING)
(GRUNTING)
l can't figure out
this last symbol.
What does it look like?
(SCREAMING)
lt's a bird. A stork!
(GASPING)
Ahmenophus.
Oh, yes, l see.
(SPEAKING ANCIENT EGYPTIAN)
(lMHOTEP SPEAKING
ANCIENT EGYPTIAN)
(SPEAKING ANCIENT EGYPTIAN)
Anck-Su-Namun!
(lMHOTEP SPEAKING
ANCIENT EGYPTIAN)
Anck-Su-Namun!
(SCREAMING)
Evy, l've got it.
Keep him busy.
No problem.
Hurry, Evy! Hurry!
You're not helping.
EVELYN: Oh! l've got it.
(READING lN ANCIENT EGYPTIAN)
(SCREAMING)
(SHOUTING lN ANCIENT EGYPTIAN)
RICK: l thought you said
it was gonna kill him!
(GROWLING)
He's mortal.
(SPEAKING ANCIENT EGYPTIAN)
Death is only the beginning.
(COINS JINGLING)
(CREAKING)
(RUMBLING)
Time to go.
You've lost the book!
Jonathan, l can't believe...
Hurry!
Come on!
Couldn't we just...
No, Jonathan!
BENl: O'Connell!
O'Connell! Wait!
Come on, come on!
Wait! Please!
Come on, come on! Beni!
Goodbye, Beni.
(SQUEAKING)
Go away.
(SKITTERING)
(SHOOING)
(BENl SCREAMING)
JONATHAN: Look out, look out!
(SCREAMING)
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
You have earned the respect
and gratitude of me
and my people.
Yes, well,
it was nothing.
May Allah smile
upon you always.
And yourself.
(CAMEL GRUNTING)
Yes, anytime.
RICK: Stay out of trouble.
He's just leaving
us here.
Well, l guess we go home
empty-handed again.
l wouldn't say that.
Oh, please!
How about you, darling?
Would you like
a little kissy-wissy?
(GRUNTING)
(JINGLING)