Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
Subtitles by explosiveskull
Our sun is dying.
And Union Corp controls all
of the remaining safe zones.
The last safe haven from
our dying star's wrath.
Those who are strong
enough to fight
are forced to fight for credits
in unknown galactic
solar systems
in search of stardust.
Citizen,
you are in possession
of government property.
Return the
identification sphere.
Citizen, you are in possession
of government property.
Stay, do not resist,
do not resist,
or I will use lethal force.
You are in possession of Code
two eight ba dess eight nine.
Do not resist, or I
will use lethal force.
Indian travel sphere, scanning.
Citizen, you are in possession
of government property.
Deactivating lethal force.
Facial code accepted.
Return to base.
Facial recognition confirmed.
Union Corp welcomes you.
Union City, now accepting
armed, unallied humans.
Proper build for a new tomorrow.
A better today, a
brighter future.
It all starts with Union.
In this city, come join a
thousand lucky soldiers who are
fighting for our future.
Help get started.
You look scared.
sweetheart.
Huh?
Union Corp
invites you on a journey
unlike anything in the universe.
All non-accepted will
have a chance to enlist.
The world needs you.
Help join the fight
to save our world.
awaits you.
Dawnseeker.
It's one of the meanest,
nastiest sumbitches
we ever laid eyes on.
Now Omnia Prime is home
to many, many surprises.
Most of which are
designed to do one thing,
and one thing very, very well,
and that's kill humans.
Or anything that doesn't
eat, breathe, or even shit
the way they are used to.
Now am I making
myself crystal clear
as to what we are up against?
Good, now the Dawnseeker
has one objective.
One objective only.
That is to find, extract
the precious asset
known as stardust,
which is the only thing that's
keeping that piece of shit
floating rock we call
Earth from reverting back
to the dark ages.
So I'm not gonna have to
tell you how important it is
that we locate the Stardust
and hightail our candy asses
back to base straight
to Nemean, understood?
Now as long as we have
this, we have him.
You rise at oh five hundred.
Get some rest, boys.
It has like five
eyes or some shit.
What do you think, Evo?
Yeah.
Miles to go.
I'm gonna get you.
Yeah, you know he gets it.
The hierarchy.
It's best you don't forget that.
'Cause if you do?
Ooh, remember this face.
That's enough.
Excuse me?
That's enough, Otto.
I'll be seeing you
around.
Attention,
the reactor sector
is being isolated.
Repeat, the reactor
sector is being isolated.
Attention, the reactor
Repeat, the reactor
sector is being isolated.
I can't do this, Father.
Fenix, you're more
important than you know.
Look at your target and focus.
You really think
I can do this?
Fenix, one day you will be
called upon to change the world,
and everything I have built
for mankind will belong to you.
How many with you?
Just me.
Darby...
Darby didn't make it.
Shit!
Where are the others?
What happened to our ship?
The others?
I've been pinned down
here for over a week.
Rendezvous at
these coordinates.
Who are you?
Name's York.
York?
Third battalion,
ninth level infantry.
My planet has been mining
here in peace for generations.
I don't follow.
You are from Planet
Beta Four, right?
Beta Four?
You mean Earth.
No, Planet Beta Four.
I wouldn't know what you call
your planet, now would I?
Tell me who sent you!
Who sent me?
What did they tell you?
That you were on
some great mission?
Some save the
world kind of shit?
Nemean has been
stripping the resources
from this planet for decades.
It's time he learned to share.
What are you talking about?
We need him!
Give me something!
If we are to make it to
the rendezvous, we need him.
He's been trying to
kill me for over a week
and all you have is we need him.
What she's saying is, if
I'd have wanted you dead,
you already would be.
You have a rescue party.
I ain't gon' be here.
The fuck are
you talking about?
We were never meant
to leave this place.
I'm impressed.
Stiffen up and let's play?
Yours cowboy.
Show you guys something.
Happened when your vessel
broke through the sky.
What happened to him?
I was hoping
you could tell me.
How the fuck would we know?
He was wearing
this fancy wristband,
figured it meant something.
Galen?
Not far from your crash site.
See, I figured his mono-pod
must've malfunctioned
in the crash.
No, pods couldn't
have caused this.
This was done to him.
How can you be so sure.
Because, it is a perfect kill.
Whoever did this wanted
us to find him this way.
You get all that
from a dead body?
No, and the fact that his
wristband is still intact,
they were clearly
only after one thing.
Which is what?
Recognition.
It says I am here.
What about the mission.
Hey, how will we get paid?
A man is dead, our entire
purpose here is at stake,
and you're worried
about your credits?
Hey, he's dead, ain't he.
It's more credits for me.
And York, York.
Say, tell me, they got credits
on whatever the fuck
planet you're from?
Huh?
Why don't you and I go
get the stardust ship
and double the price?
Make that money.
Huh?
You hear me, are you deaf?
I heard you?
Then what's the problem.
Let's get paid.
There's only one problem.
With your skills and
mine, we can make it
all the way to the solar
fields, you know that.
Come on.
It's not what I found at
the crash that concerns me.
It's what I didn't find.
The Dawnseeker.
Dead!
How can you be sure?
Because no one
could've survived that.
Nothing!
Whatever's shielding
us from what lies
beneath the safe area,
it's the solar fields.
What are those?
Designed, created,
whatever they are,
they protect us from
what's out there.
Is that why they
built a city here?
Different regimes
like to converge, trade.
And what of your regime?
Who do you fight for?
I guess we're
about to find out.
Jax, you're giving
away our position.
To who, Evo?
Face it, Jax,
we're on our own.
Did you hear that?
Yeah.
Don't move!
It's us!
How many with you?
Anyone?
Just us, why?
Did you see anyone, anything?
It's not possible.
Jax.
Just us.
Jax!
You ain't sending
us your location.
But why?
Evo, Evo, Evo!
Hope that's looking
for something bigger.
Shit!
Grenade!
Evo!
What did this?
Nothing I wanna
meet anytime soon.
We need to get to the Space Ark.
That's a lot of credits.
The Space Ark doesn't sound
like it equals credits
in my account, so I say
fuck it and fuck you.
Let's go get some stardust.
He has a transponder.
Without it, no one's
calling a ride home.
Hey, where you going?
I said where are you going?
Whoever took Evo
laid a trap for us.
You aren't even
gonna look for him?
Why?
I can't grant him
passage to the afterlife.
She's a princess.
You're wasting your time.
Yeah, I know who you are.
Nemean Chord's very own.
What?
You think we wouldn't
recognize the boss's daughter?
Tell me, since we're
all so expendable,
how long before you
leave us all behind, huh?
You wanna find your
boyfriend, go find him yourself.
Otherwise, go to hell.
You go first.
Now here's what's gonna happen.
We're gonna search
that trail over there.
We're gonna get
that transponder.
And then we're gonna
go find some stardust
because I didn't travel
50 years for nothing.
You, go grab the
stardust container.
After you, princess.
Stay back!
Evo!
Where is your transponder?
Stay back!
Help me.
One of your faction members?
No, I've never seen
energy like that.
Felt like it was
toying with us.
Thought you said this planet was
void of intelligent life forms?
Void?
What did they tell you this
place was back on Beta Four.
Best to mine
stardust, nothing more.
Mine?
Stardust can only be
found in one place
and one place only, and that's
where your dawnseeker breed.
See they're born in tubes.
They harvest the energy
from the stardust
to hatch their larva.
If they're as powerful
as I've read about,
we got much larger problems.
Hey!
Look what I found.
We have to figure out
what we're up against.
You said twos.
Pairs.
Manipulating matter,
cloaking, energy,
basically the ultimate
goddamn killing machine.
Helmet was a dampener.
What are you thinking?
That it may still be figuring
out what it's capable of.
And that's why it
didn't try to kill us?
Nah.
It's why it didn't
try to kill her.
Where's the other one?
Jax?
Jax!
Where'd she go?
Oh, I got you.
Get off me!
No need to thank me.
And who the hell are you?
Do you have a ship?
What?
A ship?
Ugh.
Why'd you stop me?
I almost had it?
Going after a
dawnseeker is suicide.
Not this one.
It hasn't fully developed yet.
How would you know?
Because we brought
it from Earth.
Earth?
Terminus hasn't
destroyed it yet?
Terminus ended centuries ago.
How long have you been here?
Okay, I say we follow it
through the north quadrant,
wait for it to get thirsty,
and then we'll find a way to.
Jax!
She was just here!
Lieutenant Thane
of the Black Suns.
Fenix, from Beta Four.
We're searching
for a fugitive,
highly skilled and dangerous.
Can't say it rings any bells.
What are you other men?
We're just out on a
stroll, taking in the sights.
And you?
I'm, uh, I'm their guide.
Hey!
We haven't seen her.
I will have answers.
No honest mercenary'd be
caught dead in these parts.
Unless you're trying
to hide something
or looking for something
that needs to be hidden.
Arrest them!
Stripping and mining
this planet's resources
is against galactic law!
Call in the coordinates.
Get a transport out
here immediately.
You are making a big mistake.
Dawnseeker has
breached your wall.
He has adapted to
the magnetic pulse.
We had similar gear in our tech.
The only thing that
breached our walls
is staring right back at me,
and if you don't stop flapping
them two things on your face,
I'm not gonna be so nice.
Good!
I wouldn't have done that.
I want a pawn to rook
formation from corner to corner.
Nothing moves out here
without me knowing about it.
Is that clear?
Sir, yes sir!
Defensive positions.
To the right!
Cut us loose!
Defensive positions!
To the right!
I said cut us loose!
Watch out!
Go!
Fall back!
E.M.P.!
Oh, that seemed...
different.
That's because it was.
It learned fast.
No, this one was more
skilled, more adept.
So got another one
of those on Beta Four?
I think we may have
found his counterpart.
What?
You shitting me?
There's another one out there?
God!
It's pinned us in.
Because it didn't
try to harm any of us?
Pulse wave knocked
out the solar fields.
What's that mean?
Whatever was on the
other side of the Space Ark
just got an open invitation.
We need to get to the
other side of the Ark.
The other side.
We need to set up a perimeter.
We need to cross over.
I thought you
said it wasn't safe
on the other side of the Ark.
That's before it was
less safe on this side.
If I've learned nothing,
I've learned nothing's safe
when the solar fields are down.
Let's get the pikes.
The way I see it is, Otto
is looking out for himself.
And Thane only cares
about his men, so,
so it's just you and
me, what do you say?
Let's just try and make
it through the night.
You know, I had a family once.
Daughter.
You remind me of her.
Smart.
Stubborn.
Till we were low on credits.
I did something I...
Promised my wife
I'd never do again.
There's a few truths
in this world.
And never change, no matter
how much you want to.
You can never trust
anyone but yourself.
You just gotta ask
yourself one question.
What do you think
they'll do to us by dawn?
Know if my men are
compromised in any way,
I will kill you myself.
I caught this one
tampering with the pikes.
Zan Desai, last
of the eternals.
We've searched the galaxy
far and wide for you.
The stories are true.
I made my name taming dogs!
You're wanted for the
destruction of planet Demo,
the killing of the
alpha group known
as the eternal Beta Four,
and numerous other charges
of treason and evasion.
Why'd you tamper with the pikes?
How did you escape?
I didn't mess with the pike.
I activated it.
You can't run
from the Black Suns.
We always get our mark.
I wasn't running.
They have what I need.
Thane, I think
we have movement.
Check it out, now!
Is it back?
Move in!
Go, go!
Sucker punching piece of shit!
Like I said, let's get to
the other side of the Ark.
Hey.
Why you always getting
your ass kicked?
You're such a bad ass.
Seriously, everybody
that meets you wants
to beat the shit out of you.
Let's go!
In order for us to
cross over, we need to know
what frequency the
Ark is vibrating at.
Frequency, what's that matter?
Well, we're operating
at a different frequency,
it could trigger our
matter as hostile.
Turn the would be
portal into a microwave.
Precisely.
And I believe there
are other mercenaries
trapped just on the other side.
You think they
left their ship.
That's the idea.
But what about
the Earth's sun?
Stardust?
Do they know?
Know that you're a criminal,
a treacherous
backstabbing snake?
I think that was
made clear, yeah.
Funny how
people never seem
to ask the right questions.
I suggested gagging you
but decided against it.
How's Father doing nowadays?
Father couldn't care less
about saving the planet
and even less if you were alive.
So you had to come
see for yourself.
You're welcome.
Some rescue.
Don't look like
you needed rescuing.
Do they know you sabotaged
the ship to crash land here?
No more than they know
what you're truly doing
on this side of the Ark.
How long are you going to
keep up this little charade?
As long as it takes.
I have no intentions
of saving Beta Four.
Although I wish
your planet well,
my job is to keep you
at bay while my employer
obtains the stardust
for his self.
Hold me at bay?
You son of a bitch!
You could've fucking killed me!
York's a galactic legend.
Singlehandedly took down the
prison, ice prison in Pompeii.
That's not a man
who's easily bested.
Now tell me, what of
this other dawnseeker.
It isn't a weapon.
It's a living species,
and from what I gather,
not from this planet.
What do you mean?
This Space Ark is a ripple
in time caught between realms.
On their planet, the
dawnseeker's no different
from you and I.
A species with
multiple layers.
That's why I'm on this side.
In order to save Earth,
you must save the sun
on the other side of the Ark.
The Earth will exist in a
different ideal of time.
So you're gonna keep those
things as trophies or what?
Each member of the Black
Suns is born and bred
on the battlefield.
Where I come from, war
has no peace after it.
Go.
Go!
Now!
The Space Ark's right ahead.
I knew you would be here.
York?
Are you alright?
We need a plan.
What are you talking about?
The Space Ark's right up there?
Yeah, but there's one problem.
See, I have my transponder.
Fenix has Evo's, and I'm
fairly certain, yeah,
there's no doubt,
you've got one.
And I don't have to tell you
that without a transponder
you can't cross over
the magnetic field
to the Space Ark.
So...
Hey no, what are you doing?
The way I see it,
someone's gotta be bait.
If you destroy
the transponders,
none of us can cross
through the Ark.
You think I
wanna survive this?
No.
See, I know why the
dawnseeker won't harm you.
'Cause you set it free!
Why don't you be a
doll and hand it over.
What are you doing?
No!
Stop!
You're next, sweetheart.
Now you.
I said you!
Go!
We have to hurry up
and get the stardust
before sun burns up
while we're not there.
The order predicted
that the space time ratio
between what's left of
Earth and the dying sun
shouldn't be a
concern until 2240.
Exactly.
What year is it?
It's July 2245.
We have a very short
window to find the stardust
and deliver it before we
have to seal ourselves
into hibernation pods
again for the winter.
Look.
What's that?
Is that?
The Ark?
This used to be
a portal to the other side?
Transfusion fiber.
This isn't just a gateway.
This is a time machine.
Careful.
Dawnseeker!
Hey!
We have to cross
through the Ark!
Go!
The Ark may close!
You need to get the stardust!
The ship.
Fenix!
We need power to
the main console.
Stardust.
I've never seen
this type before.
It's pure,
not from this planet.
How do you know that?
'Cause I brought it.
We need to get off this ship
and fly it directly
into the sun.
Last chance?
Subtitles by explosiveskull
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today