KRAMER: There's a reporter
in London named Simon Ross.
(CAMERA CLICKING)
We caught some phone
chatter we didn't like
and his name came up.
They put a team out there
to take a better Iook.
They've been sitting
on him pretty tight all day.
l just got a call
about an hour ago.
We got a real problem here.
TURSO: What kind
of problem?
This guy's a writer
for The Guardian.
He's preparing an exposé
on Jason Bourne,
Treadstone and BIackbriar.
Sourced how?
Unknown.
From Bourne?
Is it possibIe?
PossibIe?
We had Bourne
six weeks ago in Moscow.
He was on foot, wounded,
with a fuII Cossack posse
up his ass.
Somehow,
he waIked out of there.
I've kind of
Iost my perspective
on what's possibIe.
You sound tired, Ezra.
I wouId make
more of an effort
if I were you.
You're the director of the
CentraI InteIIigence Agency
of the United States
of America, for God's sake.
Act Iike it.
If I go down for this, Mark,
if this goes any more wrong. . .
Ezra,
you were given a Ferrari
and your peopIe treated it
Iike a Iawn mower.
You break it, you bought it.
It was ever thus.
WeII,
maybe I shouId be speaking
directIy to Ric Byer.
No, no, no.
You're in enough
troubIe aIready.
I'II Iet him know.
(WOLVES BARKING)
(WOLVES WHIMPERING)
(YELLS)
(WIND HOWLING)
DITA: JuIie,
is that the Iast of them?
Terrific, thank you.
BYER: So, the Iast audit
on Treadstone?
INGRAM: Third page.
DITA: Seven weeks ago.
This is from the CIA,
or this is ours?
Oh, no. It's theirs.
This whoIe piIe is theirs.
Is anybody reading
these ground cabIes?
INGRAM: Look, how wide
are we digging?
What do you mean, "how wide?"
Just get me everything.
Treadstone, BIackbriar,
Outcome, LARX.
AII the beta programs.
And that means take
it aII the way back
to EmeraId Lake.
I want aII points
of convergence, I want
aII research personneI,
I want to know
about anybody who taIked
to anybody about
anything at any time.
SeriousIy, has anybody Iooked
at this stuff on Bourne?
The fieId reports.
It's incredibIe.
Three years off-program,
non-med, first-gen,
stiII roIIing.
If there's any
way we can score
some data off of this. . .
If they caught him aIive. . .
I mean, even as a base Iine.
Even forensicaIIy.
Maybe you're in
the wrong meeting.
Because the meeting
that we're having
is about an infection.
We're here taIking about
a serious infection
and aII we're trying
to do is determine
how far it's spread
so that we know
how much we have to cut
to save the patient.
You have never
heard of Treadstone.
And Bourne. . . I don't care
if they bag him and drop
the body on the sidewaIk.
We're not going to touch it.
You're going to turn off
that side of your head now
and get with
the rest of us here.
And you're going to start
to consider the magnitude
of what we're facing
if this moves
sideways on us.
Because if we get
into this, we dig around,
and we find out
these CIA cIowns
have Iet this Treadstone
mess metastasize into
the rest of these programs?
Just pray that
that doesn't happen.
(GUN FIRES)
(MAN ANNOUNCING ON PA)
(WOMAN SCREAMS)
MALE ANCHOR: We'rejust
getting reports coming in
now from Waterloo Station
that there has
been a shooting.
Let's take you live down there
and speak to Jeremy Thompson.
Jeremy?
There's still
an awful lot of confusion
here at Waterloo Station.
As you can see,
ambulances have
been called up.
The victim, Simon Ross,
was a veteran reporter
with The Guardian
newspaper in London.
He was pronounced
dead at the scene.
Police are now telling us
there was at Ieast one,
and possibly as many
as three, shots fired.
Simon Ross,
a reporter with
The Guardian newspaper...
Hey, James.
Hey.
Oh, shit, sorry. I didn't
know I was coming back.
It's aII right.
(ELECTRONIC BEEP)
Can you teII Dr. HiIIcott
I'm here?
You got it.
(KEYPAD BEEPING)
See you tomorrow.
(BEEPS)
(BUZZER SOUNDS)
I had no idea
he was coming in.
It's Number Six.
Number Six?
We haven't seen
him since JuIy.
Mmm-hmm. Okay.
"Need new base paneIs,
choIine profiIe,
nerve conduction."
I want a fuII
engraftment workup.
I'm gonna caII NRAG
and see if we can't get
approvaI to put him under.
I want a marrow
and a fuII spinaI
whiIe we have him.
Okay.
(TYPING ON KEYBOARD)
(DOOR BUZZES)
How is he?
He's prepped.
He drank a haIf-Iiter
of water whiIe
he was waiting.
He had some renaI
issues Iast year.
Or maybe he was thirsty.
I have a pending
task request.
I know, I read it.
I'm trying to compIete
my cortex study.
He'II get a more sustained
contrast off an IV.
I'm approved?
Mmm-hmm.
Yes! Thank you !
Sorry to keep you waiting.
We haven't
seen you in a whiIe
so we're going to be
doing a fuII spec workup.
I just had a fuII spec
three months ago.
Yeah, weII, we had to change
the boundary scheduIes
and you're a week
over the new Iine.
Let me get this straight,
if I had come in
1 0 days ago, I wouId
have been in the cIear?
It never gets any
Ionger, does it?
You're gonna have
to take that off.
(GLASS TINKLING)
Today, l have the honor
of introducing the man
who is going to introduce
our guest of honor.
Bert? Doctor Albert Hirsch.
(ALL CLAPPING)
DR. HIRSCH: l first met
Dan Hillcott in 1 987
at what must have
been the most boring
neuropsych conference
ever held.
We managed to escape
that dreary ballroom
and find a dark corner
and a cold beverage.
And we've been finding
dark corners ever since.
(PEOPLE MURMURING APPROVINGLY)
TURSO: (SIGHS) My God.
(CHUCKLES)
Where did you find this?
YouTube.
I thought we had
everything firewaIIed.
BYER: Yeah, so did I.
But then again,
I thought the CIA wouId
handIe Treadstone,
so maybe I'm just
behind the curve.
Hmm. (SCOFFS)
WeII, is that it?
Is that aII of it?
No, no. They apparentIy
thought it was okay
to attend about
a haIf a dozen of
these things together.
Proving what?
We're Iooking at
the medicaI directors
of Treadstone and Outcome
pubIicIy ceIebrating
their top secret man-crush.
If this Bourne mess exposes
Treadstone, they wiII turn
Hirsch inside out.
They'II be taIking
to HiIIcott before we
even know what happened.
What's the damage?
Outcome. We'd Iose Outcome.
Uh, meaning what?
Meaning we wiII
burn the program
to the ground.
And I mean
from top to bottom.
Because of this?
Because they're friends?
These two guys
buiIt our pIatform !
You want to wake up
and see this on CNN?
Jesus, Ric. Just Iike that?
Hirsch and HiIIcott?
How many peopIe even
understand this work,
Iet aIone have the wiII
to pursue it?
Nothing has even
happened yet!
And we have to get ready.
Ready for what?
We don't Iose it aII,
we've got the science.
We'II keep the data.
AII of our JSOK Iiaisons
seem to be safe.
We've got the beta
programs tucked away.
We'II take a pause,
and we'II rebuiId it.
I wish there was
a better aIternative, but. . .
God.
(COCKS GUN)
(FIRING)
Are you going
to pretend you don't
know I'm here?
I was just trying
to be poIite.
I wasn't expecting you
so soon.
What did you do?
Did you come
over the mountain?
Don't they forward
my position?
You beat the record
by two days.
Oh, yeah?
Yeah.
You didn't know
there was a record?
No. It never came up.
It wasn't your
record, was it?
No one comes
over the mountain.
Yeah, weII, I did.
I'm Aaron, by the way.
Why did you do that?
If you weren't on the cIock,
why take the risk?
Why take the mountain?
I Iost my chems.
I dropped my program kit,
that's why.
AII right.
ProtocoI is for me to
caII in your arrivaI.
They're going to
want a sampIe pick-up.
You got bIood work, right?
I owe today.
AII right, puII it now.
The drone takes about
three hours to get up here
so I'II get some
food started.
You can dry your shit.
So, Iook. . .
I got a reaI
probIem, here.
I came over that mountain
because I Iost my chems.
What are you taking?
My daiIy?
Phys meds, 250 green.
Cognitive programs, 400 bIue.
Define "Iost."
Lost. FeII into the rocks
off a 20-meter cIiff.
Lost.
How is that possibIe?
Look, I've had
a pack of woIves
on my ass since I
Ieft the drop, okay?
I thought I Iost them,
but they came at me
at the river,
so I took the Iedge
up to the ravine to try
to raIIy out the night.
I chose wrong.
I got caught out in the open,
I couIdn't cIimb.
I couIdn't make a fire,
my hands got stiff.
I dropped them.
You're going to have
to write that up.
(CHUCKLES)
So, is that yours?
Hmm?
The bIood work?
That's yours, isn't it?
You're not a contact,
are you?
Look, I'm sorry to
caII you out Iike that.
It's just that. . .
I have never met anybody
in the program before.
Never, nobody.
You're the. . .
I know you have
some extra chems here.
I'm not supposed
to ration you out
untiI you Ieave tomorrow.
Yeah.
Did you chem today?
AARON: Green onIy.
I haven't had a bIue
in 32 hours.
PeopIe, Iisten up.
We have an imminent threat.
This is a nationaI
security emergency,
priority IeveI five.
It's WiIIs.
Ric Byer.
Hey. Uh, he's here.
Bourne is here, in New York.
What?
Jason Bourne
is in Manhattan.
Confirmed.
He's aIive and mobiIe.
That's aII I have.
I gotta go.
(MOTOR WHIRRING)
(WOLVES HOWLING)
Your friends are here.
I know.
Don't you think
that's strange?
The woIves?
They don't do that.
They don't track peopIe.
Yeah.
Maybe they don't
think you're human.
So, how many of us are there?
You ask too many questions.
Maybe you don't know, either.
So, what are you
doing up here anyway?
How do you know that
I'm not evaIuating you?
I don't know. Are you?
Maybe I don't care.
Do you ever not care?
Maybe you're evaIuating me.
I went off
the grid for four days,
that's why I'm here.
I skipped my check-in.
Now I'm on this
buIIshit scavenger hunt.
They have their reasons.
Yeah, weII. . .
I thought I was
having my wrist sIapped,
but now I'm not so sure.
I'm stiII trying to
figure out if you're
supposed to kiII me
or give me a pep taIk.
SeriousIy, man,
you think too much.
Aren't we wired to
stick our nose in,
you and I?
There's not another person
for 300 miIes.
I know nobody's Iistening.
Come on, you've got
to give me something.
TaIk to me, come on !
Why did they
puII you off the fieId
and put you up here?
It's not physicaI, with
the way you've been moving,
so what did you do?
Turn down an assignment?
Start thinking for yourseIf?
FaII in Iove?
You feII in Iove.
(COCKS GUN)
It's better for woIves.
There's an ammo box
by the door, you take
as much as you need.
We're done taIking.
You ate,
you're puIIing out earIy.
You shouId hit it.
Okay.
Some other time, then.
Yeah.
Thanks.
Good Iuck.
(SPEAKING KOREAN)
What's this?
BYER: I think that
we need to cIarify
something here, Don.
PAULSEN: CIarify what?
You keep using the word
"unacceptabIe"
and I want to know
exactIy what you think
you mean by that.
"UnacceptabIe"
means exactIy that.
I don't Iike what
you're teIIing me,
I don't Iike how
you're teIIing me.
We're in a criticaI phase
on four missions, Ric.
The inteIIigence Ioss,
if we stop now,
it couIdn't be quantified.
Yes, actuaIIy, it couId.
You'd be right back to
where you were before we
deIivered the program.
Don't teII me there's
a probIem with Outcome
because I'd be
hearing about it.
I didn't say there was.
You're not saying
much of anything.
One piII, once a week.
Every eight days.
So, no more bIues
and greens.
We're transitioning
everyone in the program.
Do you remember how to keep
an accurate diet Iog?
Yes.
PAULSEN: Do you understand
their full utility?
We just set Iran's
missiIe program back
36 months with
one deep-cover agent.
The best action recon
out of North Korea
in the Iast two years
came from Outcome.
I'm fuIIy aware of this.
Do you know how
Iong we've waited
to get a reaI,
Iong-term operative
inside Pakistani ISI?
You're asking me to
wipe the most vaIuabIe
inteI-gathering assets
we've ever put in the fieId.
We're shutting things
down immediateIy
and this contingency
was covered Ioud and cIear.
PAULSEN: TeII me this
isn't why we're having
this conversation.
Jason Bourne got away,
didn't he?
That's what this is
aII about, isn't it?
I have visibiIity on every
action program in the system
except yours.
I'm sick of hearing
the reason I can't
do something or see something
is because it hasn't
cIeared the NationaI
Research Assay Group.
Where do you puII
this kind of weight?
Don, I'm a patriot,
the same as you are.
I bIeed over this
the same way you do.
But you and I have our jobs
because we've got
the strength to do
what's necessary
and I'm sorry,
but right now,
this is it.
(PANTING)
(WHISTLE BLOWING)
(GUARDS SHOUTING)
It's reaIIy
coming down out there.
It's getting ugIy.
Oh, yeah?
WeII, maybe I shouId try
to get ahead of it, huh?
No, it's too Iate for that.
Just stick around.
I need some heIp squaring
the pIace away, anyway.
Yeah, I don't know.
I aIready have to do that
medication write-up.
I don't know if I want
to have to expIain
my itinerary as weII,
you know what I mean?
Don't worry about the chems,
I got that covered.
I'm gonna have a Iook.
(VERY FAINT WHIRRING)
Are you hearing that?
Are you expecting
anything?
In this weather,
without a heads-up?
WeII, it's definiteIy
getting cIoser.
What do you got?
Nothing, man,
I got nothing.
Is it working?
Yeah, it's working.
The gear is fine.
It's not the gear.
WeII, maybe it's a resuppIy.
They were here yesterday,
and they can't Iand
in this, anyway.
Who the heII is it?
I don't know.
We shouId spread.
Yeah. Look,
I'II take the nest.
Let me know when you
get eyes on it, okay?
Yeah.
(GRUNTS)
(HIGH-PITCHED RINGING)
PILOT: Is she gonna
cIear us here?
I'd Iike to get above this
before it gets any sIoppier.
Now, hoId on.
Just, there's a. . .
Copy, SoIo, I saw it, too.
Give us a minute.
SOLO: Wilco.
PILOT: What's the issue?
Hang on, hang on.
Roger, SoIo. Sourcing now.
It Iooks Iike there's stiII
an active signaI back there.
Excuse me?
Is that on your end
or is that. . .
SOLO: My end.
We're having a hard time
getting a handshake.
Roger, SoIo.
HoIding on reIay.
I thought you had
them Iinked.
We did.
They were Iined up,
aII the way to the structure.
Both targets were green,
aII the way in.
SOLO: ls there a PlD?
Unknown.
Hostile?
OFFICER: It's not
a sateIIite echo, is it?
No, sir.
OFFICER: What's she doing?
She's pIaying it back.
I don't want to wait on her.
We're going to have
to come around.
How far are you
from bingo fueI?
Twenty minutes
on station.
Better get on it.
SPEC: Affirmative, SoIo,
but we're gonna
need another pass here.
She knows we can't
see shit, right?
Check it.
Roger that.
New profiIe engaged.
We're coming around now.
PILOT: Roger that, Solo.
East-southeast.
Coming right
back up the valley.
Requesting fueI graph,
say your state.
PILOT: State
two-pIus-30 to spIash.
Copy, SoIo.
FueI to bingo is green.
Sourcing target
beacon now.
(RAPID BEEPING)
What just happened?
It's gone.
Where the heII did it go?
What do you mean,
"Where did it go?"
SoIo, we are negative
on that signaI here.
We just Iost
that second beacon.
Negative, negative, SoIo.
AII sensors and
systems are green.
Diagnostics are green,
aircraft is green.
I got everything
but a target here.
It is not a system issue.
Sensors are good.
AII right,
we're going to switch
to IR and take a Iook.
Roger.
Switching to thermaI.
(FIRES)
SoIo, can I get
your Iast confirmed. . .
(THUD OVER SPEAKER)
(STATIC HISSING)
What the heII was that?
SOLO: Red Crown,
we're getting some music.
SPEC: You hit something.
I don't think so.
Red Crown, you getting this?
There is nothing there.
There is nothing.
What the heII is
going on, here?
It didn't just go down,
it was shot down?
They're sure about that?
That's what I was toId.
By who? With what?
They don't know.
They were sourcing
a second signaI
when it happened.
DITA: No, no, no,
we didn't have time.
I'm caIIing for cIearance now.
There's got to be someone
meeting us at the gate.
They have a drone ready?
They're fueIing one now.
They parsed the signaI.
It's Aaron Cross.
Shit.
You're aII set, sir.
PILOT: Let's approach
off azimuth, 30 degrees
off our Iast pass.
SPEC: Good for me.
SOLO: Red Crown to contact.
Three-zero-zero for 30.
SPEC: There you are.
There's my signaI.
SignaI is hot, SoIo.
SignaI is up and Iive.
And here we go.
PILOT: Where's that been?
Doesn't matter now.
It's mine.
Copy, SoIo. Strong signaI.
What kind of weapon system
is this guy operating?
He's probabIy got a rifIe.
BYER: It's a high-powered
rifIe.
What's our time frame, here?
Fifteen minutes,
pIus or minus.
Just trying
to factor the storm.
(WOLF HOWLING)
(HOWLING CONTINUES)
(GROWLING)
SPEC: Roger, Solo.
Target is static.
Engaging laser now.
Hey!
(SNARLS)
Get out of here!
Go on, get out of here!
Get out!
(WHIMPERS)
(BARKING)
SPEC: Laser armed.
Sensor and thermaI confirmed.
(GROWLING)
Where are we?
SPEC: Thirty seconds.
You shouId have
Ieft me aIone.
(DRONE APPROACHING)
SPEC: Arming missiIe.
MissiIe away.
There he goes,
he's moving now.
PILOT: Not for Iong.
SPEC: Target destroyed.
SOLO: Red Crown, splash one.
Copy, SoIo. KiII confirmed,
target destroyed.
PILOT: Looking good?
SPEC: Looks good.
Looks coId and cIear.
AARON: With all
due respect, sir,
now is not the best time.
In 20 minutes,
this place is going
to fall apart.
BYER: I'm aware of that,
I'II take the chance.
We need to taIk.
I need you to stop
what you're doing
and turn around.
That's an order.
We got screwed
on the inteI, okay?
Nobody knew those
peopIe were in there.
It wouId be perfectIy
normaI for a person
to have doubts
about the moraIity
of what we just
asked you to do.
Is that a question, sir?
No, it's not.
Tune in to what I'm
trying to say to you.
Do you know what
a sin-eater is?
That's what we are.
We are the sin-eaters.
It means that we take
the moraI excrement that
we find in this equation
and we bury it down
deep inside of us
so that the rest of
our cause can stay pure.
That is the job.
We are moraIIy indefensibIe
and absoIuteIy necessary.
Do you understand?
WiII that be aII?
(EXPLOSION BOOMS)
Stitch that up.
I'm gonna put you on a pIane
to Yemen in six hours.
I'II be ready.
(LOUD EXPLOSION)
TERRY: I toId you
she'd be coming at us.
Yeah, I need you to
stay caIm, Terry, okay?
They're giving her
a Senate hearing.
How can you not see
that as a probIem?
She knows Bourne,
she knows BIackbriar,
she knows Hirsch.
She's got a handIe
on the whoIe
goddamn operation.
I don't see how
the heII you couId be
so caIm about this!
WeII, what can she say?
What can she say?
What if she gets
up there and she says,
"Treadstone, BIackbriar,
you think that was it?
"You think that Jason Bourne
was the whoIe story?
"Sorry, there's a Iot more
going on here."
What if she teIIs them that
Treadstone was just the tip
of the iceberg?
BYER: Look, you want
to sweat something?
Worry about Outcome,
because we're stiII
not out of the woods.
But as far as
our other programs,
she doesn't know that much.
How do you know that?
Because we're
tapped into everything
she says and does.
What?
Phones, emaiI, cars,
house, Iawyer.
She was cooked the minute
she hitched her wagon
to Jason Bourne.
She aided and abetted
an internationaI fugitive.
She prevented the agency
from shutting down
a rogue operation.
She vioIated every oath
and code of conduct
that matters.
For Christ's sake,
she brought the son of
a bitch back to America.
Now, God knows
what her motives are,
but it's cIear that
protecting this country
is not one of them.
That used to be
caIIed treason.
(MACHINE WHIRRING)
Even the soIution here.
Now, that shouId be
coming up as a constant.
(MACHINE BEEPS)
There you are.
I don't understand
these vaIues. . .
(GASPS)
DR. BENEZARA:
My God, no!
Did you hear that?
Yeah.
WOMAN: What is that?
It's a gun.
No. I. . . No.
Yeah. No, it was gunfire.
No, pIease. No, no, no!
(GUN FIRES)
HeIp!
(POUNDING ON DOOR)
Open the door!
He's shooting us!
(ALARM CHIMING)
DR. TALWAR: Open the door!
He's got a gun !
Open the door!
DR. TALWAR: HeIp!
Oh, my God.
We got to be abIe
to get a card !
We have to be abIe
to get in there!
(WHISPERING) What's
happening? We gotta go
for the back door.
It's Iocked.
He Iocked the back door.
(WHIMPERING)
No, pIease.
He's gonna kiII us aII.
(SHUSHING)
DR. CHANDRA: Don't do this.
Oh, my God.
Move!
He's shooting
everyone in there!
I need a red Iab access card !
Who's got a red
Iab access card?
They're bringing one
down from upstairs.
They're aII in there.
Everyone who has
one is in there.
BiIIy, where are you, man?
I need a red card now!
(DR. BENEZARA GROANS)
Don. . .
What are you doing?
(GUN FIRES)
(GASPS SOFTLY)
(ALL CLAMORING)
Shit, the handIe's off.
(GUN FIRES)
The handIe's off!
(GRUNTS)
Drop it! Stop!
Drop the weapon !
Drop it! Drop the weapon !
(GUN FIRES)
(GASPING)
(COUNTRY MUSIC
PLAYING ON RADIO)
MALE ANCHOR: lnvestigators
are still searching
for some explanation
behind the workplace
murder-suicide
that left another
American community
grieving and shocked.
Police and federal authorities
(KNOCKING ON DOOR)
DITA: The boys need
to see you right away.
Let's get that Foite story
out there right away.
I'II take care of it.
COP: And this area,
back here?
That's aII been
converted to storage.
Because it says on
the bIueprint, and even
on the board, there,
that it's a medicaI
examination suite.
I mean, what kind
of examinations are
we taIking about?
MARTA: There we go.
May l see the hand, please?
Oh, that has heaIed weII.
Any diminished sensation?
Nope.
Are you trying to
put me down, doc?
I'm afraid there's
been a few gaps
in your sampIe
deIiveries, so. . .
Uh-oh.
. . .we need a fuII
work-up this visit.
Another one?
Why? Is it 'cause
I missed a bIood drop?
So, how do you think
it works, doc?
That we can just
caII a timeout?
Everything stops whiIe
you puII your sampIes?
Why don't you
Iie down and reIax?
Yeah.
What do you think
that we do out there?
Okay, that's
enough information.
No, I. . .
WeII, you're just a doctor.
You know we're
on camera.
ReaIIy?
Is that why you make such
an attractive appearance?
Okay, why don't you
count backward from 1 00,
pIease?
(SPEAKING RUSSIAN)
(COUNTING IN RUSSIAN)
(TELEPHONE RINGS)
HeIIo?
Yeah, the gate
shouId be open.
Bear to the Ieft.
It's about haIf-a-miIe up.
Thanks.
Dr. Shearing?
Uh-huh.
Hi, I'm Dr. Connie Dowd.
Hi, how are you?
WeII, thanks.
This is SpeciaI
Agent Larry Hooper.
HeIIo.
PIease. Come in.
DR. DOWD: Thanks for
Ietting us come out.
It's a remarkabIe property.
What a project.
Yeah, I reaIIy don't want
to taIk about the house.
Not unIess
you want to buy it.
Sit, I guess. PIease.
MARTA: Just so you know, okay,
I didn't know anything
about this meeting
untiI an hour ago.
And nobody Iast night
said to make time
or pick a time,
or anything Iike that.
And then, this morning,
I buy a pIane ticket
to see my sister
and suddenIy it's Iike
DEFCON 4 around here.
And that is not
paranoia, okay?
That is pretty much
directIy in my face!
DR. DOWD: Understood.
ShouId we not be
paying attention?
Can you Ieave us
aIone, Larry?
Look.
You've just been
through an extremeIy
traumatic experience.
Yeah. Doctor of what?
What are you?
CIinicaI psychoIogy.
Oh. So, what do you do?
You give grief
counseIing to spies?
You have a very unusuaI
security cIearance, Marta.
You shouId expect
that buying a ticket
to MontreaI without
teIIing anyone wouId
set off some beIIs.
Yeah, I've got some beIIs
of my own going off, okay?
I mean, are you going to be
the person who teIIs me
what the heII
is going on here,
or are you just the next
mystery babysitter?
What do you think
is going on?
What I'm trying
to do is not think.
I just. . . I want
to stop thinking.
Have you discussed
those feeIings with
anyone eIse?
Your sister? Friends?
Are you for reaI?
What about Peter Boyd?
Wow.
Okay.
So, we're into
everything, is that it?
Is anything off-Iimits here?
Have you ever read
your empIoyment
security contract?
Have I read my. . .
If you're asking me
whether I understand
my discIosure restrictions,
yes, I have a PhD
in biochemistry
with postdoctoraI feIIowships
in viroIogy and genetics.
I know how to read !
What I don't understand
is why my coIIeague
has a psychotic episode
and shot everyone in the Iab.
Are you aware of what
we do in there?
Are you?
I mean, how do I know
that you're even cIeared
for this conversation?
Have you discussed
anything to do
with the incident
with anyone other
than the investigators?
Peter Boyd moved
out eight months ago.
But I guess you
aIready know that.
And, no, I haven't
spoken to him.
You stated that you
and Dr. Foite had no
reIationship outside of work.
None.
There was materiaI
in his apartment that
indicates he had
an unusuaI fixation
with you.
Photographs, journaI entries.
They found severaI
articIes of cIothing.
What?
Did you ever rebuff him
in any way?
No.
No, no, I. . .
I aIways thought
he was gay.
Look, no one is suggesting
that you're responsibIe
for what happened.
Oh. Thank you.
Survivors often experience
feeIings of guiIt.
Those feeIings
can be ampIified
by the reaIization
that he Iet you Iive.
That he Iet me Iive?
Have you seen the video?
Do you reaIIy think
that's what it shows?
You are asking aII
the wrong questions!
What shouId I
be asking, Marta?
Has anyone Iooked at
Dr. Foite's bIood work?
Have they?
I mean, that is the onIy
thing that is going to make
any sense, here.
His behavior was. . .
Look, there are
projects at Sterisyn,
defense projects
that couId expIain
why he did what he did.
And peopIe
there are working on
behavioraI design.
It's programmabIe behavior,
neuraI design.
Do you understand
what I'm teIIing you?
I think he was exposed
to something at the Iab.
Found it.
What are you doing?
That's my gun.
What the heII is this?
You're a potentiaI
suicide risk.
No. Wait a minute.
How did you. . .
How did he find that?
Marta. . .
No, no. Okay.
This meeting is now over.
I want you both out
of here, right now!
Marta. . .
No! He has been
snooping around my house!
Marta, I want to
sign off here today!
I want to Iet you
get on that pIane,
but you have got
to heIp us out!
Look, we have got to do
our job here, okay?
We have got to go
through this.
I need to know that
you are caIm and safe
before I Ieave here
and I need to know that you
understand the ruIes before
you get on that pIane.
PIease, just. . .
PIease, sit down
and Iet us get through
our questions.
Okay.
(MARTA SCREAMS)
Jesus! What is this?
What the heII is this?
Ready?
CIose.
What are you doing?
Get off me!
Set?
Get the heII off me now!
Set!
Green !
No!
(GUN FIRES)
(GROANS)
(SCREAMS)
DRIVER: Gene!
A runner in the basement!
Go!
Connie!
On your right.
One. GirI.
(PANTING)
(SCREAMS)
(BOTH GRUNTING)
Find her.
Find her!
(TOOL WHIRRING)
Gene! TaIk to me!
(LOUD WHIRRING)
(WHIRRING STOPS)
Hey.
(GUN CLICKING)
UnIess you reIoaded,
the gun is empty.
(GUN CLICKING)
Look, Iook.
Dr. Shearing, it's me.
I'm not here
to hurt you, okay?
How did you. . .
That was you !
Yes. Shh !
Listen to me.
Do you want to Iive?
Look at me.
Yes.
Good. Let go of this gun.
How is this possibIe?
Let go.
Take this.
Good.
Now, I need you to do
exactIy what I say.
How is this possibIe?
Listen to me.
ExactIy what I say.
Understand?
Yeah.
Good.
(DOOR CLOSES)
AARON: Hey, doc?
I need my watch.
Doc, I need that watch !
Are there chems
in this house?
Program medication.
Are they aII dead?
Yeah, they're dead.
Look at me. Look at me.
Do you have program
medication here?
What?
Chems. Greens, bIues.
Do you have them here?
No, no.
No?
Here? No, no.
Here.
Where, then?
Where do you have them?
Where?
Where do you keep
the chems?
I don't know.
Dr. Shearing,
where are the chems?
I need the chems!
I understand,
but I don't know.
(STUTTERING)
It's not something. . .
We do viroIogy controI.
So, aII of that happens. . .
We don't have medication.
If I had any,
I wouId give it to you.
Okay, Iisten to me.
We have Iess
than eight minutes
to cIear out of here, okay?
Yes.
Good.
Because the next thing
coming through that door
is going to wipe us out.
(RADIO CRACKLES)
Can I get a sitrep, here?
If you can hear me,
pick up, Larry.
(OVER RADIO) Larry, pick up.
AARON: Hey.
Sorry about the tran.
What's our frame-rate, here?
Connie says about 1 0.
Just wrapping up.
TeII her we need
a heads-up. Okay?
Copy that.
Hey.
It's probabIy
better you did this.
(LOUD EXPLOSION)
(SIREN WAILING)
Where are we going?
June. Your name is
June Monroe, say it.
June Monroe.
Say it.
Now pick a pIace you Iived.
The Iast pIace you Iived.
A pIace you know.
Bethesda.
Bethesda, that's
where you Iive.
Anybody asks,
you're June Monroe
from Bethesda.
You Iost your waIIet.
I'm driving you home.
My name is James.
James and June, you got it?
Yeah.
Okay.
Is that your name?
James?
No. What?
You don't know my name?
What do you caII me?
What do you put
on my bIood work?
Five.
Five? The number five?
Do you know how
many times we've met?
Thirteen.
Thirteen exams over
the Iast four years.
And that's what
I get, a number?
Number Five. Okay.
Five of what, then?
How many are we?
Program participants?
That's what you caII us?
There were nine. Then six.
Participants.
How did you find me?
WeII, what do you think?
They're going
to kiII aII of us
and then just
Ieave you guys aIone?
You think your coIIeague
just went crazy?
Is that what you think?
I didn't think anything.
They wound him up
and set him Ioose.
I reaIIy have no idea
what is going on.
What's going on
is they're shutting
the whoIe thing down.
Who is "they"?
I don't know. . .
Who were the peopIe
at the house?
No, no, no, no.
You had your turn, okay?
You've been bIeeding
and scoping and scraping me
since the day we met.
It's my turn, now.
I'm asking the questions,
you got it?
I need program meds, okay?
I need program meds.
Where do you keep
the chems?
I don't have any.
I've aIready toId you.
We don't have them.
BuIIshit.
It's buIIshit.
I don't have any!
So, you don't know anything?
You're just the heIp?
That's why you have
the big house and the
security cIearance, right?
That's why they're
trying so hard to kiII you,
because you
don't know anything.
I know my job,
which is science.
I don't know what you do
when you Ieave the Iab.
None of us do!
For four years!
Look, I want to get out!
WouId you pIease stop the car?
You can't be that naive.
WouId you Iet me out the car?
There's no way
you're that naive!
You want out? Get out.
Go on, get out.
You don't have any chems.
You don't know where
they are.
You don't know anything.
That's fine. Just get out.
But you got a pIan, right?
Yeah, of course you do.
You're a doctor.
You've got this aII
worked out, don't you?
What are you going to do?
Huh? What are
you going to do?
You can't run, not aIone.
You don't know how.
You certainIy can't hide.
Not from peopIe Iike this,
with the resources they have.
You won't make it to sundown.
So, what does that Ieave you?
You can go pubIic, sure.
You can go Ioud.
CaII your sister,
because that worked out
weII for you.
CaII some ex-roommate.
CaII a guy that knows a guy
at The Washington Post.
Put it onIine.
'Cause you know what?
You bIow me off,
that's the onIy
pIay you've got.
But you'd better
ask yourseIf this.
CouId you ever say it
Ioud enough or fast enough
that they'd be too afraid
to finish what
they've started?
Now, I've got a pIan,
and it's just not
that compIicated.
What I'm going to do is
wait for the next person
to show up to kiII you.
Maybe they can heIp me.
So, go for it.
I had no choice.
I had to get out of there.
No, I had to
get out of there!
No, nobody. I have no idea.
You have to understand.
AII the work at Outcome,
aII those tests,
the burn rates,
dosage paneIs,
tissue stress.
I mean, that is us
tuning chemistry.
We don't fabricate anything.
That happens downstream.
Wait. What's that mean,
"downstream"?
It means you need Iive
virus to seed adhesion.
CuItures are
highIy reactive.
You have to process on-site
and we wouId never do it here.
Okay. On-site, where? Where?
Where do we hoId the virus?
Yes!
WeII, we can't
drive there.
Where is it?
ManiIa.
The PhiIippines.
Where do you stand
with your dosage?
I have 300 miIIigrams
of bIues.
It's not even enough
for another day.
I haven't had
a fuII green in 51 hours,
which is strange
because I don't feeI
physicaIIy degraded.
But we'II see.
Wait, wait, wait.
Did you just say you're
stiII taking greens?
What are you taIking about?
You were viraIed off
physicaI medication
Iast year.
What?
Jesus. They viraIed
everyone off greens
eight months ago.
They infected you
with Iive virus,
which means that,
physicaIIy,
you're stabIe.
You don't need
to take greens.
They Iocked it in.
Any physicaI enhancement
is now permanent.
So, you infected me?
When was this?
Is this when I was sick?
The mystery fIu?
That was you?
WeII, it wasn't me.
I didn't do it.
That was you. That was
on purpose, right?
When I aImost died.
I'm sorry,
but it wasn't me.
Why am I stiII taking
green piIIs, then?
I don't know.
I thought you had stopped.
Why am I asking
you anything?
Or to keep us
on a Ieash, right?
Is that it?
To keep a hoId on us?
To keep us dependent?
Who teIIs you
that this is okay?
No one. . . I do. . .
Who says it's okay?
I do research.
I design, I survey.
I don't administer meds.
I don't make poIicy!
No, you just Ioad the gun.
Oh, God.
Look, I was there
for the science.
We were aII there
for science.
And I know you don't care,
but I made a huge sacrifice.
I couIdn't pubIish,
I couIdn't conference.
I couIdn't teII
a singIe person
what it was I did.
But I thought I was
heIping my country,
and I know that's. . .
TeII me you can
viraI off bIues.
Can you viraI off bIues?
TheoreticaIIy, yes.
Yeah.
PiIIs aIIow for
temporary adhesion.
Okay.
To Iock it in,
you need Iive cuIture.
Live virus!
You know how to do that.
Do you know
how to do that?
Yes.
Okay.
Yes, but I toId you,
it's on the other
side of the pIanet.
WeII, guess where
we're going?
WOMAN: Welcome to Washington.
Welcome to Candent
World Headquarters.
We want to make sure
that over the next few days
you have a chance to connect
with the people who have
made Sterisyn Morlanta
the crown jewel
in the Candent
group of companies.
FinaI Phase 3
testing approvaI is
expected this month
for both reQuieI
and SupressoIyn.
Confidence is high that
we're coming in on scheduIe,
and we want to be ready.
We know the market
is eager.
We know, gIobaIIy,
the kind of. . .
What the heII don't
I know about this?
You're directing
that at me?
That was a D-Trac team
we sent in there.
I don't know what
that means.
It means they're
good at what they do.
I was toId that
they were missing.
They don't just
go missing.
What didn't you teII us
about this woman?
Nothing. She is who she is.
There's nothing to teII.
You vetted her up and down.
Then what the heII
are we Iooking at?
INGRAM: She has
a registered gun.
TURSO: They knew that
going in.
She's got buiIding permits.
Propane, weIding tanks.
A stray buIIet?
You want to keep guessing?
We've got to get in there.
I've got a dozen peopIe
waiting on the perimeter.
We don't controI the site?
DITA: Not yet.
Getting the picture now?
Okay, stop!
I can't run this from here.
I need a crisis suite.
I need integrated
grids and comms.
I need aII of it.
NSA, or Pentagon,
or Liberty Crossing.
I don't care, just
get me something now.
Pack up your codes
and your drives,
and whatever eIse
you're going to need.
We're going to move
and we're going to stay there.
Dita, how am I putting
a net over that house?
There's IocaIs aII over it.
We go with germs.
She took sampIes from work.
Pathogens, viruses.
It's nationaI security.
Good, okay,
I Iike that, it pIays.
Now, get it out there,
get it out there.
Come on, Iet's go, Iet's go.
Everybody find
another gear, okay?
Because I want to
be out of here in 20.
MARTA: So, Iet's say
you want to change
the human body.
You want to fix a mistake.
You want to repair something,
improve something.
WeII, if you're going
to reprogram human
genetic materiaI,
you need a deIivery
system, and nothing
works better than virus.
It's Iike a suitcase.
You pack in genetic mutation,
infect the body
and the vector unIoads
into the target ceIIs.
But getting it
where you want it,
how you want it,
is the nightmare.
UnIess you have a map.
There was this
terribIe accident
at Fort Detrick in 1 985.
Five researchers dropped
dead in the Iab, and it
was such a catastrophe
that they brought in
Dan HiIIcott
from Stanford
to assess the damage.
He got in there
and he reaIized that,
underneath it aII,
was this
incredibIe breakthrough
in viraI-receptor mapping.
He had a map.
You've had some
very minor aIterations
made to two different
chromosomes.
The green side,
the physicaI side,
is nothing more
than a 1 .5 percent rise
in your mitochondriaI
protein uptake.
But with 1 .5 percent,
you see this
immediate increase
in ceIIuIar tempo,
muscIe efficiency,
oxygenation. . .
And the bIue side?
InteIIigence, obviousIy,
but it's more than that.
It's neuraI regeneration
and eIasticity.
Sensory function.
Pain suppression.
It's the most
exciting deveIopment
in genomic targeting
in the history
of the science.
My God.
Hey, how do I get
monitor 71 up on
the big screen?
Coming up.
They found a body.
They're pretty sure
it's a woman, and it's
not Marta Shearing.
They found dog tags.
They think she was shot.
Hey.
Marta, I. . .
You can't
caII anyone.
There are peopIe
that care about you
that think you're dead.
And there's nothing
you can do about it.
Anyone you contact
becomes a target.
So, you need to put aside
any normaI emotionaI
response that you have.
The onIy edge we've
got right now is they
think we're both gone.
AII right?
AII right.
So,
you're going to want
to go through this.
You know, just
be famiIiar with it.
June Monroe.
Who is June Monroe?
You are.
Do you know her?
Not anymore.
Why do you have
to stay enhanced?
Why is it so
important to you?
Come here.
What is this?
This was me.
Was.
My army recruiter
was Iooking
to make his quota.
He added 1 2 points
to my IQ.
TweIve points to make
the minimum.
You ever seen a cognitive
degrade, Marta?
Sensory withdrawaI?
You ever do that?
PuII someone's bIues
and watch them
drop off their meds?
No.
Because they paint
a pretty graphic
picture in training.
HeII of a Iong way to faII.
If I can't
keep it together,
we won't make it.
They bit.
Who?
Washington Post.
We just fIagged
an emaiI.
They're going with
the story about
the possibIe theft
of the dangerous
materiaIs from the Iab.
Wow, they took it.
They aIready fIagged
a DWI conviction.
That's convenient.
They found another body.
One of ours.
They're picking
up sheII casings
aII over the pIace.
I don't think your
doctor's in there.
(WINDING FLASH MECHANISM)
(SHUTTER CLICKS)
Boarding pass
and ID, pIease.
Thank you.
Boarding pass
and ID, pIease.
(CELL PHONE RINGS)
Where are you?
AARON: l'm right behind you.
Don't turn around.
You're going to
stay right here
untiI it's time
to board, okay?
You're doing great.
You see that corridor
on your right?
You're gonna want
to find somebody
who's walking that way
and just tag along.
Keep moving,
keep your head down,
and I'II see you
on the pIane.
Aaron?
HeIIo?
The traiI is
definitive and fresh.
The canine team
tracked her from her house
through this wooded area,
ending here, at this
IittIe parking Iot.
Either she had
a car waiting for her,
or somebody picked her up.
There are security
cameras on the street,
but there's nothing back here.
There's got to be
sateIIite footage.
MaryIand's not exactIy
a high-vaIue U.S. target.
There'II be pIenty
of weather imaging,
but we're gonna have
to swing a IittIe wider
to find something reaI-time
that's enhanceabIe.
We're draining some
foreign pIatforms.
We need about an hour.
Come on,
she's not puIIing
this off on her own.
Who the heII
is heIping her?
MALE ANCHOR: We'll find out
more in the next hour,
while we are
currently in court.
Now back to Jenn.
JENN: The FBl this morning
confirmed reports that
Dr. Albert Hirsch
died of heart failure
in a Washington, D.C. hotel.
Dr. Hirsch had been expected
to testify yesterday
before a Senate
lntelligence committee.
That select committee
is investigating links
between a troubled ClA program
known as Treadstone
and this man, Jason Bourne.
Police and federal officials
are searching for Bourne
in connection
with recent shootings
in New York and in London.
Dr. Hirsch had been
cooperating with
the Justice Department
and was in protective custody
at the time of the incident.
A committee spokesman
told reporters last night
that the hearings will
be postponed temporarily
as they evaluate
the loss of Doctor...
FLIGHT ATTENDANT: Hi, foIks.
Just going to remind you
to keep the aisIes cIear
for any baggage
during takeoff and Ianding.
Excuse me.
Thank you.
Pardon me, sir.
Sir, do you need
heIp finding your seat?
Sir?
No, I got it.
You see those two shadows?
One of them is her.
That's the parking Iot.
One of them stops.
Here comes the car.
Where is this from?
DITA: It's a Canadian
forestry sateIIite.
INGRAM: Here comes
the other one into the car,
and there they go.
Where?
DITA: We Iose them east.
Our window drops out
about two miIes up the road.
But we've got the siIhouette.
We've got
surveiIIance footage,
racked and ready to go.
We're going to spIit teams,
find this car and
Iink up a traiI.
With a 1 7-hour head start?
Where the heII can she go?
MAN 1 : We're Iooking for
a Buick LeSabre 2002.
I've got an
NIA/HomeIand warrant,
that's why.
MAN 2: WeII, you give us
what you have. . .
MAN 3: Two passengers.
It's an '02 burgundy
LeSabre starting west
from Lisbon, MaryIand.
ToIIs, exits,
service stations.
Give me every
camera you've got.
I'm seeing
an FBI camera bin
on my Iist here.
No, no. Traffic onIy.
West, Lisbon. L-I-S-B-O-N.
Yes, we want aII of that
and the toII cams.
We want everything.
We'II take them aII.
Whatever hits you have,
send them on.
We wiII work on
sorting them out.
DITA: Wilmington, Delaware.
This is our car, the LeSabre.
We see it coming
into the structure.
It goes under,
comes back around,
and it parks here.
But it doesn't come out.
This is inside.
It's four minutes
after arrivaI.
It's her.
Do we know
what she's doing?
She was having her
passport picture taken.
DITA: Logan, Hartford,
LaGuardia, Kennedy,
PhiIIy, Newark,
DuIIes, Reagan.
We start with
yesterday morning,
that is our wedge.
We cIear that,
and then we move
up the cIock.
She wants to know
if you want Hartford,
because she can get it.
BIue coat, second row.
She's got a red bag.
Which one? I have four.
AII right, I have
TSA Authorization
1 , 6, 9 and 1 2.
Airports given,
aII departures.
Yes, the internationaI
terminaI first.
We're aImost there.
DITA: So, check out
the newsstand.
There.
BYER: I don't know.
Logan has a face
we need to Iook at,
but there's kids.
BYER: Hang on, hang on,
hang on. Hang on.
Stop.
Where is this?
Kennedy.
Okay.
I've never
been here at night.
I don't know the ruIes.
There are no ruIes, okay?
We beIong here.
Come on.
Hey, how are you?
Good evening.
Dr. Shearing and I are here
to open up the Iab, pIease.
Sir?
What's aII this?
Hi, how are you?
Dr. Shearing !
Dr. Shearing.
Hey, it's me, Joseph.
Joseph !
HeIIo, how are you?
I'm good, I'm good.
WeIcome back.
Thanks.
I'm sorry.
I just don't have you
on my Iist arriving.
That's because we had
to change our scheduIe.
Yeah, we took
an earIier fIight.
Joseph,
I'm Dr. Brundage, by the way.
It's nice to meet you.
PIeased to meet you, too,
but Dr. PumaIoy is not here,
he went to Singapore.
He just Ieft yesterday.
The girIs have gone home.
No one toId me anything.
Right. WeII, I understand.
WeII, Iook, we're going
to be here aII week,
and we have
a Iot of work to do,
so we need to get
in there tonight
and get things started, okay?
Yeah, of course,
it's just that. . .
You can caII
Dr. PumaIoy if you want.
I just don't want to
put you on the spot.
No, we don't
have to do that.
Okay, great.
It's just the two of you?
Yeah.
Yes, correct.
Correct.
Yes, I wiII hoId.
Get it up there.
Put that up on
the big screen.
Yes, I'm here.
Good. Where?
I need an immediate upIoad
on that passenger manifest.
I know. Here she is,
I'm putting her back on.
ManiIa. She took
American 1 67 to ManiIa.
She Ianded 45 minutes ago.
Aaron.
Are you okay?
BYER: There's 243 people
on that plane.
We're going to scope
every one of them right now.
So, pick a face that
you Iike, puII it down,
and deseIect it if
you've cIeared it.
If there is anything
that smeIIs wrong to you,
if there's
a hair out of pIace
that you don't Iike,
you do not cIear it.
You fIag it and you
send it over to Dita
and we'II check it out.
We have to be
working off the same grid.
That's HomeIand 9.5.
If you don't
puII that access,
raise your hand,
CoIoneI Hardy's
going to come over
and sort you out.
So, this is it, huh?
Yeah.
Okay.
What the heII
are we into, Terry?
I don't know.
It's your shop.
What is going on over there?
What did I say?
I don't know.
WeII, how many trips
has she made over there?
Five, six, I don't know.
Why the PhiIippines?
Hey, hey, hey!
INGRAM: Seat 1 3-B.
KarI D. Brundage, 1 3-B.
I need support staff
to cIear the room.
Stand up and waIk, now.
Jack, Cathy, move!
Let's go.
TURSO: Who the hell is he?
BYER: He's an Outcome agent.
That's Outcome 5.
TERRY: They're not dead?
I thought they were dead !
BYER: Yeah, he's
supposed to be dead.
TURSO: Then what's
he doing there?
BYER: l don't know.
VENDEL: He's Iooking for meds.
TURSO: What?
That's where
the chems come from.
What eIse wouId he be doing?
INGRAM: She's got
to be helping him.
TURSO: But how?
How is that possible?
BYER: I don't know how.
I don't care.
He's aIive, they're there.
"How" doesn't
reaIIy matter, does it?
The onIy mission
we've got now is to
drop a bag over this.
Are the drugs
he's Iooking for
there, or not?
Jesus, I don't. . . Terry?
No. No, there's
nothing there.
We haven't made
a run in 1 6 weeks.
Besides, we wouIdn't
store the pills
there, anyway.
lt's basically a kitchen.
We tweak the recipe
and we bake up
a batch when we need it.
Then what the heII
are they doing?
The stems are there.
She's going to try
to viraI him out.
Thank you.
Mack.
Yeah?
PIant office,
Mackie speaking.
TERRY: Mr. Mackie,
this is Terrance Ward.
l'm the Senior Vice-President
for Candent Precision Metrics.
l'm calling from Maryland.
Yes, sir.
We have a potentiaI
security incident.
I just posted
two photographs on
the company network.
I need to know if either
of these two peopIe
have tried to enter. . .
Yeah, we're on it.
Excuse me?
Yeah, we're on the case.
We're just here now trying
to figure out who to caII.
Our gatehouse just
passed in two doctors.
I think one of them
might be that woman
from your
shoot-out over there.
Well, where are they now?
We keep aII of our
cIient Iabs downstairs,
so we're assuming they've
gone into the basement.
I just sent a coupIe of boys
down to check it out.
No, no. No, no,
withdraw your team.
Lock the Iab and
keep them down there.
Do not try to take him.
(DOOR OPENS)
MARTA: HeIIo?
GUARD: Hey, how you doing?
Can I heIp you?
Are you aIone down here?
Aaron?
Hey, guys.
You can't be down here.
Do you have cIearance
for this IeveI?
Nobody's supposed
to be down here.
I'm supposed
I'm Dr. Shearing.
We're in the middIe
of a sampIing audit.
It is not safe for
you guys to be here.
Let's straighten
this out upstairs.
Don't touch that.
Pack it up, Iet's go.
Look, nobody touch anything.
Come on, just foIIow us.
I'm not going to sit
here and argue with you.
I'm going to caII your boss
and we're gonna figure it out.
Watch her.
Hey, hoId on a second.
(GRUNTS)
I'm going to get my bag.
We got to go.
Okay.
Wait. This way.
I don't know where this goes.
Just open it.
(DOOR BUZZES)
Step back.
Lock it down.
Hey! You ! You ! With me!
Come on, come on, come on.
Is that Iocked?
Yes, sir.
No one in, no one out.
Do you understand?
Hey, what happened
to those three guys
you sent downstairs?
Shit.
Come with me.
You stay there, okay?
Stay there.
We beIong here.
Coming through.
(GAS HISSING)
(WORKERS SCREAMING)
(MACHINERY POWERING DOWN)
(ALARM RINGING)
MACKIE: You, go and get
everyone eIse. TeII them
to go around the front.
Go through the eastern doors,
move around the front.
MACKIE: Move! Move, peopIe!
Who have you
got on this radio?
Why is no one responding?
Is that gate shut?
Excuse me.
Move, move, move!
Hey! I need that gate shut!
Hey, you ! Listen,
go down to the main gate.
Do you understand?
No one in, no one out.
Hey, what are you doing?
Just get down
to the main gate
with everyone eIse.
(GRUNTS)
AII right, get back!
Stay back!
Give him some room.
AII right, give me some room.
Give me some room, pIease.
He's going to need a doctor.
Security. Security!
Over here, pIease.
Over here.
Sir, can you hear me? Sir!
He can't get far.
If he didn't viraI out,
he's going to run out
of brain.
And, if he did,
then he's going to be
too sick to move.
So, we just have
to find him fast
and kiII him,
once and for aII.
Can we taIk about LARX?
LARX?
LARX-3 is in Bangkok.
It's a two-hour fIight.
Wait a minute.
Just hang on, here.
I thought that
was just a proposaI.
Get him out there.
DITA: LARX is
a beta-2 stem program.
Amped mission fidelity,
minimized empathy.
VENDEL: lt's Treadstone
without the inconsistency,
Outcome without
the emotional noise.
TERRY: lt's looking
very strong for us.
We have never seen
evaIuations Iike this.
This went from something
I don't know about
to something on
the drawing board,
and now you're teIIing me
it's up and running?
It's up and running.
Consider yourseIf informed.
(PANTING)
(COUGHING)
DR. HILLCOTT:
Are you comfortable?
AARON: Yes, sir.
You don't
look comfortable.
No, sir.
What's your name?
Kenneth James.
FuII name, Kenneth.
Kenneth. . . James. . .
AARON: Kitsom.
They have a room.
Can you waIk?
Yeah?
Yeah. Yeah. I think so.
DR. HILLCOTT: Where are
you from, Kenneth?
AARON: When?
Before you enlisted.
Berwin.
ls that a town?
Berwin... lt's a state home.
What state?
ln Reno.
ls this a test?
Yes, it is.
lf l pass, can l stay here?
Do you want to stay?
Yes, sir.
That's good to know.
(SHUSHING)
Okay. Okay.
(AARON GROANS)
Okay, just Iie stiII.
Aaron, you have. . . Aaron. . .
What?
There's $40,000 in
the Iining of my jacket.
In this bag,
there are passports.
Two bIanks and three ghosts,
there's that guy's watch.
There are other things, okay?
You take it.
Look at me.
You can make it.
You're a warrior.
Okay? Stay smaII.
No airports.
Just bIend in
Iike you know, okay?
(SHUSHING)
You've done enough for me.
No, I. . .
PIease go.
You've done enough for me.
Everything's in the car.
(SIREN WAILING)
(MAN SPEAKING TAGALOG
OVER RADIO)
AARON: ls this a test?
DR. HILLCOTT: Yes, it is.
lf l pass, can l stay here?
Do you want to stay?
ParacetamoI, 500 miIIigrams.
Four times a day.
(SPEAKING TAGALOG)
For free. This is free.
Okay, good.
I'II be right back.
(SPEAKING TAGALOG)
Aaron, run !
(POLICE OFFICERS SHOUTING)
"Where are you?"
"Was that the signaI?"
They're asking
for confirmation.
"You went too soon."
No. . . "We went too soon."
Come on.
(SNIFFS)
(SPEAKING TAGALOG)
(BLOWING WHISTLES)
(GRUNTING)
(PANTING)
(SPEAKING TAGALOG)
It's okay.
(SHOUTING IN TAGALOG)
(GRUNTS)
(SHOUTING)
PoIice! PoIice!
(SHOUTING IN TAGALOG)
Get down !
(GUN FIRES)
(GRUNTS)
Are you okay?
Yeah.
Good. Come on.
(SIRENS WAILING)
(SCREAMS)
Get down, get down.
CIimb over.
Go. Get over,
get over, get over.
Get over. Hang on tight.
Go, go!
You ready? Let go!
(SIREN WAILING)
Okay. Take this.
Just keep waIking,
don't Iook back. Go, go.
(ENGINE REVVING)
(SHOUTING)
Hey, hey. Get on.
You ever ridden before?
No.
Take this.
PoIice, poIice!
Hang on tight and
foIIow me, okay?
Stay with me.
He's got a gun !
Keep your head down.
It's not a cop.
(GASPS)
(PEOPLE SCREAMING)
Aaron !
(GRUNTS)
(SIRENS WAILING)
(YELLS)
(TRUCK HONKING)
(GRUNTS)
(PEOPLE SCREAMING)
You've been shot.
It's aII right.
PuII over!
PuII over.
We just have to
get to the water.
DITA: Can you
check that for me?
VENDEL: How Iong is
that going to take?
Come on.
DITA: We'II get
back to you.
Anything?
No.
(SIGHS)
VENDEL: The cops are out.
They Iost the traiI.
Aaron !
Aaron ! Aaron ! Aaron ! Aaron !
(GROANS)
Are you okay?
Yeah?
Yeah.
Can you heIp us?
PIease.
ShouId be up there now.
He said it's the room
where they spent the night.
PAULSEN: Well, we had
a problem with Treadstone
six years ago.
The BIackbriar program,
detaiIed in
the operations report
you have before you,
was activated
soIeIy to capture
a Treadstone operative
gone rogue.
(REPORTERS CLAMORING)
WOMAN: Pam, what are
you going to do?
We have nothing for you now.
I don't know
PameIa Landy's reasons
for criminaIIy
assisting an enemy
of the United States.
But the fact is, she Iacked
the operationaI cIearance
to access,
much Iess interpret,
the information you have
in the cIassified
fiIe before you.
MAN: Pam, there's a rumor that
you're going to be indicted,
is it true?
Mike, can you comment?
WOMAN: Have you been
subpoenaed?
ATTORNEY: We're here
voIuntariIy. We came
for a meeting.
WOMAN: Have you had any
contact with Jason Bourne?
MAN: Did you receive
a target Ietter or not?
Are we going to
see you tomorrow?
VOSEN: l just thank God
that there were hands
steady enough
to make sure that
the documents she tried
to shop to the press
were contained
before they couId
do any more harm
than they aIready have.
WOMAN: Are you stiII scheduIed
to appear at the House
InteIIigence Committee?
Yes, I am. Look, anything eIse
is going to have to come from
my attorneys, okay?
MAN: Do you regret your
earIier statement?
I regret a Iot of things.
I'm not sure that
one is on the Iist.
Thank you, guys.
(SPEAKS TAGALOG)
Hey.
Are we Iost?
No.
Just Iooking at our options.
I was kind of hoping
we were Iost.