Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org
Hi. I've got an appointment
with Mr. Ullman.
My name is Jack Torrance.
His office is the first door
on the left.
Thank you.
- Mr. Ullman?
- Yeah?
I'm Jack Torrance.
Come on in, Jack.
- Very nice to meet you.
- Nice to meet you.
This is my secretary, Susie.
- Susie, how do you do?
- Any trouble finding us?
No problem at all.
Made the trip in three and a half hours.
That's very good time.
Sit down a minute, Jack.
Just make yourself at home.
Like some coffee?
If you're having some,
I wouldn't mind. Thanks.
- Susie.
- Sure.
And ask Bill Watson to join us.
Yes, I will.
Mom?
Yeah?
Do you really wanna go and live
in that hotel for the winter?
Sure I do.
It'll be lots of fun.
Yeah. I guess so.
Anyway, there's hardly anybody
to play with around here.
Yeah, I know. It always takes
a little time to make new friends.
Yeah, I guess so.
What about Tony?
He's looking forward
to the hotel, I bet.
No, I ain't, Mrs. Torrance.
Now, come on, Tony.
Don't be silly.
I don't wanna go there.
How come you don't wanna go?
I just don't.
Did they give you
any idea in Denver...
about what the job entalls?
Only in a very general way.
The winters can be
fantastically cruel.
The basic idea is to cope
with the very costly damage...
and depreciation
which can occur.
This consists mainly
of running the boller...
heating different parts of the
hotel on a daily rotating basis...
repairing damage as it occurs...
and doing repairs so the
elements can't get a foothold.
That sounds fine to me.
Physically, it's not
a very demanding job.
The only thing that can get a bit
trying here during the winter...
is a tremendous sense
of isolation.
That just happens to be
exactly what I'm looking for.
I'm outllning a new writing project.
Five months of peace
is just what I want.
That's very good, Jack.
Because, for some people...
solitude...
and isolation...
can, of itself, become a problem.
Not for me.
How about your wife and son?
Do you think they'll take to it?
They'll love it.
Great.
Before I turn you over to Bill...
there's one other thing I think
we should talk about.
Not to sound melodramatic...
but it's been known to
give a few people...
second thoughts about the job.
I'm intrigued.
I don't suppose they
said anything in Denver...
about the tragedy we had up here
during the winter of 1970.
I don't belleve they did.
My predecessor in this job...
hired a man named Charles Grady
as the winter caretaker.
He came up with his wife and
two llttle girls of about 8 and 10.
He had a good employment record,
good references.
And from what I've been told,
he seemed...
like a completely
normal individual.
But at some point
during the winter...
he must have suffered some kind
of a complete mental breakdown.
He ran amuck...
and killed his family
with an ax.
Stacked them neatly in a room
in the west wing, and then...
he put both barrels
of his shotgun in his mouth.
The pollce thought...
that it was what the old- timers
used to call cabin fever.
A kind of claustrophobic reaction
which can occur...
when people are shut in together
over long periods of time.
That is...
quite a story.
Yeah, it is.
It's still hard for me to belleve
it actually happened here.
But it did.
I think you can appreciate
why I wanted to tell you about it.
I certainly can.
I also understand
why your people in Denver...
left it for you to tell me.
Obviously, some people
can be put off...
from staying in a place where
something like that happened.
You can rest assured that's not
gonna happen with me.
And as far as my wife
is concerned...
I'm sure she'll be absolutely
fascinated when I tell her.
She's a confirmed ghost story...
and horror- film addict.
Tony, do you think
Dad'll get the job?
He already did.
He's gonna phone Wendy up
in a few minutes to tell her.
- Hi, babe.
- Hi, hon. How's it going?
Great. I'm at the hotel and
I still have a lot to go through.
I don't think I can get home
before 9 or 10.
Sounds like you got the job.
Right. It's a beautiful place.
You and Danny are gonna love it.
Tony, why don't you wanna go
to the hotel'
I don't know.
You do too know.
Now come on, tell me.
I don't want to.
Please.
No.
Now, Tony, tell me.
(dc)
Boy, we must really be high up.
The air feels so different.
- Dad?
- Yes.
I'm hungry.
Well, you should've
eaten your breakfast.
We'll get you something
as soon as we get to the hotel.
Okay, Mom.
Wasn't it around here that
the Donner party got snowbound?
I think that was farther west,
in the Sierras.
What was the Donner party?
They were a party of settlers
in covered- wagon times.
They got snowbound one winter
in the mountains.
They had to resort to cannibalism
in order to stay allve.
You mean they ate each other up?
They had to in order to survive.
Jack.
Don't worry, Mom.
I know all about cannibalism.
I saw it on TV.
See, it's okay.
He saw it on the television.
- What time does the plane leave?
- 8:30.
That gives us plenty of time
to go over everything.
- Goodbye, Mr. Ullman.
- Bye.
Good morning. I hope you
haven't been waiting too long.
No problem. We had time
to grab a bite to eat.
Good. Glad you made it
before they shut down the kitchen.
Is your famlly
having a look around?
No, my son's
discovered the games room.
- Has your Iuggage been brought in?
- Right there.
In view of all we have
to cover today...
I suggest we have a quick look
at your apartment and get started.
Have the Torrances? things
brought to their apartment.
- Fine.
- I'd better collect my famlly first.
This is our Colorado Lounge.
It's beautiful.
My God!
This place is fantastic,
isn't it, hon?
It sure is.
(dc)
This is the staff wing
of the hotel.
None of the other bedrooms
are heated during the winter.
- Goodbye, Mr. Ullman.
- Goodbye, girls.
And here are your quarters.
Living room, bedroom, bathroom.
And a small bedroom for your son.
Perfect for a child.
(dc)
- Yeah.
- Yes.
When was the Overlook bullt?
Construction started in 1907.
It was finished in 1909.
The site's supposed to be
on an Indian burial ground.
They actually had to repel...
a few lndian attacks as they
were building it.
That's our Snowcat.
Can you both drive a car?
- Yes.
- Yeah.
That's fine. Basically the Snowcat
operates very much like a car.
Won't take long
to get the hang of it.
This is the kitchen, huh?
Yeah, this is it.
How do you like it, Danny?
Is it big enough for you?
Yeah. It's the biggest place I ever seen.
Yeah, this whole place
is such an enormous maze.
I feel like I'll have to leave a trall of
breadcrumbs every time I come in.
Don't let it get you down.
It's big, but it still ain't
nothing but a kitchen.
A lot of this stuff
you'll never have to touch.
I wouldn't know
what to do with it if I did.
One thing for sure, you don't
have to worry about food.
You folks could eat here for a year
and never have the same menu twice.
Now, right here is
our walk- in freezer.
This is where we keep
all of our meat.
You got 15 rib roasts...
30 ten- pound bags of hamburger.
We got 12 turkeys,
about 40 chickens...
50 sirloin steaks,
two dozen of pork roast...
and 20 legs of lamb.
Do you like lamb, Doc?
No.
You don't?
What's your favorite food, then?
French fries and ketchup.
I think we can
manage that too, Doc.
Come along, now.
Watch your step.
How?d you know we call him Doc?
- Beg your pardon?
- Doc. You called Danny "Doc" twice.
- I did?
- Yeah.
We call him Doc sometimes,
like in the Bugs Bunny cartoons.
But how did you know?
I guess I probabIy
heard you call him that.
It's possible.
But I honestly don't remember...
calling him that
since we've been with you.
Anyway, he looks
like a Doc, doesn't he?
What's up, Doc?
Now, this is the storeroom.
In here is where we keep...
all the dried goods
and the canned goods.
We got canned fruits
and vegetables...
canned fish and meats,
hot and cold cereals.
Post Toasties, Corn Flakes,
Sugar Puffs...
Rice Krispies, oatmeal,
Wheatena and Cream of Wheat.
You got a dozen jugs
of black molasses.
We got 60 boxes of dried milk...
How'd you like some ice cream, Doc?
Sociables, finger rolls...
and 7 kinds of what- have- you.
Now, we've got dried peaches,
dried apricots...
dried raisins and dried prunes.
You know, you gotta keep regular
if you wanna be happy.
- Hi.
- How?re you getting on?
- Just fine.
Can we borrow Mrs. Torrance?
We're on our way to the basement.
I promise we won't
keep her very long.
No problem, Mr. Ullman. I was just
getting to the ice cream.
You like ice cream, Doc?
- Yeah.
- I thought you did.
You folks mind if I give Danny
some ice cream while we wait?
- Not at all.
- We don't mind.
- Good.
- Sound good to you, Doc?
- Yeah.
- Okay, you behave yourself.
- What kind of ice cream do you like?
- Chocolate.
Chocolate it shall be.
Come on, son.
It's amazing, all this activity today.
The guests and some staff
left yesterday, but the...
last day's always hectic.
Everybody wants to be on their way
as earIy as possible.
By 5:00 tonight, you'll never
know anybody was ever here.
- Just like a ghost ship, huh?
- Yes.
Do you know how I knew
your name was Doc?
You know what I'm
talking about, don't you?
I can remember when I was
a little boy...
my grandmother and I
could hold conversations...
entirely without ever
opening our mouths.
She called it "shining."
And for a long time I thought
it was just the two of us...
that had "the shine" to us.
Just like you probably thought
you was the only one.
But there are other folks...
though mostly they don't
know it, or don't belleve it.
How long have you
been able to do it?
Why don't you wanna talk about it?
I'm not supposed to.
Who says you ain't supposed to?
Tony.
Who's Tony?
Tony's the llttle boy
that llves in my mouth.
Is Tony the one that...
tells you things?
Yes.
How does he tell you things?
It's like I go to sleep,
and he shows me things.
But when I wake up,
I can't remember everything.
Does your mom and dad
know about Tony?
Yes.
Do they know he tells you things?
No. Tony told me never to tell them.
Has Tony ever told you
anything about this place?
About the Overlook Hotel'
I don't know.
Now think real hard, Doc. Think.
(dc)
Is there something bad here?
You know, Doc,
when something happens...
it can leave a trace of itself behind.
Say, like...
if someone burns toast.
Maybe things that happen
leave other kind of traces behind.
Not things that anyone can notice.
But things that people who shine
can see.
Just like they can see things
that haven't happened yet...
sometimes they can see things
that happened a long time ago.
I think a lot of things
happened right here...
in this particular hotel over the years.
And not all of them was good.
What about room 237?
Room 237?
You're scared of room 237, ain't you?
No, I ain't.
Mr. Hallorann, what is in room 237?
Nothing.
There ain't nothing in room 237.
But you ain't got no business
going in there anyway.
So stay out.
You understand? Stay out!
Good morning, hon.
Your breakfast is ready.
What time is it?
It's about 11:30.
11:30? Jesus.
I guess we've been
staying up too late.
I know it.
I made them just the way
you like them, sunny- side up.
Nice.
It's really pretty outside.
How about taking me for a walk
after you finish your breakfast?
I suppose I ought to try
to do some writing first.
Any ideas yet?
Lots of ideas.
No good ones.
Well, something'll come.
It's just a matter of settling into
the habit of writing every day.
Yeah. That's all it is.
(dc)
- All right.
- And you?re gonna lose.
And I'm gonna get you.
You'd better run fast!
Look out!
I'm coming in close.
Loser has to keep America clean.
Keep America clean.
Danny, you win.
Let's take the rest of this walking.
Okay.
Give me your hand.
- Isn't it beautiful?
- Yeah.
Dead end.
We made it.
- Isn't it beautiful?
- Yeah.
- It's so pretty.
I didn't think it was
gonna be this big. Did you?
No.
Hi, hon.
How's it going?
Fine.
Get a lot written today?
Yes.
Hey, the weather forecast
said it's gonna snow tonight.
What do you want me to do about it?
Come on, hon.
Don't be so grouchy.
I'm not...
being grouchy.
I just wanna finish my work.
Okay. I understand.
I'll come back later
with a couple of sandwiches.
Maybe you'll let me read something then.
Wendy...
let me explain something to you.
When you come in and interrupt,
you're breaking my concentration.
You're distracting me...
and it will then take me time
to get back to where I was.
Understand?
- Yeah.
- Fine.
We're gonna make a new rule:
Whenever I'm in here...
and you hear me typing...
or whatever the fuck
you hear me doing in here...
when I'm in here,
that means I am working.
That means don't come in.
Now, do you think you can handle that?
Yeah.
Fine.
Why don't you start right now
and get the fuck out of here?
Okay.
Missed!
Don't have!
No fair anymore.
I knew it.
This is KDK 12 caillng KDK 1.
KDK 12 to KDK 1.
This is KDK 1.
We're receiving you. Over.
Hi, this is Wendy Torrance
at the Overlook Hotel.
Hi, how are you folks
getting on up there? Over.
We're just fine.
But our telephones aren't doing too well.
Are the llnes down, by any chance?
Over.
Yes, quite a few of them are down
due to the storm. Over.
Any chance of them
being repaired soon? Over.
I wouldn't like to say.
Most winters they stay that way
until spring. Over.
Boy, this storm is really something,
isn't it? Over.
Yes. It's one of the worst
we've had for years.
Is there anything else we can
do for you, Mrs. Torrance? Over.
I suppose not. Over.
If you folks have any problems
up there, just give us a call.
And, Mrs. Torrance?
It might be a good idea if you
leave your radio on all the time. Over.
Okay. We'll do that.
It was real nice talking to you.
Bye. Over and out.
Hello, Danny.
Come and play with us.
Come and play with us, Danny.
Forever...
and ever...
and ever.
Tony...
I'm scared.
Remember what Mr. Hallorann said.
It's just like pictures in a book,
Danny.
It isn't real.
Can I go to my room
and get my fire engine?
Come here for a minute first.
How's it going, Doc?
Okay.
Having a good time?
Yes, Dad.
Good.
I want you to have a good time.
I am, Dad.
- Dad?
- Yes?
Do you feel bad?
No.
I'm just a llttle bit tired.
Then why don't you go to sleep?
I can't.
I got too much to do.
Dad?
Yes?
Do you like this hotel'
Yeah. I do.
I love it.
Don't you?
I guess so.
Good.
I want you to like it here.
I wish we could stay here forever...
and ever...
and ever.
Dad?
What?
You would never hurt Mommy or me,
would you?
What do you mean?
Did your mother ever say that to you?
That I would hurt you?
No, Dad.
You sure?
Yes, Dad.
I love you, Danny.
I love you more than anything else...
in the whole worId...
and I would never do anything
to hurt you.
Never.
You know that, don't you?
Yes, Dad.
Good.
Mom?
Mom, are you in there?
Jack!
What happened?
Honey...
what's wrong?
I had the most...
terrible nightmare I ever had.
- It was the most horrible dream.
- It's okay, it's okay now.
Really.
I dreamed that I...
That I killed you and Danny.
But I didn't just kill you.
I cut you up into llttle pieces.
My God.
I must be losing my mind.
Everything's gonna be all right.
Come on. Let's get up off the floor.
It's okay. There. Now, sit up.
It's okay.
Danny!
Everything's okay!
Just go play in your room for a while.
Your dad's just got a headache.
Danny, mind what I say.
Go play in your room.
Honey, let me just go get him
out of here.
I'll be right back.
Why don't you mind me?
Oh, my God.
What happened to your neck?
You did this to him...
didn't you?!
You son of a bitch!
You did this to him!
Didn't you?!
How could you?!
God! I?d give anything for a drink.
I?d give my goddamn soul...
for just a glass of beer.
Hi, Lloyd.
A llttle slow tonight, isn't it?
Yes it is, Mr. Torrance.
What'll it be?
I'm awfully glad
you asked me that, Lloyd...
because I just happen to have
two twenties...
and two tens
right here in my wallet.
I was afraid they were
gonna be there until next April.
So here's what:
You slip me a bottle of bourbon...
a llttle glass and some ice.
You can do that, can't you, Lloyd?
You're not too busy, are you?
No, sir. I'm not busy at all.
Good man.
You set them up...
and I'll knock them back,
one by one.
White man's burden, Lloyd, my man.
White man's burden.
Say, Lloyd...
it seems I'm temporarlly light.
How's my credit in this joint, anyway?
Your credit's fine, Mr. Torrance.
That's swell.
I like you, Lloyd.
I always liked you.
You were always the best of them.
Best goddamn bartender...
from Timbuktu to Portland, Maine.
Or Portland, Oregon, for that matter.
Thank you for saying so.
(dc)
I never laid a hand on him, goddamn it.
I didn't.
I wouldn't touch one hair
on his goddamn little head.
I love the little son of a bitch.
I?d do anything for him.
Any fucking thing for him.
But that bitch!
As long as I live...
she'll never let me forget
what happened.
I did hurt him once, okay?
It was an accident.
Completely unintentional.
It could have happened to anybody.
And it was three goddamn years ago!
The little fucker had thrown all my
papers all over the floor.
All I tried to do was pull him up.
A momentary loss
of muscular coordination.
I mean...
a few extra foot- pounds of energy...
per second. Per second.
Jack, thank God you?re here.
There's someone else
in the hotel with us.
There's a crazy woman
in one of the rooms.
She tried to strangle Danny.
Are you out of your fucking mind?
No! It's the truth, really.
I swear it. Danny told me.
He went up into one of the bedrooms.
The door was open, and he saw this
crazy woman in the bathtub.
She tried to strangle him!
Which room was it?
From Channel 10 in Miami...
...this isNewswatch
with Glen Rinker...
...Ann Bishop, and
the award- winning Newswatch team.
Good evening.
I'm Glen Rinker, Newswatch 10.
As Miami continues to swelter
in a record winter heat wave...
...bringing temperatures
to the 90s...
...Central and Mountain states
are buried in snow.
In Colorado, 10 inches of snow
fell in just a few hours tonight.
Travel in the Rockies
is almost impossible.
Airports are shut down,
stranding thousands of passengers.
Highways are blocked by snowdrifts.
Railroad tracks are frozen.
Officials in Colorado tell Newswatch...
...at least three people have been killed
by exposure to freezing winds.
The governor of Colorado is expected...
...to declare a weather emergency.
The National Guard might be called out
to clear streets and roads.
Weather forecasters
predict more snow...
...and heavy winds tonight
and tomorrow...
...with temperatures dropping
well below zero.
Back here in Florida,
we've got the opposite problem.
The heat and humidity
are supposed to climb.
Local beaches should be jammed.
Our weather expert, Walter Cronice...
...will have the local forecast
later on Newswatch.
We're sorry. Your call cannot
be completed as dialed.
If you need assistance,
please call the operator.
- Jack?
- Yes, it's me.
Thank God.
Did you find anything?
No. Nothing at all.
I didn't see one goddamn thing.
You went into the room Danny said?
To 237?
Yes, I did.
And you didn't see anything at all'
Absolutely nothing.
How is he?
He's still asleep.
Good.
I'm sure he'll be himself again
in the morning.
Are you sure it was the right room?
I mean, maybe Danny made a mistake.
He must have gone in that room.
The door was open, the llghts were on.
I just don't understand it.
What about those bruises
on his neck?
Somebody did that to him.
I think...
he did it to himself.
No.
That's not possible.
Once you rule out his version
of what happened...
there is no other explanation.
Is there?
(dc)
Whatever the explanation is...
...I think we...
...have to get Danny out of here.
Get him out of here?
Yes.
You mean...
just leave the hotel?
Yes.
It is so...
typical of you to create
a problem like this...
when I finally have a chance
to accompllsh something!
When I'm really into my work!
I could really write my own ticket
if I went back now, couldn't I?
Shovellng out driveways,
work in a car wash.
Any of that appeal to you?
I have let you fuck up
my llfe so far...
but I am not gonna let you
fuck this up.
Good evening. Forest Service.
Hello. My name is Dick Hallorann.
I'm the head chef at the Overlook Hotel.
Good evening.
What can I do for you?
I've been trying to make
an urgent phone call up there...
but the operator said
that the phone llnes are down.
A lot of lines around here
are down due to the storm.
I hate to put you through
any trouble...
but there's a famlly up there
all by themselves with a young kid.
With this storm and everything...
I'd appreciate it if you'd give
them a call on your radio...
just to see if everything's okay.
I'll be glad to do that.
Why don't you call me back
in about 20 minutes?
Thank you very much.
I'll do that.
All right, sir.
Good evening, Mr. Torrance.
Good evening.
Hi, Lloyd.
Been away, but now I'm back.
Good evening, Mr. Torrance.
It's good to see you.
It's good to be back, Lloyd.
What'll it be, sir?
Hair of the dog that bit me.
Bourbon on the rocks.
That'll do her.
No charge to you, Mr. Torrance.
No charge?
Your money's no good here.
Orders from the house.
Drink up, Mr. Torrance.
I'm the kind of man likes to know
who's buying their drinks, Lloyd.
It's not a matter that concerns you,
Mr. Torrance.
At least, not at this point.
Anything you say, Lloyd.
Anything you say.
Oh, dear! I'm so sorry, sir.
Oh, dear. Oh, dear.
I've made an awful mess
of your jacket, sir.
That's all right.
I've got plenty of jackets.
I'm afraid it's advocaat, sir.
It tends to stain.
Advocaat, is it?
Yes, sir.
I think the best thing...
is to come along
to the gentlemen's room...
and we'll get
some water to it, sir.
Looks like you might have got
a spot of it on yourself...
Jeevesy old boy.
That doesn't matter, sir.
You're the important one.
Awfully nice of you to say.
Of course, I intended to change
my jacket this evening...
before the fish and goose soiree.
- Very wise, sir. Very wise.
- Here. I'll just...
hold this for you there, Jeevesy.
Thank you, sir. Thank you.
Let's see if we can improve this
with a llttle water, sir.
All right. I'll just...
set my bourbon and advocaat
down right there.
Won't keep you a moment.
Fine.
What do they call you, Jeevesy?
Grady, sir. Delbert Grady.
- Grady?
- Yes, sir.
Delbert Grady.
That's right, sir.
Mr. Grady...
haven't I seen you somewhere before?
Why, no, sir. I don't believe so.
It's coming off now, sir.
Mr. Grady...
weren't you once the caretaker here?
Why, no, sir. I don't believe so.
You a married man, are you, Mr. Grady?
Yes, sir.
I have a wife and two daughters, sir.
And...
where are they now?
They're somewhere around.
I'm not quite sure at the moment.
Mr. Grady, you were the caretaker here.
I recognize you.
I saw your picture in the newspapers.
You...
chopped your wife and daughter
up into little bits.
And...
then you blew your brains out.
That's strange, sir.
I don't have any recollection
of that at all.
Mr. Grady...
you were the caretaker here.
I'm sorry to differ with you, sir.
But you...
are the caretaker.
You've always been the caretaker.
I should know, sir.
I've always been here.
Did you know, Mr. Torrance...
that your son...
is attempting
to bring an outside party...
into this situation?
Did you know that?
No.
He is, Mr. Torrance.
Who?
A nigger.
A nigger?
A nigger...
cook.
How?
Your son...
has a very great talent.
I don't think you are aware
how great it is.
But he is attempting to use
that very talent...
against your will.
Well...
he is a very willful boy.
lndeed he is, Mr. Torrance.
A very willful boy.
A rather...
naughty boy...
if I may be so bold, sir.
It's his mother.
She...
interferes.
Perhaps they need a good...
talking- to.
If you don't mind my saying so.
Perhaps...
a bit more.
My girls, sir...
they didn't care for
the Overlook at first.
One of them actually stole
a pack of matches...
and tried to burn it down.
But I...
corrected them, sir.
And when my wife tried to prevent me
from doing my duty...
I...
corrected her.
(dc)
KDK 1 calling KDK 12.
Are you receiving me?
This is KDK 1 calling KDK 12.
KDK 1 calling KDK 12.
Do you read me?
This is KDK 1 calling KDK 12.
KDK 1 calling KDK 12.
Are you receiving me?
You're with Hal and Charlie
on Radio 63, KHOW, Denver.
And we have a bad day out there.
Heavy snow throughout
the Denver metro area.
Many mountain passes...
...Wolf Creek and Red Mountain
passes are closed...
...and the chain law is in effect
at the Eisenhower Tunnel.
We hear from the news department...
...only a few flights are
landing at Stapleton Airport...
...and with storms like this...
...I guess the entire airport will
be closed within the hour.
The storm will continue through
the day and the Weather Service...
...has declared a stockman's
and traveler's advisory...
...for all areas outlying
the Denver metro region. (dc)
How do you like it?
What are you doing down here?
I just...
wanted...
to talk to you.
Okay.
Let's talk.
What do you wanna talk about?
I can't really remember.
You can't remember?
No...
I can't.
Maybe it was about Danny?
Maybe it was about him.
I think we should discuss Danny.
I think...
...we should discuss
what should be done with him.
What should be done with him?
I don't know.
I don't think that's true.
I think you have some very definite ideas
about what should be done with Danny.
And I'd like to know what they are.
Well, I...
I think maybe he should be taken
to a doctor.
You think "maybe"
he should be taken to a doctor?
Yes.
When do you think "maybe"
he should be taken to a doctor?
As soon as possible?
"As soon as possible?"
Jack, please.
You believe his health might be at stake.
Yes.
- And you are concerned about him.
- Yes.
And are you concerned about me?
Of course I am.
Of course you are!
Have you ever thought about
my responsibllities?
What are you talking about?
Have you ever had a single moment's...
thought about my responsibilities?
Have you ever thought
for a single moment...
about my responsibllities
to my employers?!
Has is ever occurred to you...
that I have agreed to look after
the hotel untll May 1 st?
Does it matter to you at all...
that the owners have placed
their complete confidence in me...
and that I have signed
a letter of agreement...
in which I've accepted
that responsibility?
Do you have the slightest idea...
what a moral and ethical
principle is? Do you?!
Has it ever occurred to you what
would happen to my future...
if I fall to live up to
my responsibllities?
Has it ever occurred to you?
Has it?!
Stay away from me!
Why?
I just wanna go back to my room.
Well...
I'm very confused.
And I just need a chance
to think things over.
You've had your whole fucking llfe
to think things over!
What good's a few minutes more
gonna do you now?
Stay away from me!
Please!
Don't hurt me.
I'm not gonna hurt you.
- Stay away from me! Stay away!
- Wendy.
Darllng.
Light of my llfe.
I'm not gonna hurt you.
You didn't let me finish my sentence.
I said, "I'm not gonna hurt you."
I'm just gonna bash your brains in.
I'm gonna bash them
right the fuck in.
Stay away from me!
Don't hurt me!
I'm not gonna hurt you.
Stay away from me!
Stay away!
Please!
Stop swinging the bat.
Stay away from me.
Put the bat down, Wendy.
Stop it!
Wendy, give me the bat.
Please!
- Stay away!
- Give me the bat.
Stop it!
Give me the bat.
- Stay away from me.
- Stop swinging the bat.
Please stop!
Give me the bat.
Stay away from me.
- Stop it!
- Give me the bat. Give me the bat.
Goddamn... !
What are you doing?
Wait a minute.
Wait a minute!
What are you doing?
Open the door!
Goddamn it!
Let me out of here!
Open the goddamn door!
Wendy, listen.
Let me out and I'll forget
the whole goddamn thing.
It'll be just like
nothing ever happened.
Wendy, baby.
I think you hurt my head real bad.
I'm dizzy.
I need a doctor.
Honey.
Don't leave me in here.
I'm gonna go now.
I'm gonna try...
to get Danny down the Sidewinder...
in the Snowcat today.
I'll bring back a doctor.
I'm gonna go now.
Yes?
You've got a big surprise
coming to you.
You're not going anywhere.
Go check out the Snowcat and the
radio, and you'll see what I mean.
Go check it out.
Go check it out!
- Wendy?
- It's Grady, Mr. Torrance.
Delbert Grady.
Grady?
Hello, Grady.
Mr. Torrance...
I see you can hardly
have taken care of the...
business we discussed.
No need to rub it in, Mr. Grady.
I'll deal with that situation
as soon as I get out of here.
Will you indeed, Mr. Torrance?
I wonder.
I have my doubts.
I, and others, have come to belleve...
that your heart is not in this.
That you haven't the belly for it.
Just give me one more chance
to prove it, Mr. Grady.
That's all I ask.
Your wife appears to be stronger
than we imagined, Mr. Torrance.
Somewhat more...
resourceful.
She seems to have got the better of you.
For the moment, Mr. Grady.
Only for the moment.
I fear you will have to deal
with this matter...
in the harshest possible way,
Mr. Torrance.
I fear...
that is the only thing to do.
There's nothing I look forward to...
with greater pleasure, Mr. Grady.
You give your word on that,
do you, Mr. Torrance?
I give you my word.
Redrum.
Danny, stop it!
Wendy, I'm home.
Come out, come out,
wherever you are.
I can't get out.
Run!
Run and hide!
Quick!
Little pigs, little pigs, let me come in.
Not by the hair on your chinny- chin- chin?
Then I'll huff...
and I'll puff...
and I'll blow your house in!
Please!
Don't!
No! Please! Please!
Please!
Stop it!
Here's Johnny!
Hello?
Anybody here?
Hello? Anybody here?
Danny-boy!
I'm coming!
I'm coming, Dan!
Great party, isn't it?
I'm coming!
You can't get away!
I'm right behind you!
- Mommy!
- Danny, come here!
Mommy.
Where...?
(dc) = there is more action in the USA version
USA Cut version is 2h 23min.
[ENGLISH]
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org