Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org
Lisa Templeton?
Yes, it's me.
Shit! Sorry!
I did not mean that!
Do not worry
about it.
I'm Dr. Elliot
Mixter.
Ahead.
You can sit.
I brought my resume, I know
you've already seen, but...
Just a precaution.
Thank you.
I see you have a lot of
experience in private residences.
Yes, quite.
Well, in an institution like this,
the proposal is very different.
It's okay.
I cleaned, in schools and
other huge areas before,
so I'm used to.
Yes, I've
noticed that.
But when I said I
wanted proposal dec...
sensitive things
we do here.
Of course.
It is likely to
work at night.
At that time patients
are locked up, but...
Many of our patients have
psychological disorders.
So...
You can be in situations
that need to clean things...
Men usually are
not clean.
If you know
what I mean.
- If I understand.
- And that bother you?
Not at all.
I have some
experiences in...
My mother was very ill, and I
had to take care of her...
And I had to deal with all that
change in your lifestyle...
So you know,
I had to...
learn very quickly,
and it has become a
routine for me then...
How is your
mother now?
She died.
I'm sorry to
hear that.
So...
It is important
to me that...
Everyone who works
here is psychiatrist
or to be responsible
for cleaning...
fully understand what the
mission of this hospital.
It's okay.
This building was built
only two years ago...
And this institution is already
working almost a year ago, so...
We are still building
our reputation.
But always making clear what
reputation we want to...
And so I invested money
up here of my own pocket.
We just
started, but...
Our ambition is
to convert...
this institution,
one of the largest centers medical
treatment in the country.
Then a requirement to
work is the ability to...
Let us be aware of the
needs of our patients.
Unlike some
institutions...
Here the well-being of our
patients comes first.
I admire that, really.
And if I get this job...
I will not
disappoint.
I'm sure not.
OMG! I am so sorry!
- I am sorry!
- It's okay.
- Please, I resolve!
- I'm really sorry.
Yes, good...
thanks for coming.
I'll be in touch.
Thank you.
- Hello?
- Hi dear!
Hello Nancy! How
are you going today?
I was a total mess!
Oh, I'm sure it
was silly...
I know I would never do anything wrong,
not in the way you're thinking...
Surely it is better
than you think.
I sneezed on the head
of the institution.
You did what?
I sneezed on him.
It was one
of those...
sneezing coming
from nowhere...
and before I knew it, I
was covered by my mucus.
God, I...
I am sorry.
Okay, I know
you're sorry.
Ok, you can laugh,
but this was my last chance to
get anywhere in this interview.
I did not cause a
good impression.
You should have taken my advice
and have used a cleavage...
No doubt you would have
gotten a job with that.
Please, you know
that's not my style...
So just ríeteme
in the face.
I was such an idiot!
Well, what are
you going to do?
I don't know.
And thanks for laughing
at my stupidity.
Sorry.
I think I will ask a
brochure for assistance,
to pay the rent...
And then maybe...
back to college...
So better qualify
for something else.
Maybe you do something
about what you're writing?
How to make a book, and maybe publish
it or something like that...
I do not know, I have
not written since...
- You know!
- I know!
What I will say may sound
cliché, but... time heals.
I'm sure you passion
for writing again!
Thank you!
Do you want to
talk about it?
No no!
I think I'll take a big
bowl of ice cream and...
And throw me in
front of the TV.
Comfort food!
If there is a day when the food
is some consolation today!
I can not
discuss that.
Call me tomorrow and
take a coffee together.
Yes of course!
All right.
Bye! -Bye!
Hello!
Lisa, I'm Dr. Mixter
High Hopes hospital.
Really? Hello!
I just called to say I
enjoyed today know...
And besides, I would
like to offer the job!
Is there?
Is this a joke
or something?
No, I would really
like to accept.
Really?
Of course! Oh, my God,
do not believe it!
If you can come at 9:00
am to sign the contract.
Thank you very very much!
I'm very grateful!
And I will not
disappoint.
I know I will not!
- See you tomorrow.
- OK, see you tomorrow!
Can I help you?
I came for the
cleaning work.
Dr. Mixter
said he would.
My name is Delaney.
Let's work together.
How good!
I'll fix this!
We -after start.
Okay!
This is the
storage room!
All you need for the
service is in this place.
Everything is
on the shelves.
The most common
service is vacuuming!
This is our
vacuum cleaner.
It is very powerful,
but also very quiet.
Because we will work when
everyone is asleep...
We do not want
to wake them...
It has a telescopic tube,
and an excellent filter.
Much of what we have here you
must be accustomed to using.
Here are some buckets, usually
to mix bleach with water...
You can do it right.
We also have this product
to remove stains...
And we use it to remove stains
from the floor and carpet.
Apply 20 minutes
before scrubbing...
But beware, it is very powerful, you
have to wash your hands after use.
One of the worst parts
of the job is that we...
to remove chewed gum
on many surfaces...
And when they are at the bottom
of the tables are dried.
That is very rude!
Yes, and I think most of the time
are employees who do this...
and no patients.
But we have this
gum remover!
It's a bit
complicated to use,
but it is easier
to remove the gum.
And the stain is heated to 180
degrees, with a pressure of 7.0...
It is about 150 liters of
heated spots per minute.
Do you mind if I see
it as you use it?
Just to finish no holes in
the furniture making...
No problem!
And now I will show you the most
dangerous chemical that we have!
This is a concrete cleaner!
It is a very toxic product!
So you have to wear gloves
and masks like we have here,
agree?
Used to clean concrete,
bricks and rusty metal.
For concrete mix.
With 1/4 water...
Rub with his sleeve,
and wait 5-10 minutes.
But in the worst
cases, use it pure.
Do not worry.
There is much
to learn.
You must learn everything
in about 3 weeks.
Good for me.
Any questions? No, I
think I understand.
Well, follow me.
This is the main
hall of the room B.
Someone must clean
cleaning here all night.
His work here will
empty the trash,
vacuuming and cleaning
the hallways.
Patients here
are category B.
Those who had a nervous
breakdown, so they are catatonic.
They are harmless.
As Ms.
Hardesty here!
Hello Ms.
Hardesty...
She never spoke a word
since he got here.
It just goes room to room,
and back to your room...
Everyday.
Then why do you
talk to her?
Because the beams
seem human,
otherwise just
seem furniture.
That's how we all
lose our humanity.
I like to think
they can hear me.
However, she does
not speak to me.
See you later Ms.
Hardesty ..
Bye!
Patients are locked in
their rooms at night.
But sometimes they need
to be cleaned as well.
During the day the
nurses cleaned.
But at night we will be
asked to clean them.
It is not the most
pleasant work...
But only it happens
occasionally.
I get it. Now comes
the most part...
hard work.
Clean dirt is not
the hardest part?
This is very easy compared
to what's behind this door.
What's behind?
This leads to the
rooms below.
And that is bad?
We could say that.
Here is where
the patients A.
Criminals
considered crazy.
- Dr Mixter did not mention?
- Yes, good...
These patients can
not be helped.
So they have become,
I do not know why...
The secret of
this hospital.
Dr. Mixter probably
thinks he can help.
Can not.
The staff calls this
place "Blood Runner".
What's that smell?
Always hangs
in the air...
No matter how
friegues the floor...
There is always the
smell of death.
Patients are
dangerous?
Yes, but do not
worry about it.
No need to deal
with them directly.
Let's clean up the
hall. Dusting.
He is Jerry Kimble.
He was convicted of
stabbing a woman 49 times
against his own son.
After killing her he
sexually assaulted her,
before strangling
her 4 years.
It is a
dangerous man.
Especially
for women.
This other
patient...
it's even worse!
Here Mr.
Dennis Palmer.
Also it is known as the
Cannibal Long Island.
He was abused
as a child.
So his goals were always
pedophiles and rapists.
The he attracted them
and tortured them.
He kept alive parts of their
bodies while they ate.
That's horrible.
The most horrible thing is that
most of the audience thought...
That was a hero!
Ironic, is not it?
She is Sadie
Krenwinkel.
What's your problem?
He was a member of
a sect of witches.
They kidnapped six people for
use in a demonic ritual.
5 killed, but one escaped and
told police where they were.
She put their
victims in circles.
And speaking of
crazy stuff.
A media loved
it, but...
it was considered
crazy by the court.
Since then it has gone through
some institutions, so...
Now she's here.
We have some strange
stories here.
Well, these are not
the strangest.
This is our
resident "nobody".
Sometimes we have
people with amnesia.
Sometimes we discover
who they are.
But we do not know
who this man is.
And who is it?
He came here 6
months ago.
It was found, lying
on the ground...
At first I was like Ms.
Hardesty, catatonic...
But then... He
became violent.
A young doctor tried to
measure their vital signs.
The patient "X" here hit him so
hard that he broke his legs...
six people were needed
to achieve contain.
Now he can not go out or to
exercise during the day.
He still does not
know who he is.
God!
God has nothing to
do with this madman.
OMG!
You scared me!
Should not you be in
bed being so late?
I don't know.
I guess you should
not be here.
You want to
play with me?
I would love to!
Maybe tomorrow...
But I think you should
go back to your bed.
It's okay.
- You changed the garbage room?
- Yes.
Good.
It is not even necessary
to change the bulb up.
In the fourth 12.
Are you having
fun. -Nice!
You know, it's
funny... I...
I thought it was not
going to get this job...
I did not do well
in the interview.
Dr. Mixter said you were the
only interviewed for the job.
- Really?
- Yes.
He must have seen you were the
right person for the job...
The Had no longer to interview
anyone else. -All right.
Some tattoos
really great!
Yes, sometimes I
forget that I have.
And most of
them mean?
It represents many
things we went through.
Like what?
How, that is none
of your business!
I did not want
to intrude.
It's okay.
Let's say that the past
be forgotten. Okay?
Fair enough.
So... How was
your first night?
It was great. I
saw a girl...
She must have been
about 13 years...
I told him to
go to bed.
I think here no
children allowed agree?
Are you sure you saw
a girl of that age?
Yes
dark hair, and you must not
have more than 13 years...
- It's okay.
- Why?
In fact there are
no children here.
What?
In fact there was no child
of that age here...
I think the younger
patient must have...
twenty. -You are
kidding, right?
Do not! Really!
Well, and what I
saw in the hall?
Are you sure you saw
a girl of that age?
Clear!
So I must warn Lisa.
This is not a good place
for a girl to be.
He found?
No.
So you who saw
the girl?
Yes.
Are you sure you
saw a girl?
Of course!
I have two employees working to
keep drugs in their place...
Come on...
I did not find
anything.
This is very
strange.
It was very uncomfortable,
that I know.
Listen, you do
me a favor.
The next time you see
something you think...
Reflect before running to
the hurried over here...
I do not have time to look shit
that does not exist in this place.
You understand?
Yes.
Ok.
I am sorry.
Do not worry
about it.
It's better to prevent
than to cure.
Okay. Can you take
care of cleaning?
- Lisa, can you do me a favor?
- Clear.
You can empty the trash from
the office of Dr. Mixter?
I have to go check
the boiler...
There are claims that the
heater does not work.
- Yes, no problem.
- Thank you.
Dr. Mixter?
What the hell are
you doing here?
I'm emptying waste.
It's funny, I did not know that Dr.
Mixter leave their trash on the table!
Simply must have
fallen... I do not know.
You know I'll have
to report it.
What?
What's up? I did
not see anything.
I discovered, girl.
That's hospital
policy.
I just got this job, and
I really need. Please?
Yes. We can
make a deal...
What do you
mean by that?
I am sure that that beautiful mouth
should be good for something,
besides telling
lies...
You are disgusting!
Come on?
You win, and me too.
I would love to...
You'll love it.
You better get out of my way, or
I'll sue for sexual harassment.
You're working here
since five minutes ago.
Who do you think Dr.
Mixter going to believe?
A maid whore?
Or a medical
professional?
Pemberton!
Leave her alone!
We're not doing
anything here...
We're just talking.
What is the problem?
No problem.
Lisa! Come with me.
We have a job in
the sector B.
You're good?
I'm fine, I'm
a little...
asustada and
intimidated.
Pemberton? If you
get to do that.
Unfortunately, it's
not the worst...
But the other scoundrel,
Hardcastle...
They like to be.
You get used to it.
They seem like they are not made
to be in charge of patients.
Let's have a coffee.
Like the Laziness
is not it?
I like to have
some peace!
Ms. Hardesty, which
makes out of bed?
I forgot, he
does not speak.
Stay there, I'll
call the manager.
You'll die here.
What did you say?
I'll call the
manager.
Look who's here, "Miss
sexual harassment."
Go to shit!
You are laughing
at what?
If you have a
big mouth.
You searched in all
hospitals for a child.
And now she fills her
bag with your balls!
I do not want trouble, but
I came to warn you...
He has a patient outside
his room in the wing B.
You are not a problem
for me dear.
I'm professional.
And I suggest that you keep in
that bag while you're here.
Yeah, whatever.
See you later
"dear".
So where you saw
this patient is?
She was here! Who?
Mrs. Hardesty.
Mrs. Hardesty?
Yes, she even
told me.
Mrs. Hardesty was
here and you spoke?
Yes!
Look, I know
you're catatonic!
But she told
me okay?
Catatonic would be
at least strange.
What do you mean?
Mrs. Hardesty,
died this morning.
But I can swear...
Why do not you go back
to do the cleaning?
Or perhaps you are on
the side of Fools?
Ok mi querida?
Hey, wait girl!
Hey, do not go
down there!
Open up!
Girl?
Palmer?
- Palmer?
- Yes!
My dick is so
hard Palmer!
So hard I can
barely stand it.
I can break the
wall with it.
And do bad
things with you!
Things very,
very bad!
I must warn Mr.
Kimble...
Threats are
not welcome!
I'm pajeando palmer!
You want to see?
You fucking fagot!
Stay out of my
sight Mr. Kimble,
and I'll stay
out of yours.
I know you're
out there girl.
I feel the smell
of your shell!
You want to join my?
Come on.
Ok, the next thing to do is
mopping the floor and so ended.
You can do that?
Maybe...
Why? What is
the problem?
Is that...
I do not feel good, so I thought
I'd take a little break...
Patients have
scared you?
Only a little.
This is normal, too they
scare me sometimes.
But I need to enter
the room of a patient
apparently he had
an accident.
Sure you prefer not to
clean the lower floors?
I think not.
I know the lower floors and are
few places that are scary!
But you just
get used.
I can hear them talking
through the gates, and...
And that makes
me nervous.
I know.
So I hear when
I'm there.
But do not worry.
When you get used to
things they get easier.
I can hear you
out there!
I've been talking to
your mother Lisa!
She's here
with me Lisa!
She told me all
about you.
I know you're out
there, Lisa!
Háblame.
What do you
want me to say?
So you see you can tell me about
summer trips to Key West!
With your mother.
Those are your favorite
memories with your mother!
So you see you want to tell
me about how you were sad...
Next to the bed
of your mother...
for 6 months long.
Taking care of
her unassisted.
With cancer
ending his body.
Sucking all
his life.
How do you
know all this?
Because your mother
is talking to me.
You're a sick bitch.
She has a message
for you Lisa.
A message!
What is it?
¡Lárgate!
Lisa What's
going on?
I will not go back there, I
do not like being there.
Ok, calm down and tell
me what happened there?
I said horrible things
out the door. Hideous!
She always tells
me too well.
She said things that did not
have like to know about me.
- Like what?
- How...
I'm crazy, right?
Do not.
This place gets
inside us sometimes.
Is that...
I wonder if I'm
not going crazy.
Well, it is
not healthy,
think of all the crazy
things you're saying.
Trust me.
Do not let come
into your head.
- It's hard to keep them out sometimes.
- Listen out...
Take a break of
the lower floors.
I'll get there.
I am sorry!
- I realized it would be so hard.
- Do not worry.
The last thing I want is that you
feel threatened by having to work.
I appreciate it, I
really appreciate it.
No problem.
That was all this
noise Palmer?
Sorry to bother Mr. Pemberton,
but wanted to know if I can...
receive any medical
attention?
How the hell did
this happen?
Well, I think it was this rudimentary
weapon which did the damage.
Jesus Christ!
Put the gun down and
step away from the door!
Put your hands on your fucking head
and stand against the wall, now!
I'm eating
your shit!
One false move and cover
the walls with your brain.
You understand? As you
wish, Mr. Pemberton.
And do not move!
Do not move a shit!
Sorry Mr. Pemberton.
Good night, Mr.
Kimble.
Pemberton?
Pemberton, where
the hell are you?
Why are you
taking so long?
Jesus, Mary
and Joseph!
Shit!
We have a code 6
in the X Wing!
We have a job to do.
So let's work!
Good night
gentlemen!
I think we will have a
show here in the morning.
Bastardo!
What the fuck are
you looking at?
Nothing!
I just heard something
and I was curious.
We ensure that it is
in the way it is.
This guy is
a menace!
He deserves everything
that happened to him!
I look not want you talking
to Mixter about it!
Nor with
anyone else!
You understand? -I
will not say anything.
Good!
You do not have to
clean somewhere else?
My dear God, you
look like shit!
Thank you, happens.
The nights
are long no!
Yes, work is
beating me...
And making my internal
clock go crazy.
But you know it's
not just that.
There's something really
wrong with this place.
Like what?
Good...
Virtually everyone
are idiots perfect!
Usually, there are
places like this!
Patients are
very violent!
Some of them
you care?
No, nothing
like that!
Are the things they say,
that can be, well...
I do not know, this might just
seeing things that do not exist.
What are you
talking about?
O...
Or this place is haunted
or I'm going crazy.
I would not be surprised,
that he was bewitched.
What do you mean?
I told my father
about your new job.
It's okay.
You know that asylum was
built a few years ago?
Yes.
He said it was built
in 112 Ocean Avenue.
And with that?
Have you not heard?
No!
There was a
famous house!
Infamous, how
should I say...
A man shot his entire
family in the 70s.
His parents, brothers, sisters, killed
his entire family with a shotgun!
And the next owners of the
house, only lasted a month!
They said they were expelled from
the house by evil spirits...
And the house became
famous in the whole world!
That's why the previous
owners sold the property.
They tired of the constant
interest of the media,
and tourists.
Are you sure you've never heard in
the house of horrors in Amityville?
I mean, I remember vaguely
heard something...
But I've never delved
into the matter.
I did not realize that
was on the grounds.
Yes, right in the place where
the house was demolished.
And you think you
are bewitched!
Either that or
I'm going crazy.
Well, we know
you're not crazy.
Maybe all the stories about
the haunted house, are true.
Perhaps the house is
gone, but not spirits.
Do you believe
in ghosts?
I've never seen one.
But I think I have
an open mind.
Did not you say you
saw something, right?
Thank you.
So, what will you
do? Give up?
Part of me thinks
I should, why...
This place has many
things that scare me.
But I think,
you know...
I've lived a lot.
If I were you, I
would resign.
There is no way to work
in a place you chills.
Yes but I really
need the money.
And now I think I feel I
should find out more...
And get to the bottom
of the matter.
Maybe you've
gone mad!
Yeah, maybe a
little crazy.
Your hair is crazy!
Oh God!
6 MEMBERS OF
THEIR OWN FAMILY
THE VICTIMS
Do you know the history
of this place?
It does not have
much history...
We are open from
about two years ago.
No, the history
of the land.
You mean to what was on the
ground before the hospital?
Yes.
I know very
little about it.
112 Ocean Avenue.
The old Amityville
haunted house!
I do not know about
the spell, but...
I know what
that guy.
The guy who killed
his family.
That's true.
I just learned about it
through a friend recently.
It was a
famous case.
Why did you
not tell me?
You looked so scared, I did not
want to make things worse.
You know why
I'm scared?
Yes, because patients
on the lower floors.
Not only that
Delaney.
I believe...
Have you seen
anything?
Do you remember that girl?
Which I saw in the hallway.
I know who is!
She is the daughter
of the DeFeo family.
They killed her!
Have you ever
you seen?
No.
Honestly? I can
be honest Lisa?
I do not believe in that
stuff about ghosts.
I do not think so, but.
I know what I saw.
Look, I think you
saw something.
Some people are not open
to this sort of thing.
But OK...
I'm not very
attached to that.
So what do
you think?
Believe in God?
You're making serious
questions this evening Lisa.
I'm curious.
Why do you ask?
I've been
thinking...
You know...
how much evil can
exist in the world...
Which we can be...
Protected by a
loving God.
Look...
I do not believe that God is a
bearded man, who lives in Heaven.
Like I do not think that the
devil is a devil with red horns.
I think... God
and Satan...
They live in
each of us.
They are good
or bad...
That depends Lisa...
Which side
we belong!
What scares me...
What if there
is a God...
But it is not
powerful enough...
To stop the evil.
Free will is in the
hands of people.
They are feeding the
evil within them...
That's what
scares me.
Dr. Mixter had to know
what was in this area,
before edify.
Of course he knew.
Even it was he who bought the
land and made the demolition.
Why would I do that
knowing the story?
Maybe he is not
superstitious, is a doctor!
Usually they do not
believe in these things.
Amityville is full of legends,
even before the Defeos.
Like what?
As the stories of Native
Americans being slaughtered
in these lands...
Many years ago.
Some people...
believe that even the
head of the Indians...
that boy possessed.
The guy who killed
his family.
- Really?
- Yes.
I do not think
that's true.
If there's anything I learned from
patients in the lower floors...
It is that the minds
of some people,
It works differently from
the minds of others.
People who do Lisa,
good bad things...
They feed the evil within
them, and that's not good.
Possession.
It is a disease.
Sickness of
the soul.
I do not know
what to believe.
Just do not let your
imagination take you Lisa.
Look, you're a girl
you have food in you.
Do not let this place
put evil in you.
Ok?
If it is okay.
The librarian seemed
to know much...
about Native Americans
in Amityville.
Yes, but I knew nothing about
someone who killed on the ground.
The librarian said that the
whole city was very angry...
When the Psychiatric Hospital
was built on the ground.
Why they did not want something
threatening in the neighborhood...
and they signed a petition
with thousands of names.
But the doctor who
runs the place...
I had a lot of money and
bribing important people.
But it is true that
there were dead or not?
You are here...
Here it is.
In the 18th
century...
There was a Native American
tribe in Amityville,
known as the Sachem.
Led by Sachem
Takapoucha as chief.
The tribe migrated from
Salem to Massachusetts
to escape Christian
persecution.
They were persecuted for being
considered practitioners of witchcraft.
They made a ritual of human
sacrifice to 6 people.
6 For it relates to the biblical
number, man and creation.
In order to invoke the
spirit of their God.
"Master of
darkness".
What believed that empowered
his followers immortality.
Many settled
in Amityville,
but later they were
expelled from the land...
By local Christians.
Some Christians wanted to expel
the tribes of their lands.
A war began.
The cristianes hired
John Underhill salem.
A collective
cemetery,
Built in 112 Ocean
Avenue in Amityville.
Underhill killed
the whole tribe.
The Indians were massacred
and buried in the ground.
Before dying, Sachem
vowed revenge.
According to a local
legend, the chief Sachem,
still she is
bewitching land.
Parapsychologists and psychics claim
that the vengeful spirits of Sachem...
influenced the 1974 murder
of the DeFeo family
on Ocean Avenue 112.
And they freaked all
owners who followed.
As revenge for
the lives taken.
So the legend is based
on historical facts?
It seems like!
You told me
last night.
What evil lives
in all of us.
You may... People can
be influenced...
for the evil
of them?
Why are you still
thinking about it?
Yes, I follow.
So you're thinking too much.
This place is coming to you.
It's coming to me for something
sinister what is happening.
And not only by
patients Wing X.
Have you ever
noticed that?
I could have
noticed something.
Why then you never say
anything, or did nothing?
This is like a bee.
What does that mean?
While the bee is flying
from flower to flower.
But when you think
something is a threat.
Pica!
You can leave
a mark...
but the person
recovers.
But bee...
Go dead!
So I wonder.
It was worth it?
Take a look at this article!
What does it say there?
The Sachem tribe,
It was a Native American tribe
that existed in the 18th century.
They migrated from Massachusetts to
Amityville, where they were killed...
in a dispute
over land.
The tribe was known for being
practitioners of witchcraft.
And they worshiped a god called
the "master of darkness."
In 2009, a modern cult emerged in
honor of the tribe that existed.
They adopted the beliefs
of the tribe ..
But not the idea of ​​what it
takes to be Native American
to join the sect.
Click on that
final link.
- This Here?
- Yes.
Our time is near.
On November
13, 2013...
6 souls will be sacrificed
to the "master of darkness"
by his devoted
followers.
To be blessed
with immortality.
Devotees do not perish
at the final judgment.
But the faithful
followers of love.
They will survive and win great
power and responsibility.
To rule the
new world.
What the fuck?
Click on the
calendar.
- Get up!
- Why?
What is this? What
does this mean Lisa?
Sadie Krenwinkel, accused of
murder and cultist Sachem...
A modern incarnation of the cult
of a tribe of Native Americans...
who practiced witchcraft
in the 18th century.
At his trial in 2010 Krenwinkel told
police about the cult Sachem...
Alleging that the sacrifice
of 6 individuals,
followers to give
immortality.
- Oh my God!
- What?
Find the name of the doctor
who testified at the trial.
Sadie!
I know what
you're doing!
There you blog!
How do you have
internet access?
You are allowed to
have it in your cell?
"Master of
Darkness" is near.
Now it's too late
to try to stop it.
The night is waiting
for the big arrival.
What are you planning? Are
you planning a sacrifice?
Good things come
of it, right?
Our time is near.
Pass!
Hola Dr. Mixter!
Hello lisa! What
can I do for you?
I have to talk to
you. Something.
It's very important.
Yes of course.
So what I can do
for you Lisa?
Well, I'll tell...
I can sound a little
weird, but...
I really
need to say.
Okay, go ahead.
Are you aware of the history of
this place before the hospital?
A specifically
that mean?
The murder of Defeos, the
house that was here...
what people say
is haunted.
On the murder of
the DeFeo yes...
But haunted?
That's just a scary thing
created by the media.
But what about the history of
the land in the 18th century?
No I do not know.
Good...
There was a group of
Native Americans...
Sachem called
the tribe...
And they were
killed...
For Christians during the
dispute of the land...
I'm sure all this
has a meaning.
Yes
Sadie Krenwinkel,
ward X.
She shares the belief
of the tribe... Sachem.
I have reason to believe that she
is having internet access...
And also, the whole paraphernalia
of Witchcraft and...
He is planning some kind of
human sacrifice for tonight.
To invoke the God in whom they
believe. The master of darkness.
I'm serious!
He has been reading
about Sadie?
All this nonsense?
I can assure you, you do not
have internet access...
and all he said.
She has a blog, and sites
like "Sister Sadie".
Sadie. That can
be anything else.
Check yourself!
The patient
X room...
They spend 23 hours a
day in those cells.
Leave for an hour to exercise,
and they are closely watched...
For six of our
employees.
There is no chance
that these patients
Internet access...
The such
paraphernalia.
Well, someone is helping
her to access...
Someone here.
Just go to your cell
and talk to her.
If I'm wrong well.
But he had to say.
And I need to
check it, please.
Wait a minute.
You were a witness
in his trial?
Yes, I witnessed.
What is insinuating?
So you know how
dangerous it is?
Yes!
And I appreciate
your concern.
One thing you need to
understand Lisa...
There are very disturbed
patients in this hospital.
We help those who
can be helped...
But patients in X
room are beyond help.
Psychological disorders of
them are very advanced...
They have
illusions...
Of greatness, or...
I'm worried about you that
you believe in illusions.
I know what this
may seem...
But please!
Check your blog!
You can access the home page,
from here in the hospital.
It's okay.
You came with a complaint about
a violation of a patient...
And a threat of
violence, so...
My duty is to
investigate!
In fact I'll start a
search immediately.
Stay there!
I'll be right
back! -Thank you.
What the hell
are you doing?
This is so that you
calm down Lisa.
Fuck off!
We are trying
to help.
Let me out of here
fucking sick!
Let's talk
softly Lisa!
Otherwise, you will
be sedated again.
Why do this?
You're having
paranoid delusions.
And you're having
disturbing visions.
I have no illusions,
I know what I saw.
You think you know.
The brain is
very powerful.
I'm sure you believe
what you saw.
But all in
your head.
That's not real.
You're a sick girl, and
precise treatment.
This makes all
your employees?
Every time someone says
something ends up in jail?
Employee?
He never worked
here Lisa.
You're a
patient here!
You always were
a patient here!
He's lying, I
know what I am!
Do not be
afraid dear.
You have always
been with us here.
Initially not as
a patient but...
But the time has come that're
a full-time resident.
I know.
It's a lot
to digest.
So I'll let you
think about it.
We begin our
morning session.
- Okay.
- Now...
What if we make you
feel more comfortable.
Thank you.
First you have
to take this.
It will help
you sleep.
Good girl!
Let's get this
over Lisa.
Together!
I will release
the belt.
But remember, if you put
the belt violent again.
Ok.
- ¿Esta This better?
- Yes.
Get some rest now.
Tomorrow we will begin
the healing process.
Our time is near.
Our God commands.
For its majesty.
Come with us
to bless.
Nothing else...
In addition to
your offer, death.
You gave life.
Mátalos!
Kill them all!
We did it!
Elliot did!
Our time is near.
Immortality is ours!
Lisa!
We have to go fast!
What?
Come on!
Why do not you want
to play with me?
You have to get
out of here!
Someone comes
around with a gun.
My skin is
too tight.
What?
Come on hurry up!
The key is stuck
in the damn door!
Do something!
It's okay!
You will be fine!
Do not go!
And now that?
Motherfucker!
Raise your hands
fucking sick!
I see you leave,
the formalities.
Among Lisa!
You still tells
me I'm crazy?
It's all in my head?
Well, maybe yes.
Maybe not.
Do not get in my
head motherfucker!
I know who I am
and what I saw.
You are
what's crazy!
He is holding a gun pointing
to a reputable doctor.
Why do this? Why?
You're part of
something big to come.
The arrival of the
master of the dark!
It will bring all his
power and immortality.
Do you really
believe that?
Because everything
seems stupid to me.
You're Nobody, apart from
being a fundamentalist...
What killed
innocent people
just because he read a lot
of crap on the internet...
He will be
here soon...
Just another sacrifice
is all you need.
How would that be if
I'll blow your head?
What are you
laughing?
It's all working
as expected.
The police
are coming.
I'll tell you
all this.
Everything about
his sick plan!
They lock him up and
throw away the key!
If you say so!
Tell Lisa!
How do I know his mother
is burning in hell?
Shut up! Do not say anything about my mother,
she does not know anything about it.
I know sometimes you wonder why
you have not cried enough.
I know you feel
guilty for not...
He has done more for her
when she was alive.
Having lived your life
without worrying about it.
I worried about her.
Let's face Lisa, you never
took care of your mother!
You never cared about
anyone besides yourself!
Shut up! Shut up!
It is burning in hell knowing
that cared about him.
His mother was a
dirty whore Lisa!
And it is
paying in hell!
Fuck off!
Thanks Victoria!
A year ago they survived a slaughter
in the High Hopes hospital.
When the cleaning
lady Lisa Templeton.
He ran with a
shotgun...
killing 6 people and
injuring many others.
Dr. Elliot Mixer, wrote
a new book called.
"High Hopes,
lost dreams."
What he gives us his account
of that fateful night.
As described in the
mind of the murderer!
Dr. Mixter, Good morning!
Catalina Good morning!
- How is it going?
- Very well thanks!
Dr. why not tell us a
little about the book?
Well, he describes every
moment of that night.
Of course it was a
horrible experience.
It was very difficult for me
to lose those feelings...
What happened,
and I wrote it!
And how it affected
the hospital?
Well, we were
closed for long!
And I know many people in town
thought we should have closed.
But it never
crossed my mind.
People come for
a tragedy!
And my staff
and I...
I certainly approached
us from that incident!
Like many colleagues,
as friends!
This has made us a better
institution in my opinion.
And we're getting
stronger!
You. Mentioned that some people
wanted to close the place.
I knew I had some resistance
to open the institute...
It is having been built in the
place the infamous "home"
Ronald DeFeo Jr. When he
killed his family in the 70s.
The people of that time explored the case
according to their previous terms...
and now they face the
same kind of opinions.
Especially in the
last week...
by selling his book
rights to make a movie.
How do you respond
to those criticisms?
I heard the charges.
But you do not
understand Catherine?
I'm helping those
involved to move forward.
I proposed to some of the
victims as criminally insane.
But he also had loyal
employees, who had families.
And I'm determined not to
let them into oblivion!
Each of these
officials...
It has its own
chapter in my book.
So if you read will
have a perfect image...
How the people
were wonderful.
I've said it
before, but...
All types of media,
newspapers, books,
television, movies...
They are a
preservation of life!
Our physical
bodies can die.
But our image will
survive, and be famous.
Prayer, work, our passion,
will be retained.
Thus our souls
be preserved.
In all these
forms of media.
We will become
unachievable.
Immortals!
Please rate this subtitle at www.osdb.link/43fcg
Help other users to choose the best subtitles