Someone needs to stop Clearway Law.
Public shouldn't leave reviews for lawyers.
Control 5! Over.
Do you copy?
Are you asleep or what?
Oh, I'm coming! I'm coming! I'm coming!
Control 5? Is everything alright?
Yeah! Everything's great!
Looks like we got a new lynx though.
Great! Yeah!
Whoa! I Can't believe it!
Where?
On the road to the dunes.
I'm going to check it out now
Meanwhile, you know what I'm going to do?
I'm going to prepare a big welcome party
I just don't know about this, Felix.
With my luck, I'll end up
with some broken bone.
Gotcha!
Go on. Off you go.
Oh! It's a Lynx! We've got to take
it to the shelter.
Look! Isn't that the lynx
from last week?
So, is it your turn or mine?
Who knows. Tell you what, I'll toss you for it
Extinction's the next step for this boy.
- Felix?
- Yes?
Are we there yet?
No, another 5 minutes or so.
How can you stay so calm? I can't
stand being shut up in here
This is the first time they've
taken you to a shelter, heh?
- Yes, and you?
- Well, I've been here about 3 or 4 times
but Felix... Uff!
I've lost count already.
Yeah
I think it's been about forty times in all.
What bad luck! If all the other
lynxes are like you,
soon there
won't be any of you left.
Betty, please. The animal
shelter's like my home.
It's a very nice place.
It's that your idea of
a very nice place?
Three weeks ago it didn't look
like a prison camp.
Incredibly nice, this is going to be
like staying in a holiday resort
I can just see myself, lying there, in there
with my little hoofies, having a manicure
...or maybe I'll get a pedicure...
I've got four feet... - Betty, please...
Spend as much time as you can with
your cubs... Enjoy life.
Well...
whatever we have left...
We don't know whether
it will be days
or just hours...
I think we should keep
a minute of silence
for ourselves.
- Hey! Where are you going?
- Same all, same all.
There he goes again.
Those crazy eyes.
The loneliness of
the visionary soul.
They'll be sorry.
What happened here?
Felix, old buddy!!!
Gus!
It's been a long time!
What're you
doing here?
Follow me.
What's the big mystery?
I thought I was here to get better
but some very strange things
are happening here.
I think it must
have something to do
with some
secret government agency,
maybe unauthorized
experiments.
WHAT!
Quiet!
But Gus, I was practically raised
in shelters like this one,
and they've always
treated us well.
Yes, look... we're not in cages
anymore.
If my wings were all right,
I could fly right out of here.
Don't you see?
It's a trap so
we'll let our guard down
but something really serious
is going to happen here.
Mark my words!
The security measures
are greater every day,
that's why we need the
very best.
Yes, sir, it's been difficult,
but we finally found him.
...I'll put him on
- Thank you
- Yes?
- Mr. Newman, this is Noah.
Yes, hold on, please.
Now where's
the darned hold button?
Bluetooth?
No
Text messages?
No!
Wait...
There it is!
I do love effective
but simple devices.
Like this one.
Sorry, just a little matter
I had to take care of.
I believe you've already been
told the details of the job.
Do you accept?
Sure, no one can say "no"
to money like that.
I'll be there tomorrow.
Gus, you're paranoid.
Nothing's the matter.
Yeah, yeah, yeah,
nothing's the matter.
We have to find out
what's going on.
I've got a plan.
In every prison there's a
bloke who can get anything.
In here it's Rupert.
Hi... You got what
I asked you for?
Here it is,
a lockpick and a torch.
Rupert, over here!
Oh sorry, I've got dirt in my eyes.
It's not the dirt...
You're a mole
and you're half-blind.
Soon we'll place
a big order with you
for the great escape.
Well, now that I'm going
to be a father,
I've got to work
a little bit harder.
Come on. Let's find out
what's going on here.
I'll lead the way.
Some of us animals are
equipped for camouflage.
Sweet!!
You take a rag from over
there and follow me.
With that orange color of yours,
we could be discovered in no time.
Oh yes... VERY discreet.
Oh no, his camouflage
is out of sync!
Who's out there?
Stupid camouflage!
I said...
who's out there?
- What's going on? What's happening?
- Shut up!
- Shut up. Right. I won't say a word.
- Just be quiet!
At least those plants
broke your fall.
And the nettles.
Ouch.
I see you still can't
control your camouflage.
Well, my shrink says
it's all in my head,
but I think
he just hates me.
...this was the most recent theft of
animals to be reported...
And the lingering question is what
and who's behind the animal's kidnappings.
What! Theft of animals?
What's going on?
C'mon! Let me see!
The Police haven't yet found the culprits
and the lingering question is what and
who is behind the kidnappings of animals.
Kidnapping of animals?
The last truck is arriving
tomorrow.
I'll feel a lot easier
when they're all here.
Those animals should get
what they deserve
and spend the rest of
their lives behind bars.
I told you!
- Look! We're on TV!
- Come on!
We have to warn the others.
Since special security measures
have been taken
no more animals
have disappeared.
I hate to have to keep them in those
little cages and surrounded by fences
but it's the only way to
keep them safe.
Who is behind all
this, and why?
In spite of the surrounding secrecy
regarding the operation,
it has been confirmed that the
last truck with the endangered species
comes today to the security
center in Doniana.
Welcome, Mr. Newman. It's a privilege
to finally meet you in person.
Thanks.
Oh, but forgive me, perhaps I can
make you feel a bit more at home.
Now let's see...
This one fits rather more apt.
- Impressive
- Wouldn't you like to sit down?
I'd rather stand if you don't mind.
As you like.
Bringing all those animals
together in a single shelter
should make things easier.
But we have what
you asked for -
a helicopter,
two trucks to gather
the animals together,
and your personal trailer.
After breaking into the
animal shelter
you will search the region for the
rest of the species.
We have also brought together a team
of men to work under your orders.
Do you have the list of animals
you want me to capture?
Yes, of course. All the information has been
up loaded to the computer in your trailer.
And remember: I need a
pair of each species,
and no animal must
be hurt in any way.
Do you
think you can do it?
Mr. Noah, you offend me.
In three weeks, you'll have
all your little critters
and I'll be far away from here spending
your money to hunt animals for real.
Aren't you taking
this all a bit too seriously?
Of course not.
It's even worse than we thought.
We'll never leave this place.
They said we'd spend the rest of our
lives behind bars!
I think you're letting your
imagination run away with you.
Yeah, well, I heard it, too.
We have to be ready to escape.
Well, when I've worked
on it a bit more.
Very good, but you'll have
to change faster.
Those killer guards up there would
have shot you full of holes already!
Very funny.
All right, next
Ooh! Saucy swimsuit!
Look! More animals are coming.
The poor fools don't know what's
in store for them.
Now what are the odds of
the outside cable coming loose
...and touching the inside fence? - Well, I'm no
chicken, but at least he's close this time.
You again! I've got news
for you, little buddy.
A girl lynx has arrived.
One of the few left.
With a little luck
if you like each other,
you could be a couple.
...They got you a girl friend
Don't be stupid.
How's she gonna be my girl friend if
I don't even know her...
Feisty, isn't she!
We'll cure you first and that way
they can get to know each other.
Why are you so angry?
Why? They capture me,
they bring me here in a cage.
They have no
reason to lock me up.
But it'll only be until your cured.
And not one second more!
I don't want to end up like
those half tamed animals.
And you?
What happened to you?
Umm, I got into a fight
with a bear,
a really BIG ONE.
Sometimes I can't
control my wild instincts.
You sure you didn't electrocute
yourself on the fence?
Your hair
is standing on end,
you've got burn
marks onlyour paws,
and, well, I saw you
when I got here.
I didn't want you to think
I was one of those tame cats.
Be careful, there are only
a few of us left,
and there'll be even fewer if you
keep having accidents like that.
So have you two swapped
telephone numbers yet?
Right, buster, it's your turn, let's
see what we can do with you.
Yes, sir?
Well, have the men present
themselves here
and then, what the heck...
I'd like to do something about
how this place is decorated.
Right away, sir
YES, SIR!!
Wel, before studying the mission,
you have to understand something.
You're under my orders
and that means you do
everything exactly as I tell you to.
No thinking for yourselves...
no alternative plans...
and above all,
DISCIPLINE
One, Two Three... FREEZE
- You lose, dummy!
- What do you think you're doing?
Oh, sir, hello sir.
Sir!
We were late, sir.
Calm down...
A right, let's review
the plan.
Tomorrow there can
be no mistakes.
Is he for real?
Congratulations, Daddy!
We just heard the good news.
How many are
there?
Umm.. Three?
No, look, there are four.
And they're so cute.
Showoffs!
More victims to perish in
this godforsaken place.
To perish? Oh...
Sorry! Sorry!
Gus! We should be happy for him
instead of saying stuff like that.
It's so beautiful they've been
born in a place like this...
Felix, we're going to throw pine cones
at the electrified fence.
Wanna come?
No, I told Lynxette
I'd show her the shelter.
See you Gus.
When we get out,
I'll show you some places.
That would be great!
Look! The
tracking station.
Let me show you.
What's that?
When they let us go,
they put a bracelet on us
so they know where
to find us if there's a problem.
Watch this, it's fun
They've got quite a file on you.
Yes, but I apply Felix's law,
"Smile, tomorrow could be worse".
Now wasn't that bad luck?
The heating's on
in this weather!
Your luck could be changing.
- I don't think so
- You met me.
Would you accept a gift?
That way I'll always know
where to find you.
In that case, I won't mind feeling
like I'm being followed.
I'm sorry I spoke to you
the way I did the first day.
I wish we'd met
outside this place.
We'll be out soon,
as long as Gus is wrong
and nothing happens...
That's better.
Almost like home,
right, Nimrod?
You're impatient, too,
hey, buddy?
Get the men together.
Tonight we're going HUNTING.
Activate silent mode!
Now turn out all the lights.
Sorry! It's ok.
Oh, groovy!
Put me down!
You've got to be nice to me!
Death grip. Gotcha.
- Ready. Tower 1 all clear.
Tower 5 all clear.
Tower 3 all clear.
West alarm deactivated.
I knew I was going to have to
keep an eye on those two.
- I feel dizzy!
- Come on.
Pure precision innit,
right on the nerve!
Guard out of action, sir,
according to prior instructions
...given during training sessions.
You can be such an idiot! Elite soldiers
like us talk in short, concise sentences.
Oh, okay.
Guy groggy, following plan.
Much better.
Approaching computer.
Looking for the security control
panel in order to access...
SHORT sentences!
Mr Newman, outer gate open,
proceeding to open inner gate.
- Something's wrong!
- One alarm is still connected.
We can't open the inner gate.
Formatting mega-ram register...
I've GOT IT,
the map of the shelter...
...right, let's see.
Oh look! Danger!
We've got to warn the others!
Attention! We've discovered
land mines in the courtyard!
Any movement could be fatal.
Number 1, don't take another step.
Relax, I'll guide you through.
You've got one...
RIGHT IN FRONT OF YOU!
Okay, Let's see.
One step backwards... and another
one...you're almost there...
Mmstghll...
...and...stop.
Oh-oh!
We've got a casualty.
What in blazes is going on NOW??
Boss! The security measures are
tougher than we thought.
...shall we continue with the operation?
- Morons!
On my signal, pick me up
in the courtyard!
...get out of it!
I want a go.
Hello sir! We've deactivated
almost all of them...
I knew you two would...
He pushed me!
I dunno. It was him..
Sir, we'll just hang about
Just in case you need us.
Watch your step sir, there
are land mines everywhere.
You idiots.
Hey, who are you?
What's going on?
All the personnel is out of action.
Go get the animals!
Now hurry up, boys! And remember.
The boss made me master.
Head of logistics, mind you. Whatever that is.
So altogether now. C'mon, one, two...
Ooh, dear. I gotta go.
Don't be late. I want all the animals out
and loaded in the trucks in ten minutes.
Typical. I just knew I'd
end up lifting boxes!
Now. The boss said we should secure
each cage and tie them down twice.
I don't think any cages are gonna fall.
I mean, that would be
really unlucky.
...the union rules say something
about lunch break.
What's going on?
Oh, no! Lynxette!
I've got to help them!
Thats all of them. Lets go!
Lynxette!
Ok, I'm coming!
I'm done here. Hey! You do something
for a change! Get the rope!
I'll take care of the wheels.
"Be a masked soldier", they said!
"Live an adventurous life, travel to exotic lands..."
Yeah right! They never said
anything about working!
Careful!
That's it. Six of you get in the
helicopter. The rest back to the truck.
And they say they don't
want me to become extinct!
Come on... Felix...
Faster!
Betty, they're kidnapping us!
Get over to the other truck and
wake up as many animals as you can.
Try these keys!
Sounds good to me!
I accept the mission!
Geronimo!
Come to mamma,
little truckie wuckie!
Three... Two... One...
Mr. Newman, I think
an animal has just escaped.
What a disaster!
Be prepared my friend,
I think you have work to do!
...Turn on the head lights
- Yes sir!
Yeah! I've always wanted to do that!
Yes, Her Majesty, the agent Gus...
GUS! Wake up! I don't know
where they're taking us.
What? You see? You see?
I told you!
Astarté, wake up!
You've got to fly to the shelter
and set off one of the alarms.
But my wing... I don't think
I can fly that far yet.
Astarté, you've got to try.
You're the only one who's fast
enough to fly back to the shelter.
I'm eager to fly again, but I don't
know that I'm fully recovered yet.
and the shelter is far away!
Well... Technically, you hawks reach
speeds of 250 kilometers per hour...
Astarté...
We need you to try.
The skies are waiting for you.
I'll do it
You will? Yeah!
Well, time to take to the skies again!
I'd almost forgotten how
much I love to fly.
Lynxette, wake up! We're being
kidnapped.
What...what's going on?
We're being kidnapped!
But don't worry, I'm going
to get you out of here.
I'm not worried.
What!
Aye!
Don't let her escape, Nimrod.
She's all yours.
Astarté!
Good job!
Felix!
Gus!
You have to help him!
He could be killed.
My tongue!
Open the cage and jump!
Don't worry Gus,
I gotcha!
I'm slipping
Good bye cruel world!
Gus!
Just what I needed.
A kidney stone!
I think... I... ran over
another animal... again
Any more mistakes and I'll rip your
throat out with my bare hands!
Lynxette!
Jump!
No! I have to free the rest!
Darn it! That female
lynx is the top priority.
Nooo!!
No,
Ey, Boss... l... think...
Never mind
They weren't keeping us prisoners
They were protecting us, Gus!
Thats the reason for the towers
and the fences...
Yeah, tell that to "mister
conspiracy" here,
What a fuss he made!
Well, if they were protecting us,
they did a pretty poor job.
What happened to Astarté?
She won't be able to do acrobatics for a while
...but she'll be all right.
She's a tough old bird.
So now what?
I think you guys should go back to
the shelter, Astarté needs some care.
I still have to
save the others.
What? Go back?
That's not an option.
If we go back to the shelter
we'll never get out of there again!
For a paranoid green thing with
camouflage problems,
you're quite right for once.
My friend, you're not going to get
rid of us that easy!
Yes, indeed! This is too
exciting to miss.
Mr. Newman?
How did the mission go?
We had a few SETBACKS!
We've only achieved
90% of the objectives.
Oh! But do you have the lynxes?
Only the female. But we'll go back for
the rest if we don't have any more...
MISHAPS.
No, no, no. Let's just stick to the plan.
We'll meet at Bolonia
Beach at dawn.
I'll be there.
and please accept my
apologies, Mister Noah.
Operation "Search and Rescue"
it's about to get under way!
Oh, fine! And tell me just how do we
find them, "super secret agent" Gus?
Hey wait a minute...
Lynxette!
- WHAT?
- No, I mean the bracelet!
I gave her one of those
locators they put on us.
Of course! The tracking devices
are back at the shelter!
Mmm! Wrong!
One: We've already said
we can't get back there!
...and Two: You gave her a WHAT?
- Gus, not now.
Are you mad? You'll be trapped
for the rest of your ife!
Just look at him.
He's having a fit.
Wait a minute...
I think I have the solution.
Whatever would we do
without you, Gus.
I must confess that considering
your reputation, and the size of your fee.
I was expecting a
flawless operation.
The setbacks were due more
to problems with the...
"human resources"
than to my hunting skills.
STOP!
I told you to check the cages
carefully, one by one.
Do you wanna get caught?
A slip-up like that could lead them
to us and ruin the whole plan!
Oh, sorry, I can add or change
the personnel if you wish.
No, this bunch of idiots will be more than
enough to capture your little critters.
Their ineptitude will just make
the job more... challenging
Hey, number eight, give us
a hand down here.
After all these years of hard work,
my master plan is ready.
Look.
I had no idea the
scope of this operation.
This looks quite fancy.
Who could we help?
Let's see...
THEM!
You are so useless, let me try.
This is like the fair ground game.
I was always good at that.
We'll finish the inventory today
and draw up the report
of all the animals we've still got to catch
- And the ones that got away?
Don't worry. I've already
thought of something.
- Give it back!
- It's my turn!
...the animals that're missing.
When I've got them all...
- What did I tell you?
- They did come highly recommended!
I quiiiit!
Loading of cargo finished.
Oh, brilliant!
I know only one way
to do things...
BIG.
Mmm?
As I said before, don't worry about
the animals that escaped.
I found someone else
to handle the problem.
I have a meeting with
him this afternoon.
Somebody bring me my briefcase.
About time.
Gotcha, you crazy old man.
Let's see what
you're cooking up.
There's nobody there!
Who the heck are you talking to?
Have you lost your mind and
now you talk to yourself?
What's going on here?
Come on! Whatever happened to
the adventure, the "Search and Rescue"?
How long have we been walking?
A week?
One: Not even ten hours,
Two...
We've stopped over twenty
times because of you.
Let's go Gus, We have to hurry before
the masked men get too far away.
No, not "masked".
"Evil secret paramilitaty
organization".
He really doesn't shut up.
It's like listening to a scratched record!
Yeah, we're making good time...
with a bit of luck...
That's it. A little bit of luck!
Just what I'm missing...
We'd better rest for a bit.
We really need it!
Don't worry, if everything goes alright,
your little ones will be safe.
Mr. Noah, if you don't mind,
I'd like to get started as soon as possible.
Young people are always
in such a rush!
We have almost all the animals and
only need a rare kind of bat,
and most importantly, wolves.
But yesterday the most important
animals were the lynxes!
Yesterday was yesterday
Today is today.
If lynxes were hard to find,
wolves are even more elusive.
We've been searching
for months to no avail.
You have to go to
an area called "El Torca"
where you will find
the long legged bat we need.
Then, you'll continue on to the
"Sierra Morena" for a pair of wolves.
We will reconvene at the new pick up point
and your mission will be over.
I'll take it from there.
- Ok, and what about the...
- You are very stubborn!
Forget about the escaped animals!
I put up the money, you HUNT!
When the time comes, follow
my instructions to the letter,
and everything will be fine.
Now, if you don't mind,
I'd like to be alone.
I have to hurry up!
Back on land!
...my teddy!
Aww!
There we are.
I was born to be a father.
Calling all moles!
Brothers, I have
a job for you!
Alpha 1 Red, negative!
Unit 3, Red B, negative!
Gamma 5, Blue C, neg...
I found them. Alpha 2 Blue C,
direction Alpha 2, Red B.
I bet we've followed
the wrong tracks.
They were the tracks
that most look like them.
It must've been another truck
with similar tyres driving the other way.
The chicken just woke up!
Betty was able to save you
in the nick of time.
Thanks, I owe you one.
Astarté, I'm sorry
about what happened.
I'm the one that's sorry!
"You can get to the shelter"
..."Everything's going to be all right"
Watch it!
He did what he thought was best for everyone.
Maybe better for him, but not for me.
Ey, be cool!
I finally found you.
And you? Where have you been?
Bro?
You're not going to believe it!
But I woke up in a big boat where a crazy
old man is collecting hundreds of animals.
I pushed my cage 'til it
fell and the door broke.
I wanted to free my family and the rest,
but the boat started moving,
so I thought I should
escape and go for help.
My family's still on board!
We have to go back and rescue them!
But you don't even know
where the ship is.
I did hear part of the plan, though.
I heard something about
wolves at Sierra Morena.
They're going to meet somewhere else
as soon as the man has all his animals.
But they still can't
find the wolves.
When they find them,
they'll all go
in a boat
to a far away island!
If we warn the wolves,
we can delay the ship's departure
and we'll have time to find it. - Great!
- Whaddya think? - Great idea.
And you?
Alright, count me in.
Oh, excuse me!
I told her a hundred times
but she still doesn't get it.
Sorry about that!
I say, Rosie!
Fly somewhere else,
you're putting me off.
So, is this lake you're
talking about, very far?
No. But it's going to seem
like an eternity!
Close your eyes, dear, so you'll get the
full effect when you first see it!
Let's go girls.
We'll migrate tomorrow.
Say something.
I'm getting bored.
Oh! I see what this is.
It's hide and go seek.
Well, ready or not,
here I come!
Hundred, ninety eight, ninety one one...
I'm here!
What's this?
Move over little ratties!
I'm going to take my space!
Let's see now.
That's better.
Hello!
And they say I'm a rare species!
I'm off for a bite.
Don't know what's up with
old grumbleguts today.
I'm sure glad we didn't have
to go wolf hunting with him.
Absolutely. If I had to choose between
wolves and bats... bats, anyday!
Look. That might be it.
One of the most precious gifts
quiropters have to offer
can be found on the
cave floor.
Err, the only thing I can see is this mud.
The guano, bat excrement,
is highly prized,
as fertilizer.
"The long legged bat is one
of the most peculiar bats"
It's peculiar alright.
"It has disproportionately long legs"
It's definitely got long legs.
...it's just the color
seems  a little odd.
Well, if it was black
it wouldn't be peculiar, would it?
It'd just be like any other bat.
So, Let's proceed to the most
delicate part of the operation.
Capturing the beast!
'Ullo!
Umm.
We're gonna get a medal the
size of a frying pan, I'm telling you.
Did you hear a helicopter?
Come on Gus!
You're slowing us down.
Don't you find it suspicious?
I've got a bad feeling
about this!
They're here!
We're surrounded!
Oops, sorry!
Gus, will you stop
being so paranoid?
Aaargh!
You and your
persecution complex!
Oh, sure, "the chameleon is crazy"
"the chameleon is seeing things".
Get ready to run
in case it's those hunters.
Don't come any closer.
You smell of humans.
What are you?
Some kind of wild cat?
I AM NOT... a tame animal.
Watch that tone of voice!
You're almost a cat and
I'm almost a dog...
and you know what humans
say about cats and dogs.
We're looking for the
leader of your pack.
We have vital information which we'll
only reveal in absolute confidentiality.
I'm one of the protectors of the pack,
and I don't know why we should
trust such a bunch of oddballs.
You've got to listen to us...
or soon you won't have a pack to protect.
You'd sound more convincing
if your voice stopped trembling.
But I don't smell a traitor.
I'll call a meeting of the pack's council.
But if anything goes wrong
you'll be sorry!
Here we are!
No human has ever
been in this place.
I'm not surprised!
We'll be safe here.
This is our most secret place.
This is amazing!
Hey, what's wrong with you?
Nothing... I just miss my family.
Don't you worry, everything's
going to be all right.
It's impossible!
Humans!
Quick! There's a rear exit
that leads to the gorge!
Wouldn't it be better
to give ourselves up?
We don't stand a chance.
Run!
Got 'im!
...and now for some
target practice!
Wolf!
LYNX?
GOAT!
Didn't we knock
you out already?
Ok, first you...
and then the rest.
Bring the cages for
the wolves.
Yes sir, the other
group has arrived.
Perfect, then we only have to take
care of that little group of rebels.
Are you pulling my leg?
Nobody's that dumb!
Who do you think you're kidding?
This isn't a
long legged bat, is it.
This one has stubby legs,
and the color's all wrong!
We're looking for a GREY bat.
- It's yours.
- What? No it isn't!
Throwaway!
And you two?
What about you two?
D'you got anything for me?
Who us, no. Nothing at all, we didn't
capture anything batty whatsoever!
No. Maybe you could, I dunno,
...try next door?
So if it's not a bat,
what is it?
Finally! At least somebody
knows what they're doing!
Mr Newman,
have you got the wolves?
Yes, they were right where
you said they would be...
but something strange is
going on here...
I saw those animals
that got away here too!
...I don't understand it!
You don't need to understand anything.
Just follow my orders, and we
shall finish the job in no time.
Hmm?
Hey Boss, you dropped
your phone.
Here.
He scares me.
Oh, you poor boy...
They said it was impossible
for them to find us there!
It's got to be my fault!
There's no other explanation.
Don't worry!
I'm sure it's not you.
No? Something bad happens
to everyone close to me...
Lynxette, Astarté, you...
How do you explain my accidents?
I mean, how did they find us
in the middle of no where!
Maybe it was just dumb luck they found us.
Yeah, right. My dumb bad luck.
How else could it have happened?
Wait a minute!
Of course... It all fits!
They implanted
microchips in our brains,
and they can follow every move
we make with a spy satellite.
Oh, no. Please!
Not again, Gus!
Haven't you learned anything
after what happened at the shelter?
The only microchips are the ones
in the bracelets at the shelter.
Not bracelets!
Nanobots!
They drop them in your ears
when you're sleeping.
I've got an idea!
Humans are such pigs.
That's it.
Just in case...
Just try to
locate us now!
Let me out!
Let me out of here!
I wish you knew how it feels
to be held prisoner in a cage.
Believe me, I do know.
But there's a very good reason why
you are locked in a cage.
Do you... You can...
understand me?
Oh, yes, you and all the rest
of the animals.
But we shouldn't talk about
this in here, right?
Bring the cage 2203
to my cabin!
What else could we do?
It was the only way to shut him up.
What a great idea!
A stroll in the desert!
Hey, It wasn't my idea!
We only know what Rupert told us.
- Who decided I was the leader?
- I would've voted for you Felix!
You got us into this mess!
Chill, you guys!
Impressive, now that's flying.
Yes, but it gives me
the heebe jeebes.
Where is he going?
Hey mister vulture!
We're not dead yet!
Make room, make room!
Tin foil!
Yellow bin!
Just a sec!
I can't believe the things
people throw away!
It's brand new!
This one goes to the
electric assorted section.
Oh, please!
Don't touch a thing!
There's enough meat
here for a full meal,
and a couple light dinners.
I don't know why
you're looking so disgusted!
You eat FLIES!
- Mister vulture...
- Diogenes, young fellow.
- We're looking for the beach.
- It's that way...
Make room!
What is all this?
Good question.
We're tidying up the place.
- Who, them?
- Oh, no they're just interns.
We have to educate the
new generations
No, no. I'm talking about THEM.
Sometimes, those bipeds
do something worth while.
Now calm down!
How can you talk with us?
Ah, that's a secret!
And it should continue
to be one.
I've always felt closer to your kind
than to humans.
And that's why you hunt us down
and keep us in cages?
What have we done
to deserve this?
Nothing at all. Actually, everything
I have is thanks to you.
When I was a child, I talked
with the animals as all children do.
But unlike the others,
when I grew up,
I never lost that ability.
It was that simple!
I wasn't bitten by
some radioactive animal.
My problems began when I
tried to tell people about it.
No one believed me.
They thought I was crazy
and they locked me up.
What nonsense! How could anyone
talk with the animals?
Those were the worst
years of my life.
So, I kept my secret.
I found more people
with the same ability.
And I knew then I had
to use my gift to help you.
And this is your way
of helping us?
Let me explain!
I started small.
It's easy to win at the track
when you get your information
...straight from
the horses mouth!
I tried other ventures, that is
also easy if you have a little help.
Things were working out
pretty well!
You know what they say...
"money gets money"
And that's how I built
my little empire.
Thanks in part to you.
So, to thank you all,
I thought up my little plan...
THIS plan!
Mr Newman?
How's the mission going?
It's a desert here!
There isn't an animal in...
They've got to be near by.
I'm afraid not, we've scouted
out the whole area and...
There they are,
Mr. Newman.
How the blazes does
the old guy do it?
What about you?
And what brings you here?
They're after us!
Yes, they're following us, but
relax, you really should learn Tai Chi!
Bad news. The hunter brought that
black hawk with him!
That's not bad news, this is
the moment I've been waiting for.
Heed not the voice of revenge
for it will lead you astray.
Oh shut up,
you bug eyed beetle eater.
Where's your circus,
bearded lady?
This from a lunatic lizzard.
At least I don't butt
heads for sport.
- Reptile!
- Ruminent!
- Big mouth.
- Horn head.
- Scaly skin.
- Fur bag.
We're not fast enough
to run away,...
Diogenes, could we use
some of your stuff?
Of course, my boy.
Anything you can recycle is yours!
Could someone distract the soldiers
and get one of those flying curtains?
Me! Me! Me! Me!
Me-me-me!
You can muzzle me.
I'm your go to goat!
He never lets me
do anything!
This is going to be
so much fun!
Old buddy, today we both
finish what we started...
NOW Nimrod!
Come on, dummy!
We're falling behind!
What do you want me to do?
Pedal?
Oh, lookit! You've got
an engine behind you!
Oh, right!
There she is!
Hoowee, I'm here!
Careful, strong winds up here!
What a cool goat!
You see that!
Get her!
Look! They're shooting!
Get your rifle and earn your keep!
What's going on?
Wake up!
I'm pretty sure no-one
saw that.
Wake up!
Today, boys and girls, with all this
stuff, a couple of rubber bands
and our own little hands, we're gonna
build an extraordinary device
...to escape from the bad guys.
- We don't have time for jokes, Gus.
We could do with some help.
And we say good bye with
the tip... GUS!!
Come on! Come on!
We don't have all day!
But what is he doing?
Oh, what a shame!
I missed!
Yellow belly bird!
Boss, we should leave
right away. The wind is changing.
Turn around. If the goat escapes,
we're doomed.
Got you now!
You won't get away this time...
- You don't see that every day.
- Ooh!
I'm sorry Felix. I went a little crazy
when I thought I'd never fly again.
It's Ok, I'm so happy
you're all better.
Thanks, some things are
more important than flying.
...like friends you can trust.
Wow! What's this!
I'm sure everybody's going to get
an 'A' in 'Show and Tell'.
You didn't forget to bring what
Felix asked you to, did you?
Of course not!
Here IT IS!
We'll continue on the ground.
Pick us up later at the windfarm.
I don't think so, we can't fly...
- PICK ME UP THERE!
Felix, hurry up!
You have to go.
Thanks for everything.
Is everybody ready?
Uh hm.
Good luck, my friends!
And who are you?
I'm a long legged bat.
I used to be a masked henchmen
but it didn't really work out.
Are you looking for a job?
Uh hm.
The wind's picking up!
OK, Betty, now!
She's working!
Climb up Felix!
Felix, no!
Stop! You've got to stop this thing!
I can't, it's going too fast!
It's not his fault.
If I go with you,
they'll catch us sooner or later.
Without me, you'll all be safe.
There's no excuse for what you've done.
Oh, but there is, the end justify the means:
to avoid your ultimate demise.
But at what price?
You can't just capture us
and hold us here because you feel like it.
Being held in cages for a little while
is a small price to pay
when you face extintion.
Soon we will take you to an island
far away from humans
where you can all live safely.
But that's still a prison.
There must be another way...
Like what?
Partial solutions don't work.
Who many of you lynxes are left?
Someone has to do something about it.
Tell me: what's the point of being free
...if you're not alive?
But what's the point of being alive
if you're not free.
You were caged once,
would you like to be locked up again?
Do you see?
Felix didn't have
anything to do with it!
We were going to get caught anyway.
We're losing speed.
Screaming Eagles Squadron to the rescue.
Ready? Bombs away!
Eagles! Eagles!
Eagles forming for a second run.
Please, please, can I?
Permission to join the party granted!
Oh, go on them.
What?
A few little droppings
are not going to stop us from...
I can't believe it!
Escape plan now!
This is the end!
Not if I can help it!
Stupid goat!
Now it's really the end!
Betty, wake up!
Rupert, I need you.
Where'd he go?
Astarté! Astarté! Wake up!
This is a very delicate situation,
It's the perfect mission for Gus.
You can't fail,
everything depends on you.
Mimetic abilities in order.
Just try to find me now,
butterfly hunter.
Rupert! What are you doing here?
I have... something to tell you.
I thought I was helping you...
and "Operation Mole" is still on...
Mole?
Well, I liked the play on words.
I needed to find the
animals that got away
and who better than a mole to be... a "mole"!
How could you?
So I made a deal with him.
Freedom for his family
in exchange for information.
After all, moles aren't
in danger of extinction.
I tagged him with a microchip
and I let him go
so he could find the wolves
and then indicate the position
of the escaped animals to the hunter.
I'm really not a bad person...
You what?
I'm sorry, but I didn't have a choice.
They didn't find us because
you're unlucky,
but because of me.
So it wasn't my fault after all.
Hey.
Wait!
Good, you're just
the one I needed
to complete the set.
I don't think I'm gonna need this.
This is small game.
Kitty, kitty.
Come here kitty.
Finally.
No!
What?
Mr Newman? Stop the operation.
We have to re-think the whole plan.
Get ready little kitty, because you're gonna
become extinct for sure now.
But first, let's renegotiate
the contract with that old man.
That's enough!
There's no sense crying over spilt milk!
The important thing now is to find the ship.
We have ways to make traitors talk...
Hold on! I don't know where the ship is.
They were supposed to capture us
and take us there.
So?
Well, there's a way to find it.
The inter-mole network.
Mr. Newman.
I just was trying to contact you.
Things have changed...
Yes, they have, a lot!
I'm in command now!
Are you crazy? You can't do this...
You work for me... You can't... Nooo.
Let me out of here right now!
Please! Let me out!
Please!
- I can't stand being locked up!
- Shut up.
I've had just about enough of
your excentric millionaire nonsense!
Now you're gonna find out
what real hunting is!
Not this stupid game.
Explain all this to me right now!
Or do you want an even smaller cage?
They've locator microchips.
They're the green signals
And this is us right here, isn't it?
Well, either that stupid cat
is a real fool
or the call of the
wild is too strong
and our little
lynx is in love.
I saw how he ran after you when
I captured you.
Fine. Let's prepare him a
little welcome party.
Everybody over here!
NOW!
I've never used such
rebellious bait!
Everything is ready, sir!
Knock the caged animals
out with a little gas.
We have to be ready for
a very special guest!
The lynx is mine,
and the rest are yours!
Well, the master of camouflage
can go and assess the situation.
As the master's camouflage is a bit dodgy,
I'll fly ahead and see what I can find out.
Lynxette!
Astarté!
Am I glad to see you!
It's ok, we're all here!
Not a move until they're
all in here together.
Don't you know the meaning
of the word SILENCE?
We'll get you out of here!
Careful, stay away from the center of the cargo bay,
...the hunters are hidden there,
and it's full of dangerous booby traps,
and you've got to free the old man.
I think he'll help us.
Rupert will know how to find him.
So what'd you see?
- Lynxette is all right.
- What about the rest?
There're all sedated
but they're fine.
Lynxette told me what to do.
You're not going to start doing
the chameleon thing now are you?
You are such a party pooper!
It's Lynxette, over there!
Wait! Remember the traps!
Now.
Take the ship out to open sea.
That way they can't escape.
Fasten your seat belts!
It's going to be a bumpy ride.
Rupert!
Throw us a life saver!
It's on your right side!
To the left!
To the right!
My right!
Not yet! Not yet!
Uhh! Ohh!
What are they waiting for!
Noo!
Betty!
She's gone! And there were so
many things I wanted to tell her!
Hello!
Oh! Did my sweet little
green thingy miss me!
Who, me? You gotta be kidding.
- Oh my little sweety!
- Put me down!
Where are they going?
You, follow the hawk!
What a strange mission! And the worst part is
dealing with those two. Supposedly on our side.
I have a plan...
Excuse me!
- That's the goat I ran over!
- We need reinforcements!
We've got three of them here!
What kind of plan is this!
Plans are for sissies!
Are you the guy who
can talk with animals?
Say something!
Anything!
- Watch out!
- Rather limited vocabulary.
Get the remote, quick!
Where are the reinforcements?
We're so important, they need
reinforcements!
Why're you looking at me
like that?
What are you doing!!
Get the remooooote!
How humilliating!
You used me!
The black button!
At the bottom!
Do I have to do everything
myself? Give it to me!
I'll think twice before getting
on your nerves again!
What? Me? I haven't
moved a muscle!
Me? Are you mad?
Just look at me!
I guess this isn't where they
asked for reinforcements, is it?
I guess not.
I won't tell if you won't.
Do you want to see something
really cool?
Don't even think about it! Remember
how mad the boss was the last time.
Oh, hush. You're such a wet blanket.
What's happening to me?
I never miss.
Please, don't touch anything!
Listen to the old man and
stop pressing buttons!
The guards at the entrance told me
this was really cool.
That's not it!
Look, Felix is in danger!
You can't go now! Wait!
And voilá!
That's the ambiance look!
Oh, look at that! My word! Absolutely fabulous!
Not me!
Wait! Look there!
Oh! What beauty!
What prodigious technique!
Stop! Stop! Look at that!
Sublime!
You can see the tragic
solitude of the human soul
through the desperate
deformation of the anatomy.
Look! Look at that!
Don't you see it?
What power! What a magnificent
symbiosis of art with african roots
and the exquisite flat
composition.
Analytic is what I see.
Are you mad? The chromatic is...
Talk to the hand!
Here kitty, kitty! Where are you?
Come out here!
Ah ha!
Calm down! Remember,
attention, patience, concentration...
It can't be!
All those lights.
I wonder what it says there?
WE'RE SINKING!
Quick! Get me out
of here!
Yes, sir. Right now!
Well, that's one way of
forcing you out of hiding.
We have to check the extent
of the damage!
You're kidding?
No, but this ship is supossed
to be prepared for situations like this.
In fact, the evacuation
is already under way.
Let's go.
Get out of the way!
Perfect! everything is
working fine.
Now we have to get
into our life rafts topside.
What about Felix?
I'll make it easier for him.
Hey, something seems to be
blocking the hatch.
It's not working.
Nothing!
I'm sorry, Rupert...
Rupert?
Look!
Thanks buddy!
It was the least I could do. Now if you'll
excuse me, I've another job to do.
Super Rupert
to the rescue!
It's extinction time!
What the...?
Good move.
Oh, no, Gus!!
You stupid primate!
Get your human
paws off my friend!
You don't know
who you're dealing with!
Let me go! Let me at him!
I'll knock his block off!
We're not finished yet!
If anybody's going to get hurt,
that'll be me!
Everything bad always
happens to me.
You're not going to catch me
off guard this time! No,little kitty!
Admit it, Felix!
You can't fight bad luck.
It's your destiny.
Felix, you're a magnet for
accidents.
Felix and his bad luck!
Felix!
I'm ok!
I'm kind of used
to this by now.
But he's not.
I guess you're not as tame
as I thought after all.
Come on! We've got
to get off the ship.
I'm trapped!
He's gonna drown!
You're worried about him?
Felix! We're running out of time.
I can't reach...
THIS!
I'm Newman!
The best hunter in the world!
I always win!
No animal can beat me!
I'm Newman!
Felix...
My dream has come to an end.
My perfect plan.
Although, wait a minute!
What if I created an island just for humans
and then we could put them alto...
Nevermind.
Don't give up!
We're coming! Don't despair!
Oh, no! They've seen us!
We're doomed!
Sink the raft! Sink it I tell you!
Oi! Hello!
There's just no
understanding some people!
I don't get it.
We're out of a job again, aren't we.
Ah, don't worry!
Something'll come up!
Thanks, I can't believe
what you did for us.
That bracelet wouldn't have
been much help locating you.
I know.
But that's not why I kept it.
I kept it because
you gave it to me.
Hey, hey! Wait a minute!
Can I be the best man?
Please!
What?
The new Gus is nice!
And no more paranoias!
Really!
Congratulations!
You are a brave animal.
Now I see my plan
didn't make much sense.
If all lynxes are
as brave as you are,
not even the great flood
could make you extinct.
He's a jinxed lynx!
But he's OUR jinxed lynx!
This is the end!
Good bye freedom!
So long hunting nights!
...Bye bye to adventures...
Now don't spoil the moment!
- Would you do the honours uncle Gus?
- Me?
Amazing!
Doc, this is too good!
I still can't believe it,
but it looks like we have a new lynx cub!
And born free in the wild!
You'll see... This is going to be
a really cushy job.
Here, wait a minute! Haven't we seen
this lynx somewhere before?
I don't know, they all
look the same to me.
The same? Each lynx is unique!
- Unique?
What do you know about unique?
Don't you start on me! Don't push me!...
If you don't mind, miss,
would you please give me a ticket
on the very next plane to
anywhere in Africa.
No! No! Kitties no! Kitties no!
Keep him away from me! Kitties no!
Watch Movies, TV Series and Live Sports
Signup Here -> WWW.ADMITME.APP