(DISCO MUSIC PLAYING)
Hey, hey
Let's sweat!
Macho, macho man
Macho man
Come on!
l've got to be
That's right!
Shake it, honey!
A macho man
Macho, macho man
Oh, yeah! Like a pony!
l'm a pony!
l've got to be a macho
Don't you feel like
a pony when you sweat?
Oh, yeah! Yeah!
Go! Do it!
Come on! Here we go!
(MUSIC CONTINUES)
One! Two!
This is my favorite exercise!
Come on! Five!
Whoa!
Macho, macho man
Macho! Macho! Oh!
l've got to be
l'm a pony!
A macho man
(ELECTRONIC SNORTING)
Come on, let's go!
Do it! Come on!
l've got to be a macho
(MUSIC CONTINUES)
l'm vogueing!
You can vogue!
Can you feel it?
l've got to be a macho man
Oh!
l'm going to have
an aneurysm.
Oh!
My calves are burning!
This is our
science department.
The genetics wing.
l'll remind you we are
in the vanguard of research.
(CHUCKLES)
(PEOPLE SCREAMING)
(SCREAMING CONTINUES)
(TIRES SCREECHING)
Get Klump in here now!
BOY 1 : Professor Klump.
Good morning.
GIRL 1 : Hey, Professor!
BOY 2: Morning.
Morning.
GIRL 2: Good morning,
Professor Klump.
How are you?
Morning.
(SCREAMING CONTINUES)
(BLOWER ENGINE STARTS)
(SCREAMING)
Oh, my goodness.
Professor Klump. The cages.
What happened?
That is most peculiar, Jason,
because l distinctly remember
locking up last night.
l locked these cages,
picked up my portfolio
and turned around...
(STUDENTS GASPING
AND CHATTERING)
Oh.
l must've grazed the switch.
Shelley's the only one
that didn't get out.
Good. l'll tend to Shelley.
You students take care
of this. Excuse me.
Hello, Shelley.
How are you today,
my little powder puff?
Yeah. Yeah.
(MURMURING BABY TALK)
Sir?
You may want to look
at the latest test results.
l'm not sure
if l'm reading them correctly.
She's lost three ounces
since the last feed?
Must be some kind
of mistake.
(KEYBOARD KEYS CLICKING)
No, no, Jason.
Her entire molecular structure
has been realigned.
We've done it.
This new formula's working.
lt's actually reconstructed
Shelley's DNA.
She lost 20%
of her body fat
in one feeding.
What if we upped
the dosage?
No, one step at a time.
We don't want
to jeopardize Shelley.
We'll keep the feedings
as scheduled.
Okay.
Schedule. Excuse me.
l'm very late.
Students, we got
a lot of work to do
and don't have much time
to do it in.
Trying to win a grant here.
So, as Arsenio used to say,
"Let's get busy!"
(SWITCHES LEVER)
(STUDENTS CHATTERING)
(RUSTLING AND SQUEAKING)
(CLEARS THROAT AND GRUNTS)
(EXHALES SLOWLY)
Comfy?
Quite.
Anything l can get for you?
Juice? Coffee? Rack of lamb?
No, sir, l'm fine.
(SNIFFS)
(CLEARS THROAT)
You did want to see me
about something,
didn't you, sir?
Well, Professor Klump,
allow me
to answer that question
by posing another.
Why are you trying
to destroy my school?
Beg your pardon, sir?
Do you know who
Louise Vindovik is?
Oh, surely, sir.
She's a lovely woman
who so generously
donates money
to help fund
our science department.
Close. Very close.
But wrong.
See, she was a lovely woman,
and she used to fund
our science department.
That was before
she was hospitalized
for nearly swallowing
a gerbil.
Not gerbil, sir. A hamster.
Gerbils are more streamlined
and hamsters have
a tendency to be fluffier.
The male hamster's scrotum
has a tendency
to be
disproportionately...
Never mind.
Those National Rifle people
are right.
lf l had one now...bang.
Sir, l'd like to concentrate
on the positives.
What Miss Vindovik witnessed
was 5,000 healthy hamsters
bred from a genetically
deficient hereditary line.
lt's actually very exciting.
Do l look excited, Klump?
No, you don't look
excited at all.
But maybe you might
be holding it in,
your excitement,
not wanting to express it.
Now listen to me carefully,
you fat tub of goo.
For years you've
single-handedly alienated
every wealthy donor we've had.
Air-conditioning schools
are outdrawing us!
We've lost so much money,
red is our school color.
lnner-city schools have
better computers than we do.
Bosnia wants
to give us money!
l'm going to set up a meeting
with Harlan Hartley...
Klump! Are you listening?
Yes, sir. Yes.
Hartley is the last
rich alumnus we've got.
And he's a science fan.
And he's considering
donating a $10 million grant
to this school.
And l want that money, Klump.
Yourjob depends upon it.
l'll let you know
how to handle it,
since l'll be watching you.
Now go.
But, sir, l don't know
if you should...
See, right back there,
just before you said
"But, sir" right there?
That was the end
of the meeting.
Well, l guess l'll leave.
You have a pleasant day.
Grace, the cream
has turned again.
(GASPS)
PROFESSOR:
Of all the equations
you'll learn
during the course
of your studies here,
this equation shall be,
l promise you,
the most helpful
throughout the course
of your studies,
because this equation
fundamentally breaks down
what DNA is composed of,
and what components of DNA...
(GIGGLING CONTINUES)
(LOUDER LAUGHTER)
l seem to have messed myself.
l haven't really
messed myself.
l mean,
l messed my shirt up.
(SCHOOL BELL RINGS)
But make sure
you read chapter 4
in your textbooks
on genetics.
Gonna be a pop quiz
on Wednesday.
There's a pop quiz. Pop quiz.
WOMAN: Professor Klump?
(MUMBLING) Hello.
Oh. Hi. l'm sorry.
l didn't mean to interrupt.
l was looking
for Professor Klump.
(SPITTING)
l'm him. l'm he.
l'm Sherman Klump.
(GUM BALLS SCATTERING)
Never mind.
l do that all the time.
Makes the...table look
more festive,
and the kids enjoy it.
The yellow and green
and purple rolling around.
The table's more colorful
and...
Would another time be better?
l could always...
No, no, don't be ridiculous.
l'm between classes
and l got a minute to chat.
(GUM BALLS SCATTERING)
How can l help you?
Hi. l'm Carla Purty.
Hello, Miss Purty.
l'm a grad student.
l'm teaching
my first chemistry class
across the hall.
Okay.
l just had to come over
and introduce myself.
l've followed your work
for many years,
and l'm a big fan.
Well, thank you very much.
l'm fatter...
Flattered that you've
been following my work
the way you have.
A chemistry teacher.
Chemistry sure is important
to have...chemistry...
to have and use it.
Chemically... Chemistry.
Well...
(SCHOOL BELL RINGS)
lt's been a pleasure
meeting you.
Oh, the pleasure was all mine,
Miss Purty.
And hope to see you around.
Well, you can't miss me.
(CHUCKLES)
Have a good day.
You do the same, Miss Purty.
Mmm-mmm.
(DOOR CLOSES)
Now, that's fine. She's fine.
(GUM BALLS SCATTERING)
(LAUGHING)
Oh, this is so fabulous.
Ain't nothing like
getting together with family
and having a good meal.
Cletus, take this bowl.
lt's hot.
PAPA: God damn,
Sherman,
it's almost like we don't
see your ass no more.
Good to see you, Son.
You think you too good
to spend time
with your family
every now and then?
l've been real busy,
Ernie.
l don't want no potatoes.
Mashed potatoes give me gas.
ln my day, Sherman,
people used to spend time
with they family
on Sundays
and special occasions.
Come around
and pay their respects.
You mess around
and miss little Ernie's
golden years,
you're gonna be mad
at yourself.
(BELCHES)
Baby's got a little gas.
(COUGHING)
Here she goes.
Y'all better cover
your plates.
Mama, have some water.
(MUTTERING) Grandma,
you spit on me.
What you talking about,
covering your plates?
Not tonight, Cletus.
l'll kick your ass.
Sherman,
l cooked all this food.
ls that all you gonna eat?
You supposed to eat that,
not scalp it.
Daddy, all the calories
in the chicken
are found in the skin.
Where all the calories is?
You know where that come from?
Watching that damn TV.
Every time you turn it on
somebody talking about
lose weight, get healthy.
Everybody looking
all anorexic,
talking about that's healthy.
l know what healthy is.
And l don't know why everybody
trying to lose weight
in the first place!
Ain't everybody supposed
to be the same size.
We're all different.
Big, small, medium, midgets.
You supposed to have all that.
Everybody wants to be
the same size,
like that Oprah Winfrey.
She gonna lose her weight.
Wasn't nothing wrong with her.
She was fine. Oprah was a fox!
She lose all that weight,
her head look all big.
And Luther Vandross.
Nigger used to be
the black Pavarotti.
Lost all that weight,
looking all ashy.
Oprah and Luther need
to keep their ass one weight,
'cause l'm confused.
Yes, l hope nothing's wrong
with Oprah.
She doesn't look well.
There ain't nothing wrong
with Oprah.
l seen Oprah on Hard Copy
last week.
Was the picture of health.
Got her a tall, young, strong
gentleman named Steadman.
So handsome.
(SINGING) Amazing grace
She's my favorite
out of all of them.
Jenny Jones, Marilyn Kagan,
(SINGING CONTINUES)
Maury Povich.
Letterman, Leno.
Montell, Ricki Lake...
l like Geraldo.
Mike Douglas.
Oh, Mike Douglas.
You know, Mike Douglas
used to make me moist
when l'd watch his show.
l admit it.
Only white man ever did that
to me was Mike Douglas.
l would like to volunteer
to take this old bird
out of her misery.
Cletus! Don't you dare
say that about Mama.
GRANDMA: No, no, hold it.
You ain't gotta protect me
from Cletus. Come on, Cletus.
Come on over here.
lt ain't but a short walk.
Come on over.
You gonna limp back.
You'll walk over,
but you're limping back.
But don't let the gray hair
fool you.
l ain't no easy win, nigger.
Your problem is,
you don't work out.
Look. That's all muscle.
Oh.
ERNIE: You fat. l'm muscle.
Oh, look at my little b...
He's a little Hercules.
Show me your muscles again.
Oh, Hercules, Hercules,
Hercules, Hercules!
Once you work out,
your metabolism starts
to speed up,
you can eat
anything you want.
He's so strong.
Recent studies have shown
that certain people
are genetically predisposed
to gaining weight.
Someday we might even
find a cure.
Only thing you need to study
is your ass.
l got a big ass.
Your mama got a big ass.
Cletus!
You do have a big ass.
Asses is big in our family.
You need to get used
to that.
l don't care
what diet you go on.
You can sew up your stomach
and your asshole,
you gonna always be fat.
All l'm trying to say is
scientific breakthroughs
are occurring
all the time...
The only thing
about to break through
is your ass through the seat
of your pants.
Sherman,
l think l do remember
hearing something on TV
about colon cleansing.
They say everyone
should have one.
l'm thinking about
getting me an appointment
and getting my colon
cleansed thoroughly.
You want your colon cleansed?
l'm gonna clean mine.
(LOUD FART)
There. Now my colon is clean.
Squeaky clean.
Every time we have a meal,
you break gas.
Don't break gas
and destroy our meal.
You the one that brought up
colon cleansing!
l did not say anything
about breaking gas!
You can talk about putting
a tube in somebody's ass,
but l can't break wind.
l didn't say nothing
about putting a hose
up nobody's ass...
What you think a colonic is?
You think you run your asshole
by the car wash?
You're choking the baby.
As long as l pay the bills,
l do what l want
at this table.
Case in point:
(LOUD FART)
Who that called my name?
Yeah, l called you
if your name is...
(LOUD FART)
Keep insulting me.
l'll toss this between
the crack of your ass.
l can go all night.
(LOUD FART)
l hope you fart
till your asshole falls out.
(CONTINUES FARTING)
(LAUGHING WILDLY)
(LOUD FART)
Oh, my baby too!
Now see what you made me do?
God damn it,
l messed up my pants.
Damn, Daddy.
You got to clean
them yourself!
You rotten.
(ERNIE JR. CONTINUES LAUGHING)
Oh, Lord,
this has been a fabulous,
wonderful, fabulous evening.
Look. Them dogs done
tore up my garbage.
Cletus, the dog's ripped open
the garbage again!
PAPA: Shoot the damn dog!
l'm not shooting no dog!
l'm trying to watch
Roseanne!
Thanks for dinner, Mama.
Sherman, what's wrong
with you?
Baby, you still worried
about what your father said
in there?
Oh, Son, listen to me.
You are special.
When the good Lord made you,
he made you beautiful
inside and out.
You can do anything, Sherman.
All you got to do is
believe in yourself
and you can do anything.
(CHUCKLING)
You're so handsome.
Give me some sugar.
Love you, Mama.
Love you too, baby.
Nighty-night. Oh, my baby.
Sherman, Sherman, Sherman.
Fabulous.
Cletus, come clean
this garbage up!
l'm watching TV!
GRANDMA:
Get your lazy ass up.
Mind your own
damn business!
GRANDMA:
You lazy mother...
(DOORBELL RINGS)
Professor?
Oh. Hi, Miss Purty...
You caught me in the middle
of a little step aerobics
l was doing out here.
Ninety-eight, ninety-nine,
one hundred.
l looked your address up
in the faculty directory.
l hope you don't mind.
No, not at all.
What can l do for you?
Oh, well, l was...
(SIGHS)
l was,
l was wondering
if one night if,
when you weren't busy.
You get a little hungry,
you might want to,
you know...
lf you planned on going out
to get something anyway,
on an occasion like that,
you don't wanna
do that alone, so...
Professor, are you
asking me out on a date?
Yes. Yes, l am.
l'd love to.
Really?
Yes.
That's fantastic!
We can go any place
you wanna go. Just name it.
We'll go there.
There's a place
my students go to
called The Scream?
The Scream?
l mean, if that's too...
Oh, no, no, no.
l love to scream.
(YELLING)
(DOG HOWLING)
Screaming's good for you.
Cleans the epiglottis.
Get all the phlegm
and mucus down.
That's disgusting.
Just tell me what night.
How's Friday?
Friday night's perfect.
The best night of the week.
Friday night at 8:00.
l'll see you Friday night.
We'll go to The Scream.
lt'll be a scream
at The Scream.
All right, Professor,
l'll see you then.
Good night, Miss Purty.
Good night.
Yes!
(MUTTERING) Yeah,
Friday night at The Scream.
(CONTINUES MUTTERING)
Gonna scream.
Friday night. Friday, Friday,
Friday, Friday night.
Friday, Friday, Friday.
(WHISTLING)
(SINGING) l got myself a date
Friday night at 8:··
And l will not be late
She might be my mate
That would be so great
Great, great, great
And l can hardly wait
Lilo, Peabo, Lou Rawls,
Teddy Pendergrass. Teddy P.
Number six! Yeah!
(MID-TEMPO BALLAD PLAYING)
(SINGING ALONG)
Close the door
Let me give you
what you been waiting for
Baby, l got
so much love to give
Don't hurt them, Teddy P!
And l wanna give it all to you
l waited all day long
Just to hold you in my arms
And it's exactly like
l thought it would be
Me loving you
and you loving me
Oh, you know you gotta, gotta,
gotta close the door...
(BANGING)
MAN: Shut the hell up
up there, God damn it!
Sorry about that down there,
Mr. Wilson!
Teddy P turned up
a little loud.
Quiet down up there!
There is a thin person
inside each and every one
of us!
So give yourselves a big hug
and say, "Yes, l can!
Do that for me..."
Thighmaster Plus
is designed to give you
better results quicker.
l lost ten pounds
in two weeks.
Thanks, Megashake.
(LUSH ORCHESTRAL MUSIC
PLAYING ON TV)
(PANTING)
(BOTH MOANING)
(CARLA SCREAMING)
LANCE: (ON TV)
You're not pathetic!
People, pounds do not
lose themselves!
You have to work, work, work!
Everybody, up! Come on! Up!
You too at home!
Everybody up and say,
LANCE AND AUDIENCE:
"Yes, l can!"
LANCE: Say it again.
(STOMPING)
PROFESSOR AND AUDIENCE:
Yes, l can! Yes, l can! Yes...
MR. WILSON: Quiet down,
God damn it!
Sorry!
Klump, shut up!
l can!
l'm so excited
and l just can't hide it
l'm about to lose control
and l think l like it
l'm so excited
And l just can't hide it
And l know, l know
l know, l know
l know l want you
We shouldn't even think
about tomorrow
Still hungry?
Sweet memories will last
a long, long time
We'll have a good time,
baby, don't you worry
(BREATHING SHARPLY)
And if we're still
playing around
Boy, that's just fine
(STRANGULATED) Help.
Let's get excited
We just can't hide it
Still hungry?
Oh, no
I know, I know, I know, I know
I know I want you
I want you
Maybe you should try
Jenny Craig.
Oh, I want to love you,
feel you
Wrap myself around you
l want to squeeze you,
tease you
One hand on you!
l just can't get enough
And if you move real slow
l'll let it go
GROUP: Whoo!
l'm so excited
Ooh-wee
And l just can't hide it
No, no, no, no, no
(GRUNTS) Yeah! Yeah!
l know, l know, l know,
l know, l know l want you
Yeah!
l want you
Look what you do to me
Yeah!
You got me burning up
Oh-oh-oh-oh now
(CONTINUES GRUNTING)
Baby, l'm so excited
MONTELL JORDAN: (SINGING)
This is how we do it
Come on, come on,
come on. Right there.
This is how we do it
lt's Friday night,
and l feel all right
The party's here
on the west side
So l reached for my 40
and l turned it up...
Oh, excuse me. Hey!
Professor K,
how's it going?
l'm good, David.
What are you
doing here?
Got a date.
You have a date?
Good luck, Professor.
Yeah, see you next week now.
The guys and l
All the gang-bangers
Excuse me. Pardon me.
Sorry about that.
Oh. Oh. Excuse me.
Excuse me.
Excuse me. Excuse me.
(GASPING)
Sorry about that.
Excuse me.
Sorry about that. Excuse me.
Excuse me!
Thank you.
Wow, these are
great seats, Professor.
Oh, yeah. Listen,
don't call me Professor.
Call me Sherman, all right?
Sherman.
Well, l'm glad
we did this, Sherman.
JORDAN: (SINGING)
With a different type
of swing, you know
Something for the honeys
So am l.
So am l!
Something for the honeys
Here's the menu.
Ooh, summertime
No funner time
for me to kick it with you
To find something someone...
CARLA: So you altered
her genes?
Yes, yes.
And if l hadn't done it,
Shelley would be
in hamster heaven right now.
Sherman,
you are absolutely amazing.
We do what we can,
you know?
Got to keep on trying.
Got to keep on pushing.
Something for you and you
And for you and for you.
Let's go. Let's go.
MAN: Montell Jordan!
They were wonderful.
All right, all right.
Let's keep this show rolling.
Ladies and gentlemen...
He was good.
...you've seen him
on Def Comedy Jam many times.
Y'all give it up for my man,
Reggie Warrington!
Give it up!
(CROWD APPLAUDING
AND CHEERING)
JAMES BROWN:
(SINGING ON STEREO) Watch me
Watch me. l got it, watch me
He sure is animated.
Yeah!
What's up?
(CROWD CHATTERING)
l said, "What's up"?
Hey!
Women be shopping, baby.
(AUDIENCE LAUGHING)
Women be shopping!
You can't stop a woman
from shopping, baby!
That's true. Women do shop.
lt is true.
See what we got in here
tonight. Oh, my God!
(AUDIENCE LAUGHING)
She's unbe-weave-able.
Look at this.
Look like a hair full
of curly fries.
(AUDIENCE LAUGHING)
(LAUGHING)
Hey, look at this white dude
right here.
What is a weave exactly?
Huh?
(LAUGHING)
Oh, no.
No, no, no, no, no, no!
Baby, no! She got more
extensions than AT·T.
(AUDIENCE APPLAUDING
AND LAUGHING)
Excuse me. l'm gonna go
to the rest room.
Oh, boy, l'm hot!
Sorry about that, ma'am.
Let me pick that up for you.
(WHOOPS)
lt's a full moon tonight!
(HOWLING)
l think l found
where they hid Jimmy Hoffa!
(LAUGHING) Excuse me.
(CHUCKLING)
Yeah,
that's a good one there.
You got more crack
than Harlem. Look at that!
(AUDIENCE LAUGHING)
Boy's so fat,
every time he turns around,
it's his birthday!
Got to put his belt on
with a boomerang.
(lMITATING BOOMERANG)
Bang!
Yeah. Okay, all right, now.
That's it. You got me.
No, l ain't got you, yet.
Should l get him?
AUDIENCE: Yeah!
Oh, look at this.
He's with a woman, too.
AUDIENCE: Aw!
Oh, no!
Who is sucking whose titties
over here?
(AUDIENCE LAUGHING
UPROARIOUSLY)
Last time this brother
felt a breast,
it was in a bucket of KFC.
Extra crispy!
Every time he goes
to Sea World, they pay him!
He must be on that new diet,
Slim Slow.
He go outside
with a red shirt on,
and all the kids
in the neighborhood say,
"Hey! Kool-Aid!"
Yeah, man, l bet
l cut his fat ass open,
it'd bleed chocolate milk.
What would you do
for a Klondike bar?
Now we know what's eating
Gilbert Grape, don't we?
(THUNDER RUMBLING)
Thank you for dinner
tonight, Sherman.
That was very sweet.
You're welcome.
Look, that comic tonight,
he was...
Sherman, you are
a brilliant man.
You have a pleasant evening.
Good night.
(KEYS JINGLING)
(DOOR CLOSES)
His fraternity
was having this thing
called Pig Day.
That's the only reason
he asked me out.
To make fun of you?
Why do we do this
to ourselves?
Every time we get depressed,
we eat and eat and eat.
You go to the store
and buy those little
candy bars in the bag,
and before you know it,
the whole bag is empty.
Then at the end, you feel
just like that bag.
Empty inside.
(SOBBING)
Don't you?
(WOMAN SOBBING)
lt's okay. lt's all right.
Just get it all out.
(SOBBING CONTINUES)
Say, "Yes, l can."
Say that.
Yes, l can.
(SOBBING CONTINUES)
(SOBBING) Yes, we can.
(SOBBING)
Can we go to commercial?
l want him prepped
and ready immediately.
Yes, Doctor.
Call Dr. Matthews.
l'm going to need
a lot of help on this one.
Let's move it.
You know the routine.
Get that crash cart here
stat!
Blood pressure,
14· over 9· and rising.
MAN: We need
that lV rig in now!
IV rig coming in.
Give me four cc's of Ambethol.
l don't know how much more
he can take.
We need the EKG cart
in here now.
Blood pressure, 1·0 over 1 10
and still climbing.
What's the status?
He's getting fatter.
We can't stop it.
Damn!
Blood pressure,
200 over 140!
(ALARM BEEPING)
Oh, my God!
He's gonna explode!
l'm getting out of here!
(WOMAN SCREAMS)
Nurse!
Wait! Wait!
(RUMBLING)
(THUNDERCLAP)
(CROWD SCREAMING)
What's going on?
Oh, my God! Get out of here!
Get out of here!
Hey, everyone,
run for the hills!
lt's Fat-zilla!
He look like King Kong
with titties.
Sherman! l brought you some
nice fried chicken, Sherman.
Oh, you look fabulous!
(LAUGHING)
(GASPS)
(GLASS BREAKING)
(SCREAMS)
(PROFESSOR BURPING)
(BURPING CONTINUES)
(MOANING)
MAN: Oh, my God!
He's gonna blow!
(FARTING)
(SCREAMING)
Way to go, Son!
That's my boy!
No!
(GASPING AND PANTING)
Huh?
(BEEPING)
(KEYBOARD KEYS CLICKING)
(BEEPING QUICKENS)
Shelley, you've been
the guinea pig long enough.
lt's time to see
if this stuff really works.
(THUNDERCLAP)
(BEEPING)
(BEEPING CONTINUES)
(GROANS)
(GROANING)
(BEEPING CONTINUES)
(BEEPING)
(ELECTRICITY CRACKLING)
Oh! Oh! l'm thin! l'm thin!
Look at my cheekbones!
l have cheekbones!
Yes! Look at my chest.
Look at my breasts.
l don't have breasts.
l'm an A cup.
l don't need a bra anymore.
Oh, God, l'm thin! l'm thin!
l'm thin! l'm thin, l'm thin.
(SINGING)
Nothing but air there
My ass is gone
Now l'm slim, slim, slim
Well, l'll be damned!
l can see my dick!
My dick!
My dick, my dick, my dick!
JAMES BROWN: (SINGING)
Whoa, l feel good
l can do stairs.
l knew that l would now
l am the stair master!
l feel good
l knew that l would now
You looking for any kind
of clothes in particular?
Spandex! All Spandex!
Where's the Spandex section?
Oh! Spandex! Like this!
l feel nice
Like sugar and spice
No titties. No titties.
l feel nice
No titties.
Not you, me.
l'm talking about me.
My titties are gone.
Your titties are lovely.
What's your name?
l can't believe l'm so thin.
l am thin. You ever feel thin?
l am thin! l am thin.
Hey, man,
where's the apple pie?
When l hold you in my arms
l know that l can do no wrong
And when l hold you in my arms
My love won't do you no harm
Tootsie Roll!
Get your tootsie!
And l feel nice
(GRUNTING)
Like sugar and spice
So nice, so nice
(GRUNTING CONTINUES)
l got you
(SHOUTING) l'm thin! l'm thin!
Excuse me.
Hey!
ls Professor Klump here?
Professor Klump?
Sherman, Sherman Klump.
No, he had to take care
of some things, Miss Purty.
So l'm running
this thing here.
Do l know you?
Do you know me?
(LAUGHS)
Sherman didn't tell you
about me?
No.
Oh, man!
lsn't that like Sherman
to hog all the credit?
l'm Sherman's confidante.
Have you seen him today?
l was wondering if he was
all right after everything
that happened at the club
the other night.
Oh, Miss Purty,
it tore his chunky ass up.
lt's strange that a man
as intelligent as Sherman
has no confidence whatsoever.
Makes me sick
sometimes to think...
l'm always telling the man,
"Sherman, no matter what,
you've got to strut.
"You got to suck in your gut
and strut."
Me, personally,
l don't have that problem.
Doesn't seem like you do.
You're just too feisty
and too fine. Me and you
need to hook up.
We need to go
to The Scream tonight,
have a couple of drinks
and strut
our respective stuff together.
l don't even know your name.
Hey, buddy,
what the hell happened here?
See?
Everybody knows Buddy.
The professor must have
got a little carried away
last night.
Oh, Officer Dagg,
l'm glad you came up.
He told me to tell you
personally, please thank
your wife Claire
for bringing that
upside-down cake for him.
He ate every crumb of it.
And can you have someone
from janitorial clean up
this mess, please?
Thank you, Officer Dagg.
Thank you.
(DOOR OPENS)
Buddy.
Buddy? ls that it,
or do you have a last name?
(DOOR CLOSES)
Love.
Love?
You see, Miss Purty,
(lN PROFESSOR'S VOICE)
there comes a time
in a man's life
when he has to...
(CLEARS THROAT AND COUGHS)
Miss Purty, people have
a tendency in life
(lN PROFESSOR'S VOICE)
to always want to rush
into things.
(lN REGULAR VOICE)
What l'm trying to say
is there's a right time
and place for everything.
Like l said,
there's a right time
and place for everything.
(lN PROFESSOR'S VOICE)
Tonight would be
a good time.
At The Scream would be perfect
to discuss it.
l'll see you tonight.
Don't be late! Excuse me!
Uh-oh.
(CHATTERING)
Good morning.
Good morning, class.
Morning, students.
Good morning!
Morning. Good morning.
You students just review
what we went over yesterday.
Professor, we weren't
here yesterday.
Well, then,
review the day before,
and tomorrow we'll do today.
That's it.
(CLASS LAUGHING)
(DOOR OPENS AND CLOSES)
Sherman!
Oh, Carla. How are you?
l've been looking for you
all morning. Are you okay?
l'm fine.
Why you looking for me?
l feel bad what happened
at the club the other night.
lt was my idea
to go to The Scream.
l've forgotten about that.
You forget, too.
That's over.
Go have a nice day.
There's something else.
l met a friend of yours
in your lab.
Buddy Love.
He's quite a character,
huh?
He asked me out,
and he said it was your idea.
Oh, did he?
Well, l know you're new
in town.
l thought
it would be nice
for a new girl to get out,
meet some people.
Did you find him
attractive?
Honestly, yes.
He's very handsome
and athletic.
But l don't feel comfortable
talking to you about that.
You can talk to me
about anything.
l want you to.
And l think you should
definitely go out
with Buddy Love.
You do?
Absolutely.
l don't think
there's anything wrong
with two young people
getting together
and having a good time.
So by all means,
do just that.
You sure
you're all right with that?
Don't worry about me.
l'm just fine.
ln fact,
l'll put in a good word
with you for Buddy.
Oh, my goodness. l'm so late.
Excuse me. l'll talk to Buddy.
You make it hard, long
soft, short
And be strokin'
l be strokin'
l stroke it to the east
and l stroke it to...
(MUSIC CONTINUES
lNDISTINCTLY)
Hey, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Now you be careful.
lf there's a scratch
in the car,
there's a scratch
in your ass.
You are too fine
to be giving me
curbside service.
l'm not. l'm leaving.
We just got here.
No, you just got here.
l've been waiting for you
for almost an hour.
They say anticipation
helps make the appetite
grow stronger.
Anticipate a night alone.
Hey, hey. Let's just have
a meal together.
Why you leaving?
You want me to beg?
l'll get down on my knees.
l'll beg you
in front of all these people.
Think l care
if these people are watching?
l'm sorry! l'm sorry!
l want the world to know
that l was late!
And l'm sorry!
My car ran out of gas.
l needed fresh drawers.
My mother's sick.
The car broke down.
Buddy, get up.
Hear me out. l am sorry!
l don't know why
this is happening tonight.
Of all nights
this has got to happen
to me tonight.
Okay.
Why? Why?
Okay!
Why?
Okay, okay, okay.
Okay. Good. Let's eat.
l am so hungry.
Hey, don't let the tears
fool you.
l'm a tooth chipper.
Six T-bones, five baked
potatoes and two servings
of creamed spinach.
l have never seen anyone
eat so much.
You are so lucky
to stay so thin.
Luck has nothing
to do with it.
lt's a matter of recombinant
ribonucleic acids
unzipped by a radioactive
guanine peptide.
What does that mean?
l don't know. l'm trying
to sound extra intelligent.
Got you!
You gonna eat that?
Guess who's back
in the house.
From Def Comedy Jam,
my man, Reggie Warrington.
Give it up!
(CHEERING)
l hate this guy.
He is so obnoxious.
Give the nigger
a chance.
JAMES BROWN: (SINGING)
Watch me
lt's your world, dog!
l'm just a squirrel
trying to get a nut.
l've got something
that makes me wanna shout
What's up?
What's up, nigger?
l said, "What's up"?
Didn't you hear me
when l say, "Hey"?
Boy, women be shopping.
Women be shopping.
You cannot stop a woman
from shopping.
(LAUGHING)
Let's see what l got
in the house tonight.
Oh, now, look at this
white guy right here.
You cannot tell me
he ain't got a small jimmie.
Man, it's so small
he needs tweezers
to take a piss.
He needs tweezers
to take a piss!
Tweezers on his dick!
Reggie's hot tonight.
Look at this. Look at this.
Oh! Oh! Oh!
l can't breathe!
Excuse me, brother.
(GASPING)
l can't breathe!
Okay.
Brother, man!
(WHEEZING)
You almost killed me,
man!
l had to give myself
the Heimlich.
You mind waiting
for the punch line first,
brother?
l'm sorry.
You're so funny.
You're so funny
the way you take a person's
personal defects
and flip it around.
Like you pick somebody
in the room and say,
"Look at your foot,"
and everybody look at it
and start laughing.
That's funny shit.
You're on your way!
You going to the top!
You're the next Lenny Bruce!
Why, thank you.
Thank you very much.
That's genius.
That'd even work with me
doing it to you.
lf l say, look at Reggie's
gums and teeth.
His mother had an affair
with Mister Ed.
See?
Everybody's laughing.
They can visualize
your mother in a barn
with Mister Ed.
(NEIGHING LUSTILY)
Look what l'm doing, Wilbur.
Look at me!
You snapping on me?
Are you snapping on Reggie?
lt's your teeth, Reggie.
l don't know
whether to smile at you
or kick a field goal.
Hey, Reggie! lt's good!
lt's all good!
And, man, what's wrong
with that breath?
l can smell it over here.
Reggie, your breath
is so stink,
people look forward
to your farts.
Breath smell like shit.
Do you smell shit?
l smell shit.
Oh! Oh!
You done did it now, boy.
l wasn't gonna say nothing
'cause l like black people.
But it's time to attack black.
That's right.
The glove's coming off.
Don't hurt me now!
Maybe it's time for Reggie
to lay into your mama.
(CROWD CHEERS)
Oh! Oh, yeah!
Maybe it's time for Reggie
to talk about your mama
a little bit.
You're the man, Reggie!
Your mother's so fat,
she went to Sizzler's,
and the bitch got
a group discount.
(AUDIENCE LAUGHING)
(HYSTERICAL LAUGHING)
(SCREAMING)
(SCREAMING CONTINUES)
(SCREAMING AND GASPING)
Okay, fat jokes!
You want to do fat jokes?
All right.
Your mother's so fat,
the bitch need a Thomas Guide
to find her asshole!
(AUDIENCE LAUGHING)
All right! Wait, wait, wait.
Your mother's so fat,
after sex l rolled over twice,
and l'm still on the bitch!
(LAUGHING CONTINUES)
Your mother is so fat,
she fell in the Grand Canyon
and got stuck!
Reggie's mama's so fat,
that the bitch gets
her toenails painted
at Earl Scheib!
Earl Scheib!
Hey, hey,
get off the stage, man.
You ain't in show business.
Reggie's mama is so fat,
her blood type is Rocky Road!
lsn't that something?
Reggie's mother is so fat,
her belt size is equator!
(HOOTING AND CHEERING)
Get it? Equator?
(BUDDY LAUGHING HYSTERICALLY)
Let's get a big
round of applause
for Reggie's mama's ass
that brought us
so much joy tonight.
Yeah! That's a big ass.
Enough! Silence!
l can't take this shit
no more.
Now, you done talked
about me enough, boy!
l tried to be peaceful,
but now it's time for Reggie
to karatasize your ass!
(WHOOPS)
Oh, yeah.
(LAUGHING)
Oh, Reggie,
l heard of dreadlocks,
but shitlocks?
That's not your hair.
Take that pile of shit
off your head.
(AUDIENCE LAUGHING)
You... You go too far
with the comedy.
(KARATE YELL)
Oh, oh! Come on! Come on.
What's that?
Oh, yeah, it's my style, boy.
You didn't know
Reggie studied.
What style is that?
This is called
"Kick-Your-Ass Style," boy.
Oh, shit.
Reggie done studied
on the streets.
Oh! Come on!
(KARATE YELL)
Oh! Oh!
(AUDIENCE GASPS AND CHEERS)
(LAUGHING)
Oh, you quick,
but l'm quicker.
Watch my feet.
Come on with it!
l'm gonna come on
with it. l'm gonna...
(KARATE YELLS)
REGGIE: Oh, damn!
(AUDIENCE GASPS)
Ladies and gentlemen,
me and Reggie
want to send one out
to a very special lady
in the house tonight.
(PIANO PLAYING)
(SINGING) Lovin' you is easy,
'cause you're beautiful
Do-un-do-un-doo-doo.
Reggie?
(BONES CRACK)
(HOWLING)
Let go.
That was pretty.
Ladies and gentlemen,
Reggie has left the building.
Thank you, and good night.
(CHEERING)
Oh, stop it! Stop it!
Now, thank you so much.
Thank you.
Thank you so...
Oh, please, please,
come on now.
Hey, who pinched my ass?
Cut it out. That's good.
All right. Thank you.
Can you get the bill for me?
Thanks, man. Too much!
That was amazing.
l can't believe you did that.
Amazing is my middle name.
l only wish Professor Klump
was here to have seen it.
Listen.
This is our moment.
l don't wanna ruin it
with talks of Sherman.
You know, your eyes,
there's something
very familiar about them,
as if l already know you.
You know,
l feel the exact same way
about you, Miss Purty.
(BALLAD PLAYING
ON SOUND SYSTEM)
Miss Purty, let me tell you.
(lN PROFESSOR'S VOICE)
That kiss was probably
the most wonderful kiss
l've ever...
(CLEARS THROAT)
What l meant to say
was that...
Your lip.
What?
Your lip is swollen.
My lip?
Yes.
Oh, my lip? Oh.
That happens every time l...
What kind of lipstick
do you have on?
Chanel.
That happens every time
l have Chanel lipstick
on my lips.
An allergic reaction.
(RUMBLING)
Oh. lt's giving me gas, too.
You have to go catch a cab.
l gotta go to the drugstore
and get some Benadryl
and Kaopectate.
Excuse me, have a
pleasant evening.
Bye, bye!
Buddy! Buddy, wait!
(MUSIC CONTINUES)
Oh, man.
Hey, Professor Klump
is here?
Yeah.
Where is he?
There he is, right there.
That guy gave you
this credit card?
Yup.
That's not Professor Klump.
That's not his credit card.
Hey!
What?
Hey! Hey!
Okay, fella, what are you
doing with the Professor's
credit card?
Where'd you get it?
l'm sorry. Perhaps
you need the money
more than l thought...
(JASON GROANS)
JASON: (SCREAMING)
Oh, my God!
(SCREAMING)
That's a bus!
You're gonna kill us, man!
What the hell is the matter...
Oh, man!
This is Freddy Krueger shit,
man!
Professor?
Hello, Jason.
JASON: (SCREAMING)
What's happening?
(SIREN WAILING)
First time we had
to use one of these
without an accident.
The class left
20 minutes ago.
Dean Richmond!
Oh, hello, sir.
You caught me in the middle
of an experiment l was doing.
l was trying to see how
the students would respond
to a teacher-less environment.
Teacher-less environment?
New field of research for you?
Yes, sir.
lnteresting.
Always thinking.
That's good, Klump.
Let me know your results.
Would you mind
explaining this?
Oh! Yeah, well,
my car's in the shop, so...
So you put
a $47,000 luxury car
on your faculty account.
lnitially, l...
l requested a Yugo,
and this is all they had...
lf it's all they had,
it's all they had.
After all, men like us
can't walk around now,
can we?
(CHUCKLING) Come on.
(BOTH LAUGHING)
Oh, well, well.
l'm glad you're taking it
like that, sir.
l thought
you was gonna get angry
and start screaming
and hollering,
and maybe even fire me.
(LAUGHING) Whoo!
Oh, Sherman, Sherman.
ln the end we know
so little of each other, hmm?
No, my friend, l've got
bigger fish to fry.
l spoke to Harlan Hartley.
He's offering that tiny
trinket that could save
your entire research program.
Oh, yes. Absolutely.
l set up a meeting with him.
He wants to hear your
grant proposal personally.
Friday, the Ritz,
dinner, 8:00 sharp.
Well, sir, l think
that's a wonderful idea,
sir. Absolutely.
And l promise you,
l will not let you down.
l know you won't.
l know
you're going to be there
and you're going to be great.
ln fact, l know
you're going to be perfect.
(LAUGHING)
Do you know how l know?
How's that?
'Cause if you're not perfect,
never mind the yelling
and the screaming
and the firing.
lf anything goes wrong
for any reason,
l'm going to kill you.
l don't mean that
as a euphemism. l'm going
to literally kill you.
l'm going to strangle you
and choke off your air supply
until you pass away.
(EXCLAIMS) Okay.
Till Friday, then.
lt's a date.
(SCHOOL BELL RINGING)
Sir, this is incredible.
lt's... lt's a complete
metabolic transformation.
How did it happen?
Was it an accident?
No, l did it
to myself, Jason.
You did? Why?
lf it was for the grant,
the data with Shelley was
already so compelling.
Well, l have compelling
reasons of my own, Jason.
l have a case of infatuation
of sorts with Miss Purty.
Professor, if you feel
this way about Carla,
why don't you tell her?
lt'd be a lot simpler
than transforming into...
This guy's testosterone levels
are right off the charts.
He was mean last night.
lt was so unlike you.
You know, l did feel that.
Sir, you can't control him.
Jason, you have no idea
what it feels like
to be Buddy Love.
lt's indescribable.
lt's just wonderful!
The way people talk to him
and treat him, and the way
she looks at him.
But he's dangerous.
He almost killed us
last night.
We should be concentrating
on getting the grant proposal
to Harlan Hartley.
This is nuts!
l guess you're right, Jason.
l never have behaved
like this before.
But on the other hand,
l've never been
in love before.
Ever.
Afternoon, Carla.
Hi, Sherman.
How are you doing today?
Pretty good.
l come over to see
how things were going
with you and Buddy.
l wish l knew.
We went out last night.
lt was great. We had
such a wonderful time.
And then all of a sudden
he runs out of the club.
He has some allergic reaction.
l don't even know
if he's all right.
He's fine.
He told me
that his lip swelled up,
he put ice on it
and the swelling came down.
Kinda strange, huh?
Well, did he even ask
about me?
Did he say why he didn't
call me and let me know
he was all right?
Carla, Buddy's kind of
unreliable.
He's kind of
what you call
a "here today,
gone tomorrow"
kind of fellow.
Oh, l see.
Mmm-hmm.
So he had you talk to me
because he's not interested
anymore.
No, it's nothing
quite like that.
Look.
l know what it feels like
to be brushed off,
and it's okay.
This is all my fault.
l should've never
encouraged you
to go out with Buddy.
Sherman, you have been
so sweet.
l'll just have to
forget about him.
l'll see you later.
Carla.
l was wondering if
l could talk to you
about you and l,
for a second.
l was...
l was wondering
what you were doing later,
'cause the family
gonna get together.
She made a meal
and we gonna be eating,
so l figured
if you not doing anything
for dinner,
we'd love to have you,
if you want to come over
for dinner.
We'd love to have you over
l'd love to.
Would you, now?
Yes, l would.
Should we call
and make sure there's
going to be enough food?
l don't think
that's going to be a problem.
(ALL CHATTERING)
MAMA: There's nothing like
being with family!
GRANDMA: l am hungry.
Come on, now.
Carla, where are you from?
Chicago.
Oh, Chicago!
We have family there.
PAPA: Windy city, huh?
l was working on a skyscraper
in Chicago once,
and my lunch blew off
the 27th floor.
Yeah, l figure
your fat ass would remember
somebody's sandwich
flying off a building.
(LOUD BELCH)
Oh, baby, eat some bread.
Miss Purty, are you
and Sherman having relations?
TOGETHER:
That's a good question.
No, Grandma.
lt's not like that.
We're colleagues.
Oh.
PROFESSOR:
We just work together.
That's how it start out
colleagues.
Me and your grandfather
was colleagues.
Next thing you know
he's on top of me in the shed,
pumping and a-sweating.
lt's not like that.
PAPA: Will you hush up?
He's never brought
a girl home.
The least you can do
is let us talk to her.
Yeah, l'd like
to get to know her
a little better myself.
Ain't nothing wrong
with having relations.
Don't be ashamed of that.
Relations is beautiful.
When l was young
l used to always
have relations.
Every night,
if a nice gentleman
bring me flowers and candy,
take me to a movie,
show me a lovely evening,
then l would take him home
and give him hot,
lovely relations.
Relations is
a beautiful thing.
lt's nothing to be ashamed of.
Especially two young people.
That blowhole.
Cletus!
Sometimes when l'm alone,
l relate to myself.
l can relate.
Oh, Mama.
l don't wanna hear this shit
while l'm eating.
MAMA: Cletus!
(WHISPERING)
l'm gonna kill you later.
Carla, do you
like children?
Yes.
Oh, that's wonderful.
l can't wait for Sherman
to bring me home
some grandbabies.
ERNIE: l know you're gonna
enjoy making them babies.
Got those childbearing hips.
(CLEARS THROAT)
Baby'll pop right out.
(MAKES POPPING SOUND)
Your family got any money?
l ain't paying
for no big-ass wedding.
l know a wonderful minister.
What religious background
are you?
l still got my wedding dress.
lf you want it,
l'll take it in.
You'd look so lovely in it.
lt's white though.
Can you wear a white
wedding dress, young lady?
Now, Sherman,
you can wear a white tuxedo.
'Cause you know Sherman,
(WHISPERING) Sherman has
never had relations.
Mama, you gonna
embarrass my baby.
GRANDMA: l hope you got
a strong back.
MAMA: Oh, look
at my baby blushing.
When you get all that man,
and release all that
that's been built up
for 35 years.
Just wanting
and wanting and wanting!
(EXCLAIMS) Might make
your head blow off.
Pop goes the weasel!
l got my own self hot
telling that story.
Pop goes the weasel,
'cause the weasel say "pop!"
You gonna get married here,
or in Chicago?
MAMA: Do you cook?
'Cause somebody's
got to feed my Sherman.
Yeah, l know
a wonderful church
down there on Main Street,
but they won't marry you
if you're a lesbian.
Not that l have anything
against lesbians.
l love lesbians.
Lesbians is cool.
There's nothing wrong
with a little bingo.
A little cunnilingus
ain't never hurt nobody.
Why is it the woman
always gets the choice where
they're gonna be married?
Tradition.
Tradition, my ass!
l ain't gonna pay
for everybody flying
to no Chicago!
You know how much
plane tickets cost?
You cheap bastard.
PAPA: We're gonna
have to drive down there.
l'm not driving
over to Chicago.
(SINGING)
Sherman gonna have relations
My baby's not getting married.
(LOUD FART)
There you go again,
popping off gas
in front of this
lovely young lady.
We're trying to have a meal.
Put that brake on this gas.
l hope your ass
turn into a frog.
Don't nobody want
to hear your flatulence,
Cletus Klump.
(LOUD FART)
MAMA: You're such a disgrace!
PAPA: l stopped holding
my gas a long time ago.
MAMA: You spoiled the dinner!
(ERNIE JR. LAUGHING)
PAPA: Say one more word.
(CHATTERING CONTINUES)
(BELL TOLLING)
Listen, Carla,
l want to apologize
about my family back there.
l think they got
the wrong idea about things.
Oh, no.
l should apologize.
l'm so sorry
if l seemed distant tonight.
l still have Buddy
on my mind.
You really care
for Buddy, huh?
l don't know.
l mean, on the outside,
he seems so cocky and brash.
But when l look in his eyes,
l see kindness, l see warmth.
And that's the side of Buddy
l wanted to get to know.
l just got
way ahead of myself.
And here l am,
talking your ear off
once again about Buddy.
No, it's quite
all right, really.
Listen, Carla,
don't you worry about Buddy.
l'll find him for you.
Thank you, Sherman.
Thank you for being
such a good friend to me.
A good friend.
Good night.
(SIGHS)
(LOUD CRASHING)
Professor?
ls that you?
l just finished
the grant proposal.
What's the matter with you?
Never seen a brother
wearing a circus tent before?
Black man can't go camping?
Now, wait a minute, you...
You can't be you.
We agreed that
you wouldn't do this.
Someone has to tend
to chunky butt's sex life.
Chunky butt is
extremely horny. Excuse me.
But Professor Klump
has a meeting tonight with
Harlan Hartley at the Ritz.
l'm gonna be at the Ritz
tonight, but it will not be
in the interest of science.
No! l can't let you go.
Professor!
lf you're in there
and you can hear me, come out!
Professor, listen to me.
The testosterone levels
are way too high.
You can't control him.
(WHEEZING)
(GROANING AND MOANING)
Oh! Jason!
What?
(GASPING)
lt's me, Sherman.
l'm talking to you from
deep down inside Buddy Love.
Listen to me closely.
Go in the back room
while l'm holding him
and get the coagulant serum
off the back shelf!
ln the storage closet?
Yes, Jason!
l got it!
Hurry, Jason!
We don't have much time.
Let's move!
(YELLS)
(MANIACAL LAUGHING)
Professor! Professor!
l have an appointment
with love!
Good night, hamster boy!
(POUNDING ON DOOR)
No, Professor!
(SCREAMING)
"Sorry l haven't phoned,
but l haven't been
myself lately.
"Join me for dinner.
Buddy Love.
"P.S. l've enclosed
a wallet-sized photo
for your enjoyment."
(CHUCKLING)
(CLASSICAL MUSIC PLAYING)
Buddy, how can l stay
mad at you?
This is gorgeous!
You're gorgeous
and l'm gorgeous,
so we should be
in gorgeous surroundings.
Let me get the room key.
Wait. Hold it.
l didn't say anything about
going to any room with you.
You said you were taking me
to dinner.
What are you talking about?
Oh, you think that... Oh!
Oh, my...
Hey, hey, hey. Slow down.
l just want to spend
some time with you,
by ourselves.
l don't want to share you
with these people.
l want to eat, alone, quiet.
l would never disrespect you.
l'm a puppy dog.
Please, can l go
get this room?
(BARKS QUIETLY)
Yes?
Yes.
l'd throw him
in the river with a Buick
tied to his neck.
He'd probably drag
the car down.
Miss Purty. Purty!
Dean Richmond.
Have you seen Professor Klump?
He's 40 minutes late.
lf Harlan Hartley
walks out that door,
$10 million goes with him.
Oh, Lord.
l'm gonna have to lay down
in front of his car.
Let's go.
Buddy, you know
Sherman's research.
He's late for a meeting.
Fill in for him.
No, it's a nice thought,
but he'd have to know
Sherman's research.
You know Sherman's
research? Who are you?
You might say
l'm a visiting professor
who might be staying
for a while.
l do know Sherman's work.
ln fact, l am Sherman's work.
Buddy!
Do you think
you can do Klump's job
and crowbar that dough
out of Hartley?
There's not a job
on this planet l can't do
twice as good as Sherman.
Good. Follow me.
l'll go do this
just 'cause you asked me,
not 'cause of him.
You just stay put.
l've got to go be brilliant.
Look at your fine self.
l bet you have on a thong
made of licorice, don't you?
Excuse me.
(RICHMOND LAUGHING)
All righty!
Well, this had better
be Professor Klump.
Klump? That fraud,
that hack, that no-talent.
No, sir, this is the man
behind Klump's work,
the real genius.
l give you
Professor Buddy Love.
All right, Professor Love.
You have one minute
to show me your research.
Oh, no, you got it
backwards, Rockefeller.
You have one minute to listen.
May l borrow this?
You haven't used it, have you?
Don't want to get
your boogers on my fingers.
Okay. Here we go.
25N times C.
You have to excuse
my handwriting.
l'm in a bit of a rush.
You have a pleasant evening.
Good night.
Professor Love,
don't you think Mr. Hartley
would like to know what
that means in lay terms?
(CHUCKLES)
Oh, you mean
rich-dummy terms?
l'll break it down
for the rich dummies
in the room. Listen up.
lf you eat
nasty stuff like this...
l know it looks good,
and some of y'all
like pork chops,
but this greasy,
nasty pork chop,
do you realize
there's a gene in your DNA
that routes this
straight to your fat cells,
and it causes
unsightly conditions.
Case in point, this woman
is suffering from what
l like to call "Jell-O arms."
The arm is taking on
a gelatin sort of vibe.
lt's quite nasty.
To my left, this gentleman
has turkey neck.
To my immediate left,
this woman is suffering
from what we like to call,
"Saddlebag syndrome."
To my extreme left,
this young lady
is suffering from what
l like to call "Tank ass."
Please, sit down.
Not tonight.
l'm your brother!
Like l was saying,
everybody, where there's
a will, there's a way.
There is a way
we can turn these genes off.
l'm not talking about
using exercise or diet.
l'm talking about
by taking a simple solution
that helps reconstruct
your metabolic
cellular strands,
thus giving you
the appearance of,
in medical terms,
gluteus minimus.
Or, in layman's terms,
an extremely tight,
wonderful ass.
Let's give a big round
of applause for the woman
with the nice ass.
Her ass is so nice,
don't you agree?
She's worked so hard.
Have a seat.
Oh, are these girls with you?
Everyone has a nice ass
at this table.
ls this
the nice-ass section?
(LAUGHTER)
Where'd you find this man?
Harlan, it's an outrage.
l assure you
he has no affiliation
with this school.
He's brilliant.
Exactly my point.
lt's an outrage
that his brilliance
has no affiliation
with this school.
That's why l found him
and brought him
to your money.
Attention. Brought him
to your attention.
(CLOCK BELL STRIKING)
My goodness,
it is time to take
my medication.
Professor!
Hartley loved you.
He's going to be at the
Alumni Ball tomorrow night.
lf you can prove
the formula works,
the ten million is ours!
What makes you so sure
that the money is ours,
instead of just being mine?
(LAUGHS)
You're good, Love. Very good.
How'd you like to fill in
for Professor Klump
on a more permanent basis?
That's what l had in mind.
He talked to me first.
Hey, l'm the one
with the gluteus minimus.
Will you guys just chill?
He said he could handle
all three of us.
With a name like Buddy Love,
l bet he can.
Carla, are you ready
to go upstairs?
l guess not.
Hey... Where you going?
What's your problem?
They're my problem,
and you can handle
all three of them, huh?
Oh, well, l thought after
dinner you might want to
have a little group activity.
After all, Buddy does
have a lot of love to give.
Oh, you are one sick,
twisted freak!
Oh, come on, Carla.
What's the... Hey!
Go on, leave!
There's more titties
over here anyway!
Think l want them two titties.
l have six titties.
l had two titties.
Now l have six.
That's multiplication.
(ALL LAUGHING)
(ON STEREO) Oh-oh-oh-oh-oh
Oh-oh-oh-oh-oh
Boys will be boys
(BUDDY CHEERING) Yeah!
Yeah! Yeah!
Oh, yeah!
This is what l call
burning calories!
Come on!
Help me burn this stuff up!
(GUESTS WHOOPING)
Yeah! Hey, this is going down
to Mr. Wilson downstairs!
(CHANTING) The roof, the roof,
the roof is on fire
(ALL CHANTING) The roof,
the roof, the roof is on fire
(WHOOPING)
(KNOCKING AT DOOR)
Sherman?
(CANS CRUNCHING)
(CANS CLATTERING)
Sherman?
(MOANING)
(SNIFFING AND SMACKING LIPS)
CARLA: Sherman?
(CHUCKLING)
Sherman?
(GASPS)
(LOUD THUD)
Sherman, is that you?
Are you all right?
Oh, hi, Carla. Hi.
(CHUCKLING)
Did you have a party
last night?
Oh, no.
My cleaning lady's...
Cleaning lady's sick,
so l got to clean up myself.
l see.
You sure she didn't die?
(LAUGHING)
(TOILET FLUSHING)
Oh. Look, l'm a little
embarrassed about the way
how my place is looking.
Why don't l clean up
and get back at you later?
No, no, no. Sherman,
l need to talk to you now.
lt's about Buddy.
He hasn't been misbehaving,
has he?
He's an egotistical pig,
and l wish l never met him.
But, Sherman,
l owe you a very big apology.
You owe me an apology?
Yes.
Last night
l was only trying to help,
l insisted that Buddy Love
speak to Harlan Hartley.
He took all the credit
for your research.
Now Dean Richmond...
WOMAN: Where's Buddy?
Oh...
Buddy came here?
(CHUCKLING NERVOUSLY)
No!
So what's this?
Are you guys...
You guys share girls?
Oh, no, no, no, no.
l guess l was next
on the list.
No, you don't understand.
l cannot believe
l came over here
feeling sorry for you.
Carla, will you please
just listen to me?
l assure you it is not
what it appears to be!
You're no better
than he is!
You are just as sick
as Buddy, and l don't wanna
see you or him again!
Carla, please
just listen. Carla!
"Eviction notice?
Violation of noise ordinance?"
(CANS CLATTERING)
Professor, we have to get
to the lab right away.
Whatever it is, is gonna
have to wait until later.
No, that's the thing.
There isn't gonna be a later.
JASON: Professor,
what did you do last night?
Jason,
l have such a bad hangover,
l honestly do not remember.
Well, the good news is
l'm not going to kill you,
not physically, anyway.
l am, however,
going to kill you
professionally.
You're not only fired
from this institution,
but l'm going to make sure
you never get hired
by any other college
in the state,
the country, the world,
maybe even the universe.
Unless, of course,
they're looking for teachers
on Planet Fat.
Oh, by the way,
Buddy Love is going to
be using your invitation
to the alumni ball,
so show a little school spirit
and see that he gets it.
(SINGING) We're in the money
Put that food down!
They ate yesterday!
...really tight
and say, "Yes, l can."
Say it again.
LANCE AND AUDIENCE:
Yes, l can!
Hey, chunky drawers!
Hey, tank ass!
What are you eating?
Mu·in? Strudel? Put it down.
Let me talk to you.
lf you're receiving
this message, that means
you went and plumped back up
to your usual, fat, sorry,
stuff-my-face-till-
l'm almost-dead self.
ls that what you did?
Shame on you, Sherman!
Do you know
what you did last night?
You had the time of your life.
Do you know
you can get arrested
in ·· states
for the shit you did
just last night?
(GIGGLING)
Oh, my goodness!
You know what you need to do?
You need to go down
to the laboratory
and mix up another batch
of this blue stuff.
Come on back to the party,
Sherman, because Carla
doesn't want you.
She wants me. Me, not you.
So come join me
because you can't beat me.
You can't beat me.
You can't beat me!
Yes, l can!
(BUDDY LAUGHS)
Yes, l can.
Professor, l got your
message. What's up?
l'm going
to that alumni ball tonight,
and l'm gonna reclaim my life.
Yes! l'm so glad
to hear you say that.
Get things straight
with Miss Purty,
and l'm gonna get that grant
from Harlan Hartley.
Excellent.
Jason, we have seen
the last of Buddy Love.
(BIG BAND PLAYS lN THE MOOD)
Horace, good to see you.
The jitterbug contest
just started.
l'm kidding, l'm kidding.
Your table's upstairs.
That's anotherjoke.
When did you marry
Sharon Stone?
Keep those legs crossed.
Hartley. Damn it.
And where the hell
is Buddy Love?
No sign of him yet, sir.
Here's an idea.
Find him!
Yes, sir.
Harlan.
Well, Richmond.
Where's your
Professor Buddy Love?
Oh, with you
it's always business.
Let's get to know each other
man-to-man.
Now, if our files are correct,
you and your fabulous wife
have a terrific daughter.
l'm divorced,
and my daughter is in rehab.
So you're saying
our files are not correct.
Listen,
you pompous butt-kisser.
l have a check in my pocket
for $10 million.
Your Buddy Love
has till midnight
to prove that formula works.
He'll be here,
the formula works,
and you have the check.
Really? On you now?
Because on behalf of...
Which pocket?
No, don't tell me.
Let me smell it. Punch?
Oh, come on, now.
Look at this.
l can't eat this.
This stuff is too tiny.
l can't get full
off this mess!
l think it's wonderful,
all the precious
little finger foods.
Finger food?
l got a finger for them.
l ain't paid no $100 ticket
for no finger food.
l could go down to Subway,
get me a sandwich for $3.
l gotta pay a $100 ticket
for finger food?
You must be crazy
to think l'm gonna eat this...
You're getting on
my damn nerves!
Shut up!
l'm hungry!
There's Carla. l wonder if
she's seen Sherman. Carla!
Carla. Oh.
(LAUGHING)
Oh, you look fabulous.
Thank you, Mrs. Klump.
Have you seen Sherman?
Yeah, where's Sherman at?
l ain't come
to pay no $100 ticket
to suffer this alone.
Cletus, shut up, please!
Hey! That's strike two.
l don't think Sherman
will be coming tonight.
Yes, he is.
Sherman called me and told me
make sure we was here.
He got a big announcement
to make.
Something about getting it
all off his chest.
Have you noticed
that Sherman's been acting
kind of strange lately?
Sherman has definitely
been acting strange lately.
l knew it!
See, Cletus? l told you.
You really think
l be listening to you.
l ain't listening to you!
Well, Mrs. Klump,
l hope you have
a wonderful evening.
Oh, you do the same.
Thank you so much.
So precious.
Look at your
little purple dress.
They gonna think we twins.
(CHUCKLING)
Mr. Klump.
Oh, yeah, yeah.
Fabulous.
You know, Cletus,
l think something's going on
between her and Sherman.
You don't go get up
in Sherman's business.
That's Sherman's business.
Sherman's business?
That's my business.
Sherman is my baby.
Sherman's 35 years old!
What you talking about
he's your baby?
l don't wanna hear it.
Shut up, please!
Carla!
That's strike three, damn it!
Don't you walk away
from me, God damn it!
(MUTTERING)
Hey, this is the last
of it, Professor.
l'll tell you this, Jason.
lf l'm gonna change my life,
it's not gonna come
from some magic drink.
Gotta come from a lot
of hard work and exercise
and plenty of these.
Good bye, Buddy Love.
Hello, Megashake.
(GULPING)
(SCREAMING)
Professor?
Oh!
l lost 300 pounds
in 30 seconds!
Thanks, Megashake!
You tricked him!
You damn right, hamster boy.
l knew Sherman
was gonna go soft on me.
That can wreak havoc
on a man's sex life.
(LAUGHING)
See, l've done
some calculations of my own.
lf l drink 500 milliliters
of formula,
l'll have enough
cellular stability
to be rid of Sherman's ass
forever!
You drink that much formula
at one time
and it will kill you!
lf l drink it all at once,
yes.
lf l drink half now
and half later, that's safe.
At midnight, l don't have
to worry about turning
into no Klumpkin.
lf you don't mind, l have
a date at the alumni ball,
and you have a date
with linoleum.
Who?
(MAMA KLUMP LAUGHS)
No, no, no, child.
Not a wild party.
Not Sherman.
He's too shy
for something like that.
He hates parties.
ln fact, we tried
to have a party for Sherman
when he was 1·-years-old
and he's so shy,
he didn't even show up.
Well, l must admit,
it didn't seem like
the Sherman l knew.
Oh, no, not my baby.
Maybe he loaned his house
out to somebody
or one of his buddies
was throwing a party.
BUDDY: Yeah!
ls that a test tube
in my pocket? Or am l just
happy to see you?
Oh! How dare you?
Oh, you know you loved it.
l felt you percolating.
(GASPS)
Whoo!
Hey, thanks a lot, man.
Thank you so much.
Oh! What you serving here?
This stuff is... Y'all got to
get some collard greens
and yams!
Some red beans and rice!
Some "Buddy" is right.
This ain't no party!
RICHMOND: Dr. Love!
This ain't no ball!
Y'all gotta get y'all
some peach cobbler up in here!
Professor Love!
Where the hell have you been?
l've been nursemaiding Hartley
for three hours,
and if l didn't need
that money...
Shut up!
Who you think
you're talking to,
Sherman Klump?
Man, if you ever talk
to me like that again,
l'll kill you!
l don't mean that
as a euphemism. l mean,
l'm gonna literally kill you.
l'm gonna strangle you
and cut off your air supply
until you pass away!
BUDDY: Now find the rich dummy
a seat. lt's show time.
lt's show time, everybody!
Show time!
(BUDDY CACKLING)
(JASON GROANING)
(BEEPING)
Oh, my God. Oh, my God!
BUDDY: That's enough
out of you! That's it.
You're the reason
everybody falling asleep.
Take a break, Nigger-ace.
Take the Everly Brothers
with you. Get out of here!
Look at everybody sleeping
because of y'all!
lt's show time!
Now why are y'all
looking at me
like y'all don't know me?
Y'all know me!
l don't know that fool.
How about now?
You recognize me?
l don't know that fool.
Maybe it's because
this morning,
l weighed 400 pounds!
You should've seen me.
Look at me now.
You know how l did it?
One sip.
l know why he like that,
'cause he drunk.
Be quiet!
Don't tell me to be quiet!
He drunk!
l like to call it
"Buddy's Wonder Tonic."
l know what wonder tonic
you had.
(WATCH ALARM BEEPING)
Right on schedule.
Cellular destabilization
due to arrive
in exactly three,
(BEEPING)
two, one...
(SLOSHING)
Ain't that a bitch!
What the hell?
My goodness!
Hey, moneybags,
you want a demonstration?
Well, then feast your eyes
on this.
(SLOSHING)
That's a hell of a trick.
(BEEPING)
Ladies and gentlemen,
for my final demonstration...
Look out, David Copperfield.
l'm about to make
a 400-pound fat man
disappear forever!
No! Wait!
l cannot let you
do this anymore!
This has got to stop!
This man is trying to kill
Professor Sherman Klump!
That's it.
l'm glad l brought my knife.
Mmm-hmm.
And l got my razor.
Hand over the vial now!
Oh, sure thing, hamster boy.
But first,
a short musical interlude.
(GASPING)
Buddy!
What has gotten into you,
and where is Sherman?
Sherman is gone!
Disappeared!
(MUTTERING)
What the hell...
And that's a pretty good trick
for a man with an ass
as big as his.
(BEEPING)
Oh! l'm late
for an appointment.
Ladies and gentlemen,
say goodbye to Sherman Klump!
l hate being called
hamster boy.
(GUESTS GASPING)
You just don't know
when to quit, do you?
(GUESTS GASPING)
(GRUNTING)
lt's too late, fat boy.
lt's over!
(STRAINING) Let go! Let go!
My goodness! Damn!
(GRUNTING AND GAGGING)
Give it up, fat boy!
lt's over!
(lN PROFESSOR'S VOICE)
lt ain't over
till the fat professor sings!
(SHRIEKING)
Let go of my hand,
you fat mother...
Say one more word, Buddy,
l'll tear your arm off!
lt's time we take Nestea...
Plunge!
(GRUNTING)
(SOBBING)
Gonna get the hell out of here
in a second. lt's okay.
(GRUNTING)
Sweet Jesus!
Sherman!
Sherman, don't do this!
You need me!
No, l don't!
You fat ass!
Tinkerbell!
Blubber butt!
Featherweight!
Somebody better call
an exorcist!
Sherman! Sherman!
You can't beat me!
This is some scary shit!
(GRUNTING)
Yes, l can!
(ALARM BEEPING)
Sherman, come back here!
Sherman!
What's happening to me?
Everything's getting
real dark! Oh!
l feel real jiggly!
(PANTING) l'm blubbifying!
Sherman!
You need me!
l taught you to be confident!
You needed me, Sherman!
Sherman! No matter what!
No matter what,
you got to strut.
(CROWD GASPS)
(SIGHS)
(CROWD MOANING)
l ain't gonna be picking up
your big ass all night, Anna.
Shit.
(GASPS)
Oh, my God.
Well, l'll be damned.
(EXHALES)
lf you give me a moment,
l believe
l can try to explain.
My research is...
Well, when l started out l...
l wanted to help people.
But l became desperate
and selfish.
What l did was wrong.
Buddy's who l thought
the whole world
wanted me to be.
He's who l thought
l wanted to be.
And sometimes
when you want something
so, so bad,
you do just about anything
to get it.
But l learned one thing
from Buddy.
l learned
that life is not about
being happy
about how much you weigh,
but just being happy
with yourself.
l'm terribly sorry
about all this.
l hope l haven't ruined
everybody's evening.
Please excuse me.
(WHISPERING) l'm sorry.
Sherman!
Sherman, wait a minute.
Sherman,
why did you lie to me?
Why didn't you say anything?
l didn't think you'd have me.
l mean,
the fact of the matter is
l'm a big man.
Now, l will lose weight,
but l'm always gonna be big
no matter what l do.
So, anybody l wind up with
is just going to have to
accept me for who l am.
And more important,
l'm just going to have to
accept myself for who l am.
Sherman,
l don't have a date tonight.
Would you like to dance
with me?
(SOFT CHUCKLE)
JASON: Professor,
l thought you might need this.
(CHUCKLES)
(CHUCKLING) Yeah, l guess
l tore this one up, huh?
(LAUGHING)
You know one thing
l couldn't stand
about that Buddy?
What's that?
He was too damn scrawny.
(BOTH CHUCKLING)
Okay, Professor! Looking good!
Have l mentioned we also have
a terrific English Department?
l'm giving him the grant.
What?
l hate to admit it,
but you're absolutely right.
He's a brilliant scientist
and a gentleman as well.
Well, l told you!
HARTLEY: Will you shut up!
l'm fine with that.
Oh, Sherman, Sherman,
Sherman, Sherman, Sherman,
Sherman, Sherman!
(LAUGHING)
Light as a feather tonight.
Come on, bump me.
Yeah!
(GASPS)
Oh, oh, my goodness!
l'm so sorry. l'm sorry.
You didn't hurt yourself,
did you?
(CHUCKLES) l'm fine.
(BOTH LAUGHING)
Yeah!
Fabulous!
(MACHO MAN PLAYING)
(FARTING)
Oh, my Lord!
(BOTH LAUGHING)
(LAUGHING) Don't start.
Do it again.
Go on, fart! l hope
your asshole fall out...
(LAUGHING)
l thought it just was...
l thought a colonic
was a massage.
(LAUGHING)
(CREW LAUGHING)
For only research, and...
(LAUGHING)
(CREW LAUGHING)
What? What film is this?
Your research.
Get back in there!
(LAUGHING)
We ain't ready for you yet.
Now what were you saying?
Hold on a minute.
Let me go deal with my girl.
What's wrong with y'all?
Professor Klump,
the cages, what happened?
They can't see me
with your head there.
(CREW LAUGHING)
l made a fart last week.
lt smelled so bad
it had a chain
hanging from it.
(LAUGHING)
(CREW LAUGHING)
(MUFFLED) l can't talk.
l seen Sherman
get so hungry once
when he was young,
he beat up a grown man.
(CREW LAUGHING)
l'm sorry.
(LAUGHING)
l'm freaking out over here
'cause Eddie's over here
saying some wild crap.
Do you...
(LAUGHING)
(FARTING)
(LAUGHING) Oh!
You're supposed to say,
"Excuse me."
(FARTING)
Oh! Oh, baby, you...
(LAUGHING)
Hey, little Hercules,
you want some more coleslaw?
(CREW LAUGHING)
Come on, Cletus. Come on.
No (BEEP) it... Come on.
Come on, Cletus.
Come on. Come on, Cletus!
(CREW LAUGHING)
Come on! Come on, Cletus. No.
Come on, come on.
No (BEEP) it... Come on.
Come on, come on, come on,
let's do this.
Let's do this!
(LAUGHING)
Hey, yeah, yeah, yeah
Hey, hey
Ooo
Oh
Yeah, hey, hey, yeah
Boy, you got a lot to learn
about love
You just gotta get down
with the right equation
Put down that book
and see what you're missing
Missing
Come and get your A
Come and get it,
come and get it
come and get it,
Ooo
Homework
Something that you got to do
lt's a school rule
And you know
you got to go through
First grade
before you get to graduation
Homework
Welcome to your education
Learn a little every day
Homework
Know a little every day
Another Friday night
Another honey
sitting in my ride
Another lyrical favor
from your sexy neighbor
Make you wave your hands
from side to side
ln '95 we did it
But this year
l bring a new twist
You see, l'm hear to announce
this song of a bounce
So everybody bounce 2 this
lt's so right
lt's so nice
l tell you, it'll make you
wanna bounce 2 this
Bounce 2 this, bounce 2 this
Yeah, it's so right
lt's so nice
l tell you it'll make you
wanna bounce 2 this
Bounce 2 this, bounce 2 this
Yeah, it's so right
Come on, baby
New York, bounce 2 this
Come on, now
Yeah, bounce 2 this
Atlanta, bounce 2 this
Yeah
Come on, baby, bounce 2 this
D.C with a go-go
Bounce 2 this
You know l mean it
lt's all right
l been to parties
across the USA
l've been to other countries
and l made those people say
For dinner,
oh, my cup is finally low
So pass the yellow Z
and hold on now
Ladies, help me sing it
WOMEN: l wanna party
across the USA
You go, sugar
l've been to other countries
and l heard those people say
For dinner
My cup was running low
Now pass the yellow Z
and let the music play
And act like you know
it's all right
lt's all right
lt's so nice
And l'll make you
wanna bounce 2 this
Bounce 2 this, bounce 2 this
l can tell
lt's so nice
You wanna boogie
l can tell
you wanna boogie, baby
With Montell you wanna boogie
lt's so nice