Aaah!
[ Laughing, Yelling ]
Heart of Darkness.
[ Laughing, Yelling
Continue ]
It.
Wow. Do you read anything
besides Stephen King?
Hell, no.
Journey to the Center
ofthe Earth.
Now, that was a classic.
Man, how does yourwife
put up with you?
All right, here we go.
Look.
Bravo, this is Sierra.
We have a black S.U.V. approaching.
[ Man On Radio ]
Roger that, Sierra.
Right on time.
[ Laughter, Yelling Continue ]
Okay. We gotta go.
We gotta change position.
[ Laughing ]
[ Sizzling ]
Clear.
[ Chattering ]
- [ Shouting In Foreign Language ]
- Bravo, this is Sierra.
Weapons confirmed.
[ Bravo ]
Check.
- Engagement orders.
- Simmer down, big guy.
We got plenty oftime.
[ Speaking Foreign Language ]
[ Continues In Foreign Language ]
[ Spotter]
You seein' this?
Unreal.
What the hell
is that guy doin' here?
[ Spotter]
Bravo, requesting
new target ofopportunity—
High-value target,
Sanan Alhad.
[ Bravo ]
Identity confirmed, Sierra.
You have execute authorization.
Please be aware, there is no Eagle extract.
- We may not get another shot.
- It's your call,
but we're out here alone.
- [ Clattering ]
- [ Grunts ]
Shit. Shh.
Okay, we got six
visible targets.
Ifthey get their hands on those boxes,
it's gonna get hot up here.
Target locked.
[ Scope Whirring ]
[ Groans ]
- [ Boy Shouts ]
- [ Yelling ]
Ohh!
Go!
[ Screaming ]
[ Sound Muffled ]
Come on, kid.
Come on. You can do it.
You can do it.
Breathe.
He's gone, man.
No.Just gimme a minute.
No! Hey.
We gotta go, man.
Go. Go!
Come on!
[ Gunfire, Screams Echoing ]
[ Spotter's Voice ]
Come on, man. He's gone!
Hi, baby.
Hey, sweetheart.
Oh, my God.
It is so good to see your face.
- Oh, you too.
- Everything good?
I'm comin' home
for a couple weeks.
Really?
Yeah.
Well, that's great news.
That means you can be
my "plus one."
- Plus what?
- All right, you remember me
talking about Darren Conner,
my super-rich client,
owns, like, a bazillion
different businesses—
Real estate, hotels, casinos—
Yeah. The one who wrote
that stupid get-rich book.
- Yeah.
- What was it?
Why Shouldn't You Have It All?
[ Chuckles ]
He's opening a new resort,
and guess who's in charge
of his super-deluxe,
invite-only opening bash.
- Who?
- You're an ass.
Yeah, sometimes.
So how about it?
Five days ofsun, beach—
It'sjust a short trip
foryou.
I was reallyjust lookin' forward
to gettin' back home—
back to Michigan.
[ Woman ]
I'm sorry.
It's myjob.
Bad timing, I know.
Why don't you just come home?
No. No, wait. Look.
You're my home, and—
[ Exhales ]
it doesn't matter where I am.
[ Chuckles ]
I love you back.
Oh, my God.
Isn't it beautiful?
Yeah. Sure is.
Hmm.
You're still
a little far away, huh?
[ Sighs ]
A little bit, yeah.
[ Man, Faintly ]
Hello! Welcome.
Thankyou forjoining us.
Can I get your bags
foryou, ma'am?
[ Woman ]
It's beautiful!
[ Man ] Right this way.
Enjoy!
Right?
Aw, it's okay, I guess.
I mean, ifyou're
into paradise and all,
you know?
Oh!
Ohh!
[ Laughs ]
Oh, you wanna fight, huh?
That serves you right.
- Robin? Nice to finally meet you.
- Oh, my gosh.
Cynthia, this is my husband.
Joe.
Robin's told me a lot
about you. Nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you.
Our goal is to have the most
energy-efficient resort...
in this part
ofthe word.
As you know, this island
rests in close proximity...
to the volcanic corridor.
Oh, yeah.
Everyone knows that, huh?
[ Cynthia ]
So we've constructed
our own geothermal plant,
allowing us to use
heat for power.
Impressive security.
Yes!
Twenty-four hour
armed guards
in security towers.
Top-of-the-line
surveillance.
We are actually having
our opening party
here tomorrow night.
[Joe ]
You're goin' in. Come here.
[ Grunts ]
[ Robin Squeals, Laughs ]
[Joe Grunts, Laughs ]
Be careful.
I gotta go
to a meeting.
I mean, I knowyou see
exotic spots like this
all the time,
but this is pretty decent
for us civilian folk.
Sierra, you copy?
Affirmative.
Hmm.
You know, I haven't
seen you like this since—
Well, since ever.
Last one
was bad, huh?
Yeah. Itjust went a little sideways.
Anything
you could have done?
I don't know. I just got
a closer look than I usually get.
[ Robin ]
You wanna talk
about it?
Just thinkin' about a change.
Well—
Not to put ideas
in your head, but—
You know
I'm proud ofyou,
whetheryou're
saving the world
or sweeping a floor.
[ Laughs ]
You know, I knew there was
some good reason I married you.
You have very low expectations.
[ Laughs ]
[ Man ]
It's so nice to see
someone's having a good time.
I wasjust waiting
foryou to arrive.
Darren Conner,
this is my husband.
Joe Linwood.
A soldier, right?
Actually, he's a marine.
Hmm. Right.
Can I talk with you?
I'm getting 20 phone calls an hour
from some Kusang representative.
They have a reporter
from some local rag up my ass...
for an interview
I do not want to give,
and some Greenpeace lawyer...
trying to hit me
with injunctions.
So could you just please
do yourjob now, thankyou?
Absolutely. On my way.
It was a pleasure.
We need to replace
the champagne.
Yes, sir.
That piss in the kitchen
I would not give
to my dog.
And you thought
yourjob was dangerous, huh?
No. I like him. Really.
[ Chuckles ]
I'll be back
as soon as I can.
Got a surprise foryou.
[ Conner, Man Talking,
Indistinct ]
Hi.
Uh, listen.
What's that kid doing
fishing on the beach?
[ Man ] May I suggest
an electrical fence
for these darkies?
[ Conner ] Forget the
electrical fence. You've
gotta clean up the beach.
[ Continues, Indistinct ]
[ Twittering ]
Oh.
Watch out now.
Watch your head.
Aaah—
Thanks.
- [ Groans ]
- [Joe ] Hello?
Hey.
Closed.
Sorry. I'm from the resort.
They said you could be booked
for a snorkeling tour.
We're not exactly
up and running yet.
Do tell.
[ Chuckles ]
Oh, come on. Please?
A favor foryour
fellow Yankees?
Oh, hell.
Ifyou're gonna hit me in that
soft spot of mine, I guess so.
Butjust so you know—
one Yankee to another--
I'm gonna overcharge ya.
- Oh, well, thanks
for the heads-up.
- He talk?
Uh, not if he
can get away with it.
Oh.
Trophy husband.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Your choice.
Okay. Thankyou.
You a grunt?
[ Chuckles ]
No.
Jarhead.
Yeah. Marine.
Mmm. I thought so.
Where you out of?
Parris Island or Pendleton?
Pendleton.
- Oh. Hollywood monkey, huh?
- [ Chuckles ]
Force Recon. You?
Just a regular S.F. ranger.
Explosives. Engineer. I blew shit up.
- Powder monkey, huh?
- [ Laughs ]
Uh, once upon a time, huh?
Joe.
Joe? Church.
Good to meet you.
Nice to meet you.
Come on.
Let's get you all geared up.
Yeah?
Yeah.
Does, uh—
Does this mean you're
not gonna overcharge me now?
[ Chuckles ]
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
[ Church ]
Yellow-- Good choice.
Sharks love yellow.
- [Joe ] That's great, baby.
- [ Robin ] He'sjoking.
Go ahead.
Turn around and look.
[ Robin ]
Oh, my God.
[Joe Chuckles ]
Joe?
Geez.
None ofthis was on any
ofthe maps until your
fancy resort showed up.
Mmm. Gets better.
The other end ofthat beach—
There's a cave.
Leads you right back
to your resort.
Just make sure
you head west, okay?
They teach you that in
the Marine Corps, don't they--
Difference between
east and west?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Oh!
Whoa!
Go get him, honey.
I will.
Whoo.
[ Laughing ]
Enjoyyourselves.
[ Robin ]
Thankyou. Bye.
This is amazing.
You know, it could be
like this all the time--
You, me—
Jet-setting around
the world.
Your professional
"plus one"?
Yeah.
Until the first day
you got bored.
I know who
I married,Joe,
and I couldn't
be happier.
Yeah, right. This goes
back to the resort.
Yeah. Wow.
- That's east.
We gotta go west.
- Yeah.
- Oh.
- [ Chuckles ]
That sorry powder monkey.
Well, Church was right.
Mm-hmm.
You wanna go back?
Mmm. Come on.
I have a party
to organize.
♪♪ [ SoftJazz ]
[ Indistinct Conversations ]
[ Woman ]
You know, they put one
in every room.
[ Woman ]
Robin!
Hi.
How are you?
Good to see you.
♪♪ [ Continues ]
I'm sure I wasn't like that,
but it was a good one.
That reporter
was nosing around again.
Only this time,
he was pestering
Mr. Chevault...
about his opinion
on the Greenpeace
legal action against me.
Need I remind you that
Mr. Chevault is one of
our major shareholders?
So that isjust not acceptable.
My apologies, Mr. Conner.
I'll get right on it.
Oh, please,
now that the damage is done—
I mean—
-Joe.
- Oh, great. G.I.Joe's here.
What? You got an opinion?
Oryou just gonna kick my ass?
[ Chuckles ]
No, sir.
See, unlike some,
I don't pick on women
half my size.
Oh.
And "G.I." is army,
moron.
I'm a marine.
Okay,Joe. It's fine.
No, Robin, it's not.
Hey, hey. It's fine.
Joe? Please. It's fine.
Number one--
I'm sorry about that.
It will not happen again.
Number two-- The reason
you're having trouble
with the reporter...
is because you constantly
ignore my recommendation
tojust give him 20 minutes.
Twenty minutes ofyour time.
I'm not gonna talk
with any reporter about—
You answer the questions
you want, and when he
brings up the injunctions,
you smile sweetly
and say it's all
being worked out.
It can only
help you look better,
and not like a rich
American outsider
with something to hide.
However,
first things first.
You have
an opening speech to give.
Okay.
[ Robin ]
Good evening, friends,
colleagues and investors.
I would like to introduce you
to our host, the chairman
ofConner Industries,
Mr. Darren Conner.
[ Applause ]
Thanks.
Ladies and gentlemen,
you honor me by being
the first official guests...
ofour magnificent
new experience.
Welcome to the Tanjalla
Beach Resort,
where you will never
have to askyourself,
"Why shouldn't I have it all?"
[ Guests Applauding ]
You know, before
I created Tanjalla,
there was nothing here--
Well, nothing but
a wasted opportunity.
This fabulous island was flawed
by inefficiency, archaic thinking...
and a subsequent
lack ofemployment
for the local population.
But I have changed all that.
Water, fire, earth, air—
- They are not only—
- Hey, marine!
[ Laughs ]
[ Firecracker Pops ]
Crazy-ass powder monkey.
Hey, man.
How manyjobs
you got, anyway?
Oh, I've been known
to moonlight.
Gonna have a good show tonight.
Here. Look at this.
Get a kick outta this.
Pop flare.
I throw it up at the end
for old times' sake.
Ah. Military's
night light.
Nobody else gets it,
but I don't give a shit.
Hmm.
[ Applause ]
What's goin' on?
You and the little woman havin' a thing?
Her boss was bein' an asshole,
and somehow...
I'm the bad guy.
Yeah, well, don't take it
personal, all right?
You gotta remember,
she's on her own
most ofthe time.
Can't be waitin' around
foryour sorry ass to show up.
Be all macho for her, right?
[ Chuckles ]
- Yeah.
- Look, brother,
I'm not the kind ofguy
to be givin' a lot ofadvice.
If I were you,
I'd polish offthose kneepads,
head back up there
and tell her how sorry I was.
Couple young things like you—
I can guarantee you,
the make-up sex would be well worth it.
[ Chuckles ]
That how you did it?
Nope.
Yeah, look at me now, right?
King ofthe world, Ma.
[ Laughs ]
Yeah, I guess so.
Mmm. Go on. Beat it.
I'm about to
light this place up.
Solar energy from the sun.
Hydroelectric
from the ocean.
Geothermal
from the earth.
And the harnessing
ofwind.
On behalf
ofConner Industries
I thankyou,
and wish you
a very enjoyable vacation.
- Here's to it!
- [ Man ]
Yeah! Hear, hear! Bravo!
Nicejob.
These hicks wouldn't know...
a thermodynamic converter
from a hot fart.
All they care is it says
"please recycle" on it.
What's next?
Mingling with guests.
Excuse me. Mr. Conner?
Hate to interrupt.
[ Boom ]
[ Whistling ]
What?
[ Man ]
Jump!
[ Shouting ]
- [ Man Shouts ]
- [ Clamoring ]
[ Groans, Screams ]
Get down. Get down!
[ Sound Muffled ]
- [ Indistinct ]
- [ Explosions, Gunfire Continue ]
[ Woman ]
No! No!
- [ Man's Voice ]
He's gone.
-Joe!
[ Grunts ]
[ Bones Crack ]
Aaah!
[ Grunting ]
[ Groans ]
[ Man ]
Stop screaming.
Nowyou just
stop right there.
Who are you?
- What— What do you think
you're doing here?
- Hello, Mr. Conner.
- [ Grunts ]
- [ Conner Groans ]
[ Grunting, Groaning ]
Joe!
Come on. Get up, buddy.
Gotta get outta here.
Let's go. Let's go.
Come on.
- [ Explosion ]
-Joe!
Robin.
[ Church ]
Stay calm. You've been out
a couple hours.
[ Grunts ]
She still inside?
[ Exhales, Grunts ]
[ Indistinct Conversations ]
[ Man ]
Okay. You have floor plan for hotel?
[ Man #2 ]
Right here.
Get some more bandages.
[ Overlapping Conversations ]
[ Man ]
Right here, sir.
It's gonna be okay.
Local authorities are on it.
Just try to relax, all right?
Hey! We're on TV.
It's on TV now.
Early reports of
a terrorist attack
on Tanjalla Beach Resort...
capturing as many
as 20 hostages.
We have confirmation
that this video, uploaded
via Internet minutes ago,
- comes from inside the resort.
- [ Crowd Clamoring ]
[ Conner]
Please-- All right! Don't!
Robin.
For the last century
we have watched helplessly...
as the disease
ofthe Western world...
has spread across our islands.
Now it is your turn
to watch.
We will kill all the hostages
in 24 hours.
Ifyou wish
to spare their lives,
you must pay tribute.
- Tribute?
- Infidels.
That's you and me, buddy.
They gotta pay tribute
for their crimes.
[ Man ]
Like money.
Ransom.
[ Man ]
What? No, no.
- No!
- [ Clamoring ]
Don't watch this, kid.
- [ Shouting ]
- [ Crowd Clamoring ]
No!
You gotta help me...
get her back.
Ho, ho. Oh, whoa.
Time-out here.
Look, there's nothing
we can do about that.
It's the military'sjob.
Listen, brother,
I was never a hero,
all right?
Okay in a group,
part ofa team,
but somethin' like this?
No. I'm sorry, man.
Sorry. Can't do it.
[ Explosion ]
[ Screams ]
[ Clamoring ]
- Stop!
- Shh, shh, shh.
Listen to me.
We will do whateveryou want.
Just don't hurt anyone.
You don't have
to threaten us, okay?
We can't identifyyou.
We haven't seen your faces.
No!
Nowyou have.
[ Screams ]
[ Woman Sobbing ]
- Stay calm.
- I wanna see my family.
For the love ofChrist,
just stay calm.
Stay calm.
- Who are these people?
- [ Robin ]
They're separatists--
fighting the spread
ofWestern influence
on their country.
You know what?
People are working
on getting us out. Okay?
- So wejust gotta stay calm,
and think with clear heads.
- [ Man ] You're right.
[ Woman Screams ]
No!
After that broadcast,
there is no way for us
to keep this quiet.
What?
Makil Shoal—
diplomatic adviser on behalf
ofthe Kusang government.
- Blueprints to the resort.
- [ Man Shouting In Distance ]
We have the perimeter
surrounded.
But I will not attack...
until we know more
about the terrorists.
That's all right, Commander.
I'm taking care ofthis.
- Who's in charge?
- Sir! This is off-limits.
Please wait over there.
No. Somebody's gonna
talk to me. Now.
Wait.
Let me.
[ Shoal ]
I apologize for that.
You know, dealing
with the military--
It's like playing chicken
with a brick wall.
No offense, ofcourse.
What's being done
about the hostages?
I'm afraid I can't
discuss it with you, Mr.—
Joe.
Two days is unacceptable.
I will be dead tomorrow.
Just make it happen.
The money is on its way.
- Tribute.
- Yeah, sure. Tribute.
Whateveryou wanna call it.
You touch just one hair on my head—
You can kiss it all good-bye.
Look,just let us go.
The money is on its way.
You got what you want.
No. I got
what I asked for.
We were living in paradise
long before the Great White Hope...
came to our shores
to save us from our happiness.
You don't know
what I want!
Think it's working?
Either way, little brother,
the message will be sent.
It's all falling
into place.
This is a political disaster.
[ Sighs ]
I am the one who convinced
my government...
to allow Conner Industries
to purchase the old resort
from the local owners.
Now I have to negotiate
the release ofthe hostages.
I can't believe this is happening.
I'm with Conner Security.
Are you sending in
troops?
Ohh, my government
is extremely reticent...
to engage in military action.
Ifthey should storm in
and the hostages are killed,
we could have a—
an international incident.
And we're still waiting
on word from the U.S.,
which means they're waiting to see
how we deal with the problem.
So what do you plan
to do?
- I've already done it.
- [ Vehicle Approaching ]
Mercenaries.
Better trained than most
ofour soldiers.
And accustomed
to dirty work.
[ Man ]
Get out.
Skunk. How are you?
Hey, thanks.
They're for sale
to the highest bidder.
Better than letting them die.
Hey, Blondie--
Nervous, orwhat?
Thank you for responding
so quickly.
Who's that?
He's with Conner Securities.
Marine Recon.
Congratulations.
Now get him out of here.
I'm goin' in
with you.
Uh-huh.
Look, I've been inside.
I know the layout.
Please, sir.
-Just leave it to us.
- With or without you,
I'm goin' in.
You do-- I'll consideryou
an enemy and shoot you
on sight.
[ Shoal ]
You need to stand down.
I'm taking over.
[ Sobbing ]
[ Chambers Round ]
- [ Footsteps ]
- [Joe ]
Hey.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Let me take him.
Blondie— Team 2.
You come with me.
Team 1 .
[ Man On Radio
Speaking Foreign Language ]
Can you tell me
what they're saying?
I don't know.
"The intruders
will be dead"?
[ Mercenary ]
Team 2, copy.
[ Mercenary On Radio ]
Team 2— Copy.
Team 2.
[ "Silenced" Gunshots ]
Something's wrong.
Move. Quick.
[ Man ]
Damn.
Shot in the back--
All of'em.
And the last one's missing.
Blondie. Ifthey had a traitor,
then maybe we have one too.
[ Groans ]
It's a trap.
Take cover!
[ Gunfire Continues ]
[ Clamoring ]
Aaah! I'm hit!
[ Groans ]
[ Screams ]
[ Grunts ]
Come on! Move!
Come on, let's go!
Move! Come on!
Get in. Come on.
Let's go.
[ Yells ]
[ Hostages Gasping ]
Somebody's gonna die.
You!
[ Women Whimpering ]
No, no, no!
- No!
- Please! Please, don't!
Please!
Calm down, little brother.
[ Grunting ]
Kill them all!
[ Yelling ]
[ Objects Clattering ]
You took charge!
I was trying to help.
I was trying
to save the hostages.
I had to do something.
You compromised everything
with your help!
You are done.
Get out of my sight.
[ Yelling ]
Calm down. Calm down. Calm down.
Just tell me what happened.
Calm down.
Blondie said there was
an American marine with them!
Is he still alive?
No, he's dead!
But he killed our men!
Our men!
[ Sobbing ]
Oh, my God!
How did they infiltrate
your team?
We are mercenaries.
We work for
the highest bidder.
I guess they paid more.
Can you please
step out?
We must make an example!
We must make a statement!
Kill them all now.
Not yet. Not yet.
Robin.
I really--
[ Sighs ]
I am really very sorry.
We have to wait
for the tribute.
Now, stay focused.
They must pay
for this, brother.
Yes, they will. They will!
They will.
Just be patient.
Be patient.
A small example,
brother.
[ Exhales ]
You gonna be okay?
Oh.
Could you please
deliver my message—
[ Groans ]
to Blondie?
Her and her.
[ Conner ]
Hey, what are you doing?
What are you doing?
Blood for blood.
You take my people,
I take yours.
You already took those men
you killed out there.
You got your blood!
Now you'rejust
a hypocrite!
Everybody thinks you are.
- [ Woman ] No, please!
- Move it!
- Stop!
Just stop right there.
You'll only get your tribute
ifyou can prove
I'm alive and well.
I'll make you kill me
if I have to.
- [ Grunting ]
- [ Woman Gasping ]
[ Woman ]
No, don't! Oh!
You made your point.
Enjoy the moment.
Burn it in your brain.
There'll come a time when
you're more useful to us
dead than alive.
[ Groans ]
Church.
I need your help.
I'm goin' to rescue.
You're goin' back in?
[ Panting ]
I got no choice.
Ahh.
Look, someone's gotta
help these people.
Well then, brother,
you got a real
death wish.
Maybe.
Come on.
My office.
Take whateveryou need.
Tell me somethin'.
What good are you gonna do her
ifyou get yourself killed?
Church. Help me.
The two of us
together, man,
with our backgrounds—
No, no, no, no, bro.
I already told you, man.
Not everybody can be
a hero, kid.
[ Sighs ]
Then let me borrow
your boat.
Wait a minute.
[ Church ]
This is as far as I go, kid.
Get ready!
Give 'em hell, marine!
[ Birdcalls ]
[ Footsteps Overhead ]
[ Chattering ]
You let that American
storm back in there!
I didn't let him
do anything.
You're in charge now,
remember?
Ifyou let him
slip through your fingers,
that's your problem.
It means somebody's
doing something.
[ Man Shouting On Radio
In Foreign Language ]
They lost more men.
Somebody's on the grounds.
Rescue party.
I don't think so.
They're not talking about
soldiers or men. They're
talking about one person.
One? They sent
one guy after us?
They keep calling him
"the American."
Your marine friend seems
to not have heard you when
you pronounced him dead.
I will cut out his heart!
Blondie. Bantoc.
Continue with the plan.
[Joe ]
Where are you going, Blondie?
[ Both Speaking
Foreign Language ]
[ Beeps ]
Go.
[ Grunts ]
I know you'rejust
in it for the money.
So unless you really
wanna die for the cause,
you tell me where they are.
[ Grunting ]
Where are they?
Where are they at?
I never talk.
You never talk?
[ Yelling ]
Where are they?
Huh? Huh?
[ Groans ]
No? Okay.
- No!
- What's over here?
[ Yelling ]
Where are they? Huh?
Where's my wife?
Where is she?
[ Foreign Language ]
Huh?
Restaurant?
Yeah.
Restaurant.
Oh, yeah.
Calob wanted me
to give you a message.
He's in the boiler room.
He can't go anywhere.
Lock it down!
Make sure this time
he dies.
You talked, didn't you?
You disappoint me.
We've heard
from the Americans.
They have the tribute.
You come with me.
All right. All right!
All right.
We have not harmed you.
We have not harmed
any more ofyour people.
We have kept ourword.
Yes?
Finalize the transfer,
but only after the—
Only after the hostages
have been released.
[ Groans ]
Shit!
[ Grunting ]
[ Neck Bones Crack ]
Mr. Shoal!
In here!
We heard
from the terrorists.
- They're ready
to release the hostages.
- Why?
Conner's family must be
giving them the money.
They denied it.
But—
What do you need?
The terrorists
have one condition.
They'll only release
the hostages to you.
I don't understand.
They told us they want
a representative
ofthe Kusang government.
You do realize
there's a possibility...
they're still planning
to kill the hostages.
And having
a government official's
head on a plate...
will just sweeten
the message.
I will take the chance.
I have already
endangered them too much.
Ifthere's any possibility
they're telling the truth—
I might have misjudged you.
He's on board.
[ Explosion ]
[ Men Yelling ]
- [ Gunfire ]
- [ Shouting, Indistinct ]
[ Fireworks Whistling, Exploding ]
Son ofa bitch.
Cease fire!
Go check it out.
Stay behind me.
[ Explosions Continue ]
Robin.
It's your husband.
- Robin.
-Joe. Oh, my--
[ Sobbing ]
Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
It's all right.
[ Firecrackers Continue ]
- So you're it?
- Keep your voice down.
What's our next move?
We run. Okay?
Come on.
Hey!
Get down.
[ All Gasping ]
[ Scattered Whimpers ]
[ Grunts ]
[ Muffled Grunt ]
[ Screams ]
[ Shoal ]
This is all my fault,
you know. I pursued Conner.
[ Muffled ]
You son ofa bitch!
I convinced him to bring
his money to Kusang,
to share some ofthat
famous Western prosperity,
to build a palace
I couldn't even afford
a room in.
You know, when the deal
was signed, I didn't get
so much as a thankyou.
But when Conner here...
started diverting
the water supply...
and making this island
his own private toilet,
who got the blame?
All my life,
I gave to this island.
Never once
did it give back to me.
And then Damo came to me.
He promised
to restore the balance--
to take back
what was stolen from us.
To be perfectly honest,
at this point,
all I care about is the money.
[Joe ]
You killed
the mercenaries.
Just sent them to die.
That was my part ofthe deal.
I send in the mercenaries.
Their failure forces
the military to stand down.
I just had to be sure they failed.
Then why should Damo
keep you alive?
We are freedom fighters,
he and I.
- And Damo
wouldn't kill a brother.
- [ Door Opens ]
The tribute is in the accounts.
How about my portion?
Oh, don't worry.
You'll get your share.
Plus, a bonus.
Thought you freedom fighters
didn't care about money.
Because we live in caves
and eat bugs.
Our money doesn't go
to Happy Meals.
Weapons, warriors.
A thousand more men like me
dedicated to the cause.
Plus, a few other goodies.
Hey. Hey.
What are you guys doing?
Hey, what are you doing?
Finishing what we started.
Hey—
These noble volunteers...
will help us bring down
this monstrosity
once and for all.
You got your money, right?
You sent your message.
This... is the message.
I helped you.
I helped the cause.
Don't make us laugh.
You're a worm who thinks
he's a crow.
You couldn't have
done this without me.
Finally, Shoal—
You get something—
[ Beeps ]
exactly right.
Please!
[ Grunts ]
Make us laugh,
freedom fighter!
No! No!
[ Yells ]
[ Hostages Gasping ]
Like you say in your book,
Mr. Conner,
why shouldn't I
have it all?
[ Muffled ]
Bastard.
We had a deal!
You've got to let them go!
[ Women Whimpering ]
You got the money!
You got me!
[ Damo ]
You disapprove?
You've never
sacrificed innocents
to get thejob done?
Innocents always die in war.
But the goal is to save people,
not kill them to win.
[ Sobbing ]
You see?
You do understand
what it means
to make a statement.
Robin! Robin!
He's all yours.
[ Blade Scraping ]
[ Sobbing ]
Please.
[ Screams ]
[ Straining, Screaming ]
[ Beeps ]
[ Bone Cracks ]
[ Damo On Radio ]
Are they secured?
Are the hostages secured?
Somebody come back.
Are they secured?
- [ Bones Cracking ]
- [ Screaming ]
[ Damo On Radio ]
Somebody talk to me.
Come back!
[ Yells ]
[ Damo On Radio ]
Do you hear me?
Come in.
Are they secured?
[ Gunshot ]
Brother, talk to me.
Come back. Are they secured?
They teach you that
in the army? Nice shot.
It was dumb luck.
What can I say?
Thanks.
Church.
[ Damo ] Come in, brother.
Do you hear me?
Go get him.
Start cuttin'.
Hurry up.
Okay.
Are you there, brother?
- Move, move, move!
- Come in. Are they secured?
Are the prisoners secured?
Someone come back, now!
They're comin'.
Go back.
Kill them all.
- Yes, sir.
- No!
[ Beeping ]
[ Church ]
Hurry it up!
This place
is wired to blow!
Move 'em out of here!
[ Shouting, Indistinct ]
- Run! Run!
- Pick it up! Come on!
Come on, people! Move!
[ Beeping ]
[ Yelling ]
- [ Gasping ]
- Here!
You're gonna be okay.
Can you use this?
Sure, sure.
Just point and pull
the trigger. Go!
[ Beeping ]
[ Panicked Chattering ]
Everybody, move in now!
Joe!
I'm over here!
Let me go!
Bomb—
-Joe! A bomb!
- [ Device Beeping ]
[ Panting ]
[ Conner]
Well, thank God
you all made it out.
Hell ofa show, huh?
[ Bird Twittering ]
Where'd they go?
Which way?
This guy won't die.
[ Gunshot ]
Give me my wife back,
you son ofa bitch.
Can you give my brother back?
[ Gunshot ]
[ Child Shouts ]
[ Woman Screams ]
-Joe?
- Robin!
Get me out of here!
Quick! Get me out!
Joe!
[ Groaning ]
Joe?
[ Sobs ]
[ Screams ]
Leave him alone!
This will never stop
with the tribute.
There'll be
a thousand more like me!
No!
It ends with you!
Go, go, go, go,
go, go, go, go!
[ Damo ]
We'll die together!
[ Both Coughing ]
[ Panting ]
Geez.
Yeah.
I thought myjob
was dangerous.
I love you so much.
Let's go home.
English - US - Placed SDH