(WOMAN SINGING
TRADITIONAL CHINESE MELODY)
-== [ www.OpenSubtitles.org ] ==-
(DRAMATIC DRUMMING)
(TEMPO INCREASES)
NARRATOR:
Everything in this world
has a time and a place.
A long time ago,
there lived a kind emperor
who ruled the lands of China.
One day, the kingdom
was invaded by warring tribes.
For months,
the emperor fought valiantly,
but his army was outnumbered.
(WEAPONS CLASH)
The kingdom was
on the verge of defeat.
(MAN GROANS, HORSE WHINNIES)
At this time,
the Celestial Dragon
appeared before the emperor.
He offered the emperor
the source of all his power--
the Dragon Pearl.
With this pearl, the emperor's
remaining 300 warriors
were transformed
into a mighty army of 3,000.
(WEAPONS CLASH)
The emperor was victorious.
(CHEERING)
But in the confusion of battle,
the pearl was lost.
His failure
to return the pearl
filled the emperor
with grief.
He soon fell ill and died.
And so, searching
for its missing pearl,
the dragon waited for the time
when it could return home.
(GATE SCRAPES)
(METALLIC RATTLING)
Hey!
Hey, hey, hey, hey!
Back. Get back!
(CLANG)
CHRIS:
You put that down.
Put it down!
Aah!
(BOTH GRUNTING)
Give me the book!
(GRUNTING)
(SHOUTING)
(GLASS BREAKS)
(GROANING)
(MAN SHOUTING)
Aah!
(CRASH)
(GROANING)
(BOTH GROANING)
Huh?
Hah!
No! Stop, for heaven's
sake, will you?
Oh!
Hey!
(GASPS, PANTS)
Chris...
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
you okay?
(THUNDER)
(GROANS)
You okay?
No, not really.
(GROANS)
(CHIME PLAYS ON P.A.)
(WOMAN MAKING ANNOUNCEMENT
IN CHINESE LANGUAGE)
(LAUGHING)
WOMAN: (OVER PA)
Your attention, please.
Flight M-U-5-7-8-5...
(SOUND FADES TO TRADITIONAL
CHINESE MUSIC PLAYED ON FLUTE)
(AMBIENT NOISE RETURNS)
Ling!
(LAUGHS)
Mama!
So fast!
(SPEAKING
CHINESE LANGUAGE)
(LING SPEAKING
(SPEAKING
CHINESE LANGUAGE)
Josh?
Hey. I'm Dr Li.
I work
with your father.
Oh, hi.
This is my daughter, Ling.
So, my dad
couldn't make it?
Oh, he apologizes.
Shall we go?
Let me have your luggage.
(SPEAKING CHINESE LANGUAGE)
Bye, Dad.
Here's Mom.
(SPEAKING CHINESE LANGUAGE)
(KISSES) Bye-bye.
(FLUTE PLAYING
TRADITIONAL CHINESE MUSIC)
The music again.
What music?
The flute!
Where's it coming from?
(PHILIP SPEAKING
CHINESE LANGUAGE)
I'm just telling
them that, uh,
if I was here earlier,
they wouldn't
have got away.
Your son's here!
CHRIS: Josh!
Hey, Dad.
There you are.
(LAUGHS)
Yep.
Look at you, big guy.
What happened
to my little guy?
It's been a while, Dad.
I know.
Listen, I'm sorry
I couldn't meet you. We...
[SPEAKING CHINESE LANGUAGE]
We had some dramas here.
JOSH: I heard, yeah.
Hey, what's that?
Oh, that's what you get
for trying to stop a thief.
Not much of a hero,
your dad.
Long story.
So...how's your mum?
Why don't you ask her?
Spoke to her last week,
actually.
Flight was good?
Yeah.
PHILIP:
Oh, uh, Chris.
Chris, uh, they want
to have a talk.
Philip, this is, um...
This is Josh, my son.
This is Philip.
He's a geophysics expert.
Hey. Nice to meet you.
Hey, Josh,
nice to meet you.
So you're the boss.
Oh, I wish.
No, Dr. Li's the boss.
My job's to stay
out of her way.
(LAUGHS)
All right, it's nice
to meet you. I'll, uh...
What were
the thieves after?
Was there some
sort of treasure?
Treasure? Oh, absolutely.
But don't tell the world
just yet, okay?
Nice to meet you.
All right.
See you.
Sorry, Josh. This is going to
take a few minutes more.
Why don't you go to your room?
The driver will take you.
See you at dinner.
Get some rest.
We'll catch up later, okay?
Okay, Dad. Yep.
It's good you're here, Josh.
Please.
Bye-bye.
Bye. Bye.
(LOCK CLICKS)
(SIGHS)
Oh! Oh.
(GROANS)
Josh!
(MAN SPEAKING
CHINESE LANGUAGE)
(SPEAKING CHINESE LANGUAGE)
You need
to wear this I.D.
(SPEAKING
CHINESE LANGUAGE)
Uh, do I look
like a tomb robber to you?
Not to me, but to them.
Philip,
I don't understand.
Why are we talking
about this now?
This is the big day.
Chris, please.
Take a look at that.
I just want to go back
over the facts, okay?
Emperor Jianwen's tomb.
The sonar images confirm
what we thought.
The potential for
artifacts is massive.
DR. LI: Are you sure
about this test?
This rising groundwater?
Not only is it rising,
Dr. Li,
it is extremely acidic.
Josh! Don't do that.
PHILIP: I have no doubt
in my mind whatsoever
it will damage whatever's
inside the tomb.
So if these pneumatic
jacks fail today,
I think we
should get a team
of diamond saw experts
and cut
and dismantle the doors.
Come on.
That's ridiculous.
Every part of this tomb
is precious. You know that.
PHILIP:
Of course, it is, Chris,
but we are running
out of time.
We need to prioritize.
And isn't saving
what's inside the tomb
most important?
CHRIS: Not if it means
destroying valuable material.
PHILIP: I do not...
DR. LI:
I understand your point,
but I agree with Chris.
We need to move carefully.
(FLUTE PLAYING
TRADITIONAL CHINESE MUSIC)
Well, my guys
are in place, so...
How about yours?
Yeah.
They're on stand-by.
(MEN SHOUTING
IN CHINESE LANGUAGE)
(SPEAKING CHINESE LANGUAGE)
He's not happy
about us digging here.
He's harmless.
(SPEAKING
CHINESE LANGUAGE)
(SHOUTING
IN CHINESE LANGUAGE)
(SHOUTING CONTINUES
IN BACKGROUND)
Whoa. You can do that?
Yeah. It's nothing.
Nothing. (CHUCKLES)
Well, I'm impressed.
(SHOUTS
IN CHINESE LANGUAGE)
(SHOUTING
It's his.
Hey, where
are you going?
To return this!
JOSH:
How do you know it's his?
LING:
I just do.
Unh!
Do you think he's one
of the thieves?
Thieves
don't carry flutes.
Is that a Chinese thing?
It's
a "use your brain" thing.
(DR. LI SPEAKING
CHINESE LANGUAGE)
CHRIS: Stand here.
Let's make sure we proceed
at 5 centimeters per minute,
and see how we go.
PHILIP:
I agree. I agree.
I had that calibrated,
so we should be ready to go.
Okay. You keep me posted
on that data.
I really need to know that.
Of course.
I wish Josh was here
to see this, you know?
Yeah. Ling
would be excited, too.
(PNEUMATIC JACKS FIRING)
(DR. LI SPEAKS
CHINESE LANGUAGE)
(WOOD CRACKING)
(EXCLAIMS
IN CHINESE LANGUAGE)
(CHEERING)
Excellent!
Oh!
Oh, I'm sorry.
Wow.
This is larger
than I thought.
Let's go.
(SPEAKING CHINESE LANGUAGE)
Okay, happy now?
Mission accomplished.
Let's go.
English boy?
Australian.
He's very rude.
Ohh.
Xie xie. Thank you.
This flute very important.
If I lost, I'm finished.
I'm nothing.
My family, boom!
Terrific story.
Let's go.
No, wait! Don't!
I heard you play
your flute earlier.
It's beautiful.
Mm-hmm.
JOSH: Okay, this
is getting weird.
Don't make
any sudden moves.
I'll handle this.
The whole world,
only one person
can hear this flute.
Okay, flute man,
time to back away.
You really can hear
this flute?
Yeah.
Okay.
(BLOWS INTO FLUTE)
(FLUTE PLAYING
TRADITIONAL CHINESE MUSIC)
Yes, that's the tune!
One more time.
(CLEARS THROAT)
(PRETENDS TO PLAY)
You see?
No.
(CLEARS THROAT)
(PRETENDS TO PLAY)
Yeah?
No.
Of course.
(BLOWS INTO FLUTE)
(FLUTE PLAYING
TRADITIONAL CHINESE MUSIC)
Yes, that's the tune!
Oh, my Buddha!
What...what tune?
There's nothing.
It doesn't work.
What do you mean, no tune?
You didn't hear that?
You cannot hear.
I cannot hear.
You can?
Ohh, no one can...
except...
(GROANS)
Except the dragon
and Chosen One.
Chosen?
Mmm.
(QUIETLY) Chosen.
Chosen.
Follow me!
Hey! No! She's
not that crazy, pal.
Not even a vote.
Nothing.
(DOOR CREAKS)
Can you let go
of my hand?
Oh, oh, I'm sorry.
(SPEAKS CHINESE LANGUAGE)
(DOOR CREAKS OPEN)
Welcome
to Dragon Temple.
My name is Wu Dong.
My family keep safe
this Dragon Temple
3,000 years.
My flute, same--
3,000 year.
6,000 year. So long,
long, long time, right?
(CHUCKLES)
Hey! Don't touch.
Don't touch.
Serious, serious.
Sorry.
DR. LI:
Chris, don't move too slowly.
Let's stay together.
Stop.
Let me take picture.
Okay. Go.
Be careful.
Look at this.
Wow!
(LAUGHS) Oh!
Finally, this is it.
Incredible.
Hey, Chris.
So beautiful.
Yeah.
(LAUGHS)
Oh!
Yes!
(CHRIS LAUGHS)
Great.
Air is good, guys.
Okay.
Air is good.
CHRIS:
The air is very good.
DR. LI:
More light to see.
[CAMERA CLICKS]
That one! Here.
That one, that one, two!
Kyah!
That one, three! Kyah!
(SPEAKING CHINESE LANGUAGE)
(MUTTERS, CHUCKLES)
Um..."The Chosen One is
the child of the child
of the child of the child
of the Emperor."
(JOSH SCOFFS)
And that's supposed
to be you?
WU DONG: Shh.
"And only Chosen One
can open the door."
What door?
(MUTTERS)
Oh. Ahh!
The door
under the floor.
The door is under a floor?
He's making this up
as he goes.
Mmm.
We can...We can...
Ahh!
We can
only find the door
through
a magic triangle.
Magic triangle.
Magic triangle?
Oh. Too messy.
Too messy.
Do something.
Messy, messy.
Do something, do something.
Do what?
Ahh!
Cleaning.
Can't find anything.
Ah.
Messy,
cannot find anything.
(WU DONG MUTTERING,
HUMMING)
Stop. Don't do that.
Why?
You're looking
for a triangle?
Well, there's one
right here.
There's a pattern, see?
It's quite deliberate.
The ash falls on the points
of the triangle.
There, there...
and here.
Maybe.
JOSH: There's
definitely a pattern.
"Eastern point is
the key to the door."
(QUIETLY) Eastern point...
East...eastern point?
Over here.
WU DONG:
No! No, no, no, no, no!
Don't do.
Chosen One,
you try, you try.
Gimme. You try.
We cannot try.
No.
Nope.
Hmm...eastern point.
(HEAVY SCRAPING)
The scroll is right.
I can't believe
my eyes can see that!
my mind can think that.
3,000 years.
Well done!
Aah!
Oh, my Buddha.
JOSH: Ling!
WU DONG: That's bad.
That's really bad.
Wu Dong, do something!
Of cour...
Okay, let's do something.
Anything!
Do something.
Wh-what can I...?
Yeah, I got it!
(GIGGLES)
Yah-ha-ha!
That's it?
That's it.
Ling!
I'm going in.
Wait!
Ling! Are you okay?
Oh...I think so.
You okay?
Yeah. Look for
the scroll that tells us
what to do next.
Okey-dokey.
But take care!
Do something,
do something. Do what?
So what do you think?
Should we go for it?
We came this far.
(JOSH GASPS)
(WIND WHISTLING,
LEAVES RUSTLING)
(DRIPPING WATER ECHOES)
Hello!
(ECHOES)
Wow. We need ropes
to get down there.
Oh!
What's that?
What?
Something...
I don't know.
(GASPS)
What's the matter?
There was...
I thought I saw...
Okay, you're starting to
freak me out a little bit.
What's going on?
Aah!
(GASPING)
What?
(GASPS)
(DRAGON GROWLING)
Aah! Aah!
Aah!
JOSH: Ling! Ling!
Ling!
JOSH: Like a Diprotodon
or a Stegosaurus!
I don't know,
like a huge monster.
Josh,
you need to calm down.
But there's a monster
down there.
If it gets out,
it'll eat people.
CHRIS: Josh.
We need tranquilizer guns.
(SPEAKING
CHINESE LANGUAGE)
Ling,
tell 'em what we saw.
(SPEAKING
CHINESE LANGUAGE)
(SPEAKS CHINESE LANGUAGE)
Josh, why don't we let
the doctor do his job?
Okay, Josh.
You know, I'm...I'm...
I'm gonna make some tea.
Doesn't anyone care
there's a monster out there?
DR. LI: You don't need
to tell me how this happened.
We can leave that
till later.
Look, I think
you should tell them
about
the Chosen One stuff,
and what we saw.
The thing in the cave!
LING: I...
I don't remember.
Ling! The monster,
come on.
I'm sorry.
I don't know what happened.
CHRIS: Josh.
I saw what I saw.
(SCOFFS) Josh,
you know
this does sound...
kind of crazy.
Crazy?
I'll tell you what's crazy.
You and Mum
getting a divorce!
Okay.
Okay, maybe I haven't
found the right way
to explain
this properly.
Your mum and I...
What happened, happened.
Doesn't matter.
No, no. It does matter.
It matters.
Hey, listen to me...
How about you listen to me?
(FOOTSTEPS)
Uh...awkward.
No. Philip, it's fine.
Fine.
Look, if you
don't mind me saying so,
we all like
to be listened to.
Even me.
All right, I'm listening.
I'm...I'm listening.
Tell us again from the beginning
exactly what you saw, hmm?
Come on!
We're nearly there.
Let's go.
Wu Dong will tell you.
Wu! Wu Dong!
Wu!
There's this guy--
Wu Dong.
He's been
guarding this place
for 3,000 years.
(LAUGHS) Not him.
His family. But...yeah.
Wu!
Hello! Anyone here?
He's taken
the day off, huh?
(SIGHS)
Hey, the coils!
Where are they?
They were here yesterday.
Anyway, these coils,
you see?
They drop ash
in strategic places.
And there's
this trapdoor over there, right?
A trapdoor.
And there's this place
where Ling does this
weird praying thing.
And this is
what she does, okay?
She comes over here.
She gets down.
She puts her head
on the ground, this one.
And then...
(LAUGHS) This is good.
Look at
the trapdoor, okay?
The trapdoor,
you push on it,
it goes down,
and it comes up, okay?
Mm-hmm.
But I can't do it.
Only Ling can.
But I don't
believe that rubbish
about "Chosen One."
Anyone can do this.
(SIGHS)
It's down there, Dad.
It is!
Josh, how about we
come back another day,
you know, with Ling,
and try again?
You know,
I have a pneumatic saw.
It'd be perfect for that.
Hey, Dad, it's Wu Dong!
Come on!
Quickly! I'll show you!
Hey! Wu Dong! It's me.
Tell my dad
about the monster.
Ni hao.
You're from the temple?
Uh...uh...
(SPEAKING
CHINESE LANGUAGE)
No, Wu Dong, in English.
Come on! The Godzilla thing.
Ask him if he knows
anything about this.
Yeah, sure.
Hey! Hey, hey!
(SPEAKING CHINESE LANGUAGE)
(SPEAKS CHINESE LANGUAGE)
Hmm!
(SPEAKING CHINESE LANGUAGE)
(SCOFFS)
(WU DONG SPEAKS
CHINESE LANGUAGE)
(SPEAKING CHINESE LANGUAGE)
(SPEAKING
CHINESE LANGUAGE)
Eh? (SPEAKING
What's he say?
He says
he's never met Josh.
What? Wu Dong,
come on. It's me.
(SPEAKING CHINESE LANGUAGE)
(WU DONG SPEAKS
CHINESE LANGUAGE)
(SPEAKING CHINESE LANGUAGE)
Oh.
(SPEAKING
CHINESE LANGUAGE)
(SPEAKS CHINESE LANGUAGE)
His name's Xiang.
(SPEAKING
CHINESE LANGUAGE)
Eh!
JOSH: He could
speak English before.
CHRIS: Josh...
And now he's lying.
There's
some conspiracy thing
happening here.
Josh, what's
really going on here?
Like what?
You tell me.
Please, Dad,
I'm not making this up.
No, no, no,
that's not what I said.
What's really
going on with you?
If you've got a problem,
talk to me about it.
Must have just
been my imagination.
(SPEAKING CHINESE LANGUAGE)
MAN: Oh.
DR. LI:
Hello, guys.
CHRIS AND PHILIP:
Morning.
Hey. (SPEAKING
CHINESE LANGUAGE)
I'm sorry about before.
You should be.
I look like
an idiot now.
The kid
who sees monsters.
I...I couldn't tell them.
Yeah. Thanks for nothing.
Look, I'm
not some chosen one.
And that thing in the cave,
it could be a trick.
Is that what you think?
All right,
let's go back,
prove it,
one way or the other.
I don't know.
This thing
about destiny.
Fine. I'll forget about it.
You forget about it.
We'll go home.
Never saw anything.
End our holidays.
Guess you never heard
flute music, either.
(DR. LI SPEAKING
CHINESE LANGUAGE)
PHILIP: I just don't think
our conventional methods
are working.
Hey, Dad, I'm going
on your computer.
Sure, Josh.
Not yet, Philip.
But we always knew
the second set of doors
would be more difficult.
They were designed
that way.
PHILIP:
I'm well aware of that,
but we don't have time.
I could run
a series of tests.
X-rays, scans...
Of course
we're gonna do that,
but this needs to be
in a temperature-
controlled environment
in Beijing,
carefully controlled.
Gentlemen, let's focus.
I think the answer's
here somewhere.
Let's look at this part.
PHILIP: You know, I'm sure
I could conduct the scans here.
DR. LI: Have you sent off
your core samples and notes?
CHRIS: I'm still
working on them.
Make it
a priority, please.
DR. LI: Tomorrow, we will take
the book down to the doors
and try to make sense
of it somehow.
Okay. Enough for today.
(SPEAKING
CHINESE LANGUAGE)
How about some hot pot?
CHRIS: Good idea.
DR. LI: My treat.
(SPEAKING
CHINESE LANGUAGE)
Chris, a truce?
Ah!
Oh!
I'm sorry. I completely
forgot about that.
How's it coming along?
CHRIS:
Oh...a little better
every day,
except when I forget.
(LAUGHS) Yeah.
Ah!
Oh.
Apologies again.
DR. LI: Let's go, guys.
Yeah, this is better.
Josh.
Toffee apples are awesome.
DR. LI:
We probably have.
(FLUTE MUSIC PLAYING)
CHRIS: Well, we should
at least arrange
some sort
of secure transport,
or better still...
Oh!
one of us will need
to go with it.
Now what?
Too valuable.
The flute! I hear it!
JOSH:
Oh, wow! Look, vases!
Josh, I really...Ah!
JOSH: Hey!
Wu Do?
Wu Dong!
I want
to talk to you.
Now he wants to talk!
Suddenly,
he's found English again.
Sometime I speak Chinese,
sometime I speak English,
because I'm Chinese.
Sorry, mate.
Wu, just forget it.
She's not the Chosen One.
Let's go, Ling.
No. She is Chosen One.
She is.
Gentleman, trust me.
She is chosen.
You see,
I don't have the choice.
You don't have
the choice, too.
The dragon miss you!
Dragon?
That thing in the cave's
a dragon?
You think it's a rabbit?
JOSH:
That doesn't make sense.
There's no such thing
as dragons.
Josh, please!
What does the dragon want?
The dragon will tell you.
DR. LI: Ling Li! Ling Li!
CHRIS: Josh!
I...I have to go!
Take...take...take care!
Josh?
I won't say anything.
Ling Li!
Ma, I'm here!
Josh, come here!
Listen, mate, don't wander
away like that.
I'm serious. It's too easy
to get lost, okay?
I don't want to have
to worry about you.
Just stick with me.
(CONVERSATION CONTINUES
INDISTINCTLY)
(KNOCKING)
LING: Josh...
Listen!
I'm going back
to the temple.
You don't have to come.
Then why
are you telling me?
I'd like you to come.
Okay. You owe me one.
And we'll need a gun.
What?
Or at least
a tranquilizer rifle
or a Taser.
Don't be ridiculous.
If that thing's a dragon,
and I'm not saying
I'm convinced,
but if it is,
they breathe fire.
They carry people off.
Not Chinese dragons.
Any dragons!
They smash whole castles.
Not Chinese dragons!
And you know that how?
Now, this is my plan.
I think we should
go to the...
(MUSIC FADES IN
OVER CONVERSATION)
I haven't ridden a bike
since I was 10!
You're pretty good.
(HURRIED FOOTSTEPS)
(DOOR CREAKS)
She came!
You came.
I had to.
Thank you, Buddha.
Thank you, dragon.
Thank you, Ling.
Thank you so much.
Thank you,
English gentleman.
Let's go.
Let's go, let's go,
let's go.
No offense.
Yeah, of course.
(SPEAKS CHINESE LANGUAGE)
Take care.
Go!
Take care!
(ROCKS CLACKING)
What's that for?
I'm not taking chances
with that thing.
You don't throw stones
at a dragon.
You'll thank me later.
Josh, have some respect.
(DRIPPING WATER ECHOES)
See anything?
Mm-mmm.
So how do you
find a dragon?
I think he finds you.
(FLUTE PLAYING
TRADITIONAL CHINESE MUSIC)
(SHIMMERING SOUND)
(QUIET LAUGH)
What are you smiling at?
He hears!
He's coming!
(RUMBLING)
(GASPS)
(DEEP GRUNT)
Whoa! Ohh!
(GROWLS)
(DRAGON ROARS)
(WHOOSH)
(GROWLS)
(EXHALES)
(MAJESTIC MUSIC)
(ROARS GENTLY)
(SPEAKING
CHINESE LANGUAGE)
Does it bite?
Don't be disrespectful.
So that's a no?
(GROWLING)
Aw, it's all right!
It's never seen
a Western boy before.
It wonders
what you are.
Can you tell it
I'm not food?
(GROWLS QUIETLY)
It's okay, big guy.
I don't bite, either.
Looks a bit...
sad.
Where's his pearl?
Pearl? What pearl?
All dragons
have pearls.
Their power comes
from the pearl.
(GROWLS)
It said so
in the box book.
(GROWLS)
Ah!
(ROCKS FALL)
(GASPS)
Ling...
(GROWLS GENTLY)
Ling!
(GROWLS)
Ling, just don't look down.
Aah!
Ling?
Just don't look down, Ling.
(WHIMPERING)
It's okay.
Ahh! Josh!
Help me!
Aah!
Aah! Aah!
(DRAGON GROWLS)
Aah!
(WHIMPERING)
It's okay.
(GROWLS)
What's happening?
Aah! Aah!
What's happening?!
(SCREAMING)
This is not okay.
This is not okay!
JOSH: Help! Help!
What's happening?!
Yeah! Yeah!
(GROWLS SOFTLY)
(BELLOWS)
Yeah!
(GROWLING)
(WOMAN VOCALIZING
TO MAJESTIC MUSIC)
(GROWLING CONTINUES)
(GRUNTS)
(ROARS)
JOSH:
Hold on! Hold on!
Ahh!
(GASPING)
You ready?
Okay, one, two...
Three.
(LAUGHS)
(ROARS)
(BELLOWS)
(THUNDER)
(ROARS)
NARRATOR:
It is written in history
that a long time ago
warring tribes invaded
the kingdom.
With the help
of the Celestial Dragon,
the emperor fought valiantly
and the kingdom was saved.
But in the heat of battle,
the Dragon Pearl
was lost forever,
and the emperor died
of a broken heart...
or so it was written.
The truth lies elsewhere.
(WOMAN CRYING)
NARRATOR: Instead, the emperor
was killed in battle,
and the pearl was not lost.
The emperor's loving daughter,
the princess,
was overcome with grief.
(SPEAKING
CHINESE LANGUAGE)
NARRATOR: In anger, she blamed
the dragon and its pearl
for her father's death.
(SPEAKING
CHINESE LANGUAGE)
NARRATOR:
To punish the dragon,
the princess ordered
that the pearl
be secretly buried
with her father.
(STOMPS)
(SPEAKING CHINESE LANGUAGE)
NARRATOR:
To protect the secret,
she burnt
the official records
and ordered the scribe
to rewrite the story.
(SPEAKING ANGRILY
IN CHINESE LANGUAGE)
It was now written that
the pearl was lost in battle,
instead of being buried
with the emperor.
This became passed down
as history.
And so,
for thousands of years,
the dragon waited
for the time
it could reunite
with its missing pearl...
and return home.
WU DONG:
Is that the truth?
The pearl? Really?
Yes! We saw it.
It was not lost
like the book said.
The dragon
and the pearl story,
it was rewritten
to mislead tomb robbers.
The princess wanted
the pearl to protect
her father...
forever.
The tomb doors.
They've already opened
the first door!
The pearl!
What are we
going to do?
Chosen One,
you must get pearl,
return to dragon.
Your duty.
Me?
JOSH: If you don't do it,
the pearl will end up
in a museum or something.
English boy!
You're right.
You must do
something now.
And quick! Move!
Wait.
Didn't Philip say something
about rising groundwater?
Coming into the tomb.
Destroying
whatever's inside.
Ling, what
are you gonna do?
I'm going
to tell my mother!
You can't do that.
That's the fastest way!
It's not the fastest way.
She's not
gonna believe you.
Look what happened
when I tried.
I'm not you!
Ling!
(SPEAKING CHINESE LANGUAGE)
PHILIP: Could
I make a suggestion?
Why don't you
let me take a look
at the box book?
I could have it
for a couple of days,
offer
a new perspective,
fresh eyes.
With respect, Philip,
not your field.
PHILIP:
Well, I don't see you
making any progress.
Chris, I've read enough
ancient texts to know
these things are
written like puzzles.
CHRIS: You know,
I think it might be better
if we just stick to
our own area of expertise,
and this is
decidedly not yours.
Guys, the book goes
to Beijing, period!
Mother!
There is something
I have to tell you.
We flew! We saw the past!
The dragon showed us!
Mother,
why are you doing this?
I'm worried
about you, Ling.
We have to return the pearl
to the dragon.
It's in the tomb.
I really think
she needs testing.
Might be
a small brain bleed.
That
can cause visions.
That's ridiculous, Ma.
Hey, Dad.
Just a minute, Josh.
No, but I was just down
in the passage.
I thought I found something.
Josh, please.
Both of us saw it.
Does Josh need
a CAT scan, too?
Ling Li!
No, that's right.
We flew on a huge dragon,
and we went into the past.
It was great.
Anything you want
to say about this?
What's that
supposed to mean?
Look, I don't know
what's wrong with Ling,
and I don't know
where she gets
these ideas from,
but I know her,
and she is sensible.
And I'm not?
I didn't say that.
But you think it.
Look, I went up to
the mountain with you, okay?
Big deal!
You know what, Josh?
It's great that
you're here. It is.
And if you're upset
about things,
I don't blame you,
but you will understand
one day, trust me.
But in the meantime,
all this nonsense
and this attitude...
I don't know
if you've noticed,
but we are busy here.
We have work to do.
It is important work.
And we have
a potential crisis
on our hands,
so enough, Josh.
Enough!
Hey, it takes time.
(SIGHS)
I told you they
wouldn't believe us.
I hate it when my mom
doesn't believe me.
Welcome to the club.
You know,
I might have a plan
to get into the tomb,
though.
What?
Huh?
DR. LI:
Ling Li, let's go.
PHILIP: Hey.
JOSH: Hey.
You okay?
Yeah, good.
Did I hear right?
You want to get
into the tomb?
I don't need to know why.
I, uh,
assume it's important.
Okay.
I just might be able
to help you.
Welcome to my den.
(CHUCKLES)
You've read all these?
Yeah. Gotta know everything
you can in this game.
Can't read enough.
Sit down, Josh.
Thanks.
Listen...
you're sharp.
The way you figure out
those puzzles is amazing.
So I think there could
be a way in.
A way in?
Mm-hmm.
The box book.
Your dad and Dr. Li
are convinced
it holds the key,
but they think
it's in the writing.
I'm not so sure.
What do you think?
Those holes that you saw
in the book--
that you saw, Josh.
What did you see in them?
Hmm?
And weren't you just down
in the passageway?
You were
telling your dad.
It doesn't matter.
Dad didn't believe me.
Come on,
he's just being a parent.
It's what they do.
Can't help themselves.
(BOTH CHUCKLE)
So what'd you see?
I don't even know, okay?
You know, I think you
should take another look
at the box book,
before it goes to Beijing.
Or before the thieves
actually take it next time.
I mean, last time,
they got it so easily.
I mean,
I keep telling them,
they need to hide
the key to the cage
in a much safer place.
Taped under
the desk drawer--
it's so obvious.
I mean, sure, your dad's
got a new safe
with a new combination,
but what's a combination?
It's just...a puzzle.
Right?
(TAPE TEARS)
DR. LI: Are you tired?
(COMBINATION DIAL CLICKING)
DR. LI:
You're angry with me.
LING: Wouldn't you be?
Remind me next time
we have an argument,
I'll suggest you get
your head scanned.
(LAUGHS) I just want
what's best for you.
That's all.
Come on.
Don't be
like this, okay? Hmm?
DR. LI: Okay, good night.
(KISSES)
Let's open them up!
Go, go, go! Go.
(SAFE CLICKS)
Mum's birthday?
Weird.
(WHISPERING)
What are you doing here?
I...
None of your business.
What are you doing here?
Same as you.
What are you doing
with that?
We need it to get
into the tomb.
But what if...?
I'll put it back.
Wait!
Or we could find out
once and for all
what the real truth is.
Okay. Let's go.
Good. I can't
read Chinese anyway.
(SIGHS)
(CALLING OUT
IN CHINESE LANGUAGE)
(SPEAKING
CHINESE LANGUAGE)
(CONVERSING
IN CHINESE LANGUAGE)
(WHISPERS)
Okay, let's go.
(LIGHTS HUMMING)
(FLASHLIGHTS CLICK)
Do they have mummies
in China?
Only in bad Western movies.
Ah, that's
where I've seen them.
Have a look at this!
All right, the doors--
no handles, no locks.
Perfect.
Maybe something hidden?
Don't know.
Hey, but come
at this, okay?
I saw this yesterday.
They've been so focused
on the text,
they haven't noticed
the most obvious.
Are you sure you know
what you're doing?
No.
(RUMBLING, CREAKING)
(LAUGHS)
Hey, look, at least
there's no poison arrows
or crashing boulders
or anything.
(LAUGHS)
But I don't know
what to do next.
(THUDS)
(BOTH LAUGH)
Okay, that's
not just a coincidence.
Oh, yeah!
(THUD)
(LAUGHS)
But now what?
Press it?
What?
Press it!
Press what?
The dragon!
Okay, let me try.
Ready?
Help, help.
(GRUNTING)
It's opening!
(CREAKING)
(HEAVY RUMBLING)
(FLASHLIGHT CLICKS)
(GROWLS)
Oh, the Emperor!
And his wife, my ancestor.
Shouldn't the pearl
be here, though?
The princess, she clearly
commanded that it stay here.
What if we've
missed something?
What if
it wasn't the truth?
How do we know?
It's here. I know it.
Here, I'll take it.
Stop.
(CHIMES RINGING)
(HEAVY RUMBLING)
(GASPS IN WONDER)
Ling, are you all right?
(CHAINS CREAKING)
(GASPS)
(PURRS)
(LAUGHS)
(PEARL PULSING)
Great job, Josh.
Hey, Philip!
You're just in time!
PHILIP: Yeah, I know.
I'll take that now.
What?
PHILIP: You know,
your dad and Dr. Li,
they think I'm stupid.
But I know more
about this pearl
than anyone.
See, when they
discovered this tomb,
I read everything I could,
like I told you.
There's power
in that pearl.
Real power.
And I intend
to find out how much.
Give him the bag, Josh.
LING: No!
MAN: Come on.
Give me the bag!
(GRUNTING)
Get the bag!
Ling!
Aah!
Oh! Oh!
Huh?
Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah!
Josh!
(GRUNTS)
Oh! Oh!
(SHOUTS)
(MEN SHOUTING)
LING: Yah!
(SHOUTS)
Hi-yah!
(STRAINING)
Josh!
Aah!
(GRUNTS, GASPS)
(BOTH SCREAMING)
(FRIGHTENED SHOUTS)
Excuse me.
Here! Ling!
Bye-bye!
Aie!
(BOTH SHOUT)
(FRIGHTENED SCREAMS)
(SHOUTS) Hey!
Come on!
(MUFFLED SHOUTING)
Josh! Here!
Let's go.
(ENGINE STARTS)
Over there!
Keep your eye on them.
Do not lose them.
Josh?
Josh.
Maybe you'd
like one of these.
I can't find Josh.
Have you seen him?
Or Ling?
I think
you should read this.
What is this?
Copies of soil analysis?
It's the sample result
Philip sent to Beijing.
There's water, all right,
but it's not rising.
You mean Philip lied
about the rising water?
It was...His report
was fraudulent?
I...
Where is Philip?
And where
are the kids?
Where are the guards?
Where's security?
(CALLING OUT
IN CHINESE LANGUAGE)
Josh?
(GUARDS' MUFFLED SHOUTS)
Ling!
Someone down there!
(GUARDS SHOUTING,
MOANING)
(SPEAKING
CHINESE LANGUAGE)
Philip Dukas.
Dukas.
Dukas!
(THUD)
(GROWLS)
(ENGINE REVVING)
(MAN SHOUTING
IN CHINESE LANGUAGE)
Come on.
MAN: Come on now!
Run!
Okay, Ling,
you go ahead.
I'll try
and stall them.
Be careful, Josh!
(MAN SHOUTS
IN CHINESE LANGUAGE)
(ENGINE REVVING)
Wait.
It's okay.
I know
where they're going.
Oh, hey!
Hey! What was that?
MAN: Hey, hey!
Hey, come back!
Where you going?!
Come on, bad guys!
Come on!
Wait! Wait!
Forget about him!
Get back in here!
(GROWLS)
Come on!
Forget him!
(LING GASPING AND PANTING)
(GRUNTS)
Are you sure
they're in the temple?
No, I'm not sure
they're in the temple.
I hope
(WHISPERS) Oh, God.
Wu Dong! Wu Dong!
Aah!
(WU DONG YELLS)
Aah! Aah!
Ohh ohh ohh!
Hai.
(MENACING CHUCKLE)
WU DONG: You okay?
My bag, Wu Dong!
My bag!
Okay.
Give it back now.
(CHUCKLES)
Or...
(SHOUTING)
Thank you.
Ha.
(WU DONG SHOUTING,
MEN GROANING)
Waah!
Ahh!
Hmm?
Eh?
Mm.
(GRUNTS AND SHOUTS)
Ohh.
(MEN GRUNTING)
The bikes are here.
I'm calling the police.
I'm going ahead.
No! I'm going with you!
No, you stay here.
Bring them up.
Wait! Wait!
Wait!
(SHOUTING)
(GROANS)
Ha-yah!
(SPEAKING
CHINESE LANGUAGE)
Ow! Ow!
(SPEAKING
CHINESE LANGUAGE)
Ohh! Hah!
(GROANING)
(SHOUTS
IN CHINESE LANGUAGE)
(SHOUTING)
Ohh!
(GASPS)
(GROANS)
(NECK CRACKS)
Ooh-hoo.
Ooh?
(SHOUTING)
Ow! Ahh!
(RIP!)
Ow! Aah!
Ohh!
(FARTS)
Let's be sensible
about this.
You hand over the pearl,
you get to leave.
Give me the bag.
Come on.
Thank you.
Josh! Ling!
JOSH: Dad!
(GRUNTS)
(BLADE SLICES)
What's going on?
Welcome
to the party, Chris.
The pearl, Dad,
he's after it.
(LAUGHING)
He can't have it.
What are you doing, Philip?
It's Josh!
Okay.
PHILIP: You back away.
CHRIS: Let him go, Philip,
and put down the knife.
Back away!
Put the knife down.
I'm warning you.
Put down the knife!
Back away!
Okay, okay,
let's talk about this.
I'm done listening
to you, Chris.
Okay, if it's...
Those days are over.
Give me the pearl, Josh.
Josh, it's okay.
PHILIP:
Nice and easy.
Give him what he wants.
It's okay.
Nice and slow.
Just give him the pearl.
Yeah.
(CHUCKLES)
(LAUGHING)
(GROWLS)
(CHUCKLING)
I got you, Josh.
(WU DONG YELLS)
(SCREAMING)
(GROANING)
(GROANS)
(SHOUTS)
(PEARL PULSING)
Huh? Ohh!
(WEAPONS CLANKING)
(CHUCKLING)
(HUMMING TUNE
PLAYED BY FLUTE)
(GROANS)
(LING'S VOICE ECHOING)
Stop that.
It's annoying.
(STOPS HUMMING)
Ling!
(GROWLING)
(GROANS)
(LING SHOUTS)
Leave her!
Let my daughter go!
Aah!
(SHOUTING AND GASPING)
Ling! Run!
Arggh!
LING: Aah! Aah!
(GROANS)
LING: Mama!
Ling!
(GASPING)
Dad, you okay?
(GROANS)
Ling!
(GASPS, WHIMPERS)
(GASPS)
Mama!
(BOTH GASP)
(GROANS)
Ling!
Mama!
Aah!
(GROWLING)
Ling!
Aah!
(DISTANT BELLOWING)
(BELLOWS)
(DRAGON GRUNTING)
(GRUNTING)
(DRAMATIC MUSIC)
(BELLOWING)
(DRAGON GROANS)
(CRACKLING AND WHOOSHING)
(SNIFFS)
I knew the dragon
would be there for me.
That's
just so incredible.
I can't believe
what's happened here.
I'm sorry I doubted you.
(SPEAKING
CHINESE LANGUAGE)
Bad guy one, bye!
Bad guy two, bye!
Bad guy three, bye!
Take care, bad guys.
Why I say take care?
Hey.
Hey, English boy.
Hey, Wu Dong.
Josh, next time you
dig up something big,
warn me, okay?
Dad, I told you
over and over.
I'm kidding. I'm kidding.
If I ever don't believe you
about anything ever again,
I don't know, just kick me
or something, okay?
You did great, son.
You did great.
Really well.
How are we going to
explain all this to Mum?
That's a good question.
Well, we'll think
of something, maybe.
In the meantime, dig up
something else, okay?
Make yourself useful.
You're part
of the team now.
DR. LI:
I'm so proud of you.
LING:
Mother, the book,
it doesn't
tell the truth.
So I guess this story
has to be rewritten
to tell
the truth this time.
(LAUGHING)
(WOMAN SINGING IN CHINESE
LANGUAGE TO FLUTE MELODY)
(SIGHS)
(PLAYS NOTES)
(PLAYING MELODY)
(GRUNTS)
(WOMAN SINGING
TO FLUTE MELODY)
(DRUMS BEAT RAPIDLY)
(WOMEN VOCALIZING
TO GENTLE MUSIC)
Please rate this subtitle at www.osdb.link/7zw93
Help other users to choose the best subtitles