(BOY SCREAMS)
No!
Mum!
Please stop.
WOMAN:
No, please! Just leave us alone!
- BOY: Mum!
- WOMAN: Please don't...
- Don't do it!
- (SHOTS FIRING)
(BOY SCREAMING)
Mum.
(DOOR CLOSING)
Mum!
(SNIFFLING)
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org
(VEHICLE MOVING)
(SNIFFLING)
(SHUSHING) Hey, you okay? Okay?
Please help me, they killed my mum.
- What? Who?
- Red masks. The men in red masks.
Have you been kidnapped, too?
Yeah, I think so.
Please. Please untie me.
Okay, okay.
- What happened?
- They shot her.
The men in red masks, they came
to our house and shot her.
Hey, hey. I'm sorry. Listen...
What's your name?
Alex.
Okay, Alex. You're being very brave.
I need you to be brave for
a little bit longer, okay?
I'm gonna go and get some help.
Listen, you need to wait for
it to stop moving, okay?
(BRAKES SQUEALING)
Okay. Go.
(YELLS)
My leg.
- (GROANS)
- (SHUSHING)
My leg!
What's your name?
It's Ryan.
Ryan.
How come you were in the van?
I have no idea.
The last thing I
remember is at Hibiscus.
Reading a chemistry text
book Dr. Langham gave me.
And I wasn't in London.
- Why would someone kidnap you?
- I don't know.
I just want my mum back.
(SOBBING)
Look, I'm gonna go
to the police, okay?
- What did you say about his biscuits?
- Hibiscus.
What's that?
A rehab facility.
It's kind of like a hospital.
I've been there for a few years,
was your mum there?
Are you sick?
It's called post-traumatic
stress disorder.
I get dizzy spells.
Panic attacks and nightmares.
Although this seems very real.
Except, I don't have my ring.
And I've never seen this before.
- June.
- (BRANCHES RUSTLING)
(GROANS)
- My watch says June the seventh.
- That's today.
Are you sure?
But when I went to
sleep it was January.
(GROANS)
(STRAINING)
MAN: Hey! Where are you?
(CELL PHONE CHIMES)
(CELL PHONE VIBRATING)
Hello?
Where are you?
No! It was you! It was you!
You! You did it!
- You did it!
- (GROANS)
You killed my mum!
Help!
Alex!
Ten days.
Hello!
(COUGHS)
Hibiscus Trauma Unit US, call.
Hello, Hibiscus?
What do you mean, "Wrong number"?
How can they have
been closed for years?
What year is this?
This year now,
right now, what year is this?
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(COUGHING VIOLENTLY)
(PANTING)
I heard you shout, you okay?
Everything all right?
Yeah.
I knocked the table, I was annoyed.
I bet you were.
It's a 200-year-old single malt
you love telling me about.
Shall we go over it,
so we're all clear?
Everything's in place.
The tests from Leonid show that
it works on a long-term trial,
as you know.
So we're still on schedule.
The medic from the interrogation
center had his little accident.
So your alias is Cedric Saunders,
and it stood up with
their background checks.
You start in five weeks,
the mercenaries are on standby.
And finally the electron
micrograph came from Kiev,
so the lab's fully equipped
and ready for our scientists.
Imagine all those individuals
locked in their own heads and they're
thinking of who or what they hurt.
Imagine we get those drones online.
What about the boy?
He's fine. The driver's gone.
I handled it.
We can't have any more incidents
like we did at the graveyard.
You sure you're okay?
Have a drink.
You want to see the feed?
AUTOMATED VOICE: Welcome, Harkin.
What can I do for you today?
Hibiscus Project online.
What are you doing to him?
It happened again, didn't it?
Your name is Ryan Reeve. Isn't it?
You're good, but I'm still better.
I started at a very young age.
My father always taught me,
"A man can't use his mind,
until he knows how to use his body."
Good lesson.
Worth all the scars.
You probably won't come back.
But if you do,
stop, wait it out,
don't talk to anyone,
don't operate machinery,
if you're driving, pull over.
You won't have time to
achieve anything anyway.
The reboot only takes nine
minutes and 47 seconds.
But still, why don't we
make this a short one?
(CHOKING)
I'm so sorry, I'm so sorry.
What am I doing here?
If you don't know that,
maybe I'm not the person
with the most problems in the room.
You told me to play dead.
Why?
I guess
because you like it.
You paid Sergio a lot of money
and I don't ask questions.
Three weeks?
Did I mention a kid,
a boy called Alex?
What's your name?
I've told you already.
Tell me again.
Dana.
You've been shouting it enough.
"I'm gonna make you beg, Dana."
That sort of thing.
I'm sorry, Dana.
The person who I was just then,
that's not who I am now.
A crazy thing is happening to me.
I wake up in these situations and
I don't know how I got there.
But the guy that was doing
that to you is not me.
So, who are you?
Who was he?
I don't know.
Mmm. Right. You still got
an hour, mystery man,
so are we gonna play this
game or the first one?
I need to find Dr. Langham.
I don't want to wear these,
do you have anything else?
Only things clients have
left behind, in the trunk.
When I came in, was there
another man with me?
Bright blue eyes.
I don't know.
Nine minutes, 47 seconds.
Okay, get dressed.
- Why?
- We're leaving.
No, no, no. I'm never allowed
to leave. Sergio owns me.
I'm gonna handle Sergio.
And you're gonna do what I tell you,
do you understand me?
My, my. We haven't changed
much at all, have we?
Hurry up.
(MUSIC PLAYING)
What is this music?
Sergio's favorite. He plays
it throughout the house
to remind girls and
clients who is in charge.
Well, like I said,
I'm gonna deal with Sergio.
No, I expect he'll
be dealing with you.
Why do you do this?
Why do any of us do anything?
Yeah, but you don't like it, you're not
feeding a habit, so why are you here?
Life has brought me here.
So if you weren't here,
what would you be doing?
Go back to my hometown.
Finish nursing school.
What's your town like?
This is pointless.
(SIGHS)
Quiet.
Under a mountain.
Nice houses with brightly painted
window frames and
white picket fences.
I miss it.
So like I said, why are you here?
My son was sick.
His care was very expensive, I had
to borrow a lot of money, quickly.
I didn't know where to go.
So I came here.
When you owe somebody
that much, they own you.
So how is your boy now?
His name is Eden.
He died.
I'm sorry.
No you're not.
AUTOMATED VOICE:
Thank you for your custom.
House rules state that only one
customer may leave at any time.
This door will now
lock for two minutes.
View our selection of
girls in front of you.
Book your favorite by
scheduling an outcall
and have all your dreams come true.
You're Sergio?
He doesn't speak much English.
Hey.
One of you tell Sergio
I'm taking this girl out.
(SPEAKING RUSSIAN)
He says you, "Just because
you pick the girl from line
"does not mean you leave with her.
"She belong to me."
That wasn't me.
(SPEAKING RUSSIAN)
You look same,
who it was.
Who are you?
I'm not entirely sure.
But you're welcome
to try and find out.
Come on now!
Hey!
I think we can help each other.
Please, please don't scream.
Here, take this.
That's enough for you
to get away from Sergio.
I just need you to do me a favor.
I need you to go to the police,
and I need you to tell them about me.
I kidnapped a child called Alex,
and I shot his mother...
If you want to be arrested,
why not just go turn yourself in?
'Cause I only get 10 minutes,
and when I change I won't want to.
Change into what?
Do this for me and you
get your freedom back.
You have no idea.
Sergio will come for me and he
will not stop until he's found me.
Look, you've lost a kid,
we can help this one.
Please.
You didn't tell me
we were in New York.
Where did you think you were?
(YELLS)
Hey! Hey!
Back up! Back the fuck up! Back up!
You all right? You okay?
...three terrorist, four
terrorist, five terrorist,
six terrorist, seven terrorist,
eight terrorist,
nine terrorist, 10 terrorist.
One terrorist, two terrorist,
three terrorist, four terrorist,
five terrorist,
six terrorist, seven terrorist,
eight terrorist,
nine terrorist, 10 terrorist.
Up.
Where's the research, 43543?
We're not gonna stop till
we've got what we need.
You talk, and we all go get a slice
of pie and enjoy the sunshine.
What do you say, Mr. Scientist?
- Fuck you.
- You want some more?
Let's go again, right now!
Wait. We've gotta give him, what?
Five, 10 minutes? Right, Doc?
Doc.
We can't break him with one hand
tied behind our backs like this.
You don't know how it is with Leonid.
Leonid.
Two years we've been
processing him, not a peep.
Now, the old doctor, he was
real big on prisoner's rights.
How about the rights
of ordinary, decent people
to sleep peacefully in
their beds at night
without worrying about
a sick fuck like him?
How about letting us
bend the rules a little?
Where are we?
Are you fucking with me?
You don't know where we are?
Is there a problem?
Come on, Doc. What the fuck?
You know where we are is classified,
and if you don't, I can't tell you.
Okay.
He's having some kind of episode.
We should just do what we've got to do.
He's not going to tell anyone.
There was a boy.
A child.
And there was a girl,
Dana, a prostitute.
She was helping me,
and then Sergio...
What are you talking about?
Just do your fucking job!
I keep blacking out and...
I kidnapped a kid.
I don't know where he
is now, because I'm me...
I mean, I am the "me" I am now.
But soon I will change and I'll know,
but I won't want to tell you.
Now, I know how this sounds.
I know this sounds crazy,
but please, you have to believe me.
There's a child's life at stake.
He's got something strapped to him.
(GRUNTS)
Doc, come on! I will shoot you!
Give it up, Doc!
(BOTH GRUNTING)
(COUGHING)
(MEN SHOUTING IN SPANISH)
Down! Down! Get the fuck down!
The mask, give it to me!
- You're the scientist?
- Of course, yes.
Is there a technology
that allows people
to control somebody else's mind?
This is hardly the time.
Tell me about mind control!
I have heard of such a program.
- Experimental death, called droning.
- How is it done?
How is it done?
The host body holds a receiver,
like a modem receiving a signal.
Where?
All neurological impulses go through
the basal ganglia in
the back of the neck,
so probably there.
Now, the mask, please.
Now how are we going
to get out of here?
Hey! Hey!
Are you the contact?
What happens now?
Where is the laboratory?
Where are Dr. Langham's people?
It's his plan! What now?
(MEN CHATTING INDISTINCTLY)
MAN: I see they've
redesigned the chronometer.
The new spectrograph 406.
They must've brought it out
while I was indisposed.
A wide-spectrum deprillator.
Already configured.
And after months of waiting
and fragmented communication,
you break me out of my cell and
give me a nice new laboratory.
Thank you so very much.
Gentlemen, let's celebrate.
Hey, the studio's benefactor
number two, have a glass.
To a fruitful collaboration.
Nostrovia!
Now that I see you are men of your
word, let me show you something.
All my work, right here.
Ingenious.
Kept all your work right
under their noses for years.
This stuff is far too good
for governments to know.
You know why I am the best? Hmm?
Because I can see the aesthetics.
My contemporaries are vulgarians.
They see only RNA bases, enzymes.
I see
Picasso.
Biology's purest sculpture.
The virus.
I'll make something simple and nasty.
An airborne pathogen
that messes with DNA in a
particularly baroque fashion.
Makes the subject grow
some extra eyes, say.
I'll make it very contagious.
We show them it works.
We threaten to release it over
some densely populated cities.
And we all grow obscenely rich.
Yeah, about that.
That's all very interesting,
- very "baroque" was it you said?
- Mmm.
Well, actually, Leonid,
we may have mislead you, somewhat.
I mean, do we need
your expertise? Yes.
Do we need you to build
this bespoke virus? Yes.
But are we going to blackmail
governments for money?
No.
No, we're not.
We're not interested in blackmail here,
and we don't need money.
You may not understand this,
but our ambitions are a little
wider.
I will not work if I do
not agree to the cause.
I'm very well aware of that.
Let me show you something.
(GUN POWERING UP)
No, no, no, no!
Stop! You'll die.
- Back away.
- What are you doing?
Lucky it's not too deep.
All right, I'm gonna stay
here until this one's over.
A change of plans, I think.
What nonsense this is, I do not know.
But it proves one thing.
You have ceased to be of use.
So thank you very
much for my freedom,
and an excellent place to work.
But I will go from here alone.
It's DNA coded.
You need an override code.
So why don't you relax
and watch some TV.
What is this?
Hello, Leonid.
The boy, of course, is Alex.
I believe you know him.
What have you done to my son?
WOMAN: No, please! Just leave
us alone. Please don't...
(ALEX SCREAMING)
No! Mum!
Mum, no.
I killed the mother,
but your son is still alive.
Although, perhaps not
for long, my dear boy.
The acid between the
sheets is irreversibly
spreading to wards your son's body
and can only be stopped by us.
It's a little much, I admit.
But it's a visual incentive and I
do have a penchant for theatrics.
I give you my word, your son will
be released if you do what we say.
All your instructions
are in front of you.
Leonid. We can save Alex.
But we need to act fast before
I change back into him.
I'm gonna black out soon and
there isn't much time left.
Leonid.
MAN: Two, one. Manual shutdown.
We are no longer
transmitting, which means...
Hello, Ryan.
Let's see.
Pulse normal.
Within tolerance.
The ports are clear.
There's nothing wrong with the
old receiver tech.
It's embedded nicely.
The vocal chords have been disabled,
and I've fixed the self-inflicted
damage on the right side of the neck
and opened the node
portal on the left.
I've gone over all the
transmission equipment.
It's working perfectly.
So, it has to be a fault or
interference with the satellite.
Quite frankly, there's nothing
we can do about that,
'cause it might just happen more,
and possibly more randomly.
Every now and again,
soldier boy is gonna get his head back
until the reboot kicks
in automatically.
Which, as we have seen,
is plenty of time for him
to make quite a mess of things.
He's incredibly persistent.
All I have to do is
just slit this vein.
I know that I can take care of
everything on my own from here.
We'll discuss this when you get back.
Bug repair the subject.
I'd keep still if I were you, Ryan.
Good night, Ryan.
I really hope we don't meet again.
Alex.
Another transmission failure, huh?
Hello, Ryan.
It's a crude solution,
I admit, laughably simple.
My idea.
Your entrance, we noted, was marked
by a moment of involuntary spasm.
So we're using that. You wake up,
you drop the ball, it inflates,
you go down for a little sleep.
Soon as you're back,
you're gone again.
There's a grand plan, Ryan.
Why are you fighting it?
Why do you even care?
Honestly, this really has
nothing to do with you.
We upped the dose a little bit,
so it'll be straight back down.
That's it, let the
drugs do their thing.
Don't fight it. Don't panic
everyone, he's okay.
(SPEAKING MANDARIN)
Sergio.
(GROANS)
You're the one controlling me.
Dr. Langham.
(BEEPING)
Alex.
Nine minutes and 47 seconds.
AUTOMATED VOICE: Initiated.
What can I do for you?
Police.
Requires override code.
Location.
Dr. Francis Langham.
Dr. Langham, tell us about the
work of the Hibiscus Trauma Unit?
We treat severely traumatized
young men and women,
men such as Ryan here.
He served three tours,
all of them hot.
WOMAN: And it all just got too much?
As it does for most.
The source of his
trauma lies elsewhere.
Do talk about it, my dear boy.
Two years ago,
my wife and I left dinner.
She was so tired and I just couldn't
decide if I wanted to drive or not.
She got in and she drove.
We crashed and she died,
and all I got was this scar.
WOMAN: Do you think your feelings
of guilt led to your condition?
I just know I should've
driven that night.
Well done, Ryan. It's important
what you read at night.
It sets the tone for your sleep.
We've done a lot of
neurological tinkering.
A lot of therapy.
And he's traveling on the right road.
Isn't that so, my dear boy?
Dr. Langham, I understand
you have been experimenting
in the use of bioware technology?
I understood we weren't going
to discuss that, Sandy.
What do you say to critics
who claim you're making radical
neurological interventions?
That what started as a
cure for your illness...
My illness has nothing to do with it.
It simply hastened my research.
What do you say to
allegations that claim
the injured British
military you import
is nothing to you but a source
of samples to play with?
I want to talk about your
own bioware firm, LSR.
We won't be talking
about that, I'm afraid.
Hello, I'm Dr. Francis Langham.
And I'm Harkin Langham.
We're the family behind LSR Bioware.
LANGHAM: How do we advertise
the amazing things we do?
We could show you our...
tech company.
But at heart,
we're just a family business.
(WHIMPERS)
HARKIN: Recording 7315. Controller.
Satellite.
These are all terms
we're familiar with.
The receiver is bioware.
Now, we're currently
working on our beta
and pilot test size which
will eventually be
picotechnology.
Coded with DNA which will give
us uninterrupted control.
Think of it as a
bio-technological modem.
(COUGHING)
Controversial bioware
firm LSR has been
shut down by the
scientific ethics board.
CEO, Francis Langham has
been called barbaric...
Son.
Straight. As always.
Of course, my dear boy!
Come.
That Van's still out there.
It's been out there for
two days. I don't like it.
I'm gonna go check it out.
Son, you're too suspicious.
Leonid works like a man possessed.
Everything is fine.
It's all this waiting
around that's annoying.
Nothing to do but wait.
It makes me edgy.
That van makes me edgy.
- I'm gonna go check it.
- I said stay!
There's something I wish
to talk to you about.
What is it?
I'm having trouble
remembering a few things.
Could be all the port switching
causing neural decay.
You're also getting knockout doses
of heavy drugs. It's not healthy.
No, well. Nothing we
can do about that.
What else are you having
trouble remembering?
The override code for the weapons?
In case Leonid...
Override 4754.
Your birthday?
4th month 2nd day. One day
too late, you always said.
Yes. Yes.
The name of our dog?
Alpha.
This is serious.
We should get you a scan.
Yes, but one more thing.
I'm having trouble remembering where...
Where we placed the boy.
I'm sure it's temporary, but I...
Yeah.
- I'm sure it will come back.
- Even so.
I'd like to write it down.
Image sized.
Since when are you right handed?
You learned to catch
the ball didn't you?
(GRUNTING)
AUTOMATED VOICE: Shutting down.
RYAN: Hey! Hey!
I need you to help me...
Sir, we need you to
calm down, all right?
Step back, sir!
- I kidnapped a boy.
- Scan.
AUTOMATED VOICE:
Scanning in progress.
- Unarmed.
- Listen to me.
Do not put your hands on us!
You need to calm down and step back!
Step back and calm down.
Otherwise, you'll be arrested.
- Arrest me! Arrest me!
- Sir, calm down.
Hey! Get on the floor with your
hands behind your head, now!
Shots fired! Freeze.
What are you going
to do now? Shoot me?
You need me alive, don't you?
What about you?
Ryan.
Just gimme the code. Gimme the code.
Authorize Sanchez 73763.
Authorize 73763.
AUTOMATED VOICE: Initialized.
Dana, what are you doing here?
You're working with them, aren't you?
Where's the kid? Where's Alex?
I'm sorry.
Sorry for what?
(SPEAKING RUSSIAN)
Sergio wants you to know that
you have been kidnapped.
After the amount of money you
guys paid last time to be let go,
he feels that, as you are rich,
a criminal and valuable to your friend,
that you are the perfect specimen.
SERGIO: Also.
I don't like you.
(HEAVY BREATHING)
It's all there.
Trust me.
Why don't you relax, huh?
I've come a long way.
Why don't you shut your fucking
mouth and finish counting?
(SPEAKING RUSSIAN)
He would like me to remind you
that this wouldn't have happened
if your friend hadn't tried
to steal his property.
By which he means me.
Okay.
Come on.
Okay?
I wonder, after receiving
all that you just did,
if you wouldn't mind letting
my friend take the girl.
We'll dispose of her when we're done.
Niet. Get out.
Come on, let's go.
We should move very quickly, Father.
I've arranged a little
surprise for them.
She really does resemble Mom.
I know why you like that girl.
- (SCREAMS)
- (SPEAKING RUSSIAN)
Go!
Don't be stupid, Ryan.
Don't make me shoot you.
- Hey!
- (GROANS)
HARKIN: God damn it!
(CLICKS)
Remember me, Ryan.
Come on, we're leaving.
Come on, let's go.
AUTOMATED VOICE:
Thank you for your custom.
House rules state that only one
customer may leave at any time.
This door will now
lock for two minutes.
View our selection of
girls in front of you.
Book your favorite by
scheduling an outcall
and have all your dreams come true.
Plan your next visit.
Try one of our many hot tub rooms.
Join our executive date...
(WOMAN SQUEALS)
(YELLING)
(SHOT FIRES)
(SHOUTS IN RUSSIAN)
Hey, I want a refund!
(GRUNTING)
(SCREAMS)
(YELLING)
(GROANING)
Dana, it's me Ryan.
You used to work as a nurse.
Your son's name is Eden.
- What do I do?
- Shut up!
Say, override 4754.
Override 4754.
0204.
Override 0204.
Didn't work.
You die, you fool.
Fool! One day too late.
Say 0104. 0104.
Override 0104.
(WHIRRING)
(SPEAKS RUSSIAN)
Hey! It's okay. It's okay.
Hey! It's okay.
I'm sorry, he made me help him.
He said that he would
kill me. I'm so sorry.
Everything's gonna be okay,
we need to get out of here, now.
Which way do we go?
Jump.
Here, take this.
Wherever I've spent the most time,
that's where the boy will be.
You need to start there.
I don't know where you've been.
Look, he pushed me out of the van.
He forced me to do that,
and then he pulled me back in again.
He only took me with him
that last time as bait.
I'm sorry. I don't
know where that is.
Okay, when I change you follow me,
you watch me, you bring the police.
I can't do that.
Then you need to get as far
away from me as possible.
Because if I see you again,
I will kill you. So, just go.
The boy that you're helping.
Is he your son?
Why do you care so much?
What else do I have?
- Get the girl.
- Move. Move. Go!
Freeze! NYPD.
Stand right where you are.
Get the girl now.
- Hands down.
- Come here.
You have the right to remain silent.
Anything you say can and will be
used against you in a court of law.
You have a right to an attorney.
If you cannot afford an attorney,
one will be provided for you.
Do you understand these rights...
six terrorist, seven terrorist, eight
terrorist, nine terrorist, 10 terrorist.
Let's go again.
One terrorist, two terrorist, three
terrorist, four terrorist, five terrorist,
six terrorist, seven terrorist, eight
terrorist, nine terrorist, 10 terrorist.
Fuck it, eleven terrorist.
Won't ask you again. Where's Leonid?
In a secret lab. Making a virus.
Finally. Where?
I want to tell you, but I'm being
controlled by Dr. Francis Langham.
I've have, like, a modem inside me.
Sometimes the signal goes
down, and I'm myself again.
It's called droning.
Now, we have procedures we
have to follow, as you know.
Always have a medic
present during waterings,
wait five minutes between
bouts, all that shit.
The thing is, this flight.
It doesn't exist.
So the rule book goes out
of the fucking window.
Wait!
Let's say I give the
benefit of the doubt.
I'm gonna try and reason with you.
Look at this shit.
And this, and this.
Leonid, the guy you're covering for,
has worked out how to do
something that no one else can.
There are guys who know how to
genetically code and engineer a virus.
We've been doing it ever since we
grew an ear on a mouse decades ago,
but Leonid's are something special.
His viruses fuck with your DNA.
This one was his first success.
Made you grow extra lungs.
Only they wouldn't stop growing.
To stop it going global we
had to scorch the earth
for 100 miles around his lab.
Now, Leonid out,
cooking up viruses in a lab?
That's a very bad idea.
So, where the fuck is
this dangerous asshole?
I don't know. I'm being controlled.
You need to speak to
Dr. Francis Langham.
- LSR Bioware?
- Yes.
Him and his son,
they made me kidnap a kid.
He and his son killed themselves
when their company went down.
They faked it. He's controlling me.
Bullshit.
This is your last chance.
I'm old school, my dad was
old school. Served 50 years.
I like old school things.
Cars, records,
guns.
No codes, just odds.
Right now it's one in six.
- Where's the lab?
- I don't know. Oh, God!
I'd advise you to start talking.
Who's in charge of the operation?
Who are you?
I don't know! Please.
Four. It's exciting, isn't it?
You sure you don't want to
tell us where the lab is?
I'm sorry.
- Please! I just wanna save the kid.
- What's the plan?
What virus is Leonid making?
I don't know...
It's the organ!
It's the organ he's
controlling me with.
It's bioware. He's made it smaller.
Nano, pico,
Leonid's virus will carry it.
Everyone infected will grow
a place the tech can sit.
This thing that they've done to me,
they're gonna do it to everyone!
He wants to control everyone!
I'm just gonna shoot him!
Please! Please! You have to
believe me, please. Please.
He's either crazy or
he's telling the truth.
Yeah, I say crazy.
I've seen worse though. Korea.
There's this guy who
thought he was the devil.
Another guy thought he was God.
Just to see what would happen,
we put 'em in a cell together.
Straight off, they started whaling
on each other. Real dirty.
- Who won?
- It was even.
But the devil had the better moves.
(METAL CREAKING)
Hey. Hey, is that plane following us?
Shit, it's firing something.
(SCREAMING)
Is that you, Ryan? Back again?
Hmm?
What do you think
about this arrangement?
No more dealing with inflatable
balls and knockout drugs.
All the tech in the world and the
best thing is to simply tie you up.
It's me, son.
- Really.
- Yes.
I'm trying to imagine what it will
be like to control anyone I choose.
The prospect makes me quite giddy.
Me, too.
We'll be more efficient and powerful
than any government in the world.
A few necessary sacrifices,
and people will not only want
control, they'll demand it.
Leonid wants to see his kid free.
Delivery is in a few days.
I would like to stretch my legs, son.
This? I might as well
be back in the chair.
We can't let that happen.
You should have been chained the
moment the fugues started, Father.
Ryan nearly destroyed
the whole project.
The solar flares are settling,
and they will no longer be
effecting the satellite's signal.
One, maybe two episodes at most.
So you gave the
satellite a high orbit.
I didn't know solar storms were going
to interfere with the satellite.
It's an 11-year cycle. This size?
It's once every thousand years.
- How am I...
- You should've checked all eventualities.
I did. I've sacrificed so much.
I have worked so hard.
You demanded obedience, and I
obeyed and succeeded, despite this.
You're right.
Your behavior these last few
months has impressed me.
Thank you.
I may not often say, but I
am proud to be your father.
Embrace me, son!
Ryan.
Clever, I admit.
But what now?
Save that kid?
From out here, the middle of nowhere?
In the amount of time
that you have left?
I don't see that happening, do you?
Just enjoy the sun on
your skin, breeze in your face.
Bird singing.
I have a suggestion.
Let's have a drink.
I'll show you a picture of your wife.
You remember her, don't you?
Come.
Have a seat.
I get it Ryan. I do.
Did I ever tell you about my mom?
She was 35. She was killed
along with 26 other people
by a solo crazed gunman who
didn't wanna pay taxes anymore.
Now, how is that fair?
He did the wrong thing.
I'm doing the right thing.
Just like your wife.
She's gone. Move on.
Don't spend the few remaining
fragments of your life suffering.
Enjoy them.
To living every moment
as if it were your last.
You're right.
So now I know what I need to do.
What's the point?
You don't wanna do that.
You'll kill us both.
You followed me.
Following, watching,
everywhere just like you asked.
I used the money you
left me and the truth is,
no one's been as good to me as you.
Ever.
There isn't anytime.
So you might as well just let me die.
Will you, Ryan, come back again?
Maybe once or twice.
That's enough to save the boy.
We both have lost people
that we care about.
We shouldn't lose this kid.
Put these on before you change.
Why are you really helping me?
What else do I have?
(RYAN GROANS)
- (BANGING ON DOOR)
- Hey!
Reply, Eden.
(CHAINS RATTLING)
Right answer, hero.
- How long?
- Three days.
We're not far,
but we haven't much time.
The other guy's been looking.
Ten minutes till you
change back, right?
Yeah.
Here you go.
All right. Let's roll.
This is where it's all going down.
Whatever it is.
Hibiscus.
I started a countdown.
So you'll know.
Okay, I need you to listen to me.
You need to run now.
'Cause if you see me again,
it won't be me.
- Do you understand?
- No.
- Yes. Yes.
- No!
- Listen, I'm trying to save your life.
- No. No.
(BEEPING)
AUTOMATED VOICE:
Welcome, Dr. Langham.
I've made your virus,
integrated the biotechnology.
Now let my son go,
you bastards. Let him go!
I'll have to test it.
- They killed Leonid...
- Drop the gun, Ryan.
Dr. Langham.
Yes!
Drop the gun or the boy dies.
We took this subject
to test the new virus
when we rescued you from the plane.
Or me, I should say.
Less than a day, the body
assimilates imbedded picotech.
Subject's online in two.
New population-control
satellite's been launched.
You're looking at the
first of the new breed.
I thought I was the first.
Third actually.
An expendable prototype.
All I have to do is walk out there,
and within days,
without them realizing it,
people will be ready
to be controlled.
Ready to be given purpose,
my dear boy.
What do you plan to do with me?
Nothing.
Your satellite will be back
online in a few moments.
I may just push white noise
through your signal,
keep you around like my
favorite old pair of slippers.
You won't be coming back again, Ryan.
Any last requests?
A drink.
I do have one more question.
Why?
You know how you control the masses?
Fear.
Humanity does appalling things.
Some of them, I've experienced.
We saw so many tragic cases
come through the unit.
It was sickening.
War. War. War.
Endless fighting and dying,
and dying and fighting.
But in the world that I create,
if you break my laws,
you will simply be switched off.
Your signal overtaken.
And that fear will create
a beautiful future.
A world without conflict.
- A world of harmony.
- Harmony.
Exactly!
So why do you wish to stop me?
Because I want my life back
and you don't have the right.
Not only do I have the right.
It's my duty.
Your life. You have no life.
I've been your life!
I took you because you ended yours
when you allowed your wife to die,
because you couldn't make a choice.
It's important what you
read last thing at night.
It sets the tone of your sleep.
That was one of the many
things you taught me.
I learnt so much from you.
So, so much.
Things I'd never
even heard of before.
Like valencies,
isomers and chemical reactions.
Did you meet him?
He's dead.
Doesn't matter.
How about this beautiful
creature next?
You're fond of her aren't you?
My dad likes her, too.
My mother had more class.
But this isn't just for her.
We need a new world and this is it.
- Your dad's plan won't work, Harkin.
- I agree.
My father's an idealist,
it doesn't mean he's wrong.
You see, I put a little
more thought into it.
There are no good guys and
bad guys, Ryan. Just opinions.
But you know the right way to get
one individual controlling everyone?
By having me controlling
the right individual.
For example, let's just say a
particularly unstable world leader.
Control's inevitable in some form,
whether it's us or not.
But this being airborne,
people are gonna purge their systems.
They're gonna mimic the tech,
they're gonna destroy the satellites.
I know that.
But me having the right person,
doing the right thing to ensure
that this planet has a future.
Now that makes sense, Ryan.
That's how I'll remake the world.
There's absolutely no
reason to stop me.
You don't give up,
I infect her, we win.
You shoot me, this falls,
it goes airborne, we win.
You do nothing, you time out, I win.
This is not a situation that
you can shoot yourself out of.
I guess not.
All this for a kid? You've caused
me so many problems, Ryan.
So, I'm gonna let you watch me
inject her before you time out.
Admittedly, it'll be a little
different for my father.
Let's just see if he likes
being inside her once again.
Something for him to toy around with
before he ultimately realizes
that he's not needed anymore.
She doesn't deserve that.
Oh, I know that.
But we should always try and do
what's right for our family, Ryan.
You of all people should know that.
Missed.
(GROANS)
Let's see how you like it!
Hey, whore, say goodbye...
(SCREAMING)
Hey, Ryan. Come on. Come on up.
You okay? Here. Here.
His name's Alex.
I want you to look after
him as if he were your own.
Thank you so much.
No! You don't have to do this.
If I don't do it,
I'm gonna change back.
Please! Please!
- I'm sorry.
- No!
Time's up!
(GROANS)
You okay? I got you.
Hang on. It's okay.
Hang on a second.
Ryan?
Hey, it's me.
It's okay now, it's over!
Harkin and Langham?
They're dead.
Look, I couldn't risk anyone else
tuning in, so I cut them out.
Where are we?
Home.
Look.
(BEEPING)
I tried explaining to
him as best I could.
It'll still probably take him a
little time to get used to you.
He's a good kid.
I was thinking that maybe we could
all hang until we figure things out.
Mmm.
(GROANS)
Baby, that was no minor surgery.
You need to rest.
I have an idea.
You take control.
- (BUZZING)
- MAN: ...hang tight. We're live in five.
Ryan?
Please rate this subtitle at www.osdb.link/44x5n
Help other users to choose the best subtitles