Watch Movies, TV Series and Live Sports
Signup Here -> WWW.ADMITME.APP
Three Swedes were arrested today
suspected of running-
-one of the world's biggest websites
for illegal downloading...
Good evening. The US government
threatened with trade sanctions-
-unless file sharing sites, like
the Pirate Bay, are shut down.
Illegal downloading has upset
big organizations in Hollywood...
The motion picture studios lost
The White House forced the
Swedish government to intervene.
We applaud the Swedish authorities.
It was an important site to stop.
The police website was attacked
on Friday-
-and last night
the government website.
The trial against the founders of
the Pirate Bay begins tomorrow.
Today they met the press.
What will happen to the Pirate Bay
if you're found guilty?
Nothing.
What are they going to do about it?
They've failed shutting it down once.
They're welcome
to come and fail again.
It's not the Pirate Bay
that's going to court tomorrow.
It is about getting us
who are connected to the Pirate Bay-
-into a political trial.
The trial tomorrow is not
about the law, it's about politics.
Half of all BitTorrent traffic
is coordinated by the Pirate Bay.
It's extreme amounts of traffic.
There are 22-25 million users
at this very moment.
A user is defined
as one ongoing upload or download.
Any questions? Please.
Where is Fredrik?
We don't know.
He was supposed to be here
but he's probably hungover.
The first question: Where is Fredrik?
I said that Fredrik likes to party.
I didn't want to lie and tell them
I knew where he was.
I tried to get hold of Fredrik
all day yesterday.
I called him a couple of times
and finally he answered.
He says: "Do you know where I am?"
I go: "No."
"I'm at Arlanda Airport."
"Why is that?"
"I'm leaving."
What?
He said that he had bought a ticket-
-to Kuala Lumpur, Malaysia. What
a great name for an escape plan.
So his plan was to head home
to his girlfriend in Laos.
Live with her and not give a shit
about anything.
Then suddenly he texted me:
"I think it's the Security Service.
The plane is broken."
"So where are you now?"
"On my way back to the hotel."
Phew!
The interest for the file-sharing
trial in Stockholm is massive.
You can't seriously think
that you can stop our world-
-our everyday, our reality.
This is so gay.
Monique Wadsted.
I also represent
the gaming industry. But not music.
We have the biggest damage claim.
I represent some of the
big film studios in Hollywood.
Warner Bros., Columbia,
20th Century Fox and MGM.
We're demanding compensations
of $13 million.
It might seem insanely high.
That should be seen as an indicator
of how big this business is.
Because this is about
5 movies during 6 months.
"The Pink Panther", "Syriana",
one "Harry Potter"-
-"Prison Break" and "Walk The Line".
There is no doubt about
what they have done.
They have run a commercial
business and making a profit.
The penalty for this type
of activity is prison.
Not fines.
Fredrik would like to tell his
version before the prosecutor starts.
Is that accepted by the prosecutor?
You may begin, Fredrik Neij.
I want to start by saying that I have
a great interest in computers and IT.
And especially for internet
and networks.
And that I... Well...
...I've lost my train of thought.
You forgot what you were saying.
You had a long interest in IT.
I got involved in the Pirate Bay
because of my interest in IT.
I think it's great fun
to work with technology.
For me, the Pirate Bay
is a technical challenge.
To run such a large website
and such a large tracker technically.
Play with computers that I could
never afford to play with on my own.
First I want to ask you...
The media often describes you
as a computer genius.
How would you describe
your competence yourself?
I do have a certain
technical competence, yes.
What does "a certain" mean,
compared to others?
I'm not sure this is the right time,
place or medium to post my CV.
But I am asking you.
Please answer politely.
I decline to answer that question.
It's too much of an estimation.
-It's what?
-Too hard to estimate.
-Too hard to estimate?
- It's a very difficult question.
How did you meet
Fredrik and Gottfrid?
I don't remember, but I assume
it was in a chat room on the internet.
When was the first time
you met IRL?
We don't use the expression IRL.
We say AFK. But that's another issue.
I don't remember that either.
Got to know each other IRL?
What is that?
In Real Life.
We don't like that expression.
We say AFK - Away From Keyboard.
We think that the internet
is for real.
This is what our office looks like.
Is this inside the Pirate Bay?
Yes. Here are some of
the people working on it.
-Are they working on it now?
-Yes.
Where are they based? In Sweden?
Let's see. USA, USA,
USA or England, England.
Finland, I think.
The Pirate Bay.
This is the web server.
Data base and search function.
The trackers are over there.
This little piece is the tracker.
It's the world's biggest tracker.
It coordinates 50%
of the world's BitTorrent traffic.
Not so many computers,
but powerful and well-configured.
Half the day has gone.
How did it feel in court?
So far it's been boring.
The prosecutors' strategy is to lie
as much as possible in the most boring possible way -
-so you fall asleep in court and become
physically undable to defend yourself.
Some say that you've made a lot of
money by spreading illegal material.
We've probably made a lot of money,
but the site costs a lot, too.
Hi. Okay, we're coming down. Bye.
-Let's eat.
-Okay. Nothing vegetarian.
Aren't you working on the site
we're on trial for while in court?
The pirated Depeche Mode CD
I have in my laptop is even funnier.
He'll open in 5 minutes.
How the hell can prosecutor Roswall
mix up megabit and megabyte?
Generally speaking, for storage you use byte and
when you measure speed you use bit.
It all started with Gottfrid's site
"America's Dumbest Soldiers".
It was a site
where you could rate from 1 to 10.
It was American soldiers
who died in the first Iraq war.
Then you could rate
how stupid they were-
-depending on
how silly their deaths were.
Neither the American government nor
anybody else appreciated the site.
I had a spare line
which I let him use for the site.
It was from British Telecom.
Someone at the US State Department
called the head of British Telecom.
He called the head of the operator
in Sweden where I worked.
So the US government ordered us
to remove the site.
We fought them for a long time
before we removed it.
We argued that it was
freedom of speech and parody.
After a while we closed it down,
when it became too much of a fuss.
Two months later Gottfrid needed
more bandwidth for the Pirate Bay.
I still had that line available.
We used it for the Pirate Bay.
Hearing with the defendant Peter
Sunde. The prosecution may begin.
Is it true that among
the Pirate Bay computers-
-you stored one that you owned?
I bought a computer
that I gave to the Pirate Bureau.
What is the Pirate Bureau?
It's an organization
that discusses the internet.
Is copyright and file sharing
discussed on their website?
Probably.
And they are critical to
the way copyright works today?
I'm not sure about that.
People have different views.
What's your opinion?
It's hard to say.
I think it's problematic.
In what way?
The fact that we're here today
shows that there is a problem.
First of all, I don't believe-
-that young people today
believe that copyright is wrong.
I think that's a myth.
This Kopimi Sect-
-has been really good
at promoting it.
It's so fucking beautiful!
We've changed it a bit.
So the question
in the newspaper was:
"If the Pirate Bay gets convicted,
won't they become martyrs?"
Monique said:
"No, they don't have any followers."
"However, they do have a small
Kopimi sect following them".
So sweet. That's us!
The Pirate Bureau came into
existence in the summer of 2003.
It was at the same time-
-as the record industry
sued Napster in the US-
-and the medical industry sued South
Africa for copying HIV-medicine.
The name "the Pirate Bureau"
was an easy choice.
It wasn't about
romanticizing pirate stuff-
-with eye patches and stuff.
We've never liked that.
The Anti-Piracy Bureau
already existed-
-we wanted to state that we're
the active part in this conflict.
The Anti-Piracy Bureau
is the reactive part.
This is Henrik Pontén
from the Anti-Piracy Bureau.
We've been tipped off
that you're selling copies.
Wait, don't close the door.
The police will come with a warrant.
They have a built a business based
on other people committing crimes.
They have created an industry with
banners and porn ads to earn revenue.
It was very profitable.
You're making your situation worse.
-I must be allowed to close the door.
-Come out, then.
If you look at studies
about file sharing-
-they don't do it for the fellowship
or to support the ideology.
It's because it's simple and free.
Then there is a small group
of people who do this...
...for reasons they claim
to be freedom of speech.
Our policy has always been
that the site is an empty page-
-that is created by the users.
We don't interfere with the content.
Freedom of speech?
I'd prefer the technological
viewpoint, a contact service.
-For communication?
-Yes.
I don't care about the piracy
ideology, copyright or politics.
I do this because it's great fun
to run a large site.
Describe the importance of the Pirate Bay.
It democratizes and creates great
conditions for freedom of speech.
What has that to do
with the copyrighted material?
The Pirate Bay makes it possible
for individuals to share material.
Even if it's copyrighted?
That's a tricky consequence
that I think we have to discuss.
What are you hoping for?
I hope we don't get a monitored,
restricted internet.
That's the biggest issue right now.
The copyright industry
is digging a grave for the internet.
They don't take into account the
public benefits of a free internet.
The problem is that old people
are running the companies.
They know how you made money
before and they don't want to change.
They're like the Amish. They don't want electricity.
They know how to make do without electricity.
Roger Wallis,
please come to Court Room 9.
Do you think people who download
movies will go and buy them as well?
-If they would buy the movie?
-Yes, get it legally.
Yes, but it depends on the quality.
If people want better quality.
Or if the DVD has special features.
You have to increase the value of
the products in order to sell them.
If you want to adjust your
business model to the new world.
Thank you. I called your institute
and asked these questions-
-because we were unable to
put together your curriculum vitae.
You've stated in court
that you're a professor-
-but your institute calls you
a temporary guest lecturer.
-Do you know how to use Google?
-Yes.
Then it's really simple
to find my CV.
-We've moved on from that question.
-I thought so too.
Let's move on.
Thank you, Your Honor.
When you were appointed,
were there any competitors?
I thought we had moved on,
Your Honor?
-I would like an answer.
-Please answer the question.
I have no idea!
I was asked to come and I went
through... And we're back on this!
...the standard selection process
at the Royal Institute of Technology.
All my publications were submitted.
Three professors
and two international experts-
-deemed that I was eligible
for the appointment.
Thank you.
Please just answer the questions.
How low can you sink?
They're so afraid of
the result of your research.
They can't attack you there, so they
attack you on a personal level.
The Royal Institute of Technology.
Professor Roger Wallis.
I think it's sick to attack
the academic world like this.
It's not the first time. I've heard
about professors in the US-
-who have indicated that file sharing
could be positive for the industry-
-that have been hunted down
with a whip.
It's sad that these American methods
are coming to Sweden.
Would you like any compensation
for participating today?
Please send flowers to my wife
for the sleepless night.
The court's budget
will not allow that.
It's now two or three days
since the court appearance.
I'm starting to look through
all the blogs around the world.
I'm looking here at "TorrentFreak":
"Pirate Bay witness
overwhelmed with flowers."
And an awful lot
of very kind people who wrote:
"At last somebody from the older
generation"... I'm an old man.
..."seems to understand
the way we think."
I also make the point here
that as a composer...
A song I wrote
bought our first house.
I support copyright, but only
if it encourages creativity-
-or economic incitement
or is an incentive to create.
Not copyright
as a huge control mechanism-
-for people who sit
on large swathes of rights.
A police officer that worked with
the Pirate Bay investigation-
-was employed by a film studio
shortly after the investigation.
In an email, Warner Bros. states
that the information in the media-
-about an alleged conflict
of interest is pure speculation.
He sold his apartment and bought
a house. Just after he got the job.
I was disappointed
when you didn't investigate him.
You're claiming stuff
I don't have a clue about.
You should gather material
and submit it to the police.
I did, but they dropped the case.
Well... In that case
there is nothing I can do.
His income that year
is higher than his police salary.
He has declared
capital gains of $120 000.
This fucking trial just gets
more and more bizarre every day.
I think there's been a power cut
at the Pirate Bay again.
-Why do you use automatic fuses?
-They're attached to the cable cover.
When an automatic fuse dies 5 times
you have to replace it.
My laptops break all the time so I
don't have time to put stickers on.
I spilled gin and tonic in one.
I spilled beer in another.
And I fell on one
and smashed the screen.
-Do you have WIFI here?
-Yes, it's called "bambuser".
-Doesn't it work?
-Key... Bambuser...
-WTF!
-Stop shouting.
I have abstinence! I haven't
been on the internet all day.
On page 24
you have received an email-
-that you forwarded
to Gottfrid and Peter Sunde.
Why did you forward it?
I didn't. Every mail
that contains DMCA-
-is automatically forwarded
to Gottfrid and Peter.
I have a lot of abbreviations
in my filter.
-Who programmed the abbreviations?
-I did.
-Why?
-Because I got a lot of spam.
Why would you consider an email-
-called "Copyright Claim" as spam?
Spam are emails
that I haven't requested.
Fredrik Neij stated
that as soon as he got an email-
-from someone
representing copyright owners-
-it was forwarded to you
from his computer. Is that correct?
Since no one seems capable
to do what we've told them-
-i.e. contact the user
that uploaded the material-
-those complaints
have either been ignored-
-or been replied to
in more or less well-phrased ways.
Why was it sent to you?
I express myself well in writing,
as opposed to Fredrik.
But such a claim didn't result
in anything but scorn and ridicule?
The first 100 times it resulted in us
saying: "Contact the uploader."
-And the following 100 times?
-Then we lost our patience.
The Company PRQ...
-Was it a web hotel?
-Yes, it had just been founded.
Is it correct that the prosecution
confiscated 195 servers-
-and that 11
belonged to the Pirate Bay?
11 or 13, I don't remember exactly.
This is outrageous.
This is a true injustice.
They're attacking a company that has
nothing to do with the Pirate Bay.
Simply because the co-founders were
involved with the Pirate Bay for fun.
Thanks to the raid
PRQ got a lot of attention.
Everybody knew that we never
give any information to the police.
Our customer database
was encrypted.
The police seized our servers, but
didn't get any customer information.
When the Pirate Bay
was shut down after the raid-
-you didn't have
any servers left, right?
You were back online after three days.
Where did you get the servers?
We leased servers from a company
called NFOrce in Holland.
It's a co-location company.
-How was that received?
-With standing ovations.
It's a pleasure to announce
that the Pirate Bay is back online!
In your face, Hollywood!
-Peter!
-Yes? I'll be there soon!
That's how you have treated me. I get
letters from your lawyers saying:
"Swedish law cannot protect you.
US law will get you".
You put private detectives on us.
I've had two outside my house.
-I know nothing about that.
-But it's your responsibility.
It could have been the film industry.
-No, it was the music industry.
-Ok.
TPB isn't interested
in music and movies.
TPB is a generic medium for
distribution of all types of files.
People shouldn't say that TPB only is about
spreading illegal movies and music.
Then your world is this small.
It's your loss.
Instead we could say
that file sharing is good.
Then we could focus on ways
to let artists make money.
-We think file sharing is good.
-Sure, but you sue everyone.
No. We don't want
to prosecute anyone.
We just want people in Sweden
to start respecting copyright laws.
What was the purpose of
the Pirate Bay in your opinion?
We never spoke about purposes.
If it was about reforming laws
or if it was about-
-hatred against some Americans.
I don't know their purpose.
But for Fredrik, and it was
Fredrik I was dealing with-
-the purpose was to make it
a big site. The biggest site in the world.
From my point of view I liked the
idea of the world's biggest site.
-How is the Pirate Bay financed?
-How the website is financed?
We have ads on the site
that generate money.
A guy called Lundström
helped you financially, didn't he?
Yes, we we're sponsored
by a company called Rix Telecom.
-What was his purpose?
-Free advertising for his company.
Carl Lundström is an interesting guy.
He's behind
many right-wing organizations.
Carl Lundström
has apparently given money to...
Answer the question!
Did he represent these organizations?
It really bugs me-
-that everybody looks at us
as right-wing extremists.
It makes me really hurt and angry.
My brother is a convicted anarchist.
He's been in court,
defending his opinions.
We've both been on
a neo-Nazi organization's hit list.
It feels strange to be accused of
founding that neo-Nazi organization.
It's really hard.
I can only stand behind
my own politics.
When you have some influence
and people listen to you-
-you should use that position
to do something good.
When did you become
the Pirate Bay's spokesperson?
Well, it's not an official title, but
a function that has been given to me.
Nobody wanted to do that part,
but it was important to communicate-
-that the Pirate Bay
was doing something important.
Since nobody else wanted to,
I started doing it.
What was Peter Sunde's role
during that time?
He showed up
when we needed a public face.
Since neither I nor Fredrik
are suited in furnished rooms.
So he had nothing
to do with running the site.
-Or any design?
-No.
-Funding?
It's AIM. You told me it was MSN.
What's the fucking difference?
They're two different networks.
It's like IRCnet and EFnet.
-Come on!
-It was the Museum of Modern Art...
You're so loud!
You give me a headache.
-I'm half deaf, of course I shout.
-You're making me deaf.
He wants to spread his misery.
-Why can't you hear anything?
-Sex, drugs and industry!
Sex?
I've heard your sex stories.
How much does a banner cost?
You are asking me about
5-year-old figures again.
If you give me a day I can
probably find some examples.
But I can't give you
any exact figures.
Does $500 per week sound
like a reasonable amount?
That sounds about right.
It's within the right range at least.
Within the right range, you say.
Was there an agreement about how
the ad revenue was to be divided?
-I have no idea.
-You don't. Fine.
-I'm so fucking tired.
-This will be your life for 5 years.
Are you Kafka or what?
It feels like "The Trial"
all over again.
I might wake up as Gregor Samsa
and can't go to work-
-because I've turned into a beetle.
When do you go back to Cambodia?
-As soon as this shit is over.
-Quiet. It's a secret.
What are your thoughts
in general about the case?
It will be nice when it's over.
Tomorrow it's just half the day.
And after the closing arguments
we're finished.
How much money
are they looking for?
They want around
20 million Euro in damages.
But good luck finding that money.
I don't have that kind of money.
If they knew that our entire office
is a chat room on IRC-
-they wouldn't believe it.
And they don't because they've been
asking questions about companies.
Yeah, we tried to get organized,
but we failed every single time.
I don't think they can grasp the idea
of an organization without a boss.
People have no idea how small we are.
We're just a couple of guys in a chat room.
I've argued that the yearly
profit is at least $170,000.
And that's the minimum.
Gottfrid Svartholm Warg stated-
-that the price for an ad on TPB
was $500 per week.
The report from
the Forensic Laboratory-
-states that
at the time of the raid-
- there were 64 unique ads.
A rough estimate...
$500 times 64-
- gives us $34 000 per week.
That amount times 52 weeks,
i.e. weeks per year-
-makes a yearly
revenue of $ 1700 000.
Thus The Pirate Bay isn't idealistic.
It's pure commercial business.
Here we go. 4 times 52.
$110 000. That's a massive sum.
We never got that kind of money back then.
If you calculate with the right
number of ads - 4 instead of 64-
-you get a much more
realistic figure.
But he has miscalculated
so many things.
Did Roswall mean 64 different ads,
or 4 ads times a bunch of pages?
-Yes.
-What the hell! Is he insane?
He's right behind you.
We're thinking of doing a
Bambuser press conference.
Hell no!! No! No!
They keep calling us organized.
They don't understand
what a joke that is.
It's disorganized crime.
You mean for all of you? I think
you are going to get convicted.
Take a picture of Monique.
It's her copyright.
-I'm leaving.
-Bye bye.
Do you need a hand?
This is the only help
you'll ever get from me.
-That's so kind.
-I am kind.
And I still have my soul, too.
Here's Fredrik,
let's get out of here.
Let's calculate
how much money we have earned.
Let's start with
an exponential function.
-You can add times 64.
-Right.
And for N we choose
a random number.
Between 10 and 5 200.
Do you write code in Swedish?
Now take the square root
to see what Monique's soul costs.
The answer?
Do it mathematically correct.
Come on, not Pi.
He's mad.
Go check that it's correct.
Okay. I'll give you some cred.
It's in my muscle memory. I can't
remember it writing with a pen.
I have to emulate a keyboard.
So what are you doing
at 11.00 on the 17th of April?
Queuing outside the court?
-11 am means 5 pm local time.
-I was thinking the same thing.
Gottfrid, can you sit over here?
I'm not taking part in any fucking
press conference. I'm sick of it!
-It's in English.
-I'm so fucking tired of cameras.
-And fucking bullshit!
-Sit here anyway. It's the last time.
Nein.
Hi everybody.
I'm here and together with me
I have some of the guys from TPB.
Take your time and ask
some questions to the guys-
-and see what they have to say.
-I didn't know we were that boring.
-You are that boring.
Because you're not part of this.
Film him!
Anakata!
Today the court will decide if
the men behind the Pirate Bay-
-are guilty of
copyright infringement.
Follow the verdict live on svt.se
from 11.00.
No, but... Sure, but don't worry.
Because I'm not worried myself.
But I'll talk to you later. Bye.
Dad was more nervous than I am.
The verdict is in for the Pirate
Bay trial. It's 11 o'clock.
All four defendants are sentenced
to one year in prison.
The offense is called "assisting
copyright infringement".
- So one year imprisonment...
-This is so insane!
This must be a joke.
Take it easy, mom.
Nothing will happen.
This is going to take 5 years.
Take it easy.
The District Court is ruled by
politicians. We call it the Dice Court.
Just stay calm.
But I can't talk right now. I have
to watch the press conference.
Okay. Take care.
The District Court has announced
the verdict in the Pirate Bay trial.
We have estimated the damages
to approximately $4,5 million.
Fuck you. He's going to get
a good job in Hollywood after this.
This is so insane!
The hottest set up ever.
I don't have time right now,
I have to decline.
No, I'm the only one in Sweden. The
others are in the desert or the jungle.
No, they are not going
to send us to jail whatsoever.
The way it works in Sweden
is that they can't...
...do anything about the case
before we can't appeal anymore.
-What are we going to call this?
-LOL?
For the lulz.
If this was a movie
this is where the heroes-
-encounter their first problem.
Karate Kid got bullied in the
beginning and got beaten up.
And we've just been beaten up.
Thanks, Hollywood, for teaching
us that the good guys win in the end.
In total they wanted around
100 million Swedish crowns, right?
And they got 30 million.
But they could have gotten 1 billion,
it doesn't matter because...
We can't pay and we wouldn't pay.
This verdict makes me upset
to the bone.
There is no chance in hell
this verdict will hold in an appeal.
I will cross the creek, the stream
and the Atlantic for a redress.
It means a lot
to have taken a stand.
It's important to re-establish Sweden
as a state governed by law.
The judge in the Pirate Bay trial
is accused of bias.
People are demanding a retrial.
Last night I learned about
the news that blew up today.
The judge in the Pirate Bay trial-
-is a member of organizations that
are working with copyright issues.
Organizations that the attorneys
from the plaintiff's are part of.
I was horrified and shocked
to learn about this.
-Why didn't you inform the court?
-Good question. I didn't.
Yes, I know how he thought.
"My friends will be happy
if I rule in their favor."
It's ridiculous. I didn't think
the legal system was that bad.
-Was it a correct decision?
-That's for others to decide.
It's Tomas, the judge.
He's the judge in the District Court.
He's a member of the
Swedish Association for Copyright.
That's the whole point.
He sits in the board for the Swedish
Association for Industrial Rights.
These two organizations
have a common publication, NIR.
And all the lawyers
that assist the prosecution:
Peter Danowsky, Henrik Pontén
and Monique Wadsted.
They're all members
of the same organization.
So he looks very mixed up
in these people's world.
From a graphical point of view
it's very obvious.
I can't say if he was biased-
-but just the fact that he
withheld this information-
-makes him unsuitable
as a judge in this case.
The verdict is questionable, since he
might be perceived as being biased.
-Here's my pirate copy.
-I have a parasite.
-Is this you? Fredrik?
-Yes.
-What's your job?
- IT. Internet.
Because of our tradition
and the regulations of the village-
-you have to pay for the engagement.
How much would you like
to pay for the engagement?
$6,000?
If you leave her you have to pay
the bride dowry times two.
That means $12,000. Agreed?
Please write your name and sign it.
Do you like it? Good.
-Yummy! Yummy!
-Hello!
If it didn't cost me $12,000
I would divorce you.
It's always this way with the
Pirate Bay. Chaos and cheating.
Last Monday a verdict came
from the Stockholm District court-
-where Judge Norström is chairman.
Black Internet, the ISP
for Pirate Bay's ISP must quit-
-and if they continue to
give access to the Pirate Bay-
-they will be fined $75 000 per day.
Then all hell broke loose.
So they're trying legal tricks
and we're trying technical tricks.
It's like a constant tactical game
with different weapons.
When we realized that
the Pirate Bay was down-
-we looked around,
because we always have backups.
Then I realized that the Pirate Party
had registered their own ISP.
The Pirate Party works for reformed
copyright laws, an open internet-
-and free access to culture.
I realized that if we're hosted
by the Pirate Party-
-it means that if someone closes them
down, they're closing down the party.
That means closing down a party
that represents Sweden in the EU.
That would be political censorship
on the highest level.
If you're hosted by the Pirate Party
you get political protection.
You could say that you get
diplomatic immunity.
After days of speculation "Rapport"
can now reveal that the Pirate Party-
-takes over the responsibility for
the security of WikiLeaks' servers.
WikiLeaks or the Pirate Party copied
what they had done with TPB.
Giving WikiLeaks protection
by a political party-
-by sharing
the same internet connection.
Every leak on WikiLeaks has been released on
TPB since there is no censorship there.
Gottfrid is good at tech stuff
and encryption-
-and he's worked on
many important projects.
Like "Collateral Murder"
that made WikiLeaks famous.
"Look at those dead bastards"
Julian has a lot of respect
for Gottfrid.
I remember when Gottfrid said:
"There's a new customer, WikiLeaks."
"They need help
because they're under attack."
The first time I got in contact
was when we had to pay a bill.
Because no one, and
that was a constant problem...
No one remembered
the stupid customer number.
And no one wanted to say
anything on the phone.
In 2008 I flew to Sweden
to pay the bill in cash.
Gottfrid always said he didn't
want money from WikiLeaks.
I flew there and paid for
one year and a bit in advance.
Julian was with me.
He flew in as well.
And we arranged this meeting
with Gottfrid to hand over the money.
And it was one of the
weirdest incidents in my life.
He came to the hotel and he had
someone waiting outside in a car.
And they had an agreement that
Gottfrid would be near a window.
So he stood there in this lobby.
With his long hair,
looking completely...
-Strange! Fucked up.
-And he behaved really strange.
And every 30 seconds he turned to
see if the guy in the car was there.
And Julian and I were standing
there and we basically thought-
-that we would go hang out
or something.
So we asked him if he
wanted to come up to the room.
And he was like: "No, no, I can't."
He was turning around.
Never heard that before.
And then handing over some cash
and the guy jumped in the car-
-and they drove off
and we felt like...
That was meeting PRQ for us.
A warm welcome to Peter Sunde.
First question: Are you a killer
that ruined the whole industry?
I would love to take credit for it but I can't.
Sorry. They did it themselves.
-There is a law case now with you.
-Just one?
I don't know how many but
some discussions going around.
You had a new idea: Flattr.
It comes from the discussions
we had during the Pirate Bay.
There were two sides. One side said
there is no problem with downloading.
The other side said they're not
making any money from the internet.
-And there was nothing happening.
-Can you explain how Flattr works?
You as a user sign up
and you put money into an account.
You decide how much
you want to spend per month.
Then you find Flattr buttons. They
look like the Facebook Like buttons.
If you click it we remember it
until the end of the month.
At the end of the month
we count your clicks-
-and we share your money equally
amongst them.
-Where is the money going?
-It's going to the creators.
That's the whole concept.
The trial in the Court of Appeal
against the Pirate Bay began today.
Let's shake hands today again.
-It's a sick team, right?
-I'm soaking wet.
To rent a car costs $400 per week.
I bought that one for $600.
I'll use it for 6 weeks.
-Is it legal?
-Sure. I've even paid the taxes.
I don't really care about parking
tickets - I have a $7 million debt.
The Court of Appeal, please.
-Is Gottfrid coming?
-I highly doubt that.
-Unless he teleports himself.
-Okay.
He wrote this morning that he's hospitalized
with a parasite infection in Cambodia.
So yes, it's highly unlikely
that he'll come.
-Do you have any other trials?
-The civil cases.
-The penalty fine stuff.
-How many are they?
One in Italy, one in Holland...
One in Denmark that we're not
summoned to, and one in Norway.
Kuwait, Ireland. Anything else?
What is the most important?
I believe it's very important to look
at how our society ought to be.
Not just rule so that big companies
can make a bigger profit.
How does this feel? 8 days to go.
It's boring
that we're just watching video.
You wanted to speak for yourself
but weren't allowed to, right?
I think the new court system
is really bad.
You can't introduce new material.
We don't even need to be in court.
They could just take the old material
and rule from that.
Hey, thanks for coming!
-How are you?
-I'm really sick.
Then why the hell
are you shaking my hand?
-He's also sick.
-What's wrong with you?
I have a cold and an eye infection.
I didn't sleep at all last night.
I just got an SMS
from Gottfrid's mother.
She wrote that he is still
in Cambodia.
She said that he is really ill.
He's had problems before as well.
When you look at him, health
isn't the first thing you think of.
-What are you working with today?
-I run websites.
In Cambodia or Thailand?
With the internet you can work anywhere
as long as you have Internet access.
State prosecutor Roswall accused
the defendants of contempt-
-since they have continued
to run the site after the verdict.
He wants the one year imprisonment
for all four to be affirmed.
The tunnel computer is located in
Pionen with the Pirate Party.
Pionen is a show-off in Apple style.
The tunnel computer is the entrance
from the internet to the Pirate Bay.
Then everything happens
in the background somewhere.
On the real servers,
that are hidden.
Right now we're on our way
to the real mountain.
That's an expensive table.
-6 cores?
-12 cores.
4 CPU's with 12 cores.
Here. The Pirate Bay.
And that's all.
We run an efficient ship.
Where are the people
who run the Pirate Bay based now?
I don't know. Ask the Pirate Party,
they are hosting the bandwidth.
But it has changed owners after
we passed it on, too. Once or twice.
We miss the support from the
Pirate Party in the District Court.
-With buses and stuff.
-The buses were the Pirate Bureau.
Was it the Pirate Bureau?
With trumpets and flags and stuff.
It feels like they
have forgotten about us.
The pirate movement's idea
to fight for free file sharing-
-just isn't accepted anymore.
It was just a little fad.
I never thought it would survive.
-I don't want them.
-You don't have to sign them.
But by law you have been served.
What does that mean?
-I can't force you to sign.
-No, you can't.
-But you've been served.
-Who are you?
-I'm the subpoena server.
-Can I see your ID?
Can I see the last 4 digits, please?
-You should quit smoking.
-Do I smell?
This is stressful for me, too.
-Does it feel bad to do this?
-Kind of.
-But they pay you well?
-No.
-Why do you do it?
-It's my job.
Do you have kids? Then I
understand, but get a better job.
I've been thinking about that.
-Is this from Danowsky?
-I don't know what it's about.
-So you don't know where it's from?
-Holland.
-Okay. Good luck.
-Thanks. Likewise.
-He's got a great job.
-I feel sorry for him.
I don't. He's like a meter maid.
Did you see the debate on TV?
A young girl said: "This is not about
young people wanting to commit crimes."
"They just have
a different consumption pattern."
"They just want to consume
movies and records that way."
"It's horrible to hunt them.
The market must adjust instead."
Life is cooler
than the internet.
That's probably a really
radical opinion around here.
After the cold war
they had to invent enemies-
-that you couldn't even kill.
Terror, piracy and drugs.
It's obvious that PRQ
has had customers-
-that some say are connected to
terror, piracy and drugs.
That can't be denied.
I guess all three of them at the
same time for one single customer.
You mean Gottfrid Svartholm Warg!
He's a pirate and a junkie.
And when you talk to him
you get a little scared.
You could say he's a Taliban.
I'm back from Cambodia.
I've been there for a month.
I've been really worried
about Gottfrid's health.
I don't want to talk
too much about...
He hasn't been using stuff
constantly.
It's been every now and then.
When he has a deadline.
He gets stressed by his work
when something has to be done.
So then he does
a whole lot of drugs.
I just couldn't stand by and watch.
I've seen friends struggle
with drugs before.
And it's... What can I say?
It's tough.
It's not something you want
to see a friend go through.
-What are we gonna do?
-Crush racism!
-When?
-Now!
-When, when, when?
-Now, now, now!
-What are we gonna do?
-Crush racism!
Brokep/Peter is a fucking
vegetarian leftist bitch ass bastard.
But he's got balls because
he's in the Pirate Bay?
-He's giving all the interviews.
-He's still a bitch.
He does it because of ideological
pussy-inflicted instincts.
He needs to look himself in the ass
and take his own life in his hands.
If he's had a beer or two, he becomes
the most annoying person on earth.
The problem is he takes a
couple of beers at least everyday.
Isn't there some connection
to right-wing parties in Sweden?
Carl Lundström,
one of the co-defendants-
-was a right-wing extremist before.
He founded a lot of crap.
But in the end-
-he married a Jewish girl.
He has four kids.
To call him a right-wing extremist
was correct 10-20 years ago.
Now I wouldn't say that.
If Carl Lundström
is xenophobic then so am I.
Every time I've been beaten or
robbed, it's been by immigrants.
And I don't mean seventh-generation
Finnish immigrants.
I mean these
dirty fucking immigrants.
What can I say. He's stupid
when it comes to things like that.
He has never thought for himself.
He just says what his parents say.
He's an alcoholic racist asshole.
-But I still love him.
-And you know what?
All the emails in the Pirate Bay
trial comes from Anakata.
Anakata the don't-know-how
to-fucking-encrypt-his-computer!
Even Peter and I encrypted
our emails. But Gottfrid didn't!
Gottfrid is the stupidest person
in the entire history of IT.
Yeah, the Pirate Bay is really tight!
I have no batteries left.
I'm surprised there are no cameras.
-Yes, today is the last day.
-Finally! I'm going home.
-You can throw them away.
-You've been served anyway.
Is this gonna come on YouTube?
-You can throw them away.
-You do it.
-You can't force me to take them.
-You've been served.
It was you who dropped the papers.
Come on!
I want to sleep.
Sabaidee!
When I get acquitted tomorrow
I'm going to sue them for millions.
Billions! At least!
We can't be worse than they are with fantasy
numbers. I landed in Sweden on Saturday.
I'm helping out with the new Leaks
project's servers in the server hall.
Everybody has left WikiLeaks
except for Julian and maybe Anakata.
Because he's like
in love with Julian.
Fuck! Blink if you're gonna
turn, you fucking anus!
Goddamnit!
-How are you?
-I'm fine.
Nice to see you again.
You're good?
Do these people know what's
happening in your life today?
-No.
-Not even your wife?
Yes.
I don't know. For Fredrik it's easy.
He can just avoid going home.
What do you mean? I don't have
any plans on going home.
I really don't know.
I don't have a clue.
I'm hesitating. But I won't
accept a conviction.
I can serve a prison sentence.
But why do it if I don't have to?
There's really no reason
for you to do that.
Look around. Why shouldn't I
stay here for 5 years?
You can't go to jail for something
you haven't done.
Political exile is what it's about.
I don't want to become a martyr.
But I don't think I'll be convicted.
Knock on wood... But we'll see.
Cheers!
Beer man!
Are you going to get drunk
from happiness or sadness?
Can I tell you in 12 minutes?
Hey! The internet just synched up!
I think it's an omen.
Stop lagging!
"If TPB founders are acquitted, it's
a victory for internet freedom."
Check out my eye infection!
"The pirate Gottfrid Svartholm Warg
handed in a medical statement."
Gottfrid Svartholm was "sick".
"...was shortened but the damages
were raised." We're convicted.
We're convicted. Domstol.se. It's Spam.
Copy the link.
The link underneath!
"The Court of Appeal considers the
defendants' contribution proven."
"Fredrik Neij is sentenced
to 10 months, Peter Sunde 8"-
-"and Carl Lundström to 4 months."
-What about Gottfrid?
-He's not in the case.
Right.
The damages went up
from $4,5 million to $6,6 million.
Well... We lost.
Fucking idiots.
I'm calling my mom.
Hi. I just wanted to say that they
gave us a shorter sentence.
But we're appealing.
8 months instead of one year.
I just wanted to call and
tell you that. So don't be worried.
I have 59 pages I have to read.
Okay, great. Take care.
Fucking idiots.
-The internet just died!
-Goddamnit! Yes, it did.
Fucking Windows crap!
The statute of limitation is 5 years.
They can't issue an international
warrant of arrest.
I can sit here and jerk off
for 5 years. And I will.
Are you gonna masturbate
for 5 years? In one go?
I'll do it on and off.
This means that
the internet is criminalized.
They label the internet as a place where
crimes are committed. "Close it down."
We're not even on BBC or CNN yet!
That irritates me! Come on!
I guess we have to live with the fact
that we're not important anymore.
-The Bay!
-When does the internet come back?
Maybe in 2 hours. If we're lucky.
Ladies and gentlemen, dear friends.
We are meeting today to discuss-
-one of the hot issues right now
in the European Parliament.
Thank you very much for having me.
It's very brave to invite me here.
I've been a pain in the ass for the
copyright industry for a long time.
I'm one of the spokespersons
for the Pirate Bay.
TPB is the largest file
sharing system in the world.
It's ten times larger than Napster
at it's peak, and it's still growing.
Please rate this subtitle at www.osdb.link/tlB
Help other users to choose the best subtitles
Watch Movies, TV Series and Live Sports
Signup Here -> WWW.ADMITME.APP