Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org
Good.
My dad had three kids.
Me, my sister, and the institute.
That's just the way it was.
You knew that if you had a baseball game or,
I don't know,
some sort of special event,
there was always a good chance
he might not be there.
I mean, don't get me wrong,
he was there a good amount of the time.
Just not all the time.
I remember I tried to trick him
into thinking I had ESP.
Or that I was moving stuff
around with my mind,
hoping it might get him to pay
a little more attention.
And he'd play along
for a few minutes, but...
then he'd leave for work.
I was four... when it happened.
So I don't have too many memories
of my father.
I kinda remember
what it felt like to be with him.
Talking with me, holding me.
One thing I've always remembered
is this game we used to play
on nights when he'd put me to bed.
He'd ask all these questions
about animals.
How many eyes does a fish have?
And I'd say, "Two."
How many noses does a monkey have?
How many ears does a gopher have?
That's really all there was to it.
I remember thinking it was fun.
We got married in 1965.
I wanted children right away,
but Henry wanted to wait.
'Cause it was about that time
that he was starting the institute.
And then he had a different
research lab job
at the same time so we could make rent.
He worked a lot.
Even after we had both kids.
But he loved it.
You know?
A man has the right to love his work.
Our goal was to conduct unbiased,
empirical research
on exceptional human abilities.
Psychokinesis, ESP, precognition.
Things that are typically considered
fringe science or parapsychology.
Dr. West, and the rest of us,
quite frankly,
all believed that there was real science
to be discovered in these areas.
We had a good time doing
what we were doing.
We were underfunded, of course,
but we were still relatively young,
so it didn't matter.
In the first few years alone,
we published close
to 30 journal articles between us.
And there were some
truly exceptional cases.
All documented.
Well, we did a lot of different
kinds of tests, but...
probably the most effective one
to measure clairvoyant abilities
were the Zener cards.
This one?
It's the lines. The wavy lines.
Well, if you select each card at random,
then the success ratio
will be close to 20%.
But we had several subjects
whose ratio was closer to 30%.
And that might not seem like very much,
but if you realize that we
did each test over 200 times,
you begin to understand
the virtual impossibility of that figure.
I think we were all secretly
hoping to discover the next Nina Kulagina.
She was a woman
from the former Soviet Union.
Truly remarkable.
Nina's psychokinetic abilities were
probably the most well-documented
and they stood up
to the strictest of scrutiny.
The closest we encountered
to that level was Norman LeClair.
French-Canadian man.
Norman's PK abilities
were astounding at times.
That's how it works. Pretty simple?
Yeah.
Try to vibrate the game board.
It's all right. Take your time.
That's all right. You gave it your best shot.
We can try again later.
Dr. West brought in colleagues,
some well-known and esteemed
researchers at the time,
to observe Norman.
All the necessary steps were taken
to prevent any claims of researcher bias
or improper testing methods.
All outside variables were controlled,
for this was to be the moment the snickering,
the talking behind hands
would finally stop.
This was proof.
- God, I can't believe that.
- Explain that.
- As we said.
- How do you explain that one?
How do you explain that?
- What do you guys think?
- Oh, my God.
Oh, they were clearly impressed.
Even though, I'd have to say,
they didn't really allow themselves
to show it.
I was happy. I was happy for Henry.
He had worked so hard for that moment.
But then, just before
the researchers left...
one of them noticed something odd
on the wristwatch
of one of our research assistants.
And it turned out that this watch
had been rigged with a small
neodymium magnet.
And every one of our tests
involved metal in some capacity.
Even the trace amounts of iron
in the cereal.
And this guy had been complicit
with Norman's ruse right from the start.
Right under our noses. It was...
it was a crushing blow.
For the institute's credibility
and for Henry's reputation.
It was... it was awful.
Is there...
something else we should know about?
Judith? With you?
It's like...
it's like being in a well sometimes.
I can see it, I can hear it,
but nobody knows I'm there.
I'd... I'd like to help you.
Whatever is going on.
Judith was first brought
to the institute
in September of 1976 by her sister...
sister Margaret. She had been reading
about the work we were doing
in a small magazine or something.
And she thought we would be interested
in testing Judith.
The first thing she did
when she walked in
was she told me it was my birthday.
Which caught me a bit off guard.
Not because it was my birthday.
It wasn't, it was the day before.
Maybe it was a guess.
You see, that's something you always have
to guard against with the work we did.
Lucky guesses. False positives.
If you let yourself fall victim
to a belief bias of any kind,
that's when you start forcing
the pieces together.
Even when they don't fit at all.
Judith...
she seemed average.
She's in her early 40s.
Can't say there's anything particularly
remarkable about her appearance.
She was kind of the type of person that you
would pass by on the street in any town.
You might say hello, smile,
but that's about it.
You would have no idea
that Judith was what she was.
I was older than her by seven years.
She was a silly kid.
And we had a lot of fun.
There was one day, she was around 35,
she slipped on a patch of ice
on the sidewalk
and hurt her back pretty badly.
And after that,
she had a little trouble moving,
and getting around.
And her pain was consistent.
It was chronic.
It was enough
that my husband and I decided
that she shouldn't be
living alone anymore.
So she moved in with us and the kids.
About a year after Judith moved in,
she began to withdraw.
I mean, she would stay
in her room for days.
I'm not sure she would even eat.
I don't know what she did
when she was alone.
She was reading some very unusual books.
And that's when it all started.
And I knew things weren't right.
There were things...
there were things that I saw her do
that I just...
I had to do something.
And to this day, part of me still regrets
doing what I did, but I had to.
But Dr. West was intrigued with Judith
almost immediately. We all were.
By this point, we'd researched
hundreds of cases,
brought in almost as many
subjects into the lab.
Judith was different, though.
We just had no idea
how different at this point.
Can you tell us your name, please?
- Judith Winstead.
- And what's your date of birth, Judith?
February 18th, 1935.
And your marital status?
- I'm not married.
- Have you ever been?
Okay. How many siblings do you have?
- One.
- Are your parents still alive?
- Judith, are your parents still alive?
- No.
Okay. Are you right-handed
or left-handed?
Judith's behavior was always odd.
Even from the first day she arrived.
But in our field, it wasn't uncommon
to encounter odd people.
So we didn't give it much thought.
Ms. Winstead?
Right-handed.
And when did you first realize
you had certain abilities?
Are you... are you all right, dear?
You're bleeding.
Oh, my God.
- Here's some...
- Give her some towels.
Oh, tilt your head back, okay?
It's not her nose, it's her hand.
Her hand is bleeding.
What? Did you... did you bite yourself?
Why?
Susan, let's get her...
get her to the ladies' room, please.
As long as you're okay with it.
- That's all right. Just take...
- Just take care of her.
Judith?
What is she... no, no, no.
What is she doing? Stop.
- Just stop. Calm down.
- Let go.
Ms. Winstead. Judith, stop, please.
Well, for starters,
Judith came to us in an unusual way.
Most times, we learn of someone
and seek them out.
We had no idea Judith
was even out there.
Nevertheless, she tested beyond
what any of us thought was even possible.
There was no measure.
Truly no measure for her abilities.
If you can, try for seven this time.
Any combination.
Three and four.
One and six.
Two and five.
Judith, what I'd like you to try to do
is to move the wheel
without actually touching it.
Try to concentrate your mind.
Focus your thoughts.
She outperformed every subject
we'd ever studied.
There was no comparison to be made.
I understand how peculiar it might seem
to hear her abilities described in this way,
but they were godlike.
Okay, Judith, what do you see this time?
- Judith?
- Star.
- And this time.
- Square.
And what do you see this time?
Judith, are you all right?
Are you all right, Judith? Do you...
can we continue with the exercise?
- I think she's...
- Judith?
I think she's okay. All right,
let's resume. Judith, what...
- The card bent.
- What?
- That card bent. We're taking a break.
- What do you mean?
Dr. West?
Looking back, I...
I guess I should've known better.
I mean, yes, we'd seen...
witnessed amazing things in the past.
But nothing like that.
Nothing, nothing like that.
Inverse square law.
Conservation of momentum.
These were well-established laws
of physics that were being violated.
The second law of thermodynamics.
All of these.
We should've been scared.
Someone with that much power would...
but we were too excited to be scared.
We finally had the proof...
not another hoax...
that we'd been seeking for years.
We had our Nina Kulagina.
What I remember, she was due to...
stay overnight in the lab
through the weekend.
We did this quite often with subjects
because anomalous events
sometimes occur
during the deep-sleep cycle.
And we monitored the subjects through
the night using various recording devices.
During Judith's first overnight, we only had
one staff member present. Kenneth.
I don't ever think I knew his last name.
He was a graduate student
at the time. Nice, quiet kid.
Came from a farming family.
I remember that because so do I.
He was...
he was alone with Judith that night
sitting not far from her bed.
I don't even think he knew
that he was being recorded
because you can see him smoking which
he wasn't supposed to be doing in the lab.
Nothing happened for hours.
Nobody ever found out what happened.
But whatever did...
that was it for him.
Never came back.
We tried contacting
Judith's sister, Margaret.
We couldn't reach her.
She'd disconnected her phone.
It became clear at that moment...
that Margaret had abandoned her.
The decision now was
what we were gonna do.
I could tell that Lawrence was already
reaching a bit of a breaking point.
It was obvious.
It wasn't so obvious with Dr. West.
Not to me anyway.
We simply made the decision that we were
going to continue our testing with her.
But after that night,
it became extremely difficult.
It was so unnerving.
Her behavior. It was so incredibly...
She... she would say things
and do things that made you...
She would scream in that voice.
Grab her!
It wasn't hers.
It was like an animal.
Henry seemed most affected by it.
He tried his best to shield
the others from that.
I knew him well enough to know that
he was deeply affected.
I watched my father change firsthand.
And I have no doubt whatsoever
that what happened in that lab
caused that change.
I remember being
in the seventh grade years later,
and other kids making fun of me.
Call him crazy. They'd say I'd be crazy.
Back then, it was different
than it is now.
Now everyone has a therapist.
They go for anything...
stubbed toe. But back then,
you went if it was something bad.
And especially if medication
was involved.
And in my husband's case, it was.
- Why do you say that, Henry?
- You don't understand.
Okay.
- I see what's happening.
- At work?
I can't help you if you don't tell me
- what you think is happening.
- I can't tell you.
What are you so afraid of, Henry?
I know it's very trying,
but we would really like to continue.
- Can you please stop that, Judith?
- Can you please stop that, please?
We'd really like to continue...
We had about 10 different
degrees between us.
Including one in medicine,
three in psychology.
And we knew...
that was not normal.
Judith was not a typical test subject.
She had made that
abundantly clear by that point.
And I felt we needed help.
I received a file from another analyst.
It was something he thought
I should take a look at.
We started a program
to investigate psi in the early '70s.
Psi-related phenomenon. About five years
after KGB conducted similar studies.
I didn't have the highest
expectations going in.
I felt we'd already been down that road.
And it proved to be a waste
of time and money.
But Marcus was a friend
of a friend, and so I went.
It's difficult to explain.
But you could feel something...
a weight, an invisible weight.
The whole lab took on that feeling
the minute he stepped through the door.
It was if he represented a challenge
to her, to her power.
Everything we had seen
up until that point,
everything Judith had done,
everything we'd witnessed,
it barely compared
to what happened after he arrived.
I assumed they'd run through
the usual battery of psi tests.
The cards, the elaborate devices
with the numbers, but they didn't.
They told me that those tests
weren't right for her.
This here's a way to convince anyone.
Easiest and simplest way
to begin the demonstration.
Now you understand
why we've called you in here.
That can't be accounted for
through any known rational explanation.
And she's able to repeat it
with a variety of different materials.
Breaking the third law
of thermal dynamics.
By the time the man from the Defense
Intelligence Agency, Robert Koepp, arrived,
we'd given up on our standard
testing procedure.
Well, we'd simply talked to her.
It was so difficult.
She knew...
too much.
Think of any object.
- Something in the room?
- No, it doesn't have to be.
No, let's make it something
not in the room.
- Okay.
Draw what you see, please.
- And what object were you thinking of?
- A hammer.
- Excuse me.
- Susan?
- Susan.
- Henry, she...
You don't frighten me!
- You don't fucking know!
- Susan! Stop it!
- What are you doing?!
- Marcus!
- Susan, calm down.
- How dare you?!
- You don't know anything!
- Take her outside, please.
Just take her outside.
She had drawn a shamrock.
Back in 1973, three years earlier,
I had traveled back to London
for my mum's funeral.
I was devastated.
Her family had immigrated
to London from Ireland
and she was very proud
of her Irish heritage.
And in her casket, she had worn
the same brooch that she'd worn
almost every day of her life.
It was a shamrock.
As soon as I saw that picture,
I realized what Judith
had whispered to me.
"You weren't there."
Which is true, I wasn't.
My mother died the day
before I made it home.
And that woman...
that thing somehow knew that.
And how much guilt.
She wanted me to behave that way.
She wanted me to react that way.
To humiliate me in front of my peers
by turning me into everything
I had tried so hard not to be.
Well, the incident with Susan
was very unsettling
because it demonstrated
Judith's ability to influence us.
She was definitely influencing Henry.
He started to pull back.
Which was unlike him.
I thought he was gonna fight
the government's involvement,
but that didn't happen.
He withdrew and they took over.
My arm!
Use the strap right there.
Please, step back.
You're gonna break her arm.
- Please, step back.
- What are you giving her?
Tell Robert.
Heartbeat's back again. Mark it.
14 minutes and 27 seconds.
- Any physical deterioration?
- Nothing. Jesus.
She's pissing again. Get the towels.
It's over there. Get it.
- No.
- That's good. Thank you.
Step back.
Check her! Make sure she's all right!
Not that, that.
Once they witnessed
the things we'd all seen,
it became a very different scenario.
It didn't matter what my preconceived
notions were before visiting the institute.
What mattered now was national security.
We left nothing to chance.
All evidence was thoroughly reviewed
by top Defense Department analysts.
Tissue samples were extracted.
Blood samples taken.
Plans were immediately
put in place to contain the situation.
The institute was locked down.
We assumed control of all testing
and information collection.
Strict security protocols
were put in place.
This was a coordinated military effort
with support from the highest levels
of the government.
Soldiers were stationed around the clock
inside the lab, all of them armed.
We were there because we believed it.
Now we wanted to see it.
The camera's ready.
- Lights ready.
- Flashing.
I think he's having a seizure. Henry?
- Get a hand under his head.
- Turn the lights on.
- Keep his mouth open.
- Turn the lights on!
Where is she?
Stop the flashing now!
The DIA report prompted swift action.
We looked at the evidence, we reviewed
the footage of the seizure incident.
Dr. West had no history of epilepsy
or any related condition,
so it's highly unlikely that the flashing
lights could've triggered it.
We could not say definitively that
Ms. Winstead caused the seizure,
but we certainly couldn't
rule it out either.
Several meetings were held to discuss
the seriousness of this threat.
I can't speak to the specifics
of what was discussed,
but suffice it to say
if you're gonna inform the White House
of something as crazy as this,
you better be damn sure it's true.
All psychological and pharmacological
explanations were ruled out.
Her blood samples came back
with impossibly high electrolyte levels.
A completely unknown molecular compound
was found in her tissue.
Something was inside her.
No doubt about that.
Not a disease.
Not a parasite.
An evil.
Do you think you know
what caused the seizure?
- Henry?
- Yes.
- Are you taking the new medication?
- It has nothing to do with that.
- Henry, it is important that you keep...
- I am taking it.
I'm seeing things at night.
I can't stop thinking about everything.
I try, but...
And even when I'm with
my family, I feel it.
I'm afraid.
I'm afraid of what might happen to them.
But, yes, I am taking
the new medication.
The story was that when the KGB
learned about Nina Kulagina's ability,
they performed a test with a living frog.
This was back in 1970.
The Soviets wanted to see
if Nina could telekinetically affect
the bioelectrical impulses
in living tissue.
To speed up and slow down its heartbeat.
And allegedly, she did.
So our government wanted to see if they
could replicate those results with Judith.
Good God.
Jesus.
- Why's he barking?
- It's her. She's still doing it.
She's doing it to the dog. No, her!
Turn on the lights! Turn on the lights!
Where is she?
Secure this room now. Right now!
- Quiet. Quiet.
- Turn on the lights!
Quiet! Everyone, quiet.
Don't move.
- Robert, what's happening?
- Take it down.
Quiet. Quiet.
Marcus.
- Nobody move. Nobody move.
- Who's touching me?
Turn on the light!
Turn on the light now.
- Turn it on.
- Turn that light back on.
Grab her!
Imagine being 22, 23 years old,
best shape of your life,
armed to the teeth.
And you scared of some lady looked like
she could've been
your primary school teacher.
That's what was going on then.
You understand?
Things took a significant
turn after that.
I think in total, there were...
six or seven unexplainable
incidents that occurred.
All outside the institute.
One of the government researcher's
cousins almost died in a car wreck.
There was... a soldier's father
was attacked by a dog.
There was a house fire,
if I remember correctly.
And on and on it went.
Now, each of these things
on their own could be a coincidence,
but the likelihood that all of them
would happen together
to the family and friends of this same group
of people in the same span of time
is astonishingly low.
My son Jeffrey started
waking up night after night
screaming with night terrors.
My wife and I found out that
that was common among toddlers.
I don't know.
I don't know if it is or not.
It was... it was so eerie.
I just...
I was starting to think that maybe
my work was following me home.
I felt bad for Sarge.
His father got bit up
real bad by some stray.
Pit bull, I think.
And let me tell ya,
she knew.
The day after that,
she kept staring at him.
He hadn't told any one of us.
Nobody knew for about another week.
But she knew.
The whole time, she knew.
It was late one night in the lab.
And I happened to notice
a paper clip on the floor
inside the air lock portion
of Judith's enclosure.
Now, that environment was meticulously kept.
It was nearly sterile.
So there was no explaining
how it got there.
Anyway...
I picked it up, I stuffed it in my pocket
and didn't give it another thought.
We were at my sister's house
for my nephew's birthday.
My wife and I never had kids,
so Matthew was very dear to us.
And I remember reaching for my keys
and thinking I heard something
fall onto the ground
from my pocket.
It was the paper clip.
Burt, knock it off.
- Claire, it's Matt!
- What?!
Matthew!
Oh, my God!
Matthew? Matthew?
- Oh, my God! Sweetheart!
- He's not breathing!
He'd stuck it in a wall socket.
I could've worn any other pants that day,
but I wore those.
And that paper clip just happened
to be what he found?
Out of all the things in the world,
a balled-up receipt, a stick of bubble gum...
that's what happened to fall out
of my pocket at that moment?
Not at any point
in the five days before that?
Not... not anywhere else?
Not in... not in the hamper?
In the washing machine?
In the dryer? There?
On his birthday?
And the way the dog was barking,
it was... it was... it was like...
What happened...
was no accident.
That was it. I'd had enough.
It was 10 years until I heard
from Lawrence again.
He and his wife moved out of the country
shortly after it happened.
I was surprised he didn't leave
the institute sooner than he did.
It was a shame
what happened to his nephew.
I don't think Lawrence
ever really forgave himself.
Well, we couldn't discount the events
that happened outside the institute.
Too much happened
for it to be coincidence.
But what it did do is make us
rethink our strategy.
What are we gonna use to immobilize her?
Fentanyl.
The gas derivative of it should
knock her out in seconds.
It could also kill her.
- Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey. No, no, no.
- Hey. You can't keep her in there.
- Now's not the time for compassion.
- She's a human being.
There are laws against
that sort of treatment for a reason.
Who do you think makes those laws?
- This is my lab.
- No, not anymore it's not.
I have sat back and kept quiet...
- while I've seen you...
- And you'd do well to stay quiet.
Get him outta here.
I never should've called you people.
Hold on.
You really think
you're equipped to handle this?
Your little lab here with your flash cards
and ESP machines?
See it...
but then it's gone.
Now it comes back. You can...
see that in the rest of the pictures.
For those few moments...
it wasn't in the room.
Might not even been in the building.
Do you understand what I'm telling you?
We don't control this,
it's not just us who will be at risk.
And if you do control it,
then who will be at risk?
We recognized the danger of allowing it
to remain even remotely unrestricted.
It was immensely powerful.
And rather than continually
try to explain it,
the decision was made
to attempt to harness it.
Repeat the following:
one, two, three, four, five.
Your instructions are clear.
Repeat the following:
one, two, three, four, five.
You will cooperate.
Now,
this is a map divided into a grid
consisting of five sections.
One, two, three, four, five.
I want you to listen carefully
and concentrate.
There are artillery and biological
weapons being stored
somewhere in this region.
Look at the grid
and tell me the number of where.
Tell me where they're being stored.
You will cooperate. Put it away.
Part of me...
will always feel responsible.
Because it was my idea
to notify the military.
I don't know what we would've
done otherwise. But...
I do wonder if Henry
might still be alive today if...
I had settled on a more...
reasonable solution.
Sergeant.
Do you hear me?
Ms. Winstead,
your instructions are to make
Sergeant Parella say exactly the following:
reposition all nuclear submarines
out of the Baltic Sea.
Once again,
reposition all nuclear submarines
out of the Baltic Sea.
Your instructions are clear.
- How many eyes does a fish have?
- Turn up his volume.
How many ears does a gopher have?
How many noses does a monkey have?
How many arms does a whale have?
How many hoofs does a horse have?
- How many noses does a monkey have?
- Dr. West?
- How many stripes does a zebra have?
- Dr. West.
How many eyes does a fish have?
How many ears does an elephant have?
How many stripes does a zebra have?
How many eyes does a fish have?
- How many eyes does a fish have?
- Henry.
- How many noses does a monkey have?
- Dr. West.
How many noses does a monkey have?
How many noses...
You can't control something like that.
I don't care who you are,
how many weapons you have.
All those things that went on...
you don't get to play games
with the Devil.
And if you do, you damn sure
don't get to make the rules.
That type of evil...
just thinking about it,
talking about it.
Even you people making this movie...
and the people watching it...
you're inviting
bad things into your life.
Too late for me.
All the things I've seen.
This wasn't like the books or the movies
or false accounts you hear about.
If those cases were legitimate,
I can assure you, we would've intervened.
This is real.
There was no speculative data.
There was no charlatans
looking to make a buck.
This was the only governmentally
confirmed case of possession.
Arguably the most significant thing we learned
was that it had an intelligence.
That meant that it was able to conduct
some form of cost-benefit analysis.
Our plan was to utilize
its ability to reason
as a stopgap measure to clear
a psychological pathway.
So they essentially offered it a choice
between cooperating or suffering.
But it was a false choice
because both options
caused Judith to suffer.
Their belief was that if they
could control her physical body,
chiefly her mind,
they could control
how the force manifested.
Possess the possession
is what they would say.
As if it was gonna work that way.
Clear, go again.
They pushed that poor woman
to her limits.
Judith Winstead, the person.
I felt... terrible for her.
But there was nothing
we could do to help her.
Please, stop.
We were eventually able to devise
a method of governing the force.
Once we controlled her,
we could effectively control it.
Once that happened,
the nature of our involvement
changed dramatically.
It was...
shocking.
But it wasn't at the same time.
We knew something was coming.
I mean, a few nights before that, I...
found him curled up in a ball
under the bathroom sink.
Talking to himself.
Crying.
I mean, he was scared to death.
Henry was nearing the end of his rope.
After a while, he rarely even
set foot in the lab.
He would lock himself in the office
for hours at a time.
Sometimes you could hear him
muttering from behind the door.
Things were reaching a tipping point.
I do. I do believe that it drove
Dr. West to that.
Trust me. We did a complete
background check. We knew everything.
We knew about the therapy,
the medication.
What happened was not
a product of psychosis.
Maybe you should take
some time away from work.
Henry? Maybe take some time off?
It doesn't matter where I am.
It's everywhere.
It's like a shadow.
Except it's not mine.
So you feel like it's following you,
the shadow.
I feel like it's already caught me.
To be totally honest, Henry,
I find a lot of this very troubling.
Is that why you're using that?
- Yeah, we always record the sessions.
- Not on a camera.
Well, I... things seem different.
- Did they make you do this?
- Did who?
- Is this to make sure I don't say anything?
- I don't know what you're talking about.
They're pushing it too far. They want
to control everything, but they can't.
It's too powerful. It's too strong.
Take it easy, Henry.
I'm trying to make you understand.
There's something happening.
- To you?
- Yes.
To me, then maybe to you,
then maybe to them.
Whoever it chooses.
There's no science left in the world
for this, but they think there is.
It doesn't even matter anymore
what I say.
It's gonna speak for itself.
So use your goddamn camera.
Write my name.
Write my words across the sky.
I don't give a damn because if it...
if they keep pushing it
the way they are...
Nod if you can hear me.
Good.
What I want you to do now is focus
on the person on the television.
Nod if you understand.
I want you to tell me his name.
Your instructions are clear.
Tell me the name of the person
you see on the television.
Alan.
Turcott.
Next, I want you to tell me
his current location.
Hanscom.
Office. Military office.
Let's get them on the phone.
- Tell them we're gonna try it out.
- We're gonna try it out.
They're ready.
Listen very carefully
to what I'm gonna tell you.
What I want you to do now is attempt
to influence Private Turcott's breathing.
Begin.
Your instructions are clear.
- Tell her to stop it.
- Stop it.
- Tell her to stop!
- Stop.
I said stop!
Hit her!
We eventually figured out
what was going on.
And we felt so foolish
for not having recognized
that that was the government's
intention from the beginning.
To weaponize her.
Having the ability
to remotely collect intel.
To be able to read
the minds of foreign leaders
to know exactly
what their plan of attack is.
Where they were and what they were
thinking at any given moment.
And, if necessary,
be able to collapse their lungs
and stop their hearts.
All from thousands of miles away.
We were looking at the future
of clandestine warfare.
Where attacks could be as strategic
and as untraceable as we saw fit.
The rigors of their testing protocol
increased enormously.
The more they pushed,
the more defiant she became.
Well, it became.
We treated her like the discovery
of any new destructive force.
Much of what we did mirrored
the testing procedures
used in the early atomic testing.
We needed to understand this power
if we were intent on utilizing it.
What are you?
How do you choose your host?
Now.
Tell me your name.
They were getting very frustrated
because everything she said
sounded like gibberish.
They kept shocking her.
When she didn't give them the answer
they wanted, they'd shock her again.
They'd up the voltage
and shock her again.
Our analysts were eventually
able to isolate
certain elements of Judith's speech.
Turned out she hadn't been
speaking gibberish at all.
What are you?
How do you choose your host?
This will all be over soon.
It just proved that she was
in control the entire time.
Just drawing us in.
Drawing us in closer.
And instead of stopping like we all knew
we should, we kept going.
We were too close to something
truly revolutionary to stop.
It was affecting everyone, but that's
the nature of any struggle, any battle.
Push and you will be resisted.
That's why you want to be
the one pushing the hardest.
You would hear them discussing new ideas
and strategies, disruption techniques,
but nobody would talk
about what was obvious.
That there are certain things in this world
that we will never understand.
And Judith Winstead was one of them.
It was acutely averse to all things
related to religion.
Even more than it was to electroshock.
And that poor priest...
he was just a pawn.
We were very much against
involving the Church.
We didn't want to turn this
into a sideshow.
At the same time,
we had to gain control somehow.
This one, too.
Thumbprint on that one as well.
- Do you understand everything?
- I do, yes.
Into the camera, please.
I understand.
Okay.
Do you have any questions?
No.
Good.
That last night in the lab was...
it was crazy.
They told us to double up
on our ammo just to stay safe.
There was a big buildup. Everyone was
mentally preparing for what might happen.
We needed to get it out of the lab
and we couldn't do that with a civilian.
We had to transfer it
into one of our own.
When I arrived at the lab that night
and found out what was going to happen...
I froze.
I wanted to scream for them
not to try that.
But I didn't say a word.
I wanted to get out of there real bad.
I remember, I wanted
to sneak out the back door
when nobody was looking and just go.
And of course I couldn't.
I should've.
- Go ahead.
- Copy that.
Get ready, Corporal.
Hey, hey, hey.
Stop the transfer.
The power of the blood
of Jesus commands you!
Bow to the Lord!
Get him out of there.
- Hit the gas. Hit the gas.
- Help! Help!
Pull him out!
Pull him out. Make sure he's okay.
Are you okay?
- I'm gonna clear it.
- No. No, no, no. Hold on.
- Did it work? Did it work?
- I... I don't know.
Give her a quick charge.
She's still out.
No, no. The electrodes
got disconnected. See?
Shit.
- Are you positive she's unconscious?
- No.
- Can we gas her again?
- It might be too much.
Well, I'm not going in there
unless I know she's completely...
- Then don't go in there.
- If we don't get those electrodes...
- Are you crazy?
- We've got nothing if it's dead.
- Hit her again! Now!
- I'm not gonna hit her again.
- Hit her again!
- Don't...
Robert, don't.
Bilateral?
Bi-frontal.
What are you doing? What are you doing?
You need to step back.
I'm gonna check him.
I'm gonna check his pulse.
- That's it?
- That's all.
Let's start clearing again...
Get him outta here. Let's go.
Come on. Let's go.
The situation was a disaster
in all possible ways.
Local law enforcement
got involved, the media.
They all wanted to know
what happened, naturally.
They had a right to the story.
Just not to all of it.
I'm still not at liberty to discuss
much more than I have.
Especially as it pertains to the events
that took place after that night.
But I can tell you this...
the measures taken were done with the best
interests of this country in mind.
It wasn't until fairly recently
that I found out
what happened to my sister.
And as horrible as it probably sounds,
I preferred it that way.
She was a good person. She was.
But people change.
Even good people.
I know that the official story
was that he was crazy.
He was a mad scientist
who had finally lost
the last of his widely
scattered marbles.
But believe me when I tell you,
Henry West was not crazy.
Which I suppose...
leaves us
with the alternate explanation.
What is this?
Please, help.
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today