Encoded by Judas
Enjoy!
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
AEREON: They are an army
unlike any other.
Crusading across the stars
toward a place called
UnderVerse,
their promised land.
A constellation
of dark new worlds.
Necromongers they're called.
And if they
cannot convert you,
they will kill you.
Leading them,
the Lord Marshal.
He alone has made
a pilgrimage to the
gates of the UnderVerse
and returned
a different being.
Stronger. Stranger.
Half alive and half
something else.
lf we are to survive,
a new balance must be found.
ln normal times, evil
would be fought by good.
But in times like these,
well, it should be fought
by another kind of evil.
Lining him up for you.
Portside shot coming up.
TOOMBS: Steady. Here we go.
Steady.
Take it! Take a shot!
Shit.
Toombs,
we're running out of rope!
Shut up! I got it! Again !
Now!
HENCHMAN: Toombs!
Riddick.
GUNNER 1 : l don't know,
Toombs. Looks kind of tight.
Not where I'm sitting.
This is the biggest
payday ever.
So throw on a fresh
pair of panties.
Let's get this right.
HENCHMAN: Three meters
clearance portside. One
and a half meters starboard.
We got a chokepoint coming up.
HENCHMAN: What the shit
was that?
Tags, you got eyes on Riddick?
Tags?
Jesus.
He just ghosted two guys,
and l never even saw him.
What do you think?
Maybe we ought to just. . .
l think you're my new gunner.
Grab a Gat.
Stay on top of him this time.
RlDDlCK: You made
three mistakes.
First, you took the job.
Second, you came light.
A four-man crew for me?
Fucking insulting.
But the worst mistake
you made. . .
RlDDlCK: Empty gun rack.
What's the bounty on my head?
1 mil.
1 .5.
What slam pays
1 .5 for a convict?
Private party.
Guy! Easy! Anonymous.
That's what the sheet said.
What planet?
Helion Prime.
Whoa. Where you going?
Last question.
And you better get this one
right, merc.
Whose ship is this?
Mine?
RlDDlCK: Knew
they'd come for me.
Took them five years,
but l knew.
You don't expect these mercs
to have any honor, any code.
But this new bounty
from a holy man,
a guy whose neck l saved.
Well, lesson learned.
No such word as "friend."
Can only end bad when you
let someone get too close.
Bad for them.
So now it's back
to all the brightness,
and everything l hate.
l wonder if she'll be there.
Act like an animal
and l'm gonna slot
you up like one.
This one is always
in trouble.
l knew it. l smell it.
Get in there!
Can we shut the goddamn noise?
RlDDlCK: They say most of your
brain shuts down in cryosleep.
SHlRAH: Brain shuts down
in cryosleep.
All but the primitive side.
The animal side.
SHlRAH: All but the Furyan
side.
Some of us still remember
the true crime
that happened here on Furya.
And once you wake,
truly wake,
you'll remember, too.
WOMAN PlLOT: Helion
Prime is on alert condition
four.
All unrecognized craft
will be escorted
to the ground
for security inspections.
PlLOT: Unrecognized craft,
follow me to Spaceport 6
for security inspections.
Do you hear me?
Follow me to
Spaceport 6 now!
WOMAN: lmam, pray for us.
WOMAN 1 : lt was confirmed
two seasons back. Yes.
WOMAN 2: They're coming here.
Are we next?
MAN 1 : Militants storm.
WOMAN 3: We're going
to the underground
shelters if it happens.
MAN 2: That's what l heard,
too.
MAN 3: Are you staying
or leaving?
MAN 4: lt's the end
of everything. Everything !
MAN 5: My neighbors. . .
MAN 6: Half my street is gone.
What are we gonna do?
l don't know.
WOMAN 4: Hood of the devil,
they called them.
WOMAN 5: Who is them?
WOMAN 4: A new creature.
MAN 7: lt's all nonsense.
Everyone is over-reacting.
MAN 8: . . .so tall
that it touches the clouds.
And there's nothing around
this statue, this colossus.
Nothing left.
lt's their calling card.
RlDDlCK: Did you know
all your doors were locked?
Five years ago,
l took two people
off that planet.
A kid, Jack,
who everyone else
thought was a boy
and a holy man
searching for New Mecca.
Your wife.
She's in the shower.
l told one man
where l might go.
l showed trust to one man.
Did l make a mistake, lmam?
There is no simple answer. . .
Whatever was said was
meant to give us a chance.
A fighting chance.
Were it not for the threat
of invasion
l never would
have betrayed you.
l give you my word, Riddick.
Riddick!
Riddick.
RlDDlCK: And a daughter. . .
LAJJUN: No.
RlDDlCK: . . .whose name
would be. . .
lf you have issue with me,
you let it be with me.
You need not know their names.
Ziza. My name is Ziza.
Ziza.
Cute kid.
ZlZA: Did you really
kill monsters?
The ones that were gonna
hurt my father?
Such are our bedtime stories.
Go, Ziza. Go on.
So now who do
l have to kill to get
this payday off my head?
lMAM: lt is said the comet
always precedes them.
These world-enders.
The Coalsack planets are gone.
Eight million settlers
missing.
The entire Aquilan System
is gone, too.
Helion Prime
shares its sunlight
with all worlds nearby.
lf we fall, they fall.
And after that. . .
My God,
how do l save my family?
Have you heard
anything l've said?
You said it's all circling
the drain. The whole universe.
Right?
That's right.
Had to end sometime.
The one you want is now here.
And whose throat is this?
lf you cut my throat,
l'll not be able
to rescind the offer
that brought you here.
Nor tell you
why it's so vital
that you did come.
The blade comes off
when the bounty comes off.
This is Aereon. An envoy
from the Elemental race.
She means you no harm.
There are very few of us
who have met a Necromonger
and lived to speak of it.
So when
l choose to speak of it,
you should choose to listen.
Necromonger.
lt is the name
that will convert or kill
every last human life.
Unless the universe
can rebalance itself.
Maybe
you should pretend
like you're talking to
someone educated
in the penal system.
ln fact, don't pretend.
Balance is everything
to Elementals.
Water to fire. Earth to air.
We have 33 different words
for it.
But now we have only time
to speak of the balance
of opposites.
lMAM: There is a story,
Riddick, of young male
Furyans
strangled at birth.
Strangled with their
own cords.
When Aereon told this story
to the Helion leaders,
l told her of you.
What do you know
of your early years?
Do you remember
your homeworld?
Where it was?
Have you met any others?
Others like yourself.
Sister,
they don't know what
to do with just one of me.
SOLDlER 1 : Open up in there!
Open up!
SOLDlER 2: Stand back!
LAJJUN: They are searching
houses.
They look for a man
who came here today.
They think he might be a spy.
A spy.
Did someone see him
come here today? Did they?
Lajjun, stop!
l will send them away.
But wait one minute,
please.
Will you wait
one minute to
save worlds?
Not my fight.
So you will leave us
to our fate?
Just like you did her.
SOLDlER 1 : Break it down !
SOLDlER 1 : Get in !
Come, let us try
to send them away.
LAJJUN: Let me have her!
SOLDlER 1 : Come on.
CLERlC: Leave us alone.
LAJJUN: There is no one here.
CLERlC: You don't understand.
He can help us!
You're not afraid
of the dark, are you?
SOLDlER 1 : Get him !
SOLDlER 2: Where is he?
SOLDlER 3: ln here.
You mentioned her.
She. . .
She went looking for you.
People died.
She went to prison.
l don't remember where.
But it was a world
so hot, you couldn't
survive on the surface.
Crematoria.
Young Jack. She thought
of you as her older brother.
She worshipped you.
You were supposed
to watch her.
She never forgave you
for leaving
just when she
needed you most.
She needed to
stay away from me.
You all do.
ZlZA: Riddick.
Are you gonna stop
the new monsters now?
AEREON: Furyans.
Defiant to the end.
No, no.
We go to the shelter.
We take only ourselves.
OFFlClAL: Turn back!
Go to the other shelter.
MAN: There is no room.
WOMAN: They won't let us in !
OFFlClAL: Get back.
lMAM: Stay close.
CONTROLLER: Flight leaders,
all squads off the ground
now.
We have heavy inbound.
Follow me in!
They're coming back!
lMAM: The next shelter.
This way!
lMAM: l'll see if it's safe.
lMAM: Stay back.
LAJJUN: Come, Ziza.
Come!
You following me?
lMAM: Lajjun and Ziza!
When it's over.
Let me go.
l must go to my family.
When it's over.
l borrowed a ship.
You can ride along
if you don't mind
riding with a convict.
l thank you,
but l must get my
family across the river.
God willing, there is still
a shelter l can get them. . .
l'm sure God
has his tricks.
But getting out of
places no one else can,
that's one of mine.
Let's get your family.
ln here.
lMAM: Get in.
LAJJUN: lmam.
Don't follow me.
There will be an afterlife
for me.
Will there be for you?
Let's go replenish the ranks.
Never fails
to inspire, does it?
Each time a dynasty falls.
Remember your place,
Dame Vaako.
My place is at your side,
dear husband.
From here
till UnderVerse come.
ln this 'verse,
life is antagonistic
to the natural state.
Here, humans in all
their various races
are a spontaneous outbreak,
an unguided mistake.
Our purpose is to
correct that mistake.
Because there
is another 'verse.
A 'verse where life
is welcomed and cherished.
A ravishing,
ever-new place
called UnderVerse.
But the road to that 'verse
crosses over the threshold.
NECROMONGERS: Threshold !
Take us to the threshold !
What you call death.
PURlFlER: So it is
this 'verse that must
be cleansed of life
so that UnderVerse
can populate and prosper.
Look around you.
Every Necromonger
in this hall,
every one
of the Legion Vast
that just swept aside
your defenses in one night
was once like you.
Fought as feebly as you.
Every Necromonger that
lives today is a convert.
There'll be no conversions!
We all began
as something else!
lt was hard for me to accept,
too, when l first heard
these words.
But l changed.
l let them take away my pain.
You betrayed your faith.
Just as you will change
when you realize
that the threshold to the
UnderVerse will be crossed
only by those
who have embraced
the Necromonger faith.
For those of you
who will right now
drop to your knees
and ask to be purified.
We will not renounce
our faith !
No one here will
do what you ask.
lt is unthinkable!
This is a world
of many peoples,
many religions!
And we simply cannot
and will not be converted.
MARSHAL: Then l'll take
your soul.
MARSHAL: Join him
or join me.
This is your one chance.
Take the Lord Marshal's offer
and bow.
l bow to no man.
He's not a man.
He's the holy Half-Dead
who has seen the UnderVerse.
Look,
l'm not with everyone here.
But l will take
a piece of him.
A piece you will have.
MARSHAL: Stop him !
lrgun. One of my best.
lf you say so.
What do you think
of this blade?
l think
it's a half-gram
heavy on the back end.
ln our faith,
you keep what you kill.
Are you familiar to me?
Have we met
on some distant field?
You'd think l'd remember.
You'd think l would, too.
Take him before
the Quasi-Deads.
Perhaps the breeder
would do it
if somebody just asked him.
lt is a rare offer.
A visit inside Necropolis.
lt's been a long time
since l smelled beautiful.
Let me show you the way.
Beautiful eyes. Come.
The last
six Lord Marshals
have called this home.
Magnificent, isn't it?
l might have
gone a different way.
True of us all.
Converts receiving the mark
of the Necromonger.
They learn how one pain
can lessen another.
There now.
That is just perfect.
The more you resist them
the greater the damage
will be.
QUASl-DEADS: A new one.
You've brought us a new one.
lnteresting breeder.
QUASl-DEADS: Making entry.
This won't take long.
We've entered his neocortex.
QUASl-DEADS: The Riddick!
Regress.
Scanning fresh memories.
Thoughts of someone
called Jack.
Riddick!
lMAM: She went to prison.
QUASl-DEADS: Now we find
thoughts of an Elemental.
The one race
that would slow the
spread of Necromongers.
lMAM: Furyans.
QUASl-DEADS: Furyans.
Where does he come from?
Who are his people?
These are the things
l need to know.
QUASl-DEADS: We find energy.
SHlRAH: You must settle
your past.
QUASl-DEADS: We find
Furyan energy.
For all of us.
QUASl-DEADS: He's Furyan!
Furyan!
A Furyan survivor!
SHlRAH: Look at our world,
at the graves
of those who didn't
escape 30 years ago.
There is no future
until we settle our past.
For all of us
who bear the mark.
QUASl-DEADS:
Kill the Furyan!
Kill the Riddick!
Kill the Riddick.
Who is this man?
Find him. Whatever it takes.
Find him.
Let me guess.
A five-man crew this time.
TOOMBS: Couple of things
you could have done better.
First, trash the locater
beacon inside my ship,
the one you jacked.
And second,
and this is really
the more important part,
dust my dick
when you get the chance.
Any questions?
Yeah.
What took you so long?
Let's go, big boy.
ln and out.
Unsuspected and undetected.
Damn, l love a good
smash-and-grab!
Not so fast, dickheads.
We're picking up fields here.
ELECTRONlC VOlCE: Unknown
fields detected on hull.
l knew it. Here it comes.
This is some kind of scan.
l don't know.
Reading our BTUs, maybe?
Let's drop one.
Dropping.
ELECTRONlC VOlCE:
Decoy launched.
Preparing to engage
ion drive.
So where do we drop
your merc-killing ass?
Who's gonna pay the most
for you now? Butcher Bay?
Butcher Bay.
Ten minutes every other day
on the dog-run.
Protein waffles aren't bad.
How about Ursa Luna?
Nice little double-max prison.
They keep
a cell open for me,
just in case l drop in.
You know the problem
with these joints now?
Health clubs for
waffle-eating pussies.
Maybe we should think
about upping our game
here a little bit.
Think about someplace
truly diabolical.
What the hell
is he thinking now?
RlDDlCK: He's thinking
a triple-max prison.
A no-daylight slam.
Only three of them
left in this system,
two of them out of range
for a shitty
little undercutter
like this one with no legs.
Leaving just one.
Crematoria.
That is what you had in mind,
right, Toombs?
How does he know
where we're going,
and we don't?
Dope it out.
l hate this run.
Just do it!
Don't know about
this new crew of yours.
They seem a bit skittish.
Probably
shouldn't tell them what
happened to the last crew.
You know,
you were supposed to
be some slick-shit killer.
Now look at you.
All back-of-the-bus and shit.
SCALES: l say
we attack Helion Two next.
Take it straight
into their teeth.
lt'll cost you 20,000 heads,
5 Warrior Ships, nothing more,
l swear it.
While l do
prize brute force,
this approach is,
perhaps, more artful.
Start at the end.
Go straight to Helion Five,
the last planet in the system.
We approach
from the night side.
Remove these cannon first,
then attack the larger
placements at speed.
We'll catch them
on their rear flank.
And in 1 0 days' time,
the rest of those worlds
will tumble before us.
You see, as with most,
their blind spot is
right behind them.
l've located an ion trail
which leads off-world.
Then you should be off-world,
Vaako.
l've deployed a tracker team.
One of the best.
Wherever Riddick has gone,
you lens him out
and cleanse him. You.
You want me to take
a frigate for one breeder?
Don't question it, Vaako!
Take it on faith.
DAME VAAKO:
He's always been
unsettled around you.
The Lord Marshal.
Unsteady.
Perhaps because he knows
he's half the warrior you are.
Some say he's too
artistic for the job.
l wouldn't be surprised
if someone promoted
him soon
to full dead.
Take care what you say.
Should l say it softly?
So it sounds
more like conspiracy?
Why is it that when anyone
breathes about the demise
of him on the throne
everyone assumes a conspiracy?
Why isn't that
just prudent planning?
When he is ready,
he will name a successor.
Who?
Toal? Scales?
The Purifier?
None of them
with the strength,
the dignity
of Lord Vaako.
You can keep
what you kill.
Stop.
That is the Necromonger way.
l said stop.
His death will come
in due time and not
a moment sooner.
Why?
Because l serve him.
We all serve him.
lt's called fidelity.
lt's called stupidity.
Well, finally,
some attention.
You have such greatness
in you.
lf only you could see it
like l do.
You know what l want?
Today l came up behind him
in perfect silence
and he knew.
l want to go down
to Necropolis.
Right now.
His half-dead soul
sensed l was behind him.
He sees everything.
When no one is looking,
when no one's around,
l'm gonna get down
on my knees
while you sit
on the throne.
MARSHAL: How unexpected. . .
An Elemental. Here?
VAAKO: One of the captives.
And why,
after 30 years,
should it be you?
He doesn't regard her
as a captive, though.
Elementals.
They talk of neutrality,
but they're
all witches and spies.
Why else
would they come
and go like the wind?
MARSHAL: But where
has he gone? Where is
the Furyan hiding now?
You be
the good warrior.
Go after this Riddick.
l'll find out
why the Lord Marshal
is so threatened by him.
Do you know you grind
your teeth at night?
Sexy.
ELECTRONlC VOlCE:
Destination reached.
Unlocking manual controls.
All right, l make 700
degrees on the day side.
300 below on the night side.
PlLOT: Let's not
get caught in the sun.
lf l owned
this place and hell,
l'd rent this place out
and live in hell.
ELECTRONlC VOlCE:
Slue angle: good.
Stand by.
And. . .
Plotted course, good.
Hit it!
Angle of approach:
not good.
Look, Ma, no hands!
Party poppers!
l think l shit myself.
Skittish, Toombs.
Very skittish.
Comfy?
When the ride's over,
your goggles are mine.
Four-way split!
29.4 kilometers.
So this is Riddick.
What in the bowels of Christ
are you talking about?
700,000?
Don't take this one, boss.
See, Anatoli here
has a nose for trouble.
And this one,
this Riddick guy. . .
Big, big trouble.
So 700,000 is good money.
l'd take the money, Toombs.
The guild
pays us a caretaker's fee
for each prisoner each year.
We pay mercs 20%
of that total fee based
on a certain life expectancy.
TOOMBS: How's about this?
You open that
safe you got hidden
behind the console there,
show me the real books.
Then we figure out my cut.
Then l'll be on my way.
Open my books.
This is what you suggest?
Wasn't a suggestion.
BOSS: These are dangerous
days, if you believe the talk.
Talk?
BOSS: About dead planets.
About some ghost army.
About them.
Them?
l'll run the numbers again.
lt takes a couple of days
probably.
So you can stay
as my guest.
At least here we
are all safe. Yes?
GUARD: Yes, boss.
l'll give it a day.
One.
GUV: There are inmates,
and there are convicts.
A convict has a certain code.
And he knows to
show a certain respect.
An inmate,
on the other hand,
pulls the pin
on his fellow man.
Does the guards' work
for them. Brings shame. . .
. . .to the game.
So which are you gonna be?
Me?
l'm just passing through.
Welcome to Crematoria.
Should l go for
the sweet spot?
Left of the spine,
fourth lumbar down
the abdominal aorta.
What a gusher.
How do l get
eyes like that?
You got to
kill a few people.
Did that.
Did a lot of that.
And then you got to
get sent to a slam.
Where you're told you
won't see daylight again?
There wasn't a doctor
who could shine my eyes
not even
for 20 menthol Kools.
Was anything you said true?
What are you gonna do?
Go for the sweet spot?
Remember who you're
talking to, Jack.
Jack's dead.
She was weak.
She couldn't cut it.
The name's Kyra now.
And l'm a new animal.
They can be quite a test.
These deep runs.
Test of our inner selves.
Don't you find that true?
Some men do.
PURlFlER: Just being
so far from the armada,
the mind can start to
fill with strange thoughts.
Doubts.
Don't you ever have doubts,
Vaako?
Doubts?
About the campaign.
About Lord Marshal.
First and always, l am
a Necromonger commander.
So if you're here
to test my loyalty,
you succeed only in
testing my patience.
No, that's not
why l'm here at all.
DAME VAAKO: l'm so glad
l could steal you away
for a moment.
Doesn't it strike you odd?
Here we have the current
Lord Marshal destroying
entire societies
and yet he can't
bring himself to kill
one stranded Elemental.
Why is that?
You don't pray to our God.
You pray to no God, l hear.
Elementals, we calculate.
Don't we all.
But now let's have
first things first.
What of Riddick?
ln truth,
l don't know
where he went.
ln truth,
l'm more interested
in where he came from.
Watch your step.
l've always wondered,
does an air Elemental fly?
Now do me a favor.
Calculate the odds of you
getting off this planet
alive
and now cut them in half.
No, we can't fly.
But we glide very well.
Save your threats,
Necromonger.
l would have told you
about Riddick for the
asking.
lt concerns a foretelling,
a prediction now
more than 30 years old.
A young warrior
once consulted a seer.
He was told a child would
be born on the planet
Furya, a male child
who would someday
cause the warrior's downfall.
QUASl-DEADS:
Cause his untimed death.
VAAKO: Furya?
Furya's a ruined world.
No life to speak of.
For good reason.
This young warrior
mounted an attack
on Furya,
killing all young males
he could find,
even strangling some
with their birth cords.
QUASl-DEADS: An artful
stroke, wouldn't you say?
So this warrior,
the one who tried
to outwit the prediction
would later become. . .
That's why he worries.
. . .our Lord Marshal.
Which would make
the man-child. . .
He worries he missed
killing that child
in its crib.
. . . Riddick!
QUASl-DEADS: That's why
it's vital to him.
Wait.
QUASl-DEADS: lt's
about a prophecy.
Wait!
QUASl-DEADS: Are you there?
You do what your lord asks.
You cleanse Riddick for him,
and in doing so, you prove
your undying loyalty.
And perhaps then
he'll finally let down
his guard.
GUV: Still here, l see.
l've been here 1 8 years.
See this?
l remember
how gorgeous she was.
Well,
gorgeous in
a certain light.
And now, for
the goddamn death of me,
l cannot remember her name.
GUARD: Feeding time!
We're here for the rest
of our unnatural lives.
Here they come!
Whatever you do,
don't make eye contact.
CONVlCT 1 : To the cages!
CONVlCT 2: Let me in !
lt's an animal thing.
GUARD 1 : Check her for me.
She's always got a blade
somewhere.
RlDDlCK: l don't think
she likes being touched.
l'd take my wounded and
go while you still can.
ls there a name for
this private little
world of yours?
What happens there
when we don't just
run away?
You'll kill us
with a soup cup?
Tea, actually.
What's that?
l'll kill you
with my tea cup.
GUARD 1 : You know the rule.
They aren't dead
if they're still
on the books.
Come on.
Death by tea cup.
Damn.
Why didn't l think of that?
l didn't come here to play
"Who's The Better Killer?"
But it's my favorite game.
Haven't you heard?
l heard you came looking
for me.
ls that all?
Then you missed the good part.
Hooked up with some
mercs out of Lupus Five.
Said they'd take me on,
teach me the trade,
give me a good cut.
They slaved me out, Riddick.
Do you know
what that could do to
you when you're that age?
When you're 1 2 years old?
l told you to
stay in New Mecca.
Did you not listen?
l had mercs on my neck.
l'll always have mercs
on my neck.
l spent five years
on a frozen heap just
to keep them away from you.
And you go and sign up
with the same fake badges
that wanted to cut you up
and use you for bait.
What are you pitching,
Riddick?
That you cutting out
was a good thing?
That you had my ass
covered from halfway
across the universe?
You signed with mercs.
There was nobody else around.
Let's pop the cork.
Get some fresh air.
So they do go topside
to swap out air.
lnteresting.
Who the hell are you?
When it happens,
it'll happen fast.
Stay on my leg
when l cut fence,
or stay here.
For the rest of
your unnatural life.
Nobody outs this place.
Nobody.
KYRA: He ain't nobody.
BOSS: Good news first.
Talked things over
with my amigos here.
We'll cut you in for 775,000.
All right.
What's the bad news?
They close
the local whorehouse?
BOSS: No. The bad news
is worse than that.
Much worse.
Our pilot, he saw this.
lt crossed
a shipping lane.
Any idea what this might be?
Never saw nothing like it.
This ship charts
back to Helion Prime.
You know, Anatoli's
got a nose for trouble
and he thinks
trouble follows you here.
Look, we dusted our tracks
and got the hell out of there.
There is no way
we didn't lose them.
Them?
This is my prisoner.
Mine. Nobody else's.
And l want my money now.
You stole a prisoner
from them?
TOOMBS: Riddick, no!
Should've taken the money,
Toombs.
Are you going to kill me?
Mercs.
Some guards here,
but this can't be
all of them.
Check their slots in the back.
And be careful.
Don't bother.
Guards ain't there.
They figured out
the Necros are coming for me.
Plan was to clean the bank,
ghost the mercs,
break wide
through the tunnel.
Then somebody
got a lucky shot off with
this rocket launcher here
and took out the sled.
Guards took off on foot
but rigged the door
so no one could follow.
They'll take the one ship
in the hangar
and leave everyone else
here to die.
How come
you know all this shit?
You weren't even here.
'Cause it was my plan.
l should have
taken the money.
Riddick!
CONVlCT 1 :
What is this?
What is he thinking?
CONVlCT 2: Once
that sun comes up. . .
We'll last five minutes.
Five minutes.
We ain't gonna last
30 seconds out there.
lt'll light you up
like a match.
20-mile buffer zone and
30 klicks to the hangar.
30 klicks,
over that terrain?
lt's moving in the right
direction. We could make it.
Stay behind the night,
ahead of the sun.
There's gonna be one speed.
Mine.
lf you can't keep up,
don't step up.
You'll just die.
Riddick!
Riddick.
GUV: Go! Come on, go!
GUV: Climb here!
GUV: Climb! Go!
Boss!
ANATOLl: Up there.
Take a look.
Because Anatoli says so?
Because his nose says so.
There's nothing up here.
Riddick.
GUARD 1 : They're heading
for the volcano fields.
GUARD 2: Going for our ship!
No chance do they get
to the hangar first.
No chance!
GUARD 1 :
Next one! Next hole!
We'll catch them there!
ANATOLl: No more running
for you.
Where did the big guy go?
Close it!
What was that?
You don't care
if you live or die?
lf l kill them first,
not really.
Maybe l do.
Keep moving !
RlDDlCK: Kyra?
Kyra!
What?
Get that ass moving !
Riddick?
Remember what l said
about not caring
if l lived or died?
You knew l was kidding,
right?
One speed.
Temperature differential.
Your rope.
lt's too late.
We're never gonna make it.
Your rope!
Give me your rope!
And your water. All of it!
Stay in the
shadow of the mountain.
Don't wait for me. Run !
Riddick!
GUARD 2: Where the hell
is that hangar?
GUV: There it is.
Listen.
Let me guess. Necros.
And a whole lot
of Necro firepower.
Shit! l hate not
being the bad guys.
l figure
we got three minutes,
before the sun hits us again,
burns out this whole valley.
Wait.
We gonna do this or not?
Just wait.
Ellen.
Her name was Ellen.
l never really forgot.
Boss!
Remember that
favorite game of yours?
"Who's The Better Killer?"
Let's play.
KYRA: Come on !
GUV: On the right!
GUV: Watch out!
SYBAR: Behind you !
Sybar!
No!
KYRA: No!
KYRA: Get up.
Please get up.
So, you can kneel.
SHlRAH:
l think you know now.
l think you know
who tore Furya apart.
This mark carries the
anger of an entire race.
But it's going to hurt.
Kyra?
PURlFlER: l was supposed
to deliver a message to you
if Vaako failed to kill you.
A message from
the Lord Marshal himself.
He tells you to
stay away from Helion.
Stay away from him.
And in return,
you'll be hunted no more.
But Vaako will most likely
report you as dead.
So this is your chance.
Your chance to do
what no man has ever done.
The girl.
Where will they take her?
We all began
as something else.
l've done
unbelievable things
in the name of a faith
that was never my own.
And he'll do to her
what he did to me.
The Necromonger in me
warns you not to go back.
But the Furyan in me
hopes you won't listen.
God knows
l've dreamed of it.
MARSHAL: l have lost
a Purifier,
but l have gained
a First among commanders.
lt is overdue, isn't it,
that we acknowledge
your many accomplishments,
your steady faith,
and above all,
your unflinching loyalty?
Obedience without question.
Loyalty till UnderVerse come.
Well done, Vaako.
This is a day of days.
Look more pleased, Vaako.
You have killed his enemy
and his suspicions.
l should have brought back
his head.
You saw him unbreathing.
You saw him dead
on the ground.
Riddick was
no common breeder.
ln a heartbeat
he dropped 20 of my men.
All mysteries
are not miracles,
not even in this religion.
And if you say it is certain,
then it is certain.
And we've already said it,
haven't we?
We have.
MARSHAL: Now,
tell me if it's true.
Tell me the Furyan
is gone
and l can close this campaign
without hearing his bootsteps.
lf he is dead,
l sense l'm not
far from the same fate,
being of no further use here.
Shouldn't l tell you
that Riddick is still alive?
Don't try me, Aereon.
l could plough you under
with the rest of Helion Prime.
No one really
knows the future.
Then tell me the odds.
That Vaako met with success.
That l will
now be the one who
can carry his people
across the threshold
into UnderVerse
where they shall
begin true life.
Tell me what l want to hear,
Aereon.
And maybe
l'll save your home world
for last.
The odds are good.
That?
That you will reach
the UnderVerse
soon.
Ascension protocol !
We still have numbers
out there, Lord Marshal.
Sweep teams,
recon ships.
They would be hard-pressed
to make it back. . .
Get my armada off the ground.
You mean on Helion?
l mean here on this very ship.
Could you be wrong?
Mind fabricates fear.
Not so wrong as you
when you left him alive!
lt's twice a mistake.
Not only your failure,
but now the report of success.
How do we salvage this? How?
Lord Marshal's
got to be warned.
You will never
see the UnderVerse!
He will kill us both
before our due time.
l say give Riddick his chance.
lf he is half
of what you think,
he can at least wound
the Lord Marshal.
And that is when you must act.
Just to take his place?
Just to keep what l kill?
That is the Necromonger way.
lt is not enough !
Then you do it for the faith !
lf he has fear,
he has weakness.
lf he has weakness,
Vaako. . .
He is unworthy of Lordship.
We do it for all Necromongers.
Protect the faith.
This can still
be a day of days.
But the timing must
be flawless.
Final protocol.
Execute on my order.
Go inside.
Are they leaving now?
Ziza, go inside.
OFFlCER: We found
this Lensor dead.
MARSHAL: Show me
his last sight.
Commander Toal.
He won't escape twice.
Stay your weapons.
He came for me.
MARSHAL: Consider this.
lf you fall here now,
you'll never rise.
But if you choose
another way,
the Necromonger way,
you'll die in due time
and rise again
in the UnderVerse.
Go to him.
lt hurts
at first.
But after a while,
the pain goes away,
just as they promise.
Are you with me, Kyra?
There's a moment when you
can almost see the UnderVerse
through his eyes.
He makes it sound perfect.
A place where
anyone can start over.
Are you with me, Kyra?
Convert now
or fall forever.
You killed everything l know.
Vaako.
Not yet.
Been a long time
since l've seen
my own blood.
MARSHAL: These are his last
moments.
MARSHAL: Give me your soul.
RlDDlCK: Fuck you !
You are not the one
to bring me down.
Now! Kill the beast
while he's wounded !
Help me, Vaako.
Kill him.
Vaako?
Forgive me.
Flawless.
No.
No!
Now, what would be the odds
of that?
l thought you were dead.
Are you with me, Kyra?
l was always with you.
l was.
You keep what you kill.
Please rate this subtitle at www.osdb.link/yudt
Help other users to choose the best subtitles