(METAL CLANGING)
BLACKSMITH:
When you forge a weapon,
you need three things.
The right metal,
temperatures
over 1,400 degrees,
and someone
who wants to kill.
Here in Jungle Village,
we got all three.
(MEN GRUNTING AND GROANING)
(RAP SONG PLAYING)
(CHUCKLES)
(GRUNTS)
(SCREAMS)
(SCREAMING)
Bring out the weapons!
(ROARING)
(YELLING)
BLACKSMITH:
Jungle Village.
A heartless place.
Ruled by many
savage clans.
Constantly at war.
(MEN GRUNTING)
Me, I'm just a blacksmith.
Minding my own business.
(INDISTINCT)
And biding my time.
I never wanted to
make tools for killing,
but I made the sacrifice
for the woman I love.
Lady Silk.
(CLICKS TONGUE AND INHALES)
She's a worker at
the Pink Blossom,
and my only refuge
in this hellhole.
Together, we had decided
to leave this place,
but it turns out
that the universe
had other plans.
Fate twisted
when Gold Lion,
the mighty leader
of the Lion Clan,
was summoned to
the governor's palace.
(MAN GRUNTING)
(BREATHES HEAVILY)
(GRUNTS)
The governor
gave him a mission
to protect
the shipment of gold
that he was sending
through Jungle Village
to his troops in the North.
(MEN TALKING INDISTINCTLY)
Gold Lion accepted.
He gave his word.
But when it comes to money,
things get funny.
(GROANS)
Gold Lion! Gold Lion!
BLACKSMITH:
Gold Lion was betrayed
by his own lieutenants,
Silver and Bronze.
(BOTH LAUGHING)
Now, the only thing
that stood in their
way was Zen Yi,
Gold Lion's favorite son.
(WOMAN GASPING)
But Zen Yi was
about to get the news
that would forever change
all of our destinies.
Chi Chi, I will never
leave your side.
(PANTING)
(CHUCKLES)
(SHOUTS IN MANDARIN)
And I will return
immediately home
to ask my father to
arrange our marriage.
Zen Yi! Zen Yi! Zen Yi!
Chan.
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
I have terrible news
from home.
It's your father.
No.
(SIGHS)
You said you would
never leave my side.
(KNOCKING ON DOOR)
CHAN: Master,
the horses are ready.
If I don't avenge
my father's death,
we'll never be safe.
(HORSE NEIGHS)
Yah!
Hyah!
Brothers, I am truly humbled
to be your new leader.
Now, my Lions,
we must keep
Gold Lion's word
to protect
the governor's gold.
Our enemies
have surely heard
of Gold Lion's death,
and it is my belief
that the Wolf Clan,
protectors of the West Gate,
thinking we're vulnerable,
will attack.
Instead of waiting,
I say we strike first
and take them by surprise.
Brothers,
should we not wait
for Zen Yi to return?
We will definitely
need his strength.
I agree.
You agree?
(EXHALES DEEPLY)
Are we not the Lions?
Hmm?
(SCREAMING)
Are we not the strongest?
Huh?
MEN: Yes!
I say we move with
power and strike now!
MEN: Yes!
BLACKSMITH:
Put the fire out.
A dozen of these
by tonight.
Three days.
Three days?
Why so long?
Hey! Never turn
your back on a wolf.
Or it will bite you
in the ass.
For the weapon
that you desire,
it's going to
take three days.
Unless you want
some shit like that.
Two days or you're dead.
Hyah! Huh!
(CHILDREN PLAYING)
(COINS JINGLING)
BLACKSMITH:
The Chinese have a saying.
"Dangerous men will
meet in our streets."
And so it was.
War raged
between the clans,
and that meant
pressure on me
to make more weapons.
And as word of
the gold shipment spread,
strangers suddenly appeared
in Jungle Village.
(GIRL GIGGLING)
(SNIFFS AND COUGHS)
(PEOPLE TALKING
INDISTINCTLY)
(LIVELY MUSIC PLAYING)
(SPEAKING MANDARIN)
God bless you.
To my illness.
Cheers.
An English gent.
The gentlest.
Are you military?
How long did you
spend in France?
Long enough to recognize
a man of refined tastes.
You've come
to the right place
to rest your bones.
Merci, Madame,
but I'm not here for rest.
I should like
a private room with a bath,
a view over the main road,
a bottle of that liquor,
and three of your finest.
Only three? Subtle.
Well, to start with.
I don't want
to appear greedy.
Mmm.
A man with much chi.
Prepare the South Suite
for our guest.
(WOMEN SPEAKING
INDISTINCTLY)
Please, girls,
the gentleman
has just arrived.
Give him a chance to
choose his own pleasures.
Hmm.
Yes, you.
And you.
(WOMAN GRUNTING)
And her.
(GROANS)
Sir, I'm afraid she's
with another customer.
Yes, but it's
the wrong customer.
(MAN LAUGHING)
"Journeys end
with lovers meeting,
"as every wise man's son
doth know."
My dear,
you are about to suffer
what no young lady
should have to endure.
Come.
(SPEAKING MANDARIN)
I seek no quarrel with you,
my stout fellow.
I am merely trying
to save this damsel
from what would be the most
traumatic experience of her
young life.
If you'll excuse us.
(GIGGLES)
(SPEAKING MANDARIN)
It doesn't have
to be that way.
It doesn't have to be
that way at all.
(YELLS)
(PEOPLE SCREAMING)
(GURGLES)
Ooh.
(SHOUTING)
My name is Mr. Knife!
You may call me Jack.
I have come to
your fine village
for a vacation.
I do not wish
to be disturbed!
My lady.
Shall I have the other half
of Crazy Hippo delivered
to your suite?
Feed him to your dogs.
It will make them
taste better.
(LAUGHS)
(SPEAKING IN MANDARIN)
I was worried about you.
Bring me some
golden nectar. Quickly.
(SIGHS)
Darling, what's wrong?
I'll be fine.
Those men are savages.
Why do you work
yourself to death
for their sake?
I don't do it for them.
I do it for you.
(COINS JINGLING)
Another day,
another dollar.
Lady Silk was happy,
and we were getting
closer to our goal.
Meanwhile, Zen Yi
was getting closer
to Jungle Village.
(SQUEAKING)
(SPEAKING MANDARIN)
You bring us your
best food and wine.
(SPEAKING MANDARIN)
Master, I think it might
be the crabapples.
Outhouse is back.
Thank you.
(SIGHS)
(YELLS)
(SCREAMING)
(MEN GRUNTING)
(RAP SONG PLAYING)
(GRUNTS)
Poor X-Blade.
No blades, just an "X."
You'll be joining
your father in hell today.
(MAN GROANING)
Who sent you?
Kiss my ring.
Long live Silver Lion. Hmm.
Mr. Ming is here.
We'll finish this later.
SILVER LION:
The 10 Rodents
couldn't handle Zen Yi.
POISON DAGGER: Perhaps
you should have sent 20.
The government shipment
is only days away.
Fifty-thousand taels
of gold bullion.
Still, capturing it
won't be easy.
It's being escorted
by the Gemini killers.
If we hit the shipment
and the gold doesn't
reach the northern
rendezvous point,
the government will
send in their forces.
POISON DAGGER: Exactly.
And to make
matters worse,
the emperor's secret emissary
has been sent here
to assist the troops.
And not even I know
what he is capable of.
Or, for that matter,
who he is.
(WOMAN MOANING)
(MOANING)
Yeah.
(SIGHS) Yes?
Compliments
of the house.
How kind. (SNIFFLES)
Is everything to
your satisfaction?
So far, so good.
Shall I send up
more girls?
What if I just cut
these ones in half?
Mmm?
If you damage my girls,
(GASPS)
I'll damage your boys.
(SWALLOWS)
Good God, that hurts.
(CHUCKLES)
In a very
pleasurable way.
What if I put
the baby's arm
inside you?
Must be very
good opium.
(WHIMPERS)
(CHUCKLES)
(CLEARS THROAT)
What are you looking at,
dirty little man?
(TOASTING)
(SPEAKS MANDARIN)
(METAL CLANGING)
Now, ladies, let me
have a quick look.
That is a good look.
Wet!
You have been
a naughty, naughty girl.
WOMAN: Oh!
You shall stay
tied up like that
till at least 6:00.
You wanna come?
Right, I think it's time
for some more games.
Yeah.
I'll start over here
with the navy.
(METAL CLANGING)
BLACKSMITH:
Things were heating up
in Jungle Village.
I was finishing the weapons
for the Wolves,
while they were
partying to a full moon.
(MEN HOWLING)
(CHUCKLES)
Every dog has its night.
And Zen Yi, the X-Blade,
burning with vengeance,
was just one day away
from our village.
Sounds like company
is approaching.
Smells like Lions.
IRON LION: Zen Yi.
ZEN Yl: Brothers,
what are you doing here?
We've come to
escort you home.
Chan, tie their horses
and bring them drinks.
Yes, master.
IRON LION: Silver Lion
is no longer the same.
He's changed.
Your father wanted peace.
Silver Lion wants war.
(MEN GRUNTING)
(GASPS)
As I figured,
a sheep in wolf's clothing.
(SCREAMING) No!
(MIMICKING) "No!"
(INAUDIBLE)
Wolves? More like wet dogs.
You are lucky you only
have one customer.
No need to be jealous.
(GIGGLING)
The Lion Clan
killed every member
of the Wolf clan.
They now control
the West Gate.
Everyone's so afraid
of these men. Are you?
I'm not afraid.
Well, you should be.
These men are
ruthless and vicious.
Give me my sword and
I'll leave this place.
And go where?
Anywhere my hands
won't be used to make
tools that kill anyone.
This place is not so bad.
Under the right circumstances
it could be paradise.
Paradise? This place?
(CHILDREN SPEAKING
INDISTINCTLY)
Hey, little one.
(GRUNTS)
Another one.
(CHILDREN LAUGHING)
(ALL SCREAMING)
The Gemini killers
will arrive with the
governor's gold by sunrise.
Our plans are in place.
We're ready for them.
Good.
Well, that leaves
one remaining issue.
Zen Yi.
(KNOCKING ON DOOR)
(DOOR OPENS)
Mr. Kwon,
so pleased to see you.
Silver Lion.
Brass Body.
It's nice to see
a familiar face.
SILVER LION:
"The Snake Charmer."
Your best work yet.
Thank you.
However, this next job
will not be so easy.
Is that so?
Zen Yi has become a thorn
in the Lion's paw.
That's what happens
when you send mice
to do a man's job.
You bring us
another trophy,
I'll double it.
(LAUGHS)
(BLOWS)
Zen Yi's blades will
have no effect on me.
(LAUGHING)
IRON LION: Should we
go straight to base?
We'll post up
at the Dragon Inn.
(SIGHS)
(MOANS)
Wakey-wakey, little blossoms.
Wakey-wakey.
(MOANING)
Go on.
Now, if you're good,
we can play
a game called,
"Let's pretend
we're Catholic."
(WOMEN LAUGHING)
And I'll see if I can find
the heretic amongst you.
(CHUCKLES)
Let's start now.
(MOANING)
(TRADITIONAL MUSIC PLAYING)
(SINGING)
Master Zen Yi.
My private room, please.
Of course. This way.
Chan, give this
to Silver Lion.
And hurry back.
(JINGLING)
That should satisfy
Madam Blossom.
She will no longer
be your master.
No, she won't.
Thank you.
We should pack our
bags and leave this
place immediately.
What's the rush?
Let us have one
last moment here.
Before we go.
Twenty-three, 24, 25.
Why 25?
Well, the earth is
25,000 miles
in circumference.
So smart.
Strong hands.
You're so beautiful.
How about we get
Madam Blossom in for
a threesome before we go?
(SINGING IN CANTONESE)
DRAGON INNKEEPER:
Hurry, hurry.
COPPER LION: Silver Lion
should be here by now.
He knows we're here,
and his tardiness says
more than his presence.
(CHILDREN SHOUTING)
Don't come in!
Don't come in! Stop!
Stop, stop, stop,
come back!
(PANTS)
(CHILDREN SCREAMING)
(YELLS) No!
(GRUNTING)
(GROANING)
Brother!
(GRUNTING)
(SCREAMS)
(ROARS)
(GRUNTING)
X-Blade,
you're a dead man.
(GRUNTING)
No!
(RUMBLING)
BLACKSMITH: Zen Yi.
BLACKSMITH:
Well, Gold Lion was dead,
and Zen Yi was
out of commission.
Now, there was all eyes
on the Geminis,
who arrived in town
with the governor's gold.
Their plan was to
post up at Dragon Inn,
spend the night,
and continue north.
I've cleared everybody out,
just as you requested.
I'm looking forward
to your famous
Cantonese braised ribs.
I knew you would ask.
It's already prepared.
Well?
Spicy.
Oh, good.
Upstairs.
(SNAPS FINGERS)
You're still
as lovely as ever.
Please.
(SPEAKING MANDARIN)
You look beautiful, Jackie.
Like a Chinese warrior.
(IMITATING MANDARIN)
(GIGGLING)
Me likey.
DRAGON INNKEEPER:
Master Silver Lion.
I'm sorry,
we're closed for the day.
Oh, you are never closed
to the Lion Clan.
Now, where are the Geminis?
Please, no trouble.
Trouble?
(GRUNTS)
Mr. And Mrs. Gemini.
How are they?
Spicy.
Where's your boss,
Gold Lion?
Unfortunately,
he couldn't make it.
What do you want here,
Silver Lion?
Oh, you know
what we want.
Friends, there's really
no need for your journey
to end here.
And by that,
I mean your life journey.
You give us the gold,
we spare you and your men.
And maybe we will
invite you to join us
and live like royalty
here in our
lovely village.
A dog living in a palace
is still a dog.
(ALL LAUGHING)
And every dog loves
to chase the pussycat.
(GRUNTS)
MAN:
The Gemini stance.
Poison Dagger.
Where are you?
Come out!
(CROWD MURMURING)
Ah, no more, no more.
Go. We are closed.
Forever.
(SPEAKS MANDARIN)
The Lions do this.
See what they did
to my inn!
You want Lion?
I cook you Lion.
How would you like it?
Steamed? Deep fried?
Pan fried? Ah!
Lion dumpling?
I was hoping
for one last dish of
your Emperor Sui Duck.
We haven't prepared
that dish in years.
Seasoned with young basil,
and Yangzi grains.
The dish is for
very special customers.
Please.
What kind of Lion is this?
Not Lions. Gemini.
A very pretty one at that.
Such a shame.
Mercury.
The mark of Poison Dagger.
Who in this village
would have access
to mercury?
Our blacksmith.
But he's not from here.
His weapons
are very dangerous.
Well,
I'm only here
for the duck.
BLACKSMITH:
As if bad things
couldn't get worse,
word got to the governor
that the Lions ambushed
the gold.
This enraged him,
and he called in
the fierce Jackal troops.
Now, these motherfuckers
had a Gatling gun
and more bullets
than China had rice.
He gave them an order.
If one tael of gold
was missing,
they was to burn
Jungle Village
to the ground.
BLACKSMITH:
Prepare these herbs.
ZEN Yl:
Why are you helping me?
Because I forged the weapons
that killed your father.
I regret that.
(EXHALES)
(GRUNTING)
Brother,
don't avert your energy.
You're not strong yet.
No.
But soon.
And I want to ask you
of one thing.
My blades, they were
destroyed by Brass Body.
I need a new suit of knives.
(SIGHS)
(TALKING INDISTINCTLY)
(METAL CLANGING)
BLACKSMITH: The X-Blade's
new suit of knives.
The final weapon
these hands would
ever forge.
And if he can avenge
his father with
these blades,
then my debt to him
will be paid.
And I can grab my girl
and get the fuck out
of Jungle Village.
Come back to bed, Jackie.
Some pleasure
before business?
You were business.
This is pleasure.
BRASS BODY: You've got
good taste, Blacksmith.
I always thought that
Lady Silk was the finest
of all the girls.
And you've been
monopolizing her.
(PANTING)
Tell me where Zen Yi is,
or I promise you,
you will never
see her again.
(SALUTING GRUNTS)
Oh, my. This is no way
to treat our guest.
Are we men,
or are we beasts?
(WHISPERS) We are men!
So, my friend, I never got
a chance to thank you for
your magnificent weapons.
They were invaluable.
(GRUNTING)
So, it seems you've
been working quite hard
these nights. I admire that.
But on what, may I ask?
Go to hell.
(CHUCKLES)
Listen, your skills
can be used by us.
Hmm?
You can be
a great asset.
If you give up Zen Yi
and pledge your
allegiance to us,
your troubles
will be over.
But, if you refuse,
we'll make sure
you never work again.
You are no Gold Lion.
Well, that hurts.
I will ask you
one last time.
Blackie, where is Zen Yi?
(SPITS)
You shouldn't
have done that.
(GRUNTING)
(SCREAMS)
(LAUGHING)
(WHIMPERING)
(SCREAMS)
Ooh.
(FIREWORKS EXPLODING)
(ALL LAUGHING)
(SHOUTING)
What do you want
to do with his body?
Leave him to the rats.
(SNIFFING)
(TALKING INDISTINCTLY)
You're tough as old boots,
Blacksmith.
Englishman.
Who are you?
You can call me Jack.
I'm the one who saved you
from the reaper.
Not my arms.
No. They're rat food,
I'm afraid.
We're going to have
to cauterize your wounds.
It won't be pleasant.
It won't be pleasant at all.
Quite a sophisticated
operation you have here.
Drink.
I see you work
with mercury.
Again.
One more. A large one.
Open your mouth,
bite on this.
(SIZZLING)
(MUFFLED SCREAMS)
(WHIMPERING)
(BREATHES HEAVILY)
(MUFFLED YELLS)
Take this, take this.
Your wounds are healing
surprisingly quickly.
How do you feel?
Am I assuming correctly
that you made this?
(SIGHS)
So, how does a man
with your obvious skill
end up in a wretched corner
of the Earth like this?
I spent most of
my life in chains,
serving others.
The master of the plantation
my family worked on was
dying of consumption.
For 35 years,
my mother served him,
nursed him,
slept with him.
And on his deathbed...
Okay, now,
what's his name?
Thaddeus.
Thaddeus...
Henry.
Smith.
(CHUCKLES)
(SOBS)
Boy, good luck.
You're gonna need it.
Momma...
(HORSE NEIGHING)
MAN: Hyah!
(MAN LAUGHING)
Hey, boy, you got
those horseshoes ready?
Didn't you hear?
I asked if them
shoes were ready.
Nigger, you can't read.
So you don't know
what this fucking
paper means.
It means nothing.
(GROANS)
MAN 1: Whoo-hoo!
Yeah! Hey, man!
(LAUGHING)
MAN 2: You're free now,
huh, nigger?
MAN 1: Come and get it!
Come and get it.
MAN 2: Come on. Yeah.
MAN 2:
Crawl, nigger, crawl.
MAN 1:
Come on, kitty!
MAN 1: Yeah! Yeah!
MAN 2: Come on.
Stay down.
Whoa!
Fidgety nigger,
ain't he?
Go on, finish him off.
Go on.
Nigger, you're gonna wish
you had never been born.
(YELLS)
MAN 1: Jake!
The nigger killed a white man!
The nigger killed a white man.
What you doing, Jane?
Nothing, sir.
Yeah.
Nothing.
I don't think so.
Your boy's around here?
Long gone.
Yeah.
We'll see.
Run. Run, son, run.
The boat I escaped on sunk.
Everyone was lost at sea.
But somehow...
(TALKING INDISTINCTLY)
(SPEAKING CANTONESE)
To disconnect ourselves from this troublesome world.
Another one.
BLACKSMITH:
I strayed from the path,
and I paid the price.
The pendulum of karma
swings both ways.
They made me a cripple.
But if you help me,
I will forge my
greatest weapon ever.
As a young mind,
we taught you that,
in the beginning,
there was the word.
Yet when man failed
to hear the word,
we were forced
to teach by action.
The chi in your body travels
through the 12 vessels
and builds up
in your Dan Tian.
Your triple burners convert
all particles to energy.
By learning
to regulate breath
and controlling your chi,
a man is capable
of amazing feats.
If one can find the source
to one's own energy,
he can transmit
that energy
to activate
inanimate objects.
You and the object
become as one.
It becomes a slave
to your will, your mind.
Your chi.
What are you
really here for?
Dear boy, gold.
So, how is your chi now?
(YELLS)
(SPEAKING MANDARIN)
(TOASTING)
Miss Silk, I'd like to
thank you and the blacksmith
for your kindness.
The blacksmith,
how is he?
The rumor is that
he's dead.
(MAN SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY)
(SHOUTING)
(TALKING INDISTINCTLY)
Zen Yi.
My friend,
you look pretty good.
For a dead man.
Thanks to him.
Care to join us
for dinner?
I hope you don't mind
your noodles a touch
on the spicy side.
This is an East Indian
recipe. Very hot.
And here's the secret.
Just a touch of butter.
Just a touch.
(LAUGHS)
A spoon, dear boy.
Baby steps.
Now, might I suggest,
given the nature
of our common enemy,
and the numbers
we're about
to encounter,
that we come up
with a plan?
MADAM BLOSSOM:
In fact, our Jungle
wasn't always an outpost.
Rumor has it,
the Fourth Emperor
built a magnificent tomb
for his queen
directly beneath
our village.
Oh, that's fascinating.
(BOTH LAUGHING)
Here. To good fortune.
Good fortune.
Now, when the captain of
the Jackals arrives with
his many armed troops,
where do you suppose
he's going to attack?
Well, presumably
the Lions' base.
Exactly, and they'll come
not only for gold,
but also for lives.
We see the Madam
is well informed.
(CHUCKLES) My sheets know
every secret in this town.
Gentlemen,
we've had dinner.
Now, dessert.
Oh. (CHUCKLES)
Shall we?
(CHUCKLES)
The Fourth Emperor,
a man of imagination.
And I thought lies
were your stock-in-trade.
Not stock.
Just trade.
What do you have in mind?
You store your gold here,
less the 3% that goes to me,
along with the right
to control my women,
my way, as I always have.
One way in,
one way out?
Of course.
Three percent
is quite steep.
Four percent.
POISON DAGGER: My friend,
better 3% to the madam
than 100% to the Jackals.
All right,
we have a deal.
Now, we need a lot of
action from you coming
from the South Gate.
Try and make some noise.
We want the others to
think there's an attack.
No problem.
I presume you're coming in
from the chopstick gate
in the north here.
And I'll keep
the southern gate locked up
until you get there.
About how much time do we have
before the Jackals arrive?
Dawn.
If we don't get
this done before then,
it'll be the end
of the village.
They're moving the gold
to the Blossom's.
I know a secret way.
Of course you do,
little mouse.
Can you show us
that secret way?
(SPEAKS MANDARIN)
Change of plans.
Be careful, men.
Sorry.
Not with the gold,
but with your jewels.
This place is rigged
with many traps
that will make women of you
if you don't respect them.
Yes. Yes.
(GRUNTS)
Rigged with traps?
Yes.
Oh.
You must tell.
Beautiful.
You may leave us now, Madam.
And thank you.
Goodbye, Madam.
She's quite lovely,
but partnership
with this woman is
going to be an issue.
Don't worry.
In the morning,
we will kill all
of these whores.
Oh, I can't wait.
(LIGHT CHUCKLE)
So generous of your friend,
the governor,
to bestow this
great gift upon us.
You must never underestimate
the power of your enemy,
Silver Lion.
You have a notable habit
of celebrating early.
Have your men begun
trapping the Lion base
with the explosives?
Oh, yes.
They should be
nearly done by now.
When the mighty Jackals
show up there in the morning,
boom, boom,
and bye-bye.
(SPEAKING MANDARIN)
(MEN LAUGHING)
(TALKING INDISTINCTLY)
WOMAN: Stop it!
Lovelies.
Do not think for a moment
that I enjoy seeing you
forced into any position.
I have been exactly
where you are.
I do not make these demands
of you lightly. Remember,
there is a purpose.
The power has always
lain with men.
Yet, it is essential
to understand that power
is not theirs by birth.
The nature of power is that
it belongs to no one until
it is taken, seized.
Seized through sex,
violence.
Gold.
Men may have
always held the power,
but power is
a fickle mistress.
And here in Jungle Village,
the winds of change
are nearly upon us.
Hear me clearly,
my darlings,
when I say that our
days of shame and disgrace
are nearly over.
Now, back to work.
Dry off,
prepare yourselves.
And we'll see
who's left standing,
and who is on their knees.
(WOMEN GROANING)
Come, ladies,
you heard Madam.
Warriors.
Brave Lions,
kings of the jungle!
Drink up!
Partake of the women.
Tonight, my friends,
the Pink Blossom is yours.
(CROWD CHEERING)
(DOOR OPENING)
(GRUNTING)
(SQUEALS)
(SOFT MUSIC PLAYING)
(MOANING)
Oh, baby.
(LAUGHING)
Do you like it?
Yeah.
(GRUNTS)
(GROANS)
Aah!
(GRUNTING)
Stupid bitch.
No!
(GASPING)
Black widow.
Thaddeus.
This way! This way!
Mmm...
You thief,
get out of here!
(GROANS)
What was that?
I always take a gun
to a knife fight.
(GASPS)
(GROANS)
Zen Yi.
Silver Lion.
Come and get me.
(LAUGHS MANIACALLY)
Jack Knife.
I thought you were dead.
Reports of my demise were
greatly exaggerated, Dagger.
Well, then.
There's business
to be done here.
Not this time, old chap.
You see,
I'm on the other side.
Government emissary?
The emperor himself,
no less.
(LAUGHING)
Zen Yi.
(GROANING)
Tiger style.
I thought your clan
was extinct.
My clan is extinct.
I killed them.
(CHOKING)
(YELLS)
I'm afraid you've come up
a little short, my friend.
Jack.
Unfortunately, Dagger,
the gears of life
move inexorably
in only one direction.
I'm glad to see you've
adopted the philosophies
of my people.
Now get me out of here!
Dagger, Dagger, Dagger.
You should have finished
what you started.
That is the difference
between you and me!
I see my jobs
through to the end.
The only difference
between you and me
is the poison we use.
Opium?
It's not a poison.
And it's not a curse.
It is a benefit and a solace
to the hardworking Chinese.
And the occasional
Englishman.
I'll see you in hell.
I suppose you will.
(COUGHING)
Save me a spot
by the fire.
(LAUGHING)
SILVER LION:
I'm to your right.
I'm to your left.
What took you so long?
Got caught up
looking at yourself
in the mirror?
(GROANS)
Now you die,
little brother.
Gold Lion raised you
as a son.
Why would you betray us?
This was my time.
(SHOUTING) My time!
And this is my gold.
Well, here's your gold.
(SCREAMING)
I'm gonna drill you
like I drilled
your little whore.
(GRUNTING)
JACKAL LIEUTENANT:
By order of the emperor,
you have five seconds
to bring out the gold,
or we will kill you all.
Five.
Four.
Three.
Two.
One.
Gentlemen!
Colonel Jack C. Wales,
emissary of the emperor.
Everything here
is under control.
(SOLDIER SHOUTING ORDERS)
(EXHALES)
Good.
My friend,
I've lost a father,
but I gained a brother.
Thaddeus.
Jack.
Thanks.
No, thank you.
I haven't had this much fun
since we protected
the crown in Macau.
BLACKSMITH:
The Chinese say,
"Where there is iron,
there is rust."
Well, not anymore.
Jungle Village was clean.
And I'm gonna make sure
that it stays that way.
(RAP SONG PLAYING)
Chi Chi.
Chi Chi! Chi Chi!
(SHOUTING)
My brother,
I'm in need of
your hands again.