Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
(ROCK MUSIC PLAYING)
(WOMAN SHRIEKS)
(FUNK MUSIC PLAYING)
My Purge playlist.
I put a lot of thought into it,
especially this final tune
as it will be the last
song you'll ever hear.
Tough choice.
(BREATHING DEEPLY)
And then I thought,
George Clinton!
The king of interplanetary
funkmanship.
George's psychedelic rock will leave
you feeling funky, obviously.
And soulful, which is
the least I can do.
Now, we played a lot of Purge games
tonight, and we have just one more.
It's simple,
yet effective.
It's called "Mommy's Choice."
(WHIMPERS)
Mommy, which one of you will
survive this year's Purge?
(STRUGGLING)
(SCREAMING) No! No!
No!
(ALL CLAMORING)
MALE REPORTER: This is just one of a
dozen protests around our capital
after reports emerged claiming
that the New Founding Fathers
had been using the Purge to
help their own economic agenda.
Here's a recent statement by incendiary
Purge detractor Dante Bishop.
For the past 20 years,
the NFFA has taken to legalized murder
to decrease
the poor population,
which in turn keeps the
government's spending down.
Less welfare,
less healthcare, less housing.
MALE REPORTER: Recent polling suggests
that the growing anti-Purge sentiment
may have a monumental effect on the
upcoming presidential election.
Establishment NFFA candidate
Minister Edwidge Owens
has been losing ground to wildcard
Independent candidate Senator Charlie Roan.
Eighteen years ago, Roan was forced
to watch the brutal execution
of her entire family
on Purge Night
and entered the political arena
soon after with one goal in mind.
To put an end to
the annual holiday.
I have no doubt that the soul
of our country is at stake.
The Purge has
to come to an end.
MALE REPORTER: Senator Roan is proving to
be the greatest threat to the NFFA regime
since they first took
office 25 years ago...
(GLASS THUDS)
Is the cunt that close?
All polls have her
a point behind.
I'm sorry, Caleb,
I've done...
No sorrys, Minister,
you're doing a great job.
Let us put you
where you need to be.
Thomas.
We have our people out there countering
all this anti-NFFA bullshit.
What else
can we do?
(SHOUTING) We do
whatever it fucking takes!
I have had it with all
these idealistic pigs.
They want the impossible.
Everyone to have.
Some cannot have.
Not enough
to go around.
It's time to do something
about all these cocksuckers,
like that rat Bishop
and the cunt Senator
trying to dismantle
everything we've built.
We are going to use
this year's Purge
to do some spring cleaning,
gentlemen.
FEMALE MODERATOR: And where will you
be spending Purge Night, Minister?
I will once again be presiding over
my party's Midnight Purge Mass
because I still
believe in it.
The Midnight
Purge Mass,
where our great NFFA leaders gather
together and slaughter innocents.
Is murder our
new religion?
FEMALE MODERATOR: Senator.
Murder is our new religion.
That's snappy.
No, the Midnight Purge Mass where
NFFA leaders gather to celebrate
the night that saved this
country from economic ruin.
We have other ways.
Now, America is
built upon sacrifice.
From the Revolution
all the way to World War II.
Our Lord God sacrificed
his only Son...
Everybody look alive.
ERIC: Copy. We have
eyes on her, boss.
MINISTER OWENS: That's why
we must sacrifice every year
in order to rid
ourselves of hatred.
Remember what I said.
She moves, we move.
(AUDIENCE CHEERING)
Now, the stats are undeniable.
There has been far less crime...
(TAPPING PODIUM) This is crap.
Do I have to listen to this?
Send me to the
Principal's office.
I can't listen
to this anymore.
Okay, we'll send you to
the Principal's office
'cause you can't
keep your mouth shut.
More low-income
people are killed
during the Purge
than anyone else.
(SCATTERED CHATTER) The money
generated from the Purge
lines the pockets of the NRA
and insurance companies.
WOMAN: Don't listen to her!
Any government system
that relies on violence
to answer
its problems
must be rebooted.
She's doing good,
Leo.
(AUDIENCE CHEERING)
It is time to call upon the
better angels of our nature.
(AUDIENCE CHEERING)
He is going
to keep lying.
Jesus Christ.
There she goes again.
Secure the audience.
I'm on it.
SENATOR ROAN: I'd like to talk to you guys.
(CHEERING CONTINUES)
Put a leash on her, Chief.
She's no good to anyone dead.
You got it, Leo.
Okay. We're on the move.
ERIC: Copy, boss.
Thank you very much. Thank you so much.
Thank you.
Go sit down. I'm happy to stay
here for the rest of the night.
Stay close to her.
Keep it tight.
Go out. Purge and purify.
Purge and purify!
Hi. Thank you again.
MALE REPORTER: As she's
done many times before,
Senator Roan broke
security protocol,
walking off the stage,
stepping into the audience.
Tell you this much,
she got 'em little titties,
but she got some
big-ass balls.
She ain't got
a snowball's chance
in a steam bath of
winning this thing,
but she be taking on
them ol' white-haired
George Washington
wannabe mofos
all by herself.
And to that,
I say bully for her.
Oh, horseshit.
She's full of it too.
Nothing'll ever change.
Hey, Laney.
Laney, Laney?
I think we've offended Marcos
with our anti-Senator talk.
The Senator's
going to win.
She's gonna make real changes too.
You'll see.
All she needs
is Florida.
She gets the 29 electoral votes from
Florida, that puts her over 270.
She can do it.
JOE: Smartass.
All that useless shit and can't
butter a damn bagel correctly.
I could butter your bagel, boss.
(GASPS)
Oh, you'd butter my bagel?
LANEY: Mmm...
Well, you got jokes
over there.
Yeah, you just be careful,
kid, with all that hope,
'cause it can be
a bad thing.
Hope can lead
to a lot of letdown.
Tell him, Irish I.
Excuse me, what?
I'm not
paying attention.
I'm thinking about
waffles and pussy.
That's all I ever really
think about, actually.
Mmm-mmm...
JOE: Irish I, ladies and gentlemen.
(ALL CHUCKLING)
The fuck you laughing at?
I'm dead serious.
Ah, fuck!
(LANEY LAUGHING)
The New Founding Fathers
believe in fairness.
And we hear what
the people are saying.
That the Purge benefits
the rich and the powerful.
That was never the intention.
From this point on,
no one is exempt.
The rules protecting level 10
government officials have been revoked.
Yeah. Come in.
You seeing this?
Yeah, NFFA is revoking
the Purge rule
that protects
government officials
of ranking 10
on Purge Night.
Yeah, I'll secure a safe house and
full security detail on the night.
No. I'm staying home
on Purge Night.
Senator, I don't think
that's a good idea.
If the voters get wind
that I'm hiding
in a fortress like
some rich asshole,
I lose votes
and the NFFA wins.
I stay home like
99% of the population.
Make it safe.
Whatever it takes.
Right.
(HIP-HOP MUSIC PLAYING)
(SCREAMS)
(SINISTER LAUGHTER)
Half price
on all masks.
Come on inside.
The Purge is
Halloween for adults!
(SINISTER LAUGHTER)
Hordes of young adults are arriving
from Spain, Denmark, South Africa.
They're being called
Murder Tourists
as they are here
for one reason.
To Purge.
We're here to
experience the Purge.
To kill. Release all
the anger and hate.
To be like Americans.
We're very excited.
(SPEAKING OTHER LANGUAGE)
Foreigners coming
to our capital to kill.
Murder tourism. It's the new booming
business in our country this year.
MRS. SABIAN: Murder tourism.
What's happened
to our country, Joe?
Mrs. Sabian,
I wish I knew.
But you take care
of yourself, Mrs. S.
Next time you need something,
just give us a call.
I'll have Marcos run it over
and save you the trip, okay?
MRS. SABIAN: I come by
to flirt with you, Joe!
What?
MRS. SABIAN: No one's
gonna take that from me.
JOE: Ah, you better get out of here. Get
on out of here. (MRS. SABIAN CHUCKLING)
Yeah!
Oh. Get out of here.
Now she nasty.
She... That's a nasty
woman, right there.
(PACKETS THUDDING)
(LAUGHING)
Joe. Mira.
Son of a bitch!
(DOOR BELL DINGING)
Where's he going?
I never saw him move so damn fast.
All right, girls, give it up.
I won't have to call the police.
Get outta my face,
old man!
Let's not do this the hard way, okay?
I'm giving you an out.
All right, give up the candy or
I'll have to take it away from you.
You touch me and I scream "rape,"
you cocksucking pig.
Now walk away.
LANEY: Give it back.
Who are you, bitch?
Better get out of my way!
That's Laney Rucker,
Kimmy.
Laney Rucker?
Holy shit.
(CHUCKLES)
OG Queen badass?
Yo! They called
you Pequeña Muerte.
Little Death.
(LAUGHING)
Yo, you're my
motherfucking hero.
That makes me proud.
Now give back
whatever you stole.
And apologize.
Oh, my God.
Sorry, mister.
I was just playin'.
So, Ms. Rucker,
what happened to you?
You look all
whitish now.
Later, Ms. Rucker.
Wish I met you back in the day.
Excuse me.
(GROANS)
Well...
You were a lot more respectful back
when you were shoplifting here.
(CHUCKLES) You know, I distinctly
remember one time,
you called me "sir."
Oh, bullshit.
But listen, I just want
to say thank you.
You're my family, Joe.
I appreciate that.
Thank you, Laney.
(CHUCKLES)
(CHATTER OVER POLICE RADIO)
LEO: I want men in there.
I want men in there.
I want a lot of men back there.
She's got some security,
but I'm revamping the entire thing.
We got new barricades
on all the doors,
all the windows
back and front.
CHIEF COUPER: Looks safe.
Chief, if you tell me
it's safe one more time,
I'm gonna throw you
down the steps.
CHIEF COUPER:
Please don't do that.
Men here. Men here.
We got a security monitor
system in this room.
We got eyes and
ears on everything.
This is her safe room.
She is not to leave her safe room.
No one is to go inside her safe room.
Do we understand each other?
This is a mess. She's not
gonna be happy about it.
I don't care if
she's happy, Chief.
And I want to go on record as
saying this is a bad idea.
No matter what
we do here,
this house and this Senator
are at risk on Purge Night.
You understand me?
Duly noted.
Let's lock it down.
"Let's lock it down."
It's just me
and you, pal.
Tell me what you want
me to do. I'm there.
Go downstairs, make sure
they take care of the doors.
Keep an eye on that guy. Done.
BISHOP ON TV: The NFFA has
created predatory capitalism
where profit-making
is the essence of democracy.
(CELLPHONE RINGING)
We've come to D.C.
to make some changes.
FEMALE REPORTER: That was Dante Bishop.
Like his predecessor Carmelo Johns...
(PHONE BEEPS)
Joe's Deli.
...Dante is suspected
of eliminating
wealthy NFFA supporters
on Purge Nights.
Excuse me?
And many are wondering why he has
come to Washington this year.
Wait, wait. Hold it.
Wait a minute.
Why are you raising
my rates now? Today?
Do you know
what today is?
Yeah, but look, I...
(STUTTERING) Yeah... I can't afford that.
What do you mean,
you're sorry?
Yeah, I'm talking to you.
Let me speak to your... Your super...
Son of a... Son of a bitch!
(PHONE DROPS)
Joe?
What the hell's
going on?
JOE: The damn
insurance company.
They just raised the premium on
my Purge coverage. By thousands.
The day before
the damn Purge.
If I don't pay it by tomorrow,
I have no Purge coverage for this store.
They can't do that.
Yeah, well,
they just did it.
Just lock the
place down, Joe.
Yeah, but that's
not enough.
If I have no insurance,
I am screwed.
(SIGHS)
I'll just have to protect
this place myself.
Are you crazy?
MARCOS: That's not a good idea, boss.
Look, we love
this place, too, Joe.
I've been coming here
since I was born.
But it's just stuff.
It can be replaced.
You can't be.
Yeah, but what about what you
do on Purge Night, Laney?
Huh?
Is that not the pot calling
the kettle brown? No?
That's different, Joe,
and you know that.
I'm protected,
and you won't be.
This is all I got, guys.
This is my slice of the pie.
(EXHALES)
Man, I cannot,
I can't lose this place.
Hold on, Joe.
Let's talk about this.
Everything is in place.
Team's in position.
Ten minutes
to lockdown, boss.
(BREATHING DEEPLY)
Hey, Mama.
(DOOR CLOSES)
You ready?
Yeah.
Vaya con Dios.
Okay, let's go.
Okay. This is gonna be home
for the next 12 hours.
You need anything,
you contact me and me only.
Clear?
Clear.
Let's begin.
(BEEPING)
(SHUTTERS WHIRRING)
(WHIRRING STOPS)
(ALARM BLARING ON TV)
FEMALE VOICE ON TV:
This is not a test.
This is your Emergency
Broadcast System
announcing the commencement
of the annual Purge
sanctioned by the
U. S. government.
Commencing at the siren,
any and all crime, including murder,
will be legal for
12 continuous hours.
Here we go.
Police, fire and
emergency medical services
will be unavailable until
tomorrow morning at 7 a. m.
And, for the first time
since its inception,
no one has been granted special
immunity from the Purge.
No citizen or group
will be exempt.
Blessed be our New Founding Fathers,
and America, a nation reborn.
May God be with you all.
(SIREN BLARING)
(STATIC)
I see you, Bobby.
(EXHALES) You know you
can relax now, right?
No, I'll relax
in the morning.
Am I interrupting?
Senator, you should
be in the den.
Eric, thank you for
being here tonight.
My pleasure.
Leo, have a drink
with me.
You don't have a choice.
Sounds serious.
Don't say a word.
Or I'll stick my
foot up your ass.
(DRINK POURING)
(SIGHS)
Sit.
It's water, Leo.
Are you scared?
I'm terrified.
What made you apply
for this position?
I like your politics.
No. No bullshit.
I want a real answer.
I lost my son
some years ago.
He was killed.
I almost did something on Purge Night
that would've destroyed a lot of lives.
I want this night gone.
I know you do, too.
Especially after
what you lost.
Yeah. Despite
all of that,
you have a big problem
with how I do things.
You take risks, Senator.
My job is to eliminate
risks and keep you alive.
You don't
make that easy.
The soul of this country
is at stake, Leo.
The only way that I can win is to risk
everything, and that includes my life.
(EXHALES)
(MUSIC PLAYING)
WOMAN: Peace, not Purge!
(LAUGHING) You go, girls!
Have a drink on us!
LANEY: Can't you see
we're working?
PURGE PARTIER:
Purge, motherfuckers!
(ALL SHOUTING)
Just gonna wait right here
and see what happens.
PURGE PARTIER: Purge!
They probably won't
bother us, okay?
(GRUNTING)
(GASPS)
(SOFTLY) Purge.
Purge. Purge.
Go, go, go! Let's move!
(MEN SHOUTING)
(MEN LAUGHING)
(WOMAN SCREAMING)
(WOMAN CRYING)
WOMAN: Help! Help! Please!
Somebody help! Help! Help!
(CONTINUES CRYING)
Please! Please!
(SCREAMS)
Stop! Stop!
Please, stop!
Please, help him!
Something's going down. Hey, looks
like someone needs our services.
Let's go.
Let's do this. Stop.
WOMAN: I shot my husband!
I shot him. Oh, God!
LANEY: Okay. Calm down.
Tell me what happened.
(WOMAN CRYING)
Oh, no! It was
a mistake! I'm sorry!
(MAN SCREAMING IN DISTANCE)
(JOE EXHALES)
MARCOS: Hey, boss!
It's me! It's me.
Come on
outta there, boy.
Good Lord, son.
It's Purge Night. You don't
sneak up on black people.
(SIGHS) Good night,
blue cheese.
Where the hell you going?
And why you carrying a chair?
I like sitting.
Yeah, well, you ain't
gonna be staying.
Look, you know I appreciate you coming
out here to watch my back, but I'm good.
I got this.
No.
(PANTING) I'll stay.
Nothing else to do.
Look, please don't
be a pain in the ass.
I want you to go
home and be safe.
I don't want you out here on
Purge Night, son. I got this!
(TIRES SCREECHING)
(HORN HONKING)
(POP MUSIC PLAYING ON CAR RADIO)
(SCREECHING CONTINUES)
(GIRLS SHOUTING
INDISTINCTLY)
(LAUGHING)
KIMMY: Purge Night, bitch! It's Purge
Night, bitch! It's Purge Night, bitch!
Give me that shit. Let's go!
Fuck you!
(POP MUSIC CONTINUES PLAYING)
Ooh!
(LAUGHING)
Happy Purge,
you old fuck!
(LAUGHING)
You better find
someplace else to go!
I got a wicked
sweet tooth tonight.
And I want my candy bar.
And I'm gonna take it.
You don't got the balls
to stop me. (LAUGHING)
(SHRIEKS) Fuck!
MARCOS: I have the balls.
Now go.
I already took care
of my mom and dad tonight.
You're next.
I want my candy bar,
cocksucker.
(GASPING)
Come on!
(CAR DOOR CLOSING)
(TIRES SCREECHING)
So, what's up with that?
Every day in Juárez
was like the Purge.
I know how
to shoot, boss.
Son, I really wish
you'd stayed home.
(CANS CLANKING)
(CANS OPENING)
I don't know.
It's that time.
Eric.
What are you still doing up here?
You're on first floor duty.
How was your chat?
Enlightening. Go.
Chief, find a bedroom.
I got it from here.
All right, Leo.
Boys. Why don't
you take a break?
Go watch some TV, huh?
It's gonna be a long night.
Yes, sir.
(SILENCED GUNSHOTS)
(STATIC)
I'm coming
outside, boys.
(KNOCKING ON DOOR)
(BEEPING)
(WHIRRING)
How ya doing
out there, Bobby?
Sniper One,
radio check.
Bobby, radio check.
Sniper Two,
radio check.
Sniper Two.
(SILENCED GUNSHOTS)
(DOOR OPENING)
Someone is coming for you.
What?
Put that on.
Leo, the house is surrounded...
Move, move!
I'm moving.
What are you...
You said you had men on the roof.
You have snipers.
Not anymore. Not anymore.
What do you mean, not anymore?
Someone betrayed us.
What?
I can't trust anyone.
Put on that vest. (BEEPING)
Listen to me!
This isn't a drill.
Someone's coming to kill you.
You understand me?
Move.
SENATOR ROAN: Moving.
What the...
Go!
Okay, what
the hell is that?
That's my little
secret. Move.
One, two, three!
SENATOR ROAN: Okay.
(BEEPING)
ERIC: Boss! It's just me!
Fuck.
Where the hell is she?
Jesus Christ.
(GRUNTING)
(PANTING)
(SCREAMS)
(GRUNTS)
What the fuck is this?
(BEEPING)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER
OVER RADIO)
I don't know what
the fuck that is.
(STATIC) Our mark may be
outside. Repeat.
Your mark may be outside.
Check your perimeters.
(SIGHS)
No payment
unless we find her.
Fuck.
I see her!
(GUNSHOTS)
(BEEPING)
Down!
LEO: (PANTING)
Come here.
Move. Go! Go!
Go! Go!
(GUNSHOTS)
Hey, Joe,
you up there?
Is that Laney?
Marcos!
My guys!
How you all doing tonight?
We're good. You?
Ah... (SIGHS)
I just dropped
someone off at triage.
His wife shot him because she couldn't
stand looking at his face anymore.
She said Purging didn't make her feel
any better like they said it would.
Just stay safe,
Lane.
Anything happens, do not
hesitate to call us.
Yeah, same goes for you.
Okay?
All right.
(VAN DRIVING AWAY)
God, I hate that she's
out there like that.
WOMAN: (SCREAMING)
Help me! Help me!
LEO: Stop. Stop!
(BOTH PANTING)
What was that?
Some kind of homegrown militia?
Those were skilled mercs with
a lot of money behind them.
Enough to get to
someone on our staff.
I'm guessing
it's the Minister.
The Minister, the NFFA,
the whole fucking lot of them.
I'm getting
too close.
(LEO PANTING)
It's a lot of blood, Leo.
We should call someone.
I don't know who to trust. We are
on our own. You understand me?
Okay. Where do we go?
East. Out of the city.
There are a lot of threats.
(EXHALES)
There's a lot
of death.
(VEHICLE APPROACHING)
MAN: Purge
Sanitation Services.
Death collection haul.
Purge victim
removal and disposal.
Keep Washington clean.
It's okay.
Death collection haul.
This is how
it's gonna go now.
Like you said, fate of
the country's at stake.
Okay? It's my show now.
Look, I'm not
an idiot.
I know what you're capable of.
I'm the one who hired you.
But if I see something I don't like,
I'm not gonna be quiet about it.
It's not in my nature.
(BREATHING DEEPLY)
Senator, I need you to follow me.
(SHOUTING IN DISTANCE)
Come on.
(MAN SHOUTING
INDISTINCTLY OVER DRONE)
It's Tommy, sir.
He's in bad shape.
He's unconscious.
Everyone else
up there is dead.
Get him to the ground unit.
Get him stabilized.
Then start street surveillance.
I'll search from above.
We need her alive, so let's
find her before the crazies do.
Sir.
(MAN SHOUTING INDISTINCTLY
OVER DRONE)
They're tracking us.
Where? I'm not seeing them.
How are they seeing us?
Mercenaries?
No. That's a homemade
drone. Purgers.
(MAN SHOUTING INDISTINCTLY
OVER DRONE)
SENATOR ROAN: Now what?
Run. Fast.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER
CONTINUES OVER DRONE)
Come, come, come!
It's behind you, Leo.
Thirty-five yards back, 15 yards up.
(BOTH PANTING)
(SCREAMING)
(GUNSHOT)
(ALL GRUNTING)
Down!
(GUNSHOT)
(SCREAMS)
(BOTH GRUNTING)
(ELECTRICITY CRACKLING)
Reason I'm so hard on you, son,
like I am is
someday I'd like to
make you a partner.
Yep. Oh, boy. Coming here from
another country like you did.
Having your own business.
American dream
is still alive.
(MAN SHOUTING INDISTINCTLY)
WOMAN: Whoo-hoo!
(PURGERS SPEAKING RUSSIAN)
(INDISTINCT SHOUTING)
We love you, America. America is
the greatest country in the world.
WOMAN: We are gonna kill you.
(ALL CLAMORING)
(SPEAKING RUSSIAN)
We will now Purge.
We will torture you and violate
your flesh. (GRUNTING)
Remove your skin and
share in your blood.
This is the American way.
(GUNSHOTS)
JOE: Senator.
Come with us.
(SHUTTERS OPENING)
Whoa, whoa,
whoa, whoa...
(EXHALES)
Stay.
Yeah.
(EXHALES)
JOE: Well, this is my place.
You can stay all night
if you want to.
Now, I got to ask you 'cause
I'm just a nosey old dog.
What in the Mississippi fuck was you
doing outside on Purge Night, Senator?
(BREATHING DEEPLY)
Yeah.
There was an assassination
attempt on me.
I can't thank you enough, Mr...
I'm sorry, I know you told me.
Dixon. You can call me Joe, Senator.
Yeah.
Joe, I'm Charlie.
Charlie.
Yeah.
That's Marcos
right there.
Marcos is...
He's a fan of yours.
Hi, Marcos.
Hey, Senator.
He actually think you can
win this thing. Oh, yeah?
(LAUGHS) Shit! Tell her what
she need to do to win, Marcos.
No, it's not
my place to say.
Well, you saved my life, Marcos.
I'd like to hear it, please.
Florida is the key.
You have to get
the elders.
That's smart.
He's not wrong, Joe.
What do you think?
I don't think you
got a damn chance.
Well, have
a little faith.
Well, I lost my faith in the system
a long time ago, Senator. Water?
Thank you.
Place is moderately secure. Cameras.
Maybe we stay here.
"Maybe we stay here"? Where you going?
You going back out there?
Joe, do you have a first aid kit?
Leo, my security, was shot.
I'm fine.
You're not fine.
You're not. Sit.
You want me
to take it off?
(SIGHS)
It's okay.
It's nothing.
Yeah? Doesn't
look like nothing.
(GROANS) Let me see.
Let me see.
I know a little bit about first aid.
I could help you.
The bullet's deep.
You need stitches.
Yeah.
But we can't
do that here.
Right. Clean it up. Patch it up.
Come on. Move.
Okay.
Fast. Come on.
(LEO WINCING)
What about you guys?
Who are you?
Is this necessary?
It's very necessary.
You, what's your name?
Where you from?
Marcos Dali.
Mexico City.
But I've been an American
citizen for two years.
You got a record?
Not here.
What did you do
in Mexico?
I tried to survive.
What are you doing
out on Purge Night?
Protecting the deli
against looters
because my boss lost his
Purge insurance yesterday.
Yeah, that's something
you can look into, Senator.
Insurance companies
screwing the working man.
Yeah?
What's your
name, pal?
You know what,
Mr. Secret Service Man?
You should be thanking my
black ass for helping you
instead of
interrogating me.
SENATOR ROAN:
His name is Joe Dixon.
LEO: Joe Dixon, have I offended you?
JOE: Yeah.
Yeah, man,
just a little bit.
Your feelings are
not a concern of mine.
Little respect.
That's all I need.
Everyone shut up,
please!
SENATOR ROAN: What?
Look.
(LAUGHTER)
KIMMY: You stupid
motherfucker!
You should have let
us take the candy bar!
Now, you're gonna fuckin' pay for it,
you stupid son of a bitch!
Whoo!
It's a good night
to Purge, isn't it?
Oh, hell!
Who the hell
is that?
The looters I was
telling you about.
Purge Night, Senator.
What did you expect?
(KIMMY SCREAMS)
Hey, you old fuck!
I'm back.
And I brought
some friends.
And I'm gonna
get that candy bar.
They have chainsaws
and they're coming inside.
All right. I got to
get you outta here.
Yeah, but they're
at both entrances.
Then I'm gonna Purge by killing you
and burning this bitch to the ground!
I gotta call her.
Who?
We have a friend out
there in a triage van.
You trust this friend?
Hey, you still
questioning my integrity.
Boy, you are
a piece of work, man.
(SIGHS) Come on,
girl, pick up.
RONDO: Those motherfuckers
blindsided us, man.
I gotta get back out there.
No, no, no.
You're not going anywhere.
I told your mom I'd look after you.
Just hurry up. Hurry up and bandage
me up so I can get back out there.
Okay, you promised me you
were gonna stay home tonight.
Well, I want
to Purge tonight.
No.
I want to Purge.
Laney, what? Laney!
(BREATHING DEEPLY)
For real, Laney?
Yeah. For real.
You heard me right.
Senator Roan.
Call me back, Lane.
We need you bad.
(GIRLS SHOUTING OUTSIDE)
(SIGHS)
She'll call back.
We can't count on your friend.
These kids will be in here soon.
What do we do?
Okay.
We're gonna work as a team
to protect this woman.
You gentlemen understand
what's at stake here, yes?
Yes? All right.
Yes.
(SINGING) We are gonna
Purge today
Purge today, Purge today
We are gonna Purge today
Burn this bitch down
Fuck!
Okay, you take the back,
I'm gonna take the front.
I'll take the front
with you.
No, you're not gonna
be on the frontline.
Are you crazy, Leo?
Give me a gun.
I will give you a gun, but you're not
on the frontline. Over my dead body.
Then you better
drop dead.
JOE: I think
he's right, Senator.
Thank you, Deli Man.
Deli Man? I agree with you,
you still throwing attitude?
Okay, enough!
Executive decision.
I'm with Leo. We need as
many guns as we can get.
(WHIRRING)
Go, go, go!
Move, move, move!
Down.
Just point and shoot.
Do not shoot me.
(WHIRRING CONTINUES)
KIMMY: If I want some candy,
I'll take some candy!
I'll take whatever
the fuck I want!
My mom's not
gonna like this!
KIMMY: This is what the Purge is all about.
Me getting mine.
You getting yours and
nobody stopping anybody!
Bye-bye, motherfucker!
Say goodnight, cocksucker.
Because here comes your candy girl!
Here they come.
(ALL LAUGHING)
BIKINI GIRL: Fucking asshole!
(LAUGHING)
Hold on!
(TIRES SCREECHING)
Wait here.
(COCKING)
(YELLING)
(COCKING GUN)
Pequeña Muerte
is back, bitches.
(BANGING)
LANEY: Hey, guys!
I got your message.
Laney!
This is our girl.
Go, go, go!
Holy shit,
it really is you.
Where do we go?
The van.
LEO: Go.
LANEY: Come on, Joe.
I'll be with you in a minute.
I'll be there.
(WHIRRING)
(SIGHS)
Joe, come on.
You get out of here,
kid. I'm staying.
They'll kill you.
JOE: Go now!
If you stay, I stay.
Just leave.
Joe, listen to me.
For some reason, the Senator
ended up in our neighborhood,
in your deli.
Maybe it's our duty
to help protect her.
We'll rebuild the deli.
Whatever it takes, you and me. I promise.
LANEY: Come on, guys. Now!
Where we headed?
Underground triage center
service in the community.
It's completely secure.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER
ON RADIO)
Expand our perimeter. They're on foot.
They can't be far.
MERC: Earl, spoke
with the ground unit.
Tommy regained
consciousness.
Says he got a shot off
at the Senator's security.
He thinks the bullet
is lodged in his shoulder.
(CHUCKLES)
(SQUELCHING)
(YELLING)
How the hell did
it get to this?
(CLEARS THROAT)
Who is he?
Why is he cuffed?
Rondo. Two bullet holes delivered by
a rival gang, but he's a good kid.
He's chained up because I didn't
want him Purging anymore.
So, Senator...
NFFA made a move
on your ass.
Seems that way.
Goddamn conniving, duplicitous,
crooked, cocksucking politicians.
Agreed.
We're not
all that bad.
My experience, Senator?
My people are on our own, no matter
what you all say or promise.
I'm kinda confused here.
Who the hell is this lady?
(SCOFFS)
You big dope!
You give people from the
neighborhood a bad name.
(GUNSHOTS)
LEO: Just some Purgers.
That's crossfire.
Not for us.
You seem really close.
How do you know
each other?
Joe gave me a job seven years ago
when I first came here from Mexico.
I've been working
for him ever since.
And you?
Joe's been looking out
for me since I was a kid.
And he helped me
get out of the life.
Sounds like Joe
is a saint.
Yeah, well,
I ain't no saint.
I'm just doing my part.
Riding around in a van,
on Purge Night, helping people?
It's pretty dangerous.
Unwritten Purge rule is leave
the triage units alone.
It's true,
for the most part.
Seriously, Laney, who the
hell are these people?
LANEY: (LAUGHING) Do you read?
(GUNSHOTS)
LEO: Down! Everybody down!
Anybody hit?
SENATOR ROAN: I'm okay. I'm okay. I'm okay.
You sure?
Yes.
JOE: Laney!
I'm okay.
Oh, Jesus Christ!
Rondo is dead.
(GRUNTS) What the fuck was that?
They found us, Senator.
(HELICOPTER BLADES WHIRRING)
I want you to turn left!
Go under the freeway.
Move! Move!
Yes.
MAN: Tonight,
the gates of hell will
open and invite me in.
It's survival of
the fucking fittest.
Who's the fittest?
I'm the fittest of them all!
What the fuck? We're gonna
lose them under there.
Ground unit,
get your asses moving
and get here now.
We got them cornered.
(ALL YELLING)
(METAL CLANGING)
(ROARING)
Turn here and stop.
(YELLING CONTINUES)
Do we just
wait here?
No, they'll have units on the ground.
They're gonna be all over us.
We all better figure it out fast
'cause I don't like it here.
SENATOR ROAN:
It doesn't make any sense.
There was no way they could've
known we'd be in this van.
Doesn't matter.
They did.
You son of a bitch.
Leo?
Move.
(WINCES)
Leo.
(LEO MOANS)
(BREATHING DEEPLY)
SENATOR ROAN: Oh!
Leo, what the hell
are you doing?
Leo, what...
(GRUNTING)
(SENATOR ROAN GASPS)
Trace bullet.
That's how he found us.
Just leave it
here and drive away.
They'll never know
we left here.
Yeah, well, I wish it were that simple.
You all need to see this.
There's a whole bunch of
negroes coming right this way.
And we sitting up here
like a bucket of motherfucking chicken.
(COCKING)
(BEEPING)
What's your ETA?
Two minutes, Earl.
MAN: Open the door, now!
(ALL CLAMORING)
What are we gonna do?
They'll start
blasting if we move.
They'll start blasting
if we don't.
Open the door!
Open the door, now!
MAN: Open the goddamn doors!
What's the plan?
(ALL SHOUTING)
(WHISTLING)
MAN: Yo, yo, yo!
Quiet down! Quiet down!
What the hell is that?
MAN: Quiet down!
MAN: I know what I heard.
I know what I heard.
(MAN WHISTLING)
I told you I ain't no saint.
Everybody's got a past.
That was a Crip whistle.
They just threw it back.
If this is the right set,
we should be good.
MAN: I know, I know
what I heard. I know.
All right.
We're not gonna hurt you.
Just help my fuckin' boy. He's gonna die.
We help you,
you do something
for us.
(BEEPING CONTINUES)
They're still under the overpass,
but they're on the move.
Get your asses in there.
(BEEPING)
They stopped.
Stop the truck.
We're going on foot.
(BEEPING CONTINUES)
(BEEPING RAPIDLY)
Clear!
(BEEPING STOPS)
Earl, we found the trace bullet,
but no sign of the target.
Yeah, we're heading back.
(WHISTLING)
Ground unit, come in.
Come in, I need a fuckin' sitrep.
(GUNSHOTS)
(GANG MEMBER LAUGHING)
GANG MEMBER ON RADIO:
Fuck you, motherfucker!
No one following.
We're clear.
DAWN: We're a few blocks away.
I'm gonna call in and tell
them we have a special guest.
Where are we?
You'll see.
(MEN CHATTERING)
What is this place?
We call this
a Safe Zone.
Senator, Dante Bishop.
Mr. Bishop.
This is Angel.
Dawn called. Told me you
guys were coming through.
So the NFFA came
at you tonight?
Can't say
I'm surprised.
Let me show you around,
get you settled in.
You set all this
up, Mr. Bishop?
Yes, this is
my organization.
We have doctors, and
nurses, EMTs, paramedics.
This is their way of
protesting this damn night.
LEO: How many people
know about this place?
Just the volunteers, and the
homeless that we invite in.
Look, these are the real
victims of the Purge.
The people that the NFFA
are trying to eliminate
so that they don't have to
take care of them anymore.
These men that are armed,
you'll have them at all the
entrances and the rooftop?
Yes. My men will
keep you safe.
Or as safe as you
can be on Purge Night.
Appreciate it.
Mr. Bishop.
Yeah.
Thank you, for all of this.
I am impressed.
Well, don't thank me.
Thank the volunteers.
Mr. Bishop,
I've heard stories
of tactics that you
employ on Purge Night.
I can't say that
I agree with any of it.
I'll tell you what.
You get elected,
you stop this night,
and I don't have
to do what I do anymore.
Let's go, Angel.
Fair enough.
BISHOP: You hold down
the fort here.
Keep an eye on her. And keep her
and her people quiet. Okay?
All right,
let's go!
I want access to every
surveillance camera in the city.
We'll do a grid search
for that fucking triage van.
It's out there somewhere.
Find it.
Yeah.
Your crew? Your guys?
They feel like family?
Boss.
We did the
right thing.
Yeah.
But it's time to go.
Gotta get back
to the deli.
What? No. Are you fucking crazy?
We're safe here.
Laney, you know I'll
walk back if I have to.
Fine. I'll drive you.
But if we run into any problems,
we're coming right back here.
Deal.
SENATOR ROAN:
Really? Can you do that?
We'll see her
again, Marcos.
And she's safe here.
Let's hit it.
I don't know, but I bet it
was really cool. (LAUGHS)
It is, it is.
Hey, you okay?
Yeah, I'm okay.
Good.
I'm gonna go take a look around.
Okay.
Stay here.
Okay, boss.
What are you
doing here?
Hand.
Why are you here?
(GRUNTING)
(CLATTERING)
What the hell's
going on here?
He was snooping around!
Hey, hey! Okay, okay, okay.
Hey! Hey.
It's all right. It's all right.
Red, back up.
It's okay. (MAN CHOKING)
Just put the gun down, all right?
Everybody's okay.
Back up.
We're okay.
All right?
We're good.
It's all good, okay?
I'm just getting
my weapon.
What's going on?
Just doing my job.
Senator, it's just
a misunderstanding.
Why don't we
go back outside?
Come on.
SENATOR ROAN:
Are you seeing this, Leo?
LEO: Yes, Senator.
Senator, why don't
we go outside...
Stop.
Those are the Minister's
biggest financial supporters.
The NFFA.
Our Lady of Sorrows.
Is that where the Minister is going
to be tonight for the Purge Mass?
We believe so.
You believe... (SCOFFS)
What is all this?
Why do you have all this?
You're gonna assassinate him.
You're gonna assassinate the
Minister tonight, aren't you?
You know, somebody's
got to say it out loud.
What in the fuck
happened tonight?
Nobody's gonna
believe it.
Mmm-hmm.
Irish Ike's gonna
be like, "Bullshit.
"Now where's my waffles and pussy?"
"...and pussy?"
(ALL LAUGHING)
He got that
one-track mind.
That boy done
lost his mind.
Shit.
I hope he's
okay tonight.
Yeah.
Hold on, guys.
Look.
Those are
government trucks.
I saw them on YouTube
from last year's Purge.
And they're going straight
back towards the Safe Zone.
You cannot do this. I need to win
this thing fair and fucking square.
They are not playing fair and fucking
square and neither should we.
This church will be
locked up like Fort Knox.
You'll never get through.
You're gonna get slaughtered.
Four churches were
built on that site.
The original by your boy George
Washington over 200 years ago.
The man liked to have escape tunnels
attached to all his structures.
They're all over D.C.
The tunnel under
the original church
has been closed up
since the '50s.
But we reopened it.
We're gonna walk
right through there
and into that church without
anybody even knowing it.
The original Founding Fathers are about
to fuck over the New Founding Fathers.
Now how you like
that for irony?
How do you know where
this mass is gonna be?
Because we do whatever it takes.
We did this for you, Senator.
No, it's not for me. Get your boss
on the phone. I need to talk to him.
He's not here.
Angel, listen to me.
You call him.
You tell him he does this and
the Minister becomes a martyr.
I cannot have my presidency
built on murder. You see that.
He will not leave
this to the voters.
He does not believe
in the American system.
Angel, believe in me.
I can make this happen.
We do. That's why we're
trying to pave a way for you
to the White House
so you can make changes.
SENATOR ROAN: You're gonna
cost me the White House.
It's Laney. She says there's
trucks approaching us.
What?
Who is that?
Government soldiers.
That's the NFFA eliminating
all their enemies this year.
They're here for Bishop,
but they will kill you.
You need to evacuate your people.
We can't move the injured.
I need to get her out of here now.
There's a way out back.
LEO: Where does it
come out?
The alleyway down to
Third and Thompson.
LEO: Third and Thompson.
Give me the phone.
Laney, I need you
at Third and Thompson now.
Yeah, we'll meet
you there.
(TIRES SCREECHING)
So, we're driving right
back into that war zone?
Stupid!
(ALL CHATTERING)
All these people.
We'll protect them.
Please, stop
the assassination.
It's too late. Now go.
Stay safe. Go!
So what we supposed to be, like
some superheroes or something?
That ain't what I do.
I hate this night!
Ah, shit. Hell with it.
Come on. Shit.
Let's do it.
Let's go get 'em.
I can't believe
we're outside again.
I'm gonna get
you through this.
(WIRE TWANGING)
(MAN EXCLAIMING)
MAN 1: My God, it's so close!
MAN 2: At your own risk now!
(LAUGHING)
Are you fucking
kidding me?
Ready?
Yeah.
One.
MAN 2: Go for it!
Two.
MAN 1: Try your luck!
Go!
(MEN MOANING)
MAN 2: Good luck out there!
(SINGING) Let me
hear you whisper
That you love me too
Keep the love-light glowing
in your eyes so true
JOE: Let's go, let's go!
Come on, I got you.
LANEY: You guys okay?
LEO: Yeah.
SENATOR ROAN:
Thank you. Again.
LANEY: Where we headed?
Drive. Out of this city.
Get us out of here.
(BREATHING DEEPLY)
You okay, Senator?
No, Marcos. I'm not.
This night
corrupts everyone.
Senator.
I can't win like this.
It goes against everything
that I believe in.
We need to focus on one thing
right now and that's survival.
I need to make sure you
get through this night.
I have to stop them
from killing the Minister.
What?
If they assassinate him,
he becomes a martyr. We lose.
Yeah. And how
do we do that?
I don't know.
We have to do something.
Do what? Do what? You're willing to
risk your life to save an assassin...
(THUDDING)
(TIRES SCREECHING)
(LEO GROANS)
(PANTING)
(GRUNTING)
LEO: Everybody all right?
LANEY: Joe, you okay?
JOE: (GROANING) I'll be okay.
SENATOR ROAN: Leo!
LEO: Gun! (GRUNTS)
(TIRES SCREECHING)
(MAGAZINE CLATTERS)
(LANEY GASPING)
I know where they're taking her.
I know why she's still alive.
Where?
You find a safe place
to hide and you stay there.
No. No way.
Whatever it is you plan on doing,
we're coming with you.
Let's go.
(SCREAMING)
(MUFFLED GRUNTS)
(CONTINUES GRUNTING)
CHOIR: May the Purge
protect us. Keep us pure.
Purge and purify.
May the Purge cleanse us.
Keep us pure.
Purge and purify.
May the Purge cleanse us.
Keep us pure.
Purge and purify.
Come on, guys,
that's enough.
We're getting paid to deliver
the package, not gift-wrap it.
Come on, let's go find a place to wait
out the rest of this fucking night, huh.
(MUFFLED MOANS)
MINISTER OWENS:
As we always do.
ALL: Blessed be
the New Founding Fathers
for letting us Purge
and cleanse our souls.
Blessed be America,
a nation reborn.
Well, it's been
a long journey
to get away from the lies
and the self-deception
to this place of knowledge and
awareness of who we really are.
People of flesh,
immensely flawed.
It's hard to see
the ugly truth.
But change can only
come from acceptance.
And change we must,
as it is our godly duty
to get rid of the fury
and the hatred
that poisons our souls,
makes us sick.
Makes us ugly.
Tonight,
we, the leaders of
this great country,
will sin, scour, sanitize
and sterilize our souls
until we are free again, and this
country will be better for it.
We are not hypocrites!
We practice what we preach.
Purge and purify!
Say it with me.
ALL: Purge and purify!
Purge and purify!
Let us begin.
All right, look, it's after midnight.
We need to move.
I need a four-man
team in there.
I need three with me.
Got it? Go!
LEO: Bishop!
Bishop!
I'm unarmed.
How well do you
know this Dante?
Not well. So keep
your eye on him.
JOE: Our boy is gonna
get himself killed.
LEO: I'm unarmed.
You know this
lunatic, Dante?
Yeah. I do.
Guns down.
What the hell
are you doing here?
Trying to get
yourself killed?
Is that the tunnel
for the cathedral?
How the fuck do you
know about the tunnel?
I asked you a question.
This is no longer an assassination.
This is a rescue mission.
MINISTER OWENS:
Jesus died for their sins.
(MUMBLING)
And now,
our modern-day martyrs
will die for our trespasses.
Our martyr's name
is Lawrence.
A lifelong drug addict.
He wants to make amends.
He wants to serve his God
and his government.
Let's thank Lawrence
for his gift.
ALL: Thank you, Lawrence.
Thank you for your gift, Lawrence.
Thank you very much, Lawrence.
We love you,
Lawrence.
(SHUDDERING)
These weapons have been
cleansed with holy water,
and they are now
instruments of destruction.
(GRUNTING) Fuck!
You all know
the loyal Harmon James.
Worked with the NFFA
tirelessly for many years.
Harmon will be the first
Purger of the evening.
LAWRENCE: I'm sorry. No, no, no. Please,
please, please, please. No, no, no.
Please, no, no!
I'm sorry! No, please!
No! I'm sorry!
Please, no, no!
Please, no!
Please! No!
Please, please!
I'm sorry!
Release, Harmon.
No!
SENATOR ROAN: No!
(SQUELCHING) Release the violence
from your darkened heart!
Scour your soul.
Let the light in.
You are blood-baptized.
And you are born again!
(BOTH GASPING)
His light entered
your heart, Harmon.
Yeah. (LAUGHS)
The power of Purging!
ALL: Purge and purify!
Purge and purify!
JOE: Psst.
No matter what happens,
we stay together.
All right, this takes us
to the mechanical room.
From there, we can
access the cathedral.
(GRUNTS)
Stay there.
Where do we go?
The church is above us.
So are 50 Secret Service agents.
You're gonna take the
staircase to the balcony.
Me and my guys, we're gonna enter from
behind the altar and this side here.
Okay, good. Let's go
get our girl, yeah?
Before we get to our communal Purge,
the Holy Horde of Many Martyrs,
I'd like to introduce
a guest
who's going to be the centerpiece of a
very special Purge ceremony tonight.
This person
has threatened to
dismantle everything
that we, New Founding
Fathers, have done.
We must rid ourselves
of the negative emotions
that she has stirred inside.
We must stop her from
poisoning our great country
by taking away
our freedoms.
Yes!
(APPLAUSE)
I would like all the Founding
Fathers to come to the altar.
Join me, brothers,
as we eliminate evil
and Purge as one.
(SINGING) There is a fountain
filled with blood
Drawn from Immanuel's veins
And sinners,
plunged beneath that flood
Lose all their
guilty stains
(SINGING CONTINUES INDISTINCTLY)
Lord of Air,
Lord of Earth,
we ask that you receive this
child into your loving arms.
We are sinners.
Let us release.
Caleb, our leader,
I invite you, sir,
to lead us in this Purging
as you have
and as you will.
Blessed be our New Founding
Fathers for letting us Purge.
(BOTH GRUNTING)
Blessed be America,
a nation reborn.
Rifle!
(ALL SCREAMING)
(GUNSHOTS FIRING)
She's alive.
Down!
(GUNFIRE STOPS)
BISHOP: Where you all at?
The hell are you
all doing up there?
Bring your asses
down here.
(LAUGHING)
My negro.
Let's go.
Thank you.
MAN: I got you. I got you.
Hi.
You okay?
Yeah.
Thank you. Again.
(GUNSHOTS)
What was that?
My men taking care of business.
Go cover me.
We're headed out.
Back exit. We have her.
MAN: And we have him.
Move.
Hey!
SENATOR ROAN: Listen to me.
BISHOP: Get off of me.
Mr. Bishop. Please.
LEO: Watch our backs.
Just take a second
and listen to me.
BISHOP: It's on our way to the exit.
I can win without this.
SENATOR ROAN: Please!
Cover our backs.
BISHOP: You will win.
I'm gonna make sure that happens.
Open up!
Stop.
This is murder.
If you do this,
you will be no
different than them.
Get her.
LEO: Nope! Don't.
Listen to her.
She knows
what she's doing.
We don't need to do this.
MAN: Hang on, Dante.
Get the fuck
out of my way.
Wait, please!
(PANTING)
Don't do this.
If you do this, you will
be no different than them.
We can't be like them.
Look at me.
(SOFTLY) Purge,
my son.
Purge.
It's your right
as an American.
Kill me. Kill me.
Purge.
You're a son of God.
God wants you to Purge.
Shut the fuck up!
Coward.
Purge!
Do it! Do it! Yes! Yes!
Kill me!
Now, I'm gonna tell you right
now, I like black people,
but I ain't gonna let you all
shoot these white folks.
These are our white people.
Okay?
So, let's put 'em down.
(SHUDDERING)
You better fucking win.
Go. Go.
Move!
Oh, my God.
You murderous pig.
I am gonna beat the shit out
of you on election day.
I'm not as politically
correct as the Senator.
(GRUNTING)
(GROANING)
Good night,
blue cheese.
Well played, Leo.
Thanks, Joe.
Come on, man.
No, I'm not gonna hurt you.
(MUFFLED MOANING)
We have to get
you out of there.
BISHOP: Stay here,
we'll find a vehicle.
SENATOR ROAN:
What about these people?
Back, back, back!
Get back!
LEO: You got this.
You know I got this.
How bad is it?
Not good.
Look, I got one more move in me.
Cover me. Go!
(SCREECHING)
(EXCLAIMING)
Shh! Be quiet!
Shut him up before he draws
the wrong kind of attention.
(GRUNTING)
(SCREAMING)
You motherfucker!
(GRUNTING)
Get up.
(GRUNTS)
Motherfucker.
Okay. No, it's okay. You're safe.
Thank you.
I gotta get the fuck outta here!
Let me out! Let me out!
SENATOR ROAN: Stop him!
(GRUNTS)
(GUN COCKING)
(GROANS)
Joe!
Joe?
You're gonna be okay,
Joe. Come on.
We gotta get you
somewhere, okay?
You're gonna be okay.
I promise you.
There's nowhere
to take me.
You're gonna be fine.
That's what's important.
She's gonna make sure of it.
Right, Senator?
Yeah.
You got this.
I got this.
(GASPS)
Marcos...
MARCOS: Joe, Joe, Joe.
Breathe, Joe, breathe.
(SOBBING) No.
LANEY: Wake up, Joe.
Wake up!
(SOBBING) Joe!
MALE REPORTER: That was
Senator Roan this morning,
casting the first
vote of the day.
It's been a great day
for the senator so far,
having already won New York,
California, and...
Wait, hold on, I am
getting word, right now,
that the Senator has
also taken Florida,
which puts her well over the 270
electoral votes for the win.
So that is it.
It is now official, the next President of
the United States will be Charlie Roan.
And President-elect Roan has already
stated that her first order of business
will be taking executive action
to put an end to the Purge.
LANEY: Updates?
It's a landslide.
All right, I'll come by tomorrow.
We can get started on the ceiling.
Sounds good.
This place is really
coming along, Marcos.
Joe would be
really happy.
I'll catch you
later, kid.
MALE REPORTER: We're just
now hearing reports
about a few scattered
incidents around the country
where NFFA supporters are reacting
violently to this defeat.
They are burning cars, breaking windows,
looting, attacking police officers...
(ROCK MUSIC PLAYING)
Please rate this subtitle at www.osdb.link/49866
Help other users to choose the best subtitles