Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
Cardinal Richelieu,
these men they...
Please help me, your eminence.
Please, please have mercy. Please.
He defaced your carriage
and stole valuables from inside.
But it's just a coach.
Please, I was hungry.
My family hasn't eaten for days.
Please. Please.
In the name of God, I beg you.
Very well.
In the name of God.
Oh, thank you, your eminence.
Your place in heaven
will always be assured.
Of course.
No! No! Don't!
No! Please!
Please! God, no!
One less mouth to feed.
Getting sloppy, Girard.
Why don't you do yourself a favor?
Surrender.
My sister's honor is at stake.
How many times do I have to tell you?
Nothing happened.
I know what I saw, D'Artagnan.
Girard, I told her
I was leaving for Paris.
She wanted to give me somethin'
to remember her by.
Liar!
This is stupid, Girard.
All I wanna do is get to Paris...
and join the Musketeers.
You, a Musketeer?
Fantasy!
My father was a Musketeer,
the king's personal bodyguard.
The king was assassinated.
Your father was a failure,
a disgrace to the Musketeers.
What did you say?
Your father was a disgrace.
My brothers will avenge me.
Already?
Charge! Charge!
Get him! He's mine!
Come back! Come back!
Ooh!
He went that way!
Yeah!
We'll get you, D'Artagnan!
In the meantime,
give my regards to your sister.
What should I do
with the Musketeer flag?
Burn it.
Musketeers.
By joint edict of his majesty
the King Louis XIII...
And his eminence Cardinal Richelieu,
the Musketeers are officially disbanded.
In preparation
for the coming war with England,
the ranks and commissions
are forthwith transferred to the infantry.
You shall be notified
and told where to report.
Until such time,
return to your homes.
And who will protect the king?
The cardinal's guards
have already assumed that responsibility.
You are ordered to disperse.
Should even one of you resist,
the entire corps will be arrested
and imprisoned.
All for one...
And one for all.
Well, there's nothing
more to be said, is there?
Your eminence.
An impressive performance.
I especially admired
that last touch...
"All for one and one for all."
If I didn't know better, I should
have thought you wanted them to riot.
It would have given us an excuse
to arrest them.
Hardly necessary.
The Musketeers are finished.
Not entirely.
There are three.
Three?
I sent a patrol to find them.
They haven't returned yet.
I want those Musketeers,
not excuses.
Bring them in at once!
Follow me.
No loose ends this time,
Captain Rochefort.
Athos.
Porthos.
Aramis.
Hyah! Hyah! Hyah!
Hyah! Hyah!
Ohh!
Whoa!
Do you have any idea
what you've done?
I've saved you and your friend
from these bandits.
These bandits are
the queen's own bodyguards.
The queen?
I'm sorry. I had no idea.
- What's your name?
- D'Artagnan.
D'Artagnan. A gascon?
I've come to Paris
to join the Musketeers.
Then I'm sure I'll be
hearing your name again.
Would that please you?
Ladies-in-waiting are forbidden
to socialize with Musketeers.
Well, I'm not a Musketeer yet.
With that kind of courage,
you will be one soon enough.
Good luck, D'Artagnan.
And thank you for the entertainment.
I enjoyed it immensely.
Wait! You didn't tell me your name!
Constance!
Constance.
Come along.
Is this Musketeer headquarters?
No, this was Musketeer headquarters.
Oh, you mean it's been moved.
No, I mean the Musketeers
have been disbanded. They no longer exist.
Feel free to poke around for souvenirs
if you wish.
But I just got here.
How am I supposed to become
a Musketeer if they've been disbanded?
I'd say you've got quite a problem.
You're not being very helpful.
You need a lesson in manners, boy.
Anytime.
Why don't you meet me outside the city,
by the ruins?
Let's say noon?
I'll be there!
There he is.
Come on! Out of my way, man!
Out of my way!
How dare you touch me?
D'Artagnan!
Get your hands off me!
Here. Hold this horse for me, all right?
I'll be right back.
You got it? Thank you.
- Sorry. Sorry.
- Excuse me!
This sash was a gift to me
from the queen of America.
There's no
queen of America.
I beg to differ, infant.
We're on quite intimate terms
unless you can prove otherwise.
Here's my proof.
Oh, I see.
It's twit of the month.
Come to challenge the mighty Porthos.
- Thinks he's lightning with a sword.
- The mighty who?
Don't tell me you've never heard of me.
The world's biggest windbag?
Little pimple, meet me
behind the Luxembourg at one o'clock,
and bring a long wooden box.
Bring your own.
"God took them and put them
in the garden to till it and care for it,
"but of the fruit of the tree,
which is in the midst of the garden,
"God hath said,
'Ye shall not eat of it.
"Neither shall ye touch it, lest ye die.'
"Then the serpent said
unto the woman, 'Ye...'"
Madam, I'm flattered,
but I am here to tutor you in theology.
Forgive me, Monsieur Aramis,
but when you started talking
about original sin,
I lost control
and became impassioned.
It won't happen again.
Please go on.
Well, there's nothing unholy
about expressing one's emotions.
On the contrary,
religion should be experienced
in an all-embracing way.
We should feel free to
express our spirituality.
Yes, darling.
- Let me in!
- My husband!
- You're married?
- Yes, I'm married.
Ohh. We must pray for our sins.
On second thought, God's often busy.
- Out of my way, woman!
- No! Stop!
Ahh! Thank you.
You broke my fall perfectly.
- But I do apologize for the inconvenience.
- Get off of me!
If there's one thing I can't abide,
it's rudeness.
- You fell on me.
- And I apologized for it.
Well, your apology's not accepted.
I hope your sword is
as quick as your mouth.
- It's quicker.
- Ahh.
A duel then.
A duel.
Meet me behind the Carmes-Deschaux
monastery at 2:00.
- I'll be there.
- As will I.
Three duels in one day.
Homesick?
Cardinal Richelieu, you surprised me.
I often have that effect on people.
I can't imagine why.
I'm really a very gentle person.
You seem a little unhappy
in your new home.
Lonely.
Is that the same thing?
Austria's loss is France's gain.
I'm not sure the king
shares your opinion.
We've barely spoken
since our wedding day.
Whenever we're together,
he seems so...
uncertain.
Arranged marriages can be difficult.
Your father and I thought yours
would bring Austria and France
closer together.
Countries align more swiftly
than people, I'm afraid.
What a pity.
Love is, I think,
wasted on the young.
His majesty, the king.
Cardinal Richelieu,
I've been looking for you.
Your majesty.
Anne, I didn't know you were here.
- Would you like me to go?
- No. Please stay.
Your eminence, I demand an answer.
Perhaps if I knew the question.
I just learned that you went ahead
and disbanded my Musketeers.
- You approved the decision.
- But not the timing.
I intended to address them myself
and explain the situation.
These men are not just my personal guards.
They are my friends.
A thousand apologies, your majesty.
We are on the brink of war with England.
The Duke of Buckingham plans
to invade La Rochelle within the month,
and we'll need the Musketeers in the field
if we are to defeat him.
I thought it best to act quickly.
I will be the judge of what is best,
for me and for France!
Of course.
Forgive me.
He is becoming as troublesome
as his father.
He's a foolish boy and barely that.
That foolish boy is about to become a man,
which is all the more reason
for us to act quickly.
- Have our loose ends been tied up?
- Two patrols have been sent.
I trust, Captain Rochefort,
that you are doing everything
in your power to rid us of these rebels.
Don't let having only one eye
impair your vision.
The loss of the other could be most...
inconvenient.
What is this?
We are having a private party,
celebrating the demise of the Musketeers.
Go away.
Athos, is that any way
to greet our guests?
Gentlemen, don't be shy.
Come in.
Your friends have been expecting you.
You're under arrest.
Under whose authority?
Mine.
Ah, hello again, Cyclops.
Let's see. When was the last time
we had the pleasure of his company?
I believe it was the day he was cast out
of the Musketeers.
Conduct unbecoming a Musketeer.
That was the charge, was it not?
You should know.
Three of you stood against me.
It was the least
we could do.
You are hereby ordered to surrender
your tunics and your commissions at once.
You can, of course, refuse,
become outlaws, hunted men.
But why not
come along quietly...
For old times' sake?
Did I miss anyone?
Congratulations, Porthos.
You brought down the house.
Oh, drat.
I was trying to hit Rochefort.
You go back, and you
tell the cardinal...
We will continue
to perform our sworn duty,
which is to protect the king.
And we will use every means
within our power to fight him.
Bold words.
I look forward
to ramming them down your throat.
Rochefort. Isn't that
a smelly kind of a cheese?
Your manners
have not improved yet.
- You're late.
- You in a hurry to die?
Here come
the grave diggers now.
Athos, you cannot fight this boy.
- Why not?
- I'm fighting him.
Not until 1 o'clock.
- I have a duel with him, too.
- Not until 2 o'clock.
Let's get on with it then.
Wouldn't want you to be late
for your future engagements.
You're a Musketeer?
You're all Musketeers?
You choose your opponents well.
- Or should I say foolishly?
- I've been looking all over for you.
Now you've found us.
We have some business to attend to...
Unless, of course,
you'd like to make it for a later date.
No.
I'm a man of honor.
But believe me when I say that
killing you will bring me no pleasure.
I'll be with you
gentlemen in a moment.
- Oh, he's a feisty little fellow.
- Feisty indeed.
There they are!
Only a fool would try and
arrest us twice in one day.
You're under arrest.
- A fool.
The boy's of no interest to me.
He's free to go.
You coming peacefully,
or do you intend to resist?
Oh, don't be so stupid.
Of course we intend to resist.
Just give us a moment, all right?
Five of them, three of us.
Hardly seems fair.
Maybe we should give them a chance
- to surrender?
- Hmm.
Excuse me, but there's four of us.
It's not your fight.
You're not a Musketeer.
I may not wear the tunic,
but I believe I have
the heart of a Musketeer.
- Warrior.
- Poet.
You got a name, boy?
D'Artagnan.
- Athos, Porthos and Aramis.
- Hello.
- Nice to meet you again.
- Pleasure.
Everyone acquainted?
Now we are prepared to resist you.
Aha!
Oh!
God, I love my work.
Take a look at our young friend.
My god, he's still alive.
May the lord forgive you for any sins
you may have committed.
Amen.
What's he doing?
Last rites.
Aramis takes death very seriously.
Is he a priest?
He used to be one of
the cardinal's students.
You, boy,
are arrogant, hot-tempered
and entirely too bold.
I like that.
Reminds me of me.
Don't encourage him.
By helping us, the boy
has made himself an outlaw as well.
- Not if he leaves Paris right now.
- I can't leave now.
- I just got here.
- Go home. Find a wench.
Raise fat babies.
Live a good long life.
All for one and one for all?
Wake up, boy.
The Musketeers are just a dream.
Hyah! Hyah! Hyah!
Hyah!
Halt! Whoa!
Whoa! Whoa!
Long live the Musketeers!
He's mine.
Whoa, whoa!
- My sword!
- It's magnificent.
Where did you steal it?
It belonged to my father.
Your father.
Well, now it
belongs to me.
I collect swords, you see.
I take them from men I've killed.
Well, I'm not dead yet.
You and the Musketeers are responsible
for the killing of the cardinal's guards,
an offense punishable by death.
They interrupted a duel
we were fighting.
- A deed also punishable by death.
- It's been a busy day.
Tell me where to find
the Musketeers...
And I will give you back
your father's sword.
Give me back my father's sword...
And I'll cut out your heart.
Idiot.
Like your father.
- Take him below.
- Yes, sir.
Hey, boy!
Leave us.
Milady de Winter.
Your eminence.
Your beauty would make
even the most chaste of men think of...
Impurity.
I don't believe you suffer
the burden of chastity.
Perhaps you're right.
I was making an observation,
not an offer.
A word of caution, milady.
A snap of my fingers and you could be
back on the block where I found you.
And with a flick of my wrist,
I could change your religion.
You're very persuasive.
For a moment, I forgot that your lovers
have a tendency to end up dead.
Love has its risks.
So does duty.
The precision with which you
disposed of your husband,
or should I say your ex-husband,
Lord de Winter, was commendable,
not to mention helpful to our cause.
- I do what is necessary.
- Yes.
I have a new mission
which requires your
- singular talent.
- What is it?
You will carry this treaty
to the Duke of Buckingham.
You're making an alliance with England?
The king has left me no choice.
The boy is beginning to believe
that he should rule France instead of me.
God forbid.
You're to leave at once for Calais.
A ship called the Persephone
will carry you to England.
She sails Tuesday at midnight.
Buckingham's signature
must be next to mine...
Before the king's birthday Friday.
Consider it done.
And doing so will earn
you the gratitude...
of a king.
Until that day,
your eminence.
Or should I say,
"your majesty"?
Majesty sounds good.
Looking for me?
Kneel. Were you taught no respect
for a man of God?
Cardinal Richelieu.
How much did you overhear?
Hardly a word, your eminence.
The voices were much too low.
- And with all the noise from the prison...
- What's your name, boy?
D'Artagnan.
Oh, yes.
Your father was a Musketeer.
He died while protecting the king.
The dream of every warrior...
dying nobly for king and country.
Tell me, D'Artagnan.
What noble business brings you here?
I came to join
the king's Musketeers.
Bad timing.
So I've heard.
Like the knights
of the round table,
the Musketeers have
outlived their usefulness...
And so have your three friends.
Tell me where they are,
and I will spare your life.
I can't tell you what I don't know.
Give my regards to the headsman
and your father.
Wait!
- You object to losing your head?
- Yes. I like it where it is.
Then tell me what I want to know,
and maybe you will keep it a while longer!
I don't know where they are.
And if you did?
I wouldn't tell you.
I admire your courage,
D'Artagnan.
You might have made
a fine Musketeer.
But now we'll never know, will we?
They're bringing him down.
It's your time, lad.
Step down.
Milady left at midnight
by private coach.
A remarkable woman.
The most beautiful I've ever known.
And the deadliest.
Which would explain my attraction.
How is our young daredevil holding up?
He's wishing he never
heard of the Musketeers.
D'Artagnan!
Don't lose your head!
Fear not, my son.
For we are with you always.
All for one...
And one for all.
Now this ax was a gift to me
from the czarina of Tokyo.
Stop! Stop! Stop! Stop!
Hyah!
My carriage!
Gentlemen, your carriage,
compliments of the cardinal.
Hyah! Hyah!
Stop! Follow them!
Come on! Come on!
D'Artagnan!
Aha! The cardinal's
sacred snack chamber.
And what have we here?
Is he a man of God
or a man of gold?
- Hyah!
- D'Artagnan!
Would you be so kind
as to redistribute this wealth?
Throw the coins, lad!
The people are hungry!
Well done.
Those Musketeers are a menace.
They must be stopped.
The boy knows our plans.
One thousand gold pieces
on each of their heads, dead or alive.
I prefer dead.
Hyah!
Hyah! Hyah!
They're firing at us!
Champagne?
We're in the middle
of a chase, Porthos.
You're right. Something red.
For a chase, the cardinal recommends
his excellent '24 cabernet.
- You can't have any. You're too young.
- Take the reins, boy.
Thank you.
The picnic was delicious.
The champagne was excellent.
Remind me to send
the cardinal a note.
The cardinal! We have to hurry!
You two have a date?
No, it's the cardinal.
He's conspiring against the king!
- Tell us something we don't know.
- He sent a messenger...
with a secret treaty
to man named Buckingham.
- The Duke of Buckingham?
- Do you know him?
He rules England the way
the cardinal rules France.
There's a ship called the Persephone.
It's waiting in Calais
to take the messenger to England.
It sails Tuesday midnight.
We get that treaty, we can prove
the cardinal guilty of treason.
Calais is over 200 leagues from here.
Is the cardinal aware of the fact
that you have this information?
Yes.
Turn here.
- Right here?
- Here!
That's it.
Next time you drive.
Hyah! Hyah!
Let's go! Hyah!
Hyah!
Gimme the reins!
- Hyah!
- Stop in the name of the cardinal!
Hyah!
- Over there! To your left!
- Stop the Musketeers!
Hyah!
Hyah! Hyah!
Unhitch the horses.
This is the end of the line, gentlemen.
I hope you enjoyed the ride.
- Very much so. Thank you.
- Porthos, the brandy.
Ooh, what a waste.
Up the hill!
They're over there!
- It's headed for the powder wagon!
- Run for it!
Run for it!
Hyah!
Your eminence, the Musketeers
have been sighted on the road to Calais.
Thanks to our winged friends,
every mercenary and bounty hunter
in France will be waiting for them.
All for one...
And more for me.
And I said, "Marquaise,
"as I told you
at the sausage festival,
"a queen is no different
from a barmaid in the dark,
"though less practiced
in the arts of massage."
Right? D'Artagnan, if you're going
to be a proper Musketeer,
you shall have to be schooled in the manly
art of wenching. Right, ladies?
Ooh. First subject.
Very good.
Very good indeed.
Let the schooling begin.
The secret to wenching
is in the first kiss.
For in that first kiss,
a lasting impression is made.
Right, ladies?
If it is... if it is weak,
she'll think you're weak.
If it is comical,
she'll think you a clown.
- With me?
- Weak, weak. Comical, clown.
And as a Musketeer is never weak
and only rarely a clown,
your first kiss...
must be all the things
that you are, like this.
Mmm.
See? You may, uh,
speak first if you like...
your name, her name,
an endearment or two.
Trust me, words are a complete waste
of time at this sensitive point.
Only the wrong words are
a complete waste of time.
The right words
can make a more lasting impression
than a thousand of Porthos' kisses.
- Not likely.
- Ah, see?
Shall I demonstrate?
As morning hues of sun-swept fire
caress your passionate face,
alone with thee a pure desire
to worship untold grace.
My soul would cry in silent prayer
toward hours swept apart.
Your essence warms the evening air
as I dance into your heart.
Mmm.
- Shakespeare.
- Aramis.
- Cheating.
- It was beautiful.
- Thank you.
- Mmm-mmm.
Very well, D'Artagnan.
Your turn.
Ahh!
As morning hues of sun-swept...
Fire.
...fire caress your poisoned face...
Bravo! The boy's a natural!
Ohh! A lively tune.
I'm inspired to dance.
Why's Athos sittin' by himself?
He takes his drinking
very seriously.
Not to worry. He'll be his usual,
charming self by morning.
Ho-ho-ho!
A lovely time!
Athos, why don't you come join us?
You fight like a man.
See if you can drink like one.
I'll drink anything
you put in front of me.
Famous last words.
What should we drink to?
Let's drink to love.
To love.
Let me tell you
a story about love, D'Artagnan.
I knew a young man once, a count,
who feared he would never fall in love.
One day, he met a woman.
This woman was more than beautiful.
She was intoxicating, mysterious,
everything he'd ever dreamed of.
He felt his heart would burst
if he couldn't have her.
What happened?
The poor idiot married her.
Isn't that what people do
when they fall in love?
Shut up and listen to me.
They were riding
through the forest one day.
She was thrown from her horse
and knocked unconscious.
When he rushed to her side,
he noticed a mark on her body...
something he'd never seen before,
something she'd managed
to keep hidden all this time.
- What was it?
- The brand of the fleur-de-lis,
the mark given to those who
are to be executed for murder.
The count was crushed.
The woman he loved, his bride,
had betrayed him.
She'd lied to him.
When she came to, she swore that she'd
been falsely accused of these crimes,
but he didn't believe her.
He rejected her for her lies
and for her past.
Then he banished her
from his province.
When the guards came to take
her away to be executed, she...
she was still professing
her undying love.
Soon after, the count realized how much
she had meant to him, but it was too late.
His betrayal was far greater
than hers could ever have been.
He gave up his title, his land,
everything he believed in,
never to be seen or heard from again,
all because of love.
Whoo! May I have this dance?
How's your head, D'Artagnan?
I'm beginning to wish
the cardinal had chopped it off.
Would you stop whistling, please?
- I'm not whistling.
- Well, somebody's whistling.
- Barmaid's kiss left him dizzy.
- I hear it, too.
Sounds like a cannonball.
Oh, I hate cannonballs.
Whoa!
- The cardinal has a long reach.
- Get outta here!
Flank left!
Fire!
There they are!
Kill the Musketeers!
We'll split up.
D'Artagnan rides with me.
- We'll see you in Calais.
- Or hell.
Hyah!
Split up!
We need heads
for the reward!
The first time
you saw D'Artagnan,
did you need the laces
in your corset loosened?
Yes. And I felt
my cheeks flush.
But your hands were cold.
My knees trembled.
- But your heart was pounding.
- Yes.
But I don't understand
why I feel this way.
We only met for a moment.
A moment is all it may take.
Do you think so?
When my father
promised me to Louis,
I was furious.
The thought of marrying
a complete stranger,
someone I'd never even seen...
I thought I'd never be happy...
And that I'd never find love.
But then the first time
I saw him and our eyes met,
- I knew.
- What did you know?
What you knew in your heart
when you first saw D'Artagnan.
What if he doesn't feel the same?
We must never give up hope.
I'll get you your robe.
What are you doing here?
Forgive me, your majesty.
I need your help...
And could not, in good conscience,
wait another minute.
On what matter?
I'm worried about
the king's happiness.
In what way?
I'm afraid he's fallen
into a dreadful melancholy...
And wishes to postpone
his birthday celebration.
Perhaps he's concerned
with more important matters,
like the coming war with England.
Which is exactly why
the celebration must be held:
To show the world
that the king of France...
can face an enemy
on any field,
to show France who is king.
He will listen to you.
I will talk to him.
Thank you.
I've always said...
that you are as intelligent...
as you are beautiful.
I'm not worthy
of such a compliment.
Ah, but you are.
It is difficult to be a man
in the service of God.
It is assumed that
certain...
wants,
desires,
are void from my existence.
But, after all, I'm still a man.
Your sacrifice brings you closer to God.
Yes.
But it is not God
to whom I wish to be close.
I want you to consider,
to know...
all that we might
accomplish together.
For France.
I think you should leave.
Remember, kings come and kings go,
but one thing remains the same,
and that is me.
Hyah!
- Do you think we lost them?
- I don't know.
I hope we're close to Calais.
My horse could use a rest,
and my rear is killing me.
You're a good man, D'Artagnan,
much like your father was.
Hyah!
You knew my father?
Only by reputation.
His death was mourned
by all Musketeers.
How did he die?
He uncovered a plot
to assassinate the king.
He was led into a trap
by a fellow Musketeer and then murdered.
Musketeer?
Shit!
There they are!
Well, we didn't lose them.
I'll try and hold them off
as long as possible.
You ride on without me.
I can't leave you here, not like this.
A Musketeer's first duty
is to protect the king.
You ride on to Calais...
and intercept
the cardinal's messenger.
- There's too many of them!
- Go or I will shoot you myself!
- Take these.
- Don't let me down.
- I'll never forget you.
- Go!
Hyah! Hyah!
Hyah!
Back.
Advance.
Yes.
Now lunge.
One, two, three, four.
Now disarm.
Excellent.
Forgive me for being late,
your majesty.
I was wrestling
with an important affair of state.
Excuse us, please.
Your eminence,
I've been hearing some very
troubling rumors about you.
There are so many to choose from.
Betrayal.
Ah, yes, that is usually the first.
Let me see if I
remember it correctly.
While the English attack from without,
the wicked cardinal
undermines from within,
forging a secret alliance with Buckingham
and placing himself on the throne.
But really, your majesty,
why stop there.
I have heard much more
festive variations.
I make oaths with pagan gods,
seduce the queen
in her own chamber,
teach pigs to dance
and horses to fly...
and keep the moon carefully hidden
within the folds of my robe.
- Have I forgotten anything?
- It does seem rather far-fetched.
Sire, if there are any
doubts about my loyalty,
they will be laid to rest
when we appear together
to celebrate your birthday.
Oh, my birthday.
You know, I've been meaning
- to speak to you...
- The queen.
has just been telling me
how eager she is to attend.
Anne is coming?
The entire nation is anxious
to celebrate the birth of its king.
It will be an event to remember.
I promise.
Hyah! Hyah!
Whoa! Whoa!
What is it, Henri?
There's a body
in the road, milady.
It's a young man.
He appears to be injured.
He's handsome.
Put him inside.
With me.
Welcome back.
Did you dream?
Where am I?
We're in Calais.
Calais?
Tuesday at midnight!
Where are my clothes?
Do you have a name or shall I
make one up for you?
My name is D'Artagnan.
D'Artagnan. I like that.
I'm the Countess de Winter, Milady.
- Countess?
- By marriage.
- But my husband's dead.
- I'm sorry.
I've learned to live with death.
Uh, Milady, I'm grateful
for all that you've done,
- but I've got...
- What?
Important business.
How mysterious.
Does it require clothes?
Yes, I need my clothes.
I'm afraid they won't be ready
for at least an hour.
Until then, you're my prisoner.
Would the prisoner care for a drink?
Well, I am thirsty.
What brings you to Calais?
I'm on a mission for the king.
I've heard that before.
- I'm serious.
- You're young.
Young men are given
to exaggeration.
However, if you'd like
to entertain me with a story,
I love a good adventure.
I came to Calais to stop a spy.
- A spy?
- Yes.
I believe you. Aren't you afraid?
- A Musketeer isn't afraid of anything.
- I knew it.
I knew you were a Musketeer
the moment I saw you.
- You did?
- Of course.
But D'Artagnan, if this spy were to
find out you were here,
your life could be
in grave danger.
A Musketeer isn't afraid of danger.
I'm dangerous.
Aren't you afraid of me?
You're not dangerous.
Then what am I?
You're beautiful.
Beauty. Danger.
They are the same.
Milady, I'm sorry...
Oh, my god!
Parker!
Kill him.
You can kill me,
but a surprise waits for you
that even Buckingham
can't prevent.
You're young and vain,
but I don't know
if you're clever.
I know how you love
a good adventure.
Take him with us.
The bodyguards are
waiting outside, Milady.
All right.
Can I help you, Lord de Winter?
- Milady de Winter, is she here?
- Oh, no.
- I've not seen her.
- She murdered my brother, old man!
Let's take the back stairs.
Whoa!
We are the Countess de Winter's party,
arrived from Paris.
Permission to come aboard?
Permission granted.
Take us to your captain.
What are you, deaf?
Dead.
They're all dead!
Not all of us.
Porthos the pirate!
- Pirate?
- I told you I was famous.
Sabine.
Athos.
Stop!
I thought you were dead.
Cardinal Richelieu
took pity on me.
You're the spy.
I've learned
the value of lies.
They've kept me alive.
The treaty, give it to me.
No.
I will shoot.
Be kind.
Aim for my heart.
Countess de Winter.
I will not be so kind.
The treaty outlines
Richelieu's plan
to forge an alliance
with Buckingham.
- No mention of the king?
- None.
However, the agreement is contingent...
upon a demonstration
of the cardinal's power.
A demonstration?
- What kind of demonstration?
- I don't know.
I know someone who does.
I wish to speak with your prisoner.
She dies in the morning.
There was a time I would have
given my life for a kind word from you.
I could not give it.
I was a fool.
Is it true what he says?
Did you kill his brother?
I have become the nightmare...
you once thought me to be.
But not before.
Not us.
No.
Do you know of the cardinal's plans?
I do.
Tell me.
Will you have my life spared?
No, I cannot.
Society demands swift justice.
I'll take my secret to the grave.
Sabine...
You will die for your crimes.
There is nothing
I can do about that now.
But how you choose
to leave this world is up to you.
What has this world ever done for me?
"I am the resurrection and the life,"
sayeth the lord.
"He who believeth in me
shall never die."
We forgive you for your crimes.
Die in peace.
On your knees.
No!
- What is this?
- Sabine, forgive me, please.
I do forgive you.
The cardinal intends
to assassinate the king...
on Friday at his birthday celebration.
God's justice be done.
Amen.
The king's life is in danger.
We have work to do.
- Impressive.
- He can do that every time.
- And he has no qualms about...
- None.
He believes a man should honor
no kings before God.
A man of faith.
How reassuring.
Whatever you're paying him,
double it.
I want the king's birthday
to be a memorable event.
And rehang this painting
in my chamber.
Just as it is.
He was always
a little too flattering.
Horsemen!
Over here!
What does it say?
Well, over there.
Search the perimeter.
I'll try to find the king.
- But...
- Go!
You look beautiful.
Thank you.
Is something wrong?
- Cardinal Richelieu.
- Yes?
He is an evil man.
Do not believe
every rumor you hear.
He is powerful.
I ride through the countryside every day.
I've seen the uses of his power.
Power sometimes frightens.
Here in the palace I've seen it too.
I know.
- What should we do?
- I'm not sure.
We will do it together.
Get back!
Captain, protect their majesties!
- Richelieu!
- Get them inside!
Kill those Musketeers!
They're trying to murder the king!
Save the king!
Go with God.
Aha!
I like this.
I think our young friend
could use some help.
Hold this.
It's about time!
Come, D'Artagnan!
We're saving the king!
You have failed.
Oh, you are so naive.
Things couldn't be more perfect
if I'd planned them myself.
The king of France dies
at the hands of his own personal guard.
Grief stricken, terrified,
the huddled masses turn for comfort...
to their devout spiritual leader...
who, ever so humbly,
assumes the throne...
- with the queen by his side.
- I would rather die.
That can be arranged!
But first your reluctant
husband will be found...
pierced through the heart
by the sword of a Musketeer.
The same sword
that failed to protect his father.
Ha!
I hope we're not interrupting.
No, on the contrary.
You're right on time.
Follow me.
No!
Leaving so soon?
Oh, you know
I abhor bloodshed.
Especially your own.
Stand aside.
You are under arrest,
charged with treason.
You, of all people,
should know that the cardinal
does not answer
to the laws of men.
Then you'll answer to God.
You first.
Aramis.
This sword belongs to me.
So it does.
Let's see if you're as brave
a man as your father was.
And as foolish.
Is he dead?
Gently, gently.
Oh! You see?
There is a God.
We're being followed.
Do something about it.
My God.
Which one do we take?
- I've never been here before.
- Split up.
Whoa, ugly.
Whoa! Whoa! Whoa!
Oh!
Ha-ha!
You smelly...
lump of lard!
Impressive.
Damn it!
How pathetic.
Killed by the same man
that killed his father.
- Tsk, tsk, tsk.
- You killed my father?
Oh, yes. As I will you.
Well, well,
one thing is certain.
You are no Musketeer.
I might have been mistaken.
For you, father.
Let us out of here!
Hyah! Hyah!
Hyah! Ah!
Where have you been?
Taking care of something ugly.
Richelieu!
You're too late, Musketeers!
By now the Duke of Buckingham's signature
is next to mine.
The alliance is complete!
That would be difficult considering
the treaty never left France!
A minor problem!
I will return twice as strong...
and the throne will be mine!
I think not.
You will never harm
another soul ever again.
- My promise to God.
- Wait!
Well done, your majesty.
Are you all right?
Yes.
Arise.
Is this the man who saved my life?
His name's D'Artagnan, sire.
D'Artagnan, I'm in your debt.
What can I do to repay
the courage you've shown me?
Your majesty,
his heart has but one desire.
And that is to become a Musketeer.
Then approach.
Kneel.
This world is an uncertain realm
filled with danger.
Honor undermined by the pursuit of power.
Freedom sacrificed when the weak
are oppressed by the strong.
But there are those who oppose
these powerful forces,
who dedicate their lives to truth,
honor and freedom.
These men are known as Musketeers.
Rise, D'Artagnan,
and join them.
Your father would be proud of you.
You're a Musketeer.
What do we do now?
What's next?
- Well, we protect the king.
- We protect the queen.
- In the name of God.
- And France. Correct?
- France, indeed.
- D'Artagnan!
My sister's honor will not
wait a moment longer!
- I'll handle this.
- D'Artagnan...
We also protect each other.
All for one...
And one for all!
Run!
When it's love you give
I'll be a man of good faith
When in love you live
I'll make a stand
I won't break
I'll be the rock you can build on
Yeah
Be there when you're old
To have and to hold
When there's love inside
I swear I'll always be strong
Then there's a reason why
I'll prove to you we belong
I'll be the wall that protects you
Yeah
From the wind and the rain
From the hurt and the pain
- Yeah
- Hey
Let's make it all for one
And all for love
Let the one you hold
Be the one you want
The one you need
'Cause when it's all for one
It's one for all
When there's someone that should know
Then just let your feelings show
And make it all for one
And all for love
When it's love you make
I'll be the fire in your night
Then it's love you take
I will defend I will fight
I'll be there when you need me
Yeah
When honor's at stake
This vow I will make
Yeah
That it's all for one
And all for love
It's all for love
Let the one you hold
Be the one you want
The one you need
'Cause when it's all for one
- It's one for all
- Yeah
When there's someone that should know
Then just let your feelings show
And make it all for one
And all for love
Don't lay our love to rest
'Cause we could stand up to the test
We got everything
And more
Than we had planned
More than the rivers
That run the land
We got it all
- In our hands
- Yeah
Now it's all for one
And all for love
It's all for love
Let the one you hold
Be the one you want
The one you need
'Cause when it's all for one
- It's one for all
When there's someone that should know
Then just let your feelings show
When there's someone that you want
When there's someone that you need
Let's make it all
All for one
And all for love
Please rate this subtitle at www.osdb.link/6dv9h
Help other users to choose the best subtitles