-== [ www.OpenSubtitles.org ] ==-
Hi...
Yes um, I was wondering if
I could get driving directions...
To a nightclub called Bunker.
Yes, Bunker.
How exactly would I get there?
It's Amy!
Hello, sweetie!
Okay.
How are you?
We miss you so much!
Yeah, we wish you were
here with us.
- Mhm.
- Yeah.
And um, how far away is this?
No we're in Germany right now.
Mhm, and then we travel to Italy in a couple of days.
Great.
Thanks.
Alvederzane!
I know.
Tell her we bought her a present from Holland.
Yeah we got you a present.
No we can't tell you what it
is, it's a surprise.
Oh yes, the other thing is that
we met this cute German waiter.
Well, Jenny thinks he's cute.
Mhm...
Yeah, and he invited us to this party
tonight, so...  We're gonna go.
But uh, we should go so...
Maybe we can talk to you later?
Okay.
All right.
We miss you!
Bye, Amy!
Kisses!
Okay.
Bye, sweetie!
I think we were supposed to turn.
Turn!?
I thought you knew exactly
where we were going!
Do we go left or right?
I'm sorry, I just don't know
where we are.
What was that?
I have no idea.
You must have run over a pot hole or something.
We need to go out
and check it out.
Aww Shit!
Shit!
Shit! Shit, why oh God...
Why?
Oh my God!
Okay, okay um...
Okay.
We're gonna call the rental car service.
Get the papers.
Okay.
Okay...
219...
200...
806.
What...
Shit, there's no signal.
What?
There's no signal!
There's always a signal.
Not out here in the middle of nowhere.
Oh my God, Shit!
Oh my God, oh my God, let's
just get back in the car.
Okay... Now what do we do?
I don't know!
Do you know how to change a tire?
- No, I don't know how to change a tire.
- Well, neither do I.
What are we supposed to just go walk
until we find a house or a person or something?
Lindsay... What are we supposed to just go walk
What are we supposed to just go walk
until we find a house or a person or something?
Lindsay. I am not getting out and walking.
Okay so we're just gonna sit here,
until the sun comes up?
I have heels and shorts on!
I'm not going outside!
Okay so we're just gonna sit here,
until the sun comes up?
I have heels and shorts on!
I'm not going outside!
Are those headlights?
Okay.
Roll down your window.
What, are you kidding!?
I'm not going to just roll down the window.
Roll down your window,
he can help!
- Hi...
- What's going on, girls?
Yeah um, we need help.
Uh... We have a flat tire.
I know you girls.
I've got a horny video
of you at home.
No... No, we speak English.
If um... Can you help us?
You're always wet
between your legs, right?
I don't know what...  He's speaking German.
Um... Uh we need... Can you call somebody?
- I can do both of you at once.  I'll fuck you good and hard.
- Um... Uh we need... Can you call somebody?
Would you like that?
- "Ficken."
- Look it up.
Hold on a second.
Fucking!
He said fucking!
- Okay, okay, buh bye.
- Roll your window up.
Bye.
Do you want to fuck or not?
- I'm sorry.
- I told you!
Is your door locked?
Yes, my door is locked.
Why is he still staring at us?
- Just don't look at him, okay?
- I'm not looking at him.
- I just want to get out of here.
- I know.
Eww.
Aw!?
Oh my God.
Okay...
We, we need to j-just go! We need
to get out of here.
We need to walk and find someplace,
somebody that can help us, okay?
- Okay, but...
- We have to!
But if we don't find a place in like 10 minutes,
we are running back to this car.
We came...
We came from over here, I swear.
How do you know that?
All the trees look the same.
Leaving the car
is the stupidest idea.
We would have been waiting for hours, Jenny.
Yeah well we could have waited,
and it wouldn't have been freezing cold.
We needed to go find help, Jenny.
Seriously find help?
How are we going to find help out here, Lindsay?
Well, you agreed to come along, Jenny.
This is not just my fault.
I don't wanna stay in the car by myself!
We just got a little lost, okay?
- A little lost, Lindsay?
- Yes!
We just got a little lost, okay?
- A little lost, Lindsay?
- Yes!
We are not a little lost!
We're really lost!
You know what, Lindsay?
I'm not walking anymore!
I'm tired of walking, okay?
- Jenny, I'm trying!
- Trying what?
- Lindsay, we've been down here for like an hour okay!?
- Yeah I know!
I'm tired and I'm cold.
I'm not moving!
- I'm not moving!
- Stop it.
No!
- Fine!
Fine.
- I'm staying right here.
- Good.
What is that?
My God is that a...
Is that a house?
Jenny!
Jenny, look!
I think it's a house!
I swear!
- It's a, it's a light or something! Come on, let's go.
- What?
Quick...
Oh! For some reason I don't believe you!
Oh thank God!
Come on!
Hello!
Anybody home?
Let's go to the front door!
Hello!
-Hello?
-Lindsay!
Lindsay, come here... To the door!
- Oh my God!
- What?
Look at the dog!
I know and I don't like dogs!
I know you don't.
- Hello?
- Is anybody home?
- Keep ringing the doorbell.
- Do you see anybody?
No...  Oh wait, yes!
Hi.
- Hi.
We got a flat tire.
Can we come in?
Can we use your phone so we
can call the car company service?
Are you alone?
Yes.
We're alone.
Come in.
Have a seat.
You're tourists?
- Um, we-we're on a road trip through Europe...
- It's like a... Yeah... A European vacation.
We're from New York.
Can you call the emergency car service?
For us?
Are you relatives?
- No.
- No, we're friends.
Anyway...
I'll make the phone call.
Okay, thanks.
Something to drink?
- Uh, water is fine.
- Yeah, just... Water.
Hello.
This is Dr. Heiter.
Sorry to call you so late.
But there's a problem. I've got two girls from New York.
They're having car trouble.
Well...
At least he's calling the car company for us.
That's just great.
Yes, thanks a lot.
Bye.
Here you go...
Water.
Thank you.
They will arrive in half an hour.
Maximum.
You have a really lovely home.
Do you live here with your wife?
No.
I don't like human beings.
God damn it! Be careful, will you!? Stupid cow!
I'm sorry.
Is there something wrong
with your eyes? Idiot.
I'll get you another one.
- No, it's okay, I... It's okay.
- We can just share.
I'll fetch a towel.
What just happened?
I don't know.
We need to get out of here right now.
Okay.
It's freaking me out.
We need to just... Call a taxi or something
so we can go back to the hotel.
Straight go back to the hotel, okay.
- Okay.
- We'll get the car in the morning or something.
- Okay. Yeah.
I'm really tired.
Listen, um, If you could just call a taxi service for us,
we're just gonna go back to the hotel.
No. I don't do another phone call.
Can I call then?
No.
- I'm tired.
- What?
- What uh...
What's going on?
Look at me.
It's a rape drug.
- What!?
- Rohypnol.
Oh my God! What!?
It causes drowsiness, dizziness,
disorientation and memory loss.
Wha... Are you kidding!?
What are you doing to h...
Jenny!
Oh my God!
What is it?
Oh my God.
Jenny.
Jenny!
Jenny, wake up!
Oh my God!
Jenny.
Lindsay!
Jenny!
What is going on!?
What are you doing?
What is this?
What the fuck are you doing to us?
What are you doing?
Jenny!
Get us ou...
My friend...
You don't match.
... Have to kill you.
Don't take it personally.
What is this?
What are you doing to us?
Stop!
Jenny!
Who the fuck are you?
Where the fuck am I?
What is this?
Answer me, what is this!?
Untie me, God damn it!
What are you doing?
Why the fuck did you tie me up?
God damn it, untie me you freak!
Who the fuck are you?
Please...
Why the fuck are you doing this!?
Why are you doing this!?
Where the fuck are you going?
It's gonna be okay... Likely good.
The Japanese possess unbelievable strength
when backed into a corner.
The Japanese possess incredible strength
What...
What are you going to do with us?
I'm Dr. Joseph Heiter.
Retired but still very well known as
the leading surgeon separating Siamese twins.
You're a crazy Nazi.
I'll get you, you dirty German madman.
Just you wait and see.
Six months ago...
I'll get you, you dirty German madman.
Just you wait and see.
I designed a never seen operation,
not separating anymore but creating.
I transformed my three Rottweilers
into a beautiful... Three-hound construction.
Good news!
Your tissues match.
So...
- I will explain this spectacular operation only once.
- Your knots won't hold me forever!
We start...
With cutting the ligament patellar.
The ligaments of the knee caps.
So knee extension...
Is no longer possible.
Pulling from "B" and "C"...
The central incisors,
lateral incisors and canines...
From the upper and lower jaws...
Shut your mouth and untie me!
The lips from "B" and "C"...
And the anus of "A" and "B"...
Are cut circular along the border
between skin and mucosa.
The mucus retains so.
Two paracellular grafts
are prepared...
And lifted from the underlining tissue.
- Just you wait until I get my hands on you.
- The shape incisions...
Below the chins of "B" to "C"...
Up to their cheeks...
Connecting the circular mucosa and skin parts...
Of anus and mouth.
From "A" to "B"... And "B" to "C".
Connecting...
The paracellulated grafts to the chin-cheek incisions.
From "A" to "B" and "B" to "C".
What are you babbling about?
The paracellulated grafts to the chin-cheek incisions.
From "A" to "B" and "B" to "C".
You really think
you'll get away with this?
The paracellulated grafts to the chin-cheek incisions.
From "A" to "B" and "B" to "C".
You really think
you'll get away with this?
Creating...
A Siamese triplet.
Connected...
Via the gastric system.
Ingestion by "A"...
Passing through "B"...
And the excretion of "C".
A human centipede.
First sequence.
Here's your breakfast.
- Hey, hey, just a minute, just a minute. Just, just, just a minute...
- Propofol... Under general anesthesia.
Please stop!
No! No!
Lindsay!
Jenny...
I want my mom!
Have you gone mad?
Come here! Come back here!
No!
Oh No!
Open up!
Please!
Stop!
Why are you doing this?
Open up!
You need help,
you're a sick man!
I am a sick man...
If you don't open up immediately I will...
Cut your knees...
And pull your teeth out
one by one!
Without any anesthesia.
It's your choice!
Open the door!
Open that door!
Stop it!
No, oh God!
No! No!
Please!
Why you doing this just...
Let me and Jenny go!
Please!
We'll give you anything!
Anything you want,
just let us go!
Don't worry...
It's only a sedation rifle.
Keep your head very still.
I don't want to lose one of your precious eyes.
Just kill me!
Ahh...
One of my Rottweilers,
also tried to escape...
Just before the operation.
After I caught the dog...
He had to take the middle position.
In this position...
The healing pains...
Are twice as intense.
Do you already regret your little escape?
In fact, I'm thankful for it.
Because now, I know definitely,
you are...
the middle piece!
Just kill me now.
I'd rather be dead.
Game... Over.
Ah shit...
The power is cut off again.
Sorry!
Shit!
Who the fuck runs the electricity around here!?
I'm so sorry.
Help!
Oh my sweet centipede...
Good boy.
Looks good.
Healing well.
Suffering will be over soon.
You're in a lot of pain, I know.
Yeah... Nice.
Okay.
Better and better.
You're... My lead.
My lead.
Hey man...
Yeah... Come...
Come on up.
Stand up.
You can do it... Yeah, yeah...
Up... Yeah...
Yeah come... Come up!
Up... Up! Up! Up! Up!
Doing well, yeah!
Yeah, come up!
Here... Come up. Ah, yeah!
Yeah!
Yeah! Very good!
I did it!
Do you really think
you're God?
Make it all go away, please.
Stop this.
Stop it now. Turn it off!
How dare you lock us up here?
You crazy idiot.
You'll regret this,
you filthy asshole.
European madman.
Goddammit, let us out!
Now! We are not animals... To be caged!
Take the world... And bring it to me.
Yeah, good boy.
Come...
Come!
Bring the bait...
I am not a dog you madman.
Good boy.
Come!
Yeah come!
- Then let's walk a little bit at least.
- Now what?
Attention!
What the hell are you doing?
One, two, three, four.
One, two, three, four. One, two...
Just die!
Bon appétit.
That's what you get.
I'm not your goddamn dog.
I'm not a dog.
Do this once more again to me...
And I'll pull your teeth out
one by one.
You kamikaze shit hole.
You want to bite me?
Now you can bite me.
Bite my boot.
Bite my boot!
Bite my boots!
Oh... Mr. Kamikaze is a chicken today.
Do you get off on this?
This is your fetish.
How dare you,
to turn your back to me?
I'll give you some educa...
Oh no...
Shit.
I have to shit.
Forgive me.
Yeah! Ha ha ha!
Feed her!
Hard!
Swallow it bitch!
Swap!
Feed her!
Hard!
I wanna sleep...
I have to sleep!
Why didn't I cut your vocal cords...
If you don't shut up...
We'll catch up on it.
... Doing a follow-up operation.
Finally! You wanna move your ass.
That's fine with me.
Maybe... You even can escape.
Speed up, come!
Come!
After you, please.
I'll teach you... To mind me!
Strong...
Good.
Constipated...
Laxative.
I'll use mine,
good stuff.
End section, you are very sick.
I think you're dying...
May have to replace you.
- Help us! Help...
- Shut up!
Yes, hello?
This is the police. We want to talk to you.
One minute...
Help us! Please, anyone!
We're in the cellar!
Hello...
Mr. Heiter... Good day.
Police...
This is my colleague Voller.
And I'm Detective Kranz.
May we come in a moment?
Of course.
Come in.
Thank you.
Take a seat.
How can I help you?
Mr. Heiter, people are missing.
Their vehicles were found
in your neighborhood.
Perhaps you could tell us more...
I'm afraid you've come
to the wrong house, you see...
I'm so busy at the moment
with my research and writing...
That I hardly leave the house.
Gentlemen... Can I offer you something
to drink?
Coffee, if you have any.
I'm afraid I don't have time
for coffee.
Water is all I have.
Mr. Kranz...
Thank you.
Mr. Voller...
So tell me,
what do you want to know?
Mr. Heiter, we know you're an international first-rate surgeon
and we don't want to disturb you...
But our investigation has hit a dead end.
And, you're a suspect.
I expect you have
your reasons.
But I have neither the time,
nor the patience...
For the banality
of missing persons.
What is that cage
being used for?
Could you get to the point?
A witness... Heard a woman...
Screaming on your property.
An American woman.
Can you explain that?
Absolutely not.
I have no idea
what you're talking about.
Your silver-colored Mercedes was seen, at the
place where the abandoned Dutch truck was found.
What do you think?
You think there's a connection!?
Oh the nerve you guys have to suspect me!
Finish your drinks
and get out of my house!
I need you out of my house... I have work to do!
Take it!
Come on.
I need you out!
Take it! Drink up!
You will regret that!
I'll see you in court.
You can count on being fired
when my lawyer hears about this.
My apologies.
I overreacted.
I'm overworked.
I don't get enough sleep.
I'll just get a towel.
Help us! We're in the cellar!
Come to the cellar! Help us!
Dear Joseph,
don't stress yourself.
Everything will be okay.
I've got two strong and healthy replacements.
So enjoy...
Your last moments with the "Jen-tail."
Because when I'm back,
I'll mercy kill it.
... Preparing for a new operation...
... A quadruplet!
See you.
Come...
What is down there... In that cellar?
Now... You're going too far.
Well what's in there?
My laboratory, a small workroom,
and a torture chamber.
You're making a fool of yourself.
Can we take a look around?
Not a chance.
Look... My research is off-limits
to you... To everyone.
Do you have a search warrant?
I can have one in 15 minutes.
I'll ask you again:
What's in the cellar?
What you're doing is illegal,
as you no doubt are aware.
Shall I call the police
myself and tell them?
When you show me a warrant,
you may search my entire home.
... And what is this?
That...
Insulin.
I have diabetes mellitus.
We'll be back in 20 minutes
with a search warrant.
I think you're hiding something.
If you want to waste
the taxpayers' money...
That's your call.
See you soon.
Fuck you!
We have to get out of here!
One, two!
Okay?
One, two, one!
Come on!
Two!
One!
Come on!
Two!
One!
One more... One!
Two!
One!
One...
Two!
One!
Come on! Almost there!
Come on, almost there!
Come on!
One!
Two!
Two! Almost there!
One!
Two! Almost there, faster!
Two!
Why here? Why are we in this room?
Goddamn!
Goddammit!
Now what?
... Eye for eye...
... Tooth for tooth...
Hey God...
Are you God?
I'm just...
I'm just a puny insect.
I cast out my parents...
Left my child without a parent.
I dismissed their love
and led a selfish life...
... Just like an insect.
In fact, lower than an insect.
But...
But dear God...
That's how I've lived my life!
And this is my punishment for living my life how I did!
I'm just...
... Trying to believe...
... That I'm still a human being.
Hey girls...
Hey look, it's God...
What a fucked up world we're living in.
Police!
Dr. Heiter, police!
Dr. Heiter...
Well, Goddamn it...
Please rate this subtitle at www.osdb.link/rfvu
Help other users to choose the best subtitles