Sync and corrections by explosiveskull
www.addic7ed.com
[ Traffic Sounds ]
[ Tires Rolling Over Gravel ]
[ Bus Brakes Hiss ]
[ Engine Stops ]
Ladies and gentlemen, we are
now arriving in New Canaan.
We will be continuing on to
Charlotte in exactly 10 minutes.
If this is your final destination,
please gather your belongings...
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org
[ Woman ] ♪ Don't look now
There's blood in the water ♪
♪ Listen close You
can hear the holler ♪
♪ There's no place
no place to hide ♪
♪ There's nowhere to run ♪
♪ From the midnight sun ♪
♪ Where you gonna go now? ♪♪
♪♪ [ Vocalizing ]
♪♪ [ Ends ]
[ Train Whistle Blows In Distance ]
Hi. Um, I was wondering
if you could help me out.
Um, I'm not trying to sell you
anything. Nothing like that.
I-I've just been trying to track
down someone who used to live here.
Oh. Nobody's lived here but us.
[ Man ] Who's that?
Who exactly are you looking for?
Her name is Millarca Karnstein.
No. No, don't recall anybody by that name.
- You sure?
- Believe me.
I-I'd remember a name like that,
especially round these parts.
Troy Pickett.
- Carmilla.
- Hi. Hi.
Now, could that, uh, be like a nickname?
I mean, could she be
going by some other name?
No, it isn't.
She passed through this town,
and she gave people this
address for her mail.
- This address?
- Yes.
So, no one else lives here who
might have known who she was?
No. Just, uh... Just me and my little girl.
I'd invite you inside, but,
uh, we're headed off to town.
I'm so sorry we can't be more help to you.
It's okay. Thanks for trying.
Okay. Uh, can I give you a ride into town?
- Would you mind?
- Not at all. Let me get my hat.
[ Carmilla ] Hi. I was wondering if
I could get some information...
from the public records.
I'm looking for police reports
or calls to the police...
filed from a particular address.
What address is it?
4880 Highway 58.
- 4880?
- Yes.
Troy Pickett's place.
That's right.
It'll be a couple of days.
Can't you get it any sooner?
Two business days.
[ Woman ] I'll get this.
Hey, uh, Linda? Will
you cover three for me?
What?
Not much of a detective.
- You were just at my house.
- Oh. Shit.
I mean, sorry.
Any luck?
No.
Anyway.
Just coffee.
- You're not gonna eat?
- No. Thanks.
Meep-meep.
Look, the reason I didn't order
lunch is because I don't...
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Sit for a sec?
Thanks for this.
It's okay.
Just play it cool, and I'll
just charge you for the coffee.
So, are you traveling all by yourself?
Mm-hmm.
Aren't you scared?
[ Chuckles ]
So this Millarca... Is, um...
Is she in some kind of trouble?
No, not that I know of.
Well, who is she?
Or who was she?
"Was," probably.
But I... I don't even know that.
At this point, I'm just looking for traces.
She owe you money or something?
She was my mother.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Why didn't you just say so?
Would it have made a difference?
I guess not.
Besides, I'm looking for answers,
not sympathy.
I'm sorry I said sorry. [ Mutters ]
When's the last time you saw her?
I never saw her.
She give you up?
[ Sighs ]
Thank you for lunch. You're too nice.
Hey!
She didn't live at the house.
He wasn't lying about that,
technically.
Meet me back here at 3:00,
and I'll show you what I mean.
- Yeah. Okay.
- I mean, it might be nothing.
I'm Carmilla Karnstein.
Laura. Laura Pickett.
I'll be here, Laura.
Okay.
Daddy used to rent it out,
but he stopped because it
was too much of a headache.
And how long ago was that?
Years.
I guess it's possible she could
have lived here for a while,
and... and he just... forgot.
So where do you go from here?
Don't know.
This was, more or less,
the end of the trail.
Here?
She drifted around a lot.
She had a tendency to skip out on rent.
That would explain a lot.
So, if you don't expect
to find your mother,
are you thinking that if
you follow in her footsteps,
that you'll be closer to her somehow?
Hey.
I have an idea.
Pull your hand off the... All the
way... All the way to the fence.
- All the way to the fence. There you go.
- Whoa!
- Whoo! Whoa!
- Pull back on the rein a little bit.
Pull back on the rein.
- Whoa.
- Pull back on the rein.
Whoa.
I got 'im.
- Whoa!
- Whoa.
- Whoa. Whoa.
There you go. There you go.
- Okay. This way. Follow me.
- Whoa.
[ Blusters ]
- Keep your arms in.
- I think he likes you better, Daddy.
Yeah. Yeah, I think so. Here we go.
Daddy?
Yes, ma'am.
You know that girl that came
up to the house earlier today?
- Uh-huh.
- She came into the diner too.
This afternoon.
To talk to you?
No, to eat.
We talked for a while though.
You know that woman she's looking for?
Millarca?
She was her mom.
Is that so?
Huh.
She stayed at the trailer, didn't she?
Yeah, for a time she did.
Why didn't you tell her?
[ Clears Throat ] Well, baby
doll, it's complicated.
But that girl's mother, she was a bad sort.
Into all kinds of bad things.
And, uh, for me to tell the girl that,
I just, uh... I didn't see the good in it.
But that was her mom.
Yeah. That's all... all the more
reason we shouldn't tell her.
See, I know it sounds cruel,
but sometimes it's best
not to know something.
And, uh, if I wasn't completely
truthful with that girl,
it's just because I
didn't want to hurt her.
And that's the God's honest truth.
Yeah.
Still, I feel bad for her though.
Yeah, I know you do. [ Chuckles ]
'Cause that's you.
I feel the same way.
- Good.
- Mm-hmm.
'Cause I told her it'd be all
right if she stayed in the trailer.
Just for a couple of nights.
Please?
Okay. Yeah.
- Thank you, Daddy!
- [ Laughing ]
Go on now. Go on.
- Thank you!
- Yeah. Yeah.
[ Gunshot ]
♪♪ [ Radio: Rock ]
- ♪♪ [ Volume Down ]
- [ Horn Honks ]
Morning.
I thought you might want a ride into town.
Thanks, but I'll just hoof it.
Daddy's going deer huntin' this weekend,
so, I thought, if you're still around,
maybe we could take in
a movie or something.
Look, just so you know
and so your father knows,
I'm not looking to move in.
You're staying for a few days, right?
Just until I figure out where to go next.
Well, if you do go into town today,
meet me at the diner at 3:00?
I'll give you a lift home.
Okay.
My room's upstairs.
If you see anything you
wanna borrow, just grab it.
All right.
[ Door Closes ]
Hey, Carmilla? Um, I was thinking
maybe we could go grab a bite first.
♪♪ [ Music Box ]
And then afterwards, I
could show you the town.
That should take all of five minutes.
I didn't check to see what movie's playing.
But people don't really watch the movies.
It's like more of a
hangout place, you know?
I love that one.
She's beautiful.
Yeah.
Do you think maybe I
could talk to her about...
She died when I was eight.
I'm sorry.
- Shit. I get it now.
- What?
Why didn't you say anything?
Come on. Let's go.
[ Speakers: Announcer ] Candy galore!
There's soft drinks, coffee...
Done.
[ Speakers: Announcer ]
and a whole lot more!
[ Sighs ] Do you see a
silver Mustang anywhere?
Oh, I think I see it over there.
So,
what do you say to someone...
when you think you like them,
but... you're not really sure,
so you... you wanna...
Um, Laura, don't take this the wrong way.
As much as I'd like to help you,
I don't think I'm the person to be giving
you advice about men, boys, whatever.
You don't have to.
- That's something someone else should do.
- I understand.
Friends?
An aunt?
Cousins? Anyone?
- I'm sorry.
- Stop apologizing.
Look, you're fine. Go have fun.
I'll just wait here, I guess.
You're the best.
[ Speakers: Announcer ] We
promise to satisfy your hunger,
your thirst, your sweet tooth.
So visit our refreshment center now.
Let's go!
If you are thirsty, try
ice-cold soft drinks...
or a cup of hot, flavorful coffee.
Get something to go with it, like
a sizzling and satisfying hot dog.
Or a tasty...
[ Sighs ] She has a date
with a silver Mustang.
[ Man ] ♪ I brake for red lights ♪
- Hey.
- [ Man ] Hi.
Don't you look pretty.
♪ I brake for some speed bumps ♪
♪ I brake for l... ♪
- ♪ Lovely lady humps ♪
- Where are we going?
Nowhere.
♪ Slow down, slow down ♪
- ♪ I'll brake for anything ♪
- ♪ Anything ♪
♪ I'll brake for
anything but you ♪
[ Man On Movie ] ...hiding
from the police.
Put them in a forest
more ominous than death,
- and listen to their screams.
- [ Woman Screams ]
♪ I brake for any... ♪♪
[ Man On Movie ] They learn
what fate awaits them.
[ Sighs ]
Some places possess
an evil of their own,
where the air is thick with
the shrieks of tortured souls,
where the earth tries to swallow every
trace of those foolish mortals...
You didn't come here to
watch a movie, did ya?
- [ Movie Continues ]
- [ Chuckles ] No.
Why?
I came here to see you.
So look at me.
Come here.
Closer.
- [ Chuckles ]
- You like that?
I bet you do.
[ Whispers ] Hey.
Just this once.
Come on.
[ Woman On Movie ] They're just
sores, nothing contagious.
Try not to let them bother you.
♪♪ [ Retro Theme ]
Laura.
[ Crying ]
[ Engine Revs ]
What'd you do to her?
And who are you, huh?
I'm the woman who wants
you to get out of the car.
Come on. Get out of the car.
Back off, cunt.
Kill the engine! Get out of the car.
Come on.
You really want me to get out of this car?
I so want you to get out of the car.
[ Laura ] Carmilla?
Take me home?
Crazy female.
You can't let 'em get
away with shit like that.
They're like bullies in a school yard.
Once they see a weakness, they
line up for a turn to exploit it.
It's not like that.
I mean, I could say no.
[ Carmilla ] Then why don't you?
Is it the attention?
Is this town that much of a shithole...
that the only way you can talk to a
guy is with his dick in your mouth?
I mean, don't get me wrong.
I happen to like cock.
I just don't like the
assholes they're attached to.
What?
Laura, relax.
Okay?
Yeah?
I'm sorry.
You ever think about maybe going away,
maybe to school?
I've thought about it.
Started saving up.
Didn't get very far.
Well, there are other things you could do.
I mean, I wanna be out on my own,
but I'm just terrified at the
idea of being all by myself.
Being alone's not so bad.
So,
are you alone right now?
No. I'm with you.
You know what I mean.
[ Man ] ♪ Feeling so high ♪
♪ On shoulders of giants
you find yourself ♪
♪ You fooled them again ♪
♪ But they know it ♪
♪ Oh, oh-oh ♪
♪ Oh ♪♪
[ Man ] So many people are
afraid to get off the road.
And they're not familiar with the
solitude you can have in the woods.
People know so little
bit about the woods.
The woods is a friendly place.
I'm going to bed.
[ Man #2 ] Treat wildlife and
the outdoors with respect.
What'd you do tonight?
Went to the drive-in.
Make it a practice to observe all the
rules of safe, responsible bow hunting.
With that girl?
Mm-hmm.
Ask the permission of
property owners to hunt...
What you all talk about?
Nothing. Just boys.
Then what?
Came back home to the trailer.
Watched TV.
Come here.
You know what? I can't help asking
because I'm worried about you.
Daddy, you don't have to worry about me.
No?
You a big girl now?
- You can take care of yourself?
- Yeah.
Uh-huh. What if you run into
the big, bad wolf out there?
- Can you handle that?
- Yeah.
Yeah? What if it's the devil himself,
and he reaches out and he grabs you?
[ Laughing ]
- Ah! [ Growls ]
- [ Squeals ]
[ Laughing ]
You know, you're my everything, Laura.
Just my everything.
You know what?
I made a covenant when your mother passed.
I said I would never...
never marry another woman,
never look at her...
till you were settled down with someone.
Daddy, I wouldn't mind
if you did. I... I...
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Come on. Shh.
That's my word, and I'm
gonna keep it, no matter what.
Yeah?
Oh, baby doll, you're my
whole world. You know that?
You're my whole world. [ Grunts ]
You know, sometimes,
when I hold you here like this,
and I close my eyes,
sometimes I swear I could...
I could be with her.
[ Crying ]
[ Crying Continues ]
[ Man On TV Continues, Faint ]
You have a right to be angry.
Fuck you.
Well, that's real nice.
That's the way you talk to people?
People that take you in,
give you a place to stay?
- [ Sighs ]
- Might be hard for you to understand,
but I was only lookin' out for you.
No, you weren't. You just wanted me gone.
But you're hiding something.
I can see it in your face.
I'll tell you anything you
want to know about Millarca.
You think that's gonna make you happy?
I got a feeling it won't.
Come here.
[ Sighs ]
You know what? I'm not looking
for any favors or a handout.
All I want to know, all I've
wanted to know from the start,
is just what she was like...
and where she might have
gone after she left here.
That's it.
Not gonna find that out reading those
police reports, I'll tell you that.
You know how she came to be here?
She was driving across Route 20.
Colored fellow behind the wheel.
Guy by the name of Dwight, um...
something or other.
It was in the middle of the night.
We found out the next day they were
trying to get to Montgomery by morning.
Montgomery.
So about the time they're
comin' through New Canaan,
this Dwight fella, he falls asleep.
Runs smack into a bridge support.
Didn't kill 'em.
Didn't kill neither one of them.
But your mama was hurt worse...
'cause the side of the
road they went off on.
So they took her
off to the hospital.
And this, uh... this colored fella,
he goes on about how he's
got to get to Montgomery,
that his daddy is sick, uh, close
to death or some such thing.
The car is scrap.
Totaled.
This fella reaches into
your mother's pocketbook...
and he takes her money.
Buys himself a bus ticket.
Ain't that somethin'?
Yeah.
Leaves her there in the
hospital, unconscious.
But he gives her a note.
It says, "I'll be back in five days."
Well, you can guess how
that turned out, huh?
So they called Montgomery.
Called all the hospitals.
But nobody's ever heard
of this guy named Dwight.
Dwight, uh...
I suppose I can call down there
and get his name, if you like.
Lewis.
Oh, you know him.
I know all about him.
[ Troy ] Ah.
So they let her out of the hospital.
What's she gonna do? Got no money.
Doesn't act like she's
got anyplace to go back to.
So she takes a job waiting
tables at the diner.
- The diner?
- My wife Karen took her in.
She and Laura are a lot
alike in that regard.
How long was she here?
Half a year.
After a month or two, we asked if she
could put something toward the rent.
Laura was little. I was on disability.
It was hard to make ends meet.
But, uh, she didn't give us no money.
Karen seemed to think she was on dope.
One day she didn't turn up at the diner.
Karen went down there to look for her.
Millarca had up and moved out.
Took a little TV and a
radio we kept down there.
We found it at the pawnshop in town.
You have no idea where she went after that?
See now, darlin', when you
steal something from somebody,
you don't generally tell
'em where you're headed.
I would have told you all
this up front, but, uh,
I didn't see the good in it.
[ Sighs ]
I'll pay you something
for the nights I was here.
No.
No, you don't have to do that. [ Grunts ]
But I tell you what.
If you're plannin' on movin' on,
I'd prefer that you did it
sooner rather than later.
See, Laura has a tendency
to get attached to people.
And I don't want to see
her get hurt no more.
Okay.
[ Sighs ]
[ Knocks ]
Carmilla? I'm coming in.
I was wondering if you
had a chance to search.
Got it for you right here.
Laura?
Baby doll, you all right?
[ Sniffles ]
You ran her off, didn't you?
No, no, no, I didn't. I-I told
her what she came here to find out.
I liked having her here.
[ Sniffles ]
- I liked having someone to talk to.
- Yeah. Well...
And you... you ran her
off 'cause you're jealous.
No. No, I... No, I...
I ran her off because if she's anything
like her mother, she's dangerous.
Dangerous?
Yeah, I'm not about to let her hurt
you the way she hurt your mother.
See there?
See what you get when you
start asking too many questions?
See, sometimes it's better
off not to know somethin'.
How did she hurt Mother?
You don't remember her?
At all?
She and your mama worked
at the diner together.
Did you know that?
Yeah, the two of them
were pretty good friends,
which I, for the life of
me, couldn't understand.
[ No Audible Dialogue ]
[ Troy ] Your mama was a
fine Christian woman.
[ Giggling ]
This Millarca, she... she
wasn't worth shootin'.
I figured her for
some kind of a gypsy,
but your mama swore she wasn't.
The way she dressed,
the way she acted,
the way she put all kinds of
ideas in your mama's head...
- Like what?
- [ Chuckles ]
Like she was wonderful
and beautiful.
So?
[ Troy ] Like she was too good to
be livin' out in the sticks...
and she should run away
with her, leave us behind.
Me and you.
Yeah, the two of them used
to run around a lot together.
Which pretty much left me to
take care of you by myself.
[ Laura ] I remember us
sittin' in the truck...
really late at night.
That's right.
You were spying on them.
[ Troy ] That's right.
I tried to tolerate it.
I pretty much put up with
anything to make your mama happy.
I mean, I... I loved her that much.
Your mother took to sleeping
in the upstairs bedroom.
I didn't know what else
to do but to let her.
Wasn't but a little bit, I started
to see something different.
She started to look sickly.
And she started losing weight. She
barely had the strength to get around.
See, when she was alone with me, she
tried acting like her same old self,
but the spark just wasn't there.
I mean, she was tired all the time.
Then she started having dizzy spells.
So I took her to the doctor.
And they... they thought she had
some kind of a blood disorder.
Yeah, they ran a bunch of tests.
Anemia and, uh, leukemia.
They didn't know what they was lookin' for.
Finally, I got fed up.
I said, "That's enough."
I told 'em, "That's it.
I... I'll look for answers my own way."
I asked the good Lord for guidance.
I remember.
I fasted, and I prayed.
I asked him for enlightenment.
Finally, he put the answer
right here in my heart.
What did he say?
Go to sleep now, all right?
I'm gonna be right in the next room.
Okay. Good night.
Leave the light on.
I'll leave the hall light on.
[ Whispers ] I'm scared.
I'll be right here.
Go to sleep now.
[ Troy ] See,
I-I-I knew...
Millarca had something
to do with it.
And one night...
I decided I was gonna find out...
what was going on.
What did you do?
[ No Audible Dialogue ]
[ Police Radio Chatter ]
"I was in the trailer rented
to me by Troy Pickett."
Karen Pickett was staying
at the trailer with me.
"Having had a domestic
disagreement with her husband."
Stop! No!
Stop! Troy!
It's not her.
It's me.
- [ Gags ]
- [ Gasps ]
[ Breathing Shakily ]
"Fearing for my life,
I fled on foot...
- [ Gasping ]
- toward Old Oak Road."
Son of a bitch.
♪♪ [ Rock ]
[ Man ] ♪ I took you down
to the river tonight ♪
♪ And I watched your body ♪
♪ Float out to sea ♪
♪ I went along for
the one-way ride ♪
- You're leaving.
- ♪ Come on, little girl ♪
- ♪ Come and rescue me ♪♪
- With me.
Tonight.
♪♪ [ Continues, Fades ]
We have to go. The sooner, the better.
Where are your things?
I can't leave yet.
There's something I have to tell you.
No. You don't have to. I read
the police report. I know.
Did the police report say
why he did what he did?
Why he beat her half to death?
Why he tried to run her over with
a truck? No. I don't need to know.
- You need to know.
- Jesus Christ, Laura.
Isn't that why you came here?
To find out who she was?
Who they were?
What they were?
My mother and your mother...
Were lovers.
- Did you know that?
- I figured as much.
There's more.
But you'll never believe me if I tell you.
Laura.
But I could show you.
I never knew how much like
my mother I was until now,
how much we have in common.
I've always hated myself for the way I am.
But now I realize it's okay.
It's how she was.
All along it was who I was meant to be.
This is the way it was that night...
when my father came down to the
trailer and looked in the window.
They were in this room.
They were on this bed.
Just as we are now.
[ Laura ] They were in this room.
They were on this bed.
Just as we are now.
[ Whispering ] They were in this room.
They were on this bed.
Just as we are now.
In this room.
On this bed.
Just as we are now.
Carmilla, it's okay.
It's okay. It's okay.
[ Laura ] He told me everything.
Let me show you.
Open my flesh wide.
Consume me.
[ Sighs ] Finish what they started.
[ Alarm Beeping ]
Laura?
- [ Beeping Continues ]
- Hey...
[ Beeping Continues ]
Oh, sweet Jesus.
Morning, Daddy.
[ Beeping Stops ]
♪♪ [ Organ ]
[ Woman ] ♪ Your eyes are embers ♪
♪ Burn me alive ♪
♪ I'm coming closer ♪
♪ Into the fire ♪
♪ I ♪
♪ Let my secrets out ♪
♪ To play ♪
♪ I ♪
♪ Want you in the worst ♪
♪ Way ♪
♪ This ice is dangerous ♪
♪ To the life I had ♪
♪ I'm only Icarus ♪
♪ Melting wings ♪
♪ I ♪
[ Thunder Rumbling ]
♪ Let my secrets out to play ♪
♪ I ♪
♪ Want you in the worst ♪
- ♪ Way ♪
- ♪ Worst way ♪
♪ Worst way ♪♪
You don't have to stay here, you know.
I can't leave.
Why not?
I was born here. This is where I belong.
Lord, hear all good prayers
for us. For Jesus' sake. Amen.
- Amen.
- Mm-hmm.
- Wait a second. What is this?
- Careful.
- What is that right there?
- I-It's fine.
I cut myself on the bread
rack at work. It's fine.
Did you put some antiseptic on that?
Just eat. Okay?
I'm bushed, and I'm not looking
forward to cleaning up the kitchen.
You could help out a little
more around here, you know.
I can't stay here. You know that.
- Just a couple of nights. I've already paid for it.
- Laura.
Please?
It's not that complicated. You drive to
your house, pack some things, we drive off.
I will. I will.
I just need to come up with an excuse.
You don't need an excuse.
You're a goddamn adult.
I'm sorry.
You say "I'm sorry" one more
time, and I swear to God...
Hold on.
- That's another thing.
- What?
I'm thinking we should try
it once without the knife.
- Carmilla...
- Relax.
Jesus, Laura.
I tried to tell you.
It's not because of them.
It's because of me.
It's who I am.
But I don't cut myself anymore. I swear.
I know, 'cause I do
all the cutting for you.
[ Knife Lands On Carpet ]
Come here.
It's just skin.
No more cutting, Laura.
Okay.
No more cutting.
Not me, not you.
[ Woman ] ♪ Baby, please ♪
♪ If you're needy ♪
♪ I'll ♪
♪ Still be ♪
♪ Standing still ♪
♪ Throw ♪
♪ Your weight ♪
- We don't need a knife.
- ♪ Cross your arms ♪♪
It doesn't have to hurt.
♪♪ [ Continues ]
No more blood.
No more guilt.
No more fear.
No more pain.
No. No, I... I... I need the knife.
I need the blood.
I need the guilt...
and to feel the pain.
How do you know if you haven't
felt love any other way?
Laura, look at me.
Focus on my eyes.
[ Moaning ]
This is what love is supposed to be like.
You been spending time
with that girl, haven't you?
- A little.
- Mm-hmm.
After what I told you?
- She's not her mother.
- Yeah?
What about you?
Aren't you like your mother?
Or are you somebody totally different?
- I wouldn't know.
- Yeah.
Sometimes people don't know who
they are till they get older.
They got nothing in common
with their parents...
and then find themselves doing
the same thing their parents did,
believing in the same things and...
usually making the same mistakes.
I hated my daddy,
and I find myself...
more and more like him every day.
And I'm just saying this...
'cause I'm trying to keep you from going
down the same path that your mama did.
- What's wrong with the path my mama took?
- Stop arguing with me.
You're just like your mama.
You think you know everything, don't
listen to nobody. Look what it got her.
Millarca didn't kill my mother.
Oh, yeah? Were you there?
- Cancer killed my mother.
- So the doctors say.
- So you think you know better than the doctors?
- I know what I saw with my eyes.
I seen your mother waste away to nothin'.
- I looked into that Millarca woman's face.
- Daddy.
Well, if you'd seen what I've seen...
I had never seen the look of
such absolute evil in my life.
Oh, would you come off it?
Listen to me. Just listen to me!
Stop your moaning and groaning and pay
attention to someone that's trying to help you!
- Calm down.
- You think you're so smart.
You and her and the doctors. Couldn't
none of you do nothin' to save her.
But I did!
Yeah.
You tried to run her
girlfriend over with your truck.
I did more than that.
What'd you do?
I caught her red-handed.
[ Troy ] Laura!
[ Gasping, Panting ]
Laura?
I'm not done talking to you.
[ Shower Water Running ]
[ Panting ]
Laura?
[ Troy Continues Panting ]
Baby doll, uh...
Daddy wants to see you.
[ Grunting ]
I-I-I... I
gotta see you.
[ Cries Out, Gasps ]
I just gotta look at you, baby,
to know I'm not too late.
If I thought anything
bad has happened to you...
[ Troy Gasping ]
- [ Gasps ]
- Oh, my Jesus!
It's not what you think!
It's not!
Daddy, wait!
Where are you going?
[ Grunting ]
[ Exhales ]
Daddy?
Don't move. You need to
wait for an ambulance.
[ Siren Chirps ]
J-Just be still.
Help will be here soon.
[ Whispers ] Fuck.
[ Police Radio Chatter ]
Where are you going?
Tell me where you're going!
Show me.
[ Creaking ]
- What are you doing here?
- I had to see you.
But you can't.
He'll kill you.
I just want to talk.
Millarca, I can't.
Why? Because he says so?
It just isn't right.
Since when?
Just for a minute.
Did something change?
- [ Moans ]
- What changed, Karen?
Did you change?
[ Footsteps ]
He's coming. Quick. Hide behind the door.
[ Whispering ]
Hey. You didn't say good night to me.
I'm sorry.
Just really tired. That's all.
Huh. What?
I just got the chills. [ Chuckles ]
Why don't you come downstairs
and watch some TV with me?
Um, tomorrow.
I will. I promise.
[ Whispering ] You don't
have to worry about me.
You don't have to worry about me.
- Anymore.
I love you.
Good night.
[ Sighs ]
I'll be very quiet.
[ Moaning ]
[ Troy ] The serpent had beguiled her.
And she had eaten,
on this very bed.
You are mine,
and you shall be mine.
And you and I...
are one...
forever.
[ Moaning Continues ]
[ Troy ] I knew I couldn't save her.
I failed your mother.
I couldn't suffer the witch to live,
so I slayed her.
[ Screaming ]
You killed her?
I had a moral obligation
to protect my family.
If I'd just acted sooner,
done what I knew in my heart was right,
maybe... maybe I-I could have saved her.
But it was too late.
Lord, hear all good prayers for us.
For Jesus' sake. Amen.
[ Troy ] Millarca had already
fed upon your mother's blood.
And your mother not only allowed it,
she'd enjoyed it.
Her blood, her soul...
was poisoned.
All I could do was...
keep her from spreading
the evil to anyone else.
I kept her under a tight rein.
I dedicated myself to
watching over the two of you,
searching for signs of blood...
her blood...
- ♪ Little ones to him belong ♪
- and yours...
waiting for Millarca
or someone like her...
to come back, looking for us.
And sure enough,
she did.
Now you're old enough to know
what I done and why I did it...
and, if that girl comes
up into this room tonight,
what it means.
What it m-means?
It means that she's like her mother.
And what I done to her mother,
I gotta do the same thing to her.
Don't, Daddy. Please.
She'll come.
Wait and see if she don't.
Please, Daddy.
Please give me a chance to explain.
[ Crying ] You don't understand.
Daddy, please. Sh-She never hurt me.
She never hurt me.
[ Wind Chimes Jingling ]
[ Hinge Creaking ]
[ TV: Man Speaking, Indistinct ]
[ TV Continues: Woman
Speaking, Indistinct ]
[ Whispers ] Laura?
Laura?
[ Laura ] Carmilla, no!
Motherfucker.
Carmilla, no.
No, Carmilla, no. You
gotta get out of here.
- You gotta get out of here.
- No. You're coming with me.
- I'm not taking off without you. I'm taking you with me.
- No, I can't go!
- Shh! Stop!
- No! No! Please!
- Listen...
- Get out of here.
No! Go! I want you to go! No!
Stop. Stop.
You gotta get out of here.
I'm fine. He won't come.
He's not gonna hurt me.
Come on, Laura.
You just... You have to leave. Okay?
You gotta go.
[ Crying ] I can't come with you.
You don't have to ever
come back here again.
[ Crying, Muttering ]
Why can't you just go?
[ Sobbing ] Please!
Go! Go! Get out of here!
I don't want you here! Go!
I don't want to go! I don't
love you! You have to leave!
- That's not true!
- Look at me, Carmilla.
[ Whispering ] You have to leave.
Go. I don't want you here.
Carmilla, please.
[ Crying ] Please.
You've gotta go!
You have to go!
- Carmilla, please go!
- No!
[ Sobbing ] No!
You have to go.
Please.
[ Whimpering, Sobbing ]
He killed your mother.
He's gonna kill you too.
- [ Gasps ]
- [ Groaning ]
[ Sobbing ]
[ Groaning Continues ]
Daddy, no!
[ Gasps ]
Die, you witch.
[ Groaning, Screaming ]
- [ Grunts ]
- [ Screams ]
[ Grunting ]
[ Carmilla Groaning ]
[ Carmilla Gasping ]
[ Grunting, Gasping ]
[ Gun Hammer Cocks ]
No, Daddy.
F... Fuck... you.
Fuck you. [ Grunting ]
Sh-She hurt me bad, Laura. You need to
get the police and bring 'em back out here.
They'll settle all this.
- Go on now.
- Carmilla? Carmilla?
[ Mutters ] Oh, shit.
- There she goes.
- [ Gasping ]
[ Phone Beeps ]
You look so pretty like that.
[ Laughing ]
I bet that hurts, don't it?
[ Troy Exhales ] Yeah.
You're losing a lot of blood there.
It'd be a shame to...
just to black out or somethin'.
[ Troy Whispering ] That's
right. Go to sleep.
Mommy loves you.
[ Gasps ]
[ Gasping, Whimpering ]
♪♪ [ Rock ]
[ Woman ] ♪ Take this ♪
♪ Plant my love ♪
♪ The roots have ♪
♪ Been set ♪
♪ Fly away ♪
♪ All your own ♪
♪ Right when I'm gone ♪
[ Sobbing ]
♪ I just want ♪
♪ To help you ♪
♪ Out ♪
♪ I just want ♪
♪ To help you ♪
♪ Out ♪
♪ Round and around ♪♪
♪♪ [ Vocalizing ]
[ Siren Wailing ]
♪♪ [ Continues ]
Sync and corrections by explosiveskull
www.addic7ed.com
♪♪ [ Ends ]
[ Wind Whistling ]
♪♪ [ Rock ]
[ Man ] ♪ I took you down
to the river tonight ♪
♪ And I watched your body ♪
♪ Float out to sea ♪
♪ I went along for
the one-way ride ♪
♪ Come on, little girl ♪
♪ Come and rescue me ♪
♪ I took you down to
the river tonight ♪
♪ And I watched your body ♪
♪ Float out to sea ♪
♪ I had a feeling
something wasn't right ♪
♪ It was the sound
of the river ♪
♪ That brought you to me ♪
♪ I was alone forever
in the world ♪
♪ But I knew somebody
would take me home ♪
♪ I got lost in
the rising tide ♪
♪ In the half light all
mistakes are gone ♪♪
♪♪ [ Continues ]
♪♪ [ Fades ]
Please rate this subtitle at www.osdb.link/8vz2
Help other users to choose the best subtitles