-== [ www.OpenSubtitles.com ] ==-
Subtitles by explosiveskull
Resync by GoldenBeard
Hot water, please.
Excuse me?
He said car is closed.
He get for you.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
American?
Guilty.
First time to Turkey?
No, no, no, no.
Been here...
a long time ago.
- Different life.
- Mmm.
- Now you come back.
- Yes.
Looking for something.
Hmm. Hey.
My brother.
He say...
you can find whatever you wish
in Turkey.
- Yeah?
- Uh-huh.
How about a man who kidnapped
his own daughter
and took her away
from her American mother?
An abusive man.
So not a real man.
No love for the child.
Just a need to punish
his ex-wife,
to take the one thing away
from her
that meant everything to her,
with no intention
of returning the child.
Do you think that...?
Excuse me.
Do you think I could find
that man in Turkey?
Or maybe...
on his way to Turkey?
I, uh...
would not be looking
for such a man.
It would be...
...dangerous.
For you.
Men like him
would think that.
And, God as my witness,
I would give him a chance.
To stop.
To reconsider.
To think about the worst thing
that could ever happen to him.
To imagine that.
There are two kinds of pain
in this world.
Pain that hurts.
Pain that alters.
Today...
...you get to choose.
Baby.
Oh, baby.
Oh, my God.
Oh, God.
Mom!
Oh, my baby.
- Are you okay?
- Mm-hmm.
My baby.
The State Department doesn't
know a thing about it, Grace.
No one does.
Just that 45 minutes ago,
someone delivered your daughter
to the desk downstairs.
Oh, I love you so much.
I love you, I love you.
My favorite driver.
Always on time like clockwork.
- Samuel.
- Ah, Roberto,
it's not easy
getting in and out here.
Copy Center?
- Huh?
- Copy Center?
Yes.
Lift off.
How am I today?
The same, only worse.
Every day, I know less.
Welcome to the club.
Thanks for the Lyft.
And a piece of advice.
Always be nice to anybody
who has access
to your toothbrush.
Okay.
Thank you for this interview
and opportunity.
Now, as you can see
from my résumé...
No, no, no, no, no, no.
Thank you for
this opportunity.
I have admired
your company's position
towards the environment
for quite some time,
and to be a part of that...
Ma.
Ma, I got accepted.
Yeah, I got accepted, Ma.
I got...
"It is with great pleasure
"that we write
to offer you admission
to the College of Engineering,
class of 2019." Ma!
Ma, Ma, I gotta
finish high school first. Yeah.
I don't get to
choose when I go, Tommy.
- Right.
- The Army does that.
I'll text you
when I'm at the gate.
- Love you, Dad.
- I love you both.
Where you headed?
Iraq.
First tour?
Yes, sir.
I'll be there to pick you up
when you get back.
Thank you.
Assalamu alaikum.
Alaikum assalam.
How they coming?
Left you something upstairs.
- Did you?
- Mm-hmm.
Thank you, Fatima.
You coming to the potluck?
Yes, I'm coming.
- Plates and napkins.
- All right.
Napkins and plates.
And forks.
Why are you doing this?
I got your name on a piece
of paper in my pocket.
It's all that matters.
Hey, hey, hey.
Look at me.
No, no, no, no, no.
Stop talking.
This is happening.
Your son's gonna be home
any second.
Right?
- Open your mouth.
- No. No.
Open your mouth.
You know what?
Weathermen are the best.
Princess
hairdressers are the best.
- Weathermen are the best.
- No, dolphin trainers.
Because you get to
play with...
Dolphin trainers
are totally the best.
And you don't have
to know anything...
The princess hairdressers
are the best.
...because there are screens
on the sides
and the front, and you don't
even see anything.
They are the best.
You get to curl their hair...
Hey.
Mr. McCall.
Ordered a book last week.
Oh, uh, yeah.
McCall...
I... I don't see it.
Um...
I'll be right back.
Man with the list.
"Hundred Books
Everyone Should Read."
Guilty as charged.
"In Search of Lost Time."
Came in yesterday.
Thank you.
What number?
Last one.
Well, I hope you start
another list.
Me, too. How much?
Uh, 40, please.
Thank you.
Sign is down?
Sale sign.
Oh, a change of circumstances.
Not going anywhere now.
I don't want a drink.
"God...
"grant me the serenity
to accept the things
"that I cannot change,
"the courage to change
the things I can...
...and the wisdom
to know the difference."
Would you, um...
would you mind taking me
back where you picked me up?
Just, other foot.
Right there.
Come on.
You got it.
Easy, easy.
One step. Keep going.
All right.
There you go.
Could you just help her
get in her apartment?
Thanks.
Stop cheating, bro.
How you doing?
I'm the, uh, Lyft driver
that you called
to take home your girlfriend.
Not a girlfriend, man.
- Just an intern.
- Oh. I'm sorry.
The, uh, credit card
was invalid.
Shithead.
Let you hang with us
'cause your daddy's a client,
and you fuck up
the first thing.
Come in.
- There you go.
- Wow.
I heard about these.
I've never seen one before.
Yeah, well, now you have.
Yeah.
Look, pay yourself whatever
and, uh,
give yourself a nice tip,
huh?
Thank you. Thank you.
You're not gonna ask me
if she got home okay?
She get home okay?
No.
Took her to Mass General.
They're pumping her stomach
as we speak.
What's her name?
You don't know, do you?
Okay.
This is the point
where usually I'd, uh,
give you a chance
to do the right thing,
but not tonight.
Tonight, I'm gonna need
your cameras,
cell phones,
anything you might've used
to record
what you did to her.
You knocked on
the wrong door tonight, pops.
Oh, God!
Jesus Christ!
Come here.
Get up.
Don't start crying now.
Give me your phone.
Right or left?
I don't know what you mean.
Handed. Are you right-
or left-handed?
- Right.
- Call 911.
You tell them the truth about
what happened in here tonight.
Your daddy's money is not
gonna save you this time.
- You understand?
- Yes, sir.
You know her name?
No.
Her name is Amy.
Give me your left hand.
I expect a five-star rating.
You understand?
Yes, sir.
Not for me, though.
For who?
For Amy.
That's right. For who?
- For Amy.
- For who?
For Amy.
Make sure I get
a five-star rating, junior.
Fuck.
Hello, Susan.
What?
How in God's name
did you know it was me?
I could smell you.
I...
For God's sake, I just peed.
Yeah, but you
ate asparagus vinaigrette
with soy sauce.
Oh, you.
Oh, I smelled your perfume.
- How are you?
- Mmm. Oh...
You good?
Better now.
Ah, very good.
- Brought you something.
- Ah, soup.
How'd that thing in Turkey
turn out?
- Ah. Happy ending.
- Hmm.
No pun intended.
Well, I guess that means
you owe me dinner.
I didn't agree to pay
for dinner. I, uh...
What, you gonna try
and weasel out of it?
I'm not weaseling. I just...
Oh, no, no, no, my friend.
I don't work for free.
How's Brian?
He's good.
Oh, he's got a new book out.
- Yeah?
- Mm-hmm.
- Maybe I should read it, huh?
- Oh, yeah.
You know,
if geopolitics of Nepal
prior to the 1816
Sugauli Treaty
is your bag, definitely.
Friendship has its limits.
So does matrimony.
I haven't read it yet.
Doubt I ever will.
You here on business?
Meetings.
Meetings, huh?
Well, birthdays
are the hardest.
I know I always think
of my brother on his.
Yeah.
I was, uh, folding
laundry the other day,
and, uh, I realized
that I didn't have
any clothes left
that Vivienne had ever seen.
I can't say
that's a bad thing.
What?
She didn't appreciate my taste
in clothing, either.
I'd buy something,
the next day it was missing.
I'd ask her about it,
and she'd say she didn't know
what I was talking about,
and...
But she'd act like she didn't
know what I was talking about.
I could tell. I mean, she's:
"I don't know what happened
to those purple shirts
that you used to buy."
And then I'd put one on
that she liked.
What?
I didn't say anything.
I'm sorry if I made a mistake
coming to you
on Vivienne's birthday.
I just...
Robert, I've been thinking.
Maybe you should go back, huh?
It's great, you helping
all these random people
and everything, but...
it's not gonna fill
that hole in your heart.
Go home, huh?
Make peace with it.
That's what Vivienne
would have wanted.
Oh, hey.
- Always a gentleman.
- That's right.
Hey, I'm obligated
to tell you these things,
being I'm the only friend
you got.
Mmm.
Airport, please.
Hey, Mr. McCall,
maybe you could find out
who did this
to Fatima's garden.
Kids.
What up, man?
How you doing?
Hey. You should make
the building do that.
It's what they supposed to.
Ah, "supposed to do"
and "will do"
are two different things,
Miles.
Yeah, but you live here,
right?
That's right.
I pay the rent, too.
You should let somebody else
do this, then.
Like who?
Shit, I don't know.
- Anybody.
- Huh?
- Not a tenant.
- You're right.
I guess anybody could do it,
but nobody does, Miles.
Ends up with everybody
complaining
because nobody did
what anybody could've done
or should've done
to begin with.
Yeah.
A'ight.
You know they got, uh...
they got painting companies
around here.
I know they charge $600, $700
to do the job.
I know that.
Word?
Shit, I'll do this for 350.
You?
Yeah.
- What?
- Nothing.
What, I look handicapped
or something?
Yo, it's a quick dip
and roll.
It ain't rocket science.
No, you're right.
I'm an artist, man.
I go to Bridgeview Arts.
Why aren't you in school?
I don't be doing
all them everyday classes.
You know, I got a...
got a special talent.
Yes, you do.
And it takes talent
to make money.
But it takes brains
to keep it, Miles.
Yeah, well, I'm out here,
uh, making my money, man.
Short money, Miles.
That's short money.
I tell you what.
350's a little high...
but I appreciate the offer.
A'ight.
- All right?
- A'ight.
It's gonna be
a lot of work, man.
- All right, Mr. McCall.
- All right.
So you still out here
doing this?
Yes, I am.
You ain't covering nothing.
Not yet.
What is this? Walmart paint?
Primer. You gotta prime it
before you paint it.
They don't teach you that
in art school?
Yeah, I knew that.
I've been thinking
about your offer.
Been, uh, calibrating, uh...
250.
- 250?
- Yeah.
250, I'll take care
of all of this for you.
- For 250?
- Yeah.
All right.
But you can only work on it
after school.
- Sh...
- Don't curse.
What time you get out?
3:15.
Okay, after school, 3:15.
Deal?
Okay?
A'ight.
But cash, a'ight?
Okay, cash.
- Don't be checking me, a'ight?
- I'll be checking for you.
A'ight.
Miles.
Stay off them corners, son.
Gun oil on his lips.
Nine-millimeter at his feet
was registered to the victim.
No other prints in the house.
You have questions?
Well, Mr. Calbert
did work for us,
and when something occurs
to one of ours,
the agency is obligated
to look into it.
So yes, you will be
hearing from us.
- Thank you.
- Susan, Susan.
Keep it locked down
until we get there, please.
I can't
find a file on this guy.
When did he become one of ours?
I don't know.
Upstairs kept him off the radar
- for some reason.
- Susan.
- Car's here. Car's here.
- Oh. Oh, hey.
- Oh, you look great.
- It's okay?
- Well, what about a tie?
- Um...
You need a tie, darling.
I'd do what she says.
- Uh...
- You have one?
- Got it.
- Great. That's perfect.
All right, I'll see you later.
- Have fun, sweetheart.
- Bye-bye.
Yeah, I'm gonna have
to go over there
and cross the T's.
You want to come?
Oh, damn, and leave
this shitty office?
You know, Brussels
has the best chocolates.
Mmm. Well, we'll go.
We'll find out.
Today, I broke
a personal best:
successive days alive.
All right.
Here, I got
photographic evidence.
That's the portrait
of my sister, Magda.
I was nine.
The war came.
Like most families,
we were separated.
My sister, Magda, and I
were sent to different camps.
I never saw her again.
60 years later, I'm in Paris,
and I see somebody
auctioning my painting.
12 million. Can you imagine?
"You got to have proof,"
they say, "to get it back."
Now I got here the proof.
Wait till the judge
sees this.
Looks like there's
coming a storm.
It's time for
your check-up, Sam.
Oh.
Hello, sweetheart.
He's still obsessed
with the painting.
Tried to help him years ago.
He said he, uh,
had proof it was his
even way back then.
He didn't.
No record, no bill of sales.
He just keeps going back to
court to hear the same thing.
Guess it gives him something
to focus on, I suppose.
It helps when you have
nobody left, yeah?
I thought the
reading went great.
Embarrassing, actually.
- No.
- I signed two books.
That's all.
Thank you.
You sure we can't drop you off
at the airport?
No, I'm fine, Brian.
Thank you.
- Thanks so much for coming.
- All right.
- Good night.
- Listen, do me a favor.
- Yeah?
See what you can find out.
Yeah?
Oh, another dinner, then.
- I'll see what I can do.
- Yeah?
I do fly off
to Brussels tomorrow.
- Thought you were retired.
- Oh, I am.
Just like you're dead.
- Okay.
- Good night.
Very good. Good night.
I saw you
painting yesterday, Miles.
It's primer.
It ain't paint.
So all this bullshit
under there...
it don't show through.
My brother painted that.
It's the place we grew up.
Yeah?
Well, you live here now.
Powder of some sort.
Hard drive contents
and cell records?
You'll have them later today.
Susan.
Okay. Thank you.
- You okay?
- Yeah, I'm fine.
Merci.
Right behind you.
I don't know.
Seems to me the judge...
he didn't even pay
any attention to me.
I mean, uh, he hardly looked
at all the evidence I had.
Well, that's it.
It was a very rare
painting, Sam.
Maybe...
maybe that's the reason
why it looks
so familiar to you.
This is my sister, Magda.
Was younger, but that's
the only picture survived.
Mmm.
My uncle commissioned
the portrait
as a gift
for her 12th birthday.
Was a young artist,
just beginning,
but, oh,
you should have seen it.
Not just the resemblance,
but a spirit that shone
through it.
It glowed, you know, like a beacon.
"My little brother,"
she'd say, "my Sammy."
I could never protect her.
To lose her twice...
I can't imagine.
Hello, Susan.
Hey. I had no idea
you were such an art lover.
That information you wanted
just came in.
- Kind of surprising.
- Okay.
I'm sending it to you
right now.
Good.
- Yeah?
- Hey.
Calbert's bank records
are fine.
Texts, e-mails.
No marital discord.
No girlfriends,
no boyfriends, no lovers.
Not even an inappropriate
message to a coworker.
And what about the wife?
Oh, come on, Dave.
Women fuck around, too.
I mean, think about it.
When's the last time you sent
your wife flowers, hmm?
Noted. Noted.
Data on Calbert's hard drive
just came in.
No, we'll talk about it
on the plane.
I want to get out of here
as soon as we can.
Run some theories by Stan.
Pardon.
Oh, uh... watch.
Excusez-moi. Monsieur.
Pardon. Merci.
Pardon.
I'll see you downstairs
at 6:00?
You got it.
Oh, hey, and how about
some of that delicious
Belgian chocolate
you're always talking about?
Or you're not getting
on the plane.
Guess I'm going back out.
Oh, crap.
Oh, great.
Oh, my...!
What do you want?
- What do you...? No!
- Get up, bitch!
You're-you're hurting me!
Where is the money?
I don't have any money!
Fucking why?
Who the fuck are you?
Come on!
No! Let me go!
Brick will make this pop out.
Picasso this entire building.
Picasso it?
- Yeah.
- Yeah, okay.
How much?
It's on the house.
I like that.
You been drawing a long time?
Since, uh...
about third grade.
What is this?
That's how I sign my work.
My brother, he was a boxer.
It's the right hand of God.
He catch you with it,
you know,
you go to Heaven or, uh...
Okay.
- He still fighting?
- Uh...
Somebody shot him.
Coming back from the gym.
Not even ganged up on
or nothing.
Just wanted his gym bag.
What?
I didn't say anything.
Anyway...
My grandmother says,
if you don't...
remember somebody out loud,
they die twice.
Grandmother was wise.
Hey, Brian.
Y-Yeah, listen,
I'm-I'm reading
your book right now,
and I can't believe you...
Yeah.
Got it.
Yo, Mr. McCall, you good?
Hey, yo, Mr. McCall.
Oh, thanks, Dave.
You know, the...
the police in Brussels,
th-they say that...
it happens in these hotels,
these robberies.
But she never wore any jewelry.
Not even a watch, and...
Except for this.
Here.
What did the agency say?
Uh, they said...
they'd do everything
in their power.
They're working
with Interpol.
Promised to find
whoever it was.
But...
I don't know what to do now.
Where's the phone?
Is it yours?
It's not mine!
Where the fuck is it?
Things to remember as the storm
continues its march northward.
We saw what Frances did
in the southeast part
of the country.
It appears to be moving here
as slowly
as it left the Gulf Coast.
That is what worries
meteorologists now.
Even as the storm is moving
up the Eastern Seaboard,
every city and town
that has been hit
has experienced storm surge...
...dangerous flood levels,
because the storm...
National Guard has been
deployed in several states
to prepare for lootings...
Excusez-moi. Monsieur.
Pardon. Merci.
Watch.
Excusez-moi. Monsieur.
I'll see you downstairs
at 6:00?
You got it.
I'll see you
downstairs at 6:00?
You got it.
You got fat, Dave.
I was in the same lobby
when that bomb went off.
Looking right at you...
...when that hotel
came down on us.
You were there,
and then you weren't.
Wasn't my day.
I went to your funeral.
Grieved a long time over you.
Susan, she knew?
I was your partner
for seven years, Mac.
I never kept anything
from you.
I'm sorry, Dave.
I am.
I never had a chance
to say how sorry I was...
about Vivienne.
You still at the beach?
Not in a long time.
Well, I got me that cabin.
Take the wife and kids up
a couple times a year.
Wouldn't have any of it...
if it weren't for Susan.
Life got...
...dark.
She talked me off that ledge
I was heading over.
Probably over a bowl of soup.
I owe her my life.
You ever talk to the boys?
No, not for years.
Hell of a team we were, right?
She never pushed
a button, Dave.
- Who?
- Susan.
On the elevator.
She never pushed
her floor number.
I checked all the video.
Backpackers got on first.
They pushed number 16.
She didn't have to.
They knew what floor
she was on.
They find 'em?
Pieces of them.
Couple of tweakers.
With sheets
as long as my arm.
My good arm, anyway.
Gas explosion.
At least that's what
they're calling it.
What do you call it?
Tying up loose ends.
Autopsy report.
Stab wound.
Two millimeters.
The lower third rib.
Close-quarter technique.
Exactly. That was taught.
This was no robbery.
Something else went on
in that room.
Mac, whatever it is,
whatever you need...
I'm in.
I know.
Same mud.
Same blood.
What's the deal, bruh?
Listen. Uh...
York.
Dave.
Listen, the gun...
next to Calbert
was on his right side.
He was right-handed. Why?
His wife was shot
by somebody left-handed.
Somebody else
was in that room.
Powder residue came
from a latex glove.
20,000 euros were found
in the backpackers' flat.
- Hey, Bob.
- Dave.
Those guys were set up.
Right. Agency assets
are taken out all the time.
Opposite side
loves sending a message.
Why stage it?
They didn't know
he was one of ours.
Susan was about to figure out
who was in that room.
That's why
she was killed, Dave.
The two were connected.
I'll get back to you
when I know more.
Keep me posted.
Yo, man, elevator's closed.
Listen up, little nigga.
You ready to put in work?
'Cause everybody in my camp
put in work.
- One down little nigga.
- Ain't no snitchin'.
- Ain't no bullshittin'.
- Clock in, nigga.
Yo, what's up
with that bitch hit?
Yeah, baby,
fucking hit that shit.
You got it, little man.
Pass that bump.
Let me get that, man.
Hey, you all
right, little nigga?
- Yeah, yeah. Yeah.
- Good?
- You sure? It's all that.
- A'ight.
Listen, man.
You know you gotta
spin the bend tonight, right?
spin the bend.
- Yeah.
- Didn't them niggas kill your brother?
- You gotta empty the whole thing on 'em.
- Yeah.
Right.
You gotta go take care
of that tonight.
Run down on them niggas.
Make sure you kill one
of them ill niggas tonight.
Make sure you empty
that whole thing.
Yo, listen.
Your mother already
buried your brother.
Don't have her bury two sons.
You hear me?
Yeah.
Don't come back
without it empty.
That's a fact, B.
- Shit.
- Let's go, Miles.
- Holy shit.
- Sit down. Sit down. Sit down.
- Sit down.
- Who the fuck is this nigga?
I'm your father.
Your mommy
just didn't tell you.
Let's go, Miles.
Do you know this nigga?
Yo, where you going, B?
Yeah?
Shit.
- Bam.
- Yo, who the fuck was that, yo?
Yo, what
the fuck happened, yo?
- What the fuck is going on, yo?
- The fuck happened to you?
- Come on.
- Yo, get the fuck off of me, man.
Huh?
Do you know
where the fuck we at?
I know. Do you?
I know where we are.
This what you want?
Is it what you want?
I thought you wanted to draw.
Isn't that what you said?
- Draw?
- Yeah.
Paint?
Yeah.
What the fuck
is that gonna get me?
That shit about to put food
on my fucking ma's table?
Huh?
That shit gonna pay
the fucking bills?
Nah.
You need to be a gangster.
You need to be a killer.
Little Yummy, huh?
You need them.
Okay,
if that's what you want.
If that's what makes you feel
like a man, then be a real man.
Let's get jumped in
right now.
- Here. Start with me.
- No.
No, start with me.
- Here. Start with me.
- No.
- No, take it.
- No, no.
Come on, killer.
Put it right there.
- No.
- You know how to hold it?
You know what you're doing?
Come on, killer.
There you go.
There you go. There you go.
Five pounds of pressure...
that's all it takes.
Come on, gangster.
Five pounds of pressure...
that's all it takes.
- Five pounds of pressure.
- Fuck.
That's all it takes.
All right.
Come on, give it to me.
You don't want it.
Give it to me.
Come on, give it to me.
I ain't gonna do nothing to it.
See? You know
what they are up there?
They're liars, and so am I.
- Hey, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo.
- See? See what happens
- when you deal with a liar?
- Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey.
Huh? You see what happens
when you deal with a liar?
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
I lied to your little punk ass.
- A'ight.
- Now I'm-a kill you.
What do you see when you
look at me? Tell me.
- You better give me a right answer.
- I don't know.
- What you see when you
- look at me, killer?
- I don't know!
- What you see, Yummy?
- I don't know.
- You don't know?
I don't know.
All right?
"Man" ain't spelled G-U-N, son.
You got a choice.
You got talent.
You got a chance,
and I don't want to hear about
your environment and what
your mama didn't give you
and the white man
won't give you no shot.
You got a chance.
Use it while you still alive.
You don't know what death is.
You have no idea what death is.
Make a decision.
All right.
Hey, yo, Mr. McCall.
Why me?
Why not you?
But... but why me?
Let's find out together.
And with a storm this size,
that surge could be
as much as six feet.
It's the speed of the hurricane
and that giant eye
that could absolutely
deluge the coast.
...and the fact
that it's moving so slowly,
appears in no hurry to move on.
Waiting in
on the press conference
of the governor
about the continuing efforts
to prepare for the storm...
- Hello?
- Mr. McCall?
Who is it?
It's me, Miles.
I finished the bricks
outside.
Yeah, I saw it.
Oh, uh, this is your change
for the extra paint.
- That's all of it?
- Yeah.
So, anyway, uh...
you have something to drink?
Yes, I do.
- Would you like something to drink?
- Yeah.
Come on in.
Iced tea or water?
What I look like, Jackie Chan?
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
Yo, you know
they sell these in sets.
Yeah.
What you making?
Arroz con pollo.
Yeah, Moms makes
the same thing.
- Does she?
- Yeah, she puts some...
I'm not your moms.
And that's not your pot.
And this is not your house.
You understand?
- Yeah. Yeah.
- Okay.
Yo, this wall
need a paint job.
Yeah, it does.
Yeah.
- I could do it for you.
- Could you?
Yeah.
How much?
If I could get a plate
of that food...
Yeah, man...
No, seriously, uh, 115.
That cool?
All right,
I'll make a deal with you.
115, huh?
Yeah.
Here you go. Free.
Read that. Can you read?
- Yeah.
- What does it say?
Ta-Nehisi Coates,
"Between the World and Me."
All right.
You read that, we got a deal.
Airport?
Yeah.
Is it somebody's birthday?
My daughter.
Nice.
How old is she?
She's five.
Guess you don't fly
that often, huh?
Been driving in the opposite
direction of Logan
for the last three minutes.
Hey!
Um, no crust, either.
- Eat up, sweetie.
- Mom? Mom says I have to go
to the dentist.
She never has to go
- That's gotta be the gardener?
- Grapes.
- Can I have a treat?
- You know where the grapes are.
Oh, my God.
My life... is so hard.
Here's your grapes.
- What...?
- Come on.
- Show me what you can do.
- But...
- Seriously?
- Seriously.
Come on.
Hi, baby.
Mommy made a nice map.
"A. Maine." Very good.
"B. New Hams..."
"New Hamster."
Carol, who is it?
Carol?
It's New Hampshire,
not New Hamster.
But I like it as "New Hamster."
Okay, you leave it
"New Hamster."
Honey, the front
doorbell is broken.
Your old Army buddy
was at the back door
for almost five minutes.
Actually, I was his team leader
seven years.
Oh, my...
Baby, I'm so sorry.
I must have forgot...
this is...
I got the days mixed up.
This is Robert McCall.
- This is my wife, Carol.
- Hi.
- Hi. Pleasure to meet you.
- My pleasure. Thanks.
These are...
these are our daughters.
- Molly, Alice.
- Hi. Hi.
- Come here, baby. Come here.
- How are you?
- Please make yourself at home.
- Say hi to...
- Oh, thank you. Thank you.
- Call him Mac.
- Do you want some coffee?
- Uh, no. I'm fine, thank you.
Sorry about the mess.
- We were just...
- No problem, no problem.
I gotta get these two
off to school.
- Okay.
- Girls, let's go.
Out of these pajamas.
Nice.
Robert, nice to meet you.
Oh, my pleasure.
- All righty.
- Sit down. Come here.
Yep.
Take these off. Let's go.
- You all right?
- Yeah. Mm-hmm.
Give those teeth a brush.
You got a beautiful family.
Thanks.
What's going on?
Uh...
I took this off the guy...
who tried to kill me
yesterday.
It's like you said...
they're cleaning up.
Everybody who's looking
into the Brussels hit...
nobody's safe.
You, your family.
Nobody.
That's military-grade
encryption.
You should take it
to your office,
run the numbers and, uh,
check the names against
the passenger manifests
in and out of Brussels in the
days surrounding the flight.
Whoever we're looking for
made calls to that phone.
I'm on it. I'm on it.
Tell me I'm wrong, Dave.
You gonna answer it?
What happened, Dave?
You died.
That's what happened.
Three months after you...
mmm, disappeared,
government shut us down.
I went private right after.
Doing the same things you and I
did for God and country...
killing names
on a piece of paper.
Only now...
now there's a price
next to them.
- We killed the enemy.
- Who said they were the enemy?
Not us. Not me.
We just followed orders.
Mac...
there are no good
and bad people anymore.
No.
No enemies.
Just...
unfortunates.
And Susan?
Unfortunate.
No one
knew the Brussels contract
was a deep agency asset.
Susan was gonna figure out
who was in that dining room.
She was the only one
who could have, right?
Until you crawled out
of your grave.
You get the chocolate?
Oh, fuck.
Susan worked
in a dangerous world, Mac.
Could have happened anytime
by anybody.
But it wasn't anybody;
it was you.
Just...
You spare me the righteous
bullshit, all right?
You do what you have to do,
and you move on.
There's no moving on
from this, Dave.
We all gotta pay
for our sins.
Oh, yeah,
what about you?
Do you deserve to die
for yours?
Hundred times over.
Oh. All right.
Well, guess what.
There is no sin.
No virtue.
It's just shit people do.
They trained us
to kill people
and risk our lives doing it,
and then one day,
you get a call
saying they're done with you.
"Thank you for your service.
Here's a plaque."
You need a job?
Good luck.
You need medical insurance?
See the VA.
See, one day,
you're an asset.
The next, you're
a fucking afterthought.
It was a natural evolution.
It's who we were.
It's what we did.
It's what you did.
Now it's what we do.
"We"?
It's not just me, Mac.
It's all of us.
Ari, Resnik, Kovac.
All of us.
Family.
Gentlemen.
Mac.
You look pretty good
for a dead guy.
We all want you to know
none of this is, uh, personal.
What you do, what you
become is not my concern.
The world is full
of so-called men like you.
And in a perfect world,
everything we do
comes with a price, but...
this ain't a perfect world.
People do bad things.
If you're lucky,
you get a chance to...
set it right.
But most of the time,
it goes unpunished.
This ain't
one of them times.
The mistake you made
was you killed my friend,
so I'm going to kill
each and every one of you,
and the only disappointment
in it for me
is that I only get
to do it once.
Train's gotta go.
Alice has music practice
at 7:45.
- Hey, Ari, fellas.
- Hey, Carol.
Robert, hope
to see you again.
Nice to meet you, too.
Uh...
Dave said you could give me
a lift to the, uh, station?
- Bye, Daddy.
- Bye, Dad.
Help and company?
Let's go.
See?
Help and company.
You take the little one.
Okay.
Come on.
See you at work.
Look, I don't think my wife
had a favorite.
She never gave a lot of thought
to clothes.
I'm fine.
I'll bring something over
in the morning.
Who's coming after me?
The men who killed Susan.
Why?
Because you're a loose end.
What's up, Miles?
Hey, yo, what up, man?
Where are you?
Yeah, I'm at your crib,
actually.
All right, listen, son.
I don't have time right...
Finishing up these walls.
Going with
the spearmint green.
Yo, you got any food
around here? I'm starving.
What's all that barking?
Go to the window.
Tell me what you see.
Yeah.
Hey, these dogs outside
going crazy.
Listen. Hey.
Out toward the street...
tell me what you see.
Oh, it's just some dude
out here delivering pizza.
Hang on.
Hey, yo.
Hey, yo, Mr. McCall.
Shit.
Oh, shit.
Hey, Mr. McCall, I think
somebody's trying to get ins...
Miles, listen to me
real carefully.
Go to the bedroom.
Go to my bedroom.
You'll see a bookshelf.
- Go.
- Yo, what?
Just go.
- Hey, yo, what...?
- Miles.
- A'ight. A'ight.
- Miles. See it?
- Yeah.
- All right.
Middle shelf, there's a book by
Richard Wright, "Native Son."
- What?
- Listen. Just do what I tell you.
"Native Son." "Native Son."
- Pull it out.
- What, you want me to read it?
Pull the book out.
You'll see a button behind it.
I want you to push the button.
You're gonna push the button.
It'll open up.
You go inside.
You close the door behind you.
A'ight.
Man. Oh, man, oh, man.
Yo, what is this place?
All right, calm down,
calm down.
Just sit down. Be quiet.
Be very quiet.
Don't move.
Hey, Mr. McCall.
Yo, who are these people?
Let me worry about that.
Clear.
Calm down.
- Get in the hole. Go inside.
- All right.
Yo, man, I don't do well
in small spaces, man.
Yo, I can't even breathe, man.
Son, son, slow down.
Fucking lungs is...
is closing up and shit.
He's looking right at me.
Don't worry about him.
It's a two-way mirror.
You can see them.
They can't see you.
Man, it's too dark in here.
Yo, I can't even feel my legs.
I can't even see my feet.
Relax. Just breathe.
Don't talk too loud.
Turn your phone off.
They'll see the light.
Turn it off.
Fuck.
How you doing, Dave?
You know who it is.
Listen, since you're
in my house,
water my plants for me,
will you?
'Cause I'm not gonna be back
for a while.
It's a mistake to go to war
with us, McCall.
You got it backwards, Dave.
You're going to war with me.
You know where I'll be.
I know where he's headed.
He's going home.
Hey, kid.
Back up.
- The town's evacuated.
- How you doing, Officer?
Just got off a double shift.
Just gonna check
- and see if I left my gas on.
- All right, make it quick.
Let the gray BMW through.
Copy that.
What do we have here?
I need you to turn around.
Town's been evacuated.
Where are you?
Slow down.
That was his wife's bakery.
Go.
Pull over here.
Clear the alley.
Mac's house is back there.
Making entry, yellow house.
All clear. Coming out.
Taking high ground.
I got movement... 12:00.
Kovac, move in.
Ari, what's your sitrep?
Locking down, south side.
Making entry, north side.
Kovac.
Kovac!
Kovac, come back!
Shots fired!
Shots fired! I'm going in.
Going in.
York, you got eyes on him?
I see him.
Making entry, north side.
Fuck.
Ah, fuck.
Kovac's down. He's gone.
- Say again.
- Kovac.
He's down. He's fucked.
Push towards the ocean.
Repeat... push
towards the ocean.
What the fuck?
Ari.
Resnik! Somebody talk to me.
Son of a bitch!
Ari's down! Ari's down!
And Mac made
a fucking mess of him!
There's pictures of Susan
everywhere.
He's picking us apart, man.
I need fucking eyes!
Goddamn it!
I'm on the southwest corner
of the yellow building.
I got a blood trail...
looks like he's headed
- across the main drag.
- Rear of the bakery.
Copy that.
Move inside, Resnik.
Move inside.
Resnik, do you copy?
Resnik!
Come back!
Fuck!
Just me and you, Dave.
Nobody's left.
Not exactly.
Remember what you taught me.
Always have
a contingency plan.
Come on, Mac.
Show yourself.
I don't know
who the kid is, Mac,
or if he means
anything to you.
I took the chance
that he matters.
I'll make it simple.
Step out, show yourself,
and I won't kill the kid.
The wind makes it interesting.
Side mirror.
Two more.
Third one goes through
the middle of the trunk.
Taillight.
I was a hair off on that one.
I might've hit the kid.
All right!
Time's up, Mac.
Nice move, Mac.
But it's not gonna make
any difference.
Where are you,
you son of a bitch?
Fuck you, Mac!
Fuck you!
You couldn't save your wife,
you couldn't save Susan,
and you're not gonna save
this fucking kid.
Is that in your playbook?
Is that in
your fucking playbook?
Show yourself!
All right, take your time.
Right here.
Sit down right here.
There we go.
Put this on.
All right.
There you go.
Let's see.
Ah...
Yeah, it went in and out.
It's not bad.
- Hey, yo.
- Yeah?
My moms is gonna be pissed.
Yeah, I'll talk to her.
Yo, not at me, man.
- At you.
- You talk to her, then.
A'ight.
Count to three.
- One, two, three.
- Three.
- It's all good.
- Yep.
I got your back.
I appreciate it.
Hey, Mr. McCall.
Yeah?
Who are you, man?
- Hey, Mr. McCall.
- Yeah?
I think the bleeding stopped.
Good. Good.
Sit down.
This your place?
Yes, it is.
Come on, sit down.
What are you drawing?
I'm, uh...
I'm working on
a superhero character.
- What's his power?
He knows things
before you do.
You know,
he has, uh...
secret rooms,
magic locks.
You know,
shit like that.
S-St-Stuff like that.
He fly?
Nah.
He act-actually drives
a Malibu.
That's funny?
Honestly... that's cool.
- Okay.
- I love it.
Oh, respect.
I-I appreciate that.
So... so you
can understand, um,
that when a resident,
uh, says things
that are, um...
that are grandiose by nature,
we tend to dismiss it.
So you can imagine how, um,
surprised we were today
when, uh... when, um...
If you could just
give me a moment, okay?
Here.
My Sammy?
Magda. Oh!
Subtitles by explosiveskull
Resync by GoldenBeard
Please rate this subtitle at www.osdb.link/6xvwp
Help other users to choose the best subtitles