[Military drums play]
Atten-hut!
Here's our man.
Professor Howard Plummer.
He's been kidnapped
by a group of Serbian rebels.
I know we've been up for 72
hours, but I expect perfection.
Nothing else.
[Beeping]
The enemy has a boat,
four jet skis, and a chopper.
I'll take you guys in
until we hit radar range.
Then you'll dive from there.
Once we hit our target,
Red One, Red Two,
you take out our escorts.
I'll handle the chopper,
and I'll find the professor.
Red Three, you radio in
for our copter.
- Do you copy?
- Sir, yes sir!
- [SEALS] Sir, yes sir!
We are SEALS.
And this is what we do.
[All grunting, yelling]
[Engine shutting down]
[Yelling in Serbian]
[Beeping]
- Ah!
- [Grunting]
[Over radio] Red Two, handle the boat.
I'll take care of the bozos
on the jet ski.
- [Grunting]
- [Straining]
- [Groaning]
Ah!
Oh!
[Man straining]
[Muffled]
Gotcha.
Lieutenant Shane Wolfe,
U.S. Navy.
- Where is the briefcase?
- [Grunting]
It's right behind you.
Man, am I glad to see you.
- I never thought I'd see my family...
- I'll get you out.
We're gonna do it my way.
No highway option.
Yeah, I'm with you. Absolutely.
Lieutenant, thank you so much
for saving my life.
If I had died back there,
my wife, she would've killed me.
Just a joke.
Do you mind if I call my wife
to tell her I'm okay?
I have strict orders
to get you out of here safely.
We gotta keep moving.
Lieutenant, I am safe.
Please. She thinks I'm dead.
- All right, make it quick.
- Okay.
- Zoe, Seth, Lulu, Peter, Tyler.
- [Beeping]
It's voice activated.
[Chuckles] Hey.
These are my kids.
You'd like 'em.
They're really great.
I doubt it. Hurry up.
Hey! We're almost ready.
Give us another sec.
- Professor!
- [Gunshots]
[Grunts]
The doctor says you've
healed up real good, Shane.
I should've been
out of here weeks ago.
Look, I know heads
are gonna roll for this.
Hey, you took a bullet.
Yeah, but I want you to know
I take full responsibility
for what happened
to the professor.
Plummer was the best
security expert
the Department of Defense
ever had.
He was working on a program to scramble
launch codes that he called "GHOST":
Guided High-altitude
Scrambling Transmitter.
One pulse from a GHOST satellite
and a country can't launch
its own nukes.
That's why the Serbians
kidnapped him.
They must have thought that
GHOST was in that briefcase.
GHOST is still out there.
Which is why I'm sending you
back in.
I know you've never lost anybody
before, Shane.
I was with your father
when he led a platoon...
With all due respect,
I'd appreciate it if we kept
my father out of this.
All I'm saying is that it
happens to the best of them.
And you're the best.
I need someone I can trust on this
- and I know I can trust you.
- Okay.
I'll put a team together.
No. It's not
that kind of mission.
This is at the top of the Pentagon's
priority list.
[Man] Two days ago,
I got a call from Admiral Blair.
It seems that the professor's widow
contacted him.
Whoever killed her husband
must think that GHOST
is still in that house.
Now, maybe it is, maybe it isn't.
A safety deposit box has been discovered
in Zurich in the Plummers' name.
I've been assigned to escort Mrs.
Plummer there to retrieve the contents.
We're hoping it's the GHOST program.
In the meantime, someone
needs to watch over those kids.
That's where you come in.
While there, you'll be looking
for the hidden program as well.
[Squeaking]
[Squeaks]
[Doorbell]
Ah!
You must be Lieutenant Wolfe!
Admiral Blair said you'd be coming.
Come on in.
Meet the rest of the gang.
Come on.
Kids! Get your butts
down here and say hello!
Okay, you've already met Lulu.
This is Zoe, Seth and Peter.
Kids, this is Lieutenant Wolfe.
He's gonna stay with you
while I'm away.
- [Kids] Hi.
- Hi.
- Oh! This is Helga and Tyler.
- [Baby cooing]
Ma'am. Baby.
- That's a pretty dress.
- [Romanian accent] Thank you.
I have date
with butcher tonight.
I want to look nice.
[Gasping] Ah!
[Speaking Romanian]
[Whimpering]
You have a pleasant family.
Well, for the younger ones,
I think it hasn't really
sunk in yet.
It's been hardest
on Zoe and Seth.
But they don't really
like to talk about it.
Well, it must be hard
on all of you.
[Mrs. Plummer]
Howard wasn't around much.
His work took him
all over the world.
He'd be gone six,
seven months at a time.
Yeah, I can understand
that lifestyle.
Anyway, about a week ago,
someone broke into the house.
No one was home.
I didn't tell the kids 'cause
I didn't wanna scare them.
Mrs. Plummer, I've dealt with...
- Ow! Oh, my God!
- [Quacking]
I'm sorry. That's Gary.
He was Howard's.
Gary, down!
He bit me.
Yeah, well,
he thinks he's a guard dog.
- Mrs. Plummer?
- Oh, call me Julie. Please.
I'm gonna go outside
and have a look around.
Out, out.
I'm gonna miss you.
Mmm...
I'm gonna miss you too.
I'll be back in 48 hours, okay?
Bye, pumpkin.
I love you, pumpkin.
Oh, and kids? Remember,
whatever Lieutenant Wolfe
asks you to do, do it.
Mom, chill.
We're gonna be fine.
I'm sorry.
I don't do this very often.
You're going away for a few days.
Yeah, I know.
I got it.
Okay. Here you go, Helga.
- I take baby.
- Bye. Bye.
- It's okay.
- [Baby cries]
You remember
the emergency numbers, right?
Don't worry, Mrs. Plummer,
your kids'll be safe with me.
Your little angels will be fine,
Mrs. Plummer.
- Go.
- [Engine turns]
- [Helga] Bye-bye.
- Bye.
[Helga] Have some fun.
[Chuckles] Bye-bye.
Tell me,
are you licensed to kill?
No, ma'am.
Too bad.
It could have come in handy.
[Baby crying]
- [Gunshots]
- [Lulu] Ah!
[Man] Prepare to be annihilated.
[Lulu] Please!
[Zoe] Oh, my God! Shut up!
[Man] Prepare to be annihilated.
- [Gunshots]
- [Crashing]
Hey!
- Where's the baby?
- [Zoe] Tell me. Come on.
[Zoe laughing] No!
Shut up! No, she didn't.
- Shut up! Shut your mouth!
- [Quacking]
[Zoe] Oh, my God. Tell me!
Is there anyone here
that understands
the meaning of the word
"discipline"?
Hey, Flipper. You don't like it?
Do something. I make bottle.
- [Gasps]
- [Crying]
Thank you, Peter.
[Chuckles]
[Beeping]
- Yes!
- [Beeping stops]
- Ow!
- Gotcha!
- Ah!
- [Grunting]
[Sirens blaring]
What's your problem?
Get off me!
[Zoe] Oh, my God!
What are you doing, you spaz?
That's my boyfriend!
So you're the one breaking in!
- Go back inside!
- No!
[Woman speaking Korean]
[Speaking Korean]
We speak English, buddy.
Look, about the sirens
and the strobe lights.
We own a bakery, so we're up
kind of early. Would you mind?
Sorry.
[Sirens stop]
Oh, and we found this
in our pool filter.
Keep that zoo reined in,
huh, babysitter?
[Squeaking]
Yo, fool, handle me like that again
and I'll lay knuckles upside your head!
Okay! Enough is enough!
Come on, Scott, let's go!
- Come on.
- No, you don't.
Get back here.
Give me 20.
I meant push-ups!
- Zoe?
- Drop down! Do 20!
- This is not the Army or Navy!
- [Wolfe] One...
Real nice move, Lt. Smooth.
He'll probably never speak to me!
- Then I did you a favor.
- Whoa!
Personal bubble invasion.
Your mother was worried sick
about you!
You should call here and tell her.
I'm sure you'll take care of that
for me.
Stay out of my life!
[Grunts]
[Groans]
Wait! You can't do this!
I have plans!
It's Saturday night! Ow!
Not anymore.
- You too. Lights out.
- [Scoffs] Bite me.
Boy, this family's in
for a rude awakening.
# Don't make a move
till you're in the groove
# And do the Peter Panda dance
# Just hop three times
like a kangaroo
# Side-step twice
just like those crabs do
# Three steps forward
One step back
# Then quick like a turtle
Lie on your back
# Roll like a log
till you can't no more...
[birds chirping]
[Whistle blowing]
[Shrieks]
What are you doing?
You're burning daylight! Move!
It's Sunday.
And it's 6am!
You're insane!
- Listen up!
- [Helga chattering]
Your behavior is unacceptable.
In order to maintain
a state of safety,
we need to maintain
a state of order.
[Helga] One more little bite?
We going to be strong mine
worker when we grow up.
Excuse me.
Excuse me!
Now, I've only got one rule.
Everything is done my way.
No highway option.
- Do you copy?
What? I said, "Do you copy?"
- Do not copy me.
Hey, I mean it.
Cut it out!
- Uh...
- [Gary quacking]
- [Peter farts]
- [Quacking]
- Peter farted.
- [Kids groaning]
- [Zoe] Oh, that is so gross.
- [Wolfe] Quiet!
Everybody up.
That means you too.
Tracking devices,
never take them off.
The panic button
is for emergencies only.
Touch that,
you'd better be dying.
- [Beeps]
- Or you're dead.
I would rather chew off my arm
than wear that.
Just because my mom is paranoid doesn't
mean we have to take orders from you.
Let me explain how
the chain of command works.
I tell you what to do
and you do it!
End of chain.
I'm not gonna have time
to remember all of your names.
You'll be Red Leader.
Red Baby. Red One. Red.
Where's the older male?
There were five.
He walks like Dracula
with footsteps
silent like death.
[Zoe] He's in his room.
Red Two!
Red Two, open up!
[Toilet flushing]
What have you done?
What? I thought...
Is this what you're
trained to do?
A "shock and awe" on my door?
I can fix that
with a hammer and some nails.
- It's real easy to fix.
- No, it's not! Look!
It's broken in half!
You can't fix that!
If you'd been wearing this,
this wouldn't have happened.
What are you talking about?
I was in the bathroom!
You know I would never
ask you for your help...
...but he has got to go.
[Beeping]
[Lulu] Somebody help me, please!
- Help me, somebody!
- [Moaning]
- Stop it, Peter! This is nuts!
- Peter, cut this out.
Hey, good soldiers
aren't scared of anything.
I'm not scared. I'm annoyed.
Ever since he heard Daddy say
there was a ghost in the house,
he puts on that blanket and chases me
everywhere. It drives me crazy.
Peter, have you seen this ghost?
All right, here he comes.
Hey! You leave towel
on floor in bathroom.
I pick up after kids,
not you.
And light a match next time.
[Gasping] Oh!
[Groaning]
[Honking]
[French accent]
Good news.
Your background checks
have cleared,
and we are free
to give you the box.
- Oh.
- Excellent.
Just as soon as you
provide us with the passwords.
Passwords?
It was your husband's wish
that the person who collects the box
must provide us
with the passwords.
Great.
- Is it "The GHOST?"
- Ghost.
Mmm... No.
- [Door slamming]
- [Grumbling]
These brats! Sugi pula!
I had it!
- Remain calm.
- I am calm.
I quit!
That makes me calm.
Let's not be hasty about this.
[Ringing]
[Mrs. Miller] Hello? Hello?
- Don't even think about it!
- [Mrs. Miller] Lt. Wolfe?
It's Julie Plummer.
- Who's this?
- Julie Plummer.
- What's that?
- Julie Plummer!
- [Grunting]
- Ah!
- Oh, Mrs. Plummer.
- Did something fall?
- What was that noise?
- Nothing. Everything's okay!
You'll be happy to know that I found
the culprit that's been sneaking around!
- Great. Who was it?
- Just some teenager.
Teenager? I wanted to tell you
I'm gonna be a few more days.
- You'll be a few more days?
- [Screaming]
- Yes, is that a problem?
- No, that's no problem!
[Straining] No, I'm fine.
I'm just... I'm just doing my...
- [grunts]
- Your what?
- Duty.
- Sure everything's okay?
Things are great,
Mrs. Plummer.
Yeah, you just do
whatever you have to.
- Well, tell the kids I said...
- Bye, Mrs. Plummer!
[Wolfe] Just hang...
Let's calm down.
[Both panting]
Just... just try to relax.
- [Growling]
- [Groaning] Ah!
- Ah! She bit me!
- [Helga grunting]
- [Sirens blaring]
- Red Leader!
I command you to come back here!
That's a direct order!
You can't leave a man behind!
Red Leader!
I don't even know
how to change a diaper!
[Woman] Don't worry!
If she loves you,
she'll come back, huh?
[Bells ringing]
Okay, everybody, listen up.
There's been a change of plans.
Your mother's not coming home
as soon as she expected.
- When is she coming back?
- [Wolfe] Soon.
For now,
we'll just have some more big fun.
That's what we've been doing?
Having fun?
- Tomorrow's a school day.
- [Seth] I have wrestling.
I need a release for Driver's Ed.
I've got Fireflies.
I have to go to the mall.
I have to stop her
from spending so much.
Whoa, okay, Halt. Halt!
We'll take this hill
one inch at a time.
Only then can we rise
to the challenge.
[Peter farts]
[Wolfe] Okay,
who's gonna change Red Baby?
Guys?
Ah!
God! Red Baby!
- Alrighty. We'll try this.
- [Toilet flushing]
Yes. Whoa.
Ooh. Soak that up a bit.
Hi. Zoe says you look
like The Hulk.
I think you're cute.
Thank you.
- Do you do kung fu?
- Yes.
Did you ever punch someone
so hard that their head came off?
No.
Why are your boobs so big?
They're not boobs.
Do you have to wear a bra?
Will my boobs
get as big as yours someday?
You know, little girl,
I think it's time you went
nappy-poo in beddy-bye land.
Do I look like I'm five to you?
What did I say?
Disrespectful. And to think
I was interested in you!
[Door slams]
[Wolfe] Okay, troops! Breakfast!
What are you waiting for?
Dig in.
Feel free to mix and match.
Stay away from the cheese.
It'll back you up.
Don't worry about running out.
I can get lots more of these.
I've survived months
off this stuff.
Okay, like, I'm really gonna eat
all of these carbs?
[Gary quacking]
I can cross my eyes.
Wanna see?
No.
[Crying]
Tyler hates it when I do that.
I know how he feels.
What's he...? Red Four!
[Tyler crying]
[Ringing]
- Plummer residence.
- [Man muffled over phone]
Yes, I know it's Monday today.
No, Mrs. Plummer's away.
Yes, we'll be right there.
Who was that?
Your vice principal.
He said that if you and Seth
are late again,
you're both suspended.
He wants to see you
in his office right away.
[Beeping]
What is it?
- It's a minivan.
- Ugh.
[Wolfe] Now,
is this supposed to...?
- How do we...?
- Excuse me, Mr. Wolfe?
If you don't hurry up,
we're gonna be late for sure.
Not on my watch.
- Hold that.
- How fast is your watch?
You'll be suspended for sure.
[Screeching]
- [Seth] Whoa! Whoa! Whoa!
- [Zoe] Oh, my God!
Who drives like this?
You're crazy!
- [Bell ringing]
- [Kids chattering]
[Seth] What are you doing?
Stop!
[Footsteps approaching]
- [Bell ringing]
- Got 'em here.
My fault.
Yeah, I always said these kids
needed a parole officer.
I guess, uh, Mrs. Plummer
thought so too, huh?
Wow, you got a real, uh,
upper torso going on, huh?
You ever, uh, do any time?
- [Low] Sasquatch.
- [Zoe giggles]
- You got something to say, boy?
- No.
No? Good.
Wow, it looks like you
have a pair of legs
coming out of your shoulders.
- You hit the gym a lot, do you?
- Eh.
- [Low] Woolly Mammoth.
- You know what, Creeper?
You just bought yourself
an extra 15 minutes on the mats.
With the Murninator!
Excuse me.
Lieutenant Shane Wolfe.
I'm watching the kids
for the Plummers. A few days.
Oh, babysitter, huh?
Well, good.
Whatever job you can get, right?
I'm Murney.
Duane Murney.
My friends call me
"Little Puppet. "
I'm the VP here.
I'm in charge of discipline,
conduct and truancy
from top to bottom,
K through 12.
You're in my house now,
strong man.
- You're the vice principal.
- And the wrestling coach.
See the Creeper over there?
He has played hooky from every
wrestling practice this month.
And her, she has missed
22 Driver's Ed classes.
Out of 23!
These are the worst students
in my school.
- I'm ashamed...
- [woman] Your school?
Good morning, kids.
[Clears throat] Mr. Murney,
thanks for watching my chair.
- I'll take it from here.
- [Murney] Roger. Absolutely.
I was just informing
our new friend here
about some of the duties
as vice principal.
Speaking of which, how's it
going with the investigation
into the baloney slices
on the cafeteria ceiling?
- Taking some interesting turns.
- Keep up the good work.
Right. I'll be on the roof.
Bye, now.
All right, it's time
to get back to class.
I'll cut you some slack seeing as
it's Lt. Wolfe's first day. Thank you.
Okay.
- Can I get you some coffee?
- Yes, please.
So, what's with this Murninator?
He's big, he's hairy,
he's sometimes smelly,
but he's harmless
and he has tenure.
[Sighs] So, you're the bodyguard?
Mrs. Plummer thought the kids...
She briefed me on everything
and she told me that the kids
aren't fully aware of the situation
and that's the way she wants it.
She also told me
you're a "Teams" guy.
- Yes, I am.
- Well, Petty Officer Third Class
- Claire Fletcher at your service.
- You're kidding.
Four years at Naval Base
Coronado. They paid for college.
- Honor, courage.
- Commitment.
It's the way I run this school.
I like that.
So, permission to stick around
and keep eyes on the kids?
Permission granted.
[Kids chattering]
[Girls] We don't need no music
We don't need no band
All we need is Mustangs
and jammin' in the stands
We said jammin' in the stands
J- A-M-M-I-N
Jammin' in the stands
What? J-A-M-M-I-N
- Go, Mustangs! Whoo!
- [Beeping]
[Wolfe] "Black belt.
Honorable discharge. "
Clean as a whistle.
[Chuckles]
- Yeah, you little punk!
- Where's your babysitter now?
Hey!
- Enough.
- All right, you heard the lady.
Let's break it up, guys.
Come on. Hmm?
Relax, Popeye.
Boys will be boys, huh?
It's kinda good for the Creeper.
Gives him a chance to punk up.
- Learn to defend himself.
- Six against one?
Well, the odds are never pretty.
But look at it as, like,
a preparation for him.
The naked streets of Bethesda
can be so dark and dangerous.
- Right, Creeper?
- Ooh. Whoa.
You're pretty quick there, frogman.
I, myself,
happen to be a black belt.
That's why they wanted me
to coach the wrestling team.
Ooh-ah! [snorts]
Sensei. [neck cracks]
You know what that's called, homeboy?
Total control.
You all right? Hmm?
Maybe sometime you can pop by
the wrestling class
and, uh, we'll show the boys
how a couple pros do it.
What do you think?
I'll go easy on you.
- I'm on duty.
- You're on duty.
Oh, that's right,
you're a babysitter.
So it's kinda like "doo-doo" duty.
[Laughs]
Don't worry about it.
We'll do it on a day when you're
not, uh, washing your hair. Hmm?
And I'll see you in class.
At ease.
That guy don't have his head on right.
I was fine!
I don't need your help!
Okay, okay.
- Aw. Hey, rough day?
- I tried feeding him.
Yeah? Did you try changing him?
- Would you help me?
- No.
- Just the thought of...
- [beeping]
- Emergency.
- What are you...? I... Hey!
Hi.
[Girl] What's up with him?
- [Honking]
- [Screeching]
[Screeching]
Where are you going?
[Man] Hey!
What's wrong with you?
[Beeping continues]
[Door slams]
[All gasping]
Ha-ha.
I should go, okay?
Call me, you guys,
if you need anything.
My number's on the fridge.
Are you okay?
- Oh... Wow.
- [Flies buzzing]
Is there anything I can do?
- I'm okay.
- Okay.
- Can I get you anything?
- I'm fine.
I mean, they're just kids,
you know.
Call me if you need anything.
Okay?
After you shower.
Or, before. It doesn't matter.
I'll see you guys.
- [Gagging]
- [Door shuts]
Very funny.
Thank you for the letter.
[Giggling]
[Lulu] Guys, be quiet.
I told you he had boobs.
Lulu, can I see you
in the family room?
Who are those people?
My troop. Monday, Wednesday
and Saturday are troop nights.
- Get rid of 'em.
- I can't.
Parents go out on troop nights.
They'll be back at 8:00.
Mom's our den mother!
You better tell your little
friends that they have to...
- Today we're supposed to sell cookies.
- I don't do cookies.
We have to. If we don't
sell enough cookies,
we can't go
to the Jamboree.
They're waving at me.
All right, ladies!
Here's how it's gonna be!
Tonight I'm your den mother.
That means if you want
to live to see tomorrow,
you do exactly as I say!
Do we understand each other?
Den mother,
you frighten me.
Good.
Now, let's move out!
- I call the front!
- Middle back!
Fine, I'll get the back.
[Zoe] Yeah, he's kind
of a dork, but he's okay.
- [Julie on phone] How's Helga?
- Helga's fine.
- When are you getting home?
- I'm sorry...
Look, Mom, I'd love to stay and chat
all day, but I have homework to do.
[Cash register beeping]
Oh, no!
They're back!
Hey, Skeever, what glows
in the dark till you squish 'em?
Fireflies!
[Boys laughing]
Please. Leave us alone.
This is troop 16 territory.
How are we supposed
to sell raffle tickets
if this place reeks
of your skanky cookies?
Hey! Hey!
- Boo!
- [Girls screaming]
[Boys laughing]
[Boys] Get outta here!
- These cookies taste disgusting.
- I know.
- We really scared these guys.
- Where are my troops?
[Beeping]
Lulu, what happened?
Those boys over there
broke our cookies.
Broke your cookies.
- Mm-hm.
- Lulu, this is not a toy.
Forget those boys. I am here
to protect you, not cookies.
Understand?
Good, now get in the car.
We're all going home.
Wait. You can't take us home yet.
You're supposed to take us to eat.
Where do you usually go?
Welcome to Woody Woodchuck's!
[Children yelling, playing]
[Woman] Let go!
And they say war is hell.
# Whenever we go out
The people always shout
# There goes Shane Jacob
Jingleheimer Schmidt
# Dah dah dah dah dah
# Shane Jacob
Jingleheimer Schmidt
# His name is my name too #
- [tires screech]
- [Girls scream]
Ah! I figured you'd
come back for him.
Lulu, watch your brother.
Inexcusable!
- I've never left a man behind.
- Oh, relax.
Once we found a kid in the ball pool
when we opened in the morning.
Whoa! Whoa!
Not cool! Uh, there is no
freestyling in the ball pool!
[Giggling]
Should we send
someone in after him?
[Screaming]
We're good.
- [Hip-hop music plays]
- [Yelling]
[Lulu] Holy baloney.
Ooh! Someone's gonna get busted!
- Who are these people?
- What's wrong with this?
- We need to talk.
- Don't hate the player, hate the game.
[Air squealing]
Beat it.
[Music stops]
Party's over!
Oh, my God, it's here.
You're all gonna clean
this house spotless.
No highway option.
Now, get cleaning.
- I'm outta here!
- [Zoe] Wait! Scott!
[Scott] Move! Later!
[Screaming]
Oh, no, you don't.
This is my favorite shirt.
Thank you.
Come on, Seth! You've
been in there for an hour!
[Footsteps]
Thanks a lot, Lt. Loser! Now
I'm gonna be the school joke.
I don't know what
I'll say to my friends.
You call those people
your friends?
They have no respect for you.
They have no respect for your home.
You have no respect
for yourself!
I do, too, respect myself!
Company downstairs.
That means you too.
You're not my dad.
In case you
haven't noticed,
this family is going through
a really hard time
and you're just making
everything a lot worse.
You have no feelings.
We hate you
and you hate us.
So why don't you
just leave us alone?
Don't worry. When your
mom comes back, I'm gone.
[Crashing]
- Now what?
- Scott.
Run! Take the babies!
Go to your rooms!
[Karate yells]
[Grunting]
Shane! Come over here!
Take one of these!
Lulu!
- Get inside. Come on.
- Hey! Hey! Wait!
[Screaming]
Don't move.
[Quacking]
Ahhhh!
[Grunting, groaning]
[Panting]
Kids, it's safe!
- Who was that? What'd they want?
- What happened?
- Don't leave us!
- [Seth] What do they want?
They were after the program
that your father invented.
They were after this.
All right, all right, come on,
guys. Let's hope this is it.
- 9- 2-6, 3-1-0-4-3.
- 9- 2-6...
3- 1-0-4-3.
They want our
Ghost movie?
Haven't they heard
of Blockbuster?
- Tell her Rita Miller.
- Rita Miller.
So there really are people
out there to get us?
Yes, there are, Zoe.
That's why I'm here.
I think we're gonna need
a little more cooperation.
From now on,
you listen to me...
...and I'll listen to you too.
Deal?
- Relax. Relax.
- I'm relaxed.
- If you just relax...
- I'm relaxed! I'm relaxed!
You've got to relax!
Please, it's on the...
Okay. I'm not
feeling well, here.
- Oh, my God! There's a bee!
- There's no bee!
- There's a bee!
- There's no bee! Stop! Please!
[Crashing]
Okay, so she wrecked the car.
The insurance will pay for it.
They were parallel parking.
The instructor jumped.
But it's not about her.
It's about the boy.
Has he been
skipping class again?
Skipping class? He always
skips sixth period, but...
All right. Seth!
Okay, take off the hat.
Go ahead.
Look at that.
That's how he showed up for practice.
I was doing a little recon in
his locker and I found this.
Okay?
[Murney] If it was a girlie
magazine or a hamster, fine.
Boys will be boys.
But this is sick.
All right. He dyed his hair.
He's not a Nazi.
This is not normal.
We're very concerned.
[Bell rings]
Why don't you get back to class?
Mr. Murney, would you
give me a minute?
Look, I'm sure this
is about their father.
We've tried to get Seth and Zoe to talk
to the psychologist, but they won't.
Maybe you can get through to them?
See what's going on?
I'll talk to them
and see what I can do.
Thanks.
[Wolfe] Seth, I don't understand
unless you explain it to me.
Why would you join wrestling
if you hate it?
Because my father
wanted me to!
Look, I know you're
just trying to help, but don't!
I can take care of myself.
Refrigerator magnet.
Smart kid.
Red One!
You're in charge. Anyone gets within
40 clicks of the perimeter, signal me.
Keep all doors sealed, do
your homework, preheat the oven
and don't let Lulu
in the cookie jar.
- [Boy #1] Everything's ready?
- [Boy #2] Yeah.
[Boy #3] Come on.
All right. All my Nazis
are finally here.
I want all of you
at attention!
Okay, let's start
where we left off yesterday.
[Piano plays]
# You are 16, going on 17
# Baby, it's time to think
# Better beware
Be canny and careful
# Baby, you're on the brink
# You are 16, going on 17
# Fellows will fall in line
[clears throat]
[Sighing]
[Sighs]
We open in a week, people.
The set isn't finished.
Mother Abbess just quit
because she got shingles!
And every step-ball change would
make Bob Fosse rise from the grave
just so he could have
a heart attack again!
- I'm really sorry. I'll get it right.
- No, you won't, Seth.
You and your mother
over here can't get it right.
And I know this
because I am a professional.
I directed Show Boat
with Greg Brady.
It wasn't union,
but it was good.
Obviously, I quit!
Exeunt stage right!
Seriously, Seth, if you drop me
again, I'm going to kill you.
- Hi.
- Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Come on.
I'm not gonna quit!
- I don't expect you to understand...
- Hey...
I may not understand a whole
hell of a lot about this kinda stuff,
but I definitely
understand not quitting.
And from what I see,
you're pretty good.
A little discipline,
you could make a go of this.
- But what about Murney?
- He's an all-talk spaz.
So, The Sound of Music?
- I saw it when I was a kid.
- Really?
The idea of a nun ditching her
habit for a guy in the military.
Nothing wrong with that.
Do you think girls
will think I'm weird?
They probably already do, Seth.
But you'll kill 'em later.
Come here.
Forget about everyone else
for a second.
Is performing
what makes you happy?
Yeah,
more than anything.
All right, fall in.
Company. Center stage.
Company! Center stage!
Who is this guy?
Now, do you or do you not have
what it takes to perform this musical?
- We don't have a director.
- I've directed rescue missions
all around the world.
I've directed numerous
snatch-and-grabs
from countries whose names
you are not allowed to know.
I've choreographed
multi-pronged amphibious landings
and stealth air attacks!
Do you think I have
the military proficiency...
...to direct this production?
Yes.
- Yes, what?
- [All] Yes, sir!
[Wolfe] Once upon a time,
there was a family...
...of elves.
And one day the little elf family
went into the magic forest
to find a secret...
...gnome...
...facility,
where the gnomes were
turning mushrooms into uranium.
So three elves laid down heavy
suppressive fire on the gnomes
while the others maneuvered
around to the right flank,
finishing off anything left alive.
[Sighs]
And not one of those elves
were left behind that day.
We got 'em all.
Even the teeniest...
...littlest elf of all...
...Rodriguez.
You're gonna have to do
the Panda dance or he won't stop.
- Oh, come on...
- [baby crying]
I don't know how to do
the Panda dance.
I'll write it down for you.
Close your eyes. Go to sleep.
I'll be right back.
You gotta do the dance.
Like Dad used to do.
He made it up for him.
[Seth] You have to do the dance
to make him sleep.
Come on.
# When you're down and low
Lower than the floor
# And you think that you
ain't got a chance, bum, bum
# Don't make a move
till you're in the groove
- Lulu.
- Thank you.
Seth.
Zoe. Uh!
Today you drive.
But I can't even
pass Driver's Ed.
Exactly.
We're all gonna die.
Have you ever given
a driving lesson before?
In a minivan? No.
Think of it like
a Bradley Assault Vehicle.
Especially when Zoe's driving.
- [Gasps]
- [Tires screeching]
- [Lulu] Zoe Plummer!
- [Seth] Zoe, what are you doing?
- [Seth] What are...? Slow down!
- [Lulu] Truck!
[Screaming]
- [Wolfe] Whoa! Whoa!
- [Tires screeching]
- [Lulu] Whoa!
- [Wolfe] Not bad.
Land! Solid land!
- I think it went well.
- Oh, it's so dramatic.
Hey, hey, hey. No fighting.
- Play nicely.
- [Boy] Sorry.
- Hi.
- Hey, how are you?
I have noticed an improvement in the
Plummer kids and I'm very impressed.
Yeah, you know,
they're just misunderstood.
[Wolfe] Peter, careful!
Don't make me come up there!
Someone needs to take the time
to talk to 'em.
- You're getting a little attached.
- I take my job very seriously.
But it's like you said.
They're just kids.
Well, keep up the good work.
Oh!
You look very nice today.
Oh. Thanks.
I don't think you understand.
Don't you ever do that again.
Is that clear?
Okay, I've had it.
I caught the kid dancing to no music.
I want him out of my class.
Somebody's gotta give this punk
a talking to.
Seth?
Well, you got something
to say, twinkle toes?
Yeah. Yeah, I do, Murney.
- I quit.
- You quit.
You know why you quit?
Because you're a quitter.
And everybody knows
that quitters...
...quit.
What are you scared of, Prancer?
- I'm not scared. I want to act.
- And I want to take up origami.
- I'm in The Sound of Music.
- Oh. A musical.
You're giving up wrestling
to be in a musical.
That happens when there
isn't a man in the house.
There is a man
in the house. It's me.
[Laughing] Well,
it's gotta be a tiny house.
You think you're tough, boy,
don't you?
Wanna shave the tiger?
Do you? Huh?
- You want it tough?
- Where did you wanna do this?
- What are you talking about?
- You said you wanted to wrestle.
Where? When?
- After school.
- [Wolfe] Okay.
- Today?
- That's right. The gym.
Okay?
Remember. You mess with
the bull, you get the horns.
[Snorting]
[Murney] Out of my way!
- How did that feel?
- It was good.
[Boy] Murney is getting
his butt kicked at 3:00!
[Cheering, pounding bleachers]
Oh, that is so gross.
[Murney] Come on! Come on!
What? That's it!
Someone's gonna get hurt today
and you know who it is?
You're about to enter
Murney's House of Pain!
What do you say we go over
the rules, cue ball? Huh?
[Crowd] Oooh!
Rule number one.
Never be too eager
to rush your opponent.
Wanna play prison rules, frogman?
Wanna play prison rules? You got it.
- I'll be your daddy.
- [Crowd cheering]
- [Cracking]
- Ah!
All right.
Now you've unlocked the beast.
Oh, God!
From this position,
it's relatively easy
- to manipulate your opponent.
- Ohhh!
[Groaning]
And thus we have
the chicken wing.
The chicken wing. [screams]
The arm bar.
The crow bar.
Or my personal favorite...
- Ahhhh!
... the pacifier!
Any questions?
Anything you
didn't understand?
Ah. The nipple crippler.
This is a useless, not to mention,
shameless move
that ultimately is a sure sign
of desperation.
And finally...
Pinned!
That was awesome!
- Are you okay, Murney?
- Get away from me!
Can I get a little help, please?
I can't move my back. Watch the back!
Go!
Sorry!
I didn't get that cone!
Crawl!
[Beeping]
See? But he usually
breaks down the door.
[Tires screech]
Excellent!
Now do it backwards.
Okay.
# When you're down and low
Lower than the floor
# And you feel like you
ain't got a chance
# Don't make a move
till you're in the groove
# And do the
Peter Panda dance
# Just hop three times
like a kangaroo
# Side-step twice
just like the crabs do
# Three steps forward
One step back
# And quick like a turtle
Lie on your back
# Roll like a log
till you can't roll no more
# Better jump quick
like there ain't no floor
# Hold your breath
Jump to the left
# And that's the Peter
I swear that's the Peter
# That's the
Peter Panda dance #
[Tyler coos]
- Again.
- Again?
You're going to sleep.
Good night, Peter Panda.
Good night, Daddy.
Good night, little fella.
Good night.
Hey, Skeever, what do you put in a jar
and shake till they're dead?
Fireflies?
Go away
and we won't hurt you.
[Girls give karate yell]
[Shouting]
Hiya!
Don't even think about it.
Cookie!
Eat it, you jerk!
Go get 'em!
[Phone ringing]
Customer service.
[Moaning]
From now on, you do things our way!
No highway option!
- Ah!
- [Moaning]
# I don't care what has been said
Fireflies rock full speed ahead
# Give me guff, I'm in your face
Fireflies rule the human race
- # Sound off
- # One-two, three-four
# One-two... three-four! #
[cheering]
- [Julie] Gary the duck?
- [Man #1] No.
[Man #2] We've been
here two weeks.
This is a matter of national security.
Well, I am sorry, sir, but none
of these answers ring true.
Howard. I'm so stupid.
Is it "my angel"?
Yes, it is indeed.
Well, I'll leave you to your business.
Please, Howard,
no more surprises.
Zoe, a rookie sniper
could drop you like a deer.
- Good.
- Good?
All right,
this is about Scott again.
No, it's not.
You were right about him.
Stupid guy.
- So, what's wrong?
- Nothing.
Nothing. Okay.
You know, when I was little,
my mom left.
My dad was a spec ops soldier like me.
When I was eight, he shipped
me off to military school.
I guess he liked being a soldier
more than he liked being a dad.
One day, I get a letter.
No more dad.
That's terrible.
For a long time I thought if I talked
about it, I was letting him down.
Like I was supposed to be brave
or something.
Yeah.
It's okay to talk
about your dad, Zoe.
I do miss him so much.
I don't know, I just...
I wanna be strong for Lulu
and Tyler and Peter
and Seth and my mom.
That's such
a big burden to carry.
I know.
[Sobbing] I miss him so much.
It's okay to miss your dad.
- [Phone rings]
- [Wolfe] I'll get it.
- Really?
- Yes.
Seth! Seth! Guess what?
Mom's coming home.
- When?
- Tomorrow! She's coming home tomorrow!
- When did you talk?
- Mommy's coming.
Here, buddy,
Mommy's coming home!
Mom's coming home!
[Lulu] She is?
[Seth] She's coming back.
[Excited chattering]
[Seth] Peter,
aren't you excited?
- When's she gonna be here?
- [Zoe] So, what are we gonna do?
We should dress up nice.
We should make her something.
- We'll clean up the entire house.
- That's a good idea.
- [Zoe] We should make a banner too.
- [Lulu] In the family room.
[Quacking]
What's wrong, Gary?
Foot got stuck?
Hang on, hang on.
Okay, now just stay still.
Hi. Come on in.
- Are you ready?
- Yeah, almost.
[Phone dialing]
[Phone rings]
- Yes?
- Hey, it's Shane.
I have excellent news.
I think I found GHOST.
- Do you have it?
- It's in a steel vault.
It needs some sort of two-pronged key.
I've been working on it, but it's tough.
Great. Good work.
We're on our way.
Don't do anything further.
I'll be there soon.
Yes, sir.
Ready?
The good news is,
once I give this to my C.O.,
whoever's been bothering you
ain't gonna be.
- Really?
- Really.
What's wrong? Your mother's
coming. You should be happy.
But, Shane, doesn't that
mean you have to go?
You should get ready.
Your mother will be home soon.
I had a fight with Zoe before I left,
so they probably trashed the place.
Welcome home, Mom.
[Julie] Hi! I missed you!
Guy!
Shane, I am so proud of you.
I truly am.
I am going to give you
your choice of assignment.
Anywhere you want to go,
you just name it.
Well, I appreciate that.
But I'll have to think about it.
You're gonna think about it?
Well, the military's
all I've ever known.
- I have no regrets.
- I should hope not.
It's just that being
with this family...
- I've never had a...
- [man] Put your hands up!
The Chuns?
You gotta be kidding.
I swear I checked them out.
Give us the key.
- [Man] Put your hands up!
- Okay. All right.
Here.
Now!
You promised us GHOST
months ago!
Well, I'm sorry.
There were delays.
Shane!
Stop talking.
Shane's not gonna be
babysitting you anymore.
I trusted you.
Howard trusted you.
You've betrayed us
and you've betrayed this country.
Guess what?
North Korea pays better.
Chun, watch them.
They're squirmy.
You two, come with me.
[Muffled yelling]
[Beeping, bolts releasing]
Did you bring the
stethoscope, Mrs. Chun?
No, but I've
got some C-4.
I just had my eyebrows done.
[Crying]
Quiet!
I said "Quiet,"
you little bug!
Now, Peter!
Ah!
Hiya!
Well, that's cute!
[Groans]
That stuff doesn't hurt!
[Lulu] Shane! You can't do this!
You can't leave a man behind!
Hold on, I got it.
[Zoe] Shane!
- Where's Mom?
- Mom?
I'll find her.
You guys run and get help!
- [Crying]
- Hurry!
Are you sure
you're gonna be okay?
Yes, Lulu. Go, get help.
Hold on!
[Speaking in foreign language]
They're headed for the car!
- [Lulu] Zoe, call 911.
- I forgot my cell phone.
- [Seth] Great. The only time you don't.
- [Zoe] We're gonna be okay!
Oh, my God!
What do we do?
Find a cop!
Ahh!
[Screaming]
- He's gaining on us.
- I'll handle it.
[Screaming]
[Chun yelling]
[Yelling]
Look, Zoe! It's the cops!
[Siren wails]
I assume you heard the Baloney
Bandit has struck again.
I accept total responsibility.
My intelligence, well, it was faulty.
- If I had better resources...
- [siren wails]
I told you not to pass her
in Driver's Ed.
You have exactly three seconds
to get me through this mine field.
- One, two...
- [Wolfe] Bill.
She doesn't know.
And you're not taking another
parent away from those kids.
Leave the family alone
and I'll get you in.
You better not be bluffing.
Zoe! Seth!
Lulu! Peter! Tyler!
Ah!
That was the code. I saw Mr. Plummer
use it to open the briefcase.
You think this is a game?
Code or no code, open it. Now.
You can't make him do this.
I know Howard.
You haven't got a chance.
# When you're down and low
Lower than the floor
# And you feel like you
don't have a chance
# Don't make a move
till you're in the groove
# And do the
Peter Panda dance
# Hop three times
like a kangaroo
# Side-step twice
just like the crabs do
# Three steps forward
One step back
Quick like a turtle!
Lie on your back!
# Roll like a log
till you can't no more
# Better jump quick
like there ain't no floor
# Hold your breath
Step to the left
And that's
the Peter Panda dance.
All right. Go.
Yeah, right.
Okay, I'll go first.
Great work, Shane.
I knew you'd figure it out.
I think you'd better open it.
Wait, wait, wait!
Back away.
You open it.
Come on.
I walked the floor first.
No way.
You can do it, soldier man.
[Julie] Ah!
[Grunting]
Ahhh!
[Panting]
Any last words, Shane?
Say good night,
Peter Panda.
Shane, are you okay?
Oh!
She was never
a good neighbor.
Zoe, you're going too fast!
You're not gonna
have time to stop!
Who said anything about
stopping? I'm parking.
[Tires screeching]
- What are you doing to these kids?
- [Cop] Hands where I can see them!
[Wolfe] Okay. Calm down.
Everybody!
Put your weapons down!
I want the GHOST.
[Quacking]
[Wolfe] Um... Calm down.
It's just a duck.
- [Chun] Where's the GHOST?
- [Wolfe] I have it.
[Chun] Bring it here!
Put it on the ground.
[Whispering] Now, Gary.
Go for his balls.
Okay, duck whisperer,
step away!
- Gary, now!
- [Quacking]
Ah!
Couldn't let you
have all the fun.
So I guess you'll be
taking off now, huh?
Seeing as there's no reason
to stick around anymore.
I'm still here,
aren't I?
Yeah.
- What now?
- I don't know. I'm on dry land.
True.
Which means you're
the superior officer.
True.
So you tell me.
Um...
- [clears throat]
- Lulu!
Excuse me, ma'am.
Could I have a few words?
Sure.
Well, we... I... You know.
Oh.
We'll talk later.
- Mission accomplished, soldier.
- I suppose it is.
- I guess you'll be leaving us now.
- I guess so.
I want you to have this.
Because I don't want you
ever to forget me.
I will never forget you.
'Cause you're the
best friend I ever had.
No matter how far...
...or long life takes me away,
I will always be thinking about you.
I love you, Shane.
I love you too.
From now on, it's your command.
At ease, soldiers.
[Wolfe] Your father would
be so proud of all of you.
Awww.
Look who just woke up.
- [Lulu] Shane?
- Yes?
- Are we ever gonna see you again?
- What are you talking about?
We still have one more mission.
# You are 16, going on 17
# Baby, it's time to think
# Better beware
Be canny and careful
# Baby, you're on the brink
# You are 16, going on 17
# Fellows will fall in line
- # Eager young lads
- Yes!
# Will offer
you food and wine
# Climb every mountain
# Ford every stream
Looks like you have
a hit on your hands.
- You think so?
- Mm-hmm.
You should take over the drama
department instead of wrestling.
It's gonna be nice
having you around now.
Now that Murney's found
his true calling.
# Climb every mountain
# Ford every stream
It's gonna be my pleasure
serving with you.
# Find your dream #
SYNC-CORRECTED BY CLONE