Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
Only use it as a last resort.
When all else is failed.
- It has served me well, as you can see.
- Yes, father.
- Won't you sit down?
- No. Time is short.
You must be off.
I've given you my secret thrust.
I give you at least 15 crowns.
And this.
Your grandfather bought this
sword against the Moors of Lepanto.
I made some use of it.
Under the late King Henry.
Now it is yours.
It'll introduce you to Monsieur Treville,
who commands the King's musketeers.
He will remember it well.
And me.
My son, you're going
to be a musketeer.
You are young, brave and
a Gascon and a D'Artagnan.
Fights, whenever you can.
Never submit to insults...
except from the King
and Cardinal Richelieu.
Now be weary of the Cardinal, for
he rules France through the King.
But you are a King's man, and the Queen.
So...
Now, go and say goodbye
to your mother.
Your ointment is in pack.
Rub it well to every scratches.
And dry your cloak and your
shoes well. / Yes, mother.
Goodbye.
Goodbye, father.
Don't sell the horse.
Let him die honorably of old age!
And fight, remember!
Take care.
Come on!
As someone probably rides
on a buttercup.
Perhaps it is a cheese with legs.
Tell me what you're laugh at.
Then we'll laugh together.
If you were a gentleman,
I would speak to you.
But I am speaking to you!
Turn, if you are a man!
He is a Gascon. /
Should I kill him? / No.
Put him on his ridiculous horse
and let him go.
No time to talk, My Lady.
The cardinal command you to England.
Let him know when the Duke is leaving.
- And then?
- Awaits his further commands.
And you? When shall I see you again?
You... You assassin!
I shall chastise you, Sir.
Forgive me, Madame.
But, I must kill your friend.
Are you not terrified?
Away, pumpkin!
You will hear from me.
He's very handsome.
Claude, pay the bill!
You...
Where is Monsieur Treville?
/ Upstairs. / Thank you.
I like the belt buckles.
I am a man of his money at
night spends precious shirts.
Or one's mistresses money.
No, my own.
I paid with 12 pistoles.
It is golden belt.
Astonishing! There's enough gold
in France to stretch so much?
Might I lift the cloak?
- No, I have a cold.
Discretion is being a part of vanity.
I don't understand.
I know the one about valor,
but in such clothing
I can not be prudent.
A very clean sword
thrust. A souvenir from...
the Cardinal's guard.
- You're a liar. It's a smallpox.
If one sees... / Don't pretend you know
to make any difference to the treatment.
Monsieur Treville will see you now.
Thank you.
Your father says that
you carry his old sword.
Yes.
Do me the honor of taking one
arms, 'till yours grow longer.
Sir, I ask charity of no one.
Then you aren't likely to get it.
No, not charity, but love and courtesy
for the son of an old friend.
To keep his enemies further off.
In that case, sir.
I bid thank you.
That is as much as
I can offer you.
You see, there is no place in
the musketeers for any man...
untill he has serve in a campaign or
distinguish himself in the killing.
But, what I can do is write
a letter to Monsieur de Salle,
who commands the guards.
You coward! I spit on you!
What?
Not on you, Sir.
On that fellow, without the eye!
You, Sir! I said stop, Sir!
Excuse me, I'm in a hurry!
- You're certainly in a hurry.
You hurdled into me and
expect an excuse is sufficient?
You need a lesson in manners.
I said "excuse me".
I need no lesson in manners.
You shall have one anyway.
Where?
The Carmelite convent, at twelve.
- Gold all the way around.
- Stop! You run with your eyes shut!
- Sir, I beg your pardon.
- I demand satisfaction.
Where?
- At the Luxembourg, one o'clock.
Oh, look... at the statue.
Forgive me, gentlemen.
- You drop this.
- Gold departing from departing pansy!
That's not mine.
Pardon, I saw it fall.
You see too much,
it is a fault among peasant.
- I am a Gascon, Sir.
- And need to learn civilized behavior.
I am no bully, as a future priest
I fight only if I must.
But you have compromised a lady.
Shall we say at Hotel
Treville, two o'clock? / Sir!
Sir, your purse!
Well, if I'm to be killed, at
least by the hand of a musketeer.
You're punctual.
Even though you're not running.
But you did hurt my shoulder.
I trust it will not inconvenient you, Sir.
If you wish to postpone...
By all means. I fight just
as well with my left hand.
If you find this places you to
a disadvantage, I do apologize.
You're very courteous, Sir.
About your wound, I have
an ointment from my mother.
You overwhelmed me, young man.
Ah, here come my second.
You fight him? But I'm meeting him
myself. / Not 'till one o'clock, sir.
No, I do! / At two. / How
long you been in Paris?
- Since 8 o'clock this morning.
- You wasted no time.
My father recommended
that I fight duels.
Let us hope you can
do him some credits.
- The Cardinal's guard!
- Cease, quickly!
Ah, musketeers!
Dueling in defiance of the edicts.
This is a private matter.
Would you please be on your way.
We have a duty to suppress disorder...
...and arrest brawlers. Put up
your sword and come along with us?
Impossible. / Unthinkable. / Unlikely.
Then we must charge you.
They are six and we are
only three. / No... four.
You are not one of us.
This is not your affair, boy.
I may not have the tunic, but I
have the heart of a musketeer!
Young man, you may retire.
Save your skin. And quickly.
What is your name?
/ D'Artagnan. / Well, then.
Athos, Porthos, Aramis and D'Artagnan!
Forward!
First, let us pray.
Gentle Jesus, meek and hard!
May I?
Sorry.
A sword!
For God's sake.
Thank you.
D'Artagnan!
No!
No! Leave him to me!
- Put down your sword!
- No!
Surrender, Biscart! I order you.
Oh, that's different.
Ring the bell.
The nuns will tend to your wounded.
Come, the sooner we go, the
better. / Yes, it was over too soon.
Look at that best flemish velvet!
Ruined by you!
You will pay for it!
10 pistole it costs me!
No, 20 pistole. And 20 more as a fine,
to teach you manners!
Thief!
Charity is one of cardinal virtue!
Are we going to stand here and chat,
until marshal comes to arrest us? Go!
Let's be off.
About your friend's wounds...
I have an ointment from my mother.
You might find it effective...
I threw my sword in the air...
- Porthos! Porthos!
The purse, please. The Musketeers
motto: One for all and all for one.
Which loosely translate as 10 for him,
10 for him, 10 for you and 10 for me.
My dear Aramis needs 10,
to impress his mistress.
My good Porthos needs 10,
to enable himself to dress decently.
And you need 10 for
lodging and a servant.
- And I...
- And you?
I need a drink.
The future looks rosier
from the bottom of a glass.
Mind, where...
This is a horse?
This is the steps.
I think you'll like it here, monsieur.
For only two francs a day...
this chamber here... wonderful.
And scrupulously clean, as you see.
Slopped empty every second day.
And more redundant on a modest fee.
You're rascal can sleep out there.
If you beat him for insolence,
the scream will scarce be heard.
They don't fallof tree,
chamber like this in Paris.
Where else you get a
magnificent view of the city?
Honestly, this pig sty is not fit for...
a king or cardinal.
But it will suits me very well.
Two francs, you say?
You take it?
- Whenever it's offered.
My wife, sir!
Is she not beautiful?
- Enchanting.
Thank you. / She is as
delicate as petals falling...
From afar!
You know, my wife is the
dressmaker to the Queen.
A very nice person, the Queen.
My wife has her every confidence.
I am very proud of being her husband.
She lives here?
- No, I live here.
My beautiful Constance stays
at the palace. Where else?
She visited me once a week.
Tonight, in fact.
Madame must look
forward to that eagerly.
Yes.
Faster!
Faster, you idiot!
Come on! Somebody, make it faster!
Wonderful! It is really wonderful.
I feel sick.
The queen to king's knight 4.
Your ruffians have spite
the Cardinal's guard.
Your Musketeers, sire.
- Your ruffians.
Knight to king's bishop five
I am hard put to explain it to him,
who guards France while I sleep,
and works tirelessly while
I amused myself.
Your Majesty refers to God?
- I refer to Cardinal Richelieu,
which is not quite the same thing.
Oh, Cardinal...
This matter of Treville's musketeers...
Broken heads and broken swords.
Trifles, Sire. The Duke of
Buckingham is in Paris.
Buckingham? Here?
Why, in God's name?
To plot against my honor?
- The Queen.
You will arrest the plotter.
- Sire, you are off.
The Queen is faithful to you and
to France. She loves you warmly.
I am not scorched by the heat.
You arrest him.
What a scandal should we do that?
Arrest the prime minister of England?
No, Sire. What we must do is
keep the noble Duke on a string,
to pursue his sordid
pact with Protestants
his politics muffled in a cloak.
And the Queen muffled in
her cloak, under the window?
Her majesty beauty attracts
all manners of worship...
and worshippers.
But her virtue is beyond question.
As for the Duke of Buckingham,
he will be watched.
Bishop to queen two.
Chess.
That one.
Open up! Open up!
Or else, we break it down!
Don't worry, Constance!
- Oh, my darling!
You will come with me.
- No, I won't.
No, I won't.
We'll see about that.
You will come with me.
- Yes, I... I'll come with you.
Stop her! Stop her!
What have you done with my wife?
Monsieur D'Artagnan, I want you... / I'm
yours, as soon as I get my breathe back.
Did I hurt you?
Monsieur, I must get to the queen tonight.
- I can not allow it.
I was torn from my bed.
- The best place for you.
The bed is the best place for you.
Sit down.
Thank you, Monsieur.
- Oh! My husband.
- Where?
In the Bastille.
Oh, a... I'm sorry.
Now, the best possible course is a good
night sleep. Try to forget about it.
I can not sleep, with my
husband in the Bastille.
- I'm frightened.
- I'm not.
You want to sleep with me. You need a
good cuddle to chase the fright away.
I must go to Her Majesty.
She needs me urgently.
I can not let you go.
The streets are full of dangers,
and your legs and
feet are dirty.
Yes.
You must help me. You are young
and gallant. My husband is weak
troubled with wind.
Can I tell you?
Can I trust you? / With your
life which beats in your breast.
I hear the flutter of life
like a little white bird.
I must be the queen.
- I can hear the wings.
The Cardinal wishes to ruined it.
Because I'm in the Queen's confidence..
Perhaps he hopes to
attack her through me.
You can not go to the
Queen with dirty legs.
No.
Are you strong enough to wash them?
- No.
My poor husband, without
him I feel so helpless.
I have never washed
the legs of a woman.
I have done a horse.
With the horse, you start at the top.
I can not go dirty to the Queen.
Do you think I will be safe here?
Oh yes, Constance, yes...
Oh, it's...
...a bit cold.
At least let me escort you part
of the way. / No, I must go alone.
I have to meet someone before
I go to the queen. / Who?
Are you jealous so soon?
Of every inch of you.
I must go now. Promise you won't follow.
Ouch!
Money for the blind man.
You all right, darling?
Money for a cripple...
Get off!
Money for a cripple!
Not your day, is it?
- Money for an orphan!
Money for a war veteran.
Money...
Before you climb out...
Sir, you have some change?
One moment, sir.
But you promised.
- I can see why you make me promised.
You have nothing to do with me.
- No, but with this lady.
Take my arm. Good evening, sir.
In God's name, my lord.
- My lord? Are you...
The Duke of Buckingham.
See? You will spoil everything!
- My darling, forgive me.
My Lord, what can I say?
I love her and was jealous.
A perfectly excellent reason for
attacking a stranger in the dark.
Woud you oblige me with a small matter?
Anything, my lord.
- When we enter the palace,
we must not be seen.
If anyone try to follow us, would you
be good enough to kill him. Thank you.
Oh, yes... yes.
Does Your Grace know of any private
place which as private as this public one?
- Well...
- Wait here!
Anne. / Why have you come?
/ To see you.
Oh, it is folly.
The king suspects...
and the Cardinal knows.
He'll ruin me.
His spies are... what if they caught us?
- Decidedly we must not be found,
not with the dirty laundry is washed.
It's hopeless.
I'm the wife of the king.
An ill mannered little Parisian lout to
ignored you, & jealous at the same time?
What do you owe him?
I will not disgrace him.
Which is why I ask you to go
and not to return.
We are not ordinary folk.
- Indeed.
It thrust both ways.
I am no little gentleman or a farm boy.
I am a master of a great state, Anne.
With great ships and
armies, too, if need be.
The English have come to France before.
But never with a better
reason than I have.
Do you think I would
fret for a war to win you?
If you doubt it, wait 'till France
claim to the throne of England raises.
Dear, dear Anne...
You look lovelier than...
...than everything I've seen
in a laundry before.
Tell me again,
that you love me.
You must go.
It's not safe here.
It will be one day.
Until then...
Give me something to remember you by.
A token, anything.
Oh, come. A farm boy
sweetheart would give him one.
These are my best things.
Within a year I will
bring them back to you.
So, that's how they do it!
At no notion, I should wear my shirt
in the future with more respect.
Oh, God!
Go on! Quickly!
Stand still!
In here!
Excuse me!
Please tell me where are we going...
Dance, you rabbit! I'm not
through with you! Come here!
Oh, thank you.
Come on!
Oh, my lord.
I probably could've manage, but
my thanks to you gentlemen, anyway.
- Who was that?
- I don't know.
But he sounded a touch of foreign to me.
Look at this? What on
earth was this all about?
In you go.
- I want you tell me,
I did nothing. I was lying in bed, alone
when suddenly he break into my room.
I swear I've done nothing!
What will they do to me?
You are in the Bastille.
You must have done something.
What you have done is high treason.
You are accused of conspiring with
your wife and the Duke of Buckingham.
No, no...
Do you know your accuser?
Who brought you here?
That is the man!
Take him away.
- That is not the man!
There's another man. This is
a very honorable gentleman...
They have met, the Queen and
Buckingham. / Where? / At the Palace.
I learned too late. / He slipped
through your finger? / Through yours.
I had no orders. / What happen? /
Madame Bonacieux accompanied Buckingham.
I told you to arrest and hold her.
I failed.
One does occasionally.
If I blundered as you do,
my head would fall.
I would say, from a
greater height than mine.
You would?
The height of ambition.
/ You have none? / No.
Do you fear me?
Yes, I fear you, Eminence.
I also hate you.
I love you, son.
Even when you fail.
The queen gave Buckingham
the 12 diamonds studs.
The King gave her for her birthday.
Where went Buckingham, I do not know.
Spare me, not what you know.
Buckingham will be in Calais...
We let him go this time.
No... no... not break!
Let me go, please! Stop it!
It hurts!
It supposed to.
You have deceived me!
Deceived me!
For thinking of you were a traitor.
Rise, my friend.
What can I say?
I find that our suspicion
about you were entirely unjust.
The Cardinal has taken my
hand and called me "friend".
We must make you a better man
than that. Take these 100 pistoles...
And forgive me.
- I forgive Your Eminence?
You can not mean that, I
mean, what am I? I am nothing.
I am less than nothing.
Friend, you are generous.
Is not it? I hope you will
come to visit me again,
so that we can talk.
Until our next meeting.
I think I have done all
that can be done with him.
I set him loose to spy on his wife.
- He think I was frightened of him?
The gallant Buckingham will most
certainly wear those diamonds studs.
Send word to Milady de Winter in
England. She is to get close to him...
and obtain two of the studs.
You go there to meet her and see that
she brings them to me immediately.
How she gets them, is her affair.
You'll like this place.
It's very cheap.
Wait a minute.
I can win some money for us.
He's the one!
He will win!
Come on, boy!
- Then it's not enough for dinner.
I'm going to win here!
He's the one!
I am starved.
How about chicken? Always popular
on Wednesday. / It's Tuesday.
Chops? / Oh, how revolting!
I long for good food.
Tell him to cook this, will you?
You great overgrown child!
I know what you are doing.
People like you, I know!
All right?
This should cover the
inconvenience, Sir.
Oh, look at its feathers!
Did you hear it cry?
Have you heard?
His Eminence wants to see you dance.
He suggest that I give
a Ball in your honor.
What pleases your majesty is a delight
to me. / So, at the Hôtel de Ville then.
In two weeks. We should be merry.
Ball, Ballet, Costumes
and figures and whatever.
And you'll be able to wear the
diamonds studs that I gave you.
That will crown her majesty's evening.
The diamonds studs?
Yes, the studs, my
present to you. Why not?
Do not you, that they are you? / Yes.
Yes, they are beautiful.
- Then I wish they're worn, then?
I wish you to wear them.
I depend upon it, madame.
This bird has got a grip on me.
It brought tears to my eyes,
clinged to my wrist. See?
Oh, the ball with the diamonds...
You want to see the Queen's dance.
You becoming a romantic
under your priestly robe.
Even a cardinal has
weaknesses, your Majesty.
Whereas the king has
none, eh? See the tears?
This conversation took place in the
bedroom of Bonacieux at the palace.
The Queen said:
"I am lost, I am lost".
Bonacieux said: "Your Majesty."
"Constance, I am lost."
"Your Majesty."
"What can I do?"
"We can get the studs back". / "In
14 days? From London? I am lost".
"A messenger can reach London and
return to Paris with the studs".
"A messenger, who? I can trust no one.
That devil has informants everywhere.
That evil, filthy, revolting,
wretched man. Evil, filthy,
revolting, evil man, calls
himself a man of the church".
According to this.
I will find a messenger, Majesty.
I trust upon him. I swear it.
He can carry a letter from
you to Lord Buckingham.
Yes, a letter.
I shall write it.
It's for my honor
and for my life.
You've someone you can trust with that?
/ Your Majesty, he will not fail...
The Queen is in danger...
...unless this letter can be
taken immediately to London.
If you could set out at once.
She has no one to trust but me.
And I can't trust no one but you.
Letters, dangers...
Come to bed,
Constance, my small chicken.
And I will...
I'll do anything you ask if
you promise to take the letter.
What do I know about letters? I've been
so many days and nights without you.
No, I'm serious...
- You think I'm not?
The letter must go to London now.
/ It must because you say so...
I don't wish to be trusted me...
because that suspicious
letter smacks of intrigue.
Constance, Constance...
Yes, intrigue.
What came out here?
I was dragged to the Bastille.
But I don't wish to be
sent to the Bastille,
because they got very deep dungeons
and terrible instruments of torture,
operated by very unsympathetic men.
They slit very important
parts of people.
Hadn't been for the Cardinal...
The Cardinal?
- Yes, the Cardinal.
You think, you alone have friends
in high places. Let me tell you...
The Cardinal took my
hand and called me friend.
And he gave me this purse.
You were the cardinal?
- I tell you something else.
He doesn't like this kind of intrigue.
To whom is that the letter go?
It's nothing to you if you
do not wish to carry it.
Very well, madam mischief.
If you don't wish to go to bed with me,
I shall have to leave you.
For a very important appointment.
For a very important appointment!
- Oh, you!
- Me.
Then you heard? / Every
word. / Then you know.
You and the Queen, you need
someone who is gallant, courageous,
discreet, active, smart and loyal is.
I also know the way to London...
and your good husband, whose
probably on his way to the Cardinal,
has thoughtfully provided my expenses.
- Can I trust you?
- Trust me?
Trust me? Oh, the question!
You can trust me because I love you.
And you love me. If not,
there's something wrong with you.
You must swear never to reveal the
name of the person to whom it goes.
On my honor.
His name is the Duke of Buckingham.
This way, sir!
He moves quickly, that husband of yours!
...happened all the time.
Constance! Constance!
She's gone.
As you might've known, you're an
imbecile, and not accept the letter.
She has doubtly fled to the palace.
None here. The candle is still warm.
- Quick to the palace!
She can't be gone far.
This letter, have your wife mentioned...
the Duke of Buckingham?
- No, no names.
This D'Artagnan lodges
with you, does he not?
We shall find a lodging for D'Artagnan
& his friends as a precautions.
In the Bastille.
- And afterwards?
In the Bastille
there is no "Afterwards".
What?
That man has insulted me,
broke my father's sword,
had me club to the ground and laid
violent hands on the woman I love.
He is... inconvenient.
Let me tell you something about this,
"inconvenient" gentleman of yours.
His name is Rochefort.
He's the the Cardinal's
living blade and he's deadly.
Now running already,
you slow oaf!
15:0.
Still 15th
15 both.
30:15.
If you see Rochefort on the street,
do not make the effort,
to greet him.
Aramis! What the hell are you doing?
Your only chance.
- A full risk.
Rochefort or not, I have to
get to London with this letter.
For the Queen. I must be back
with the answer in 14 days.
With Cardinal's friend hunting
you, you won't get five miles.
Game. Final set.
You want this letter delivered?
If the four of us go,
it should get there.
There goes tomorrow's dinner, sir.
Wager on a Huguenot for Papacy
than on you two. Get your things.
We're riding to London.
- London?
Great lump of bollock indeed?
Your soul is corrupted. You shall
not inherite the kingdom of God.
- When do we leave?
- At once.
How do we get horses?
- We sell our servants.
A servant sells his secrets,
Gentleman one before.
If one of us falls,
take the other three the letter.
Who falls, must take his chances.
Agreed?
No one asked delicately the cause
in which we're being expected to die?
When on a campaign, does the king gives
his reason? If we have to fight, we fight.
Then let's go & be killed as we're
told. Is life worth so many questions?
Be careful with the bridle!
Has cost more than you deserve.
I'll go, sir. / God be with
you, sir! / And you, too.
- We toast, sir?
- With pleasure.
Will you drink to
health of the Cardinal?
Gladly, if you drink
with us on the king.
Not on the king.
On the Cardinal.
You're drunk, sir.
There's only one answer for that.
This you will owe me one!
This is your folly. Kill the fellow
and follow us as soon as you can.
Come on!
We are down to three. / Porthos
can take him out. The guy's drunk.
He looks sober enough
when he came en guard.
Damn! Look here!
Stop! Stop!
Get away! Ride out!
Come on!
Drop it!
The same fate awaits us
perhaps ten miles further.
But at least we should be
safe enough to run. Forward!
Treason it may be,
But I will retain the beauty of
French women above all others.
An Englishman can never believe you.
Go to bed, Felton!
This expression could every
man prepare nightmares.
I can take anyone if you
have pass from the Cardinal.
I have a pass.
This morning that no one should leave
without the signature of
the Mayor master builder.
Very well.
I'll be back in an hour.
Keep a close watch. Enemies of
the state were trying to escape.
You could do me a favor, sir.
That pass in your pocket. Hand it over,
save us a great deal of inconvenient.
You were the Gascon
rascall with a yellow horse,
on the streets with the musketeers
rumlungert corners and beating.
The street corners you've been
careful to avoid, Monsieur Cyclops.
Where are your three accomplices?
You would've done been better...
It's me!
Don't worry, sir. I'm coming.
I'm coming!
I've told you.
Monsieur, are you killed?
Not quite.
Just a scrape along the ribs.
Oh, Father! What you
almost did to your son.
Is he dead?
Alas, he's only stunned.
Shall I kill him?
Certainly not.
Ties his wrists and gag him.
We give him the chance to bleed to
death, but we're not murdering him.
The pass is only for one.
- I am only one.
- That is a servant.
- Okay.
You alright?
Look, will you? Dover!
My lord!
So, it's the jealous lover.
I trust you haven't come to England
to fasten another quarrel on me?
I'm afraid I can not read.
How long have you been on the road?
- Six days, my lord.
Then so, we must bustle!
Come on, Plachet, we must bustle.
Oh, good. I like bustling.
Go, sir! At the gallop!
One, two...
Yes, sir.
She is my deity.
Here they are.
I hoped to keep them always.
God in heaven, two are missing!
/ What? / Let me think.
I had all twelve at the
ball two weeks ago...
Countess de Winter.
My God!
A pretty price for the infidelity.
You should be in France by now.
Felton!
They had been stolen
by a Cardinal's spy!
Felton, my secretary!
I want to place an order.
Someone got a pen?
Write to all ports on the canal!
No vessels to sail without my order!
If the king asks, tell him I'm...
thinking of war with France.
And keep the road to Dover clear!
Six days?
You shall kill yourself return
this studs to Queen in time.
But the missing ones? / O'Reilly, put
a price on these, each one. Their worth?
Something is missing... and there.
I'd say... 500 pounds.
How long to make two of them?
A week? / I'll pay 5,000 each, if
they're finish the day after tomorrow.
Done. Could I tell my
wife, I'm not coming home?
I'll do better. Jackson, a carriage and
escort of cavalry for Mrs. O'Reilly..
Prepare room for them.
- Oh, how nice.
Have you hurt yourself?
- It's nothing.
Beautiful, beautiful.
Would it be a compliment
to say they match your eyes?
Unusually gallantry.
Your normal humour, would be
to compare them to my heart.
It did occur to me.
Up the Cardinal,
down the Queen.
Whip it!
There, sir. Pick out O'Reilly's
two new ones if you can.
And now, for the honor of the
great lady whom we both serve...
...is for you to see that
she receive them in time.
My lord, it is done already.
- And you, sir.
How can I ever repay you?
Let us understand one another...
You are an Englishman,
an enemy of France.
You owe me nothing yet,
I did it for the Queen.
And for another who is dear
to me as the Queen is to you.
I take my leave.
I forgot that England is
an island. How do I get off?
You'll find fresh horses, and a clear
road to Dover, and waits for a ship.
Monsieur, you would take
no reward from a friend.
Will you at least accept this?
And this, from an enemy.
That is different.
I'm tired!
- Me too. We're almost there.
Put your back into it!
- I got piles!
We need fresh horses. / Do
you recognize this place? / No.
The last place on earth
we were all alive together.
Until we meet again, my friends!
That will not last long.
Get me out of here!
Look! The rope. Quickly!
The horse!
For God's sake, where are you?
Through the gate!
These horses are done.
It's about time!
Come on! / Show off! / Why
you always lagging behind?
Did you hear that voice?
- That unfortunate accent!
All for one and one for all.
My wife's in there.
She dances with all the best people.
And sometimes she
waves at me. Sometimes.
Madame, why are you not
wearing the diamond studs?
You knew that I wishes to see them.
Your Majesty, in this big
crowds I fear I might lose them.
You were wrong.
I made you this present...
...to adore yourself.
I am highly displeased.
If Your Majesty pleases,
I can send to the palace for them.
Do so. And immediately.
Keep going, Reggie. It's filling up.
I'm doing my best.
- Not good enough.
Her Majesty was radiantly pale.
May I respectfully direct Your Majesty's
attention to these sweets in this box?
I feel sure you would agree,
they are at royal confection.
What does this mean? / If the
Queen has her studs, which I doubt,
Count them, Sire.
If there are only ten,
asked Her Majesty
where the other two.
No one may enter without an invitation.
It's the Cardinal's order.
I beg your pardon, sir?
I said...
Doesn't matter.
Come on. That's it.
Come on! That's good.
Again!
Madame, he may still come.
I feel sure he will.
How can he, Constance.
It's no use.
It's over. It's...
That has to be Constance.
Light the fireworks,
when you hear the fanfare.
- D'Artagnan!
- What?
I'm almost there, Constance.
Come down there!
Sorry.
Why are we stopping, gentlemen?
Hurry! / I am hurrying!
Stand fast, boy!
Blast!
Come on!
Guards! After him!
Follow that bear!
There you are, my old friends!
Here are your men to the rescue!
Thank God, you're all alive!
Can you get me up there, please?
Wait a minute...
He tore up our carpet.
Quickly, gentlemen! To your places!
Three, four, five... silly me!
One, two, three, four...
Stand still!
Get off! Come!
Excuse me, please?
Thank you, for adhering my wishes.
But I believe you've lost two studs.
I'll bring them to you.
Sire, you bring me two more.
How kind of you. Now I have fourteen.
14?
13, 14.. What does this mean, Cardinal?
It means, sire, that...
...I wished to present those studs to
Her Majesty, but not dare to offer them.
I gave them to her through you.
I'm terribly grateful to your Eminence.
For I'm certain that these two studs
cost you much more than the other twelve,
cost by His Majesty.
Eminence, D'Artagnan gain
entry to the hotel. / Quite so.
You failed me.
I've lost points.
The game continues.
- You would not seek this boy?
To what end? Vengeance?
That is an expensive luxury.
Statesmen can not afford it.
No, I could use such a man.
Perhaps I shall seek him out after all.
Your Eminence is a great player,
great enough to lose.
I do not like to lose.
You must suit yourself, my lady.
But if in the end you should,
do it with becoming grace.
My darling, darling.
Never again will I let you
go in such terrible danger.
Time gallop, sometimes fighting,
stab times. What the hell!
It's the day's work.
But to find my beautiful
Constance in the end...
Did you miss me?
A foolish question.
I work for him.
Yes.
Young Gascon, now you're a musketeer.
Carry the King's musket with honor.
Now that you are the...
four musketeers.
Now we're four.
My boss. He waves to you.
Here, take it!
The King!
Please rate this subtitle at www.osdb.link/dphe
Help other users to choose the best subtitles