Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
You're dipping your shoulder
before you throw the right.
The hell I am.
When's tip-off?
At 8:00. We should pregame.
That place is a ripoff.
I'm not spending eight bucks on a beer.
I got a shift in the morning, so we
should probably take it easy tonight.
Yeah, right.
Where are the seats?
- Ain't courtside.
- Nosebleeds then?
I was your CO.
We did two tours together.
Hell, I took a bullet for you.
You ought to know me better than that.
There. You did it again.
There's that place over on Franklin.
Three-dollar draft, pretty decent wings.
That place is a dump.
Yeah, well, I'm not exactly
swimming in EMT money, all right?
My job at the VA barely covers my tab.
I'm telling you,
you're tipping your strikes.
I can see you coming a mile away.
Yeah. See that one?
Nope.
- You still hit like a girl.
- Nothing wrong with that.
You done?
I'm not the one getting my ass kicked.
I taught you that.
I know.
All right, come on.
- We're gonna be late.
- Coffee's on you.
What else is new?
Good morning, Portland.
We start the hour with an update
from the Horace Hayes trial. Kelly?
Yes, good morning, Tom.
Well, there certainly is a nervous
energy in the air today
with closing arguments being read
in the Horace Hayes trial
and deliberations
set to begin this afternoon.
While many members of the community
fear another hung jury
and the possibility of Hayes
walking free,
the prosecution
certainly seemed confident
as they convened in the hallway.
And any updates on the rest
of the alleged Irish crime family?
Yes, I pressed the District Attorney...
- Hey.
- Yo. When's your dad back?
I don't know.
Whenever they reach a verdict.
So you've got the house to yourself
tomorrow night?
Yeah. But, no, not gonna happen.
- What?
- You know what.
- I'm not having people over.
- Why not?
We've got finals next week, for one.
What if I invited Andrew?
- My dad will kill me.
- He'll never know.
That's not the point.
We'll keep it low-key.
Okay, fine, but just a couple of people.
That's it. I'm serious.
Yes.
I'll see you at practice.
Can I help you?
Get in the car, Sarah.
How do you know my name?
Circle around!
Where the fuck did she go?
That way. Go!
Come on, Sarah.
We're not gonna hurt you.
Sarah.
I got her, Maddy!
Get off me!
You should have got in the car.
What do you want from me?
Put him on.
Someone wants to say hi.
- Sarah!
- Dad!
- Oh, my God! Sarah.
- Hey!
Dad!
Patrick, your daughter's gonna be fine.
We just need to talk
about my father's trial.
What do you want from me?
You hang the jury,
or we'll hang your girl.
Get her in the car.
Thanks for coming out
with me today, man.
- I appreciate it.
- No worries.
It wasn't like it was
my day off or anything.
Come on, might as well
get out and help a few people out.
Yeah, yeah, yeah. Happy to help.
I just didn't know
the ODVA made house calls.
Normally, we don't.
Usually, they have got me sitting
behind a desk, filing claims.
I can't stand being in the office.
But, every now and then,
they let me get out,
make a few rounds,
check in on some Vets.
I'm good with people.
- So who we checking on today?
- Tommy.
Nam Vet, won a Purple Heart.
Squatting in this building
for two years.
Can't seem to get him out.
Does he have any family?
No, not anymore. I got a place set up
for him and everything,
but I can't get through to him.
What makes you think
he's gonna listen to me?
Remember a kid named Robert Walker,
served with you in Afghanistan?
Yeah, Robbie,
sniper attached to our unit.
KIA by a roadside just outside Kabul.
Why?
This is his father.
This place looks like a war zone.
Wait till you see the inside.
Hey, and heads up about Graham.
He's a little touchy,
but he's all right.
Works for the landlord.
You're late!
I've been waiting out here for an hour.
It's nice to see you too, Graham.
Fuck you.
Seems nice.
People actually live out here?
Yeah, this place is
a squatter's paradise.
Nobody tells them what to do,
and they get the run of the land.
Middle of nowhere.
Yeah. Tommy likes living off the grid.
What's in the bag?
Just a little care package.
Bread, Ding Dongs, stuff like that.
Who's this guy?
My buddy Jake.
He's helping me out today.
How you doing?
Terrible. I said I'd help,
but I don't like sitting around all day.
Take it easy, Graham.
- We're gonna be in and out.
- All right.
Let's get it over with.
Place gives me the creeps.
Yeah, I'm surprised they let you
out here all by yourself today.
I'm not worried.
- Got a permit for that thing?
- Of course.
- Got it last week.
- Better hope you never need it.
Better to have one and not need it
- than not to have one...
- Look, Graham, do us a favor.
Keep it in your pants, all right?
I don't want you shooting me
by accident.
Smells great in here.
Man, it's usually like
a hobo hotel in this place.
Where is everybody?
No clue.
Say, Graham, when's the last time
you were out here?
A couple of months ago.
The last time I let you in.
Hello?
Well, it looks like somebody cleared
the place and kicked everybody out.
Maybe they all got jobs.
You can see they left in a hurry.
Didn't even finish their dinner.
Well, it wasn't us.
You know it's not worth the trouble.
We clear them out. They come back.
Clear them out. They come back,
like a pack of strays.
They're human beings.
- Yeah. Right!
- Hey.
If you don't care about these people,
then why are you still here?
We're big boys. We'll be all right.
No, no, that's not how it works.
I let you in. I let you out.
You know, we don't need a lawsuit...
Look, you two, cut it out.
All right? We're on the same team.
- Are we sure he's still here?
- I hope so.
He holes up in a store room in the back.
How'd you find this guy
in the first place?
Graham called it in.
He may be an asshole,
but he's not a monster.
Thank you.
Easy there, Rambo. It's a raccoon.
Graham, what did I say?
That thing isn't a toy.
- No, but I thought...
- Look.
You pull the piece again,
I'm gonna make you eat it.
- Do we understand each other?
- Yeah, yeah, I got it.
Tommy, open up!
Tommy, it's Luke.
Come on, Tommy.
All right, we're coming in.
Hope you're decent.
You ain't coming inside of nothing.
This is my home.
That's fine. Take it easy.
I already told you, I ain't going.
You hear me? I ain't going.
- You got something to say to me?
- No, no, no.
Not me. You can stay here
for as long as you like.
Tommy, look, I don't know what
you're talking about.
It's me, Luke, from the VA.
We spoke last month.
I'm still not leaving.
That's fine. Why don't you
just put that thing down?
Okay? Please? Put it down.
It ain't even loaded.
Then maybe you shouldn't go pointing it
at people's faces, then.
This is America, ain't it?
I just wanted to check and see
how you were doing.
I brought you some food.
- Who the hell are you?
- I'm Jake Carter.
Is that supposed to mean something
to me?
I served with your son in Afghanistan.
Robbie?
He was attached to my unit.
He was a good boy.
He was a good Marine.
They brought him home in a box!
Look, Tommy,
why don't we sit down for a second
and talk.
No, I don't think so.
Come on, man. We're just trying to help.
You can't help. No one can help me.
- Tommy...
- Just leave me be.
I've asked you twice.
I won't ask you again.
That went well.
- Well, at least he didn't shoot us.
- Yeah.
That's a plus.
Yeah, I've got to take this.
Okay, come on. Time's up. Let's go.
Come on. Yeah, I'll catch up with you.
Hi.
Yeah, this is he. Great.
You all right?
Yeah, I just thought
we had him for a second.
- Can't save everyone, brother.
- We can try.
"No man left behind," right?
That's what they taught us.
We're not at war anymore, man.
He's still a Marine.
What's upstairs?
Old office space.
They usually don't squat upstairs
'cause the ceiling is leaking.
All right, let's go.
Yeah. Listen...
Yeah, send them over,
and then I can... I'll print them off.
I'm sure...
Yeah, we can come up with a deal
that's gonna be advantageous
for both of us.
That's gonna be...
That's gonna be great.
Where do you wanna start?
Hey.
Is everything all right in there?
Quiet.
Come on. We know you're in there.
We can hear you.
We just wanna make sure
everybody's all right.
What do you think?
Maybe Graham's got a key?
Help!
Do that again, and I'll kill you.
You're up.
Figures.
- Can I help you?
- You know what?
We can see you all are eating dinner.
We're interrupting, so we're gonna...
Are you okay?
She's fine. Just a little disagreement.
I'd like to hear it from her,
if you don't mind.
Why not?
Tell him, Sarah.
- I'm fine.
- See? She's fine.
Maybe we should call the police,
let them sort this out?
- That won't be necessary.
- I insist.
There's no need for the police, Jake.
Maybe we should just be on our way.
- Unbelievable.
- Move.
- Take it easy. All right!
- Just stay calm.
Hey.
You won't be needing this.
Search them.
Now, let's see
who we're dealing with here.
"Luke Trapper, Veteran Affairs."
How noble of you.
"Jake Carter, EMT."
And would you look at that?
Both of you are soldiers.
- How cute.
- Marines.
Marines.
Is that why you're out here
kicking down doors?
- Trying to relive your glory days?
- Something like that.
Well, you jumped the gun on this one,
didn't you, chap?
You guys ready?
I wanna get out of here before...
Don't move!
Graham, put that thing away.
You're gonna get us all killed.
Listen to your friend, okay?
I said don't move.
Just let them go, please.
That ship has sailed, Sarah.
You should have kept your mouth shut.
Have you ever shot that gun before?
Stop, okay?
'Cause it's got one hell of a kick.
- Stop talking.
- Plus,
you left the safety on.
Luke!
Move it!
- What was that, Jake?
- No clue.
Shit, we're trapped in here.
- Are you all right?
- No, no, no.
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
Look at me. Look at me.
- They're gonna kill us.
- No, they're not.
We're not gonna let that happen,
are we, Luke?
Probably not.
Come on!
- What's your name?
- Sarah.
All right, Sarah.
We're gonna get you out of here.
You believe me, right?
- Yes.
- Then say it.
You're gonna get me out of here.
- That's right.
- How?
Still working on that.
A little help over here.
Never mind. We're good.
Shit!
Come on. Come here. Come here.
Get it over here. Get it over...
- What?
- We need her alive.
- Yeah, I know that.
- Then why are you shooting at them?
He broke John's hand.
I don't care about John's hand.
No more guns.
We can't risk hitting the girl.
Understood?
Whatever you say, Maddy.
Call my brother.
Tell him to bring the boys.
Until my father's verdict is in,
we can't take any chances.
What about them?
Guard the door.
It's a dead end.
- They're not going anywhere.
- Let's go.
Here. Happy birthday.
Ladies and gentlemen of the jury,
you have witnessed iron clad proof
of Horace Hayes' guilt.
We have indisputable scientific evidence
on a murder weapon,
and CCTV images
from the night of March 4th
showing Horace Hayes and his associates
entering the building
where three of Portland's finest
police officers were slain,
men with families and children.
And beyond that, we have unveiled
an extremely dangerous
head of a crime family
with a far reach across America.
To truly kill a snake,
you must cut off its head.
Now, go do what's right.
Thank you, Your Honor.
- Hey.
Can you believe we're even supposed
to deliberate this shit?
As if some asshole isn't gonna find
this guy guilty.
- Wait. Wait, Ben.
- Yeah.
No, nothing.
Okay, deliberation, room three.
Let's go.
It's too high.
Got to find a way out of here.
I'm working on it.
We got company.
Squad or platoon?
Looks like the whole division.
Sarah, you mind telling us
what these people want with you?
My father's a juror
on the Horace Hayes trial.
They want a mistrial.
They're using me as leverage.
- The Hayes family?
- Yeah.
This just keeps getting better
and better.
Yo, we're here.
Oscar, we got two Marines
trapped up here.
Clear the rest of the building.
No one should be here
except for you guys.
Hey.
Scout out the building.
Make sure there isn't any more Marines
wandering around.
What are you talking about?
Just do it.
Marines?
All right, stand back.
Wait till we give the "all clear."
Wait. Where are you going?
You're up.
I'm going to kick your ass, man!
Maddy! They're over here!
Over here!
You good?
Yeah.
We need a phone.
Got one. Passcode.
- Come on.
- Don't lock it out.
You can make an emergency call
from the lock screen.
- I don't see it.
- Here. Give it to me.
- He must have blocked it.
- Mine, too.
We've got to keep moving.
Hey.
I'm taking the girl.
And you're dead.
I owe you one.
- Two, by my count.
- Two?
Ramādī, '06.
- I had that guy.
- The hell you did.
Give me a hand.
We need to get to the truck.
Okay. Come on.
Keep your head down and keep swinging.
Wait. We can't just go
charging out there like Leeroy Jenkins.
We need a plan.
Leeroy who?
Doesn't matter. They know where we are.
They'll be waiting for us.
Then we'll just go through them.
I'm sure you're probably, like,
the baddest guys at the bar and all,
but they have guns. We have a hammer.
Look, the longer we sit here,
the more of them there are gonna be.
We either keep moving, or we die.
I'm not going out there.
He's right. We've got to keep moving.
It's the only way.
Keep looking. Next room.
Maybe it's not.
- Where does this lead?
- The grain room.
Lock it down. No one in, no one out.
- Go.
- Get the guys.
Lock this mother down!
Come on.
We're running out of time.
Grain room's this way.
They've got nowhere to go.
Luke, hurry.
Ready or not, soldier boys!
- How far down?
- Far.
You know where it lets out?
There's only one way to find out.
Last chance, Marines.
What's it gonna be, huh?
Easy way or the hard way?
There's about 10 feet diagonal,
followed by a long drop.
Keep yourself wedged,
and take it slowly.
Get in there. Come on. Come on.
All right, come on. You're up. Let's go.
Yup.
Take it easy. You can do it.
You can do it, Sarah.
Easy. Easy, Sarah.
You're doing great.
- Slowly.
- Just go.
You're doing great, Sarah.
We have to hurry.
Not too fast.
Keep pressed into the sides.
Sarah, you can do this.
Keep calm. Nice and slow.
Oh, shit.
Jake?
Jake!
We're good!
- I slipped.
- You think?
Sorry.
Get up, man.
Hey, leatherneck, catch!
Oh, shit.
Let's go, let's go.
Luke! Are you all right?
Nope. Not at all.
- Is it deep?
- Yeah.
- You should've caught me.
- I didn't have time.
You caught her.
Jeez...
Leave that be.
Luke, it's better where it is.
That's easy for you to say.
- Yeah, I really wouldn't do that.
- Don't.
I think I'm gonna throw up.
You're a stubborn son of a bitch,
you know that?
Could you hand me that?
I'm gonna try to stop the bleeding.
Hey, soldier boys, we're coming for you.
I'm gonna kill that guy.
It's that way.
All right, well, it's not that bad.
Yo.
- I thought you finished that guy.
- So did I.
Look, just give us the girl,
and you two can walk away.
That's not gonna happen.
You just met her.
You can't be that attached.
I guess we're gonna find out.
Round two.
I got this one.
You get beefcake over there.
No!
Get off!
Stop screaming.
- I got three.
- So did I. I had the big one.
Horseshit. This guy had a cattle prod.
Thanks, Graham.
Come on.
This way.
- It's chained shut.
- Let the big bull charge.
You shouldn't be slamming that shoulder
into anything.
You know, why don't you let me worry
about that?
We need to stop the bleeding.
Well, then, buddy, why don't you drop me
by the old CASEVAC
on the way out of here?
Are you guys serious?
I thought that thing wasn't loaded.
It is now.
We need your help.
Funny how that works.
Please.
All right, come on now.
Maddy and her brother kicked everyone
out of here last week.
And they just let you stay?
Yeah. I guess I'm one stubborn SOB.
You're telling me.
Do you have a first aid kit?
I need gauze, disinfectant,
whatever you got.
Son, I don't even got electricity.
- Where did you...
- Don't touch my stuff.
Seriously, though,
where'd you find all this?
Goodwill, garbage cans, dumpsters.
Why'd you save it all?
Well, it don't seem right
throwing it all away.
People die for that flag.
- How does it look?
- You might have nicked the thoracic.
There's too much blood. I can't be sure.
We need a hospital.
- That isn't an option.
- Luke, I'm serious.
This is bad. For once in your life,
just listen to me.
You could bleed out.
Remember Helmand, '09?
No more stories, Luke.
We don't have time. I've got to think.
We got cut off, pinned down.
The exit road out.
- Slick Willy, he took one in the gut.
- Yeah, I remember.
It was something, huh?
Field cook?
Bingo.
Can you spare a round?
Man, just dump the whole thing in there.
I don't want to have to do this twice.
I'm trying to minimize the damage.
So this actually works?
Sometimes.
- And is it safe?
- I didn't say that.
How are you two still alive?
Good question.
For the pain.
I don't like to drink alone.
You don't got to ask me twice.
To Robbie.
Yeah. All right. To Robbie.
All right, light me up, doc.
- You ready for this?
- No, but do it anyway.
We'll find them, Maddy.
Excuse me?
I said, we'll find them, make them pay.
But you've already found them. Yeah.
Twice, by my count.
You told us not to use guns.
I did say that, didn't I?
We could've stopped it. We could've...
You shouldn't need guns.
Maddy, wait...
Where were you?
Securing the exits.
Like you asked.
- They got out.
- They didn't.
Then where are they?
Just make sure you have a clear shot.
I wouldn't want you
to end up like Rooney.
- I'll kill them myself.
- She lives. They die.
- Yeah.
- Good.
Now, get out of here.
What are you looking at?
I told you it would work.
You'll need antibiotics
when we get out of here.
Still got a couple left over
from that ear infection.
- I'll take them when I get home.
- No.
You need a real doctor, real medicine.
Just promise me
you'll go to the hospital.
- All right, relax.
- And now we're even.
This takes care
of saving your life upstairs.
You still owe me for these two.
How could I forget?
Now, could you put something on
so we can get out of here?
Well, this is all I got.
Nice T-shirt, Grandma.
Don't let me die in this thing.
We're not dying in here.
Is there a back way out of this place?
Something that they don't know about?
There's some old tunnels
that lead down to the docks.
Where's the entrance?
There's a dead phone in the loading bay.
But, hey, I don't know what shape
the tunnels are in.
What do you think?
Better than staying in here.
- Can you take us there?
- One more patrol ain't gonna hurt me.
Let's just hope it doesn't turn
into a combat mission.
We'll need these.
Now...
Fall in, men.
Stay together.
Keep close.
Hey, Tommy,
how come you never let me
get you out of this place?
I made my own bed.
I'm man enough to lie in it.
You're even more stubborn than I am.
Hey.
You guys check the old man's room.
- You, stay with me.
- I don't see him.
It's all clear.
Wait.
Maybe they didn't hear us.
Run!
Don't hit the girl!
Get this off me.
Over here!
Luke, come on.
They're right on our tail.
Just gonna slow them down a bit.
We've got a problem.
That's the entrance to the tunnels.
Don't tell me that.
- The car is right on top of it.
- Of course it is.
Put it in neutral.
- Get up!
- Go. Move it.
Let's go!
You up for this, old man?
Shut up and push.
Incoming!
- Is it in neutral?
- I don't know.
- What do you mean, you don't know?
- I drive a Prius.
I'm gonna die in this shirt.
Hit the clutch.
- Which one's the...
- The left one.
Sarah, get out. Let's go!
Out the side. Out the side.
- A little help over here.
- Working on it.
I got him.
Keep your head down.
She made it.
Get ready to move.
Now!
How many are there?
Two!
No, five.
Where are you going?
I've got one left.
I'm out.
Move forward!
Luke!
Run!
Please work.
- You see that?
- Hard to miss.
Tommy!
Okay, okay.
Tommy, come here.
Hang in there, buddy.
Hang in there, okay?
You're gonna be all right.
Just keep breathing.
Don't lie to me, kid.
I know a kill shot when I see it.
Come on. I've seen worse.
Yeah, I'm a dead man.
We just need to get you out of here.
No, no, no.
I'm fine right here.
Wait. Wait. Wait.
Take this for me.
It was Robbie's.
Now,
finish your mission, Marine.
Semper Fi.
Grab a gun. Let's finish this.
They're in the tunnels.
Those tunnels lead to the docks.
Call Kat.
Make sure she's waiting for them.
You get down there and drive them to us.
- What are you gonna do, then?
- What you couldn't.
This trial has been going on
for 13 days, man.
- I wanna go home.
- Yeah, so do I.
Then repeat after me, "Guilty."
Look, I'm sorry.
I just don't see it that way, okay?
They killed cops, Patrick. Cops.
- Allegedly.
- No, not allegedly.
It's right there in black and white.
Look.
You have a daughter, right?
You don't want this monster
on the street with her.
Do you?
No, I don't.
But you have my vote.
And I'm not going to change my mind.
So what do they call these things again?
Shanghai Tunnels.
Downtown is littered with them. I didn't
think they ran way out here.
I'm surprised
they haven't filled them in by now.
They're a big deal.
I did a paper on them
for my AP Lit class.
They used to give tours and stuff.
Great, maybe we'll run into a tour group
while we're down here,
and they can schlep us out of here.
No, I don't think so.
Why is that?
Well, two years ago,
a tunnel collapsed on a tour group,
killed three people,
so they don't run them anymore.
It's just too dangerous.
Do us a favor. Keep that shit
to yourself until we get out of here.
Yeah, yeah, sure. Sorry.
- What's up, Kat?
- Yeah, we're in.
We're gonna chase them to you.
You got this?
Don't worry about it, sweetheart.
I'll bury those boys down here.
Let's go.
Another dead end.
What do you think?
Eeny, meeny, miny, moe...
Well, better than anything I got.
Hey, shut off your lights for a second.
Why would we do that?
Because, if it's dark enough,
maybe we'll see daylight,
and, you know, find our way out of here.
Worth a shot.
Look, the last time I listened to her,
I got hit in the head,
fell down a grain chute,
and then impaled on a steel rod.
Looks like they already found us.
No, they know we're down here,
but they don't know where we are.
They must have heard us
or saw our flashlights.
No, if they saw us,
we'd be dead already.
Hey...
- See? I told you.
- Sarah.
That ain't daylight, kid.
Come on.
Back up.
Chill out, man. Chill out.
She might be one of them.
One of what?
No, no, come on. She ran into me.
I didn't touch her.
What are you doing down here?
We were squatting upstairs.
We got kicked out.
We've been living down here ever since.
And you just wander
the tunnels by yourself?
I heard an explosion.
I came to check it out. That's all.
- Could you lower that thing?
- Not yet.
- Do you have a phone?
- No.
I don't know who you are.
Right now, I don't care.
But you're gonna lead us out of here.
- Can you do that?
- Yeah.
Come on. It's this way.
You really think
she looks like a squatter?
I can see that,
but it's either her or those guys.
She's not the one shooting at us.
- Yet.
- Just keep your eyes open.
This way.
- How much further?
- Not much, I promise.
So you live down here by yourself?
No, just me and a couple friends.
Yeah, what's your name?
- Kat.
How come you and your friends
didn't move into another building
instead of living down here like rats?
We like our privacy.
Nobody bothers us down here.
Almost there.
I thought you didn't have a phone.
Yeah, I was lying about that actually.
What else are you lying about?
Well, this isn't the way out, for one.
- I knew we couldn't trust her.
- Yeah.
Hey, boys.
Get down!
No!
Sarah...
Don't worry, sweetie.
We're gonna shoot her in the head
and then dump her body in the harbor.
It'll be painless.
You good?
What are you gonna do
with that, jarhead?
Improvise.
Adapt.
Overcome.
They got Sarah.
Not for long.
I feel a breeze.
- Clear.
- We got an exit.
Go! Go!
Hey! I got them!
Shit!
We found you.
- I thought you said it was clear.
- It was.
Well, looks like
we're not making it for tip-off.
We never were.
Hell, I don't even like basketball.
I just bought those tickets to guilt you
into coming out with me today.
You could've just asked me.
I hate owing people favors.
Could've called it even.
Yeah.
But I like being owed.
Shit!
I can't believe it.
After six tours, I'm gonna die in
a tunnel with another man's rifle.
Come on out, guys.
We got you surrounded.
Hey.
Remember Kunjak?
You telling stories now?
Thought that was my thing.
You took two bullets in the gut,
covering my retreat.
I was your CO.
My job was to keep you alive.
That was a tactical retreat.
Exactly.
Jesus, Jake.
I think they're out.
Then go get them.
Are you all right?
Get Sarah. Finish this.
Don't do it, Jake.
Don't you do it.
We're even.
No!
No! Jake!
Goodbye, Marine.
Jake!
- Where does that come out?
- No idea.
You two, find him.
- What about me?
- We got a boat to catch.
You didn't have to kill him.
Luke's not gonna let you get away
with it! He's gonna find you!
Then I'll put him in the ground, too.
Sarah.
If this dude's got a brain,
he's halfway to Portland by now.
It's a waste of time.
Let's get to the boat.
Here. Take her. Let's go.
I wonder how the trial is going.
Now would you look at that.
"Hung jury. Judge declares mistrial
on all counts. Horace Hayes to walk."
Looks like your daddy pulled through
for you after all.
Then let me go.
We did what you asked.
We won't tell anyone. Please.
Sweetheart, you should know me
better than that by now.
You're a loose end,
and so is your daddy.
Bitch.
- Take her on board.
- My pleasure.
Kill him!
Get off me!
- What's going on?
- Go! Go! Go!
- What about the others?
- Now!
Luke!
Nice shirt.
Did you happen to bring my knife
by any chance?
No.
But I know where you left it.
Don't worry about it, sweetheart.
He can keep it.
So was that your plan?
Jump on the boat and beat
the poor little woman into submission?
Honestly, I'm just kind
of making this up as I go along.
I expected more from you.
This is a fight you can't win, Marine.
I've never really been good at losing.
What are you gonna do with that?
Just a little something
a friend taught me.
No!
So wait a minute.
Let me get this straight.
You killed all these men?
More or less.
But where's Ms. Hayes now?
Bottom of the ocean.
You sure?
I put her there.
What about Horace?
Does he just walk?
I wouldn't worry about that.
I think they got a whole slew
of new charges for him.
Sarah!
- Dad.
- I'm sorry, baby.
- I'm so, so sorry.
- We'll pick this up later.
I'm okay. I'm fine. I'm fine.
Thanks to him.
Thank you.
The officers told me what you did.
I don't know what we would have done.
- It wasn't just me.
- Soldier coming through.
Hey. Could you give me a second?
Semper Fi, brother.
We're even.
- Just give me a second.
- Sure.
How are you doing?
I was gonna ask you the same thing.
Just saying goodbye.
I'm so sorry about Jake.
You know, he'd do it all again tomorrow,
even knowing the outcome.
He died a Marine.
I should probably go to the hospital.
Yeah. I think
that's probably a good idea.
Please rate this subtitle at www.osdb.link/72gxc
Help other users to choose the best subtitles