Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
It's okay, son...
I know you want this to be over.
I'm right here.
I will be right here...
But, you don't give up.
You hear me?
As long as you can still
grab a breath, you fight.
You breathe... keep breathing.
Hawk.
Ah, shit.
Goddamn sumbitches.
The sumbitch
got shit for brains.
You seen Coulter?
Nope.
Listen up!
When them plews is cleaned,
I want you to hoop 'em up
real tight.
Remember, we're not doing
no 15-pelt bales!
We're going
30-pelt bales!
Fitzgerald!
Cap'n.
Where are we with the haul?
What are you thinking?
I'm thinking, whatever it is
they're hunting out there...
...I hope it don't need
another shot.
Make sure we're ready
to head out by dawn.
Been done by this morning.
I'd have liked
to be out by how,
but the men
are too tired.
We're only a few days
from the fort.
We're trapped out.
All we have to worry about
is fresh meat for the boys.
Well, you, uh, seen Coulter?
Hey, we took down
an elk. A big one.
We need help
to haul the meat back.
Let me know
when it's on the spit.
I'll help you
with it then.
Come on, I need your help.
We needed help when we were
loading them bales.
I been eating this damn
beaver meat so long...
...I'm starting to
miss my wife's cooking.
I'm starting
to miss your wife.
Shut up.
Help!
Help.
Is that Coulter?
You go get the Captain.
Jesus Christ.
Anybody see them?
Stay quiet.
Watch the ridge.
What was that?
Pa?
Let's go.
They got Thomas.
I can't see 'em.
Get down!
We're surrounded!
They're everywhere!
Stay here! Stay here!
Paul, no!
They want us out in the open.
Nobody move!
Stay where you are!
They want the pelts.
We got to get
on that boat right now
or we'll lose it all.
Get to the boat!
To the boat, son! Move!
Move, move!
Leave the furs!
Leave the furs! To the boat!
Hawk!
Grab some pelts!
Come on, grab the pelts!
Grab the pelts!
Give this
to my little girl.
You're coming with us.
I'll get help.
Leave the furs!
Leave the pelts!
Willman!
Lean on me.
Just keep going.
Get to the boat!
Fucking savage!
Get on the fucking boat!
Help!
Cut the rope!
Wait for Amos!
No! We go now!
Fire the cannon!
Don't leave! Wait!
My daughter, Powaqa, is not here.
Collect all the pelts we can carry.
We'll trade pelts with the French
for horses and keep searching for her.
...and dust becomes flour...
...and when the morning
is clear...
...this child of God will meet
Jesus Christ himself. Amen.
You ready?
Hold still.
Where did you learn that?
My father was a doctor.
Bridger!
Captain,
we got a swarm of
tree niggers out here
waiting to finish the job.
Tell me you got
some kind of plan.
Glass?
Missouri's no good.
Not while the Ree's
running it.
We got to
get off this boat.
Oh, you want to
get off the boat?
Then what do we do, huh?
Take our furs and sit
out there amongst the Ree
like a bunch of ducks?
Only safe thing to do is track
a new course back up on land.
That'll add weeks
to the trip.
Better than floating
where they can get eyes on us.
They got eyes on you
right now, son.
What I'm saying is
we stay on the boat.
Chart a course
toward the fort
and take our chances
on the water.
Glass knows
this territory best.
It's his job
to get us home safe.
Get us home safe?
Yeah.
Need I remind you
we already lost 32 men?
It's 33 now.
They were my men, Fitzgerald.
I know how many I lost.
We do like Glass says.
That's the end of it.
We have to
set the boat loose.
If the Ree are tracking us,
they'll find it downriver.
Best course is to
hike inland to the Grand
and follow it
to Fort Kiowa.
On foot?
It'll be winter
before we get there.
Yeah, unless
we come across a post,
trade for some horses.
Ain't no posts
that far over!
Captain, losing this boat
is a goddamn mistake.
The Ree
ain't that stupid.
We keep it, we can lay it up
around Arrow's Peak.
Quit acting like you know
what you're talking about.
Ain't nobody talking to you.
Who'd listen
to you anyway?
Can't find your way out of
your breeches to take a shit.
All I'm saying is
Camp Rhulen is just up the way.
We can hole up there.
We walk.
Yeah, I'm sure we will.
Wish my dad
was a doctor.
Then he could've bought me
a captain's job.
What do we do, eh?
Pray these pelts ain't rotten
if we ever get back here?
Make sure
to mark this place.
We're leaving a fortune
under these rocks.
Glass, chart a course.
Tightest you can that
gets us around the Ree.
This ain't right.
We all know these furs
ain't gonna be here
by the time we come back.
There's no way we can haul
them all the way to the fort.
Arikara are
all through the territory.
We'll want
our hands free.
We're gonna
lose those pelts.
You rather keep the pelts
or your life?
Life?
What life you talking about?
I ain't got no life.
I just got living
and the only way I get that
is through these pelts.
Fuck!
Ain't no way I'm going home
after six months
working my ass off
like a mule...
...risking my neck,
men dying, and for what?
Damn near lost everything.
Job's been fucked
from the start!
There's the one
been fucking us.
You wonder how the Ree
got the dead drop on us...
...when Mr. Glass
was supposed
to look out
for that very thing?
All them Pawnee buddies of his.
Pawnee's as much against
the Ree as the rest of us.
Yeah?
Well, what about
his little half-breed son?
What kind of savage
you think his mama was?
Oh, lay off the boy, Fitz.
All I'm saying is...
...a savage... is savage.
Hey, Glass...
...is it true
what they say
about you shooting a lieutenant
while living
with them savages?
Twenty-one dead soldiers
and 40 dead feathernecks.
But you and your boy
the only ones to walk out alive.
Kind of a miracle.
Shut up, Fitzgerald.
Is that what you did?
Shot one of your own
to save this little dog here?
Shut up!
Why? Was he playing with
this little boy's mama, huh?
Did he kill her?
Hey, you can quit
polishing that rifle
when I'm talking to you.
I'm working on it.
You can work on it
when I'm done talking to you.
Look at me.
That's enough!
You're forgetting
your place, boy.
As far as I can tell,
my place is here
on the smart end
of this rifle.
You move along, Fitzgerald.
That's an order!
Listen!
There's only a couple hours
of light left.
We got to stash these pelts
and get rid of the boat.
Let's go!
I told you to be invisible, son.
At least he...
...If you want to survive,
keep your mouth shut.
- At least he heard me...
- They don't hear your voice!
They just see the color of your face.
You understand?
Yes.
You have to listen to me, son.
You have to listen.
Beckett!
Weston!
Why are
they not jumping?
It looks
like they changed their minds.
Smart sumbitches.
Smart.
I ought to be
on that boat.
They did the right thing.
It's time to move.
Get up.
We're headed out.
I'm coming.
It's better you lay down.
When the rest of the men are ready
you send them to me.
I'm going west.
You are my son.
There are only two here.
Powaqa is not here.
The others probably took her.
They went north.
We'll pick up their tracks on the mountain.
Was it
the right decision?
Leaving the boat?
The Ree own that river.
They would've flanked us.
We stay east of the Grand
through the mountains,
we cut a week off our trip.
Lands are bone dry up there.
Nothing for the Ree to hunt.
Except us.
Is it true
what Fitzgerald said?
Is that why you came out
here to the edge of the world?
Glass?
I do like the quiet.
Your boy...
...he's seen a lot.
He got a mother
you need to get him back to?
Mr. Glass!
There are cubs here!
We got cubs here!
Christ Almighty.
He's down here!
Keep your eyes open.
There's bears around.
I need your help now!
Oh, my God.
Get me rags now!
Give me rags
before he bleeds out. Rags.
Prepare the kit. Bridger!
You hold that.
Easy. Oh, my God.
Got to give him
credit for taking that grizz
down with him.
He shouldn't have shot.
The place is crawling
with tree niggers.
That's enough!
We're still
in Ree territory.
He's one of our own men.
Scout a circle around us.
North and west.
Take those two with you.
Bill, Fryman,
you take south and east.
Watch for anyone
that might've heard that shot.
We have to stitch him up.
What about me? Captain?
You just stay here.
Hold it down.
I'm so sorry, Mr. Glass.
Bridger,
press down here.
He's bleeding
down here, too.
They're torturing the bastard.
The proper thing to do
would be...
...to finish him off quick.
Unless he has a chance
of pulling through.
Pulling through?
You saw what that
grizz did to him.
He'll be dead inside an hour.
Mmm-hmm.
Yeah, we all will be
if he don't quit wailing like that.
Toward you and twist it
into place. I'll hold him. Go.
- Pa.
- Hold him. Go.
Go!
Now!
He passed out.
I'll take advantage
and stitch up his neck.
Water.
Bridger, tell the others
we'll camp here tonight.
I'm right here.
I'll be right here...
Toussaint, he's here.
I thought he wouldn't make it.
I'm glad you made it here.
We need horses and rifles.
We bring you many pelts.
No horses... just what we agreed.
Take all the pelts you want.
We need horses and rifles.
I need a woman with big tits...
Who can cook.
We can't give you any horses.
What's he saying?
I don't know, something about horses.
Bring us something to drink... some whisky.
Tell him to stop asking about the horses.
Always good doing business with you.
Horses.
No horses.
All we can trade are guns and ammunition.
Tell him if he asks about horses again,
there is no deal.
Where did you get these? The Americans?
They're already branded.
I'll only be able to get
half price for them.
Get him away from there.
I said no horses.
We'll take these three horses.
I'm not going to say it again.
They aren't part of the deal.
Now tell your man to step away.
We had an agreement, you have to honor it.
In French
You stand there and talk to me about honor?
I told you he speaks French.
Those pelts are stolen.
You all have stolen everything from us.
Everything!
The land.
The animals.
Two white men snuck into our village,
and took my daughter, Powaqa.
We leave you these pelts
because honor demands it.
I take your horses to find my daughter.
You are free to try and stop me.
Business is business.
Prepare five horses for them.
I want everybody up
at the crack of dawn.
Carrying Glass will be hard...
...so we need to get ahead
as far as possible.
We'll divide into two groups.
Fitzgerald, Jones, Fryman,
you take the east side
of the river.
Anderson, you scout up front.
That claw
don't belong to you.
It ain't for me.
Stop!
Don't let him down!
Watch it.
How we gonna
make it up this?
Slow down.
It's killing us, Captain!
Lift it, Bridger!
Goddamn it,
keep it steady.
Lift it up higher.
I am.
And heave!
I'll go up and pull.
My foot!
Enough of this shit!
We'll never make it across
like this, Captain.
He's burning up.
Cap'n, you ain't doing us
nor him no favors...
...by letting him
go on suffering like this.
Captain, it's all
the same up here.
We're gonna have to go back.
Find another way.
Glass. Hugh.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Lay that rag over his eyes,
Mr. Bridger.
What?
Lay the rag
over his eyes.
Wait!
I'm sorry, Hugh.
Sir, I can't do that.
How do we
get back without him?
Only he knows the way.
Lay the rag
over his eyes.
I can't.
Wait! How do
we get back...
Lay it over his eyes!
Step back.
Bridger, stop!
Bridger, Henry.
Henry! Henry, please.
Captain. Captain.
Please. Please leave...
There's a $70 bonus
from the Rocky Mountain Fur
Company to the two men...
...that stay with Glass
to see this through.
I'll stay!
Me, too.
Money or not, I'll stay.
I'll need a third.
Sorry, Captain.
I have a family.
I'm not crazy.
Captain, three men
can't hold off a party of Ree,
much less some boys.
Besides, $70 ain't gonna buy
nobody a new set of ears.
A hundred, then.
This man is the only reason
we're still alive.
We were 45 men
when this started.
Now we're ten. Almost nine.
He's my father.
He can have my share.
Mine, too.
He can have my share also.
All right.
If Mr. Bridger
feels the same way,
I'll lag behind with them.
You?
Yep.
You already lost
my share of the pelts...
...so I got no choice
but to make it up
by some other means.
Sticking around
for another day or two
don't make no difference.
$300... at least I get to
go home with something.
Glass is to be cared
for until, understood?
Yeah. You have my word.
I understand.
You boys get him
down off this slope
and somewhere safe
before dark.
Fitzgerald.
Glass is to be cared for
as long as necessary.
And a proper burial
when it's time.
He's earned it.
I understand.
You hurt yourself?
I'll be fine.
Can you hear that wind, father?
Remember what mother used to say
about the wind?
The wind cannot defeat
a tree with strong roots.
You are still breathing...
I miss her so much.
I will be right here...
I'm right here.
As long as you can still grab a breath,
you fight.
You breathe. Keep breathing.
When there is a storm...
And you stand in front of a tree...
If you look at its branches,
you swear it will fall.
But if you watch the trunk,
you will see its stability.
Three hundred bucks
goes a long way
toward retirement.
Go down to Texas, find me
a decent piece of land,
and start pissing in the wind.
Get me the hell out of this
godforsaken place.
Ree done that to you?
I'm just asking.
Yeah, they done it.
They took their
sweet time with it.
At the start,
I didn't feel nothing.
I just heard the sound...
...of the knife scraping
against my skull and...
...them all laughing
and whooping
and hollering and whatnot.
Then the blood came.
It was cold. It started
streaming down my face,
in my eyes, and...
...breathing it in.
Choking on it.
That's when I felt it.
Yeah, felt all of it.
I got my head
turned inside out.
Jesus.
Them Indians
down Texas way...
...they may rob you,
but they ain't gonna take your topknot.
When was it?
Goddamn it,
will you quit that noise now,
will you?
Quit it.
I'm falling further back
from Henry and the boys
on account of tending to you.
Got to get up
the damn mountain,
but winter
keeps chasing us down.
If you ready
to take the sacrament...
...I can do that for you.
What you holding to, Glass?
You know...
...it would be better...
...if you were to take that
last breath of yours now...
for all of us.
Now you hung tough.
And that's something.
I'm begging you.
Them Ree are so close
I can smell 'em.
You can smell 'em, too.
You got to think of your boy.
All right?
'Cause you're gonna kill him.
You'll kill us all.
I can muzzle you
if you like.
Take away this suffering
quick and easy.
No one ever has to know
that you give up.
All you have to do is blink
if you want me to do that.
Save your boy and blink.
You just have to blink.
Yeah. There it is.
You'd best hope
the good Lord'll
get His ass here
quick, huh?
Maybe He'll forgive your sins,
maybe not.
Thus I do commend thee
to the Lord.
Through Jesus Christ the Lord
of all reality and mercy...
...and the Father
and the Creator, I hold thee...
Get away! Get away!
You okay?
Jim! Jim! Help!
Help!
Calm down.
Jim! Help!
Don't shout! You're gonna
get us all killed!
Keep away! I'll tell
the Captain what you did.
They'll hang you!
They'll hang you! Jim, help!
We have an understanding.
What's fucking wrong
with you people?
Shit.
I got one beaver, Hawk.
Breathing changed?
I hadn't noticed.
Damn, he's cold as ice.
Here you go, Mr. Glass.
This will help you.
Keep you warm.
It's all right.
Where's Hawk?
He ain't with you?
No.
No?
I understand, Mr. Glass.
It's all right.
I think I'll get a fire going.
Yeah.
Sounds like a good idea.
Hawk!
Shh. Ree.
There's about 20 of them
down by the creek.
They're headed this way.
Grab your shit and let's go.
Shit. What do we do?
Run, right now.
What about Hawk?
He ain't our problem no more.
We can't just leave him.
Either he's gutted or scalped.
And if he ain't
he can find us, can't he?
What about Glass?
He ain't our problem.
Like us, he's on his own.
We made a promise
to the Captain.
A proper burial
when the time was needed.
He needs that rifle!
He couldn't do nothing with it
if you tarred it to his hand.
We can't do this.
We got no fucking choice.
No, we can't.
Look at him.
All right, shit, then, buddy.
Get him up.
You want to take him?
Come on now!
Easy. Slowly, Fitz.
Easy with him.
Just get your shit.
Get your shit!
Shut up.
Shut up!
Hold up!
Fitz. What are you doing?
What does it look like?
Proper burial.
Like you wanted.
No, not like this.
Why not?
He's alive, Fitz.
He's alive.
So shoot him.
I have to go.
I'm sorry, Mr. Glass.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
Captain! This way!
There's a path down here!
There ain't shit down there!
We got to climb over!
Glass said to stay east!
Glass can go to hell!
What's the map say?
Keep climbing.
We climb, Captain.
We keep climbing.
Till we reach Old Gabe.
We climb.
We got to wait for Murph.
Yeah.
You wait for him.
Captain?
Sir...
...Murphy says
there's a way down there.
Who we following?
You follow who you want!
I'm going up!
Stubby, keep going up!
Murph! Come here!
I'm not leaving you, son.
I'm right here.
Fire's done.
I can't even feel my feet.
Didn't we put enough distance
between us and them Ree?
A dozen Ree can make
twice as good time as we can.
Twenty.
What?
You said you saw
twenty Ree.
Yeah? What you
talking about?
You woke me up.
Mmm-hmm.
You said you saw
twenty Ree by the creek.
Well, yeah,
twenty, a dozen...
...it don't matter.
I wasn't gonna hang around
counting fucking feathers.
As a matter of fact...
...what was you doing down
by the creek all by yourself?
I'd already brought up
plenty of water.
Hey!
Answer me, Fitzgerald.
I asked you a question.
Don't question me
on account of you feel guilty.
Answer me
or I'll blow your head off.
You got
a short-term memory, boy.
Your ass would be floating
around the Missouri right now
if it wasn't for me.
You want to ask questions?
What you want to ask?
If you want to know, ask it.
Hmm?
You want to know
why you left
Mr. Glass back there
for dead, huh?
Or why you left your little
boyfriend running around?
You want to know
if he's still alive?
I'll tell you why.
It's 'cause you ain't a man yet.
It's 'cause you was
scared shitless.
You're scared now.
The Ree.
What of them?
Tell me, did you see 'em?
Put your rifle down.
Did you see the Ree?
No.
Not a single one.
You fucking lied to me?
You lied to me!
I had to scare
some sense into you, boy.
Glass was dead.
Hawk we don't know about.
No point in either of us
dying either, you understand?
The way I see it,
I saved your life twice now.
I ought to be God to you.
And God giveth...
and God taketh away.
Lucky fucker.
Next time you want to
shoot somebody...
...you might
want to use powder,
prime your rifle.
Come on. Let's git.
Grab your shit.
Fresh blood. This could be Powaqa.
A dead boy.
A Pawnee boy.
Let's go.
Who did this?
I don't know.
Could be
Captain Leavenworth's boys.
Mmm. Yeah.
Put some eyes on the back
of your head.
These Injuns ain't never
as dead as you think they are.
Look at 'em, huh?
They're always
stealing our shit.
We got horses over here!
Hey, Bridger.
We got horses!
What you want to do
about these pigs?
The Lord's on our side, kid.
You all right there, kid?
Your head in the right place?
I guess.
I can't help thinking about
whether we did the right...
Ain't our place to wonder.
The good Lord...
...got us on a road
whether we choose it or not.
My pop, he weren't
a religious man, you know?
If you couldn't grow it,
kill it, or eat it,
he just plain old
didn't believe in it.
And this one time he head on
up the old Saba hills.
San Saba hills?
He joined a couple Texas
Ranger buddies of his to hunt.
Pretty routine. He done it
like a hundred times before.
Should have been a 3-day kill,
but on the second day,
it all went fucked.
Somehow that night
he lost his buddies.
And to top it off...
...them Comanches
went and took the horses.
So he was starving
and delirious...
...and he crawls up
into this mott, this...
...group of trees out
in the middle of nowhere
just sticking up
in this ocean of scrub...
...and he found religion.
At that moment,
he told me...
...he found God.
Uh-huh.
And it turns out that God...
...He's a squirrel.
Yeah. A big, old meaty one.
"I found God,"
he used to say.
"And while sitting there
and basking in the glory
"and sublimity of mercy..."
shot and ate
that son of a bitch."
Mmm.
Yeah. You might want to
close your eyes, kid.
I'm injured.
What happened to you?
A bear.
Grizzly.
My men... left me for dead.
Killed my son.
I lost my family too.
Sioux killed my people.
I'm going south to find more Pawnee.
My heart bleeds...
But revenge is in the creator's hands.
You will ride with me...
Your body is rotten.
Need to heal.
You could die.
Yeah!
There she is.
We did it.
You ought to be
proud of yourself, boy.
Yeah.
We followed orders.
We just skipped
the funeral part.
Don't go clown there
and start growing no conscience.
'Cause sure
as night'll come
they'll have us swinging
from a couple ropes.
We did
what we had to do.
We had the extra day
so we managed to dig.
...a little deeper,
lay rocks on top
so scavengers
couldn't get at him.
It was done right and all.
He was buried right.
Sir, can we...
The truth is that...
...when Hawk disappeared,
I was worried about savages.
And I was ready to get,
to move on out.
Yeah, but, Bridger here
argued to stay.
He argued to stay...
...so he could at least
build a cross or something...
...to put on top
of Glass's grave,
and that's what he did.
That's what we did.
I'm glad you pulled
your weight, Mr. Bridger.
He more than
pulled his weight, Captain.
This man here,
he was my partner.
Am I to assume that the agreed
arrangement did not change?
Uh, fortunately for me,
it did not.
Mmm-hmm.
Thank you...
...for your courage,
honor, and service.
Deal or no deal,
Mr. Bridger,
you deserve something
for what you did.
Thank you.
Kid's been beating himself up
awful bad the whole trip.
We all saw
the shape Glass was in.
There was no more
to be done. Right?
Yeah.
We all saw him.
When there is a storm...
And you stand in front of a tree...
If you look at its branches,
you swear it will fall.
But if you watch the trunk,
you will see its stability.
There are traces of a camp...
Where?
Entering the moon forest.
Maybe from two days ago.
They are moving east.
Tell the others.
Let's move quickly,
Powaqa could be with them!
Bring me the girl...
Those five horses weren't for free.
Shh...
Don't make a sound.
I will get a horse.
I'll cut off your balls.
Where is Toussaint?
Come here...
- May I join you?
- Yes.
Yeah?
Yes.
I was wondering when we might
be getting paid for that haul.
'Cause them pelts
we collected
are still out there,
you know...
...under a couple foot
of dirt and snow.
But that ain't
my fault.
I'm waiting for
Captain Leavenworth
to arrive
with his army.
Then we'll have
enough men...
...to shoot some civilization
into those fucking Arikara
and get back
our pelts.
All right. All right.
When's that supposed to happen?
I don't know.
But until then,
nobody gets paid.
Listen here, all right?
I was hired to trap 'em.
I wasn't hired to guard 'em.
The way I see it,
now you, you got a safe.
It's probably full of money.
You signed a contract
to protect your boss
and your boss's property.
And that safe
isn't full anymore.
It's short about $300.
What the hell is that
supposed to mean?
It means,
according to my records...
...you purchased more goods
on the expedition
than what you are
owed by the company.
Now, Happy New Year,
Fitzgerald.
Fryman!
White man at the gate!
Speak English.
I have no weapon.
Open her up!
Get the Captain!
Where are your men?
All dead.
Who was he?
I don't know.
Something to eat, please?
Food comes at a price.
I have no money.
Then you don't eat.
Give back some of them stolen
pelts you buy from the Injuns.
Not now, Jones.
Huh?
Silver.
How is this? Silver.
This all you got?
We was nine.
My friend, he die
in the snow.
And the other was...
...kill by wolf. I see it.
By wolf, yeah, kill.
Where'd you get this?
Canteen.
He drop it.
He kill Toussaint, he drop it...
Who? Who?
I don't know.
I don't see.
It could be Hawk.
Yeah, could be.
That half-breed runt
couldn't steal no horse.
- Maybe it was Weston.
- Or Beckett.
How far from here?
Thirty mile.
Northwest,
near the Yellowstone.
The Yellowstone!
Get the horses saddled.
Torches and supplies.
Ten dollars a man.
Anderson, you stay here.
Yes, sir.
Feed him and watch him.
I'll get you a drink.
When we get to
the Yellowstone,
we split into two groups!
Hawk!
Hawk, you out there?
Whoa! Whoa!
Keep your guard up!
Eyes in front!
Who are you?
Beckett? Is that you?
Glass?
Glass!
Jesus Christ!
Jesus Christ,
what happened?
Where is he?
Jones, take him. Go.
I'm riding ahead.
Bill, take Bridger.
Take Bridger!
Have you seen Fitzgerald?
No, sir.
Get up. Get up!
You seen Fitzgerald?
No, sir.
Fitzgerald?
Whoa, easy.
Where did he go?
Who?
Fitzgerald. Where did he go?
I have no idea.
Tell me or I'll take
your head off.
I swear to God...
Tell me. Tell me!
Texas!
He said he was going to Texas.
He said he was gonna reenlist.
Then he started
talking about property.
"A decent
piece of land."
He's heading for Texas.
That's all I know.
Stay here.
Fitzgerald!
Goddamn it!
Jones! Get the Captain!
Fryman!
Open the gate!
Open it up!
Murphy,
get the Captain.
Get him to the doctor. Now!
You said he was dead!
I thought
he was, I swear!
He lied to me!
You're a liar.
You left him out there!
Say the Lord's Prayer.
Say the Lord's Prayer!
- Our Father, Who art in heaven.
- Who art... I can't!
Shut up! Shut up!
From here out,
you're a prisoner charged with treason!
Take him to the cage!
Take him to the cage
or you'll hang alongside him!
I thought he was gonna die!
Fitz lied to me!
I couldn't help him!
Glass!
Fitz lied to me!
How is he?
He'll be fine,
but there is swelling.
He needs to rest.
I'll be back
to check up on him.
He ran off,
didn't he?
Bridger's telling the truth.
How's that?
Fitzgerald lied to him.
He was just following orders.
He wasn't there when
Fitzgerald stabbed my boy to death.
Is that what happened?
He killed Hawk.
I need a horse and gun.
No, you need to rest and eat.
I'm going after him.
No.
You'll never find him
without me.
If we wait till morning
he'll get away.
No, he won't.
He's afraid.
He knows how far
I came for him.
Same as that elk.
When they get afraid,
they run deep into the woods.
I got him trapped.
He just doesn't know it yet.
How can you be so sure?
'Cause he has
everything to lose.
All I had was that boy.
And he took him away from me.
I can't let you
go back out there.
Not again.
I ain't afraid
to die anymore.
I done it already.
I'm going with you.
That's his horse,
all right.
No way he could've ridden him
through the night.
How far ahead?
Half a day at the most.
Could be Ree.
If they aren't his,
we lose him.
Unless he reenlisted
so he could justify killing again...
...these tracks
right here are his.
I can't remember
my wife's face.
Last week,
she was still with me.
Now she's gone.
I worry I won't recognize her
when I get back home.
Is it true
you killed an officer?
I just killed the man
who was trying to kill my son.
Smoke.
How close?
No more than
a mile up that way.
I'm gonna head up to the west.
You go down to the east.
Let's see if we can
find some tracks.
And if it's the Ree?
If it's the Ree,
you turn right back around
and meet me back here.
Now, I wouldn't expect
to find a man of your stature...
...so far away
from his stove
on a morning
as cold as this, Captain.
You lost?
I'm here to take you back
to Fort Kiowa...
...where you
will be tried for murder.
Is that so?
I ain't crazy
about your plan.
Besides, I got
one of my own.
We had a deal, Glass!
I tried to tell your boy,
all right?
I tried to tell him,
but he wouldn't listen
and he kept on screaming.
He was gonna get
everybody killed.
But you and me...
we had a deal.
You know what
happened out there.
And on my soul,
the Lord... He knows...
...what happened out there.
There was no deal.
You killed my boy.
Well, maybe you should've
raised a man,
instead of some
girlie little bitch.
Goddamn it.
You came all this way
just for your revenge, huh?
Well, you enjoy it, Glass.
'Cause there ain't nothing
gonna bring your boy back.
No, it won't.
Revenge is in God's hands...
...not mine.
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today