-== [ www.OpenSubtitles.com ] ==-
Hello, Max.
I'm dropping these off,
they were my Albert's shoes.
They shouldn't go to waste,
you should sell them.
I don't sell shoes,
Mrs. Stevens.
And his overcoat
is in there too.
It's very nice,
you should wear it.
Well, I don't...
You should take your
coat, Mrs. Stevens.
I don't need it.
Uh, $16.
So, where did you go?
Oh, yeah?
Who else was there?
Thanks.
Mmm.
Sir, you have a light?
No, uh, do I...
Excuse me, sir.
Do you have a light?
Sure.
Thank you.
Thanks. Sorry.
Yeah, I know, he
thinks he's adorable.
There you go. Cheers.
Hello, mate,
you all right?
Hey.
Morning, kid.
Mornin', Jimmy.
Yeah, that's crazy.
Now, that's
an attractive-looking couple.
Babe?
Yeah.
Come on.
All right,
gotta go.
If they ever have a kid,
you won't be able
to look directly at it.
What about you?
Max, you got
any prospects?
Me? No.
Well, you should.
You're a good-looking guy.
You got a good job.
That kid's got
nothing on you.
He's got his
own driver.
What, you got somewhere
you wanna go?
I don't know.
Maybe it's about time
I figure out my own
thing, you know.
You're a cobbler,
that's your thing.
It's my father's thing.
And his father
before that.
You should be proud.
Yeah. I gotta get
back to work.
Hey, hey,
how's your mother?
You give her those pears?
I did.
She says, "Thank you."
All right,
let her know...
Kids.
Hi.
Is this your shop?
No, it's actually
my father's.
Is he here?
No, he is not.
Well, I've been trying
to talk to all the
proprietors in the area.
Do you expect
him back soon?
No, I don't expect
him back soon.
Can I help you?
Okay, I'm... I'm sorry.
Uh, what's your name?
Max Simkin.
Well, Max,
I'm Carmen Herrara
from the Lower East
Side Action Committee.
Okay.
Basically, we're dedicated
to the preservation
and rejuvenation of
the Lower East Side.
Uh-huh.
We're trying to stop
real estate developers
from converting
the neighborhood
into luxury housing
and retail spaces,
forcing the regular
people out.
How are they
forcing them out?
Money.
I mean, they buy them out
or they raise the rent.
How much do you think
I'd get for a place
like this?
That doesn't matter.
It does to me.
Max, we need people
like you to stay.
That's why we're
doing all of this.
Well, maybe you should
have checked with me first,
make sure I wanna stay.
Yeah, that's fair.
You know what?
Come here, I wanna
show you something.
Look around you, Max.
What do you see?
The city.
Exactly.
A living city.
And your shop
is a part of it.
How long have you had
this shop for, Max?
Fourth generation.
That's amazing.
See? This is not just
a playground for the rich.
It is for all of us.
Don't you think?
Yeah, I guess.
Good. So could
you sign this?
Okay.
Great. Thanks.
Do you have
plans tonight?
Excuse me?
There's a rally
if you're interested.
Mmm. Mmm.
Here. Here's a flyer.
Mr. Solomon is a
wonderful old man who
lives on Grand Street
and they're trying to evict
him from his apartment.
Okay.
Our office is on
Orchard Street,
come by.
You should really
get involved, Max.
Okay.
Hey. Did you get
her number?
It's not that.
Ma?
Uh-huh.
What are you doing here?
You'll break
your eardrums.
Did you bring any pears?
I brought you pears
yesterday, Ma, remember?
From Jimmy.
Yes, call Papa.
Tell him to bring pears.
Okay. I will.
Good boy.
How was work?
Work was, uh, same
as every other day.
Why don't you call
the Abramowitz girl?
Take her out on
a date this weekend.
She always liked you.
Uh, she got married
10 years ago.
She's got three kids.
She's a pretty girl.
You should step up
to the plate.
Um.
Okay, I will.
But not tonight.
You ready for dinner?
Yeah, it's in
the microwave.
Yo, shoeman!
Come on, let's go, man.
Time is money.
What's up, man?
Come on, hook me up.
Yeah, sure.
How you doing today,
my G? Working hard?
Yes.
Yeah? Good. Good.
Can't knock the hustle.
Work hard, play harder,
right player?
God bless Americola.
You like that watch, huh?
Sure.
Shit, I got a collection
at home worth
three times this shop.
You can always tell
a man by his watch,
right, shoeman?
Four bucks.
Four bucks?
That's the rate.
Fair enough.
Oh, almost forgot.
I need these
fixed, shoeman.
Okay.
What do you want done?
New soles,
and I need 'em tonight.
We close at 6:00.
You close when
I get my shoes.
I'm just playing
with you, shoeman.
See you at 6:00.
Right.
You sure you
can't come today?
Okay. Well, I'll see you
tomorrow. Thank you.
Max?
Yeah!
What are you
doing down here?
Using this old stitcher.
Mine... Mine busted.
Whoa. Look at this thing.
Yeah, it's something, huh?
My pop taught me how
to use this when I was little.
And it still works?
I'm surprised, but
it's doing the trick.
Yeah.
Shows you what I know.
I was always telling your
pop he should sell this crap
and make some money,
but he could never
throw anything away.
Yeah, except his family.
He didn't throw
you away, Max.
Hmm.
Uh, my post is up
on the chair.
Oh. All right, I'll...
I'll leave you the news.
Hey, I'm going around
the corner for a beer,
you wanna come?
Nah, I gotta wait
for a customer.
Ah, good for you.
Keep 'em
coming back.
Yes.
Listen.
I picked up an extra jar
from the Pickle Guys.
Hey, thank you.
Okay, good night, kid.
Good night, Jimmy.
What the hell was that?
Oh, boy.
Wow.
What the hell?
It's the stitcher.
Oh, my God.
He's dead! He's dead!
He's dead!
Whoa!
I'm a woman.
Ooh. No, I'm not.
No, I'm not.
Ten and a half?
Yeah.
Nice.
Yep, that's them. Great.
All right.
Sorry about losing
the ticket, pal.
Don't worry, everybody does.
I put taps on
the front and back.
Beautiful.
How much?
That's 12 bucks.
You got it.
You look familiar.
You an actor
or something?
Uh, no. TV reporter.
Yeah. That's right. Uh,
from New York One.
Yeah.
The guy with
the two first names.
Yeah.
Danny Donald.
Danny Donald. Wow.
My mother watches
you all the time.
Yeah? That's great.
You look like you,
but you're a little
different.
You like that?
You like being on TV?
It's great.
I love going to work.
I'm a lucky guy.
Yeah.
Here, it's my card.
Oh, yes.
Tell your mother I said,
"Thanks for watching."
Oh, yeah.
Thanks again.
Yeah, I will.
Hello.
Can I help you?
Uh, what time
do you close?
6:00. It's on the door.
Okay.
You want a haircut?
No. I have to go now.
Okay.
So go.
Good-bye, Jimmy.
It freaking works.
I can't believe it.
He had no idea who I was.
I could be anybody I want.
This is great.
I'm gonna hang out
in the Chinatown.
I have an accent.
Nice!
Ten and a half.
Got some big
feet there, kid.
I'm big boned.
Thank you.
Welcome, sir.
Where's the bathroom?
Ah, yes. To your left
and down the stairs.
Park it.
Okay. Thank you.
Excuse me.
Yeah?
What size are
your shoes?
Ten and a half. Why?
Gimme them.
What?
Give me your shoes.
Are you serious?
Yes, I'm real serious.
I don't believe
this shit.
Wow!
Whoo!
Bye-bye.
Mmm.
Oh.
What is this?
Yeah, those
are for you.
Oh, so pretty.
I knew you'd like them.
How was your day, Maxie?
It was good.
It was really good.
It was the best day
I've had in a long time.
Good.
You work so hard.
How was your day, Ma?
Uh, better, now that
my  tateleh is home.
Yeah.
Hey, Ma, let me
ask you something.
You ever wish you
were somebody else?
No.
I'm your mother.
That's all I ever
wanted to be.
But if you could do
whatever you wanted to do
what would it be?
Um.
Have dinner with your father.
That would be nice.
That would be
really nice.
Hi.
How are you?
Good. How are you?
Very good.
Good. Emiliano wanted
me to drop these off.
What does he want done?
Whatever they need.
Well, it's a 10 and a half.
I could clean
'em up for you.
Okay.
Mmm, looks like
they need new soles.
Sounds good.
Here you are.
Thank you.
Okay, thank you.
Hey, man.
What can I get you?
I'll have a light beer.
No light beer.
Here is the beer list.
And here is our
cocktail list.
Why don't you
check that out?
What's a pickletini?
Uh, it's vodka
and pickle juice.
Want one?
Sure. Okay.
You'll love it.
Enjoy, buddy.
Hi.
I know who
you are.
You do?
Yeah.
I saw you spin at the
Jane on New Year's.
You saw me spin?
Isn't that what
you call it?
Anyway, I tried
to pick you up.
Oh, yeah?
Did it work?
No. You went home
with that model.
You were all
over each other.
Oh, yeah,
that's my girlfriend.
It wasn't
your girlfriend.
Yeah, we live together.
No, it definitely
wasn't your girlfriend.
Well, how do
you know that?
'Cause it was a guy.
What... A guy?
Are you kidding me?
It's okay.
I don't care.
I think it's hot.
You... You do?
Mmm-hmm.
Oh.
Hi.
So, where are we going?
Uh, I don't know.
Where do you live?
Can't do that, love.
Boyfriend, sorry.
Oh. Oh. Uh, okay,
well, we could go to my place.
Just got to make a call.
Who are you calling?
Uh, my mother.
You... You live
with your mother?
Yeah. And she gets a
little screwy at night,
so I don't wanna
surprise her.
Really?
Where do you live?
Sheepshead Bay.
Get home safe.
My name is Bond,
James Bond.
And I live in
Sheepshead Bay
with my mother.
Oh, hey.
How's it goin', mate?
All right.
Beautiful night for it.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah?
I forgot my keys.
You're a dork.
I'm about to take a shower.
You there?
Yeah.
Come here.
You want me to come in?
Yeah, come here.
Oh, you gotta be kidding me.
What the hell
are you wearing?
You're beautiful.
Are you high?
No, but I wish I was.
Get over here.
Oh sure, okay.
Thank you.
Look, I'm sorry
I screamed at you before.
It's just...
I get scared and I need
to know you want me here.
Oh, I... I do.
I definitely do.
Get in here, cute boy.
Me with...
Really, in there?
With you?
Yeah, really.
Your friends can wait.
Oh, yeah. Yep. Yeah.
Definitely,
they can wait.
My friends can wait.
What?
I can't do this.
I gotta go.
Are you serious?
Yeah, I am.
I'm really sorry.
Why are you acting
like such a spaz?
I'm not, I just...
Is this thing locked?
What's the matter
with you?
I've got it, right.
What are you doing?
I gotta go.
I'm really sorry.
Bye.
Emiliano?
Emiliano, come back.
Emiliano!
We are here in the
Lower East Side
for the Grand Street
housing protest.
And we're here with
Mr. Solomon...
Ma?
...you refused to go.
Can I ask why?
Hey.
- I stay here until I die.
- It's Danny Donald.
You're not gonna be
pushed around, I see.
Never.
He came by the shop
the other day,
I meant to tell you.
How's work?
Work?
Work, uh...
Work was something.
And it's Carmen.
...and I too have lived
here all of my life...
She was in the shop, too.
...to stay here and
raise my family here
and not be kicked out.
If people wanna
come out and support
your cause...
Please come by and
get involved, we would
love to have you.
All right. Thank you,
thank you. Good luck!
Danny Donald from
the Lower East Side,
for New York One.
I like him.
Yeah me, too.
Who's Carmen?
Max!
Hey.
Hi, how's it going?
Good. You left
your door open.
Oh, pfft!
Can you shut that
for me, please?
Sure.
Thanks.
I'm delivering
groceries to one of
our elderly neighbors.
All by yourself?
Yeah, Max,
I'm a badass.
Yeah, okay.
So, you like pickles, huh?
Yeah. Do you?
No, not really.
But I'm glad that
you're supporting
a local business.
That's cool.
Oh, we need more names
for our petition.
Do you think you could
get your dad to sign?
No.
Max, this is important.
I know. My, uh,
father took off
a while ago.
He ain't around anymore.
I'm sorry.
It happens.
Yeah, it does.
My dad split
when I was 12.
Life goes on.
Yeah, right.
Yeah, I gotta
deliver these.
I'll see you soon, Max.
Okay.
Come by the office,
get involved.
Yeah. Okay.
Hey, Pop.
There you are.
Ma?
Wow!
You look beautiful.
Come on, it's time.
Okay, my love.
Abraham?
Hello, Sarah.
Of course I'm home.
We have a date.
I missed you so much.
I'm here now.
But where did you go?
I went for pears.
Remember?
Yes, of course.
I'm so glad you're home.
Me too.
Good-bye, Pop.
Good-bye, son.
Ma, you overslept?
Is that what happens
when you have a big date?
Ma?
Ma.
Oh, Ma.
Oh, no.
Max. Max.
You should start saving
for a nice headstone.
She deserves a
nice headstone,
your mother.
They're not cheap, Max.
Yeah.
Good of you to come.
How you doin', kid?
You're gonna
freeze out here.
I'm all right.
Hey, this was...
This was really nice.
What you did.
She'd have liked it.
You were a good
son to her, Max.
Look, Max,
if your dad was
here right now...
But he's not here.
I was all she had and
I wasn't good enough.
Of course you were.
You don't know
the half of it, Jimmy.
I can't even afford
a decent headstone.
I can help out, kid,
you know that.
Why?
What have I ever
done for you?
done for anybody?
Look, you're hurting
right now, but don't
beat yourself up. Okay?
I better go back
inside, Jimmy.
Thanks for coming.
Max?
I promise
it's gonna get better.
Just give it time.
Don't do anything
you'll regret.
It's a little
late for that.
Yo, shoeman?
Shoeman?
Yes.
Yo, where you been, man?
I've been back and forth
to the shop all week
waiting on your punk ass.
I'm sorry.
I was sitting  shivah .
Where they do that at?
It's a Jewish ritual for
when somebody dies.
You Jewish?
Yeah.
Lucky you.
So who croaked, man?
What?
Who died? Or you just
making some shit up?
My mother.
Oh, man.
Sorry to hear that.
She leave you
any money, man?
No, right? Figures.
Ain't that just
like a woman?
Do you have your ticket?
Do I look like
I got my ticket, man?
Just go back there
and get my shoes
before I kick some skin
off your forehead.
You know how much
them gators cost?
No, I don't.
But you need
your ticket.
New rules, shoeman.
You find my shoes
by tomorrow
or you gonna be reunited
with your moms real quick,
you got that?
I got it.
Hey, Mommy,
you want another baby daddy?
Jerk.
You got two days to pay
or I'll kill you.
So long.
Yo, fatty had a party,
what you lookin' at, man?
I ain't no box
of Twinkies, yo.
Take the stairs.
Hello?
Jesus!
What are you doing here?
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
I thought you left.
What?
Why are you back?
Oh, um,
I forgot something.
Oh, yeah,
what'd you forgot?
You forgot to
hit me again?
No.
Yeah, well I'm taking
my shit and I'm leaving.
Okay.
Do you know where my
watches are by any chance?
I didn't touch your
stupid watches.
I was just asking
where they were.
I have no idea,
but if I did
I'd take them and
I'd sell them shits.
You took my money,
Leon, and you know it.
I worked my ass off
and you just took it!
Let me get
that for you.
Don't touch my stuff!
I was just trying to help.
Leon, one day you're
gonna get yours.
You're gonna get yours.
Go to hell.
Man, this guy is a jerk.
Come on.
Where?
Where, where?
What the crap?
Oh, my God.
What is that?
Ahhh!
What the...
Hey.
Ahhh!
I don't know who you are,
but you're dead.
Hi.
It's no use. I tied
you down pretty good.
Just tell me where you hide
your watches and I'll split.
You finished?
Look, I don't wanna hurt you.
I'm not a bad person.
I just gotta take
care of some things
and do right by my mother.
Okay?
I don't know who put
you up to this, fat boy,
but I'm gonna cut a slab
of bacon off your back.
That's rude.
And I'm not fat,
I'm big-boned.
Oh, well, suit yourself.
But you'll be sorry.
I heard somebody's
not cooperating.
You done?
I'm gonna make this easy.
The watches?
You gotta know
you can't hide looking
the way you do.
I'll take my chances.
The watches.
There's a fake wall behind
the bathroom mirror.
So here's
how we're gonna do this.
I'm gonna take your
watches, tase you,
and you're gonna
wake up in your bed
like it's a bad dream.
Wow.
That was a
great hiding spot.
Okay, you ready?
Be careful with that, man,
that's not a regular Taser.
That's weapons-grade shit!
I'm sorry, man.
I have to do this,
it's the only way.
Yo, boss!
Yo!
Oh, crap.
You scream
and I will tase you
and throw you out
the back window.
You got that?
Now, who is that?
That's my boys.
We've got business.
And when they see you,
they're gonna just about
break you in half.
What kind of business?
Gotta pick up
my money, bitch.
How much money?
What the hell
is it to you?
Fifty large.
$50,000?
Hey, boss.
Hey.
New coat?
Yeah.
Let's go.
Gotta make a
quick stop, boss.
Got a little
surprise for you.
I just wanna
pick up my money.
It's on the way.
You're gonna like this.
Hey, boss,
remember our
old friend Patrick?
Patrick the Ratprick.
I didn't know
it was you, Leon.
I'm sorry.
I didn't know.
We found Ratprick
down in Philly.
Bitch tried to run.
No more.
No more, please. Please.
No more? Okay.
Okay.
Bye-bye, Ratprick.
No, don't! Hold on!
Stop, stop, stop!
Okay, boss,
what do you want to do?
I don't know.
I gotta think about this.
Is there a bathroom
around here?
What?
I gotta pee.
Oh man, oh man, oh man.
Oh man, oh man.
You should not be here.
You can do this.
You sorry for what
you did, Ratprick?
Yeah.
And you're never
gonna do it again?
No.
Okay, I believe you.
You believe me?
He believes me.
Let him go.
Let him go?
That's it?
Yeah, that's it.
Maybe take him
to the hospital,
he's in bad shape.
Boss, he stole from us.
I know!
The guy apologized.
Just do what I said.
I'm the boss, right?
Thank you!
Thanks a lot!
Leon, follow me.
You stay here.
Good evening,
Mr. Ludlow.
I am making duck ragu.
First time,
very tricky business.
Do you like duck, Leon?
I don't know.
Yeah, me neither.
I'm a Jew from Queens.
What do I know from duck?
Are you okay, Leon?
Yeah. I'm fine.
Good. I am ready to
move forward on the
Grand Street deal.
I will need the trash
taken out before Friday.
You get the rest
when the job is done.
Okay.
There is no margin
for error on this one.
None. None. You got it?
Yeah, I got it.
Maybe you'll stop by
for some duck ragu
when you're through.
Holy crap.
Okay, Ludlow, it's time.
Welcome home, Mommy.
Turn around.
So where are your
friends at, huh?
What?
The fat kid,
the guy that
looks like me.
No, it's just me.
Damn, you ugly.
And what have we here, hmm?
Thought you were gonna
steal my watches, huh?
Don't shoot me, please.
Oh, don't worry.
I ain't gonna
shoot you, she-man.
I am gonna
choke you to death.
Shoeman!
Hey.
No.
Oh, my God.
What the crap?
Thank you.
Hey.
Yeah, what do you need?
I'd like to
report a crime.
What kind of crime?
Murder.
I killed a man,
but by accident.
Why don't you
have a seat?
You unlawfully
entered the alleged
victim's house?
Yes. His girlfriend
let me in.
His ex-girlfriend.
They broke up.
I think he was hitting her.
So, why did she let you in?
Because I looked
just like him.
But you don't
look like him now.
No, not at all.
He is black.
And you said that you
killed him with a...
Stiletto heel.
Yes, that's right.
Six-inch platform,
molded plastic, but with
metal tube reinforcement.
Not great quality,
but it did the trick,
unfortunately.
Right.
The body is just
right in the living room.
You might wanna
stay out here. It's...
It's pretty ugly
in there.
What the hell?
The body was right here.
There was blood everywhere.
He was dead. I swear.
Where are my shoes?
There was a blue bag here
with my shoes in it
and $50,000 cash
and a gun
and my Taser.
Where's my Taser?
It's all gone.
In fact, there was
a whole cache of guns.
What the hell?
Something
screwy's going on.
We need to get some
leads or something.
Yeah.
I'm telling you,
he was dead. I...
I killed him.
Guys, I mean, should
we question the super?
Maybe he knows.
Sir, let go
of the door.
Like...
I'm telling you the truth!
You gotta be kidding me.
What the crap is going on?
Gotta stop this.
Max.
Hey, Jimmy.
You leaving?
You just got here.
Yeah. I gotta go
take care of somethin'.
It's peak hours.
What's so important?
Don't worry about it.
What are you doing?
I'm worried, okay.
What's going on?
One second. What?
You've been running
around half-cocked since
your mother passed away.
Will you just be
straight with me?
All right, look,
I took some money that
doesn't belong to me,
and I gotta go give it
back. All right?
No.
Hey, hey, hey, hey!
Whoa, whoa!
Damn it, Jimmy.
Why did you do that?
'Cause I'm trying
to stop you from
screwing up your life.
Your shop's closed
half the time.
You're acting all crazy.
I'm not blind, Max.
I know where this is going.
I've seen it before.
You have not seen
this before. Trust me.
Oh, yes, I have.
You know with who?
Your father.
My father?
Yeah.
He was acting
just like you are
before he took off.
What are you saying?
Listen, your old man,
he got into some trouble
with some bad people
and he had to disappear.
He had to make them think
that he was dead and
never coming back,
or else they were
gonna hurt you,
hurt your mother.
You knew this
all this time
and you didn't tell me.
How come you
didn't tell me?
He made me promise not to.
He what?
He said that I was the
only one he could trust.
What the hell
are you doing, kid?
New rules, Jimmy!
You stay out
of my business.
You hear me?
Max, I just don't want you
to make the same mistakes
your old man did.
Maxie!
Max!
Mrs. Greenawalt,
I got someone out here
who wants to see you.
Who is it?
You got to see
for yourself.
Hello, Greenawalt.
Hello.
Ludlow sent me
to give you this.
And, um, what is it?
Your money.
He can't take out the trash.
He can't?
No, he can't.
He's sorry.
Okay.
And your name is?
I'm Marsha.
And where is Leon,
Marsha?
I don't know.
I don't believe you.
You see, um,
Leon left me,
well, and you
in a very difficult
situation here.
If we don't get this
little matter cleaned up,
I stand to lose an
enormous amount of money
and I don't like
losing money.
You don't have enough?
No. I don't.
Thank you for bringing
back my money.
Brian will give your
receipt now. Brian.
You hungry?
No.
You mind if we
stop to get some food?
Yeah, I mind, Brian.
We're kind of busy right now.
I'm starving, Jeffrey.
Well,
you should've thought
of that before we left.
I wasn't hungry then.
We'll get something
to eat after we get
rid of our friend.
We need to talk about
Grand Street anyway.
We torching the place?
Yeah, tomorrow night.
You smell something?
I thought that was you.
No, it's not me, Jeffrey.
Maybe princess
pissed herself.
Hey, mister, you okay?
Huh?
Don't eat me!
Please don't eat me!
All right. All right.
I'm not! I'm not
gonna eat you!
Kid!
Ah!
Kid, wake up!
I'm not gonna eat you!
Kid!
Hey, there he is.
You finished?
Yep, just in time.
Are you feeling better?
Yeah.
I'm sorry about
the way I acted.
Oh, don't worry
about it, Max.
I should have told you
about your father sooner.
I'm sorry.
You're a good friend,
Jimmy.
To him and to me.
How about a pickle?
Yeah, thanks.
Why don't you let me
give you shave?
I think I'll stick
with the pickle.
Oh, crap.
Mr. Solomon is a
wonderful old man who
lives on Grand Street
and they're trying to evict
him from his apartment.
I will need the
trash taken out before Friday.
We torching the place?
Yeah, tomorrow night.
I stay here until I die.
Max?
Hey, I think I'm ready
to get involved.
And how did you
hear all of this?
I heard it. I...
Look, I have a
special ability
to see and hear
stuff I shouldn't.
Max, I really need to
get back to the office.
I know it sounds crazy,
but I'm not crazy.
You gotta believe me.
Max, I'm gonna ask
you this one time
and I want you to
tell me the truth.
Are you making
this all up just
to get with me?
What? No. I swear.
I do think you
are very pretty,
but I'm telling
you the truth.
Okay, so who are
these people?
Do you know any names?
The woman's name
is Greenawalt.
Elaine Greenawalt?
Yeah, that's it.
You know her?
Yeah.
Her company owns
Mr. Solomon's building.
She's got a pretty
nice place upstate too.
You went
to her house?
This is the building.
Once he's gone,
they can sell
the whole block.
It's worth a fortune.
Wow. You really
think you can stop them?
Of course, I do.
I told you, Max,
I'm a badass.
Oh yeah,
that's right.
Come on,
he lives on
the third floor.
He's the last one left.
See? Everyone's gone.
Hello, Carmen.
Hi, Mr. Solomon.
This is my friend, Max.
And we need to talk
to you about something.
Oh, come.
How are you?
And these men,
they said they
want to kill me?
They said
they would burn
your building down
with you in it.
So, yeah.
You believe him?
Yeah, I do.
Thank you very much
for telling me this,
but I can't leave.
Are you kidding me?
These are bad people,
Mr. Solomon.
They are not
messing around.
Max, my wife
and I lived in this
apartment 45 years.
I raised my daughter
here, Sonia.
I cannot run away.
Mr. Solomon, where does
your daughter live now?
Chicago.
Can I ask you a
personal question?
Hmm.
What size are your shoes?
Mr. Solomon.
I am Elaine Greenawalt.
It's nice to
finally meet you.
I want to make a deal.
I'm ready to leave.
How much?
$100,000 cash
and a bus ticket
to Chicago.
How soon can you be ready?
Tomorrow.
Okay.
Brian here will escort
you to Chicago.
No. I don't need escort.
I wanna see that
you get there safely.
Do we have a deal,
Mr. Solomon?
A deal.
Good.
Ah.
Come in, but
take off shoes.
You're wearing yours.
It's my house.
Oh, come on,
quit stalling,
old man.
Then you don't
come inside.
Take off.
Just do it.
Let's get this
over with.
It's all there, pal.
Hundred grand.
This is all
you're bringing?
What about the rest
of this crap?
I leave it
all behind.
Start new life.
Where the hell
are our shoes?
Oh, bad crime.
That's why
I'm leaving.
You think you're
funny, asshole?
Forget the shoes, Brian.
What do you mean
"Forget the shoes"?
It's freezing out, Jeffrey.
We'll pick up some new ones.
Mrs. Greenawalt.
Yeah, is he gone?
They're on the bus.
Good.
Now get over to Solomon's.
I want you to sweep
the entire building
and wait outside until
morning. Clear?
Yes, ma'am.
What the...
Ludlow?
I don't believe this asshole.
Brian?
What the hell are
you doing here?
Behind you!
I love this thing.
Hello.
Any problems?
No.
Good, I'm 10 minutes away.
I'm meeting Mr. Tan
in front of the building.
Okay.
I'm parked right out front.
I'll wait here.
Good idea.
Idiot.
Thanks for the
phone, handsome.
Where the hell
is this idiot?
Call Jeffrey.
What are you doing?
That's private property.
I'm visiting a friend.
Who?
Leonard Solomon.
He doesn't live here
anymore. He moved.
Really? Somebody
should tell him that.
Oh, and by the way.
Oh, no.
Sir, can you step
over here, please?
Wait, wait, wait, wait,
wait. I didn't do...
Hey, Solomon!
Solomon, stop! Solomon!
No.
Hello.
You are on the bus
to Chicago,
I just talked to Brian.
He lied.
That's impossible.
No, not really.
I just gave him
some of the money
that you gave to me.
What kind of game
are you trying to play
here, Mr. Solomon?
You and I had a deal.
No game.
This is my home.
I'm not leaving.
Okay.
Let me tell you how
this is gonna work.
If you don't get up
and walk out of here
right now,
I am going to burn
this whole place to the
ground with you in it.
And then I'm gonna
send someone to Chicago
to find your daughter,
and throw her off
the Sears Tower tonight.
Is that clear?
Yes.
That's very clear.
And that is good
for the television.
For the television?
Mmm-hmm.
What are you talking about,
you senile old man?
New York One.
Hello, Mrs. Greenawalt.
Danny Donald
for New York One.
You're who?
Yeah, that's Danny Donald.
Care to tell me
what you're doing here?
What am I doing here?
I just heard you
threaten to kill
Mr. Solomon
and then threaten
to kill his daughter
in Chicago.
I'm not in Chicago!
I did not say that!
No? Oh, because we
have it all on tape.
I could play it back
for you right now.
You know what,
I did not give consent
to being filmed for
television right now.
You set this up
and I will make you pay.
Maybe they've got
duck ragu in prison.
You son of a bitch!
Get away!
Hi.
I came to get
Emiliano's shoes.
Oh, yeah.
New soles.
Perfect.
He's gonna be happy.
He wanted to wear
them tonight.
Oh yeah? Going out
on a big date?
No. It's boys' night.
Huh. No charge.
Really? That's really
sweet. Thank you.
Thank you.
Hi, Max.
Hi, Carmen.
My favorite boots.
I busted the zipper
and I thought
they were goners
and then I remembered that
I know a badass cobbler.
Ah, well, these
are good shoes.
I could do something
with these.
Yeah, work your magic.
So, I talked to
Mr. Solomon this morning.
Oh, yeah?
How's he doing?
He said he's having
a wonderful time
and that when
he comes home, he wants
to thank you in person.
Oh, okay.
How did you pull it off, Max?
Pull what off?
Solomon, Greenawalt,
all of it.
Here's your ticket.
Thanks.
Don't lose it.
So, do you have plans
next Friday night?
No. Why?
You having
another rally?
No.
I would like to have
dinner with you.
Would you like to have
dinner with me, Max?
Yeah. Sure, yeah.
Got a pen?
Here's my number.
Don't lose it.
I won't.
Good.
Bye, Max.
Bye, Carmen.
Shit!
Whoa, whoa. Hold it.
I'm not here to hurt you.
Bullshit.
Leave me alone.
I'm not staying.
I just want to
give you these.
Take a look.
You're giving me
your watches?
Sell them,
they're worth a lot.
Why are you doing this?
I'm sorry for what I did.
You deserve better,
much better.
Hey, man,
you got a light?
No.
I do. Let's go.
Hello, Leon.
Remember me?
Ratprick?
My name is Patrick,
you piece of shit. Patrick.
Time for some payback.
Okay, hold up.
Just let me take my shoe off.
Don't worry about your shoes.
You're not gonna need them.
But I let you go.
Well, we all make mistakes.
You look like crap,
by the way. Let's go.
You smell like
crap, too.
You been rolling around
the garbage, Leon, hmm?
Well, you should've
stayed...
Hey, look out!
Where am I?
You're in my shop.
How did I get here?
Here, drink.
You took quite a knock.
What happened, Jimmy?
You were in a car accident.
I found you,
pulled you out.
Have a pickle.
No, I'm good.
Just take one.
I don't want a pickle.
I don't care if you
want one, you need it.
Just take one.
What're you talking
about, I need it?
Pickles preserve you
when you change, Max,
they give you strength.
Otherwise you get all
screwed up jumping
from body to body.
You know?
Of course I know.
Who do you think
got rid of that putz,
Ludlow?
That stiletto heel
made quite a mess, kid.
That was you. How?
You see the thing is,
I'm not just a barber, Max.
I'm also a cobbler.
And...
I'm your father.
Pop?
That's right, Max.
But you're...
No, I'm right here.
Oh!
You were right next door
to me the whole time
and you didn't tell me?
I wanted to tell you.
Yeah, you should have.
I was all alone. And Ma?
Ma never knew.
She thought you were
dead or something.
I felt like I was dead.
All that time on the
outside, looking in.
Because you left us!
No, because I didn't
have a choice, Max.
You had a choice.
Will you try to understand?
No! I don't understand.
I don't understand!
I don't understand
any of this!
Maxie, I wanted to
tell you so many times,
but it was too dangerous.
If it was so dangerous, why
are you telling me now, huh?
Because it's time.
It's time you knew the truth.
You're ready.
I'm ready?
That's right, son.
For what?
What are you
talking about?
Come to the
basement, Max.
You need to see something.
See what?
Your birthright.
You gotta be kidding me.
As my father's
shoes worked for me,
mine will work for you.
Who are all these people?
Customers.
They help us to help others.
They're all labeled.
Derek Jeter?
That one was for me.
Pop, you made
all these shoes?
These shoes go all the
way back to your great
grandfather, Pinchas.
He passed them on to
my father, Herschel,
just as I am passing
it onto you.
It's a privilege to walk
in another man's shoes, Max,
but it's also
a responsibility.
I think you've learned
that by now.
You're a guardian
of souls, Max.
You are the cobbler.
This is your thing.
I missed you, Max.
I really missed you.
Pop...
I'm so...
Listen to me, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry about Ma.
I didn't mean to.
Oh.
I didn't know.
I'm the one who left.
I made the mistakes.
And you...
You did right by her.
By me...
You did right.
It's been a long day.
What do you say
we close up shop
and go home?
Yeah, let's go home.
Son, I can't go
out the front.
Not like this.
Let's go out the back.
What back?
This back.
Wow! I don't believe it.
Believe it.
Beats the subway.
Pop, this is yours?
It's ours.
Webb, this is
my son, Max.
Nice to meet
you, Max.
Hi, Webb.
Webb, we are heading
home to Brooklyn.
Very good, sir.
Did Jimmy
have this place?
No, no, no, no.
I put this in after
I bought Jimmy out.
Where is he?
The Caribbean.
He sends his regards.
You know, barbers
have always been very
trusted friends to us.
We never have to
worry about 'em.
Who do we have
to worry about?
Dry cleaners.
Dry cleaners?
Really?
They're not nice fellas
and they're very powerful.
Wow.
Uh...
So, Pop, you mean
we're not the only ones?
No, no, no.
There's plenty of
tradesmen like us out there.
Some good, some bad,
and it's been that
way for centuries.
Tomorrow, we'll sit down
with the stitcher.
I'll show you everything.
Oh, man,
that thing is great, Pop.
Where did we get it?
The stitcher?
Oh, that's a good
story, actually.
A long time ago,
on the coldest
of winter nights,
a vagrant came knocking
at the door of our shop.
Your great-great grandfather
gave him shelter
when no one else would.
He fed the man,
mended his shoes...
In the morning,
the vagrant...
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today