Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
It's gettin' cold.
That is one fine frame.
One fine frame that is.
How much...
does a fine frame like that cost,
do you think?
I never told you, but you sound a little
like Dr Seuss when you're drunk.
Anna. I'm serious.
Serious I am, Anna.
I'd say it cost at least a couple hundred.
- I'm gonna read it for you.
- Do I really sound like Dr Seuss?
"In recognition of his
outstanding achievement...
in the field of child psychology,
his dedication to his work...
and his continuing efforts
to improve the quality of life..."
Will you concentrate?
"...his continuing efforts to
improve the quality of life...
for countless children
and their families...
the city of Philadelphia
proudly bestows upon its son...
Dr Malcolm Crowe..." that's you...
"...the Mayor's Citation
for professional excellence."
They called you their son.
Wow.
We should hang it in the bathroom.
This is an important night for us.
Finally, someone is recognizing
the sacrifices you've made...
that you have put everything second,
including me...
for those families that
they're talking about.
They're also saying that
my husband has a gift.
You have a gift that teaches children
how to be strong in situations...
where most adults
would piss on themselves.
I believe what they wrote is real.
Thank you.
I would like some wine in a glass.
I would not like it in a mug.
I would not like it in a jug.
Look.
Anna, don't move. Don't make a sound.
This is 47 Locus Street.
You've broken a window
and entered a private residence.
You don't know so many things.
There are no needles or prescription
drugs of any kind in this house.
Do you know why you're afraid
when you're alone?
- I do. I do.
- What do you want?
What he promised me!
I want what he promised.
- Oh, my God.
- Do I know you?
Don't you know me, hero?
Don't you even remember your own patients?
Downtown clinic.
Single-parent family.
Possible mood disorder.
I was afraid!
You told me I was having trouble
coping with my parents' divorce.
You were wrong. You were wrong.
Now look at me!
- I don't want to be afraid no more.
- Please, just give me a minute to think.
I waited ten years for you!
- I'm not giving you nothin'!
- Ben Friedkin?
Some people, they call me "freak."
Ryan Sumner?
I am. I am a freak. Look at...
Vincent.
Vincent Grey.
- No, you don't.
- I do remember you.
Quiet, very smart.
Compassionate.
Unusually compassionate.
You forgot cursed.
You failed me.
You failed me!
Vincent, I'm sorry if I wasn't...
if I didn't help you.
But if you just let me try...
If you just give me a chance...
Oh, God! Oh, God, honey.
- Did Vincent...
- Don't talk.
It's okay, Cole.
My name is Dr Malcolm Crowe.
We were supposed to meet today,
but I missed our appointment.
I'm sorry.
You know, in the olden days in Europe,
people used to hide out in churches.
They would claim sanctuary.
What were they hiding from?
Bad people, mostly.
People that wanted to
put them in jail, hurt them.
I noticed your eyeglasses.
They don't have any lenses in them.
They're my dad's. The lenses hurt my eyes.
What were you talking about with
your soldiers when I came in? Day...
It's called Latin.
All your soldiers speak Latin?
No. Just one.
Are you a good doctor?
Well...
I used to be.
I won an award once from the mayor.
It had an expensive frame.
- I'm gonna see you again, right?
- If that's okay with you.
It's me.
Pennsylvania Turnpike westbound
slows at Valley Forge 24.
On the Blue Ridge, both directions generally
slow between number three and number two...
Hey, good morning.
Cole.
Cole!
Hey, your Cocoa Puffs are gettin' soggy.
Let me see you. Oh, honey, you got a spot.
Head up.
Okay, here we go.
Something you were looking for, baby?
Pop-Tarts?
They're right here.
Oh.
Well, what are you thinking, Mama?
Lots of things.
Anything bad about me?
Hey, look at my face.
I was not thinkin'
somethin' bad about you.
Got it?
Got it.
Here, head up.
- That's Tommy, Mama.
- That's okay. You tuck it in.
Hey, Cole, you want this?
Hey, freak, how'd you like that
"arm around the shoulder" bit?
I just made that up. I went with it.
It's what great actors do.
It's called improv.
Hey, baby.
How was your day?
You know, you can tell me things
if you need to.
Well, you know what I did today?
I, uh, I won the Pennsylvania Lottery
in the morning...
I quit my jobs, and I ate
a big picnic in the park...
with lots of chocolate mousse pie.
And then I swam
in the fountain all afternoon.
What'd you do?
I was picked first for
kickball teams at recess.
I hit a grand slam to win the game.
Everybody lifted me up on their shoulders
and carried me around, cheering.
Well, in that case, I am gonna
make you some triangle pancakes.
You got an hour.
Hi.
Wanna sit?
Don't feel like talking today?
Wanna play a game?
It's a mind-reading game.
Here's how it works.
I read your mind.
If what I say is right,
you take one step towards the chair.
If what I say is wrong, you take
one step back towards the doorway.
If you reach the chair, you sit down.
If you reach the door, you can go.
Wanna play?
Okay.
When your mother and father
were first divorced...
your mom went to see a doctor like me,
and he didn't help her.
So you think I'm not going
to be able to help you.
You're worried that she said
she told him things...
things she couldn't tell anyone else.
Secrets.
You have a secret,
but you don't want to tell me.
Your dad gave you that watch
as a present just before he went away.
He forgot it in a drawer.
Doesn't work.
You keep pretty quiet in school, but...
you're a good student, you've never
really been in any serious trouble.
We were supposed to draw a picture.
Anything we wanted.
I drew a man.
He got hurt in the neck by
another man with a screwdriver.
You saw that on TV, Cole?
Everyone got upset.
They had a meeting.
Mom started crying.
I don't draw like that any more.
How do you draw now?
I draw people smiling...
dogs running...
rainbows.
They don't have meetings about rainbows.
No. I guess they don't.
What am I thinking now?
I don't know what you're thinking now.
I was thinking you're nice...
but you can't help me.
I thought you meant the other Italian
restaurant I asked you to marry me in.
I'm so sorry, Anna.
I just can't seem to keep track of time.
And I didn't have
a very good session today. I...
They're both so similar.
The same mannerisms, same expressions,
same things hanging over their head.
I think it might be some kind of abuse.
Cole has scratches on his arm.
I think they might be fingernail cuts.
Defensive cuts, maybe. I don't know.
Maybe a teacher or a neighbour.
I don't think it's the mother.
I've seen her with him, and...
it doesn't seem to fit.
Or I could just be wrong. Maybe he's
just a kid who likes to climb trees a lot.
Anna.
I know that I've been
a little distant, all right?
I know that it makes you mad.
I just feel like I've been given...
a second chance,
and I don't want it to slip away.
Anna.
Happy anniversary.
Stop looking at me. I don't like
when people look at me like that.
Okay.
I walk this way to school
with Tommy Tammisimo.
- He your best buddy?
- He hates me.
Do you hate him?
No.
Did your mom set that up?
Yes.
Did you ever talk to your mom
about how things are with Tommy?
- I don't tell her things.
- Why not?
'Cause she doesn't look at me like
everybody else, and I don't want her to.
- I don't want her to know.
- Know what?
That I'm a freak.
Hey.
You are not a freak. Okay?
Don't you believe anybody that tries to
convince you of that. That's bullshit.
You don't have to go through
your life believing that.
Okay?
Come on.
- You said the "S" word.
- Yeah, I know.
Sorry.
So your dad lives in Pittsburgh
with a lady that works in a tollbooth.
I wonder if she has to pee
when she's working.
Think she just holds it?
I don't know. I was just
thinking about that myself.
You asked a lot of questions
about Dad today.
How come?
Well, sometimes we do things
to draw attention...
to express our feelings
about certain issues...
divorce, whatever.
For example, a person might
leave something on a desk...
for someone else to find.
Do you know what free-association
writing is, Cole?
No.
Free-association writing is when you
take a pencil in your hand, and...
you put the pencil to a piece
of paper and you start writing.
And you don't look at what you're writing
or think about what you're writing.
You just keep your hand moving.
And after a while, if you keep
your hand moving long enough...
words and thoughts start coming out that
you didn't even know you had in you.
It could be something
you heard somewhere else...
or feelings you had deep inside of you.
Have you ever done any
free-association writing, Cole?
Yes.
What did you write?
Upset words.
Did you ever write any upset words
before your father left?
I don't remember.
Can you do something for me?
I want you to think about what you
wanna get out of our time together...
what our goal should be.
Something I want?
If you could change something
in your life, anything at all...
what would it be?
Instead of something I want,
can it be something I don't want?
Okay.
I don't want to be scared any more.
You gonna get that?
Are you gonna get that?
- Hi.
- Don't you see enough of me at the store?
- Yeah, I'm on my way...
out to the flea market
in the Amish country.
I thought maybe you'd wanna come along
and show me how to buy...
at one of these things.
I don't know if I can deal
with the Amish today.
I can't curse or spit
or anything around them.
I just figured maybe you'd just want
to get out and get some air...
because you've seemed kind of down lately.
Um, I'm okay.
All right. Do you think that maybe
I should stop by on my way back?
Show you what I've got?
'Cause that wouldn't be a problem.
No, I... You know, I can see it on Monday.
Sure, yeah, that's fine. I'm just...
Okay, so I guess I'm gonna get going then,
and I'll speak to you later.
- Don't step in the horse manure.
- Thank you very much.
Keep moving, cheese dick.
Can anybody guess what city was capital
of the United States of America...
from 1790 to 1800?
I'll give you a hint:
It's the city you live in.
- Philadelphia!
- Right, right.
Philadelphia is one of
the oldest cities in this country.
Lot of generations have
lived here and died here.
Almost any place you go in this city
has a history and a story behind it...
even this school
and the grounds it sits on.
Can anyone guess what this building
was used for a hundred years ago...
before you went to school here,
before I went to this school even?
Yes, Cole.
They used to hang people here.
No, uh, that... Mm-mm. That's not correct.
Where'd you hear that?
They pulled the people in,
crying and kissing their families bye.
People watching spit at them.
Uh, Cole, this... this building
was a legal courthouse.
Laws were passed here... some of
the very first laws of this country.
This whole building was full of,
uh, lawyers, lawmakers.
They were the ones that hanged everybody.
Uh... Look, I do...
I don't know which one
of these guys told you that...
but, uh, they were
just trying to scare you.
I don't like people
looking at me like that.
- Like what?
- Stop it!
I, uh, I don't know how else to look. I...
You're Stuttering Stanley!
Excuse me?
You talked funny when you went to school.
You talked funny all the way to high school.
What?
You shouldn't look at people.
It makes them feel bad.
- How did you...
- Stop looking at me!
- Who have you been speaking-ing to?
- Stuttering Stanley!
- Stuttering Stanley! Stuttering Stanley!
- Stop it.
- Stop it! Stop that!
- Stuttering Stanley! Stuttering Stanley!
- Stop it!
- Stuttering Stanley! Stuttering...
- Shut up, you freak!
Hey, big guy.
How's it goin'?
I don't wanna talk
about anything right now.
Okay.
You like magic?
Observe: The magic penny.
Looks like an ordinary penny.
But I do my little magic shake, and...
now it's in my right hand.
But that's not the end of the magic trick.
I do another little shake, and...
right there in the vest pocket.
But that's not the end of the magic trick.
I do another little shake...
and...
right back in the left hand
where it started.
- That isn't magic.
- What are you talking about?
Of course it's magic.
You just kept the penny
in that hand the whole time.
Think so?
I didn't know you were funny.
Malcolm, sit your cute
butt down and listen up.
No doubt about it. Anna is like my sister.
And you better make her happy.
And I'm not talkin' about no...
"Mmm, this taste like real butter"
kind of happy.
I'm talkin' about... Just let it go.
'Julie Andrews, mm-hmm,
twirling around like...
a mental patient on a mountaintop"
kind of happy.
Now, that's the kind of happy
I'm talkin' about.
Come here. Don't tell her I told you...
but she said she knew she love you...
from the first time
she met you on the street.
He'd do anything for you.
I love you guys.
My nose is running. Turn it...
And then you do the magic shake.
The penny has moved from my pocket...
all the way back
to the hand it started in.
That's stupid.
It's supposed to be funny.
It's stupid. I want my penny back.
- He doesn't get invited places, so...
- It's our pleasure.
Last time was a Chuck E. Cheese party
a year ago.
He hid in one of those purple
plastic tunnels and didn't come out.
- Chuck E. Who?
- Cheese. It's a kids' place.
- Excuse me.
- Sorry.
Is someone out there?
Open this door, please. Come on.
I can't breathe.
If you can hear me, open this door.
I swear on my life I didn't
take the master's horse.
Open this door,
or I'll break through it and grab you!
The star of the commercial
always gets his own trailer.
For what?
He needs a place to think
about his character, alone.
You only had one line.
Derrick, check it out.
Oh, yeah. My dad made me invite him.
Happy birthday, Derrick.
Is there somethin'
you want to see in there?
No.
We're gonna put on a pretend play.
- Wanna be in it?
- Okay.
It's called "Locked in the Dungeon."
Yeah, Cole, and, uh, you get to be
the one locked in the dungeon.
Don't! Don't! Don't! Don't!
Don't!
Let me out! No! No! No!
No! No! No!
Mom!
No, no, no!
Cole?
Cole!
Is there a key for this door? Cole?
Honey, honey, can you hear me?
- Oh, my God! Cole!
- Oh, my God! Help me! Help! Help!
The tests would indicate
he did not have a seizure.
He's doing fine.
After some rest, he can go home tonight.
There are some cuts
and bruises on your son...
- that are concerning me.
- Oh, man.
Yeah, those are from sports.
You think I hurt my child?
You think I'm a bad mother?
Mrs Sloan over there...
she's a social worker with the hospital...
and she's gonna ask you a couple
procedural questions.
What happened to my child today?
Something was happening to him, physically
happening. Something was very wrong!
Hey.
Did your father used to
tell you bedtime stories?
Once upon a time
there was this young prince...
and he decided that
he wanted to go for a drive.
And he got his driver,
and they started driving.
Driving, driving.
Driving a lot. And, uh, um...
they drove so much that he fell asleep.
And...
then he woke up, and he realized
they were still driving.
- This was a very long trip.
- Dr Crowe?
You haven't told bedtime stories before.
Uh, not too many, no.
You have to add some twists and stuff.
Okay. Some twists.
Like what kind of twists?
Give me an example.
- Maybe they run out of gas.
- They run out of gas?
That's good, 'cause they're
driving, right? Okay, so...
Tell me the story about why you're sad.
You think I'm sad?
What makes you think that?
Your eyes told me.
Not supposed to talk
about stuff like that.
Once upon a time, there was
this person named Malcolm.
He worked with children.
He loved it.
He loved it more than anything else.
And then one night,
he found out that he made a...
mistake with one of them.
He couldn't help that one.
And he can't stop thinking about it.
He, uh, can't forget.
Ever since then,
things have been different.
He's not the same person
that he used to be.
And his wife doesn't like
the person that he's become.
They barely speak any more.
They're like strangers.
And then one day, Malcolm meets
this wonderful little boy.
A really cool little boy.
He reminds him a lot of the other one.
And Malcolm decides
to try and help this new boy...
'cause he feels that
if he could help this new boy...
it'd be like helping that other one too.
How does the story end?
I don't know.
I wanna tell you my secret now.
Okay.
I see dead people.
In your dreams?
While you're awake?
Dead people, like, in graves, in coffins?
Walking around like regular people.
They don't see each other.
They only see what they wanna see.
They don't know they're dead.
How often do you see them?
All the time.
They're everywhere.
You won't tell anyone my secret, right?
No. I promise.
Will you stay here until I fall asleep?
Of course.
Cole has pathologies more severe
than initially assessed.
He's suffering from
visual hallucinations...
paranoia...
some kind of school-age schizophrenia.
Medication, hospitalization
may be required.
And I'm not helping him.
Hi. This is Lynn Sear, Cole's mom.
Yeah, uh... Yeah, I'd like
to talk to you about...
your boy and his friends keeping
their goddam hands off my son.
Mama?
No, dinner is not ready!
What are you gonna do?
You can't hurt me any more!
Neddy! You're a terrible husband! Neddy!
Look what you made me do! Neddy!
Once there was a boy,
very different from all the other boys.
He lived in the jungle...
and he could speak to the animals.
Did you think the play sucked big time?
What?
Tommy Tammisimo acted
in a cough syrup commercial.
He said everyone was self-conscious
and unrealistic.
He said the play sucked big time.
This Tommy kid sounds like a real punk.
I thought the play was excellent.
Better than Cats.
- Cats?
- Never mind.
Cole, I was really interested
in what you told me at the hospital.
I'd like to hear more about it.
Cole?
What?
Is something up there?
Cole?
I don't see anything.
Be real still.
Sometimes you feel it inside...
like you're falling down real fast...
but you're really just standing still.
You ever feel the prickly things
on the back of your neck?
Yes.
And the tiny hairs on your arm,
you know, when they stand up?
Yes.
That's them.
They get mad.
It gets cold.
I don't see anything.
Are you sure they're there?
Cole.
Please make them leave.
I'm working on it.
Come on.
Mommy, Daddy?
My throat hurts.
Run. Run!
Pedia Ease cough suppressant.
Gentle, fast, effec...
Cole.
I don't care what they say.
This thing is broken.
Take 'em off.
I don't want them on my table.
I saw what was in your bureau drawer
when I was cleaning.
Got something you want to confess?
The bumblebee pendant?
Why do you keep taking it?
It was Grandma's.
You know, what if it broke?
You know how sad I'd be.
You cry 'cause you miss Grandma so much.
That's right.
Sometimes people think they lose things...
and they really didn't lose them,
it just gets moved.
So did you move the bumblebee pendant?
Don't get mad.
So who moved it this time?
Maybe someone came in our house, took
the bumblebee pendant out of my closet...
and placed it nicely in your drawer.
- Maybe.
- God, I am so tired, Cole.
I'm tired in my body,
I'm tired in my mind...
I'm tired in my heart.
I need some help.
You know, I don't know if you notice,
but our little family isn't doin' so good.
I mean, I've been prayin'.
I must not be prayin' right.
Looks like we're just gonna
have to answer each other's prayers.
If we can't talk to each other,
we're not gonna make it.
Now, tell me, baby.
I won't get mad, honey.
Did you take the bumblebee pendant?
No.
You've had enough roast beef.
You need to leave the table.
Go!
Hey, come on. I'll show you
where my dad keeps his gun. Come on.
Sebastian, come on.
Mama?
If you're not very mad...
could I sleep in your bed tonight?
Look at my face.
I'm not very mad.
Baby, why are you shaking?
Cole, what's wrong?
Oh, God! Please tell me!
Oh, please.
Oh.
It's Edwardian, beautifully worked...
with mine-cut diamonds
and an actual colour Burmese sapphire.
- It's timeless.
- Oh.
Have you, uh, got anything
a little plainer?
"Plainer"? You want a plain ring to go
with your plain fiancée, is that how it is?
No, baby, don't... don't get in a tizzy.
Uh, you're so beautiful.
Uh, you're like a Burmese sapphire
all by yourself.
- You don't need all that.
- Uh-huh.
Why don't you try it on
and see how you both feel about it.
There. How does that feel?
I think this piece, um,
communicates a longing.
I imagine that the woman who owned it
loved a man that she couldn't be with.
Did he have wavy hair and chestnut eyes?
Um, I don't know, but...
a lot of the pieces
in this store communicate...
and I think you should choose
a piece that speaks to you.
I think maybe when people own things
and then they pass away...
a part of themselves
gets printed on those things...
like... like fingerprints.
I'll just wrap it up.
You don't need a guy with a Master's.
You need a wrestler with a neck
larger than his head.
No, I need a wrestler with a Master's.
- What's this?
- Happy birthday.
- From you?
- Mm-hmm.
It's a first edition.
Wow.
- You know, this is too much.
- No.
Took it out of your Christmas bonus.
It's perfect, Anna.
Thanks.
What do you want more than anything?
I don't know.
I told you what I want.
I know what I want.
I want to be able
to talk to my wife again.
The way we used to talk to each other.
Like there was no one else
in the world except us.
How are you gonna do that?
Can't be your doctor any more.
I haven't paid
enough attention to my family.
Bad things happen when you do that.
Do you understand?
I'm gonna transfer you.
I know two psychologists...
Don't fail me.
Don't give up. You're the only one
who can help me. I know it.
I can't help you.
You...
Someone else can help you.
You believe me, right?
Dr Crowe, you believe my secret, right?
I don't know how to answer that, Cole.
How can you help me...
if you don't believe me?
Some magic's real.
Do you know why you're afraid
when you're alone?
I do. I do.
I'm sorry about that, Vincent. I hope
I didn't leave you alone too long.
Whew. It's cold in here.
Vincent, why are you crying?
You won't believe.
I'm sorry about that, Vincent. I hope
I didn't leave you alone too long.
Whew. It's cold in here.
Vincent...
No, you know what?
I never liked 'em either.
When I was a kid, I had
this blood test done...
and I threw up chili cheese fries
all over this male nurse.
Excuse me. Dr Reed is on line two.
Vincent, will you excuse me?
I have to take this.
- Um, just give me a minute, okay?
- Okay.
Oh, my God.
You been running around?
Make you feel better?
I like to run around. It's good exercise.
Do you want to ask me questions now?
Wanna be a lance corporal in Company M,
Third Battalion, Seventh Marines?
We're being dispatched
into the Quang Nam province.
Maybe later.
Something happened, didn't it?
You wiggin' out?
Yes, I think I am.
You know what "Yo no quiero morir" means?
It's Spanish. It means
"I don't want to die."
What do you think these ghosts want
when they talk to you?
I want you to think about it, Cole.
I want you to think about it
really carefully.
What do you think they want?
- Just help.
- That's right.
That's what I think too.
They just want help, even the scary ones.
And I think I might know
a way to make them go away.
How?
Listen to them.
What if they don't want help?
What if they're just angry
and they just wanna hurt somebody?
- I don't think that's the way it works.
- How do you know for sure?
I don't.
Hey!
Hey! Hey!
What's happening?
Cole.
What's happening to you?
Is someone hurting you?
I'll kick their ass.
Cole, if they're hurting you...
Mom?
Mama, you sleep now.
I'm feeling much better now.
Do you want to tell me something?
She came a long way
to visit me, didn't she?
I guess she did.
Can you get some water?
That's her sister.
You know, when I went through this
with my father's cancer, I...
I just can't imagine a child
being in bed for two years.
How many... How many doctors?
- I think it was six.
- Six different doctors?
I think so, yes.
I just heard the, uh,
little one is falling ill now.
God help them.
Don't go home, okay?
I definitely won't.
Mister?
Excuse me, mister.
Are you Kyra's daddy?
It's for you.
She wanted to tell you something.
Oh, no, here he comes.
He's coming my way. Psst!
Would you like to dance?
Um, well, actually,
I just came with my friends.
Oh, well, how about this?
We can dance for a little bit, and...
if you don't like the way I dance,
you can kick me.
Oh, okay, then.
It's time for lunch, Kyra.
I'm feeling much better now.
That's so great, honey.
It's time for your food.
Can I go outside if I eat this?
I don't know. You know how you get sick
in the afternoons. We'll see.
Don't say that it tastes funny.
You know I don't like to hear that.
Tami's mom called.
You were keeping her sick.
You liked it, she said.
She looked out for you.
Is Kyra coming back?
Not any more.
Yeah. Got it? That's enough.
That's enough make-up.
Okay.
They're calling for the stable boy.
Oh, we have to hurry.
Who, uh, who were you talkin' to?
Just practising my lines.
Thanks for giving me
this part, Mr Cunningham.
You know, when I went to school here, there was
a terrible fire in this section of the theatre.
- They rebuilt the whole thing.
- Yeah, I know.
Only he who is pure of heart
can take the sword from the stone.
Let the boy try.
But he's a stable boy.
He cleans up after the horses.
Silence, village idiot.
Let the boy step forward.
Hail, King Arthur!
Yea! Hip, hip, hooray!
I thought you were really great
in the play, Cole.
- Really?
- Yeah.
- You know what else?
- What?
I thought Tommy Tammisimo sucked big time.
I got an idea
how you can talk to your wife.
Wait till she's asleep.
Then she'll listen to you,
and she won't even know it.
I'm not gonna see you any more, am I?
I think we said everything
we needed to say.
Maybe it's time to say things
to someone closer to you.
Maybe we can pretend like we're gonna
see each other tomorrow.
Just for pretend.
Okay.
I'm gonna go now.
I'll see you tomorrow, Cole.
I'm okay, Officer. I'm okay.
I don't know what happened. I...
Geez, I hope nobody got hurt.
You're very quiet.
You're mad I missed the play, aren't you?
You know, I have two jobs, baby.
You know how important they are for us.
I'd give anything to have been there.
I'm ready to communicate with you now.
"Communicate"?
Tell you my secrets.
What is it?
You know the accident up there?
Yeah.
Someone got hurt.
They did?
A lady.
She died.
Oh, my God. What, you can see her?
Yes.
Where is she?
Standing next to my window.
Cole, you're scaring me.
They scare me, too, sometimes.
"They"?
Ghosts.
You see ghosts, Cole?
They want me to do things for them.
They... They talk to you?
They tell you to do things?
They're the ones that used to hurt me.
What are you thinking, Mama?
- You think I'm a freak?
- Look at my face.
I would never think that about you, ever.
- Got it?
- Got it.
Just let me think for a minute.
Grandma says hi.
She says she's sorry
for taking the bumblebee pendant.
She just likes it a lot.
What?
Grandma comes to visit me sometimes.
Cole, that's very wrong.
- Grandma's gone. You know that.
- I know.
- She wanted me to tell you...
- Cole, please stop.
She wanted me to tell you
she saw you dance.
She said when you were little...
you and her had a fight...
right before your dance recital.
You thought she didn't come
to see you dance.
She did.
She hid in the back so you wouldn't see.
She said you were like an angel.
She said...
you came to the place
where they buried her...
asked her a question?
She said the answer is...
every day.
What did you ask?
Do...
Do I make her proud?
Mama.
Hi, everybody.
As most of you know,
I'm not used to doing this...
and I promised Anna that I'd try
not to embarrass her.
I'll leave that to her mother.
But we do want to thank
all of you for coming...
and for sharing
this wonderful day with us.
It's, uh, bittersweet, almost, for me...
because I hate giving her up,
but Malcolm's going to be...
Anna?
I miss you.
I miss you too.
Why, Malcolm?
What?
- What is it? What...
- Why did you leave me?
I didn't leave you.
I see people.
They don't know they're dead.
How often do you see them?
All the time.
They're everywhere.
They only see what they wanna see.
Okay, Mikey.
Come on. Give me a minute.
Oh, God! Oh, God, honey.
- Let me see. Let me see.
- It doesn't even hurt.
Let me see. Take your hand off...
Oh, God.
Okay.
No. Oh...
I th... I think I'm okay.
Really, I think it just went...
went in and out.
I...
It doesn't even hurt any more.
I think I can go now.
I just needed to do a couple things.
I needed to help someone.
I think I did.
And I needed to tell you something.
You were never second.
Ever.
I love you.
You sleep now.
Everything'll be different in the morning.
Good night, Malcolm.
Good night, sweetheart.
Please rate this subtitle at www.osdb.link/46qa2
Help other users to choose the best subtitles