Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
I wish to report, sir,
a small boat met the Pharaon,
three leagues off the island.
I delivered the letter into
the hands of Captain Leclere.
They say the king is prepared for war.
So is the emperor.
Maintain the pump and gather oil!
Aye, aye!
Man the main topsail!
Man the topsail!
Here, Captain, take these.
No. No more pills.
Will I reach port as captain or...
...fish bait?
- Well, sir, your fever, uh--
- Yes, I know I have a fever.
- Where's Dantes?
- He's coming, sir.
Standby to carry the deck cargo!
That cargo? It's worth
12,051 francs and 30 cents!
What good is it if the ship goes down?
If Captain Leclere was on that,
the ship wouldn't go down!
And as long as I'm super-cargo
on this ship--
You'll stay off the quarterdeck!
Captain Leclere wants to see you.
The doctor said to come at once!
He thinks I'm going to die.
For the first time in 20 years,
he's right.
No, he isn't, sir.
You wouldn't leave me in command
for the first time
with a storm like this
on my hands, now, would you?
The old ship knows your hand
on the wheel.
She'll obey you.
But he wants to throw
the deck cargo overboard!
Can't be two captains
on one ship, Danglars.
I want to talk to Dantes alone.
I'm giving my last command as captain.
Deliver this to a man you will see.
He's expecting the captain
of the Pharaon
to bring it to him.
But who is he, sir?
There's-- There's no address.
He'll make himself known to you
by one word:
Elba.
Elba?
Sounds pretty heavy.
How is it up there?
Blowing up for a hurricane, sir.
There!
King's magistrate's not so
hungry this morning.
The guillotine will send him
only 10 heads for breakfast.
They've done nothing to deserve
having their heads chopped off.
Nothing except love
their exiled emperor
who always protected 'em.
Watch your mouth.
They'll have your head
in the basket, too.
Find out what that's about.
The Pharaon's been sighted.
She's coming in now.
See? I told you heaven was
with our cause.
Very soon, gentlemen, every
loyal follower of Napoleon
will be able to raise his head
once more.
Will you meet the ship
and contact Leclere?
Oh! Oh, no!
The-- the king's magistrate
might meet the ship, too.
I can't afford to have him
catch sight of me, can I?
No, no, I must remain in hiding here
until after sunset.
Stop right here, Marcel.
You may enjoy mingling
with these fishwives. I don't.
I'll wait for you in Fernand's office.
You may run along to this sailor.
- But without my consent.
- Yes, Mother.
Clear up the main and mizzen royals!
Steady as she goes.
Leclere dead?
Excuse me.
Good morning, Mr. Morrel.
Good morning, Mme de Rosas.
I thought you'd be here.
- That is the Pharaon, isn't it?
- Yes.
What can a mother do
with a daughter? Nothing!
You're an official.
You've got to stop
this sailor business.
Can't you refuse to have
the Pharaon enter the harbor?
Send it to another port?
Have it sink? Or something.
I'm collector of customs,
not ruler of the sea.
Well, it's a custom
I'm talking about, a bad custom!
A lady in love with a sailor.
It's merely a young girl's
infatuation.
She sees a hero in Dantes.
And what does she see in you?
A man who protests loudly
that he loves her
and does nothing about it.
The Pharaon is flying
the captain's pennant
at half-mast.
That means Leclere is dead.
He was ill before he left.
I was afraid he wouldn't
last out the voyage.
Well, what about the letter?
We arranged before he sailed
if he got worse
to transfer the letter
to his first mate.
And that's a man name, uh, Dantes.
Well, well, well,
whatever his name is,
keep a close eye on him
and let me know
when he gets to a place
where it'll be safe
for me to meet him.
Thank you, Edmond,
for bringing the ship safely home.
- I wish Captain Leclere hadn't--
- He died at sea.
- A sailor doesn't ask for more.
- No, sir.
- You stopped off Elba?
- Yes, sir.
There was a letter?
Why? What do you know about it?
What do you know about it?
Nothing, sir, except that
Captain Leclere
gave it to me to deliver to some man.
He said he'd make himself known to me.
Let him find you, Edmond.
Marseilles is full
of the king's spies.
Well, that hardly concerns me,
does it, sir?
I'm only carrying out
the captain's orders.
Would you like to
go over the log with me?
While you keep the most
beautiful lady in Marseilles
waiting on the dock?
On the dock?
I'll be here when you come back,
Captain Dantes.
- Captain?
- Yes, Captain Dantes.
From now on, you're in command
of the Pharaon.
Oh, sir!
You keep that enthusiasm for her.
Yes, sir.
I was afraid that-- that--
That I had forgotten you?
Yes.
You really ought to, you know?
What if I can't?
Well, I think something ought to
be done about it.
What are you going to do?
Well, I--
I'm gonna kiss you again.
But I want you to interrupt them.
Embracing in front of the whole city.
Good morning, Mercedes.
Oh, Fernand.
You know Captain Dantes,
Mssr de Mondego?
- Yes.
- Oh, naturally.
One o'clock, Edmond.
One o'clock.
Good morning, sir.
Your mother couldn't
possibly understand
this fascination for you.
- Never.
- But I can.
I knew you would.
Up to a certain point,
but not marriage.
Why not?
- Well, he has no family--
- I'll give him one.
Fernand, I've been warned,
scolded, threatened,
until I'm blue in the face.
I don't care about duty,
social position,
or what people say.
There are only two things that
really matter:
a man and a woman.
And Dantes is your man?
- Yes.
- I shan't say another word.
I shouldn't have spoken at all
had your mother not insisted.
I shall forget everything you've said.
I'm sure you will.
Goodbye.
I shall never forgive you.
Well, Fernand, I hope you've
made her see the light.
Clearer than ever.
I'm afraid I--
We'll get you some wooden shoes
and a bucket of fish.
Then you'll be in style.
Danglars, one of my own men,
gave me the information.
Dantes has the letter with him now.
Follow this Edmond Dantes.
Watch him, but don't arrest him
till he delivers the letter to
his confederate, whoever he is,
then seize them both
and bring them here.
Here's your warrant.
Yes, Mssr. Magistrate.
Well, Mondego,
in exposing this spy,
you've done a great service
to your king.
And to you, De Villefort.
And to Mme. De Rosas.
Merely what any friend would do
to save her from what we might
call an appalling marriage.
What brings you here?
I seek a golden treasure,
valuable above price.
Not so easy to obtain,
Mssr. Pirate.
First you must make formal demand,
because the custom of my country
is the same as that of others.
Is it a proposal you want?
Yes, and a formal one.
Well,
- I Edmond Dantes--
- Yes?
ask that--
I'm wrecked!
Coward!
The pirate's sunk.
I can't make the land.
Stuck on the reef of formality.
Yes.
But if you'll come aloft with me--
Aloft?
Yes, up in the rigging.
I can't think down here.
Suppose I refuse you up there?
Girl overboard.
Look, you can see the sea from here!
And clouds, like silver ships.
The ships that Edmond Dantes
will have some day.
Sailing into harbor
with what for cargo?
Oh, a lot of dreams...
And his proposal to Mercedes.
And her answer.
Yes?
Dantes is at the Café Reserve.
Mssr. Morrel is giving a dinner
in his honor.
Well, we, uh,
we can't wait any longer.
You stay here, I'll go there at once.
- Sure you're having a good time?
- Oh, yes. I like your friends.
They aren't just pretending to
be happy, they really are.
Oh, come now, before
the next dance starts.
Glasses, everybody!
Waiters, bring up the brandy!
More glasses, more wine!
I am looking for the captain
of the Pharaon. Is he here?
Yes, sir.
I have an important message for him.
Don't think I can disturb him.
I'm afraid you must.
Dear everybody!
To the betrothal of Edmond Dantes,
captain of the Pharaon
and Mme. Mercedes De Rosas.
May calm seas and a fair breeze
bring their ships safely
to the port of happiness,
prosperity, and a long life.
Drink to liberty and equality.
A gentleman with an urgent
message for you.
For me?
- The captain of the Pharaon.
- Oh, yes. I'll go with you now.
I'll be back in a moment.
Well, you've done it.
Now will you dance with me,
the rejected suitor
who hasn't changed his feelings
about you one bit?
- Here's the captain, sir.
- Good evening.
You are the captain of the Pharaon?
Yes, sir.
Elba.
- I've been expecting you.
- No, no. Not here.
Follow me.
- Thank you. That's all.
- Good night.
Mssr., you're under arrest by
order of the king's magistrate.
- Mssr. De Villefort?
- Yes, sir
Oh, uh, very well.
Take him to the court chambers.
Follow me.
- You delivered the letter?
- Yes.
I am glad that's done.
Captain Dantes?
The king's magistrate
orders your arrest.
On what charge?
Suspicion of bearing
treasonable information.
Something's happened.
Something's wrong.
Nothing really.
I have to go to the court, that's all.
To answer questioning about
someone else.
I'll come along with you
if you like, Captain.
Perhaps I could be of some service.
Please do. I'm going too.
- To the jail? You will not.
- Oh, but Mother, I am.
Please stay here, everybody,
and dance.
It's nothing serious.
We'll be back soon.
Nice disgraceful start
for betrothal, isn't it?
Meddling again, eh?
I thought you were in Paris.
Instead you find me
in Marseilles, your prisoner.
Amusing, isn't it?
The humor completely escapes me.
It would.
Excuse me, I'm old-fashioned.
I don't think a father should
stand before his son.
If the king knew
that one of the conspirators
against him was my father--
My son would lose his office.
For that reason, you must protect me.
I will protect you.
And myself too.
I'll have you sent away
under guard on a ship tonight.
If you're planning to deport all
the French citizens
whose sympathies are with Napoleon,
there won't be anybody left in France.
How many messages has this
Dantes brought to you?
None.
Leclere was my man.
He's dead.
Dantes knows nothing of it.
I don't believe it.
There. I hope you appreciate
that I'm saving your life.
I see. Perhaps I can do a favor
for you sometime.
I shouldn't hesitate to ask it
in return for this.
Turn this prisoner over to Crown.
Yes, sir.
Goodnight, my, uh--
my most noble magistrate.
Yeah, none of that.
Come on along.
Thanks for breaking up
an intolerable party so soon.
Bring in Edmond Dantes alone.
Captain Dantes.
Edmond Dantes, captain of the Pharaon?
Yes, sir.
As you're a friend
of Mssr. Mondego's,
I'll do what I can for you.
Thank you, sir.
Now, do you call yourself
a loyal subject
of His Majesty the King?
Yes, sir.
And yet you're found
carrying a message
plotting treason against your ruler.
Oh, but, sir,
I was only carrying out
my captain's orders.
I knew nothing about what
was in the letter.
Who is the man you
delivered the letter to?
I don't know his name.
- Ever see him before?
- Never.
Could you give an accurate
description of him?
I'm sure I could. He's about
your height--
That's enough.
You can identify him another time
- Why did you stop at Elba?
- Captain's orders.
- Where's the captain?
- Dead.
Dead? Who's to vouch
for your innocence?
Almost any member of the crew
would tell you that--
Would Mssr. Danglars know?
Certainly.
- Bring Mssr. Danglars in.
- Yes, sir.
This places me in
a very difficult position.
I never dreamed--
Oh, I'm not holding you
responsible, Inspector Mondego.
Ah. Who gave the order
to stop at Elba?
The first mate,
Mssr. Dantes, sir.
Describe what happened.
We lay off the island
a whole day, sir.
An officer came alongside
in a small boat
and gave Mssr. Dantes
a letter, sir.
No, you're mistaken, Danglars.
He went to the captain's cabin.
I stayed on deck.
I saw what happened.
One of you is obviously lying.
- I have nothing to hide, sir.
- Neither have I.
Mssr. Danglars has been
in my office many times.
I know him to be a most sincere
and honest man.
Oh, I see.
Danglars told you about Elba
and the letter
because he wanted to be captain.
And you told the magistrate here
because--
because of Mercedes.
You appear here as my friends.
Mssr. Morrel is outside.
He'll tell you that--
That's enough.
Take this prisoner
to the Chateau d'If.
Yes, sir.
Why to the Chateau d' If?
Why not right here till my trial?
Your trial?
Oh yes.
Well, it's only the matter of an hour
to bring you back across the harbor.
Can I see my fiancée,
Mme. De Rosas?
No.
Will you give me a few minutes
with Mssr. Morrel?
No. He's under suspicion too.
Uh, will you want me anymore, sir?
- No.
- Uh, for the trial?
He's had his trial.
Who's there?
Prisoner, sir, from the mainland.
- Criminal or political?
- Political, sir.
Well, put him anyplace.
I'll see him in the morning.
This note is important, sir.
I'd like to write a message.
Certainly, certainly.
Now let me see:
34, occupied, 35, occupied.
Ah, 27 empty.
Twenty seven, a splendid apartment.
Thank you very much.
Will you kindly see this delivered
to Mssr. Morrel in Marseilles
early tomorrow?
Certainly, certainly.
He'll have my attorney here
in the morning.
Certainly. Twenty-seven, I said.
Good night.
Speak to me. Anything!
Just a word!
God bless you.
No talking to the prisoners.
This ain't the right cell!
Can't you read?
This ain't 27, it's 37.
His attorney will be here
in the morning.
E...
L...
B...
A.
Napoleon has escaped from Elba.
N...
A...
P...
O...
L...
Gentlemen, the king.
Mssr. De Villefort,
His Majesty's royal agent
at Marseilles.
Good evening.
State your urgent business.
Sire, I was fortunate
in arresting a spy
who possessed this letter which
states that Napoleon
would leave Elba for France
on February the 26th.
And this is the first of March.
He'd have landed by now.
I commend your zeal, de Villefort,
but I have thousands
of secret agents in the South,
one of whom certainly would have
warned us by now.
- Now--
- Your Majesty.
What a fuss!
Speak, Blacas.
- Napoleon has landed in France.
- Impossible!
A message just came
by signal telegraph.
He was received, sire, with open arms.
The usurper in France!
And no inkling before this
from our valiant agents?
Blind fools!
Blind fools all of them.
All but one, my friend de Villefort.
Summon the minister of war!
De Villefort, even in this
moment of crisis,
the king does not forget.
Here, take this as a token
of my gratitude.
Where's the minister of war?!
Well then, we have three prisoners
in our dungeons here,
the reason for whose imprisonment
has long since been forgotten,
so that even their names don't
appear in our records.
Edmond Dantes is henceforth
listed as dead.
As Number 27, he
will merit no concern.
You're here.
So Dantes is dead, eh? Or am I
asking too many questions?
He died just in time.
Morrel is in Paris
for an audience with Bonaparte
and Bonaparte acts quickly.
Well, it didn't take him long
to put me out of office.
This is my last
and most important official act.
Political prisoners will be
released at once.
And Dantes with Morrel's backing
could easily find me
a home at the Chateau d'If.
Come in.
Oh, Fernand.
A letter from Mssr. Morrel
by special post.
He's arranged his audience
with the emperor
and promises that Edmond will be
freed in a week!
I'm afraid it's already too late.
Too late?
He's not--?
In trying to escape,
he was shot and killed.
He wouldn't do that.
I wrote him every day that we
would save him.
Then take me to his grave.
Sea is the cemetery
of the Chateau d'If.
Good morning.
Is it a nice day?
Or is it stormy?
Did you ask the governor if I
could please see him?
It's about my attorney, my trial.
Nice conversation I have
with you both every day.
Why don't you say something?
Speak to me, swear at me, anything!
That hurts! Let go! Let go!
That's just to see if you could speak.
You tell the governor
I won't eat any more
of his wormy food scraps.
Do you--?
Do you hear?
After this, we feed him
through the door.
So you don't like our food, eh?
Before you get down from there,
you'll be chewing it
out of your beard.
The only reason we ain't killing you
for attacking a guard
is because the governor
gets two sous a day
for every live prisoner.
Come on.
He ain't dead.
Mssr. Mondego.
I'm leaving Mercedes in your care
because you have always loved her.
And always will.
Mother.
No, no.
I'm not going to die yet, Mercedes.
Not until you promise
you will marry Fernand.
Fernand Marie-Antoine de Mondego,
do you accept this woman who
stands before you as your wife?
I do.
Mercedes Yvonne Melanie De Rosas,
do you accept this man
who stands before you
as your husband?
I do.
Ego conjungo vos in matrimonium,
in nomine Patris et Filii
et Spiritu Sancti.
Amen.
Mercedes.
Mercedes? Yes?
Thank God you're a prisoner, too.
I thought you might be
a jailor deceiving me.
Encourage me to betray myself.
Can you understand what I'm saying?
Can you speak?
No. I'm too-- too--
To feel the warmth
of a comrade's hand.
I had no means of knowing
there was a dungeon
lower down than mine.
I burrowed 30 feet through
solid rock for six years,
hoping to reach the outside wall
and make my escape.
And now I find I'm only
in another cell.
Six years!
I'm sorry.
I am the Abbe Faria.
I was Edmond Dantes.
How long have you been here?
I don't know.
Since the 28th of February, 1815.
How long is that?
Eight years.
This is the 7th of June, 1823.
Only eight years?
I'm still young.
That's funny.
I'm 68.
I've been in prisons 20 years.
I'll help you out.
Let's talk.
No, no. It's not yet big enough
for my shoulders.
Oh, I'll dig it away.
I'll work all night!
The guards must think the figure
in the bed is you asleep.
Yes.
- Can you see?
- Perfectly.
Owl's eyes.
Nature's compensation
for those obliged
to live always in the dark.
Here. Now we can stand.
You see this stone,
bevelled and grooved,
applying the same
engineering principles
used in the building of the pyramids.
Good likeness, isn't it?
I'll get a candle.
I want you to see my work.
- Candle?
- Made from beef fats.
- And a match.
- Matches!
Made from the gratings of a twig broom
and some sulphur they gave me
when I complained
of a skin affliction.
You see these?
Thread, made from blanket ravelling.
Needles and pens from fishbones.
Ink from pot black and vinegar.
Knife, file, chisel,
from an old kettle
that I managed to hide.
And, Edmond,
could it seem like bragging if I,
honored by degrees
from five universities,
managed to outwit
the six-year-old mind
of my jailors?
They call me a mad old priest
and harmless,
and I encourage them in this belief,
and in return, they
grant me certain favors,
such as chunks of chalk rock and slate
with which I've inscribed
on these walls
the creeds and formulas
on which are based
the sum total of mans' knowledge.
This is my chronometer,
from which I calculate the time.
My calendar.
My faith.
All quotations that you see
in the languages in which
they were originally written.
Greek, Hebrew, Latin,
Sanskrit over there.
French, Italian, English,
and German and Arabic.
I don't expect you to understand
much of it now,
but with patience and
willingness, you can master it.
And they call you mad.
They call me mad because
I speak the truth.
Because I've repeatedly offered them
as high as six million francs
to release me.
Six million francs?
Oh, I see.
You think I'm crazy, too.
Well, I don't blame you.
But everyone has heard of
the de Spada family fortune.
I have, since boyhood.
A buried treasure, wasn't it?
Dating from ancient Rome.
Well, for 20 years,
I was librarian and tutor
to the Duke de Spada.
He had no children
and made me his soul heir.
I planned to use it
to ease suffering humanity.
But this so enraged
the old duke's enemies
who planned after his death
to seize the fortune for themselves
that they submitted me first
to torture
and then threw me into prison
in an effort to force from me
the secret hiding place
which I alone know.
Together, we will dig our way
to freedom
and one half the treasure
shall be yours.
I'll dig my fingers to the bone.
I'll tear these rocks apart!
Money, riches,
power with which to strangle
and crush three rotten rascals!
Stop! Just stop.
Oh, what a miserable creature you are.
Your eyes green with greed.
Your heart filled with revenge.
In such a condition, you're not
fit to have one soul.
Patience.
What a long road you have to travel.
Be thankful your digging tools
are but bits of crockery and iron.
It will take time.
Pray for it to be a long time.
So that when you emerge
into the light,
it will not be as a revengeful
horseman of the apocalypse,
but as an avenging angel doing
the work of God.
I'll obey you in everything.
Everything.
We must watch out for the jailor.
Quick, back to your own cell.
Pray.
Most Heavenly Father,
at Thy will
the most barren earth blossoms
into beautiful bloom.
Amen.
And then Baron Rondeau
fell at the last hurdle
and burst his breeches.
You really must see it.
And the horses are too, too--
Well, you know what horses are.
Get Fernand to take you.
Since he's been treasurer to the king,
he has no time
for... frivolities.
So?
- Well, good-bye, Mercedes.
- Good-bye.
I've just heard
that the king's treasurer
is so occupied with official business
that he has no time for frivolities.
My official business this evening
takes me to 58 Avenue Montaigne.
I shall be home.
You see, Mother?
This is how the sail goes up and down.
I see.
Mercedes!
Yes, Fernand?
Oh, forgive my great
familiarity, Countess.
- Countess?
- Yes, Countess.
Today the king has restored
to my family its rightful title.
My son, you are now a viscount.
But I don't wanna be a viscount.
I wanna be a sailor.
You'll be a viscount
on your father's side.
Good evening, Danglars.
Everything is arranged.
The banking house
of Danglars and Company
opens its doors for Paris
for the first time tomorrow morning.
Congratulations.
I'll finish myself, Francois.
And in return,
for the many valuable clients
you have sent me,
here are your shares
in the company as I promised.
I shall deliver Mondego's
as soon as I leave you.
Thank you.
Oh, I read this morning that
the king had rewarded you again.
Oh, yes.
I think I can promise you
His Majesty's personal account
very soon.
That will mean certain success.
And you shall have
a larger share for that.
I expect it.
Yes! I said expect it and--
and you shall have it.
Er, there is only one fly
in the ointment.
- Mm? Who is it?
- Uh, Deputy Mundine.
Oh, he's always shouting
about the people's rights.
He threatens proposing a new law
which will seriously curtail
our profits.
He will be silenced tomorrow morning.
Francois, my hat!
Time, time, time, time, time!
How much longer do you really
think we'll have to dig?
Nearly five years,
according to my estimate.
Only five years.
Well, well.
Just like the day after tomorrow
for us.
Edmond, Edmond, come quickly.
I've just examined the tunnel.
Your lunar observations were correct.
This morning at 10:17
was the highest tide in six months.
And water seeped through a crevice
and loosened some rocks.
Wonderful.
I'll come along now.
You were right, Father.
Almost a pool of water here.
- Salt water. Taste it!
- Only three feet more to go.
Listen, can you hear the sea
pounding against the rocks?
Doing some of our work for us.
See?
Rocks falling all the time.
Be careful.
Come back!
Quickly!
No! Father! Father!
Are you hurt?
Don't lay me down.
Sit me up.
My ribs are crushed.
I don't want the blood
to get to my head yet.
Cross my legs.
Put my hands on my elbows.
Edmond,
loosen my belt and take
the de Spada parchment.
In my will,
written on a piece of cloth,
it names you my sole heir.
When people die,
we feel aggrieved
because their minds are lost to us.
How fortunate am I.
I leave my mind behind
in your possession.
It is part of yours.
Use it as an instrument for justice.
My blessing.
Edmond, if you could only see.
Death is so beautiful.
- Help! Help!
- What was that?
Help! Help!
In here, Number 34.
The old Abbe.
Well, something's happened to him.
- He looks dead.
- He is dead.
We'll get the undertakers.
That's the only way they ever
get outta this place.
Hurry up, Jules.
You get the chain and shot.
Thirty-six pounder.
I ain't gonna carry it
way back here by myself.
Gotta get the stretcher, too.
All right.
That's good enough.
Go on back and shut that door.
Think he's gonna get up and walk away?
- This oughta sink him.
- Go on. Throw it on.
- Who closed the door?
- Don't look at me.
Come on. Put that rope
around his feet.
Tie it good.
I'll take the head.
No, it's your turn to take the feet.
All right.
Pretty heavy for an old man, ain't he?
Yeah. Too heavy.
God... have... mercy...
on... his... soul.
Captain Vampa!
What is it?
Harbor police?
No, a man in the water.
Let some other ship pick him up.
We don't want any strangers aboard.
I always say land your fish first.
Then, if you don't like it,
throw it back.
What do you say?
Shall we pick him up?
- Aye.
- Aye, sir.
All right.
Bring her round,
and we'll pick him up the larboard.
Hand him up there, corporal.
Come. Heave.
All together. Come on.
Hang on.
Put him down there.
Where'd you come from, Neptune?
Well, I-- I--
No lies.
I know.
Your skin's as wet as a fish's belly.
Prison or the galleys?
Get him some food.
I suppose you'd like to get rid
of this seaweed?
This coat of mine will be
all right for now.
Ali here cannot talk, but he
wants to give you the sandals.
You look like a ghost.
I am.
The sun'll take care of that.
Jacopo says you've been a sailor.
- Yes.
- I'm Captain Vampa.
We smuggle for a living.
The crew all shares and shares alike.
We could use a good sailor.
Uh, what's your name or...
what shall we call you?
- Sinbad.
- Sinbad?
Sinbad the sailor.
What you lookin' at on Monte Cristo?
There's nothing there but wild goats.
Nothing but goats,
that's what I'm looking at.
Captain Bonnie was due here
this morning
with a cargo of tobacco
to trade for our laces.
If he's not here by nightfall, I'll--
Maybe he's round the lee
of the island.
Well, I'll up anchor and see.
If you like, while you're gone,
I'll go ashore and kill our dinner.
You can pick me up when we get back.
Well, it better be young and tender
or we'll leave you there.
Up anchor, all hands.
Jacopo, I'm going ashore
in the small boat.
My dear Abbe,
if you were only really here
beside me... to see.
You were right.
The world is mine.
The Chateau d'If.
On these moonlight nights
I can hear the good people
of Marseilles saying,
"Isn't it beautiful?"
Here are the names of the three.
Burn them into your memory.
Never forget them.
I want to know everything
about them, everything.
About their wives,
sweethearts, mistresses.
About their children,
family life, state connections.
Dates, facts, histories, details
down to the finest points.
I wish to know them as
intimately as I know myself.
And as I know my weaknesses,
I shall discover theirs.
And then,
I'll strike.
They all live in Paris,
where I'm sending you now.
I'll give you money enough
for the first month.
Spend freely.
Live like a king if you will,
but get me what I want.
In 60 days, draw on
the Count de Monte Cristo
through the banking firm
of Thompson and French in Rome.
For in 60 days I will have established
my right to that title
and the banking firm I will own.
Ali, we're going to Albania,
to trace carefully the steps
of one Mondego there,
and if I'm not mistaken,
we'll dig up a trail as foul
as stinking fish.
We all meet next in Rome,
where plotting is a custom
more ancient than the catacombs.
- I'm sorry.
- Thank you.
You make one doubt, my dear Count,
that I was ever champion
of the king's guards.
You take your fencing very seriously.
If I seem vicious in my attack,
it's because I always imagine
you're not my friend,
but my enemy.
- Tomorrow at eight?
- As usual.
- Excellency!
- Welcome, Jacopo!
It's good to see you.
Well, tell me all about Paris.
Is it as gay as they say,
with wine, women and song?
Oh, very gay.
I made several mistakes.
I had too much money to spend.
Well, it didn't prevent
your collecting
a mass of remarkable information.
Look. I've had every word copied
in my famous biographies.
The Villefort history alone occupies
more than 7,000 entries.
When I discover what really
could be found out
about a person,
it made a very good
little boy out of me.
And taught me exactly how to deal with
three very bad little boys,
who are leaders of a great nation.
I must attack them
with the same weapons
they've so viciously used
against their countless enemies.
Mondego with flattery,
Danglars with money,
De Villefort, law.
Well, now, the late news.
Albert, the young viscount
de Mondego, is here in Rome.
Good.
And when he left, I found myself
in the same stagecoach with him.
- Much to your surprise.
- Of course.
Well, he's a fine young man
from your reports;
courageous, strong,
a junior officer in the navy.
A sailor.
We'll give him one full day
of pleasure,
then tomorrow night, perhaps--
The catacombs?
The catacombs.
Well, Jacopo, we'll soon be
leaving Rome.
I'm ready, at last,
to open the gates of Paris
with Albert Mondego for my key.
You tell your friend
that if the 25,000 gold
was not paid by midnight
that your body would take its place
among these other beauties?
I never thought I was worth that much.
I don't see why he should.
That would be bad.
Deliver this to Signor
Jocopo Cavlarani.
If you could wait until I reach
my father by post, I--
We can't wait.
Which one of these beauties
do you think I'll be like?
One's as good as another.
Make your own choice.
- Excellencey.
- Good evening, Vampa.
The boy?
Asleep.
He don't frighten easily.
Oh, you're here.
Yes. I didn't have
any money on hand,
so I rushed to the Count
of Monte Cristo.
He kindly offered
to come here with me.
The Count de Monte Cristo.
This is the Viscount de Mondego.
What does this mean?
Excellency, I had no way
of knowing he was your friend.
What can I do?
How can I pay for my mistake?
In the future, it would be wiser
to be more careful.
Yes, Excellency.
Jacopo told me you were a great man,
but I never realized
you had influence over--
over everything.
Only enough to protect my friends.
I hope you don't think this happens
to every visitor to Rome.
Perhaps we can make you forget it
by filling the rest of your holiday
with nothing but pleasure.
Er, the gentleman's hat.
I'm dying to meet this Monte Cristo
who's so remarkable,
marvelous, courtly,
and all the other adjectives
you've called him.
- You'll see. He's-- he's--
- I know, I know.
He's never been to Paris before.
You've told me that, too.
Many times.
He said he'd be here
at 10 o'clock precisely.
It's almost that now.
I know everything about him
except why he wanted
a copy of my portrait.
I told you that, too.
When he was visiting me at my hotel
and saw the miniature of you
I always carry with me,
he simply asked if he could have
it copied for his gallery.
Yes, but--
But why not? Aren't you the most
beautiful woman in Paris?
In all France for that matter?
In all the world.
Mssr. de Villefort.
- Good morning, Fernand.
- Oh, good morning, de Villefort.
I stopped by to show you
Danglars' suggestions for the week.
Oh, buying heavily
of Spanish bonds, eh?
I suppose as usual it would be
wise to follow suit.
Yes.
We'll drop our buying orders
at his bank on the way.
Will you come in my carriage?
Or are there too many ladies
waiting at their windows
to wave to you as you go by?
Never too many, de Villefort.
I can't go for a little.
I promised Albert that I would meet
this mysterious Count de Monte Cristo.
Oh, he saved Albert's life, didn't he?
Something of the sort, yes.
Oh, there they are now.
Suppose I wait for you in there?
Would you mind?
And then please interrupt me
after a moment?
I will.
Yes?
Father...
the Count de Monte Cristo.
Charmed.
My son has told me
of your many kindnesses,
how you saved him
from the hands of bandits,
with which, I believe,
your country's infested.
I dare say there are bandits
in other countries.
Known by other names.
Perhaps.
My pardon.
I'm sorry to interrupt,
but we've little time, Fernand.
Good morning, Albert.
Count de Monte Cristo,
may I present the King's
attorney, Mssr. de Villefort.
Honored.
It is a pleasure, sir.
I have followed your brilliant career
with a great deal of interest.
Thank you.
Thank you, indeed.
Excellencies, the great country
of France awaits your services.
Please don't let me detain you.
If you will be so kind.
We shall meet soon again,
my dear count.
I shall plan for it, Count de Mondego.
Albert, is your mother well?
Yes, Father.
Tell her that I shall do my best
to see her sometime today.
Oh, if in a moment I excuse myself,
you'll understand it's only to
send a message to my lady love
naming our rendezvous
for this afternoon.
I understand.
The Countess is waiting.
My dear Count, how can I
ever thank you for--
for what you've done for my son?
It was humiliating to think
that one of my country's guests
should suffer such an indignity.
Won't you sit down?
I'd have known you anywhere.
From your portrait.
Oh, yes.
Albert told me you had it copied.
Why?
A painter rarely catches beauty.
When he does,
the combination I can't resist.
I hope you weren't displeased.
On the contrary.
Getting along famously, aren't you?
Yes.
I must tear myself away.
I have a house I've never seen
awaiting my inspection.
You'll call again?
If I don't provoke your hospitality.
You know my address,
you won't neglect me?
Tomorrow?
In the afternoon, I shall be home.
Mother!
Who is he?
The Count de Monte Cristo.
No, I mean--
Tell me everything you know about him.
Why, Mother.
Is he so strange?
I don't know.
There's just something about him
that frightens me.
Oh, silly.
Perhaps I am...
R...
E...
N...
C...
H.
Nothing would give me greater
pleasure, my dear Count,
than to take care
of your banking in Paris,
but there must be some mistake
in this letter of advice.
Are Thompson and French
in the habit of making mistakes?
Oh, never before. My most
reliable correspondents. But I--
This is their stationary,
properly watermarked.
You've compared the handwriting
and tested the signatures?
Yes, invisible stamp,
everything authentic,
but one word only I question:
unlimited.
It says I am to grant you
unlimited credit.
The house of Baron Danglars
was highly recommended
as quite adequate to fulfill
my quick demands.
- But if, of course--
- Of course, of course.
I might modestly claim
that there's no stronger house
than mine in Paris,
but please give me some idea of,
uh, what amount
one of your 'quick demands'
might entail.
Well, I doubt whether I shall
require more than
six millions from you this year
to cover my living expenses.
Six million?
More than it takes
to run the royal palace!
Really, Baron?
Yes, about six millions, I should say.
You see, I always carry
a million with me.
Well, I-- I shall arrange for it.
It'll take me several days.
You won't need any today?
Yes. Please buy for me
this morning
50,000 shares of British Maritime.
British Maritime, 50,000 shares!
Is it going to raise?
Oh, I invest only in certainties.
Every European banking house
of major importance
sends me a daily telegraph,
a service I personally finance.
And, uh, British Maritime?
Will go up at least, uh, 12 points
within the next two days.
If you speculate, you might do well.
But perhaps you hesitate
to take my advice.
Certainly not, my dear Count!
Even a banker likes to add
to his store of, um, pennies.
Um, I'll take, um, fi-- er,
10,000 shares myself
to prove my confidence.
As you wish.
The market's open.
Good morning, Baron.
Uh, good morning, Excellency.
My office, my reserves, my-- my--
Well, everything I have
is at your service.
The respected Baron Danglars, eh?
Cheat.
Hypocrite.
Skunk.
And up it went.
Twelve points in two days,
exactly as he said.
I sold.
And profited 120,000 francs.
And never let us profit.
Oh, suppose I'd have risked
your money and lost.
How you'd have cried.
You always do.
Well, next time--
If his buying orders go through you--
Yes, yes, yes.
When he buys, we buy.
When he sells, we sell.
Perfectly simple and perfectly honest.
Besides, he's invited me
to participate.
Gives me tips.
I think he likes me.
Mondego's vanity will blind him
to my motives.
Danglars we'll stuff with profits
till we're ready to pluck the goose.
But de Villefort is shrewd.
If he should get suspicious,
and put his pack
of secret service agents
on my trail--
Come in.
Mssr. Fouquet
to see Your Excellency.
Mssr. Fouquet!
You know who he is?
Who doesn't?
The greatest detective in Europe!
- Show Mssr. Fouquet in.
- But, uh--
We'll find out if he lives
up to his reputation.
Your Excellency.
Oh, this is Mssr. Jacopo,
my personal confidant.
You're at liberty to speak.
I just returned from Marseilles
with a complete record
of Edmond Dantes
from his birth to his death.
He is dead, then?
Yes. I found that he'd lived
for 16 years
after he was entered as dead
in the record.
But finally he was drowned
while cleverly trying
to effect his escape.
There can be no doubt, then?
He drowned?
It would be a miracle
if he got out of that sack.
But, uh--
But?
I'm surprised to hear you
use a "but", Mssr. Fouquet.
I am informed that he lived
and was picked up
by Italian smugglers,
becoming a member of their crew.
Well, it's possible, but--
Excuse me.
I just said that it might be possible,
but if it is, I'll find him!
He gave me a scare.
I didn't know he was working for you.
I couldn't afford to have him
working for anyone else, now could I?
I must find out what they
can find out about me.
I'm saving de Villefort the trouble.
The time will come when I'll
want him to know who I am.
I'll hand him the information
on a silver platter.
This investigation business
has gotten to be an awful habit
with you!
You even investigate yourself!
You want everyone to know who you are?
One day I'll want to publish it
to the whole world.
So tomorrow, I'm going to buy
a newspaper.
Using my house as a rendezvous, eh?
What'll your father say to that?
If you knew how desperately
we try to meet each other unobserved.
- Shall I?
- Please.
I have an idea.
Is it a plan to reconcile
our fathers to our marriage?
You're the only one who can do it.
They're bursting with admiration
for you.
Really?
Well, this is a different plan.
To repay the kindness shown to
me in Paris, I'm giving a ball.
My guest of honor is to be
the father of my first
Parisian friend,
Count de Mondego.
Oh, how Father will be puffed up
about that.
I thought it particularly
apropos to combine with it
an Albanian pageant
and series of tableaux
representing the court of Ali Pasha
at which your father gained such
extraordinary fame and honors.
Isn't it exciting, Albert?
Of course, I shall want
your mother's permission.
Can you get it for me, do you think?
No, sir, I'm-- I'm afraid you'll
have to get that yourself.
She wondered why you never
called after that first day.
Well, I shall be privileged.
Tomorrow afternoon?
Well, now business is over,
let's talk about your future.
If you could only get Father...
- Don't you think you could--?
- ...to listen to reason!
I thought there must be
something like this somewhere.
I've had it ever since,
for many years.
Well, it speaks the truth.
Edmond Dantes is dead.
Then, who is this
Count de Monte Cristo
who so closely resembles him?
The resemblance has
been noted by no one but you.
He is, in fact,
to answer your question,
a person so utterly unlike
a man named Dantes
that they might have been
born of different parents.
Even the soul is not the same.
I can believe that.
The present is the only time
that holds the truth.
The past is lies,
with this for witness.
It was once truth that Edmond
and Mercedes loved each other.
Today that truth is false,
and how fortunate it is.
For now we find her
not a simple sailor's wife,
but a countess,
consort of a noble,
while Dantes,
one life finished, lives another.
The past for you dies very easily.
Easily?
What's dead is dead.
In that respect, I'm a fatalist.
Then, tell me,
Mssr. Fatalistic Count,
what does your heart crave now?
Intelligence, first of all.
Then, perhaps,
simply to live gracefully.
Hence the graceful gesture
of honoring my husband
with a regal entertainment.
Yes.
And why my husband
out of all the others?
Because I have a real affection
for his son,
whom I met by chance in Rome
and further, because
I hold his charming wife
in great esteem and admiration.
Forgive me for ever mistrusting
your motives.
Henceforth, the Count de Monte Cristo
and the Countess de Mondego
will meet and greet each other
with nothing but the airy,
meaningless compliments
that befit their social position.
And Edmond Dantes?
Is dead.
I have forgotten him.
Good.
I shall look forward to receiving
the most gracious Countess
as my guest.
I appreciate the significant honor
you are bestowing on both the Count
and your obedient servant.
The Marquis and Marquise
of Fleur-de-Couer...
Mssr. le Colonel Barbizan.
Ah, my Ali Pasha.
It took them two hours
at the Comedie Francaise
to put on my makeup.
Is my beard long enough?
To me, perfect, but Mondego
would know more about that.
How does he look to you?
Remarkable. Excellent.
Very good. Very good indeed.
Thank you.
The Great Duke of Worthingham.
Lavish, that's what it is, lavish!
You are the only man in Paris
that never counts the cost!
Except you, Danglars.
Oh, Baron Danglars, you've
met Count de Mondego?
- Yes.
- Ooh, of course, of course.
All three of us originally
came from Marseilles.
Really? To think that one city
boasts the birth place
of three such eminent men.
I hope I may have
the privilege one day
of entertaining in your honor, too,
Mssr. de Villefort.
You're too kind.
And, Baron Danglars,
I am planning for you a similar affair
which I hope will do you justice.
Ooh, my, my, my!
I-- I shall be most grateful.
One, two, three of you I must honor.
Will you excuse me?
Isn't he amazing, eh?
- Beauchamp.
- Good evening, Excellency.
When I bought your newspaper,
I told you from time to time
I'd give you certain truths to print.
Watch closely what goes on,
then seek me out.
The first tableau portrays
His Excellency
the Count de Mondego,
presenting his credentials
as French ambassador
to Ali Pasha.
Bravo! Bravo!
Bravo!
We will now see Ali Pasha
in his harem.
Look, Emily!
There's Hortense DeBre
and Reni Latour.
Both have been mistresses of Mondego.
This isn't Ali Pasha's harem,
it's Mondego's.
Princess Haydee, go now
and mingle with the guests.
After the curtains part,
look carefully at the tableau
then run quickly onto the stage
and speak in a loud, clear voice
whatever comes to your lips.
The final tableau represents
Count de Mondego's valiant
but vain efforts
to save the life of Ali Pasha
at the hands of the Turks.
- Bravo!
Bravo!
That's a lie!
I am Ali Pasha's daughter.
The Count de Mondego betrayed him!
Betrayed France!
Sold my father to the Turks,
who paid him money
to arrange my father's death!
Then he killed all the witnesses
and sold me and my mother
into slavery!
You killed my father!
Mme, please! Please!
Count de Mondego, honored guests,
please forgive this
unfortunate occurrence.
This fanatic woman entered here
under veiled disguise.
I have ordered her arrest.
Every great man is attacked
by crazed imposters.
I hope that Count de Mondego
will accept
the deep apologies of my house.
His valiant record is
a matter of history.
We are here to do him honor.
Who was that crazy woman?
I'll have her brought to you
for questioning.
Oh, no, no. Don't, don't.
Please don't.
It's perhaps best
to forget the whole affair.
That's very kind of you.
Shall we not dance?
How perfectly ridiculous.
What a shock for you, my dear.
How charmingly Monte Cristo
handled it.
- Excellency!
- Beauchamp...
I was looking for you.
A man is waiting at your office
with a locked dispatch box
for which this is the key.
The box contains signed evidence
and testimony
that this is the real Princess Haydee
and that what she said is true.
Devote your entire paper to it.
Prepare for a jump in circulation
and deliver the first copy
off the press
by special messenger
into the hands of Count de Mondego.
I regret the hour,
but I have urgent need
of the Count's advice.
He has just retired, Your Excellency.
I shouldn't dare disturb him now.
However, he always rises at six.
I'll wait.
You're up early, Mondego.
Where are you?
Don't shoot.
You've only one bullet
and would surely miss.
Where are you?
If you could see as I can in the dark,
you would observe my pistol
aimed carefully at your head.
Two steps to your right
you will find a table.
Now first put down your pistol.
It has a quick trigger
and your hand is shaking.
Thank you.
To your right
on the edge of the table,
you'll find some matches.
When I say, "Ready", strike a light.
Ready.
I'm glad you brought the pistol.
I didn't have one.
Will you light the candle there?
Another one. I like to see
the faces of my guests.
Forgive my precautions
for saving my life.
You intended to take it, didn't you?
I wouldn't have killed you
without first
forcing from you a full explanation.
After which, I would've given you
your choice of weapons.
As you did Ali Pasha?
You're avenging Ali Pasha, then?
No.
Myself.
I don't recall that our paths
ever crossed
before three months ago.
As Monte Cristo, no.
Who are you, then?
Obviously, some imposter
posing as a count.
Who else are you?
Before I tell you, Mondego,
what is your choice of weapons?
Pistols, if you will,
but I prefer not to awaken Paris
at such an early hour.
Swords? Daggers? Fists?
Swords would suit me perfectly.
Swords, then.
I have them here.
A trick I learned to fool the jailors
while tunneling myself
out of the Chateau d'If.
Yes,
the Chateau d'If.
Does that clue mean nothing to you?
Dust off your memory.
Go back 20 years.
Back to the days
when you first discovered
that a life meant nothing
if it furthered your ambition.
Think.
An innocent, unsophisticated sailor
whose name was--
- Dantes!
- Right!
Edmond Dantes.
Simple, isn't it?
Very simple, indeed.
I might have questioned my skill
against the formidable Monte Cristo,
but against Edmond Dantes?
Swords.
You very cleverly planned
my destruction, Dantes,
but you won't have the pleasure
of living to see it.
Good. I'm accustomed to fighting
as the underdog.
It's not my sword, Mondego,
but your past that disarmed you.
Jacopo, take Count de Mondego
to his home in my carriage.
Take him secretly
to his garden entrance.
By this time, his front door
is surely besieged
by reporters from every newspaper
and perhaps the police.
He is to communicate with no one.
Good morning.
There he is! There he is!
Your Excellency. Baron Danglars
personally visited
my office this morning
and gave me this.
It's a thousand francs, sir,
in return for which,
I was to send him copies
of all telegraph messages
addressed to you.
Keep it for your children's education.
Thank you, sir.
Send the Baron the copies
as he requested.
I'll see that he gets
the proper information.
Yes, sir.
"Monte Cristo."
"Future political situation
makes Anglo-Spanish shares
wonderful investment."
"Suggest unlimited buying."
"Thompson and French."
This is what I've been waiting for.
Start buying at once!
Investing de Villefort
and other special clients
money as well?
No.
Only mine.
- Oh, but the risk--
- Risk?
This is one of Monte Cristo's
certainties.
Haven't we made money
on every one of them?
Convert all my holdings
into Anglo-Spanish.
All?
All.
I've investigated carefully!
Neither Rothschild nor Lorenti
is buying Anglo-Spanish.
They don't know everything.
I'm tired of playing second fiddle
to Rothschild, Lorenti, Monte Cristo!
After this when we meet,
I want them to take their hats
off first!
Buy!
Show Baron Danglars in.
Anglo-Spanish has collapsed!
I'm ruined!
We're both ruined!
Why?
I knew it would collapse.
You knew?
But you've been buying!
No.
But Thompson and French--
But their advice was--
I received their advice,
but their message was in code.
Though it said to buy,
it really meant to sell.
You see, Thompson and French
is owned by a man named Edmond Dantes.
Who?
Monte Cristo.
You said--
Edmond Dantes.
Monte Cristo.
They're the same, Danglars.
- Is he alive?
- Yes, but--
Call a doctor.
He's lost his mind.
- Permanently?
- Irretrievably.
Marseilles...
Morrel...
Dantes...
Chateau d'If.
A mental suicide, doctor.
- Mental suicide?
- Yes.
He destroyed his mind with an overdose
of two deadly poisons.
Poisons?
Avarice and greed.
Welcome, Albert.
It's been a long time.
I've just returned from Marseilles.
We buried my father there.
Well, yes, I know. I--
There are certain circumstances
leading to my father's death
I don't quite understand.
That's why I've come to you
who knows everything.
Surely. If I can--
My friends report
that this Princess Haydee
has been seen with you
in your carriage several times.
That's true.
She is here now, living in your house.
At present, yes, but--
Do you deny that you had
previous knowledge of her intent
to expose my father?
Do you deny that he visited you
the morning of his death,
was returned home in your carriage
under guard and--
and a few minutes later shot himself?
He came to me for help
I couldn't give.
Your open association
with Princess Haydee
is an intolerable affront
to the family of Mondego
and one that can only be appeased by--
Stop!
Don't say it.
Don't say it, Albert.
Don't challenge me.
Rather anyone but you.
I have other friends who respect me.
I must prove to them that running away
is not the habit of all Mondegos.
If killing me will save your honor--
I don't wish to kill you.
But--
Well, then, we might--
I see what you're thinking.
You're suggesting a bloodless duel.
Then, all my life I--
I live a lie,
knowing that I placed cowardice
ahead of honor.
Even my father wouldn't stoop to that.
I await your pleasure.
Tomorrow at dawn.
The place and details
my seconds will arrange.
They will present themselves
this afternoon.
Good morning, sir.
Good morning.
- Something's happened?
- Yes.
Something admirable and terrible,
something I never planned.
Your meeting with Albert is at seven.
It is already five.
You only have an hour left for rest.
Will you use his
duelling pistols or yours?
His, I suspect.
What difference does it make?
Mssr. Fouquet is waiting.
here is the link
that Fouquet's chain lacks.
Tell him to go at once
and drag de Villefort from his bed.
The great King's Attorney
won't be sleepy long
when he has in his hands the evidence
that'll send me back to prison.
If I survive the duel, I shall
go through with the trial.
- If I die--
- De Villefort will go free.
Yes.
This chest contains my past, my plans,
and my unfinished business.
Also my will, which makes provisions
for my friends, servants,
and you,
my trusted confidant.
Yep.
My house is now in order.
Yes, I'll see her at once.
Edmond, don't kill my boy.
- He told you.
- Not a word.
Bernard, one of his seconds,
thought I ought to know.
I see.
I wonder if you do.
No.
I'm the only one who sees.
Sees you as you were.
And sees you as you are now,
devoid of every human feeling,
bent upon destroying everything
that lies upon your path of vengeance.
Please believe I've put my task
above the mean level
of personal vengeance.
I am exposing criminals,
not for their sins against myself,
but for their black injustices
to others.
Not only for what they have done,
but for what they continue to do.
They are the ones devoid
of all humanity,
the ones that profited
by the sufferings of others.
Whom will it profit
if you kill my son?
Surely you don't think this duel
part of my design?
What else am I to think?
Knowingly how skillfully you
have destroyed the others.
Let me tell you about Albert.
He worships you.
Never in his life has he felt
such a strong affection
for anyone but me.
He never understood his father.
There was no bond of sympathy
between them.
Why?
'Cause that was a part of my design.
I reared him in the image
of the man I loved.
He is the son Edmond Dantes
would have had.
I had hoped that he'd be claimed
by Monte Cristo.
I claimed him long ago, Mercedes.
But the situation now is desperate.
His honor is at stake.
We must protect it.
He has a growing fear
that he'll be like--
I know. His father.
That he'll be thought a coward.
Promise me you'll let the duel
go through.
For the sake of his future.
He must have self-respect.
You promise me
he'll have a future, then?
You really think I'd guide
my bullet to its mark?
No.
Not now I don't.
But you see, I had to be quite sure.
Not for myself alone.
There's Valentine de Villefort.
I can't forget
that when I was her age,
I lost the man I loved.
We can't cast a shadow across
the path of Valentine.
I'm afraid it's already too late.
What?
Jacopo, has Fouquet left?
Yes, Excellency, I saw him on his way.
He'll be at his door by now.
The King's Attorney's door.
De Villefort is the next one
on my list.
If you would spare the feelings
of De Villefort's daughter,
tell Albert to take careful aim
and shoot to kill.
Gentlemen, you have your instructions.
Six paces, turn at my command.
Fire at will.
Ready?
One.
Two.
Three.
Four.
Five.
Six.
Turn!
Your Excellency,
Count de Monte Cristo,
Count de Mondego.
Your aim was true.
Why didn't you hold it?
I couldn't.
I'm sorry. It would've saved me
a lot of trouble.
Mother told me who you were.
I see.
Edmond Dantes.
You're under arrest by order
of the King's Attorney.
To the jury.
One last close look before you
assemble to take a ballot,
the result of which
can never be in doubt.
And you, citizens of France,
look at this man,
who, while purporting to be
an honest sailor,
was in reality a spy.
Who while imprisoned
in the Chateau d'If
threatened the lives of guards,
undermined the structure with tunnels,
and when he discovered the old
Abbe held a secret to a treasure
he perhaps caused his death
by crushing his poor body
with great rocks.
Think of his fiendishly
contrived escape
in the burial sack,
his unearthing of the treasure,
his practice of the title of Count.
Setting himself up as a nobleman!
Know him for what he is.
Traitor, spy, doubtless murderer,
companion of thieves,
patron of bandits, imposter,
and criminal at large before his king!
They'll send him back to prison.
- Why doesn't he speak?
- I don't know.
His defense is all prepared.
He won't use it.
The King's Attorney has concluded?
The Prosecution rests its case.
It is my duty to advise the accused
that if he declines
to speak in his defense,
the case must be judged wholly
on the testimony
presented by the prosecution.
I have nothing to say.
- He's shielding Valentine.
- Valentine?
Me?
Come with me, my dear.
I must tell you something.
This court is in recess
until the jury return.
That was 20 years ago.
I thought you ought to know.
Court convening.
Albert, quickly. I can't stay,
but I must write him a note.
Oh, yes.
Mother says you must defend yourself.
It isn't fair to her if you don't.
And it isn't fair to me.
The court is now in session.
Mssr. le President.
If it is not too late!
May I have the privilege
of defending myself?
It is the right of every citizen.
Your Excellencies, Judges of France,
Gentlemen of the jury,
my motives in not speaking
in my defense
were purely selfish.
I was placing self above my duty
to my fellow men.
A duty which was made clear
to me by the--
the spiritual vision of a saintly man.
The Abbe Faria.
As we together
for eight torturous years
scratched our way through solid rock
to reach the world again
in order that we might
in some small way
bring to the seat of trial
some inhuman humans
who make capital of justice.
Mssr. le President,
I find all this quite
unnecessary and irrelevant.
The accused is permitted to continue.
Without further interruption.
The interruption is well-timed,
but in order to prove
Edmond Dantes innocent,
I must ask recourse to a witness.
And is the witness obtainable?
He is here in this court.
Name him and he shall be called.
Unfortunately, the court precedent
precludes my calling him.
Any precedent can be set aside.
Who is he?
- The King's Attorney.
- The King's Attorney?
That hardly is according
to general court procedure.
But as Mssr. de Villefort
has already stepped down
from his great office to
personally prosecute this case,
I'm sure he'll agree
to set aside his cap
and cloak of prosecutor long enough
to serve as witness.
Is this your signature and seal?
Yes.
It is the death certificate
of Edmond Dantes.
Mssr. de Villefort's been
prosecuting a dead man.
I was a magistrate, not a coroner.
Were you given to understand
that I was dead?
Of course, by the governor
of the Chateau d'If.
I apologize for the misunderstanding.
One more question,
Mssr. de Villefort.
Why did you commit me to prison
without trial?
Because it was to your
political advantage to do so.
Absurd.
I gained no advantage.
Because you knew that if I was
given trial, your father,
a leader of the revolution,
would be exposed.
You shielded your father
and sacrificed Edmond Dantes,
cast him into oblivion,
pronounced him dead.
I acted for the good of my country
at a time when such traitors as Dantes
held the power to plunge us
into anarchy.
On what evidence was I convicted
of being a dangerous traitor?
On the most reliable testimony.
Whose?
A member of your own crew,
the super-cargo.
His name?
I've-- I've forgotten.
I'll refresh your memory.
His name was Danglars.
Yes, Danglars,
later Baron Danglars,
the banker.
Reputed to be honesty itself.
I have his record here.
He, to further his own ends,
gave false testimony
to send me to prison.
He cheated his way to power,
looted his own bank,
robbed thousands of honest workers
of their savings,
and yet he was but a tool in the hands
of an even more despicable criminal
who stood behind him,
directed his evil practice,
shared his profits,
protected him from justice,
was his lifelong friend
and fellow conspirator,
Raymond de Villefort.
This is an incredible accusation.
I am prepared to prove it, sir.
This is not only an accusation,
it is a warning.
Danglars is finished,
but de Villefort goes on
as the power behind
that banking house,
and if the government
does not immediately investigate
the manipulations,
the bank will collapse,
carrying with it to destruction,
not only thousands
upon thousands of investors,
but the huge funds placed there
by the National Treasury itself!
How can anything this criminal says
be used as evidence?
Here is the evidence of my innocence.
Attested and reattested affidavits
from unimpeachable authorities,
and here is his record,
a complete history
of Raymond de Villefort,
an exposure that will rock this court
and France to its foundations.
In the interests of justice we
must at least examine these.
This is out of order!
I'm being treated as a prisoner,
not as a witness.
I demand a trial!
He demands what he denied me!
May I ask His Majesty's
impartial judges
to look at this man who
so abused the privilege
of public office,
who so used treachery
in place of justice,
who so maliciously corrupted
every phase of government
with his touch!
It is not my place to prosecute
or judge this man,
I am a prisoner.
It is within the province
of this court
to pronounce me innocent or guilty,
but I have followed the path
of duty to my country
and my fellow men by
giving this prisoner to France.
- It can't be far from here.
- Mother.
Mother.
May we come up?
You find your own tree.
Please rate this subtitle at www.osdb.link/9k95x
Help other users to choose the best subtitles