-== [ www.OpenSubtitles.com ] ==-
Percy!
Look at him with his horse.
Wave to your father.
Gentlemen!
Today, I will be delivered
to the Archduke Ferdinand at the gala.
I expect you to behave
with distinction on this hunt.
Good luck...
and Godspeed.
Could they not fit you a rocking chair
on that horse, grandad?
You'll all be my gun bearers by evening.
I've no doubt of that.
Keep up there! Keep up there!
Major, there's no path there!
Major! Major!
Good boy.
You caught him?
Superb horsemanship, Major.
Excellent shot, sir.
These woods have been deadly to horses.
To Death;
the best source to Life.
You'll be the toast of the gala.
Here they come.
Oh, he's triumphant!
- Daddy did it!
- Come here, you.
- Daddy!
- Well done, Daddy.
Someday, you and I
will go hunting together.
We're going to be late.
Oh, God, it's this damn thing.
You must be so pleased
with yourselves. You, men.
Making us wear these awful things.
At least you're not wearing trousers.
Oh, I would if I could.
I know.
Well?
Rather lovely.
"Rather lovely."
What is it? What's amiss?
You've got the deer.
All eyes will be on you this evening.
Well, my darling, I will be the only man
there tonight, of my rank,
whose uniform is unadorned.
How can that matter now?
The great Secretary Bryce
will be at the gala.
Oh, Ms. Fawcett.
You've no medals.
"Oh, no, Mr. Bryce.
You see, I've been terribly busy
teaching ancient militiamen to
point their rifles at tree stumps, so...
No, no.
No medals for me, sir."
Tell me.
Who's this Secretary Bryce
when he's at home?
The last man here upon whom we might
possibly rely for advancement.
I see.
I'm getting older, cheeky,
and very impatient of lost years.
I know the medals are ridiculous. I do.
But this may be our final chance.
Secretary Bryce,
this is Major Fawcett.
- Major.
- It's an honor, sir.
Honor's mine, sir.
Good to meet you. Meet Secretary Bryce;
Secretary Bryce, Madame Bellamy.
Major and Mrs. Percy Fawcett.
They're toasting
the kill without you.
...this most magnificent animal...
Well, I am dancing with you,
so I've got the better of the bargain.
May I, Major?
Spoken too soon.
Come.
By the way, who got the kill?
Oh, that would be
Major Fawcett, Mr. Secretary.
Well, we should invite him to supper.
Oh..
Well, may I say...
he's been rather unfortunate
in his choice of ancestors.
I see.
Well, then...
Tell me. How is Lady...
No more than 20 cases, Clive.
Hurry along, men. Come on!
Come on. Put your back into it.
- Fawcett!
- Put your backs into it.
Hurry it along.
- Sir.
- You're off to London tomorrow,
to the Royal Geographical Society.
The Royal Geographical, sir?
There's a major exploration afoot.
Sounds like a grand adventure.
Thank you, sir.
Thank you.
Major Fawcett, sir.
Oh, yes, yes. Come in.
Absent George Goldie,
president of the RGS,
this is Mr. John Scott Keltie,
our secretary.
How do you do, Major?
How do you do, sir?
Our paths have not crossed
during our work here
several years back, did they?
They did not, sir.
I was likely consumed
with my studies at the time.
Of course.
- Please, sit down.
- Thank you.
Ah! The army seems to have
posted you in many places in the path.
Yes, I've served in Salon
and in Hong Kong before that;
most recently in lreland.
As you can see, I've been transferred
a fair bit around the Empire.
Major, what do you know about Bolivia?
- In South America, sir?
- That's right.
Only what I've read.
Hmm. Then you can't know very much.
This is as good a map
of Bolivia as we have.
Map's a bit blank as you can see.
Nothing's really known about it at all.
A land of primitives.
But there are rubber plantations
all over Amazonia.
Very profitable.
There is now considerable argument
between Bolivia and Brazil
as to what constitutes their border.
So fantastically high
is the price of rubber,
that war could arise.
Do you follow?
- I do, sir.
- Mm-hmm.
Although, I'm not sure what this
has to do with me.
I'm getting to that.
Neither country will accept
mapping done by the other,
so they've requested us to act as referee.
- Mm.
- As you've completed your mapping here...
with distinction.
You came under our consideration.
- I see.
- Mm-hmm.
Sirs, may I speak candidly?
Please.
My survey work was long ago.
And to be quite honest,
I was rather hoping for a position
where I might see a fair bit of action.
Major.
This is far more than just survey work!
This is exploration in the jungle.
The environment's brutally difficult.
Terrible disease.
Murderous savages.
The journey may well mean your life.
At the very least,
you will be gone for several years.
But were you to succeed,
such an undertaking
could earn you soldierly decoration.
And...
even reclaim your family name.
You know we knew your father.
Did you?
Yes.
I did not.
Terrible thing.
Man's love of drink and gaming.
But as I say, success in this venture
could change your lot...
considerably.
How come I've never seen
a plain change color?
Like that.
Does it look big, like a big brain?
It looks round.
- It looks round in that doesn't it?
- It does.
Jack, will you go and play?
I want to talk to
your father for a minute.
Do you want to pick me a flower?
Uh... Ooh...
- Shall I throw the ball for her?
- Yeah.
Ready?
Steady.
Throw it that way.
Throw it that far!
Oh, I knew it!
Hey, it's all wet.
He'll not know you when you return.
But you must go. I know that.
Indeed.
I have something to tell you.
I think I'm going to have another child.
I know I'm having another child.
Don't be sad.
I'm an independent woman.
I hadn't noticed.
Cheeky... Darling...
I know this is a sacrifice for all of us.
But it will be worth it.
I have no doubt.
Come here.
Cut you bloody throat!
...you're a dead man!
Who are you?
What do you want?
Henry Costin.
I replied to your ad eleven times.
I'm your aide-de-camp.
Mr. Costin?
What are my duties, sir?
We've been at sea a week.
Why are you just presenting yourself now?
I wanted to make sure
you were up to the task, sir.
Are you drunk, Mr. Costin?
No.
You could've fooled me.
Well...
I might have had a little.
I've got a...
letter of commendation.
They say I'm both skilled
at rifle and pistols...
and for bravery.
That's very impressive.
You have a family?
No, none at all.
I see; so nothing to shed.
I take it you do then.
Mr. Costin, I would like to be clear.
My reputation as a man
rests entirely on our success.
I think you shall find me
capable of every sacrifice.
Therefore, I must insist.
Oh! Right you are, sir.
We'll need all the fortitude you've got.
Understood.
We are explorers now.
I just received a cable.
We have new orders to map the Verde River,
- Please!
- find its source.
It forms a critical part of the border
between Bolivia and Brazil.
Our survey route is to begin
at a place called Fazenda Jacobina,
which does not appear to be on this map.
I know Facenda Jacobina.
It's an old rubber town.
It's meant to be quite enchanting.
Really?
You may not be
completely useless after all.
Time is of the essence now.
War's at stake.
So you, and I, and a couple of mules
are gonna stop a war?
Well then you and I...
are going to have to
depend on each other.
Neither of us will survive this alone.
Right you are.
What's that you're reading?
Poem, from my wife, by Kipling.
It's called "The Explorer."
And what?
Would you like to hear it?
It'll be a long way
until we reach Amazonia.
Be my guest.
"'There's no sense in going further;
it's the edge of cultivation, '
So they said, and I believed it;
broke my land and sowed my crop;
Built my barns and strung my fences..."
"...in the little border station
Tucked away below the foothills
where the trails run out and stop.
Till a voice, as bad as Conscience,
rang interminable changes
On one everlasting Whisper
day and night repeated; so:
'Something hidden.
Go and find it.
Go and look behind the Ranges;
Something lost behind the Ranges.
Lost and waiting for you.
Go!"'
Twenty-nine degrees.
Sixteen minutes south of the equator.
Twenty-nine.
Sixt...
Sixteen.
Rather deadly looking snake here.
We might be a little bit
too English for this jungle.
Strangers in a strange land.
Major Fawcett.
Is that you?
- Yes.
- Welcome to Fazenda Jacobina.
Lance Corporal Manley, sir,
liaison to the government of Japanese...
You start on ceremony.
A simple handshake will suffice.
This is Mr. Costin.
I hate to be the bearer of bad news,
but I have received a telegram
from the border commission.
Go on.
They strongly advise you to...
abort the mission.
It's become far too dangerous.
- They've already fired...
- Where are the government offices?
Sir...
Government, sir?
I'm afraid you left government behind
a long time ago.
In that case, you'd better
send them a telegram.
Informing them that
we will not stand down,
and we shall proceed as planned.
How quickly can you
find us an lndian guide?
Well, I...
I had an lndian guide sir, but...
But what happened to him?
What? Was he afraid of a little hard work?
Not quite, sir.
It's out of my hands now.
You need to speak to Baron De Gondoriz.
He runs the rubber company here.
Good evening, Baron.
Thank you for seeing us.
We are from the British Army.
We're to be venturing up the Rio Verde,
and find ourselves in need
of some of your men.
In exchange, I promise very favorable
treatment from my country.
Keep him chained up.
He can't be trusted.
He needs a good beatin'
every now and again.
Por favor.
You goin' up river, are you?
Yes.
We're surveying.
Well...
Ain't nobody comes back from up there.
Ever.
Is this slave good enough for you?
Yes.
Do you speak English?
He understands.
We taught him.
What will you take for him?
And any four men of his choosing?
It offends you to negotiate with me.
- No, not at all.
- Please.
Do not embarrass yourself.
You come here to make maps.
Why is that?
So that there may be peace.
What is peace?
Peace means my business would flourish.
I would flourish.
Peace...
means only that nothing will change.
I will help you.
Because you will make sure
that nothing will change.
I forgot to give you this, Major.
It came directly here
while you were surveying.
Can you show me how far the river goes?
Muy bien.
We've three full rafts,
four horses.
This our party?
Bloody desperate lot you've got us.
They're as dependable as any
that can be found here, Mr. Costin.
We're the only ones who will pay them.
Lot will do twelve hours a day; no less.
The river will be our home
for the next two years.
We shall not fail.
Mankind awaits our discoveries.
Have you ever seen a land
Like old El Dorado
Of gold and of silver,
Of gold and of silver
Have you ever seen a land
Like old El Dorado
Of gold and of silver,
And silver and gold
I can see the fish,
but I can't catch them.
Nothing again.
I don't understand.
The river is deep here.
There is plenty of fish.
It's a desert.
A green desert.
All right, pull it in.
Try again further up.
Major Fawcett.
What on earth is she doing
all the way out here?
She's come to load rubber, no doubt.
Or maybe she's looking
for the gold at El Dorado.
It's German.
The trunk says "Hamburg."
Someone aboard.
Hey!
Are you German?
Cosin! The water!
Get out of the water!
Where's Fawcett? Fawcett!
It's nothing.
Are we close?
Even the lndian's gone mad now.
He was talking to me
about gold cities today.
Like a little child.
He thinks we are conquistadors
to be led to our death.
Well, the lndian seemed
a bit mad to begin with.
I'd like you to read this
to me if you can.
If we are to meet our end here,
what difference does it make?
Afraid it would be quite unbearable,
for me to read it myself.
Feel free to summarize.
Right you are, sir.
Your wife has moved the family to Devon.
She's given birth to a boy named Brian.
Your oldest boy, Jack,
is excelling in all ways, she says.
I see my son's face
in my dreams now.
What kind of fool am I,
to leave my family for this place?
What did you hope to achieve out here?
I don't know.
All we have left now is to get
to the source of the river.
Mr. Costin.
Major.
Food gone.
Jesus Christ, we are going
die from hungry.
One piece.
Give me that!
Control yourselves!
We are not savages.
We're leaving our bones here, Major.
And for what?
A map?
Are you gonna forget that
we're not making it back without any food?
Have you ever thought about that?
Well, we're here starving to death.
We're not even looking for gold.
Let's have at it then.
Ah! My ear!
My ear!
- My ear!
- Next one'll be up your ass.
Thank you, Mr. Costin.
Woo!
No one's ever been here before me!
No one! Ever!
We made it!
Woo!
The first! We're the first!
Major.
Major, we've lost the lndian.
He's run off.
He got us here.
My last reading.
- Am I dreaming this?
- No. I see it too.
Please.
It's our only chance.
Must have.
Thank God.
Couldn't have done that
better myself, sir.
What is it, chief?
It's pottery.
From the ground.
Look it's all over.
Look at this.
They're ancient.
Christ. He was right.
The lndian was right.
When he said no one had been here before.
I think he meant no white man, Mr. Costin.
I think he meant no white man.
We thought the lndian mad.
There must've been dwellings here.
Thank God that boar's
more meat on it than we do.
All right, easy, easy, easy.
The exit from hell
is always difficult, Mr. Costin.
But we will get back.
The world will know what we've found here.
We have to keep going!
Thank you. Thank you.
Major Fawcett, you are
England's bravest explorer.
Thank you, sir.
Your son.
This must be Brian.
And here's Jack.
Are you my father?
I am, indeed, son.
Come. Give me a hug.
Let's go home.
Thank you all.
Percy, come. Meet our host,
Mr. James Murray.
He's very anxious to meet you.
A person of considerable resources.
He certainly has a beautiful home.
With, of course,
a reputation to match.
Ah, Mr. Murray.
Major Fawcett, I see you down there.
Welcome... to the inner circle.
Thank, Mr. Murray.
- Mrs. Fawcett.
- Good evening.
Percy, they're all so excited
to hear your speech to the RGS.
Listen to them, will you?
They're all talking about your mission.
Extraordinary.
I'm just honored to be here, sir.
I read your article
in The Times this morning
about the slave trade
in the Americas. It's uh...
You're an enlightened man.
Poor savages.
Native does deserve our sympathy.
Yes.
I think we have only
just scratched the surface of Amazonia.
Most certainly.
I was, um...
Well, I'm a biologist, but I'm also
somewhat of an explorer.
I was second in command under
Shackleton in the Antarctica.
Did you know that?
I don't think there's anyone here
who's not well aware
of your accomplishments, Mr. Murray.
Here, here.
You have distinguished
yourself with great bravery.
I know what these expeditions require.
Well, it's been my lifelong ambition to...
go to the Amazon, you know?
I must say, I hope that the RGS
continues its pursuits,
but I...
I have come to believe that mapmaking
should be a secondary interest.
Really?
I witnessed several
archaeological discoveries
that I believe may have
enormous significance.
- Such as?
- Pottery in the jungle.
Where no white man
has ever been before.
My friend, a word in your ear, please.
Your exploits have opened
every door for you.
I would suggest keeping
such findings to yourself.
Mm-hmm.
It is one thing to defend
the primitive jungle men.
It is quite another to elevate
their capacity beyond reason.
I mean, no one here would dispute
that you believed what you saw, but...
such a trip is very hard on the mind;
very hard, indeed.
Mr. Keltie.
I think you should find
my mind perfectly fit.
And still open, thank heavens.
- Good afternoon, gentlemen.
- Good afternoon.
I would like to introduce
one of our brothers
whose achievements are now known to you
and not inconsiderable.
Major Percy Fawcett.
Thank you, sir.
By rights, I should be with my husband.
It's men only I'm afraid, madam.
My esteemed colleagues,
it is now my firm belief
that Amazonia is far more
than the green desert
which many of us had supposed.
I am proposing that Amazonia...
contain a hidden civilization
One that may well
predate our own.
Major Fawcett!
I am Mr. William Barkley of Bedford,
and I have been to South America.
Please, Mr. Barkley, I'm sure we'd all
be thrilled to hear about your holiday.
But we are currently
discussing exploration.
Now to be clear.
Are you insisting on
mythical kingdoms of gold?
Now, those fantasies
lured the conquistadors
to their destruction.
Sir, it was the conquistadors and we
who have been destroying Amazonia.
I have seen, with my own eyes,
evidence of their civilization.
And I assure you, sir, it is real.
Perhaps it is too difficult
for some of you to admit.
We, who have been steeped
in the bigotry of the church for so long,
cannot give much credence
to an older civilization.
Particularly one created
by a race the white man
has so brutally condemned
to slavery and death.
Are you insisting that these savages,
they're our equals?
I do not know, Mr. Barkley,
but I intend to find out.
What?! Savages
in Westminster Abbey?
Hence, your disrespect, sir!
But what is at stake?
If we may find a city...
where one was considered
impossible to exist...
It may well write a whole
new chapter in human history.
Yes! Yes!
Consider my evidence.
I have archaeological finds.
Antiquities as sophisticated as
any in Asia or Europe...
in the middle of the jungle!
Pots and pans!
Pans! Pots and pans!
- Settle down, children! Settle down!
- Ooh...
After my return from the jungle,
I have examined a single document;
dating from the conquistadors, Mr Barkley!
It states explicitly
the discovery of a lost city.
Uncovered in Trinity College, Dublin,
this week by my lovely wife.
W ritten by a Portuguese soldier
in 1753, and I quote,
"We came upon the ruins of
an ancient city bedecked with gold.
Roads...
Temples...
Ancient symbols...
What? El Dorado?
No, gentlemen!
- I call it "Zed."
- Zed?
The ultimate piece of the human puzzle!
It is there and we must find it!
Mr. Fawcett!
Mr. Fawcett, I say we return!
I say we go and find the glory!
What say you?
What I say, Mr. Murray...
is I accept that challenge!
Mr. Costin!
I see you seated there.
Will you return with us?
Mr. Fawcett.
That jungle is hell, but...
one kind of likes it.
We shall return!
And we shall find the glory!
I have such high hopes, Cheeky.
With this journey, we may be able
to tear down their
narrowminded convictions.
I do believe I am quite ready
to accompany on your next journey.
What do you mean?
The children will be
back in school by then.
And I have learned to read the stars...
and navigate.
I've become very well versed
in the history of the region.
After all, it is I who found the document.
I know, darling.
But that would be impossible.
It's not a place at all for a woman.
"Not a place for a woman"?
Yes.
We believe firmly
in the equality between us.
In equality, yes,
but in mind, not in body.
Ah.
The rigor of such a trip would be
beyond your imagination.
I believe it is generally acknowledged
that the pain a woman experiences
during childbirth far exceeds
anything a man must endure.
- This is not about childbirth.
- Oh, what would you know of childbirth?
Have you witnessed two minutes of it,
let alone endured it?
The jungle...
is about years of practice...
training, the art of soldiering.
I have that.
It is about maggots in your skin.
It is about deadly snakes
and disease that make you vomit blood.
You could not bear it.
And I could not bear that either.
Somehow I managed to bear the dangers
you faced the years you were gone.
This way me might be together
for some of our lives!
You are my wife!
I need you here.
Oh, God.
Not as a tentmate
in need of constant care.
And in this fantasy of yours,
what happens to the children?
Please, try to be reasonable.
You will throw reasonable in my face.
Was it reasonable to stay here
and struggle to provide
for the children while you
wandered the jungle?
No. You have given no thought,
not on thought, to my
aspirations as a woman.
Have you thought about that?
Men and women have performed
their roles since the beginning of time!
It is the cornerstone
of our civilization.
I must say, I did expect more
understanding from you,
and I am disgraced
- by your ignorant posture!
- Mother!
It's all right, darling.
I'm sorry we were shouting.
- Run along I'll come in...
- Mother, please don't fight!
It's all right, Jack. Go.
121 miles
to Oviedo's last marking.
You should put some grease on that.
Will do.
Where's Mr. Murray?
He's bringing up the rear, chief.
Mr. Murray!
Yes?
How are you managing?
I am managing well, thank you.
My pack is just a little heavy it seems,
Perhaps I shall...
rid myself of the unnecessary
accoutrements, yes?
I wouldn't do that if I were you.
You don't want to be ill-equipped
for the journey ahead.
Well, yes.
However...
an awful lot of this...
scientific equipment seems
to be slowing us down.
When we reach the river then,
but you must keep one
spare set of clothing.
And, of course, your mattress.
I believe I shall go
naked as Adam in this...
infernal heat.
What a site that would be.
Let's keep going.
That bugger wishes he was
back on the South Pole.
He'll pull his weight soon enough.
Don't worry.
Should we treat ourselves
to the mail, gentlemen?
We've still got the sack
from San Carlos.
You've got two from
your wife and son, Major.
There's been a major discovery in Peru.
Oh, and an American,
Hiram Bingham, he's found the lost city
in the lndies, Machu Picchu.
He says that Dr. Hamilton Rice
is hot on his trail.
Seems we're in a race
with the Americans now.
They're after a bit of our prestige.
It's too far north.
Mm.
Still... Proves there's much to be found.
We've lost the other boat.
Savages!
- Arm yourselves!
- No! Hold your fire.
Everyone out of the boat.
Take cover!
Mr. Manley!
Get your concertina.
My concertina, sir?
Yes, do it now!
Play "Soldiers of the Queen"!
Come on!
Mr. Costin, come and sing with me.
Come!
Are you ready?
And!
We're soldiers of the Queen, my lads
Who've been my lads,
Who've seen my lads
In the fight for England's glory, lads
The England's soldiers of the Queen!
- Amigos.
- Hola.
Mano, mano, mano.
Amigos!
Mano, mano, mano!
Amigo!
Boys! Point!
If the red man attacks.
You rally to me at all costs.
Rally to me at all costs.
Oh, good God.
We are safe.
The chief has invited us to be his guests.
You all right?
This is a tribe of cannibals.
I know. I know.
The chief explained it's
a dead member of their tribe.
His spirit will enter them if they eat it.
We must attempt to engage.
They may have critical information
about our destination.
I... I refuse this madness.
I refuse it.
Men, come with me... Come.
Boys, we have to get back to that boat.
Costin.
Sí.
Gracias.
He's heard rumors of a city,
but he's not sure.
He said further up the river he thinks
there will be people who can help us.
All right, then.
Gracias, amigo.
- Comida?
- Food?
Comida?
- Uh...
- Comida. Sí, gracias.
To you.
That is remarkable.
That substance
only stuns the fish.
They don't kill more than
what they have to.
Remarkable.
These so-called savages
have cultivated the jungle.
Where no one thought it could be done.
We've been so...
arrogant and contemptuous.
I no less than others.
Look how it's all laid out.
It's mathematical in its precision.
Well, it's what you've been saying.
Imagine what Z must be like.
Well, the canoe's useless now.
We'll have to use the raft.
We leave at sunrise.
Chief.
Chief!
Think I found him.
Hello, old sport.
I appear to have gotten myself lost.
Thank God you're all alive.
I had assumed that you'd been
cannibalized by those savages.
Look at my leg. I have a nasty wound.
You'll be looked after. Come.
- No.
- We must keep moving.
I think I have a bit of a fever coming on.
Manley, help me clean all of this up.
This was in my bag.
It was a gift from my wife and children
for all of us to share.
I know. I was just very...
hungry.
I'm a little bit dead. If you don't mind
I'm going to rest for a little...
while longer.
You have no right to be tired.
My own children, at their tender ages,
could be counted on more than you.
And I could be home... with them.
And yet, I am here with you
to attempt great things.
Have you water please?
You'll get water when we get to the raft.
Mr. Manley, help me get him on his feet.
Stay where you are, Mr. Murray.
It's essential we keep the balance.
Murray!
Stay down!
Stay down, God damn you!
Murray, stay low to the ground!
Swim to shore!
We'll bank further down!
Let go! Swim to shore!
- Let go!
- No!
You're tipping the raft!
We're losing supplies! God damn you!
I said let go, you pigheaded weakling!
Let go!
Mr. Manley, help me!
Help me get to shore!
- Shut up.
- Chief!
We've lost a third of our rations.
- I was drowning!
- There was no chance of that!
And this after you stole our food!
I suppose I should have starved myself.
That would have been the honorable
course of action, wouldn't it?
Isn't that what you want?
You want me to die.
I... Please slow down.
Give a dying man a chance.
I just want to be dead.
...young upstart and his
vulgar quest for glory.
Like a Judas...
he has delivered me...
into this...
jungle.
Well, we're two weeks behind...
according to the sextant and the charts.
Chief.
This leg wound of his
is becoming more infected.
Mr. Murray's got blood poisoning now.
I noticed.
You think he'll make it?
Slim chance.
He is not worth kissing...
the hem of your garment.
As I...
am not worthy of yours.
Give me strength to survive.
He is not worthy.
No. No.
Yes? What is it?
There are mining encampments
south of us on the river.
In the morning, you'll be
on your way to them.
I'm going to give you our last horse
with what supplies I can spare
and an lndian to guide you.
I have a family at home.
I cannot allow you to jeopardize
the welfare of the entire crew.
You don't give a wit about me.
Or about any of the party.
You don't even care about going home.
You only care...
about your lost...
city.
I'm going to see
if there's a path through!
Chief!
I saw it!
We're getting close!
Keep going!
We need to go back.
Guy's a bloody bastard!
Cost us our last horse!
And this is how he repays us.
Rations ruined!
Murray's covered them in oil!
Look at it!
We must turn back.
There is no turning back.
We are right here!
We've nothing to show for our efforts.
- No evidence...
- What do we go on with?
With what we have on our backs,
we'll last a week at most!
It's over, Percy!
To be sent to the RGS:
Mr. James Murray was forced
to separate from our expedition
to seek medical attention.
His location is currently unknown,
and he has most likely perished.
The rest of the group
shall arrive back in England
as soon as is possible.
It looks like a war with France.
Better all get home or
we'll miss our chance to fight.
Please send that immediately.
Yes, sir.
Chase it. Go on! Go on, Bri.
That is Joan,
as you might have guessed.
Oh, Jack!
Your daughter.
Sorry! I didn't mean to do that.
Beautiful child.
Hello, Joan.
- I'll fetch the boys.
- No.
Let them finish.
When they're done, send them in.
It should be I who tells them
what has happened.
You're real.
Three, two, one... Go!
How much they've grown.
You've done beautifully with them.
My ball!
Hey, come on!
Gentlemen, welcome to our new home.
Thank you for coming
at such short notice.
Mr. John. Gentlemen.
Please, will you step this way?
- Congratulations on your knighthood.
- Ah, thank you.
I think that you know everybody here.
Mr. James Murray arrived
in London just this morning.
We felt it critical to assemble
as soon as possible.
Congratulations on your safe return.
It's a remarkable effort.
Mr. Murray contends
that you abandoned him.
Is this correct?
No. It is not.
He was given money and food.
It was an unfortunate but necessary
maneuver in order to save lives.
Sir George.
We spent all our time.
Playing around in the mud
with the savages.
I never saw any evidence of a lost city.
You were the reason we did not reach
our destination, Mr. Murray.
You poured paraffin on all our supplies.
I reject that accusation, Sir John.
I cannot tolerate any further insult
from this young man.
I... have retained counsel
and I will proceed accordingly.
And as for his lackeys,
they are swine and not to be trusted.
You should've been beaten in the jungle
like the dog that you are.
Please gentlemen.
Our nation is now at war.
It ill becomes us to indulge
personal conflicts.
I earnestly beseech you
to come to an understanding.
Very well.
I most generously offer that...
If you are willing
to apologize to me here
in front of this entire society,
I will consider withdrawing my claims
against the RGS and yourself,
with certain conditions, of course.
Well, Major.
Will you apologize?
For the general good...
I am prepared to reconcile.
Thank you.
I will, of course, need to hear
Mr. Murray's conditions.
On the day that I agreed
to join you on your mission
and allowed your star to enter my sphere,
your wife was present
to witness your ascent.
My only condition is that
she again be present
to witness your acknowledgement
of the wrongs...
that you have done to me.
Sir.
Mr. Murray.
The last time I saw you, I was putting you
on the only remaining horse,
giving you far more
than your share of our food.
The men begged me
to leave you where you lay,
but I could not do that.
And as a consequence, I saved your life.
You saved my life?
You saved my...
I demand an apology right now.
You will apologize to me.
I will apologize...
Thank you.
...to my men.
I'm sorry I ever considered Mr. Murray
worthy of your company.
And as I ever mistook
a man's rank for his medal,
but I shall not make that mistake again.
What your purpose is
in this ambush, I cannot say.
But you need fear
no more embarrassment from me.
I hereby resign from this institution,
and I shall proceed on my own.
No, p-please, Major! Please!
This is outrageous!
Please, you must reconsider!
Magnus!
I shall teach him.
What's wrong?
You've received a letter.
All former officers not currently posted,
must send their names to the war office.
Let us hope it is a brief conflict.
Talk to the boys.
Don't be concerned, my love.
I've spent a whole life training for this.
Hello, boy.
Father.
Jack.
Brian.
Has Harvey been walked?
- Um, no, not yet.
- All right.
I'll do it.
Father, you will not have
to leave again, will you?
To fight?
If the reports are true,
I'm afraid I must.
Father, you've only just returned.
It's... it's hardly fair.
I'm obligated to serve.
Obligated.
What of your obligation to mother?
And to us?
Your family.
The... the family that you've chosen
to abandon for so many years.
Jack.
How dare you talk to me like that.
How dare... How dare you, father...
You do not think of us.
You think of lndians,
or Germans, or any other path
to glory that you can find.
Jack, stop it! That's enough!
Mother, I will not stop.
You have returned a failure.
The papers are full of it.
And you want to abandon us again?
- It's contemptuous...
- Enough!
Percy...
I hate him.
Oh, Jack.
Everything your father has done,
since the day you came into this world,
has been to better your life.
And for your sake, I hope, one day,
you will come regret
the things you just said to him.
Please, just go.
Please. Please, just go.
Well, what do you know, chief?
It appears our old friend,
Mr. James Murray,
is not so powerful after all.
Why do you say that?
The bastard's gone off on an
Artic expedition with Canadians and...
mutinied.
He's not been heard from since.
Take a look.
I'm sure his magnificent skills
will bring him back safely.
Someone should warn the Eskimos
that Mr. Murray is on the prowl.
All right, Major.
Mr. Costin!
Despite the medium of fine
spiritualistic skills of the Russians.
Come! She'll read your fortune.
I can't believe he smuggled her in here.
Welcome to the world beyond.
- Sorry, chap. Come on.
- That's enough. It's the Major's turn.
Move on. I'm with him.
Let's see the Major's fortune.
We will be in battle soon, madam.
Any spiritual aid would be
greatly appreciated.
You are the explorer?
I was.
As were these fine men,
who have transferred here
so we could all be together.
Give me your hand.
Feel my hand.
Listen to my voice.
Is it... a forest?
You dream to be in a forest.
I wish to find a lost city.
Can you...
see yourself there now?
Try to picture it in your mind.
Yes.
I can see it.
You cannot blind yourself to this vision.
What you seek...
is far greater...
than you ever imagined.
A vast land bejeweled with peoples.
Your soul will never be quiet
until you find this new place.
It is your destiny.
With it, you will illuminate the world.
The whole world has set itself afire.
I must look elsewhere to quench the blaze.
Good morning, gentlemen.
- Sir.
- Good morning, sir.
When I was younger,
I ventured all for king and country,
for place and rank.
I believed that to be
the makings of a man.
But my travels have taught me,
such ambitions
are mere phantoms.
I know in our hearts,
we fight for our loves ones, as we should.
But they are not here.
So instead let us fight for each other.
Good luck.
And may God be with all of you.
And fuck the bloody bush!
Well said, Mr. Costin!
Right men! Into positions!
Take down the gunner!
Take down the gunner up ahead!
Come on!
Come on! Keep going!
Come on! Push forward!
Gas!
Manley! Gas!
Darling, it is I.
We are here.
The children are here.
- Nina.
- Yes, my darling.
Come.
That is Joan.
Let him feel your face. Come along.
See?
Brian.
Where's Jack?
Father, I'm here.
I thought I had died.
Oh, no.
You were exposed to chlorine gas.
Your eyes were affected,
but they are very confident
that your sight shall return.
The rest of the men?
- Costin?
- Mr. Costin was unharmed.
You'll brigade suffered many losses,
but it was the only one
that did not retreat.
Thanks to you bravery, they are raising
your rank to Lieutenant Colonel.
Lieutenant Colonel?
After all that he has done?
Jack.
I think I was dreaming...
about Amazonia.
I...
I'm afraid you may never be able
to return to your jungle.
I am sorry.
Shh, my darling.
Shh. Rest.
All will be well.
I must go back.
But love...
You cannot think
of these things right now.
I'm going to take
the children for some air.
Come along.
Father.
Jack.
America has quite
a fascination with you.
Our readers have been asking
where you've been since the war.
I'm grateful for their interest.
You may tell your readers
I've recovered from my wounds
and have been adapting to home life.
Your pursuits in South America
have led to a tremendous interest
in exploration in the Unites States.
There have been many new voyages planned.
Have there?
Yes, Dr. Hamilton Rice leaves for Brazil
soon with radio and airplanes.
He's taking a large
and very well-armed party.
Well, let us hope that Dr. Rice,
with all his arms,
does not destroy what he
wishes to discover.
- Allow me to ask you a question.
- Yes, sir.
How did you find us here?
Well, your son, Colonel.
He wrote us a letter.
Didn't he tell you?
Good shot, Jack.
Thank you, father.
Getting quite expert with that rifle.
Practice makes perfect, you know?
I have something for you.
This was given to me
by a Guaraní lndian chief.
Great man.
It's yours now.
Thank you.
It must've been a glorious day.
You still believe in Z, do you not?
That we underestimated the lndian.
That is why we should go back.
You and I, together.
We could find the city once and for all.
Jack.
I'm an old bastard now.
Father, you and I, we both know it.
You easily outmatch my strengths.
And now you can see as clear as day again.
There is nothing stopping us.
Father.
The Americans will
venture there with their guns.
And then we must pray that they
do not destroy the lndian.
We must find it before they do.
I want nothing more than
to go with you, Father.
It's everything you've always wanted.
You would have to consult
a higher authority.
I understand that it's dangerous,
But you've said so yourself
with everything that's happened in Europe,
it's not possible to choose
a safe passage through life.
So many men near my own age
did not return from the war.
And who is to say
it will not happen again?
It could, mother.
It could happen again.
By all accounts, I should be furious
because you've just...
You've just used my very own
words against me.
And how can I refute them?
They are my own.
Joan's been so annoying!
Bloody slapped me!
All right, Joan, don't slap him.
Thank you. Off! Go on!
She hit me around the face.
Brian, I'm in the middle
of a conversation!
Go and help you sister get some wood,
please, from the log pile now.
Now!
Fight your own battles!
Momma, please.
There is little doubt
that I would worry night and day
about my boys in the jungle.
But we have never let fear
determine our future.
That's all.
Mother, thank you.
Thank you, thank you, thank you.
- Father, this...
- Jack, Jack, Jack.
- We are not there yet.
- I know.
We'll have to raise
a great deal of money.
Of course, I understand. Yes.
Go on. Let me talk to your mother.
And training?
Well, of course,
I shall begin right away.
You and I, and Mr. Costin
I'm sure would love to join us.
Thank you, mother. Thank you.
What?
I'm just surprised you agreed so quickly.
What choice did I have?
It's his essential nature;
would be wrong to betray that.
Besides, you will be there to guide him.
Here they are, Chief.
Here's the last of my notebooks.
A map would be helpful.
Can I truly not persuade you to come?
We came so close, Henry.
Think of what it would mean...
To finally find it together.
Chief, I have a wife and child now.
My own children were
younger than yours is now
when we went on our first trip.
Can't say it was not a sacrifice.
But if you could see my boy now,
his vim and vigor,
I guarantee it would tear down
your resistance in an instant.
Would you like
some more brandy, sir?
Nope. Thank you, Nigel.
- For yourself, sir?
- No, thank you.
Chief, please don't
misunderstand me. I'm...
But it's something...
This search for Z...
I can no longer bear the cost.
You've come to doubt its existence?
No.
I only doubt Z could provide
all the answers you seek from it.
I wish you success, my dear friend.
This will be
no pampered expedition.
Top heavy missions get nowhere.
They linger on the fringe of civilization
and bask in publicity.
We will not.
We will be in the field for three years,
standing on our own two feet,
surviving by our wits.
Tribesmen shall take our dispatchers
to be delivered for publication
as often as possible.
But who's going to finance
this latest journey of yours?
The money is generously being supplied
by a consortium of American newspapers
and Mr. John D. Rockefeller, Jr.
Are you aware The Royal
Geographical Society
has just offered to help
with the financing?
I'm glad to see our nation
is not to be left behind.
I would like now to introduce
my companion for this historic expedition,
my own son, Mr. Jack Fawcett.
He is a man of great discipline
and keenest muscle.
Well, we couldn't very well be shamed
by the Americans now could we?
No, but I am proud to say
that we did finally
manage to meet them halfway.
Sir George, God rest his soul,
always bore you great affection.
But I admit my error in not accepting
your beliefs long ago.
Oh.
All that matters now is the future.
Yes.
I have carried this
for the last twenty years.
When we reach Z,
I shall send it to you as a sign.
Just in case I decide not to come back.
Oh, nonsense, nonsense.
Oh, now we have something for you.
Mr. Barkley, please.
The society's highest honor,
the Founder's Gold Medal.
You are
truly deserving, Colonel.
- Truly.
- Indeed.
All the arrangements are made.
We leave for Portugal on the seventh,
and then we meet again in Brazil.
No one can best us now.
Remember, the code with the coordinates
is in my desk, and Mr. Costin
- has a copy in safekeeping.
- Yes, you've told me a thousand times.
Now run along or you'll miss your boat.
You're a man now; responsible
for you mother and sister's care.
It's a fine calling.
No less, perhaps even
more virtuous than ours.
All right?
Goodbye, father.
I shall indeed miss you as I always have.
- Look after your father for me.
- Of course, I will, of course.
- And have fun.
- Yes.
And be bold.
Goodbye, Joan.
Goodbye, father.
I love you.
On to Z then,
and to new history!
Goodbye, the boys!
Woo!
Forty million, father!
Paper says forty million people
are following our journey!
It's incredible!
It's wonderful.
How are you faring?
Never felt better.
Neither have I.
We'll be on the river soon,
and if we're lucky to see an opera.
This is where they sang?
It's astonishing.
It's just a pity you
couldn't see it intact.
Yes.
The jungle is
restoring the balance.
Dearest Cheeky,
This is the last letter
you shall receive until we reach Z.
The rest of our party is returning home.
Jack is acquitting himself marvelously.
Today we reached a tribe of Indians
who told us of a cave entirely unknown
to anyone outside of their clan...
They tell of an enormous rock there,
covered with painted pictures
of men and horses.
It's location is, perhaps,
the gateway to Z...
The chief has been
very generous to us here,
and he reminds me, yet again,
that we are all made of the same clay...
I expect we will be in touch
with the old civilization within months.
Thereafter, our fate is
in the lap of the gods.
You need have no fear of any failure.
Stop it! Stop it! Stop!
Stay calm.
I know the approach just keep going.
Amigos.
All right, come on back the way we came.
Slowly, slowly, don't rush.
Into the brush! Go!
Jack!
I'm all right. I'm all right.
No, Jack! Keep going! Keep going!
Be brave.
Nothing will happen to us
that is not our destiny.
We're going to die.
We're going
to die here today.
So much of life is a mystery, my boy.
We know so little of this world.
But you and I have made a journey that
other men cannot even imagine.
And this has given
understanding to our hearts.
I love you, father.
I love you, son.
A toast, shall we?
Actually, Lord Bernard, I wanted...
I wanted to read something if I could.
Now I'm in for it.
It's something I wrote in the event
that I did not survive the birth.
"My Percy, I know your first
instinct will be to grieve,
but I adjure you rather
to consider our son
and the love you must show him.
I knew it would be a boy.
Always teach him to dream,
to seek the unknown,
to look for what is beautiful
is its own reward.
And I beg you to remember
those words so easy to forget:
A man's reach...
should exceed his grasp,
or what's a Heaven for?
My dearest love, forever."
A man came to see me yesterday.
He was from Brazil.
He has seen...
Jack and Percy...
living with the lndians.
He says they claim...
to have reached Z.
My dear, it's... it's...
It's been years.
We've sent almost 100 men to look
for your husband and your son, and...
I fear we have to accept the inevitable.
Sir John, I confess that the brutal
wear and tear is great,
and I suffer with heart and soul.
It has taken...
all my strength of will
to push horrors from my mind,
but I beg you...
not to lose confidence.
I cannot...
doubt...
after so many years of sacrifice.
It has become...
my own life's work.
The Brazilian gave me this to give to you.
He said Percy told him
you would understand.
I have trained myself
to be impartial to evidence, but surely...
Surely, this is a sign.
Yes.
I will have it examined.
Thank you.
That is all I can ask.
Please rate this subtitle at www.osdb.link/s7xj
Help other users to choose the best subtitles