Created and Encoded by --  Bokutox -- of  www.YIFY-TORRENTS.com. The Best 720p/1080p/3d movies with the lowest file size on the internet.
This is not a drill, soldier.
We clear on that?
This is a live project.
You're a go.
Training is over.
I'm okay. It's fine.
Just a headache.
You're burning up.
It's okay.
Just a headache.
Anything new?  No.
It's just bits and pieces.
I can hear Conklin's voice,
and there's that photograph, but ...
I just can't stay with it.
But you're sure it's not
just a bad dream? It happened.
It was a mission.
And I was there.
You should write it down.
Two years we're scribbling in that notebook ?
It hasn't been two years.
It's always bad, and now it's just
the same thing over and over again.
But that's why we write it down. Because
sooner or later, you remember something good.
I do remember something good.
All the time.
- I want one final go around.
- All teams listen up.
- We are standing by for final green.
- Survey Two, I need to know when you've got eyes.
- This is Survey Two. I have eyes.
- Copy that.
Survey One, this is Hub.
Do you have visual contact?
Hub, this is Survey One.
Mobile One is in motion.
Survey Three, that is good.
- Hub.
- Director Marshall from Langley.
- Langley.
- Stand by, please.
- Martin?
- I'm here. So is Donnie and Jack Weller.
We understand you're using
the full allocation for this buy.
It's where we came out.
It's a lot of money, Pam.
For a thief, a mole. If it does nothing more
than narrow the list of suspects, it's a bargain at 10 times the price.
Hub, this is Survey Two.
Escort is breaking off ...
Mobile One is entering the building.
Gentlemen, I have the seller on-site and in play.
Quite frankly, there's nothing much more to discuss.
- All right, Pam. Your call.
- Go.
- We're on.
- Audio contact only.
Switching to channel one now.
Copy that. It's affirmative.
Hub, Mobile One and seller
have entered the office.
Copy that.
This is everything?
Those were shots.
Survey One, come in. Survey One, I need to know
what happened. What do you see?
- Do you see any shadows? I see nothing.
- What is your visual?
- Get some men in there. Get some men in there right now.
- Pull it up, Kurt.
Eye contact. I don't care if it's visual ?
Mobile One, can you copy, please?
- Are you there, Mobile One?
- I'm sorry.
What do you see?
... Petroleum Association's annual
conference here in Berlin ...
is Pekos Oil chief executive officer
Yuri Gretkov.
In just six years, Gretkov has turned
Pekos into an oil empire, which in turn ?
He's become one of
the wealthiest men in Russia ...
after consolidating drilling rights
in the Caspian Sea and gaining control of one of the wo ?
How much?
Good morning, sir.
Morning.
He is my friend.
There's been a death in the family.
I wonder if you've seen him.
- Hey.
- Get in.
- What's wrong?
- We're blown.
How?
We pushed it. We got lazy.
Idiot!
All right. That's twice now
I've seen the same guy.
I saw him in town.
He was at the telegraph office.
Are you sure?
How-How can you be sure? It's just wrong.
The guy, the car he's driving,
what he's wearing ? it's just wrong.
Look, Jason, let's stay calm.
It could be anybody. This is real.
This is real. That's him.
That's him right there.
Get your head down.
Silver Hyundai. Get your head down.
How far is he?
How far?
A hundred meters.
Here, take the wheel.
You're gonna drive.
Switch.
Just head to the bridge.
- Turn here. Cut through the field.
- Hang on.
All right, you keep going to the shack.
I'll meet you there in one hour.
I'm gonna bail out on the other side of this
bridge. It's the only way he can follow us.
What if it's not who you think it is?
It's them. It's Treadstone.
Jason, don't do it.
Look, Marie, I warned 'em.
I don't want you to do it.
I told them what would happen if they didn't leave us alone.
- It's never gonna be over like this.
I don't want ?  We don't have a choice.
Yes, you do.
Thank you.
Two of these explosive charges
placed on the power lines, and one of them failed.
The fingerprints from the one
that didn't go off.
- And the Germans can't match it?
- No. Nobody's got it.
We checked out every database
we could access. But we're hooked into Langley now.
Run it.
Okay.
What the hell's Treadstone?
All right. Get me a flight.
We're going to Langley.
Two men dead, three million in cash gone,
no Neski files,
and all very public.
This is still a clandestine agency, no?
I don't view this event
as a failure.
You call it a success?
We have a lead.
A fingerprint left by the assassin.
He's one of us.
- Who is it?
- What can you tell me about Treadstone?
Treadstone?
It's where the trail dead-ends.
If you want an answer,
you're going to have to give me ...
a level-five S.C.I. access.
We have a lead, Marty.
All right.
You've got your clearance.
But you're on
a very short leash.
And you'll give a full report
to the group. I wanna know where you're going with this.
Sir.
Ward?
Yes?
Pamela Landy.
Hey, Pam.
What can I do for you?
I was hoping you had some time for me.
Time for what?
- I'm free right now, actually.
- That sounds ominous. Let me check my schedule.
Excuse me. I need to, uh ?
Excuse me. Can I help you?
Yeah, I'm here to see Mr. Abbott.
Twenty minutes?
See ya.
Operation Treadstone.
Never heard of it.
That's not gonna fly. With all due respect, Pam,
I think you might've wandered past your pay grade.
That's a warrant from Director Marshall
granting me unrestricted access to ...
all personnel and materials
associated with Treadstone.
So, what are we looking at?
I wanna know about it.
Know about it?
It was a kill squad. Black-on-black.
We closed it down two years ago.
Nobody wants to know about Treadstone. Not around here.
So I think you better take this
back to Marty and let him know exactly what you're doing.
He does. I've been down to the archives.
I have the files, Ward.
- Let's talk about Conklin.
- What are you after, Pam?
You wanna fry me?
You want my desk. Is that it?
I wanna know what happened.
What happened?
Jason Bourne happened.
You got the files. Then let's cut the crap.
Conklin had these guys wound so tight,
they were bound to snap.
Bourne was his number-one.
The guy went for a job, screwed the op, never came back.
Conklin couldn't fix it,
couldn't find Bourne, couldn't adjust. It all went sideways.
So you had Conklin killed?
I mean, if we're cutting the crap.
I've given 30 years
and two marriages to this agency.
I've shoveled shit on four continents.
I'm due to retire next year.
But if you think I'm gonna sit here
and let you dangle me with this,
you can go to hell ... and Marshall too.
It had to be done.
- And Bourne? Where is he now?
- Dead in a ditch.
- Drunk in a barn Mogadishu. Who knows?
- I think I do.
I had a deal going down
in Berlin last week.
During the buy, both our case officer
and the seller were killed.
They were killed by Jason Bourne.
They're ready for us upstairs.
Seven years ago, $20 million of C.I.A. funds disappeared
during a wire transfer through Moscow.
In the investigation that followed,
we were contacted by a Russian politician, Vladimir Neski.
Neski claimed we had a leak
and that we'd been ripped off by one of our own.
And were we?
We never found out.
We were negotiating a meet
with Mr. Neski when he was killed.
- By who?
- His wife.
The case had gone cold until a month ago
when we founda source.
Another Russian in Berlin
who claimed to have access to the Neski murder files.
We thought we had
another bite at the apple.
Turns out the assassin
was one of our own ? Jason Bourne.
I know Treadstone's not
a very popular subject around here,
but we found some interesting things
when we dug a little deeper.
This is Conklin's personal computer.
His Treadstone files are bloated with code keys
and case files that he neither needed nor had clearance for.
Buried in the hard drive, we found a deleted file
with an account number to a bank in Zurich.
At the time of his death, he was sitting on a
personal account in the amount of $760,000.
You know what his budget was?
We were throwing money at him and asking him to keep it dark.
- It was his own account.
He was up to something. This is supposed to be definitive?
What's definitive is that
I just lost two people in Berlin. So what's your theory?
Conklin's reaching out from the grave
to protect his good name? The man is dead.
- No one's disputing that, Ward.
- For Christ's sake, Marty, you knew Conklin.
Does this scan? I mean, at all?
Cut to the chase, Pam.
I think that Bourne and Conklin
were in business together,
that Bourne's still involved
and that whatever information I was trying to buy in Berlin ...
was big enough to bring Bourne
out from hiding to kill again.
How's that scan?
Excuse me, sir,
but you're not gonna believe this.
Jason Bourne's passport
just popped up on the grid in Naples.
Okay. Contact Naples.
They need to know who they're dealing with.
Find out what kind of local assets
we have in place there.
Nah, it's nothing. Some guy's name
came up on the computer.
All right.
Mr. Bourne, I'm John Nevins.
I'm with the U.S. Consulate.
I just have a few questions for you.
You're coming out of Tangier.
Is that correct?
What's the, uh, nature
of your visit to Naples?
Look, I don't know what you did, and
I don't know who you're working for.
But I promise you this ?
you're gonna play ball
one way or the other.
This is Nevins.
This is Tom Cronin, C.I. Operations
Officer calling from Langley, Virginia.
- Do you have a Jason Bourne in custody?
- Yes, I do.
Listen, he's an agency priority target.
Call me back
as soon as he's secure. I understand.
He's been detained.
Here's the number.
He's being interrogated by
a field officer out of the consulate.
- Hello.
- This is Pamela Landy, C.I. supervisor.
Where do we stand?
I, uh, think he got away.
Damn it.
- Have you locked down the area?
- Locked it down? No. No.
This is, uh ? This is Italy.
They don't exactly lock down ?
- How long have you worked for the agency?
Me? For four years.
If you ever wanna make it to five, you're gonna listen to
me real close. Bourne is armed and extremely dangerous.
Last week in Berlin he assassinated two men ?
one a highly experienced field officer.
I want you to secure that area.
I want any evidence secured, and I want it done right now.
Is that clear?
Yes, sir ? ma'am.
I'm getting on a plane to Berlin
in 45 minutes, which means you're gonna call me back in 30.
And when I ask you where we stand,
I had better be impressed.
- Berlin?
- I already have a team in place there.
I doubt that Bourne's in Naples
ready to start a family.
- You have no idea what you're getting into.
- Do you have any idea?
From the minute he left Treadstone, he's killed and
eluded every single person that you've sent to find him.
You read a couple of files on Jason Bourne,
and that makes you an expert? This is my case, Ward.
Enough. I want you both
on that plane.
We are, all of us, going to do
what we were either too lazy or inept to do the last time around.
We're gonna find this son of a bitch
and take him down.
I 'm not having Jason Bourne
destroy any more of this agency.
- Is that definitive enough for you?
- Yes.
Jason Bourne is armed
and extremely dangerous.
Last week in Berlin he assassinated two men ?
one a highly experienced field officer.
I want that area ?
... he assassinated two men ?
one a highly experienced field officer.
I want that area secured.
I want any evidence secured, and I want it done right now ?
This is not a drill, soldier.
We clear on that?
You'd been working at Treadstone
for three years,
and your cover at the time was what?
That I was an American student in Paris.
And what exactly did your job
with Treadstone in Paris consist of?
I had two responsibilities.
One was to coordinate logistical operations.
The other was to monitor
the health of the agents.
Health, meaning what?
Their mental health.
- Because of what they had been through,
they were prone to a variety of problems. What kind?
Depression, anger,
compulsive behaviors.
They had physical symptoms.
Headaches, sensitivity to light.
- Amnesia?
- Before Bourne? No.
The plane's ready.
There's a car waiting for you.
- Good luck.
- No. You were his local contact.
You were with him the night Conklin died.
You're coming with us.
Langley pulled an image out of Naples.
It's uploading right now.
It's coming in now.
- I need clearance.
- He's not hiding, that's for sure.
- Why Naples? Why now?
- Could be random.
- Maybe he's running.
- On his own passport?
- What is he actually doing?
- He's making his first mistake.
It's not a mistake.
They don't make mistakes.
They don't do random.
There's always an objective.
Always a target.
The objective and targets
always came from us. Who's giving them to him now?
Scary version?
He is.
- I emptied it.
- It felt a little light.
Put it down.
- Front.
- Sorry. Old habits.
Use your teeth.
Ah.
Word in the ether was
you'd lost your memory.
You still should've moved.
- What do you want?
- Conklin.
He's dead.
Shot dead in Paris. Dead the night you walked out.
So who's running Treadstone now?
Nobody. They shut it down.
It's over. We're the last two.
If it's over,
then why are they still after me?
- I don't know.
- Ever heard the name Pamela Landy?
- I don't know who that is.
- Pamela Landy and Berlin. What's going on in Berlin?
I don't know.
Why would I lie?
I thought you were here to kill me.
What'd you do?
I'm sorry.
Did you call it in?
Get up. Come on.
You have a car out front?
The keys are in my coat pocket.
But we should ?
What?
Go out the back.
I have another car.
Pamela Landy.
Nein, mein Herr.
Danke.
Pamela Landy.
Nein.
Pamela Landy, bitte.
Ja.
Pamela Landy, please.
One moment, please.
Thank you.
I wanted to call a guest.
Pamela Landy.
Just one second, please.
Hello?
I'm sorry, sir. The phone's busy right now.
Just try later. Thank you.
Okay. Let's take a look at the timeline.
What's Bourne's objective?
Now, I wanna break this out
in boxes.
Naples outbound. Check everything.
Flights, trains, police reports. That's box one.
- Teddy, that's yours.
- Got it.
Box number two.
Call it "prior connections. '"
I want to rerun all Bourne's
Treadstone material. Every footstep.
Kim, box three.
I want to identify his method of travel.
Stay on the local cops.
We need a vehicle, a parking ticket, something.
Langley's offered to upload
any satellite imaging we need, so let's find a target for them.
Danny, box four. I need fresh eyes.
Review the buy where we lost the Neski files.
Timeline it with what we know about Bourne's movements.
Turn it upside down and see what we find.
Come on, guys. We ran this guy's life
with total control for all those years.We should be a step ahead of him.
You wanna go home?
Find Jason Bourne.
- Pamela Landy.
- This is Jason Bourne.
- Bourne? It's Bourne. We need 90 seconds
to triangulate his position.
What do you want?
Are you running Treadstone?
Treadstone was closed down
two years ago. You know that.
Then who's planning
the missions now?
There are no missions. It's over.
- Then what do you want with me?
- Berlin.
Have you forgotten
what happened in Berlin?
You killed two people, Bourne.
Neski ? Vladimir Neski ?
Vladimir Neski ?
Bourne?
I wanna come in.
- Okay. How do you wanna do it?
- We need 35 seconds.
- I need someone I know to bring me in.
- Who?
There was a girl in Paris.
She was part of the program.
She used to handle logistics.
Alexander Strasse, 30 minutes, under the World Clock.
Send her alone.
Give her your phone.
What if I can't find her?
It's easy.
She's standing right next to you.
- There's just so many areas ?
- It's a very simple layout.
Get the second quadrant.
Pull it out.
Where is it? Get the second quadrant, please.
Pull it all the way up.
Clock is right here ? Shit, he's
put her in the middle of everything.
This is a security nightmare.
There is no way we are going to get her covered ?
Call a Mayday into Berlin station.
We need snipers, D.O.D., whatever they've got.
No snipers. You put snipers
on the roof and it'll scare him off, and I need answers.
- You can't really believe he wants to come in.
- He knows something about the Neski case.
- I'm not gonna pass up this chance to find out what it is.
- Don't be a fool. Not when we're this close.
Are we talking about protecting Nicky
or killing Bourne?
- We're talking about killing Bourne.
- We're talking about the next dead body. It might be Nicky. It will be someone.
You're not hearing me.
Bourne dead gives me nothing.
Can I talk to you privately?
- What?
- I know how you're feeling.
You lost two men in Berlin
and you want it to mean something.
But nothing Bourne gives you
will bring your men back.
Nothing in those files
makes their sacrifice worthwhile. You have to let go.
We're professionals.
When an operation goes bad, we tie it off.
If there's something you're not telling me, I want it now before I send
that girl out there. Do you understand?
You talk about this stuff
like you read it in a book.
What do you want to do?
Put the snipers in place.
If things go bad, we take him out.
You got it.
Hub, this is Survey One.
We have a crowd moving in.
- It's some sort of protest march.
- I'm sorry. This is as close as I can get.
- Survey Two, can you get in any closer?
- Kurt, make sure the south end is covered.
Roger. Affirmative. Copy that.
Hello. There's a tram coming
towards you. Get on it.
- She's moving to the tram.
- Where's it going?
The tram is going
to Alexanderplatz Station.
Survey Five, I can't see him.
I don't see him.
Hub, this is Survey Two,
she's getting on a tram.
- She's getting on the tram.
- Zoom in on the tram.
- Bourne's on the tram.
- I don't think he's on the tram.
He's on the tram.
Send them in to follow.
Tell them to keep their distance.
Okay, Delta, let's go.
Get on it.
Come on. Let's go.
- Tell her to hurry.
- There's nothing on the south side.
Alexanderplatz Station,
25 seconds.
This is Survey Three. There's a lot of protesters here.
There's no way we can cover out there.
- Get her out of there.
- Go! Delta, move! Now!
- She's not here. She's gone.
- Goddamn it!
- They are not on the tram.
- He's one guy!
- Jason, please don't hurt me.
- What were my words?
I said leave me alone,
leave me out of it.
I did. I swear.
Jason, I told them that I believed you.
I'm gonna ask you
some simple questions.
You're gonna answer me honestly,
or I swear to God I'm gonna kill you.
- Delta, give me something.
- They're on it! They're on it!
Who's Pamela Landy?
- She's a task force chief.
- Is she running Treadstone?
No, she's the deputy director.
Why is she trying to kill me?
Last week an agency field officer tried
to make a buy off of one other ops.
He was trying to sell out
a mole or something and you got to him before we did.
- I killed him?
- You left a print.
There were partial prints that trace back to Treadstone.
They know it was you.
- That is insane.
- Why are you doing this? Why come back now?
Landy will find ?
Stop. Stop.
Last week I was 4,000 miles away
in India, watching Marie die.
They came for me,
and they killed her instead.
This ends now.
Find her.
What do you people want with me?
Why are you trying to frame me?
- Please! I'm only here because of Paris. Abbott dragged us ?
- Abbott? Who's Abbott?
Conklin's boss.
He-He shut down Treadstone.
Is he here in Berlin?
Yes.
Did he run Treadstone?
Yes. Conklin reported to him.
Please. Please, I swear ?
What was Landy buying? What kind of files?
Conklin ? Stuff on Conklin.
It was something to do
with a Russian politician.
Neski. Wh-What?
What are you talking about?
Training is over ? Training is over ?
Training is over ?
When ? When was I here in Berlin?
What are you talking about?
For Treadstone. I did a job here.
When? No, you never worked
in Berlin before.
My first job. In Berlin.
You know my file.
- You've never worked Berlin before.
- My first job!
No, your first assignment was Geneva.
You fucking people!
I swear! I swear!
I know I was here, Nicky!
- It's not in your file!
- I know I was here!
No, I swear ? Oh, please!
Pam, I want to show you something.
It's Alexanderplatz.
We got three levels, we got 15 tunnels.
They're all converging in a five-block radius.
Over here, Luftschulzbunker.
That was an old war shelter.
How many men are out there? Two coming down the back stairs.
The rest, they're fanned out for a search.
- What's our security situation here?
- Where, "here"? The ground?
Here, here, in the building. Check
everything, and recheck all the stairwells, hallways, everything.
It's done.
Okay, let's go public.
Release his photo to the Berlin police.
- And check out his story about the girlfriend in India too.
- I'm on it.
You're in a big puddle of shit, Pamela,
and you don't have the shoes for it.
- He said he didn't know anything about Berlin.
- He knew that Nicky was wearing a wire.
- Don't you think that was for our benefit?
- He didn't sound like a man in control to me.
We know he was in Berlin.
His mind is broken.
We broke it. And now ?
What now? Terminate him?
You've been pushing that agenda ever since we got here.
- He also said you were running Treadstone. Should we believe that too?
- I'm convinced Bourne knows something.
He knows that you're after him,
and in the interest of self-preservation
you might start with that.
Check on those photos.
Have they gone out?
I need to show you something.
All right, I finished my box work, but I
wanted to show you before I showed Landy.
Came down here last night ...
because none of this
is making any sense.
I'm with you ? Conklin was a nut.
But a traitor?
I just can't get there.
What do you have, Danny?
All right, you put a four-gam Kel on here,
it's gonna take out power to the building.
You know that.
There were two charges that were supposed to go off simultaneously.
The second one, over here, didn't go off.
Now, first of all, this is nothing.
It's a sub-line for the breaker above.
And second, why put the charge
all the way down here?
If you're good enough to get in here and handle the gear,
you're good enough to know you don't need this.
Bourne would know.
It was staged?
Is it a slam dunk? No.
But what if somebody were trying to cover their tracks
by blaming Conklin and Bourne?
What if Bourne didn't have
anything to do with this?
- Show me again.
- All right.
Well, you put ?
Pull over. He's getting out.
This is not a drill, soldier.
We clear on that?
This is a live project,
and you're a go.
I'll see you on the other side.
- Good evening, sir. How can I help you?
- I want to get a room for the night.
Do you have a reservation?
No.
Actually, is room 645 available?
I've stayed there before.
I'm sorry, sir. That room is occupied.
How about room 644?
It's right across the hall.
Sir?
644?
That's fine. Thank you.
I just need your passport
and signature right here, please.
Have a nice night.
Ja.
Berlin Polizei.
Where?
Brecker Hotel.
Okay, we're there.
Take the van!
- Brecker? How far?
- About five or six minutes.
Hi!
Hey!
Congratulations, soldier.
Training is over.
Polizei! Polizei!
Go!
Black coat, possibly leather,
dark T-shirt, dark pants.
The cops out there wanna corral all the guests together
and check 'em out one by one.
That will really work.
What the hell's he doing here?
Maybe he just wanted to stay the night.
Polizei!
Polizei! Polizei!
They missed him?
Yeah, so far.
But they found Nicky.
She's back at the Westin. Bourne let her go.
He let her go?
Yeah.
Where's Danny Zorn? He ought to
head over there and debrief her.
Why did Bourne come here?
We don't know yet.
Landy's upstairs in one of the rooms.
She said she'd call you
when she's done.
Okay.
I think I'll, uh ... take a cab
back to the hotel.
So, the room he checked into
was across the hall.
Mmm.
Why would he come in here?
What are you thinking?
I recognize this room from a photo.
There was a chalk outline right here
around the body of Vladimir Neski.
This is where
his wife killed him?
Do you still think
Guess he got out
through this window.
We just got word
from the Berlin police.
They found Danny Zorn's body.
I want you two to stay on Bourne.
Check everything that's out there.
Call Abbott.
Tell him to wait for me in his hotel.
I'm coming to see him.
- Da.
- It's me.
They're onto Neski.
This is not a clean phone.
They can't prove anything without Bourne.
Kill Bourne,
and you kill this investigation.
I'm afraid, Ward, the time has come for us
to part company.
Listen, Yuri, you bought those oil leases
with 20 million in stolen C.I.A. seed money.
You owe me.
I gave you your cut.
We both got rich.
I don't owe you anything.
The plan can still be salvaged.
Just get Bourne. You hear me?
He's still out there.
Now get him.
Get Jason ?
I don't suppose it would do me
much good to cry for help, huh?
Not much.
You killed her.
It was a mistake.
It was supposed to be you.
There were files linking me
to the Neski murder.
If the files disappeared
and they suspected you,
they'd be chasing a ghost
for 10 years.
So we got in the way.
Is that why Neski died?
Is that why you killed Marie?
You killed Marie ...
the minute
you climbed into her car.
The minute you entered her life,
she was dead.
I told you people
to leave us alone.
I fell off the grid.
I was halfway around the world.
There's no place
it won't catch up to you.
It's how every story ends.
It's what you are, Jason ?
a killer.
You always will be.
Go ahead. Go on. Go on!
Do it! Do it!
She wouldn't want me to.
That's the only reason
you're alive.
I'm a patriot.
I serve my country.
And Danny Zorn?
What was he? Unlucky.
Collateral damage.
So, what do we do now?
I'm not sorry.
No, no, no, forget it.
Call me as soon as he's here.
No, that's nothing.
- Good synch-up.
- Who's this guy?
Platform "B".
Go ahead. Go on. Go on!
Do it! Do it!
She wouldn't want me to.
That's the only reason
you're alive.
Got a call from Langley.
They're, uh, going through
Abbott's records,
and Marshall wants to know
what's going on with Bourne.
Wait, Teddy. Teddy, who's this?
Look at this guy.
He 's about to enter ?
Right there! There!
Right through there.
That's Bourne.
- Get down here! We got something!
- We got a sighting! Check it out!
There. I got it on the big monitor.
Hold on.
Here it comes again.
- Whoa, whoa. Hold on. He's just entered frame.
- It's the coat. That's him!
What train is that?
- That's the train to Moscow.
- Why the hell would he go to Moscow?
Get me
the Russian interior ministry.
Da.
I speak English.
I'm not gonna hurt you.
I won't hurt you.
You're older.
Older than I thought you'd be.
That picture.
Does that mean a lot to you?
It's nothing.
It's just a picture.
No.
It's 'cause you don't know
how they died.
I do.
No, you don't.
I would want to know.
I would want to know that my ?
that my mother didn't kill my father,
that she didn't kill herself.
What?
It's not what happened
to your parents.
I killed them.
It was my job.
It was my first time.
Your father
was supposed to be alone.
But then your mother ...
came out of nowhere,
and I had to change my plan.
It changes things,
that knowledge.
Doesn't it?
When what you love
gets taken from you,
you wanna know the truth.
I'm sorry.
- Pamela Landy.
- I hear you're still looking for me.
Bourne?
What do you want?
I wanted to thank you ...
for the tape.
We got what we needed.
It's all tied off ... It's over.
I guess I owe you an apology.
Is that official?
No. Off the record.
You know how it is.
Goodbye.
Wait. Wait.
David Webb.
That's your real name.
You were born 4-15-71
in Nixa, Missouri.
Why don't you come in
and we'll talk about it.
Bourne?
Get some rest, Pam.
You look tired.