1
00:05:01,551 --> 00:05:03,302
Don't shoot me.

2
00:05:03,762 --> 00:05:05,388
Who is that?

3
00:05:05,722 --> 00:05:08,432
There's your money. Release the hostages.

4
00:05:08,517 --> 00:05:09,475
How much in there?

5
00:05:09,559 --> 00:05:10,601
Three.

6
00:05:10,685 --> 00:05:13,312
You're too late. We want $5 million.

7
00:05:17,818 --> 00:05:19,693
What do you know? A greedy pirate.

8
00:05:21,238 --> 00:05:22,238
Last chance!

9
00:05:23,115 --> 00:05:24,115
Take it or leave it.

10
00:05:24,366 --> 00:05:26,617
We want the money now!

11
00:05:28,078 --> 00:05:29,453
- Warning shot.
- No!

12
00:05:33,959 --> 00:05:35,418
A little low.

13
00:05:41,425 --> 00:05:42,591
Lights out!

14
00:06:13,331 --> 00:06:15,916
I'll kill him! I swear I'll kill him!

15
00:06:23,383 --> 00:06:24,383
Drop your guns!

16
00:06:24,468 --> 00:06:25,509
Fat chance.

17
00:06:25,635 --> 00:06:26,760
Yeah, that'll happen.

18
00:06:27,304 --> 00:06:29,513
Last chance. Let the hostages go

19
00:06:30,307 --> 00:06:31,974
or you're out of there.

20
00:06:32,142 --> 00:06:34,477
Bring the money here to me.

21
00:06:34,686 --> 00:06:36,395
I'll take the four on the left.

22
00:06:36,480 --> 00:06:38,564
I want you to take the two on the right.
Leave the rest alone.

23
00:06:40,817 --> 00:06:42,985
I'll kill them all! I don't care.

24
00:06:43,195 --> 00:06:45,988
You should take the two on the right.
You're not that fast any more.

25
00:06:46,239 --> 00:06:47,823
The only thing faster is lightning.

26
00:06:49,493 --> 00:06:50,493
We'll see.

27
00:06:52,162 --> 00:06:54,663
Bullets go faster than blades.

28
00:06:55,624 --> 00:06:57,416
Bring the money here now!

29
00:06:57,667 --> 00:06:58,667
You want the money?

30
00:07:01,338 --> 00:07:02,671
Go get it.

31
00:07:06,676 --> 00:07:07,760
What's that?

32
00:07:07,844 --> 00:07:09,178
I'm getting a text.

33
00:07:09,596 --> 00:07:10,596
Excuse me?

34
00:07:10,931 --> 00:07:11,931
Kill them!

35
00:07:19,189 --> 00:07:21,065
- I call that a tie.
- Come on, keep dreaming.

36
00:07:21,441 --> 00:07:23,734
These guys are arrested development.

37
00:07:23,818 --> 00:07:25,528
A little compassion, folks.

38
00:07:25,737 --> 00:07:27,071
You know, I don't think
you hit one of them.

39
00:07:27,697 --> 00:07:29,156
I don't see any knives, actually.

40
00:07:29,616 --> 00:07:30,616
How are you guys doing?

41
00:07:32,744 --> 00:07:35,037
- What the hell is he doing?
- Hanging a pirate.

42
00:07:35,205 --> 00:07:36,872
Don't be ridiculous.

43
00:07:37,541 --> 00:07:40,334
Gunner! What are you doing?

44
00:07:40,669 --> 00:07:42,419
Hanging a pirate!

45
00:07:42,712 --> 00:07:45,673
- That is seriously demented.
- This is no good.

46
00:07:46,091 --> 00:07:48,008
- You're on your own.
- Appreciate it.

47
00:07:48,093 --> 00:07:49,552
It's good to have friends.

48
00:07:49,719 --> 00:07:51,303
- Gunner.
- Yeah?

49
00:07:51,388 --> 00:07:53,597
This isn't how we work. Let him go.

50
00:07:53,848 --> 00:07:55,599
Why? He'd do it to us.

51
00:07:55,684 --> 00:07:57,351
Gunner, last chance.

52
00:07:57,435 --> 00:07:59,311
Let him go or we're letting you go.

53
00:07:59,729 --> 00:08:00,896
It's good to hang pirates.

54
00:08:20,000 --> 00:08:22,084
- We don't kill like that.
- Yeah?

55
00:08:22,502 --> 00:08:24,211
Not polite enough?

56
00:08:25,422 --> 00:08:27,298
- Let him go, Gunner.
- How are you doing, Barney?

57
00:08:27,716 --> 00:08:28,757
Pretty good.

58
00:08:29,092 --> 00:08:30,926
My partner here kicked me
with steel-tipped boots.

59
00:08:31,011 --> 00:08:32,886
- Can you believe that?
- You deserved it.

60
00:08:33,430 --> 00:08:34,513
I think I'll need stitches.

61
00:08:34,598 --> 00:08:35,639
Maybe.

62
00:08:36,057 --> 00:08:38,475
- I hate stitches.
- Everyone does.

63
00:08:39,269 --> 00:08:40,519
Let him go, Gunner.

64
00:08:40,604 --> 00:08:41,729
Let him go?

65
00:08:42,939 --> 00:08:44,023
Let him go.

66
00:09:21,978 --> 00:09:24,396
- Think he's cool?
- Be careful. Go.

67
00:09:40,622 --> 00:09:41,705
Gunner, you cool?

68
00:09:44,918 --> 00:09:46,001
Yeah.

69
00:09:57,847 --> 00:09:59,264
No, keep it.

70
00:10:00,266 --> 00:10:01,934
You appreciate a good blade.

71
00:10:15,907 --> 00:10:16,949
He all right?

72
00:10:17,033 --> 00:10:18,033
Yeah.

73
00:10:19,035 --> 00:10:21,036
The life just got to him.

74
00:10:22,580 --> 00:10:24,039
It'll get to all of us.

75
00:10:58,741 --> 00:10:59,741
Coming!

76
00:11:03,163 --> 00:11:04,204
Who is it?

77
00:11:04,289 --> 00:11:07,875
Someday you'll find a man
who'll be happy just to watch you sleep.

78
00:11:12,297 --> 00:11:15,257
- Hi. I didn't know you were back.
- Hey, babe.

79
00:11:16,426 --> 00:11:18,177
Yeah, I just arrived.

80
00:11:18,261 --> 00:11:20,220
- Hey.
- You look great.

81
00:11:21,431 --> 00:11:23,182
I wish you would have called.

82
00:11:23,266 --> 00:11:25,642
I've never been a good caller.

83
00:11:26,269 --> 00:11:28,145
I haven't heard from you in over a month.

84
00:11:28,229 --> 00:11:30,522
Really? Time flies, huh?

85
00:11:31,191 --> 00:11:33,275
Won't happen again! Sorry.

86
00:11:33,610 --> 00:11:36,570
But I do have a surprise.

87
00:11:37,238 --> 00:11:39,448
Rose-flavored. Your favorite.

88
00:11:42,535 --> 00:11:44,995
And I did have something else for you.

89
00:11:46,247 --> 00:11:50,626
It's something I picked up from Burma.

90
00:11:51,044 --> 00:11:52,461
It's a ruby.

91
00:11:54,380 --> 00:11:57,799
It's a good color,
but it's hard to see in this light.

92
00:11:59,636 --> 00:12:02,804
This kind of looked a little shinier
when I bought it in the shop, you know?

93
00:12:02,889 --> 00:12:05,182
Lace, everything all right?

94
00:12:09,145 --> 00:12:10,854
- Yeah.
- Who is he?

95
00:12:13,107 --> 00:12:14,149
He's a friend.

96
00:12:14,234 --> 00:12:16,360
Kind of late. You got a name?

97
00:12:19,489 --> 00:12:21,490
Friend. She just told you.

98
00:12:24,035 --> 00:12:25,160
Lee, come on.

99
00:12:25,411 --> 00:12:27,538
Don't leave like this. Lee, I'm sorry.

100
00:12:28,540 --> 00:12:29,748
I thought things were good between us.

101
00:12:29,832 --> 00:12:33,252
I felt like you never cared about getting
in my life or letting me into yours.

102
00:12:33,336 --> 00:12:34,878
- Stop.
- Yeah, sure I did.

103
00:12:34,963 --> 00:12:37,714
No.
I have known you for over a year and a half,

104
00:12:37,799 --> 00:12:39,633
and I don't even know
what you do for a living.

105
00:12:39,717 --> 00:12:42,427
What's it matter?
When I'm here, I'm with you. That matters.

106
00:12:42,512 --> 00:12:45,931
What matters is when you're here,
you're not really here.

107
00:12:46,391 --> 00:12:48,100
You're a good man. I love you, but...

108
00:12:48,184 --> 00:12:49,977
- Lace!
- I hate his voice.

109
00:12:50,353 --> 00:12:52,604
- Did you say something?
- Don't let him come down here.

110
00:12:52,855 --> 00:12:54,273
Please tell me you understand
what I'm saying.

111
00:12:54,357 --> 00:12:56,692
- You have to understand.
- I understand.

112
00:12:56,943 --> 00:12:57,943
You take care.

113
00:12:58,027 --> 00:12:59,278
Lee.

114
00:13:04,367 --> 00:13:05,659
He's no good, Lace.

115
00:13:46,909 --> 00:13:48,327
Hey, brother, don't you ever sleep?

116
00:13:51,164 --> 00:13:53,123
This is my friend...

117
00:13:54,876 --> 00:13:55,876
What's your name again, baby?

118
00:13:55,960 --> 00:13:57,044
- Cheyenne.
- Cheyenne.

119
00:13:57,253 --> 00:13:59,379
Cheyenne, Arapaho, Cherokee, Pawnee.

120
00:14:00,423 --> 00:14:01,423
You want a drink?

121
00:14:02,050 --> 00:14:03,300
I'm good.

122
00:14:04,427 --> 00:14:06,011
Why don't you run upstairs

123
00:14:06,095 --> 00:14:10,390
and get me one of them
super-duper six-olive martinis, baby?

124
00:14:10,475 --> 00:14:12,017
- Anything for you, baby.
- You got it.

125
00:14:14,312 --> 00:14:16,605
- Got a crush on me.
- Like the last 50.

126
00:14:16,689 --> 00:14:18,231
Hey, brother, who's counting?

127
00:14:18,316 --> 00:14:20,942
- Damn, you look good.
- Look at you.

128
00:14:21,027 --> 00:14:23,028
You look like a goddamn
cold piece of steel, brother.

129
00:14:23,112 --> 00:14:27,407
Yeah, well.
Okay, my friend, let's finish this bird up.

130
00:14:27,909 --> 00:14:31,495
Well, let's do it, bro. It's taken you
a couple of years to do a couple of letters.

131
00:14:35,375 --> 00:14:37,459
We had to get rid of Gunner.

132
00:14:37,960 --> 00:14:41,129
Well, he went Crankenstein on your ass.
You got to cut him loose.

133
00:14:41,214 --> 00:14:43,006
You wanna fill in?

134
00:14:43,091 --> 00:14:44,257
Let me tell you something.

135
00:14:44,342 --> 00:14:46,218
Remember where we was last time?

136
00:14:46,302 --> 00:14:48,428
Where were we?
We were ass-deep in that mud and blood.

137
00:14:48,513 --> 00:14:51,556
- Nigeria.
- Yeah, your hand was all shot to shit.

138
00:14:52,517 --> 00:14:54,976
You were bleeding all over the place,
and I was bleeding,

139
00:14:55,645 --> 00:14:57,312
and you know what I did?
I promised myself,

140
00:14:58,481 --> 00:15:02,484
I don't wanna die all alone,
full of holes in the mud and blood.

141
00:15:03,361 --> 00:15:05,821
I'm gonna die with something that counts.
I'm gonna die with a woman.

142
00:15:05,988 --> 00:15:09,241
I wanna die with someone
who cares about me, you know.

143
00:15:09,784 --> 00:15:11,326
I don't wanna die for a woman.

144
00:15:11,411 --> 00:15:13,453
I wanna die laying next to a woman.
That's what I want.

145
00:15:16,457 --> 00:15:18,750
- It's Christmastime.
- Yeah, I can smell him from here.

146
00:15:24,382 --> 00:15:26,591
Mr. Christmas. How you doing, brother?

147
00:15:27,135 --> 00:15:28,635
I'm good, Tool.

148
00:15:29,178 --> 00:15:30,929
Take a look at this. What do you think?

149
00:15:31,180 --> 00:15:33,014
It still looks like a black chicken.

150
00:15:33,099 --> 00:15:34,975
- Black chicken?
- Black chicken? You done?

151
00:15:35,935 --> 00:15:38,228
- All done.
- It's a damn raven.

152
00:15:39,480 --> 00:15:42,149
Man. It's good to see you, brother.

153
00:15:43,693 --> 00:15:45,444
Wow! You know what?

154
00:15:47,238 --> 00:15:49,489
For you, I got a great idea.

155
00:15:50,199 --> 00:15:53,243
Why don't you let me doodle, like, a...

156
00:15:53,327 --> 00:15:56,413
I don't know, Charlotte's web on your head?

157
00:15:56,706 --> 00:15:58,123
On the top of your head.

158
00:15:58,499 --> 00:16:00,125
You know, something different,
something exciting.

159
00:16:00,209 --> 00:16:03,044
'Cause you got one of them
perfectly-shaped domed, muscular heads.

160
00:16:03,379 --> 00:16:07,132
I could put a web on the top of the head.

161
00:16:07,759 --> 00:16:10,510
Maybe a pregnant Charlotte
coming out of your ear,

162
00:16:10,595 --> 00:16:14,222
peeking around,
making sure them bugs don't come inside.

163
00:16:14,307 --> 00:16:16,391
Her long leg dangling down your neck.

164
00:16:17,059 --> 00:16:19,144
- Yeah. Sexy, right?
- Very sexy.

165
00:16:19,353 --> 00:16:22,147
Give you a little mystery,
a little more character.

166
00:16:22,231 --> 00:16:24,483
And very sexy. You understand?

167
00:16:24,567 --> 00:16:26,109
It makes him stand out.

168
00:16:27,487 --> 00:16:28,528
He looks thrilled.

169
00:16:28,613 --> 00:16:32,407
Well. Okay, I'll tell you what.
I'm feeling a little lucky tonight.

170
00:16:33,075 --> 00:16:35,202
I'm feeling very accurate.

171
00:16:35,328 --> 00:16:38,079
- Another time. Come on.
- Come on, take him on.

172
00:16:38,289 --> 00:16:40,040
Come on, Christmas. Bring it, baby.

173
00:16:40,124 --> 00:16:41,500
Don't encourage him, please.

174
00:16:41,793 --> 00:16:42,793
He never beat you in your life.

175
00:16:42,877 --> 00:16:45,337
Come on, Christmas, no disgrace in losing.

176
00:17:03,689 --> 00:17:04,898
Yes?

177
00:17:09,111 --> 00:17:10,195
Yeah.

178
00:17:12,240 --> 00:17:13,323
Okay.

179
00:17:16,118 --> 00:17:18,161
Well, I got three pieces of work.

180
00:17:19,038 --> 00:17:22,833
Two a walk in the park,
and one to hell and back.

181
00:17:23,209 --> 00:17:25,877
- I need some time alone.
- Hey, cheer up. Make the meeting.

182
00:19:04,477 --> 00:19:06,603
Now we can see inside of him.

183
00:19:07,521 --> 00:19:09,230
And I see lies.

184
00:19:10,816 --> 00:19:14,486
He wasn't stealing from you.
He was stealing from us both.

185
00:19:16,113 --> 00:19:19,282
You want your apes' respect?
Snuff those two.

186
00:19:32,838 --> 00:19:34,130
Let's just keep it simple.

187
00:19:34,215 --> 00:19:36,675
If the money's right,
we don't care where the job is.

188
00:19:36,759 --> 00:19:38,718
- Got it?
- Let's quit jerking off,

189
00:19:38,803 --> 00:19:40,637
get down to business, see who's hungry.

190
00:19:40,721 --> 00:19:43,640
I know your real name's
probably not Barney Ross.

191
00:19:43,724 --> 00:19:45,600
You don't need to know my name.

192
00:19:45,685 --> 00:19:49,104
The only thing you need to know is
the job's real and the money's real.

193
00:19:49,188 --> 00:19:51,731
But since we're in this nice place,

194
00:19:52,900 --> 00:19:55,110
you might as well just call me Mr. Church.

195
00:19:56,070 --> 00:19:57,946
Okay, Church. What can I do for you?

196
00:19:58,572 --> 00:20:01,449
In a minute.
I'm still waiting for one more guy.

197
00:20:01,701 --> 00:20:02,951
Who?

198
00:20:14,213 --> 00:20:15,422
You know him?

199
00:20:15,506 --> 00:20:17,465
Yeah, we used to be
on the same team together.

200
00:20:17,842 --> 00:20:19,718
What's my oldest, worst friend doing here?

201
00:20:20,052 --> 00:20:22,721
Both of your names came
to the top of the list.

202
00:20:22,805 --> 00:20:24,723
- Is that a problem?
- Yeah.

203
00:20:24,807 --> 00:20:26,725
Should've shot him when I had the chance.

204
00:20:26,809 --> 00:20:28,101
Big Barney Ross.

205
00:20:28,477 --> 00:20:30,270
Bigger Trench mouse.

206
00:20:30,479 --> 00:20:33,565
- What are you doing? Praying for work?
- Could be.

207
00:20:33,649 --> 00:20:34,983
Have you been sick?

208
00:20:35,401 --> 00:20:37,527
- You've lost weight.
- Really?

209
00:20:37,611 --> 00:20:40,030
Whatever weight I lost, you found, pal.

210
00:20:41,824 --> 00:20:44,159
You guys aren't gonna start sucking
each other's dicks, are you?

211
00:20:49,540 --> 00:20:52,709
Let's get down to business,
see who wants the work.

212
00:20:52,793 --> 00:20:54,169
You ever hear of an island called Vilena?

213
00:20:54,336 --> 00:20:55,879
- No.
- Yeah.

214
00:20:58,132 --> 00:20:59,340
It's a little island in the Gulf.

215
00:20:59,425 --> 00:21:00,467
That's right.

216
00:21:00,843 --> 00:21:03,219
- You should read more.
- Thanks.

217
00:21:05,056 --> 00:21:08,058
There are resources on that island
that my people are very interested in.

218
00:21:08,350 --> 00:21:12,062
But a general by the name of Garza
has overthrown the half-ass government.

219
00:21:12,146 --> 00:21:13,605
That's right.

220
00:21:14,565 --> 00:21:16,858
My people are having a problem
with this fanatic Garza.

221
00:21:17,193 --> 00:21:19,486
- So you want Garza gone?
- I want him dead.

222
00:21:19,570 --> 00:21:21,154
All it takes is a little army.

223
00:21:21,238 --> 00:21:22,655
Only an idiot would do this job.

224
00:21:23,324 --> 00:21:25,408
- How much?
- Oh, like I said.

225
00:21:28,704 --> 00:21:31,414
I'm busy anyway,
so give this job to my friend here.

226
00:21:31,499 --> 00:21:32,957
He loves playing in the jungle.

227
00:21:33,125 --> 00:21:34,501
- Right?
- Right.

228
00:21:34,668 --> 00:21:37,837
- That's right.
- Hey, why don't we have dinner?

229
00:21:38,172 --> 00:21:39,255
Sure. When?

230
00:21:39,548 --> 00:21:41,591
- In a thousand years.
- Too soon.

231
00:21:44,762 --> 00:21:47,388
- What's his fucking problem?
- He wants to be president.

232
00:21:51,060 --> 00:21:52,936
I got to recon this island first.

233
00:21:53,062 --> 00:21:54,729
I'll have a contact for you on the island.

234
00:21:57,191 --> 00:21:58,191
Good riddance.

235
00:21:59,110 --> 00:22:01,152
I got a feeling everyone else
has passed on this job,

236
00:22:01,237 --> 00:22:03,404
so our fee is $5 mil.

237
00:22:04,031 --> 00:22:06,324
- $5 mil?
- And I want half upfront,

238
00:22:06,408 --> 00:22:07,951
and the other half in an offshore account.

239
00:22:08,035 --> 00:22:10,662
- You got a problem with that?
- No.

240
00:22:12,456 --> 00:22:16,292
What I have a problem with
is people who try to fuck me over.

241
00:22:18,420 --> 00:22:21,548
So if you take this money
and you don't deliver,

242
00:22:22,258 --> 00:22:26,594
or you try to fuck me in some kind of weird
cockamamie scheme of yours,

243
00:22:27,263 --> 00:22:28,972
me and my people

244
00:22:29,682 --> 00:22:32,350
are gonna come get you and your people

245
00:22:32,768 --> 00:22:37,355
and chop you up
into little fucking dog treats.

246
00:22:39,066 --> 00:22:40,233
You got a problem with that?

247
00:22:46,574 --> 00:22:47,615
Let's talk.

248
00:23:17,897 --> 00:23:19,105
Vilena.

249
00:23:19,815 --> 00:23:21,274
Yeah, Vilena.

250
00:23:22,484 --> 00:23:24,277
They got work there?

251
00:23:29,992 --> 00:23:31,201
Come on.

252
00:23:31,869 --> 00:23:33,453
You know you shouldn't be here, Gunner.

253
00:23:33,787 --> 00:23:35,413
Don't replace me.

254
00:23:36,665 --> 00:23:37,749
I'm good.

255
00:23:39,501 --> 00:23:41,002
I'm still good.

256
00:23:41,712 --> 00:23:43,087
You're still using.

257
00:23:43,214 --> 00:23:44,839
I can't trust you any more, man.

258
00:23:46,550 --> 00:23:48,843
- You can't trust me?
- I can't.

259
00:23:52,681 --> 00:23:54,432
You can't trust me?

260
00:24:03,234 --> 00:24:04,525
Be careful.

261
00:24:04,610 --> 00:24:06,069
You threatening me, Gunner?

262
00:24:07,821 --> 00:24:10,698
Nah, I'm a nice guy.

263
00:24:20,209 --> 00:24:22,460
So, going over the info
this guy Church gave me,

264
00:24:22,544 --> 00:24:25,421
there's probably about
6,000 people on the island.

265
00:24:25,714 --> 00:24:26,881
How many soldiers?

266
00:24:27,091 --> 00:24:28,383
Maybe a couple of hundred.

267
00:24:30,010 --> 00:24:32,470
It wouldn't take much more than that
to control a space that small.

268
00:24:32,554 --> 00:24:34,597
Great, they've got a small army.

269
00:24:34,682 --> 00:24:35,682
What do we got?

270
00:24:35,766 --> 00:24:36,849
Four and a half men.

271
00:24:38,560 --> 00:24:40,061
Not so funny.

272
00:24:40,813 --> 00:24:42,146
- I need a raise.
- Why?

273
00:24:42,231 --> 00:24:43,815
I need more money for my son.

274
00:24:44,108 --> 00:24:45,733
I want to send him to a better school.

275
00:24:45,943 --> 00:24:48,111
- When did Yin Yang get a family?
- I have no idea.

276
00:24:48,195 --> 00:24:50,071
You don't ask, I don't tell.

277
00:24:50,656 --> 00:24:53,449
Anyway, the pay share stays the same.

278
00:24:54,410 --> 00:24:55,660
That's the way it's gonna be.

279
00:24:55,744 --> 00:24:58,079
Now the target on this island
is a guy named General Garza.

280
00:24:58,372 --> 00:25:01,207
- What's the problem?
- Who gives a shit what the problem is?

281
00:25:01,709 --> 00:25:04,002
We got enough problems
right here of our own.

282
00:25:04,086 --> 00:25:07,088
We don't get rid of those first,
they're gonna get rid of us.

283
00:25:07,506 --> 00:25:10,258
Toll Road, when was
the last time you saw your analyst?

284
00:25:12,594 --> 00:25:14,345
- This morning.
- Yeah? What'd you talk about?

285
00:25:17,433 --> 00:25:19,600
Avoidant personality disorder.

286
00:25:19,685 --> 00:25:20,768
You think too much.

287
00:25:20,936 --> 00:25:23,604
You know, Toll Road,
you're an unusual guy,

288
00:25:24,106 --> 00:25:26,733
and you're always gonna have
unusual problems, right?

289
00:25:27,026 --> 00:25:29,527
Unusual? You're talking about my ear.

290
00:25:30,529 --> 00:25:32,030
Come on. Don't start with the ear again.

291
00:25:32,114 --> 00:25:33,281
- Not the ear story.
- The ear story, not again.

292
00:25:33,365 --> 00:25:35,366
- We all know the ear story.
- We don't want to hear the ear story.

293
00:25:35,451 --> 00:25:36,534
Let's just concentrate on the job.

294
00:25:36,618 --> 00:25:39,245
No. Shit no. You guys started this.

295
00:25:39,496 --> 00:25:42,290
- We all know I wrestled in college.
- Right.

296
00:25:42,374 --> 00:25:46,919
A common injury associated with that sport
is trauma to the ear, a clot.

297
00:25:47,504 --> 00:25:50,631
Which, if left unattended,
causes a contraction in the cartilage

298
00:25:50,841 --> 00:25:52,884
and forms cauliflower ears.

299
00:25:52,968 --> 00:25:55,803
- And your point is?
- It ain't easy being green.

300
00:25:58,640 --> 00:26:01,684
Anyway, me and Christmas
are gonna head down to Vilena

301
00:26:01,769 --> 00:26:03,895
and scout the island
to see if we should take the job.

302
00:26:03,979 --> 00:26:06,647
How much we get paid?
I need more money for my family.

303
00:26:08,442 --> 00:26:10,777
- What family?
- My family.

304
00:26:28,170 --> 00:26:30,004
Listen, that girl wasn't your type.

305
00:26:30,422 --> 00:26:31,672
Her loss, right?

306
00:26:31,757 --> 00:26:33,674
I should have broke that bastard's jaw.

307
00:26:33,842 --> 00:26:35,593
Maybe you were lucky.
He could have broke yours.

308
00:26:35,677 --> 00:26:39,305
- Impossible.
- You know, Christmas, I understand,

309
00:26:39,390 --> 00:26:42,558
but let's just say you were with her
for a couple of hours,

310
00:26:42,643 --> 00:26:44,435
and it's nice, and it's hot and heavy,

311
00:26:44,520 --> 00:26:46,521
but after that, think about it.

312
00:26:46,605 --> 00:26:48,523
What do you do for the rest of the day?

313
00:26:48,690 --> 00:26:50,441
She probably did you a favor.

314
00:26:50,526 --> 00:26:53,194
Now you have more time
to feel sorry for yourself.

315
00:26:54,446 --> 00:26:55,780
You're a bleak bastard.

316
00:28:00,262 --> 00:28:02,847
Morning. Morning.

317
00:28:05,976 --> 00:28:07,768
Morning! Speak English?

318
00:28:10,397 --> 00:28:11,439
Big plane, huh?

319
00:28:12,316 --> 00:28:15,193
Yeah, we use it to transport
injured animals.

320
00:28:15,277 --> 00:28:17,737
- Why are you here?
- Ornithologists.

321
00:28:17,821 --> 00:28:20,281
We're photographing exotic birds.

322
00:28:32,836 --> 00:28:33,961
You're nervous?

323
00:28:34,254 --> 00:28:35,504
Nervous?

324
00:28:36,798 --> 00:28:38,549
No. Why?

325
00:28:38,926 --> 00:28:40,635
You just look nervous.

326
00:28:41,303 --> 00:28:42,970
I'm not nervous. Do I look nervous?

327
00:28:43,055 --> 00:28:44,305
Your skin looks a little dry.

328
00:28:44,389 --> 00:28:46,015
I think you should fly
with the window closed.

329
00:28:46,642 --> 00:28:49,936
- It's the altitude.
- It is the altitude. It'll get to you.

330
00:29:15,921 --> 00:29:18,714
- What's the address?
- Yeah, it's in my head.

331
00:29:18,924 --> 00:29:20,758
Do you wanna share it?

332
00:29:21,218 --> 00:29:23,135
It's the Gloria Cantina.

333
00:29:23,220 --> 00:29:26,180
So actually, Cantina Gloria in Spanish.

334
00:29:26,890 --> 00:29:29,100
Spanish. Who are you, Zorro?

335
00:29:30,602 --> 00:29:32,019
Army.

336
00:29:32,104 --> 00:29:33,396
- Shit.
- Come on.

337
00:29:33,480 --> 00:29:34,730
In there.

338
00:29:53,041 --> 00:29:54,041
You rolling?

339
00:29:54,293 --> 00:29:55,334
Yeah.

340
00:29:58,088 --> 00:29:59,714
You, you, move the truck!

341
00:30:04,553 --> 00:30:06,137
Get the suit. Tighten up on the suit.

342
00:30:06,221 --> 00:30:07,471
Got him.

343
00:30:14,396 --> 00:30:17,148
Look at these clowns,
hand-picked monkeys.

344
00:30:27,659 --> 00:30:28,826
What's wrong with this picture?

345
00:30:31,538 --> 00:30:32,913
Everything.

346
00:30:33,332 --> 00:30:34,999
Let's get out of here.

347
00:30:36,251 --> 00:30:37,543
No, that's the point, you know.

348
00:30:37,627 --> 00:30:40,212
You think you know someone,
and you truly do not.

349
00:30:40,297 --> 00:30:43,341
Aren't you the guy who said,
"The man who best gets along with women

350
00:30:43,425 --> 00:30:45,843
"is the man who can
get along without them"?

351
00:30:45,927 --> 00:30:47,845
- That's bullshit.
- Truthfully, she wasn't your type.

352
00:30:47,929 --> 00:30:50,306
- Well, I wasn't finished.
- Look, enjoy your freedom.

353
00:30:50,390 --> 00:30:53,601
- Yeah, you wait till it happens to you.
- It has.

354
00:30:59,900 --> 00:31:00,900
Contact's late.

355
00:31:01,360 --> 00:31:02,943
All right, let's go.

356
00:31:03,612 --> 00:31:04,779
Chill.

357
00:31:15,332 --> 00:31:16,707
Have you ever been rejected?

358
00:31:21,755 --> 00:31:24,799
You're really pushing the boundaries
of our relationship, you know that?

359
00:31:39,314 --> 00:31:41,524
- Is that the contact?
- Could be.

360
00:31:44,486 --> 00:31:45,903
Too bad she's so homely.

361
00:31:45,987 --> 00:31:47,321
Stay focused.

362
00:31:50,659 --> 00:31:51,700
Are you the contact?

363
00:31:51,785 --> 00:31:53,327
I'm Sandra.

364
00:31:53,787 --> 00:31:54,870
What are your names?

365
00:31:55,122 --> 00:31:56,831
Buda, Pest.

366
00:32:01,336 --> 00:32:02,503
Follow me, please.

367
00:32:07,342 --> 00:32:09,427
Buda and Pest? Nice.

368
00:32:21,064 --> 00:32:23,190
Did you do all these?

369
00:32:24,276 --> 00:32:26,652
Yes. Take one.

370
00:32:27,279 --> 00:32:28,362
A gift.

371
00:32:28,530 --> 00:32:29,864
I don't take free gifts.

372
00:32:31,908 --> 00:32:33,617
- How much you want for it?
- Nothing.

373
00:32:33,702 --> 00:32:35,661
Taking money for something is not a gift.

374
00:32:36,204 --> 00:32:38,497
Taking nothing for something is.

375
00:32:39,207 --> 00:32:40,458
Is it like this all the time?

376
00:32:40,834 --> 00:32:43,169
This place was a beautiful place.

377
00:32:44,087 --> 00:32:48,048
Then one day, they came with money,
and General Garza sold his soul.

378
00:32:48,133 --> 00:32:49,800
And people who fight back are killed.

379
00:32:50,051 --> 00:32:51,385
You said "they" came with money.

380
00:32:51,470 --> 00:32:52,470
Who's "they"?

381
00:32:52,554 --> 00:32:54,346
Some Americans. That's all I know.

382
00:32:54,931 --> 00:32:57,308
But someday all of this will change back.

383
00:32:58,894 --> 00:32:59,852
You really believe that?

384
00:32:59,936 --> 00:33:01,270
Yes.

385
00:33:01,480 --> 00:33:03,772
The best day will be
the one when we can say

386
00:33:03,857 --> 00:33:05,983
our lives are our own again.

387
00:33:10,780 --> 00:33:12,072
You have a family, Sandra?

388
00:33:12,908 --> 00:33:15,242
My mother, when I was little, she died.

389
00:33:15,327 --> 00:33:18,245
And my father, he's gone, too.

390
00:33:19,581 --> 00:33:21,457
Sandra, how close
can you get to the palace?

391
00:33:21,583 --> 00:33:23,375
The palace? Why?

392
00:33:23,835 --> 00:33:26,086
We just wanna check out the view.

393
00:33:26,546 --> 00:33:27,671
There is no view.

394
00:33:27,756 --> 00:33:29,423
Why don't we just go there anyway, okay?

395
00:33:43,897 --> 00:33:45,189
Where is my grove?

396
00:33:46,608 --> 00:33:48,567
Where is your manpower?

397
00:33:53,281 --> 00:33:56,450
Do you know how long it takes
for a coca field to produce?

398
00:33:56,785 --> 00:33:58,202
Of course you don't. Let me tell you.

399
00:33:58,537 --> 00:34:00,496
We are eight weeks behind schedule.

400
00:34:00,872 --> 00:34:04,083
Kick your peasants' asses.
Get me my product.

401
00:34:04,292 --> 00:34:08,420
When you talk like this to me
in front of my men, it's no good.

402
00:34:10,173 --> 00:34:12,299
I am your lifeline.

403
00:34:12,634 --> 00:34:14,969
I am the one who coordinates
all this confusion.

404
00:34:15,595 --> 00:34:17,429
I am making you rich.

405
00:34:17,514 --> 00:34:19,557
And being wealthy is very good.

406
00:34:19,641 --> 00:34:23,644
It allows people to be the real asswipes
nature intended them to be.

407
00:34:28,650 --> 00:34:32,820
Sometimes things
are just not worth the money.

408
00:34:33,572 --> 00:34:34,572
Sure they are.

409
00:34:50,422 --> 00:34:51,422
Sandra, are we close?

410
00:34:51,756 --> 00:34:52,923
It's just over there.

411
00:34:53,258 --> 00:34:54,675
Pull over, please.

412
00:35:01,266 --> 00:35:04,059
- Where are you going?
- Where am I going?

413
00:35:04,728 --> 00:35:06,895
Well, I suppose you could say

414
00:35:06,980 --> 00:35:09,732
I like to look at the world
from different views.

415
00:35:12,360 --> 00:35:13,360
Don't lose my hat.

416
00:35:17,490 --> 00:35:18,657
We should get going.

417
00:35:19,367 --> 00:35:20,868
He's very emotional.

418
00:36:01,451 --> 00:36:03,452
What are you looking for?

419
00:36:06,915 --> 00:36:10,501
Sandra, how do I know
you're not setting us up?

420
00:36:11,169 --> 00:36:13,128
What does "setting us up" mean?

421
00:36:13,213 --> 00:36:15,506
You don't look like the kind of person
that we deal with all the time.

422
00:36:15,590 --> 00:36:17,758
How did you get involved in this?

423
00:36:17,967 --> 00:36:19,760
An American came here.

424
00:36:19,844 --> 00:36:23,931
He asked my friend to show you around.
He was afraid, so he asked me to.

425
00:36:24,015 --> 00:36:25,015
And you're not afraid?

426
00:36:25,225 --> 00:36:26,683
I'm afraid.

427
00:36:26,976 --> 00:36:29,228
But he said maybe you can help Vilena.

428
00:36:29,771 --> 00:36:31,438
I don't think so.

429
00:36:31,815 --> 00:36:34,149
Listen, if I were you, I'd leave.

430
00:36:35,276 --> 00:36:36,652
Just leave.

431
00:36:44,119 --> 00:36:45,786
You should leave.

432
00:36:53,586 --> 00:36:55,337
Don't say anything. Let me talk.

433
00:37:28,913 --> 00:37:29,997
Run!

434
00:37:55,482 --> 00:37:57,191
- Get her.
- Got it.

435
00:38:10,997 --> 00:38:12,247
Are you crazy?

436
00:38:12,415 --> 00:38:14,458
- You could have killed me!
- You're welcome.

437
00:38:19,380 --> 00:38:20,380
What?

438
00:38:22,842 --> 00:38:25,552
All right, speed it up. We're on the way.

439
00:38:30,433 --> 00:38:31,934
If we get out of here, it's a miracle.

440
00:38:33,728 --> 00:38:35,604
- She's coming with us, right?
- She'd better.

441
00:38:38,441 --> 00:38:39,983
- How can we leave?
- We got a plane.

442
00:38:40,068 --> 00:38:42,402
- No, I can't leave.
- Yeah, well, you don't have a choice.

443
00:38:42,570 --> 00:38:44,571
- Yes, I do.
- Yeah? They'll find you in an hour.

444
00:38:44,739 --> 00:38:47,366
- Maybe, but I'm staying.
- Staying for what? There's nothing here.

445
00:38:47,575 --> 00:38:48,867
Not to you.

446
00:38:51,663 --> 00:38:53,789
Look, if you stay, then you're dead.
She's leaving with us.

447
00:39:41,963 --> 00:39:44,172
- I got the guys inside.
- Give me a 60-second lead.

448
00:39:44,299 --> 00:39:45,966
- You got it. Go, go, go!
- Come on.

449
00:40:02,734 --> 00:40:03,734
Get in.

450
00:40:05,028 --> 00:40:06,069
- Get in.
- No.

451
00:40:06,154 --> 00:40:07,487
- Get in.
- No, no, I can't.

452
00:40:07,822 --> 00:40:09,615
- Let's go.
- I can't. I belong here.

453
00:40:09,699 --> 00:40:11,617
- There's no time.
- Go, you go.

454
00:40:11,826 --> 00:40:13,577
Please, go.

455
00:40:13,661 --> 00:40:14,661
Shit.

456
00:40:32,305 --> 00:40:33,430
Hey!

457
00:40:35,391 --> 00:40:36,391
You look nervous.

458
00:41:01,959 --> 00:41:03,126
Come on!

459
00:41:18,059 --> 00:41:19,267
Run, you bastard!

460
00:41:23,356 --> 00:41:24,564
Come on!

461
00:42:09,944 --> 00:42:11,945
- Where's the girl?
- Gone. She wouldn't leave.

462
00:42:12,029 --> 00:42:13,572
Wouldn't leave?

463
00:42:14,031 --> 00:42:15,615
Why the hell would anybody wanna stay?

464
00:42:25,960 --> 00:42:27,335
The hell...

465
00:42:29,630 --> 00:42:31,047
The hell with it.

466
00:42:31,132 --> 00:42:33,717
- Climb, baby, climb.
- Come on, baby.

467
00:42:45,646 --> 00:42:46,646
God damn it.

468
00:42:55,156 --> 00:42:56,531
- Going back?
- Yeah.

469
00:42:56,616 --> 00:42:58,658
- Fry and die.
- Fry and die. Let's do it.

470
00:44:11,524 --> 00:44:13,275
What are they doing?

471
00:44:32,295 --> 00:44:33,378
Yes!

472
00:44:45,099 --> 00:44:46,266
Great job.

473
00:44:47,268 --> 00:44:48,435
That was a statement.

474
00:45:06,829 --> 00:45:10,498
How did two obvious professionals
pass right through security personnel,

475
00:45:10,583 --> 00:45:12,959
kill 41 soldiers and get away?

476
00:45:14,170 --> 00:45:15,837
With help, that's how.

477
00:45:16,464 --> 00:45:19,674
Everything's under control,
except one detail,

478
00:45:19,759 --> 00:45:23,219
a daughter who wants her father
and company dead and gone.

479
00:45:23,304 --> 00:45:24,888
Bad Shakespeare.

480
00:45:25,389 --> 00:45:28,141
Somehow the company parasites got to her.

481
00:45:28,267 --> 00:45:29,976
Look, she's your daughter, and that's tragic.

482
00:45:31,687 --> 00:45:33,813
But blood or not, she goes.

483
00:45:34,857 --> 00:45:36,650
Call it the price of doing business.

484
00:45:37,401 --> 00:45:39,152
You don't kill your familia.

485
00:45:39,820 --> 00:45:42,614
Come around my house
during the holidays, pal.

486
00:46:02,551 --> 00:46:03,843
Nice bird.

487
00:46:04,929 --> 00:46:06,262
First of all, I don't feel comfortable

488
00:46:06,347 --> 00:46:08,890
talking business with a giant
carrying a shotgun.

489
00:46:09,433 --> 00:46:10,767
Pretty boy wouldn't give it up.

490
00:46:11,185 --> 00:46:12,477
Not if you wanna know where they are.

491
00:46:12,728 --> 00:46:13,853
What do you know?

492
00:46:14,230 --> 00:46:15,230
I used to be one of them.

493
00:46:19,986 --> 00:46:20,944
Why are you turning on them?

494
00:46:21,028 --> 00:46:22,112
Lovers' quarrel.

495
00:46:23,739 --> 00:46:24,739
We settle on 50.

496
00:46:24,907 --> 00:46:26,116
No, math whizz.

497
00:46:26,575 --> 00:46:29,369
We settle on 100 grand,
upfront, in my pocket.

498
00:46:30,121 --> 00:46:31,830
The guy thinks he's a real badass.

499
00:46:32,206 --> 00:46:33,873
This geezer's a bloody joke.

500
00:46:34,208 --> 00:46:35,709
Life's a joke, shitbird!

501
00:46:37,461 --> 00:46:39,796
If you don't want that Fu Manchu
knocked back into the '60s,

502
00:46:39,880 --> 00:46:43,383
you'd better keep your gum-chewing trap
shut and show some respect!

503
00:46:44,010 --> 00:46:45,135
Bring it.

504
00:46:45,219 --> 00:46:46,469
Hey, be nice.

505
00:46:47,263 --> 00:46:49,180
Need a facelift, pretty boy?

506
00:46:51,892 --> 00:46:52,892
Back off, Paine.

507
00:46:52,977 --> 00:46:54,019
I'm gonna kill him.

508
00:46:54,103 --> 00:46:55,520
We need him.

509
00:46:57,231 --> 00:46:58,523
Back off!

510
00:47:03,654 --> 00:47:05,238
Here's what I think is happening.

511
00:47:05,322 --> 00:47:08,700
This guy who calls himself Church
is really a front for the CIA.

512
00:47:09,076 --> 00:47:10,994
So we're working for the agency?

513
00:47:11,078 --> 00:47:13,538
Yeah.
Church hired us to take out the General,

514
00:47:13,622 --> 00:47:16,583
but the real target's this guy,
James Munroe.

515
00:47:18,586 --> 00:47:20,920
He used to be with the agency,
but got greedy,

516
00:47:21,005 --> 00:47:22,589
went rogue and teamed up with the General

517
00:47:22,673 --> 00:47:24,758
to keep the whole drug operation
for themselves.

518
00:47:24,842 --> 00:47:26,885
And that's a big cash loss.

519
00:47:26,969 --> 00:47:30,013
But Church and the agency
can't afford to send in the Navy SEALs

520
00:47:30,097 --> 00:47:32,766
or the Special Forces
to take out one of their own.

521
00:47:32,850 --> 00:47:36,061
That'd be a bad headline,
so they hire us to kill him.

522
00:47:37,104 --> 00:47:38,730
And they're back in business.

523
00:47:38,814 --> 00:47:41,941
- And we're taken out.
- Nobody's gonna miss us.

524
00:47:42,318 --> 00:47:44,611
- Is it still $5 million?
- You'd never live to spend it.

525
00:47:44,695 --> 00:47:47,238
I'm telling Church the deal's off.

526
00:47:47,698 --> 00:47:49,365
Sound about right?

527
00:47:49,450 --> 00:47:50,533
That's about right.

528
00:47:50,618 --> 00:47:51,659
I agree.

529
00:48:17,019 --> 00:48:18,436
Where is he?

530
00:48:32,118 --> 00:48:34,410
- Who the hell is that?
- Some punk.

531
00:48:34,787 --> 00:48:37,247
- Don't worry about it.
- We got your back.

532
00:48:37,331 --> 00:48:40,166
If he comes over here, we'll bust his ass.

533
00:48:46,799 --> 00:48:48,049
What do you want?

534
00:48:49,343 --> 00:48:50,593
Your life.

535
00:48:51,554 --> 00:48:52,679
I was thinking about taking it.

536
00:48:52,763 --> 00:48:53,930
Is that right?

537
00:48:54,014 --> 00:48:58,059
But I don't do so well in tight spaces,
so going to prison worries me.

538
00:48:59,478 --> 00:49:00,645
You shouldn't have bruised her face.

539
00:49:00,729 --> 00:49:01,729
Really?

540
00:49:01,856 --> 00:49:03,690
I would have liked to have kept it
the way it was.

541
00:49:03,774 --> 00:49:05,608
Keep the bitch, 'cause I'm done with it.

542
00:49:37,308 --> 00:49:38,308
Lee.

543
00:49:43,981 --> 00:49:47,734
Next time, I'll deflate all your balls, friend.

544
00:49:57,620 --> 00:50:00,079
Now you know what I do for a living.

545
00:50:00,623 --> 00:50:02,624
I'm not perfect, but you should have waited.

546
00:50:04,126 --> 00:50:05,877
I was worth it.

547
00:51:06,730 --> 00:51:08,398
So your daughter paints, too?

548
00:51:10,359 --> 00:51:12,068
This is how it starts!

549
00:51:12,403 --> 00:51:13,861
Let's go. There's nothing here.

550
00:51:13,946 --> 00:51:16,281
Or how it ends!

551
00:51:44,518 --> 00:51:47,603
What's the matter, Barney?
Don't you ever sleep?

552
00:51:47,688 --> 00:51:49,605
No. What happened to your girlfriend?

553
00:51:50,190 --> 00:51:52,817
Another one bites the dust, brother.

554
00:51:53,694 --> 00:51:58,114
I was gonna paint this for her,
and you know what? I'm gonna finish it.

555
00:51:58,490 --> 00:52:00,783
Then I'm just gonna smash the shit
out of it.

556
00:52:00,868 --> 00:52:02,285
You wanna be alone?

557
00:52:03,871 --> 00:52:05,997
Not really. So, what's up?

558
00:52:06,373 --> 00:52:08,458
On this island, there was this girl.

559
00:52:08,542 --> 00:52:10,626
There usually are.

560
00:52:10,711 --> 00:52:15,465
You know, she showed us around.
She was the target's daughter.

561
00:52:17,259 --> 00:52:21,262
And when she had a chance to leave,
she didn't do it.

562
00:52:22,473 --> 00:52:24,557
She had some guts.

563
00:52:25,851 --> 00:52:28,311
Why can't I get that out of my mind?

564
00:52:29,897 --> 00:52:31,939
You know, she stands for something.

565
00:52:32,024 --> 00:52:34,108
You know, man, we don't stand for shit.

566
00:52:34,193 --> 00:52:39,364
We used to, but that dried all up,
like this is gonna dry all up.

567
00:52:39,448 --> 00:52:41,741
This here paint is gonna dry.

568
00:52:42,576 --> 00:52:44,077
What dried up?

569
00:52:46,413 --> 00:52:49,165
Just belief, man. Just the belief in the soul,

570
00:52:49,249 --> 00:52:52,335
just, I don't know,
the human parts, brother.

571
00:52:53,587 --> 00:52:55,922
You remember that time
we was up in Bosnia?

572
00:52:56,673 --> 00:53:00,301
We took down them Serb bad boys.

573
00:53:02,513 --> 00:53:05,765
All our guys were getting chopped up
all around us,

574
00:53:06,600 --> 00:53:08,434
and there was blood everywhere.

575
00:53:08,519 --> 00:53:10,269
I never thought I was gonna make it
out of there,

576
00:53:10,354 --> 00:53:13,314
- and I know you didn't, either.
- Yeah.

577
00:53:13,399 --> 00:53:16,859
Kind of feeling like dead, too, you know?

578
00:53:16,944 --> 00:53:19,654
My head's all a very black place.

579
00:53:19,738 --> 00:53:21,697
I don't believe in shit.

580
00:53:22,616 --> 00:53:25,451
Just goddamn Dracula black.

581
00:53:26,703 --> 00:53:31,374
I remember I got this bottle of the local shit
they have over there, that Slivovitz.

582
00:53:31,458 --> 00:53:34,627
I don't know,
I think that's what it was called.

583
00:53:35,379 --> 00:53:37,463
And I ain't feeling no pain now.

584
00:53:39,049 --> 00:53:40,508
And I'd come up on this...

585
00:53:42,136 --> 00:53:44,762
I'd come up on this old wooden bridge,
and I see this...

586
00:53:51,186 --> 00:53:54,689
I see this woman standing there, you know?
And she's...

587
00:53:55,899 --> 00:53:57,650
I stepped out, and she saw me,

588
00:53:57,734 --> 00:54:02,321
and she's just looking right in my eyes,
and I was looking right in her eyes.

589
00:54:04,116 --> 00:54:06,075
I knew what she was gonna do.

590
00:54:06,160 --> 00:54:09,662
She looked at me,
and I knew she was gonna jump.

591
00:54:10,664 --> 00:54:11,914
You know what I did, man?

592
00:54:11,999 --> 00:54:17,211
I just turned around and I kept walking,
until I heard that splash.

593
00:54:20,966 --> 00:54:22,633
Then she was gone.

594
00:54:24,553 --> 00:54:26,929
And after taking all them lives,

595
00:54:27,014 --> 00:54:32,602
here was one that I could have saved,
but I didn't.

596
00:54:35,230 --> 00:54:37,648
And what I realized later on was,

597
00:54:40,027 --> 00:54:43,321
if I had saved that woman, I might have,

598
00:54:45,657 --> 00:54:48,367
I don't know,
saved what was left of my soul, you know?

599
00:55:32,287 --> 00:55:38,000
A very wise dead man once told me
that a real man never strikes a woman.

600
00:55:39,044 --> 00:55:43,256
You push some if you have to,
but you never strike them.

601
00:55:44,758 --> 00:55:46,801
That's the way I was raised.

602
00:55:46,885 --> 00:55:51,180
This man, however,
does not share that moral dilemma. No.

603
00:55:52,724 --> 00:55:54,100
This man,

604
00:55:57,271 --> 00:55:58,604
well...

605
00:55:59,565 --> 00:56:04,569
So the question, Sandra,
why were the Americans here?

606
00:56:54,703 --> 00:56:56,537
Don't fight back.

607
00:56:58,165 --> 00:56:59,665
Just relax.

608
00:57:30,072 --> 00:57:32,948
Again, what did the Americans tell you?

609
00:57:33,659 --> 00:57:35,242
Who were they after?

610
00:57:37,621 --> 00:57:39,038
Continue.

611
00:57:59,893 --> 00:58:02,770
- I'm going back to Vilena.
- Yeah? Something change?

612
00:58:03,271 --> 00:58:04,980
- What's the plan?
- There is no plan.

613
00:58:05,065 --> 00:58:08,651
- Wait, wait, wait. We need a strategy.
- I'm going. You're not.

614
00:58:08,735 --> 00:58:11,404
- What?
- I said I'm going. You guys aren't.

615
00:58:11,488 --> 00:58:14,323
- What are you, out of your mind?
- It's personal business.

616
00:58:14,408 --> 00:58:16,992
- You don't owe that woman nothing.
- I didn't say I did.

617
00:58:17,077 --> 00:58:19,120
You want to kill yourself? Go ahead, fine.
Your call.

618
00:58:19,204 --> 00:58:22,206
Listen, I don't want to kill myself.
You guys, take care. I got to do this.

619
00:58:22,290 --> 00:58:24,208
- Hey, hey, hey.
- What?

620
00:58:24,292 --> 00:58:26,043
Don't lay this guilt crap on us.
We don't deserve it.

621
00:58:26,128 --> 00:58:30,673
This is my choice. There's no guilt.
There's no guilt. Take care.

622
00:58:36,346 --> 00:58:39,181
Yeah, fuck it. His choice. Yeah.

623
00:58:48,275 --> 00:58:49,400
I said I'm going alone.

624
00:58:49,484 --> 00:58:50,484
I'm going, too.

625
00:58:50,694 --> 00:58:52,486
Come on, Yang, get the hell out.

626
00:58:52,654 --> 00:58:54,113
Just drive.

627
00:59:03,707 --> 00:59:05,958
Don't lose your nerve.

628
00:59:07,586 --> 00:59:09,795
Don't talk to me, cockroach.

629
00:59:21,391 --> 00:59:23,434
So, why are you doing this?

630
00:59:23,518 --> 00:59:25,227
Friends die together.

631
00:59:26,980 --> 00:59:29,273
Hey. Give me the good luck ring. Come on.

632
00:59:30,233 --> 00:59:32,151
Don't make me hurt you, Yang. Come on.

633
00:59:33,695 --> 00:59:35,362
- Speed better than luck.
- Whatever.

634
00:59:37,157 --> 00:59:38,199
It's difficult.

635
00:59:38,533 --> 00:59:39,575
What is?

636
00:59:39,993 --> 00:59:41,994
My life is difficult. I need more money.

637
00:59:42,078 --> 00:59:43,078
Why is that?

638
00:59:43,163 --> 00:59:45,206
- I work harder than the rest.
- No, you don't.

639
00:59:45,290 --> 00:59:49,919
Yes, I do. Because they're taller,
everything is harder for me.

640
00:59:50,003 --> 00:59:54,256
When I get hurt, the wound is bigger
because I'm smaller.

641
00:59:55,217 --> 00:59:57,009
When I travel, I need to go farther.

642
00:59:57,093 --> 00:59:58,511
I know, 'cause you're smaller, right?

643
00:59:58,845 --> 00:59:59,970
Yes.

644
01:00:02,098 --> 01:00:03,349
My life is harder than you think.

645
01:00:05,602 --> 01:00:08,854
- I need more money.
- I know. You told me.

646
01:00:08,939 --> 01:00:10,272
For your family, right?

647
01:00:10,357 --> 01:00:11,607
I don't have family.

648
01:00:11,691 --> 01:00:12,691
I know.

649
01:00:14,319 --> 01:00:15,611
Maybe one day I will.

650
01:00:16,863 --> 01:00:18,155
Down!

651
01:00:44,224 --> 01:00:45,808
- Get out there!
- Why me?

652
01:00:45,892 --> 01:00:47,309
Because you're smaller.

653
01:01:06,162 --> 01:01:07,413
Do that again, I'll kill you!

654
01:01:43,408 --> 01:01:44,617
Gunner!

655
01:01:49,789 --> 01:01:50,998
Come on, Gunner.

656
01:01:52,834 --> 01:01:54,209
Man's good.

657
01:02:26,326 --> 01:02:29,453
What are you doing? You're dead, junkie!

658
01:02:35,669 --> 01:02:36,835
Insect.

659
01:02:50,642 --> 01:02:51,725
Bail!

660
01:03:00,527 --> 01:03:01,819
Shit!

661
01:03:30,682 --> 01:03:31,724
Yang!

662
01:03:39,607 --> 01:03:42,609
What do you wear, size three?
Bring it, happy feet.

663
01:04:48,218 --> 01:04:49,635
My turn!

664
01:04:58,061 --> 01:04:59,102
Gunner!

665
01:05:06,027 --> 01:05:07,736
Shit!

666
01:05:35,640 --> 01:05:37,099
You shot me.

667
01:05:38,226 --> 01:05:40,727
Hey, don't say that.
You were gonna kill him.

668
01:05:41,437 --> 01:05:43,313
I was just gonna scare him.

669
01:05:44,023 --> 01:05:45,857
Don't put that on me. You never liked him.

670
01:05:48,945 --> 01:05:50,404
Am I dying?

671
01:05:50,488 --> 01:05:52,781
The shot's a couple of inches
above your heart.

672
01:05:55,577 --> 01:05:57,536
I'll take that as a yes.

673
01:06:00,665 --> 01:06:03,959
Gunner, who sent you? Who hired you?

674
01:06:05,378 --> 01:06:06,753
Who cares?

675
01:06:06,838 --> 01:06:08,338
Do yourself a favor.

676
01:06:09,090 --> 01:06:13,760
Don't go out a total asshole.
Cooperate for once in your miserable life.

677
01:06:14,721 --> 01:06:16,597
Then bury me right.

678
01:06:16,681 --> 01:06:18,140
You got it.

679
01:06:18,224 --> 01:06:22,644
Who sent you? Who sent you?
ls the girl still alive?

680
01:06:22,729 --> 01:06:24,146
Come closer.

681
01:06:42,749 --> 01:06:44,791
You know, it's not easy being your friend.

682
01:06:45,460 --> 01:06:46,668
That's true.

683
01:06:46,753 --> 01:06:49,254
Man, we'll die with you.
Just don't ask us to do it twice.

684
01:06:49,756 --> 01:06:53,425
I know the layout.
I'll tell you about it on the way.

685
01:06:53,426 --> 01:06:55,052
What the hell happened to you?

686
01:06:55,136 --> 01:06:56,887
It's too sad to talk about it.

687
01:07:00,350 --> 01:07:01,683
Let's fly.

688
01:07:18,993 --> 01:07:22,412
You know, the enemy's
always been terrified of noise,

689
01:07:22,497 --> 01:07:24,289
especially shotguns.

690
01:07:25,708 --> 01:07:28,293
With this big boy spitting out
250 rounds a minute,

691
01:07:28,378 --> 01:07:30,087
you tell me who's tolerating that.

692
01:07:32,590 --> 01:07:34,841
Absolutely zero.

693
01:07:35,468 --> 01:07:39,346
So let me get this right.
Gunner tries to kill you, you shoot him

694
01:07:39,430 --> 01:07:41,431
and, at death's door,
he gives you the whole layout?

695
01:07:41,516 --> 01:07:42,891
Yeah, something like that.

696
01:07:42,975 --> 01:07:45,686
- I would have win.
- I know you would have win.

697
01:07:48,147 --> 01:07:51,608
You know what? I trust you.

698
01:07:52,276 --> 01:07:54,569
I want you to meet my girlfriend.

699
01:07:55,488 --> 01:07:58,323
Omya Kaboom.

700
01:07:58,408 --> 01:07:59,908
You lost me there.

701
01:07:59,992 --> 01:08:02,661
When Omya's prime is struck,

702
01:08:02,745 --> 01:08:06,164
she gets off a miniature warhead
that arms itself.

703
01:08:06,916 --> 01:08:09,876
And when that happens,
anything that gets in my lady's way

704
01:08:09,961 --> 01:08:12,629
becomes instant red sauce and Jell-O.

705
01:08:12,714 --> 01:08:14,005
And if that doesn't work,

706
01:08:18,344 --> 01:08:20,095
her sister will.

707
01:08:20,179 --> 01:08:21,638
You should meet my doctor.

708
01:08:21,723 --> 01:08:23,056
Too late.

709
01:09:49,477 --> 01:09:51,853
It's 3:36. We have 20 minutes
to take this place down.

710
01:09:51,938 --> 01:09:53,814
I'll take the cellar.

711
01:09:53,898 --> 01:09:55,148
We've got company.

712
01:09:56,400 --> 01:09:57,776
I got him. You guys take off.

713
01:10:26,138 --> 01:10:28,890
Is there a reason you've taken
the soldiers this man has trained

714
01:10:28,975 --> 01:10:31,351
and made them look like fools?

715
01:10:32,228 --> 01:10:34,479
They look like warriors.

716
01:10:38,776 --> 01:10:41,111
Warriors loyal to me.

717
01:10:42,405 --> 01:10:46,491
I thought the people of Vilena
hired these mercenaries to kill me.

718
01:10:47,869 --> 01:10:52,414
But then I think maybe this is your plan,
because you cannot control me.

719
01:10:52,498 --> 01:10:55,959
And torturing Sandra works for you.

720
01:10:56,794 --> 01:10:59,671
You want to kill her to make me suffer.

721
01:11:01,007 --> 01:11:04,259
A man can never kill a child.

722
01:11:05,511 --> 01:11:06,887
But you can.

723
01:11:06,971 --> 01:11:08,847
Bring Sandra here.

724
01:11:09,765 --> 01:11:13,768
Bring her now or I will kill you.

725
01:11:13,853 --> 01:11:15,228
Go get her.

726
01:14:19,205 --> 01:14:21,915
- No, no.
- Sandra, Sandra, it's me. Sandra.

727
01:14:21,999 --> 01:14:25,376
Hey, it's me, it's me. Sandra, it's me.

728
01:14:26,045 --> 01:14:28,880
It's me. It's me. It's okay.

729
01:14:29,924 --> 01:14:32,342
Nobody's gonna hurt you, all right?

730
01:14:32,426 --> 01:14:33,760
How are you here?

731
01:14:33,886 --> 01:14:35,428
I just am.

732
01:14:37,223 --> 01:14:39,265
- Can you move?
- Yes.

733
01:14:39,350 --> 01:14:40,809
Okay.

734
01:14:40,893 --> 01:14:43,228
Yeah, okay. All right, let's go.

735
01:14:47,149 --> 01:14:48,149
Time's up.

736
01:14:48,234 --> 01:14:49,567
- Where's Barney?
- What's the call?

737
01:14:49,652 --> 01:14:50,652
We can't find him in 10 minutes,

738
01:14:50,736 --> 01:14:51,694
we're going out the same way we came in.

739
01:14:51,779 --> 01:14:53,113
- No way.
- That's what he'd want.

740
01:14:53,197 --> 01:14:55,240
Ten minutes! Let's go.

741
01:15:22,560 --> 01:15:24,102
No. Stop him!

742
01:15:25,229 --> 01:15:27,272
- This is not his fight. It's mine.
- Get her out of here.

743
01:15:28,315 --> 01:15:29,357
Seal the building.

744
01:15:30,609 --> 01:15:32,318
Stand him up.

745
01:15:36,365 --> 01:15:38,992
You know,
if you didn't have this Kevlar vest,

746
01:15:39,076 --> 01:15:41,327
your insides are gonna be
like fucking mush.

747
01:15:41,412 --> 01:15:42,537
Well, ain't that sad?

748
01:15:42,621 --> 01:15:43,788
You know, you're a lucky man.

749
01:15:43,873 --> 01:15:45,373
You're the lucky man.

750
01:15:45,457 --> 01:15:47,834
No, no, you're a lucky man.

751
01:15:48,502 --> 01:15:50,879
- He told me to keep you conscious.
- Did he?

752
01:15:52,590 --> 01:15:54,215
All right.

753
01:15:57,970 --> 01:15:59,512
You're a real tough guy, aren't you?

754
01:15:59,597 --> 01:16:02,056
- What?
- Are you a real tough guy?

755
01:16:02,641 --> 01:16:04,517
Look at me, you piece of trash.

756
01:16:04,643 --> 01:16:06,186
How many men you got?

757
01:16:06,270 --> 01:16:07,896
Just your mother.

758
01:16:21,452 --> 01:16:22,869
Now this is your last time.

759
01:16:22,953 --> 01:16:26,539
You give me the right answer,
and I'll cut you a break.

760
01:16:28,459 --> 01:16:31,544
If you give me the wrong answer,
you will die a damn slow death.

761
01:16:31,629 --> 01:16:33,213
Do you understand me?

762
01:16:33,297 --> 01:16:35,089
- Do you understand me?
- Yep.

763
01:16:35,174 --> 01:16:38,009
- Who sent you?
- Can't breathe.

764
01:16:38,010 --> 01:16:39,719
Loosen up.

765
01:16:40,471 --> 01:16:41,721
Who sent you?

766
01:16:44,224 --> 01:16:46,267
Your hairdresser.

767
01:18:58,233 --> 01:18:59,484
Go, we gotta go!

768
01:19:20,380 --> 01:19:22,173
Come on.

769
01:19:45,697 --> 01:19:46,864
Shit!

770
01:20:08,428 --> 01:20:09,887
Remember this shit at Christmas!

771
01:20:13,517 --> 01:20:14,517
Damn, that thing's loud.

772
01:20:14,601 --> 01:20:17,186
- What happened to you?
- I got my ass kicked.

773
01:20:19,773 --> 01:20:21,440
Come on. Get my rifle. Let's go.

774
01:20:28,615 --> 01:20:29,740
What's this?

775
01:20:32,327 --> 01:20:35,037
Everything bad that has happened,
you bring.

776
01:20:35,122 --> 01:20:36,747
Take your money!

777
01:20:37,791 --> 01:20:40,918
I only see death with you. Take it all and go.

778
01:20:41,086 --> 01:20:42,295
I'm not going anywhere.

779
01:20:42,379 --> 01:20:43,629
You are done here.

780
01:20:43,714 --> 01:20:45,006
You can't succeed without me.

781
01:20:45,215 --> 01:20:46,549
I am the leader.

782
01:20:46,633 --> 01:20:48,217
You're a puppet in a hat.

783
01:20:49,761 --> 01:20:50,887
No.

784
01:21:09,740 --> 01:21:10,948
Now!

785
01:21:13,744 --> 01:21:15,077
Get back.

786
01:21:23,962 --> 01:21:25,588
Throw down your weapons.

787
01:21:26,965 --> 01:21:28,507
There's no way out.

788
01:21:31,220 --> 01:21:32,720
Shit's getting old!

789
01:21:33,055 --> 01:21:35,264
- Your lucky ring stinks.
- I know.

790
01:21:35,724 --> 01:21:37,308
- Let's backtrack.
- The building's rigged.

791
01:21:37,392 --> 01:21:39,435
It's the only way out.

792
01:21:50,072 --> 01:21:51,364
Chopper's ready in five minutes.

793
01:21:51,448 --> 01:21:52,490
We're not leaving yet.

794
01:22:02,042 --> 01:22:04,919
- What's he saying?
- He said we're dead with an accent.

795
01:22:05,003 --> 01:22:06,337
We ain't dead.

796
01:22:06,421 --> 01:22:08,214
- Blow the building.
- Not yet.

797
01:22:08,298 --> 01:22:11,926
We will kill this American disease.

798
01:22:29,486 --> 01:22:30,778
Blow the building!

799
01:22:30,862 --> 01:22:32,113
She's still in there!

800
01:22:32,197 --> 01:22:33,698
The money!

801
01:22:38,745 --> 01:22:40,745
Blow it!

802
01:22:51,883 --> 01:22:54,802
She's out. Blow the fucking building!

803
01:24:44,746 --> 01:24:46,205
I'm out!

804
01:25:40,010 --> 01:25:41,677
Let's go. Come on.

805
01:25:42,679 --> 01:25:44,221
Cut Munroe off!

806
01:26:44,324 --> 01:26:45,449
Come on!

807
01:28:26,968 --> 01:28:28,218
Hey!

808
01:28:28,303 --> 01:28:29,762
- Thing's too heavy.
- Give me it.

809
01:28:29,846 --> 01:28:32,556
- What do you want me to do?
- Throw it as hard as you can.

810
01:28:58,583 --> 01:29:00,417
- Blow the dump.
- Got it!

811
01:29:32,742 --> 01:29:33,784
Munroe!

812
01:29:35,704 --> 01:29:39,123
Drop the weapons,
or I'll put a bullet through her eye.

813
01:29:41,418 --> 01:29:42,626
Don't test me.

814
01:29:53,513 --> 01:29:55,055
No, no, no.

815
01:29:55,140 --> 01:29:57,474
Shut up or I'll kill you.

816
01:29:59,436 --> 01:30:02,563
The agency parasites hired you,
didn't they?

817
01:30:02,647 --> 01:30:06,483
I'd have paid you twice as much
to go fishing.

818
01:30:06,568 --> 01:30:09,278
You'd have to think
I'm pretty freaking stupid

819
01:30:09,362 --> 01:30:11,113
to surrender to the agency.

820
01:30:11,197 --> 01:30:15,993
Why would I do that? I created this.
I made it all happen.

821
01:30:16,536 --> 01:30:20,664
And then they wanted me out. Why?
Because I saw the big picture.

822
01:30:21,583 --> 01:30:22,750
Stop walking.

823
01:30:24,586 --> 01:30:28,589
And what about me and you?
We're both the same.

824
01:30:28,673 --> 01:30:32,801
We're both mercenaries.
We're both dead inside.

825
01:30:33,178 --> 01:30:35,220
So why the hell did you come after me?

826
01:30:35,305 --> 01:30:38,766
I didn't come after you, dipshit.
I came for her!

827
01:30:57,994 --> 01:30:59,703
- You okay?
- Yeah.

828
01:31:00,497 --> 01:31:02,164
Call it a tie.

829
01:31:04,709 --> 01:31:06,001
Yeah, I guess so.

830
01:31:06,377 --> 01:31:08,754
You know, you're not as fast as you think.

831
01:31:08,838 --> 01:31:11,006
I'm beginning to sense that.

832
01:31:23,770 --> 01:31:27,815
The second account number's mine.
It'll help get things going around here.

833
01:31:27,899 --> 01:31:30,234
No, I can't. You've done so much.

834
01:31:30,318 --> 01:31:34,571
Yeah, well, so have you. A gift for a gift.
You take it.

835
01:31:35,031 --> 01:31:39,076
- Will you come back?
- I promise I'll always be around.

836
01:31:48,127 --> 01:31:49,711
You take care, Sandra.

837
01:31:52,590 --> 01:31:53,715
You take care.

838
01:31:59,764 --> 01:32:00,931
Bye.

839
01:32:28,001 --> 01:32:29,001
What?

840
01:32:29,627 --> 01:32:30,627
Truthfully?

841
01:32:30,962 --> 01:32:32,212
Yeah?

842
01:32:32,714 --> 01:32:34,631
I never really thought she was your type.

843
01:32:59,657 --> 01:33:01,533
All right, baby. All right.

844
01:33:01,618 --> 01:33:02,993
Come on, let's see what you got.

845
01:33:05,622 --> 01:33:06,914
That's my boy!

846
01:33:11,669 --> 01:33:12,836
Go south!

847
01:33:18,343 --> 01:33:20,385
You lost! You lost!

848
01:33:24,057 --> 01:33:26,516
So you're back from the dead.
How you healing?

849
01:33:27,101 --> 01:33:30,562
Good, considering
you could have killed me.

850
01:33:30,688 --> 01:33:32,230
I forgive you.

851
01:33:32,523 --> 01:33:33,774
Okay.

852
01:33:34,275 --> 01:33:35,943
I would have win.

853
01:33:36,027 --> 01:33:37,694
Of course.

854
01:33:39,781 --> 01:33:40,822
Hey, Gunner.

855
01:33:41,532 --> 01:33:44,534
Whatever doesn't kill you
makes you stronger, brother. Therapy.

856
01:33:45,912 --> 01:33:47,204
Man's got a point.

857
01:33:51,417 --> 01:33:52,542
You know what?

858
01:33:53,044 --> 01:33:54,753
I'm gonna do you a favor, Tool.

859
01:33:56,255 --> 01:33:58,632
"I once knew a man called Tool..."

860
01:33:58,716 --> 01:34:00,467
I love poetry.

861
01:34:00,885 --> 01:34:04,262
"To me, was the epitome of cool"

862
01:34:05,765 --> 01:34:07,057
"He was good with a knife"

863
01:34:10,186 --> 01:34:11,895
"Bad with a wife..."

864
01:34:13,022 --> 01:34:14,022
That hurts.

865
01:34:14,107 --> 01:34:16,358
"But to think he could beat me"

866
01:34:17,443 --> 01:34:20,570
"Dreaming he'd defeat me"

867
01:34:22,281 --> 01:34:23,615
"Cool Tool"

868
01:34:25,702 --> 01:34:27,035
"You gotta be a fool"

869
01:34:31,332 --> 01:34:33,332
Oh, yeah.