- What kind is it?
- I don't know.
White?
And the frame?
- Dark.
- Postmark?
Same as last time.
And no note.
No.
I'm so sorry, Henrik.
Will you appeal?
What is this?
The media event of the year?
Don't try to play it down, Mikael.
It won't work.
Don't try to play it up.
That won't work either.
Mikael, can we get a quote?
Mikael, will you appeal?
Yes. I'll appeal to you, Viggo.
Up until today, Mr. Blomkvist
was able to play the victim...
...the brave journalist going up
against the bad guy.
I don't know why malicious intent
couldn't be proven.
- When you call a guy a criminal--
- If you want to say these things--
Mikael Blomkvist likes publicity.
There's really no greater disgrace
for a journalist than libel.
-- Was found guilty today on 16 counts
of aggravated libel.
Can I get that sandwich there?
And a black coffee.
In an article published earlier
this year, Blomkvist claimed...
Wennerström, founder and president
of the Wennerström Group...
...used state funds intended
for industrial development in Poland...
...in an arms deal with the right-wing
Ustase in Croatia.
I have nothing against Mr. Blomkvist.
He's a fine journalist...
...who I don't believe
is guided by malice.
But what he wrote was inaccurate.
And inaccuracies
can't go unanswered.
All journalists have to accept,
like the rest of us...
...actions have consequences.
Blomkvist was ordered to pay...
...600,000 Swedish kronor
in damages and all court costs.
Can I get a packet of Marlboro Red
and a lighter?
Yeah.
- Where have you been?
- Walking. Thinking.
- Smoking?
- Yeah. Just one.
TV4 called.
I told them no statement...
...until we've read
the judgment in its entirety.
Well, I have. Anyone else?
Everyone who wants
to see you humiliated.
- Been on the phone all morning?
- I'm as much to blame.
- You are? You wrote it?
- I read it. I ran it.
- Not the same.
- Our credibility isn't dead yet.
Mine is.
I'm tired.
I'm gonna go home,
crawl under the duvet for a week.
I'll call Greger,
tell him I'm not coming home.
Thank you.
It's possible we could wait forever.
- You called her and spoke to her?
- I'm afraid that doesn't mean much.
No one here particularly likes her.
I find it's much better
if she works from home.
But you told her
I wanted to meet with her.
I've told her many times
I prefer her not to meet clients.
- You like her?
- Very much.
She's one of the best investigators
I have, as you saw from her report.
- But?
- I'm concerned you won't like her.
- She's different.
- In what way?
In every way.
Miss Salander is here.
Lisbeth.
Mr. Dirch Frode.
How do you do?
Something wrong with the report?
No, it was quite thorough.
But I'm also interested
in what's not in it.
- There's nothing not in it.
- Your opinion of him isn't.
- I'm not paid to give my opinion.
- So you don't have one?
He's clean, in my opinion.
You mean he's hygienic?
He's who he presents himself to be.
In his business, that's an asset.
Well, there's less in his asset column
after his conviction today.
True. He made a fool of himself.
If it happened that way.
Are you suggesting
that he was set up?
That was never part
of my assignment.
But you're right.
He did make a fool of himself
professionally.
How much of a fool did he make
of himself financially?
The judgment will just about
empty his savings.
- May I go?
- Moment.
Your report is light in another area.
His personal life.
Anything you chose not to disclose?
Nothing that warranted inclusion.
Does that mean yes or no?
I think what Miss Salander means, and
I agree, is that everyone has a right...
...to a certain amount of privacy,
even if they're being investigated.
Not in this case.
I need to know anything about him...
...I might find unsavory,
even if she doesn't.
He's had a longstanding
sexual relationship...
...with his co-editor of the magazine.
It wrecked his marriage but not hers.
Sometimes he performs cunnilingus.
Not often enough, in my opinion.
No, you're right not to include that.
I know.
You needed a better attorney.
You needed your sister.
- She offered.
- He declined.
- As she hoped.
- Never a good idea.
- Mixing family and business.
- I would've lost anyway.
It wasn't about Mikael. It was about
Wennerström sending a message...
...to the press and the FSA,
saying, "Don't ask questions."
Cheer up.
Dad.
Nilla, you don't have
to worry about me.
- Mom's worried.
- About me?
About the money.
Good evening.
Nilla? What are you doing?
Nothing.
Are you serious?
I don't wanna talk about it
since I know you won't approve.
Of...?
- Nilla.
- Light of Life.
Light of what?
- Hello?
- Herr Blomkvist.
- Yeah.
- Forgive me for intruding on Christmas.
My name is Dirch Frode.
I'm an attorney. I represent Henrik
Vanger. Perhaps you've heard of him?
Yeah, of course I have.
He'd love to talk to you
about a private matter.
This is an awkward moment.
Oh, I'm sorry. I'm about to sit down
to a Christmas dinner myself.
No, that's not exactly what I meant.
You're referring
to your recent legal problems.
That has provided us
with much amusement.
I'm sorry?
Herr Vanger has little love
for Herr Wennerström either.
- Have him call me.
- But he would love to speak to you...
...in person, if possible. Up north.
- In Hedestad.
- That's not gonna be possible.
Herr Blomkvist, he's far too old
to go to Stockholm. Please.
Be so kind as to consider.
Hedestad is lovely in the winter.
I'll call you back on this number.
Okay?
Usually when I wake up in a cold bed
it's at home.
- I'm sorry.
- What are you doing?
- I'm writing a press release.
- Saying?
You're taking over as publisher,
you're very sorry...
...for any nuisance
Mr. Wennerström was caused...
...and I can't be reached for comment.
- Are you giving up?
Stepping aside.
This makes me sick.
- First time in Hedestad?
- And the last.
Oh, don't say that.
It's lovely in the spring.
You said it would be lovely
in the winter.
Well, this is unseasonable.
Well, I'll be on the 4:30 train
back to Stockholm.
Unless we get snowed in.
I'm joking-
You'll be home tonight,
if that's what you wish.
Welcome.
Come inside.
It's warm.
How do you do?
So...
...what do you know about me?
You used to run one of the largest
industrial firms in the country.
- "Used to." That's correct.
- Oh, I didn't mean that.
- Should I stay?
- No.
My grandfather forged the tracks...
...that the 4:30 train
will take you home on.
We stitched this country together.
We made the steel, milled the lumber
that built modern Sweden.
And what do you think
our most profitable product now is?
Fertilizer.
I'm not obsessed by
the declining health of the company.
But I am with
the settling of accounts.
And the clock is ticking.
I need your help.
I'm-- Doing what?
Officially, assisting
with my memoirs.
But what you'll really be doing...
...is solving a mystery
by doing what you do so well.
Your recent legal mishap
notwithstanding.
You will be investigating thieves,
misers, bullies...
...the most detestable collection
of people that you will ever meet.
My family.
Would you like to sit? I could possibly
clear a place if necessary.
- Did you make it?
- Have you something for me?
I am on welfare, I do not administer it.
This is not enough.
No, thank you.
This is Harriet.
The granddaughter
of my brother Richard.
Richard was a Nazi
of the first order...
...joining the Nationalist Socialist
Freedom League when he was 17.
Isn't it interesting how fascists
always steal the word "freedom"?
Oh, the 4:30. Yes, I know. Okay.
Anyway, Richard died a martyr
to the Nazi cause in 1940.
Missed all the real excitement.
But not the opportunity to regularly
beat his wife, Margareta...
...and their son, Gottfried.
Now, Gottfried, Harriet's father...
...was what they used to call
a good-time Charlie.
- They still call them that.
- Do they? Okay.
He was a charmer,
a ladies' man and a drunk.
In other words, a born salesman.
Which he did for the company...
...traveling around
and taking clients out to dinner.
- Well, somebody's gotta do it.
- That's right.
Anyway, he died in 1965.
Drowned, drunk, here on the island.
His wife, Isabella, who had been pretty
much useless as a parent before...
...became even more so
after his death...
...which is when I began
looking after the children.
Martin, who runs Vanger Industries,
now that I'm retired.
That's right, I Googled him.
And Harriet.
She was bright, curious...
...a winning combination
in any person.
- And beautiful.
- Yeah.
Something happened to her?
Someone in the family
murdered Harriet...
...and for the past 40 years...
...has been trying
to drive me insane.
It was September 24th, 1966.
A Saturday.
Harriet was 16.
My brothers...
...and their wives and their children
and grandchildren...
...were all gathered here...
...for our loathsome annual
board meeting and dinner.
It was also the day the yacht club
held their autumn parade.
Harriet, with one or two school
friends, went into town to see it.
She returned a little after 2:00.
She came into the parlor.
She asked if she could talk to me.
I honestly don't remember
what I was doing...
...that I thought
was more important...
...but I told her
to give me a few minutes.
It was during those few minutes
that something else occurred.
The accident had nothing to do
with Harriet...
...and yet everything.
It was chaos as everybody
put down what they were doing.
Police, ambulance, fire brigade...
...reporters, photographers, onlookers
all quickly arrived from town...
...just as we on the island, the family,
hurried to the bridge from our side.
The driver of the car...
...a man named Aronsson...
...was pinned and severely injured.
We tried desperately
to pry him loose with our hands...
...since metal tools might spark.
It was an hour after the crash
that Harriet was in the kitchen.
Anna herself saw her.
Well, we finally got poor Aronsson
out of his car and off to the hospital.
Just as we from our side...
...slowly drifted back to the house.
The sun was down,
the excitement over.
We sat down to dinner.
It was then that I noticed...
...Harriet wasn't there.
And she wasn't there
the next morning.
Or the next.
Or the next 40 years.
What was she going to tell me?
Why didn't I make time for her?
Why didn't I listen?
- And she couldn't have just run away?
- No. Not without being seen.
The firemen stayed out all night...
...on the bridge
pumping up gasoline.
No one swam across
or took a boat.
All the boats were still tied up
on this side Sunday.
Believe me, I checked.
She couldn't have just fallen
and drowned?
No. The currents aren't strong here.
Anything that falls in the water turns up.
Like her father.
His body didn't drift
more than 10 meters...
...when he drowned the year before.
Oh, no. Someone killed her.
Someone on the island that day.
Someone close enough to know...
...what she used to give me
each year on my birthday.
Those are from her.
And the rest, from her killer.
Who knows about these?
There's me, the police, the killer...
...and now you.
After the police investigation
evaporated...
...I kept at it, studying
all the information there was.
I have spent half my life
examining the events of a single day.
I understand your frustration...
...but what you're asking me to do,
it's a waste of money.
- But we haven't discussed your fee.
- We don't need to.
Thank you.
I can't find something
you've been unable to find in 40 years.
You don't know that. You have
a very keen investigative mind.
Here's what I propose:
You come stay on the island.
I have a nice little cottage
by the water you can use.
You study the material I send you.
You find something I've missed
or you don't.
What you're asking me to do
is set aside my life and career for--
Think of this
as a well-deserved holiday
A way of avoiding all those people
that you might want to avoid right now.
As for compensation,
I'll pay you double your salary...
...for as many months as it takes.
- Quadruple it if you solve the mystery.
- Herr Vanger--
I'm not done.
I will throw in one more thing...
...even though
you're a terrible negotiator.
It's something you want
more than anything else...
...and it can't be bought at any price.
So let me give it to you.
Hans-Erik Wennerström.
He began his career
working for me...
...and I have followed it with interest,
shall we say, ever since.
You were right about him.
You just couldn't prove it.
We're in the middle of the worst crisis
ever, and you're writing a memoir.
- You fired me. I need something to do.
- You fired you.
I need you here, not the North Pole.
Mikael, you know
what this is going to look like.
Like I've been gutted.
I'm running away. I am.
Wennerström wants to see me
wave a white flag, not a red flag.
If it looks like there's a problem
between us, it'll satisfy him.
There is a problem between us.
He won't be satisfied
until he shuts us down.
- You're leaving me to fight him alone.
- It's four hours by train.
It's not the North Pole.
Hey, he)'-
Network busy.
Please try again later.
What?
Some milk?
Network busy.
Please try again later.
Oh, yeah. These as well.
- You're Mr. Palmgren's daughter?
- His ward. He doesn't have a daughter.
Please.
He's had severe
cerebral hemorrhaging...
...either from the fall itself
or from a stroke that led to the fall.
His blood pressure is still high.
I'm hopeful he'll regain consciousness,
but that's not assured.
And it's possible, even if he does...
...that there will be
neurological damage.
Oh, jeez.
Hi. I'm Gunnar.
The caretaker.
- Oh, hey, Gunnar. Come in.
- Okay.
- You want to put it in there?
You're an author.
Well, I'm doing a biography
of Herr Vanger.
- I saw you on television.
- That's unfortunate.
Bit of trouble, I guess.
- No jail time though. That's good.
- No.
Cost you a lot of money
though, yeah?
There.
The entire island
is owned by my family.
Your closest neighbor
is my brother Harald...
...another Nazi, if you can believe.
Two in the family.
Oh, yes, he's quite detestable,
to put it nicely.
But you'll probably never see him.
He's a recluse.
- He was there that day?
- Indeed, he was.
His daughter, Cecilia,
lives over there.
They don't speak.
Does anybody speak
to anybody on this island?
Actually, Isabella, Harriet's mother,
who lives there...
...she speaks to Harald, which is one
of the reasons I don't speak to her.
Right.
Cecilia's brother, Birger,
lives over there.
Who doesn't he speak to?
You, probably.
But you wouldn't want him to. He can
be just as unpleasant as Harald.
Quickly losing track
of who's who here.
How you'll wish it were always so.
Soon you will know us all
only too well. With my apologies.
Now, out there, my grandnephew
Martin's house, Harriet's brother.
- Who speaks to him?
- I speak to him.
He runs the company now,
as I think I told you.
Someone's shooting his dinner.
Gunnar, probably.
Oh, yes, I met him earlier.
He was 19 when
Harriet disappeared.
Well, he lives over there.
- And you live there.
- Sorry?
Your house.
Oh, yes.
Yes, you're right.
The man who hires the detective...
...should always be kept
on the suspects list.
Her mother.
But what about the search? Please.
Please. I beg you.
The fact that I never found a body
was not surprising.
You can't dig up an entire island.
But neither could I find the motive.
Was it spontaneous?
Was it calculated?
Did she know something
someone wished she didn't?
- Was it about business?
- Business? Well, she was 16.
And very bright.
Henrik told me and many others
he could easily see her...
...running the company one day.
She was with some friends
that day at a parade.
She told them she was feeling unwell.
She left early.
But they also told me
she kept secrets from them too.
The main thing I learned was that
teenage girls are complicated.
- I have one.
- Then you know.
I wanted to...
...ask you about this.
She received that from Henrik
the Christmas before.
I've studied it more times
than I can say.
I know every page of it.
- It's the last page I was curious about.
- As was I.
It's a list of names, numbers
and it must have some significance.
All local phone numbers.
The first belonged
to a woman, Margot...
...whose mother was Magda,
who denied knowing Harriet.
The fourth, R.L.,
belonged to Rosmarie Larsson...
...an elderly woman who died
some years before.
The other three were not connected
in any way that I could find.
I reminded you of things
you'd rather forget, and I'm sorry.
I can't forget.
It's my Rebecka case.
I don't know what that is.
Every policeman has at least one
unsolved case to obsess over.
Back then we had an
Officer Torstensson.
Year after year, he kept
going back to this Rebecka case.
Taking out the files,
studying them over and over.
We were young.
We laughed at him.
And that was also
a missing-girl case?
No, no, no,
that's not why I mention it.
I'm talking about
the soul of a policeman.
Poor old Torstensson
never solved it.
And he never let it go.
So how's Mr. Palmgren doing?
I heard he had a stroke
of some kind?
It's terrible.
Now, what exactly do you do
at this security company?
Make coffee, sort mail.
But not full-time.
Not even part-time consistently.
They somehow got along without
coffee or mail in July and August?
- How much do you make there?
- Enough.
How much is your rent?
I Pay my rent.
And when was the last time
you were late?
Never.
You think that thing through your
eyebrow makes you attractive?
Here's the problem.
There's a discrepancy
between the obligation...
...of Mr. Palmgren's guardianship
and the management of your finances.
There's no discrepancy. It was clear
I could manage my own finances.
That is not clear to me.
- I'm not a child.
- You are not. But you were.
And between then and now,
you were committed...
...to the locked ward of St. Stefan's
where you continued...
...to display violent aggression.
And you failed to adapt
to four foster homes...
...were arrested twice for intoxication,
twice for narcotics...
...again for assault,
smashing a bottle into a man's face.
And it's not even that long ago.
You may have conned Mr. Palmgren
into thinking that you have changed...
...but when I'm looking at this...
...not to mention the way
you're looking at me now...
...I don't think you have.
So the good old
Mr. Palmgren days are over.
Starting now, you will be given
a monthly allowance.
You'll provide me with receipts
for your expenses.
If the numbers don't balance, I assume
the difference is going to drugs.
I've taken care of myself
since I was 10.
The state has taken care of you.
Miss Salander, please, look at me,
this is important.
Since your behavior
is elaborately documented in here...
...it will shock no one
if I chose an alternative...
...to the very lenient arrangement
I have just outlined.
Would you prefer
institutionalization?
- Mikael?
- Yes.
- I'm Liv.
- Oh, hi.
We're going to the same place.
Hop in.
Oh, good, thank you.
I found him at death's door,
halfway up the hill.
- I'm afraid I'm a little out of shape.
- It's a climb for anyone.
- I should've warned you. Come in.
- Thank you, Martin.
Henrik says great things about you.
- No, no. Leave your shoes on.
- Martin? Smells wonderful.
- What are we drinking?
- What a place. Look at that view.
I used to work in the company's
petrochemical division in Göteborg.
When it was sold, I went with it.
A dark day.
I live in Hong Kong, but come back
to Stockholm for family events.
And I drive up to spend
a couple of days with Martin.
- It's just the moose steak she wants.
- Who can blame her? It's wonderful.
Something's left open.
Do you like this wine...
...or you want to try something else?
- No, no, it's fine.
You're writing a book now,
Martin said.
- Henrik's biography.
- I love Henrik. He's fascinating.
Martin too.
Together they are the old Sweden
and the new.
Yes, they are.
You know about Harriet, right?
- You don't?
- Yes, I do.
The family doesn't want to talk about it,
but it can't be swept under the rug.
- What can't?
- Harriet.
We can talk about it later.
We can talk about it now.
Liv knows everything
about my crazy family.
- That's why she'll never marry me.
- That's one reason.
I don't want to read
about that in the book.
Everything else is fine.
Harriet certainly.
You know,
everything changed after that.
Not just the family
but the company as well.
- How so?
- We're not Ericsson or Nordea.
But we're still the largest
family-owned company in the country.
At our height we had
40,000 employees.
We have half of that now.
And that downward slide
began after my sister's death.
It broke Henrik's
entrepreneurial spirit...
...and his heart.
- You were here that day?
- I came in later...
...after the accident on the bridge,
with the 4:30 train.
- I know it well.
- A terrible day.
And the days after, you know?
Searching, not finding. Even worse.
This event, Mikael, it has to have
a big part in your book.
I got a call from social welfare.
I've been assigned a new guardian.
- Hi.
- Hello.
I thought I'd come over
and say hello.
- I'm Cecilia.
- Oh, yes. Please, come in.
Can I get you some coffee?
No, thank you.
We are all uncomfortable with the idea
of a chronicle of our family.
It's not about the family.
It's about Henrik and the company.
Like I said.
It's not my intention to present
a malicious portrait of anyone.
Unlike the one
that landed you in court.
Unlike that one, yes.
So you're not really here to find out
what happened to Harriet.
I can't ignore such a dramatic event,
but, no, that's by no means my focus.
Those boxes that Gunnar
carted down here...
...which are where, in the closet now?
Those weren't Henrik's investigation?
I wonder sometimes who's crazier,
my Nazi father or my obsessed uncle.
Since we're talking about her...
...since you brought her up,
what was she like?
What was Harriet like?
- I'm sure Henrik has told you.
- He was my age back then.
He couldn't know what was
really going on with a teenager.
You were the same age.
My sister Anita
was closer to her in age.
She knew Harriet better than anyone.
You should talk to her.
- I'd love to. Where is she?
- If I had to guess, London.
You don't know
where your sister lives?
I haven't seen her in years.
We never really got along.
- I'm getting used to that comment.
- She hates this place more than I do.
She left.
Moved to London, that was it.
You couldn't pay her to send
a Christmas card, much less visit.
I'll track her down for you.
If you do, and try talking
to her about us...
...don't be surprised
if she tells you to fuck oh'.
You're backed up, aren't you?
Hard drive at home, yeah.
Okay. That's good,
because this one's done.
Have you ever had any
sexually transmitted diseases?
And when was the last time
that you were tested for HIV?
How many partners have you had
in the last month?
And how many of those were men?
It's regulation, I have to ask
these things. It's a health matter.
Write what you want.
And why do you need
such an expensive computer?
- For work.
- Making coffee, sorting mail.
- I should have control of my money.
- And you will.
Once you learn to be sociable,
get along with people.
Can you do that?
Why don't we start
with that now, huh?
Why don't we start with me?
You do something for me,
I do something for you.
That's what normal people do.
I want you to have that computer.
Feel that.
That's gabardine.
Unzip it.
And...
I like the reticence.
It's almost convincing.
Anita Vanger.
- Through there.
- Thank you.
Excuse me.
I probably should have made
an appointment.
No, it's fine.
- Please have a seat.
- Thank you.
- Mikael.
- Mikael. How do you do?
How do you do?
So you're looking
for investment counseling?
Well, I would be if I had any money.
I'm sorry, I don't understand.
I'm writing a biography of your
Uncle Henrik. That's why I'm here.
I haven't seen him in over 20 years.
Actually it's a lot more than that.
Haven't seen my sister,
haven't seen anyone in that family.
Most of what I'm writing about
predates that...
...so your recollections are valid.
I wouldn't know where to start,
if that was a question.
Well, then let me narrow it down.
I've gotten up to the 1960s...
...to the event that, you know,
changed everything in Henrik's life.
Harriet.
Everything that I know about that
I told to whatever his name was.
Morell.
My recollections
were a lot better then.
I'm not really speaking
about the event itself.
I just want to get a clearer sense
of what Harriet was like.
She was very messed up.
Well, just like all us Vanger kids,
really, but...
Crazy mother.
Drunken father.
At least her father wasn't a Nazi.
- Was he abusive?
- Mine?
No, hers.
Not that I ever saw, but you could tell
that something was going on.
Some days
she'd be very withdrawn.
And then the next minute
she'd be putting on makeup...
...and wearing the tightest sweater
that she had to school.
And then she'd be studying
her Bible like a nun.
No Vanger was ever religious.
Can you imagine?
She was obviously very unhappy.
- What do you think happened to her?
- Everyone knows what.
You don't have any thoughts
about who or why?
All that I know
is that I felt really sorry for her.
I got away when I was 18
and I never went back.
And she'd have done the same.
But she never made it to 18.
Mr. Bjurman, please.
It's Lisbeth Salander.
Hold for a moment, please.
Lisbeth, I haven't seen you
Are you well?
I'm fine. I'm sorry I missed our
appointment, I had a lot of work.
Something the matter?
No, no, nothing to be
concerned about.
Actually, I need another advance
on my allowance.
Can I come to your office tonight?
I don't work at night, Lisbeth.
Why don't you come to my house,
huh? Do you have a pen?
I don't need a pen.
What's the address?
It's...
- Hello?
- It's me.
Lisbeth.
Come on in.
- You like it?
- It's nice.
It's home.
What do you need money for
this time?
Food.
How are you?
I'm so glad you decided
to come and visit.
I just want my money.
Well, let's see if we can
help you out with that.
Wait.
Is there a problem?
I just want to know...
...am I going to have to do this
every time I need money to eat?
You're so cute when you're surly.
I forgot to ask you:
You like anal sex?
Faith is the assurance
of things hoped for...
...the evidence of things not seen.
Through faith we understand...
...that the world was created
by the word of God.
- I'll drive you home.
- I can get home on my own.
Are you sure?
- Is it any warmer inside?
- No.
I apologize if you've been having
financial problems...
...at the magazine
during Mikael's absence.
- We'll work through them.
- Are you sure?
How long do you think
you can hang on?
Six months?
That sounds about right.
I used to be
in the newspaper business.
- We owned six dailies back in the '50s.
- We still own one.
- The Courier, here in town.
- Which I let my nephew, Birger, run...
...because he can't run
anything else.
So, what would you say
to taking on a partner?
Well, we've never had
to consider it before.
We value our independence
very much.
Independence in publishing
is dependent on advertisers.
However much you have, you retain.
We don't care about content.
Excuse me? Did I miss something?
Talking about investing
in the magazine.
- I gathered that. But why?
- Not out of greed, that's for sure.
I feel badly that I've taken Mikael away
from you at the worst possible time.
But now I am convinced that this is
the right thing to do. The moral thing.
That's one reason. And...
And...?
The enemies of my friends
are my enemies.
How long have you been
discussing this with them?
I haven't. They called yesterday
and asked me to come up.
- Why didn't you tell me?
- You live in the woods.
- I deserve to be treated like an idiot?
- I wanted to hear what they had to say.
You would've said no
before they could.
Well, I'm saying it now.
It's a bad idea.
You heard me tell them
we had six months. I lied.
We will be out of business in three.
But you don't know this family
like I do. They're crazy.
We're not marrying into it.
If we do this,
that's exactly what we're doing.
So you wanna say no, let's say no.
Instead of 50 percent of something,
let's own 100 percent of nothing.
- Mikael?
- What?
I'm leaving this godforsaken island
in the morning.
- So?
- So are you coming to bed or not?
How much do one of those cost?
Around 3000.
This is really gonna hurt.
Your call.
Vanger Industries took a controlling
interest in Millennium magazine...
...which, according to analysts,
has been in financial trouble...
Millennium is an excellent magazine
We think it's undervalued right now.
Which is good business for us.
Well, there's another reason.
I don't like bullies.
Are you referring
to Mr. Wennerström?
I'm referring to anyone who tries
to sue his enemies into submission.
If Herr Wennerström
would like to try it again...
...he will find himself fighting a
company that can afford to fight back.
I've always admired Henrik Vanger.
He's a titan and a gentleman.
But he's also quite old now...
...which may explain how he could be
taken in by a convicted liar.
Three-twenty.
Shit.
The current archive is on CDs.
The older stuff, still negatives.
What general period
are you interested in?
September, 1966.
Thank you.
Is this about Harriet Vanger?
You're too young
to know about that.
Everyone here grows up
knowing about her.
It's how we're taught
about strangers.
- Lisbeth.
- I need to pay my rent.
I need some money.
Oh, come on in.
I feel a bit badly
how we left it last time.
Me too.
Good. You're alive.
You recognize this? I had it with me
last time. I set it here, remember?
And this snap, you see it?
It's not a snap.
It's a wide-angle fiber-optics lens.
I thought it was going to be
another blow job...
...which is disgusting enough.
But I misjudged
just how sick you are.
Okay. Here's what's going to happen.
Pay attention.
Look at me.
Once you can sit again...
...which could be a while, I admit,
we're going to go to my bank...
...and tell them that I alone
have access to my money.
Nod. After that
you will never contact me again.
Each month you will prepare a report
of a meeting we will never have.
In it, you'll describe
how well I'm doing.
How "sociable" I'm becoming.
Then you will negotiate with the court...
...to have my declaration
of incompetence lifted.
If you fail, this video will spread
across the internet like a virus.
Nod.
And if anything should happen to me,
if I get run over by a car...
...if you run me over with a car,
this will upload automatically.
Nod that you understand.
Gabardine.
I'm taking the keys to this apartment
because I'll be checking on you.
If I find a girl in here with you, whether
she came of her own free will or not...
No, not the video.
I'll kill you.
Do you doubt anything I've said?
Do you doubt what's in the reports that
have followed me around all my life?
What do they say?
If you had to sum it up.
They say I'm insane.
No, it's okay,
you can nod because it's true.
I am insane.
Nod!
I know it's going to be hard for you
to abide by my rules.
The abstinence part most of all.
So I'm going to make it
easier for you.
Lie still.
I've never done this before.
And there will be blood.
- Hi.
What are you doing here?
On my way to Skelleftea.
I can only stay a couple of hours.
What's in Skelleftea?
Bible camp.
Oh, yeah.
I'm not dangerous.
It's fine, Nilla.
Whatever you want to do is fine.
Everybody needs something.
Just as long as it's not God.
I didn't say that.
I haven't been around enough to
really know what's going on with you.
And I apologize for that. But I'd never
want you not to tell me something...
...because you think
I might not want to hear it.
That's what I'm doing.
It should've been me visiting you.
- I'm sorry.
- It's okay.
It was nice seeing you.
Bye-bye
- I'll see you.
- Yeah.
Thanks.
Oh, don't go too hard
on the Catholics.
- The what?
- The article you're writing.
Oh, I'm not writing
an article about Catholics.
The Bible quotes by your desk.
I love you.
A woman who is a medium
or a sorcerer...
...shall be put to death by stoning.
If a dove is the sinner's offering...
...the priest shall wring off its head,
cleave its wings...
...and burn it upon the altar.
- Hello?
- Detective Morell, it's Mikael Blomkvist.
Yes, hello. How are you?
Not still freezing in Hedestad,
I hope, for your sake.
You know that Rebecka case
you mentioned.
Would you recall her last name?
Of course I do.
But what has that to do with anything?
- Nothing, probably.
- Jacobsson. Rebecka Jacobsson.
And how was she killed?
She was decapitated.
Her arms were cutoff
and she was burned.
But all that happened in the 1940s.
- What have you found?
- I have to call you back.
Why--?
- Is it Henrik?
- We were talking.
He rubbed his arm,
then he collapsed.
- Think he's gonna be okay?
- I honestly don't know.
- You go. Talk to you later.
- I'm sorry.
Evening.
So how is he?
Well, the good news is he survived.
How he does now, we'll have to see.
- He's in intensive care.
- Right.
- May I have one of those?
- You want a sandwich?
- Small Scotch.
- Sure.
Thank you.
I hate to be indelicate,
but Henrik promised me something...
...when I agreed to do this.
- Wennerström.
I need to know what he has on him.
Now. In case...
In case he dies?
- Well, that is indelicate.
- And I apologize.
I don't know what he has on him,
if you're asking me.
And he can't tell you
in the condition he's in, so...
We also didn't discuss who I'd report
to if something should happen to him.
Oh, well, you'd report to me,
of course.
But we both know that nothing's
going to come of this, don't we?
- No. No, we don't know that.
- What do you mean?
- I may have found something.
- You're joking.
What have you found?
The last time I reported on something
without being absolutely sure...
...I lost my life savings.
I need a research assistant.
Can you authorize that?
Yes. Do you have one in mind?
- I can find someone.
- I know an excellent one.
She did the background check
on you.
The what?
Well, you don't think we can
hire just anyone...
...without doing
a background check.
I want to read that.
Herr Frode was kind enough
to share your report with me.
The investigator's name.
That is her name, yes?
See, I can't find any record of her,
and I'm pretty good at that.
- Would it matter what her name is?
- If I wanted to speak to her, yes.
- It's against policy.
- You sure?
Just like your sources.
You understand.
Okay.
Here's a name for you.
My sister.
She's also my lawyer.
She'll be contacting you.
There are things in here that can
only have come from one place.
The reason you can find no record of
her is because her records are sealed.
- She's a ward of the state.
- What's that gotta do with anything?
She's had a rough life.
Can we please
not make it any rougher?
Who is it?
It's Mikael Blomkvist.
- Actually, I'm not really up yet.
- May I come in?
Please?
Hi. You and I need to talk.
I've got us some breakf--
I'm sorry, I didn't realize
you had some company.
Who do you think you are?
I'm the guy you know better
than my closest friends do.
Why don't you put some clothes on,
get rid of your girlfriend.
We need to talk.
I'm sorry, you have to go.
Okay.
Do you need me to stay?
No.
- Bye.
Bye.
- Sorry.
- It's okay.
I guess I must have alarmed you,
turning up like that.
If you touch me,
I'll more than alarm you.
That won't be necessary.
Your report, very detailed.
- But for me, it wasn't very entertaining.
- It wasn't meant to be.
When I write about people,
I try to entertain the reader.
Wennerström wasn't
entertained much.
Your boss, Armansky...
...yeah, he tells me you only do jobs
that interest you...
...so I suppose I should be flattered.
You gonna sit down?
He also says that you're the one
he goes to when the job is sensitive.
That's the word he used, "sensitive."
I'm gonna use "illegal"...
...because that's what it was
when you hacked into my computer.
No, I'm not gonna do anything
about that. I could, but I won't.
What I'm gonna do
is I'm gonna tell you a story...
...and if it entertains you, maybe you'll
decide to help me research further.
And if not, I'll do the washing up
and you'll never see me again.
Here, you should eat that.
What kind of research?
Lisbeth-- Oh, can I call you Lisbeth?
I want you to help me catch
a killer of women.
I've got R.J.
Rebecka Jacobsson.
I've got absolutely no idea...
...who the rest of these are
or how they're connected...
...to the death of a 16-year-old girl,
but they must be somehow.
What we've gotta do is find out who
they are, what happened to them...
...and what these Leviticus verses
have to do with anything.
- What are you doing?
- Getting started.
- You can keep talking if you want.
- Don't you need to look over these?
I got it.
Cat!
How'd you get in?
No one has asked me about
Magda in over 40 years.
Why would a lady like you want
to know about an awful murder?
- It interests me.
- Does it?
Her husband was the first suspect.
The husband is always
the first suspect and usually the last.
But not this time.
We moved on to a neighbor.
Then a vagrant.
Once you get to strangers,
it's only a matter of time...
...before you get to gypsies and you
know you're never going to solve it.
How exactly was she killed?
- Miss...?
- Salander.
Miss Salander. I hope you don't mind
me asking, but when did you last eat?
I have a high metabolism.
I can't put on weight.
I'm asking because it is better to look
at what I am about to show you...
...on an empty stomach.
If a man's offering is a lamb,
it shall be a female without blemish.
He should lay his hand
upon its head...
...slaughter it, empty its blood
on the base of the altar...
...and he shall be forgiven.
- How is he?
- He needs surgery...
...but there's no DNR in place.
So it's up to the family to decide...
...should the occasion arise,
whether to resuscitate or not.
And they're not good at decisions.
So how was it with Miss Salander?
She said yes. Do you think
I might be able to see him?
He was asleep the last time I looked,
but let me check.
- Thank you.
- Don't check.
Tell him to pack his things
and leave.
- Mother, please.
- Don't use that tone with me.
Isabella, Mr. Blomkvist
works for Henrik.
- We should put this to a vote.
- Don't be an idiot, Birger.
We all know what Henrik wants.
Can we just do that?
Henrik is fighting for his life in there.
This is the last thing he needs.
Excuse me, Mrs. Vanger,
there is no smoking in here.
Go back to Stockholm.
When we need a family chronicle
written by a libelist...
...we know who to call.
All right. Thanks.
This way, miss.
If a woman approaches any beast...
...and lies with it, you shall kill
the woman and the beast.
Their blood shall be upon them.
My family's impossible.
That's why the company's
such a mess.
I apologize for my
mother's behavior.
I'm used to it.
It has nothing to do with you.
It's between her and Henrik.
She lost it when my father died,
and her drinking and her...
Got so bad Henrik took me
and my sister away from her...
...and left her excommunicated
in the old house...
...on the other side of the island.
She hasn't forgiven him.
You must stay.
You're the last chance Henrik has
at some kind of resolution.
Put this to rest one way or another.
I'll keep my mother away.
But please, hurry.
Of course.
Lisbeth.
- I'll get that.
- It's okay.
- Martin Vanger.
- How do you do?
Fine.
- It's a girlfriend, or...?
- Assistant.
Thank you so much.
- Good night.
Problems finding the place?
Everyone in town knows
who and where you are.
That's comforting. Are you hungry?
I can make you a sandwich.
No.
I used to have a motorbike,
a Triumph.
I know.
The five cases from Harriet's list.
And five more she missed.
Three I'm sure of.
Rebecka was the first,
just as you thought.
The second, M.H., is Mari Holmberg,
a prostitute in Kalmar...
...murdered in 1954,
matching Leviticus 20:18.
Right. "if a man lies with a woman
having her sickness...
...he has made naked her fountain
and she has uncovered...
...the fountain of her blood."
Raped and stabbed, but cause of death
was suffocation by sanitary napkin.
- Okay.
- R.L. Rakel Lunde, 1957.
A cleaning woman
and part-time palm reader.
Tied with a clothesline, gagged, raped.
Head crushed with a rock.
Leviticus 20:27.
"A woman who is a medium
or sorceress...
...shall be put to death by stoning."
- I usually like to smoke outside.
- Sara Witt, 1964.
Daughter of a pastor.
Tied to her bed.
Raped. Charred in the fire
that burned down her house.
Leviticus 21:9.
"The daughter of a priest who profanes
herself by playing the harlot...
...profanes her father
and shall be burned with fire."
Magda Lovisa Sjöberg, 1960.
Found in a barn.
Stabbed and raped with farm tools.
The cow in the next stall
had its throat slit.
Its blood was splashed on her
and hers on it.
Leviticus 20:16.
"If a woman lies with any beast...
...you shall kill the woman and the
beast. Their blood is upon them."
Lea Persson, 1962.
Found by her sister in their pet shop.
Raped, beaten.
The killer uncaged the animals,
smashed the aquariums.
There was a parakeet inside her.
Next, Eva Gustavsson, 1960.
A runaway. Raped, strangled.
A burnt pigeon tied around her neck.
Lena Andersson, 1967. A student.
Raped, stabbed, decapitated--
- Okay.
- I'm not finished.
We're looking for
a serial murderer...
...but what could that have to do
with a teenager living on an island?
She was looking for him too.
Rape. Torture. Fire.
Animals. Religion.
- Am I missing anything?
- The names.
They're all Biblical.
The first woman, the whore,
the Virgin Mary.
Rebecka, Sara,
all from the Old Testament.
Which means they're all Jewish.
One thing the Vangers have more than
their fair share of, it's anti-Semites.
There's one right there.
I can sleep on a couch.
Okay.
Right.
Oh, yeah, there might be
a cat somewhere.
- Good night.
- Night.
Harriet's name isn't.
Isn't what?
- Jewish.
- No.
- What are you doing?
- Reading your notes.
They're encrypted.
Please. Have some coffee.
Okay.
Then we're gonna have
a very serious conversation...
...about what's yours
and what's mine.
It's amazing what you figured out
with the parade photos.
Thank you.
- It's too bad you don't have hers.
- Whose?
Her.
Can I--? Sorry.
Yeah, all right.
Close that.
No. Not that.
That's the one. Yep.
Where the fuck's that? That's down
there, isn't it? Okay. Oh, yeah, yeah.
And...
What does that say there?
- "N" something "R-S-J."
- That's "Norsjö," yeah.
Then something
Something "R-I-F."
"Carpentry."
Well, we need to find a carpenter.
Fuck!
The carpentry shop is gone. I don't
even know if he worked there or not...
...but if he did, maybe he used
to come in here for hardware.
I don't recognize him. Sorry.
Well, I had to start somewhere.
I'm no detective, but 1966, I would
have started at a retirement home.
This is Brannlund's kid.
Do you know where I might find him?
The son?
Next to his father at the cemetery.
He was killed in an accident
on a construction site, years ago.
But...
...she might still be alive.
His widow.
Do you know where
I might find her?
Please drive to highlighted route.
In 1966, you were in Hedestad
with your husband.
Who took these?
A local photographer.
You were taking pictures
too that day...
...and I'd love to look at them
if by some miracle you have them.
It wouldn't be a miracle.
We were on our honeymoon.
But Why?
This girl here. Here, you can see
her better in the enlargement.
See, that's you there.
Just after this was taken...
...after she'd seen something
across the street, she was murdered.
How awful.
- There you are.
- Thank you.
Would you mind if I made
a copy of this?
No.
I can't give you any of this stuff without
authorization from Mr. Armansky.
So call him.
Next time,
fill out the proper paperwork.
Which one are you?
Going down.
How's your sex life?
I didn't care much
for your last report.
It felt perfunctory,
like your heart wasn't in it.
Let's see a little more enthusiasm
for my recovery in next month's.
Don't speak. I don't want to hear
your voice, just nod.
Start looking for a shrink
you can bribe...
...to swear under oath he can find
absolutely nothing wrong with me.
And stop visiting
tattoo-removal websites.
Or I'll do it again...
...right here.
- Is that dental floss?
- Yes.
You're gonna sterilize that, right?
Couldn't we just use tape
or something?
No.
What?
Thank you. Jesus!
- Drink.
- Okay.
Just be careful. It's my eye.
- Don't move.
- You're not a doctor.
- Take off your wet clothes.
- What?
Yeah. Thank you.
Yeah, I think it's stopped bleeding.
It still fucking hurts, though.
Madness.
I mean, madness.
This is fucking madness.
You're okay, you're okay,
you're okay.
Jesus, that hurts. Fuck.
This is insane.
I mean, these people--
Somebody was shooting at me.
I mean, it wasn't an accident.
No one's shooting at you now.
You know, I'm pretty sure
this is a bad idea.
Why?
I'm old and we work together--
You work with what's-her-name
and that's worked out for you.
Yeah, well, I do have some standards,
believe it or not.
You need to stop talking.
Oh, shit.
Do you want me to open a window?
- I like working with you.
- I like working with you too.
- It could have been a stray shot.
- Not by Gunnar.
If he wanted to shoot him,
he wouldn't be here.
And then we have poachers.
They shoot at anything that moves.
Or he's right, Dirch. What if he is?
This has to stop.
Do you want to stop, Mikael?
Look, I have police reports, photos...
...Henrik's notes, my notes,
Lisbeth's research.
What I don't have is Vanger Industries'
records. That's what I want.
- Why?
- Will you authorize it?
What, the private corporate records?
Well, how far back?
Henrik said I could have access
to everything. This is what I need.
- That's not what he meant.
- I'll sign a nondisclosure statement.
Just a minute.
I think Henrik would say yes.
That's why he has me. To protect
him from himself. It's insane.
What have we got to hide?
After 120 years of business,
probably a lot.
If this is what he needs to finish,
he should have permission.
What am I looking for?
Any connections between
Vanger Industries...
...and the towns
where the women were killed.
And everything about Frode.
Your father was taking pictures
that day that no one has seen.
- I'd like to take a look at them.
- So ask him.
- I was wondering if you could do that.
- I don't speak to him.
Could you make an exception
in my case?
Are you afraid to be
in the same room with him?
I'm not saying you shouldn't be.
So you won't help me?
Sorry.
Please?
- Are you finished?
- I need to know where all factories...
...offices and projects
were from 1949 to 1966.
- You already have everything.
- No, I don't.
Nothing on subsidiary corporations,
partnerships or suppliers.
- You'll have to do without.
- Mr. Frode said I have access...
...to whatever I need. I need this
- You have access to this floor.
Call him.
Thank you for seeing me.
Come in.
- Tea?
- Please.
Sven Olov Lindholm.
Me.
Handsome.
Birger Furugard.
Me.
Per Engdahl.
But your interest is in my more
candid photographic work.
Friends, relations, that kind of thing.
Please.
"Blom" or "Bloom"?
Blomkvist.
I'm not a recluse.
I don't close my door to anybody.
Thank you.
They just don't visit.
Well...
...perhaps if you redecorated.
Hide the past like they do?
Under a thin, shiny veneer?
Like an IKEA table?
I am the most honest of all of them.
- The family?
- Sweden.
Landscape?
Some nice landscapes there?
Who is this?
The blurry one.
I can't tell.
Oh, that's Gottfried's boy.
- That's Martin.
- Yeah.
Handsome but useless young man.
Like his father.
- We're closing.
- Nowhere near finished.
- I'm not authorized to stay late.
- I am.
And I need access to everything,
including anything that's locked.
Call Frode.
Leave the keys with the guard.
Come on.
Shit!
Martin?
Mikael.
Hi there.
Your evening stroll?
Yes, that's right, I...
- How are you?
- Good.
I stopped by the hospital
on my way home.
Henrik asked me
to ask you something.
What was that?
Come on in. I'll make you a drink.
Hello, Martin.
Shut the door. It's quite windy.
- What happened to you?
- When?
Just now.
I fell in the dark.
You don't have a flashlight?
I'll get you one.
I just wasn't being careful, that's all.
How's the investigation going?
- Nothing new to report.
- No?
Dirch says the girl is really clever.
Maybe she'll turn something up.
Maybe.
Thank you for that.
- So, what did he say?
- What?
You said Henrik asked you
to ask me something.
- Well, I just did.
- What?
- How's the investigation?
- Oh, yeah.
That was his question.
Do you hunt?
We should go hunting
together sometime.
Sure.
Nothing at all new to report?
No. Nothing.
- I can see you're anxious.
- No.
No, I mean to get home
after the walk.
Yeah, well, I suppose I am.
To have dinner with your girlfriend.
Assistant.
We'll have better luck with a gun.
- I'm sorry?
- When we go hunting.
A gun. Rather than a knife.
I want to show you something.
Bring your drink.
Leave my knife.
To the right.
Hi, leave a message. I'll call--
You know what's harder
than shooting someone?
Just missing him.
That was a very good shot
up at the cabin.
It didn't work. I'm here.
Mikael, it did work. You're here.
Inside.
You spilled your drink.
Why didn't you just go home?
May I?
How did you do it?
What did you find?
We can talk
or we can just get on with it.
I found a photograph...
...no one has seen.
- Of?
- You.
In an Uppsala prep school blazer.
What does that prove?
You lied about
where you were that day.
- Did I?
- Or rather, when.
So what? People lie all the time.
It also says that you and Lena
Andersson were schoolmates.
Lena
That was a long time ago.
Where's this photo now? Is it with
all the other crap on your desk?
There's a copy on my laptop.
There's another copy...
...on a secure website.
- Secure website.
That's a lie.
How much does the girl know?
I hope it's as much as you do.
That'll make it fun.
Where is she?
Stockholm. She went this morning.
That's a lie.
She's at our offices
looking at more old crap.
I got a call
from our archives manager.
She was very perturbed
with this girl Lisbeth.
I like that name.
Lisbeth.
So when Lisbeth leaves,
I will get a call from security...
...so I can be at your cottage
to greet her.
I can't thank you enough
for bringing her to me.
Hey, he)'-
So, what do you wanna know?
You're a journalist,
ask me questions.
What do I do with the girls?
That's a good question.
Well, before, I do what we're doing:
Sit down, relax, have a drink.
I like that part a lot.
Having a chat when both of you know
that one of you is going to die.
And afterwards, I just get rid of them,
far out at sea.
Unlike my father,
who left them scattered...
...all over the place, like trophies.
That's not very smart, if you ask me.
Well, he was a loud
and garish man.
Frankly, he got what he deserved.
You can't be a sloppy technician
like that.
You can't drink to excess
like he did.
This takes discipline.
It's a science of a thousand details.
The planning, the execution.
It's the cleanup.
I guess I don't have to tell you...
...but you're going to create
quite a mess here.
Let me ask you something.
Why don't people
trust their instincts?
They sense something is wrong...
...someone is walking too close
behind them.
You knew something was wrong.
But you came back into the house.
Did I force you?
Did I drag you in? No.
All I had to do was offer you a drink.
It's hard to believe that
the fear of offending...
...can be stronger than the fear
of pain, but you know what? It is.
And they always come willingly.
And then they sit there.
They know it's all over,
just like you do.
But somehow,
they still think they have a chance.
"Maybe if I say the right thing.
Maybe if I'm polite.
If I cry, if I beg."
And when I see the hope
draining from their face...
...like it is from yours right now...
...I can feel myself...
...getting hard.
But, you know, we're not that different,
you and I. We both have urges.
Satisfying mine...
...requires more towels.
It might amuse you to know...
...that while you were upstairs
having moose with me and Liv...
...who, by the way,
finds me very conventional...
...I had Irina down here in that cage.
Who is Irina, you might ask?
Just another girl.
Just another immigrant whore.
- Who misses them?
- Your sister wasn't.
What?
Your sister Harriet
wasn't just another girl.
You found her?
What happened to her?
You killed her.
You useless fucking detective.
This too tight to talk?
Good. I'm tired of talking to you.
I've never had a man in here before.
In fact, I've never touched a man...
...except my father.
That was our duty.
Harriet's and mine.
Hey.
There's a gun.
There's a gun on the television.
- May I kill him?
- Yeah.
How come a 23-year-old...
...is a ward of the state?
I'm mentally incompetent
and can't manage daily life.
Since when have they said that?
Since I was 12.
What happened when you were 12?
I'm sorry,
that's none of my business.
I tried to kill my father.
Burned him alive.
Got about 80 percent of him.
I made some coffee.
- Who's that?
- It's Harriet.
I found it in Martin's basement
among his souvenirs.
No, Martin didn't deny
killing anyone.
But when I mentioned Harriet,
he was confused.
He got angry at me because I couldn't
tell him what had happened to her.
He didn't kill her.
His father didn't do it.
He was dead the year before.
What if she did somehow manage
to get away?
I mean, if...
...she is still alive...
...then there's only one person in this
family who'd know where she is.
Fuck me. Fuck me. Fuck me.
Your turn.
Right.
Here.
Hi. Look, I'm sorry to bother you.
What do you want?
- Has no one called you?
- About?
Your cousin Martin.
- What about him?
- He died in a car accident...
...last Thursday. There's going
to be a memorial in Hedestad.
I'm not interested in any memorial.
- Well, I understand.
- What do you understand?
Well, that you don't care
very much for your family.
- Look, I just thought you should know.
- Now I know.
How'd it go?
Okay, I think.
She's on.
And she's shopping.
She's still playing solitaire?
- And she hasn't called anyone?
- No.
We have her cell phone too?
I was so sure
she was gonna lead us to her.
Put your hand back in my shirt.
There's only one reason
she hasn't called Harriet.
She can't. Because Harriet is dead.
I was just thinking that--
- Just one second.
- Okay.
What were you going to say?
I was just thinking,
there could be one other possibility.
Well, we could, absolutely.
What is it now?
Before he died,
your brother hung me from a hook...
...Harriet.
So you sent the flowers.
Yes, I did.
We found in the Swedish Family
Registry that Anita was married.
- But the family never knew, did they?
- No.
So I'm guessing she then came here
on her married-name passport...
...and you followed
on her maiden-name passport.
No, actually,
it was the other way around.
She thought that it was safer
if I traveled with Spencer myself.
Well, what did he think about that?
Nothing. Only that he loved her.
She said, "if you love me,
you'll do this and not ask why."
And he never did.
And they both died 20 years ago.
Car accident.
You found that out too.
Is that you?
I was 14 the first time he raped me.
Martin.
No, my father.
Martin only started after he had died.
- Well, why didn't you tell somebody?
- I did. My mother.
- Henrik would've done something.
- I almost told him.
But I was afraid
because of what I'd done.
- I...
- You still don't understand, do you?
A year after the first time...
...and there were many times
during that year...
...my father got drunker
than usual one night...
...and he started bragging
about the women he'd killed.
He quoted from the Bible
as he tore my clothes off.
He tied a belt around my neck.
He wanted to kill me.
I got out of the house.
I went down to the dock.
He came staggering after me.
I could never fight him off
in a small space...
...but out in the open...
...I was strong enough
to deal with an old drunk.
When it was over...
...I looked up and Martin was
standing there, staring at me.
And all I'd accomplished was
substitute one for another.
A couple of months later, Henrik
sent Martin to school in Uppsala.
And I thought that maybe, just maybe,
the nightmare was finally over.
And then I saw him
the day of the parade...
...across the street.
And I knew
that it would never be over.
So how did you escape?
Anita. She...
She insisted
that I leave everything behind.
If I took anything the police might have
suspected that I was still alive.
As everyone ate dinner, I was no more
than 20 meters away from them.
I spent the night there.
That's when the search started.
In the morning, she came to get me.
I'd grown up with that bridge
as my link to home...
...but all I could think is...
...if I could just
get away from them...
...just get past the police...
...then I might be safe.
And I was.
Until you showed up.
You're safe now.
How did you get away?
Someone saved me too
- How are you feeling?
- I'm fine.
Thank you, Anna.
I made you a promise...
...whether you found anything or not.
So, what do you have to tell me?
What's this?
Hello, Henrik.
I barely remember Wennerström
working here, much less being fired
How could you?
It was such a long time ago...
...which is kind of more to the point than
the money he embezzled from you.
You're referring
to the statute of limitations...
...but I had no idea this is what
Henrik was holding out.
If I had, I never would've let him
bring you up here.
He wasn't trying to deceive you.
He knows you can't try somebody
35 years after the event.
- I like Henrik, but he knows that.
- A man's reputation means something.
He believes that. He thought
you could destroy Wennerström...
...in the court of public opinion.
- The court of public opinion...
...celebrates people's bad behavior.
- He's an elderly man.
He promised me
Wennerström's carcass on a plate.
This isn't even the plate.
- I can't do anything with this.
- Yes, of course.
What happened with Wennerström?
How did he get you?
I was stupid. I heard something.
I got it from an anonymous source...
...who I'm now sure
was one of Wennerström's lackeys.
It was fake.
Which he easily proved in court.
You were emphatic
that the way I looked into your life...
...was illegal and immoral. Would you
feel the same about Wennerström?
- Go on.
- I did some work on my own on him...
...before you hired me.
I haven't looked at it all...
...because you
and Harriet-fucking-Vanger...
...have kept me busy.
But I may have something.
You may have something?
Maybe.
They launder money
from arms and drug sales...
...and crime syndicates in Russia.
And that money accounts for all
but 5 percent of his holdings.
The rest ends up in accounts
in the Cayman Islands.
- And how do you know this?
- This time you don't want to know.
This time I do want to know.
I have access to his computer.
- And his accountant's and lawyer's.
- And how do you have that?
I could've gotten it from a source
inside the company.
- You didn't.
- But that's what you'll say.
And what will you say to me?
Well, that depends
if you really want to know.
I do.
Mikael, how did you get access?
Financial journalist
Mikael Blomkvist...
...who, this time last year
was convicted of libel...
...in a Stockholm courtroom...
...doesn't seem to have learned
from his mistakes.
Or maybe he has.
In the current issue of Millennium
magazine, he now charges...
...the company that sued him,
the Wennerström Group...
The shit hits the fan.
...Of criminal activities
on a global scale.
What happens now?
Well, he'll say it's a personal vendetta,
which won't wash.
The police will investigate,
Fl will investigate.
It'll go to court.
Maybe he'll go to prison.
You think?
Probably not.
These guys never do.
What's wrong with you?
- It's embarrassing.
- Tell me.
I need to borrow some money.
Fifty thousand.
I have a chance to make an investment.
It's a smart, safe investment.
- I really don't think I've got 50,000.
- Yes, you do.
You have 65,000
in your two accounts.
I'm sorry that I know that.
You'll get the money back,
I promise.
Okay.
You want a coffee?
These allegations, like the last one
from this so-called journalist...
...are as ridiculous
as they are untrue.
I'll be seeing Mr. Blomkvist in court
again, and I'm looking forward to it.
What about his documentation?
Fabricated. All of it.
The Securities Fraud Office isn't quite
as certain as Mr. Wennerström of that.
If a fraction of what Mr. Blomkvist
alleges proves to be true...
...not only will there be
a securities investigation...
...but an organized-crime inquiry
as well.
Mr. Blomkvist names no sources.
And we can't force him to.
But we can look for them.
- Beginning where?
- Those closest to Mr. Wennerström.
Only someone in the inner circle
of a corporation like this...
...has access to this kind
of information.
Mr. Wennerström isn't available
for comment...
...but I'm happy
to answer questions.
- Where is he?
- At home, I imagine
No, he's not.
Has he left the country?
I don't think so.
- Okay. Thank you.
- Thank you.
Welcome to the Dolder Grand, miss.
May I have your passport, please?
With his failure to appear...
...before a Security Exchange
Commission panel...
...a warrant has been issued
for the Wennerström Group CEO.
I can confirm that he left Sweden...
...on a private jet
that landed in Paris last week.
Whether he's still there,
we don't know.
He can be anywhere by now.
Thank you.
I have accounts at Bank
of Kroenenfeld, Cayman Islands.
I'd like to transfer them
and convert to bonds.
- Naturally, you have the clearing codes.
- Naturally.
How many accounts
will you transfer?
Thirty.
- This will take some time.
- You will receive 4 percent commission.
- I will.
- Then it won't be a waste of it.
A Swedish tourist vacationing
here in Barbados...
...says he knows where fugitive
financier Hans-Erik Wennerström is:
Here, in this Caribbean island's
capital, Bridgetown.
Police released this photo and
believe it is the disgraced billionaire.
How many of these would you like
to convert for deposit?
All 50, into five accounts.
Yes. That looks correct.
The man who is now being called
Sweden's Charles Ponzi...
...may no longer have a country
to call home...
...but does have enough money
to buy one.
According to the International
Banking Commission...
Wennerström, a week after
the Millennium article appeared
...on newsstands,
began emptying accounts...
...at Bank of Kroenenfeld
in the Cayman Islands.
That money,
approximately 2 billion euros...
...was then spread over
a number of accounts...
...with the help of this confederate,
seen here in Zurich.
- Hey.
- The money I borrowed.
- Already?
Thank you.
No, I quit.
It was a good investment?
It was okay.
What are you doing later?
I'm seeing my daughter.
Okay.
You look nice.
It's Christmas again.
I'll see you soon.
Mr. Wennerström
won the libel case..
You got that call in the office.
I miss our meetings.
I'm sure you don't. Why would you?
I was always such
a headache for you.
Never showing up with good news,
only problems.
I have good news now.
I made a friend.
I mean, one that you'd approve of.
I'm happy.
A man who authorities here
in Marbella have confirmed...
...is fugitive Hans-Erik Wennerström,
shot three times in the head...
...in what police are calling
a classic gangland execution.
The investigation
into Wennerström's ties...
...to crime organizations worldwide
will now turn into speculation.
Which of them caught up with him
before Swedish authorities could?
Wennerström spent the last days
of his flamboyant life...
- It's nice.
- Your father?
- A friend.
- Must be a very good friend.
- We're late.
- Fashionably late.