Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org
NARRATOR: In Ancient Egypt,
before the time of the pharaohs,
legend tells of King Memtep,
who made a covenant with Anubis,
Lord of the Underworld,
to create a cursed sword so powerful
that whoever possessed it
could rule the world.
Fueled by taking the souls of its enemies,
the sword was forged in the fires of hell
by the Lord of the Underworld,
who gave this sword his very name,
The Fang of Anubis.
The names of those slain by the sword
were forever etched in the Book of Souls,
where they remained imprisoned
for all eternity,
condemned to never-ending darkness.
But if evil can be so easily
created in a fiery forge,
then surely, there must be
a way to destroy the sword
and release the souls.
(ROARING)
(ROCKS CRUMBLING)
(BIRD SQUAWKING)
These hieroglyphs are ancient.
- It looks like they are from...
- Mesopotamia.
Sumerian.
What do they say, priestess?
(GASPS)
Here lies the treasure you seek.
King Memtep?
Before you plunder the antiquities
of this tomb, you must know,
unleashing this evil that once was,
will come with a great price.
Power is not given, priestess.
It must be taken.
(STONE SLAB SLIDING)
(GRUNTING)
The Fang of Anubis, forgotten to time.
But the ages have not dulled
your cutting edge, have they?
(GRUNTING)
NARRATOR: Nebserek went forth,
sweeping across the barren lands
with the Fang of Anubis at his command.
Driven by its dark magic,
he conquered his enemies
and raised a powerful, jackal army
proclaiming himself their god-king.
We will cleanse this land!
With death and fire!
NARRATOR: But one enemy eluded him,
the last Akkadian, the sole
heir to the great free tribe
who destroyed his people
in a war waged long ago.
Branded by vengeance, Nebserek became
obsessed with finding his enemy.
Have your bird find
the Scorpion King, priestess.
The gods will grant you
your vengeance in time.
The time for vengeance is now.
Send the bird.
NARRATOR: But some sleeping giants
are better left to their slumber.
It's beautiful.
No, it's strong.
That's what counts.
With this, you can harvest the winter
wheat, reap the summer grain,
feed your family and livestock.
Not much left in this world
you can put your faith in,
but forged metal pounded into shape.
This, you can trust.
ABEL: When will you make a sword?
Done with swords.
I could learn to use one
to become a great warrior.
Abel?
Listen to me, Abel.
Being a warrior is not what you think.
Swinging a sword in war
is a hard burden to bear.
No priests or gods can save you
from the savagery of battle.
You understand?
Abel!
Go to your father.
(HORSES NEIGHING)
(SOLDIERS SHOUTING)
(BIRD SQUAWKING)
(SHOUTING CONTINUES IN DISTANCE)
Come on!
(HORSES NEIGHING)
I seek the Scorpion King.
We have no king here.
He calls himself Mathayus.
We know of no such man.
Burn it to the ground and find him.
Please! We're just farm...
Kill him first.
(MAN LAUGHING)
No!
Please!
On your knees, insect!
Where is Mathayus?
Here I am.
(LAUGHS)
Go!
(BLADES SWISHING)
Draw!
(GRUNTS)
- No! Come back!
- Mathayus!
- No! Mathayus!
- Got you!
MOTHER: (SOBBING) No! No!
Please.
Let the boy go.
Not one more step.
All right.
Spare the boy, take me.
I'll take both.
No! No! No!
No.
Abel.
(HORSES NEIGHING)
(INCANTING IN NATIVE LANGUAGE)
Here. Drink this.
(GROANS)
What is it?
A medicinal tonic
mixed with lithops for pain.
You're welcome.
You need food.
(GRUNTS)
The Scorpion King escaped.
Bend your knee when you speak to me.
- Escaped?
- Yes.
He had help, my god-king.
I need his soul.
You have the...
No.
Only when I plunge this blade
into his heart will I have my vengeance.
Find me this Akkadian!
Cover yourself.
Where'd you dig that up?
Burial mound. The man who wore
it did not need it anymore.
I am Tala, warrior of Nubia.
What do you want from me?
A legendary king to come back to life.
I'm just a blacksmith.
Blacksmith?
That is your story?
How did a legendary Scorpion King,
last of the Akkadians, demigod,
become a blacksmith?
Civilization became too uncivilized for me.
I have searched for you for a long time.
Your name inspires.
It is a rallying cry.
My people need a hero
to bring peace, a warrior hero.
Like I said, you got the wrong guy.
My father was Balthazar, King of Nubia.
Balthazar?
He lived well,
but not long enough.
Sorry he's gone.
My father told me that
you two had a great bond,
that if Nubia ever needed an ally,
the Scorpion King would ride from
the east with his armies and fight with us.
I have no army.
You have your strength, and you have me.
A princess?
A warrior.
Do you know Nebserek
the warlord sweeps across Egypt,
with his hordes, enslaving, burning?
He wields a cursed sword, the Fang of Anubis.
No one can stand against him
while he possesses it.
But legend tells of a way
to defeat the sword.
The secret is contained in the Book of Souls.
It is a hidden text,
and I know where to find it.
Sounds like a bedtime story.
Nebserek marches on Nubia, on my people.
With the Book of Souls, we can stop him.
You're on a quest?
Yes.
Good luck.
You are coming with me!
I don't quest.
Why?
They're always 1,000 times
more difficult than you think,
and someone won't make it back alive.
The jackal is Nebserek's symbol.
We share the same enemy.
Help me find the Book of Souls,
and I will help you kill
the owner of the dagger.
I'll take both.
No!
You were born a warrior.
It is your fate to fight for
those less fortunate souls.
Stand or fall, I will fight by your side.
I implore you, remember who you are.
(FALCON CRIES)
MENNOFER:
This man you seek, the Scorpion King,
travels with a Nubian.
(FALCON CHIRPING)
And they are close.
Close to what?
Legend tells of a gateway
in the Valley of the 13th Moon,
where it is said the Book of Souls rests,
hidden away from all mankind.
He who possesses the Book of Souls
has the power to destroy the Fang of Anubis.
These sands have been searched
by many hands for many years.
Searched, yes, but not by the Scorpion King.
(SNAKES HISSING)
(VULTURES SQUAWKING)
MATHAYUS: We should go around.
The Valley of the 13th Moon
is a half-day's ride away.
Going around is a day out of our way.
- You don't wanna go in there.
- I must.
- We can't be late.
- Late for what?
The final day of this lunar cycle.
The moon can wait.
I've waited 56 moons for this rising.
Hyah! Hyah!
Why are we stopping here, blacksmith?
(HORSE WHINNIES RESTLESSLY)
- Put your weapons down.
- There's nobody here.
Yes, there is. Drop your weapons, now.
Forgive her. She can't see!
Who are you talking to?
The Black Arrows.
They weren't trying to hit us.
If they were, we'd be dead.
(LAUGHS MENACINGLY)
Told you we should've gone around.
You trespass on our sacred lands,
and for this you must die.
We meant no insult.
The territory is marked.
You chose to ignore the warning.
How did woman, very beautiful woman,
fall in with hard man
like this, huh? Tell me.
He's my father's blacksmith.
A blacksmith and a breeder.
(CROWD LAUGHING)
He likes you.
Can you cook? Cook?
Can you cook, hmm?
I'm a Nubian warrior.
Yes, I can cook.
I will give you two wild pigs,
and five amphoras of
pomegranate wine for her, huh?
Yeah?
Five wild pigs and 10 amphoras.
No, no, no!
I thought you were going to kill him.
I am.
But after I do,
I will take you for my own, huh?
Feed him to the wastelands.
We will drink to his death with my wine.
- No?
- I'm not for sale.
And I'm not a breeder.
Uruk!
(SPEAKING IN NATIVE LANGUAGE)
(WHISPERING IN NATIVE LANGUAGE)
The shaman says you are
from the Land of the East.
The Scorpion King is what you
are called, huh?
- Just a blacksmith.
- This is what I said.
You are very small
to be such legendary warrior.
So how do you want it? I can
split your skulls with an axe
and stick them on a spike.
You can burn on a pyre.
Or I can lash you to a stump
and let the vultures and insects have you.
What is your name, warrior?
I am Uruk, son of Kali,
leader of the Black Arrows,
and People of the Sand.
Chieftain Uruk,
your people are hunters, are they not?
Mmm.
So, give me the same chance
to live as any beast.
You are not a beast. You are a man.
Yes. I bleed red like you.
And like you, I'd rather die
on my feet than my knees.
I will only send four men to kill you.
Better make it five.
When this hunt is done,
and I'm still alive,
you let me keep the girl, and we ride free.
Agreed.
(HORNS BLOWING)
What did I tell you about quests?
(URUK CHUCKLES)
When you reach that arrow,
we will hunt you.
Run fast, blacksmith,
or your death will be slow.
(LAUGHS)
Run!
(SHOUTING)
(GROANS)
Uruk!
Drop it! Drop it.
You are a worthy adversary, Akkadian.
You could have killed me and my men,
as we would have surely killed you.
But you chose mercy.
There will be no mercy for those
who have not shown mercy.
Five pigs and some wine?
That's all I fetch in your simple mind?
You never tasted pomegranate wine.
(BOTH PROMPTING HORSES)
(SOLDIERS SHOUTING)
There it is, the Valley of the 13th Moon.
Tell me about the Book of Souls.
It is said to be guarded
by the Temple of Scrolls.
It can only be entered
on the eve of the blue moon.
Once every three years on the lunar cycle.
That is tonight.
How do you know all this?
My family has been the guardian
of this book since before the pharaohs,
passing it down
from generation to generation.
No one's been there or seen this book
because they've never needed it until now.
Before he passed, my father
entrusted me with this guardianship.
As fate would have it, he didn't have
time to tell me much about the book.
And you're sure it's down there?
The prophecy says it is.
So, we're just going to ride down there,
walk through the front door,
and they're going to give you this book?
It's not exactly a door.
It's more of a gateway.
MATHAYUS: Doesn't look like
a Temple of Scrolls to me.
TALA: It's in ancient writing.
"The one that repeats its form."
Sumerian.
Not so different than the
language I learned as a boy.
TALA: The moon repeats
its form every 30 days.
The blue moon repeats its form every
three years after the summer solstice.
We've found it.
We found a stone gateway
in the middle of nowhere,
leading to nothing.
We must hurry, it's almost nightfall.
We can't miss the moonrise.
What does your scroll say?
"After you pass the moonstone threshold,
"take 400 paces just east of north."
This way!
What now?
Don't rush me. It's my first time doing this.
Moon's rising.
Let's do this, blacksmith.
The lenses must align with a cipher.
A combination.
What is it?
I'm looking.
"The one that repeats its form."
That's the cipher!
It's what's written on the gateway.
Let's go. It won't stay open for long.
What is that?
Quicksilver. Nature's guard against evil.
I hate quests.
Blacksmith, this way.
Tell me you know what
this magic book looks like.
It could be a scroll on vellum,
written in codex form,
perhaps a tome?
Maybe papyrus book scribbled in burnt bones.
So, you're saying you have no idea, right?
Yes, that is what I'm saying.
(GROWLING)
(GROWLS)
Kill intruder!
Ouch! No fair!
Enkidu! Enough!
These people opened the portal
with a lunar scroll.
They are not our foe.
They are armed!
One of them attacked me unfairly from behind.
I am sure they meant no harm.
(GRUMBLES)
I am Tala, daughter of Balthazar,
warrior of Nubia.
We have come for the Book of Souls.
Have you?
And you've brought a brute?
A barbarian?
You're Akkadian.
What is that thing?
(GRUNTS) I'm not a thing!
A golem.
ENKIDU: Stupid human.
Enkidu is formed from clay,
brought to life by magic.
My father made him to be my protector.
I have the strength of 10 men.
Maybe 20.
(GRUNTS)
I bet you wouldn't sell her for five
pigs and some pomegranate wine.
Barbarian.
(LAUGHING) Pretty human.
So you've come for the Book of Souls?
TALA: Yes.
My people are in peril.
We need it to vanquish a warlord
who leads his army across Egypt.
He carries a cursed sword.
None can stand against it.
I have nothing on how
to defeat a cursed sword.
But the legend says the book is here.
You must help us. We are running out of time.
I'm sorry.
There is nothing here for you.
The book is here?
I have many scrolls, Akkadian.
Some codices, some tomes.
I have read them all,
committed them to memory,
but I have not a single book.
Tala, what does your scroll
say about this Book of Souls?
The scroll says, "The Book of Souls
is written on vellum of alabaster.
"The body of its forbidden text is
uncovered in the blue light of the moon."
"Vellum, of alabaster.
"The body of its forbidden text
"is uncovered only
in the blue light of the moon."
Enkidu!
No!
It's...
You.
You are the Book of Souls.
The moonlight reveals the text?
Yes.
It is revealed on the third moon
in a season of four moons.
Seven times in the 19-year Metonic cycle.
What's written here?
Names of souls taken by a sword
forged in the Underworld by Anubis.
Do you know who they are?
Yes.
With every soul the sword takes,
I can hear their screams,
see their faces.
Some fates are worse than death.
(HORSES GALLOPING)
I have no quarrel with you, Chieftain Uruk.
I seek the Book of Souls
in the Valley of the 13th Moon.
Your jackal bellies are never full, are they?
Whatever the Akkadian paid
for passage, King Nebserek will triple it.
He paid with courage and respect.
Give us passage and you will be spared.
Stand your ground and I will crush you.
We are People of the Sand.
Sand cannot be crushed.
It can only change its form.
(CHEERING)
You're going to pay for that.
That was my favorite table.
(GRUNTS) That was my only table.
You shouldn't have broke it, then.
Puny human.
My father was a great Sumerian mage.
He brought me here before I could even walk.
He told me very little about my curse.
You have no idea how to defeat this curse?
The sword was found in King Memtep's
tomb beneath a city called Amonesh.
Your quest must take you there.
The secret lies within King Memtep's tomb.
All right, then.
We will go to Amonesh, and break this curse.
First command! Keep Amina here, forever.
(GRUNTS)
I hate this puny human.
There's a trade route that leads
to the city of Aqaba.
There is a port here.
You can hire a boat to cross
the sea to Amonesh.
(GRUMBLES) Amina likes him.
- This life...
- ENKIDU: He's ugly.
Must be hard to bear.
I have escaped the pain of the living.
And the joys?
Yes.
It is more a burden than a blessing.
He's got muscles, but I fight muscles...
Come with us into the world.
There is nothing more I would love than
to see your world through my own eyes.
ENKIDU: A man of puny flesh.
But I'm afraid that's not possible.
And if I can make it possible?
ENKIDU:
He's got muscles, but I fight muscles.
I think I found a shorter route...
No fire, no fire!
- Put it out! Put it out!
- ENKIDU: No fire! No fire!
It's gone. Enkidu, don't be afraid.
Don't be afraid.
- Fire's gone?
- Yes.
- I forgot to tell them.
- And I'm still here?
Calm yourself, Enkidu.
I hate fire.
Enkidu cannot abide fire,
- not even the smallest of flames.
- I hate it.
ENKIDU: Fire. I hate it.
It's okay.
ENKIDU: Stupid humans!
They are too far ahead of us.
We need to split up.
There's only two ways out of that valley,
and we'll shut them both off.
Ride the Silk Road to where
the dunes meet the sea.
We have been riding all night.
The men, the horses, they need rest.
You will ride until the horses hearts
stop beating in their chests,
and then you will go on foot,
crawling if you must,
until I get what I came for.
(HORSES NEIGHING)
(MEN SHOUTING)
Enkidu?
What do you want, barbarian?
To show you something.
I've seen this tunnel many times.
I don't like this tunnel.
I've never liked tunnels.
It's dark. I don't like tunnels...
No!
No! No fire!
Amina! Amina!
Amina!
We must go! It won't last long.
Don't leave! Don't go!
Let's ride!
The horses are rested
and we need to keep moving.
One more minute?
The sea is beautiful.
I can hear the voices whispering
from ancient shores.
I can taste the salt.
I hope Enkidu will be all right without me.
We've never been apart.
How does such a creature
have a mortal fear of fire?
Enkidu is clay.
The manifestation of fire
can turn him to stone.
You're an unexpected surprise, Akkadian.
As are you... Amina.
(MEN AND HORSES IN DISTANCE)
Stop the Akkadian!
I'll take the two on the right.
- That leaves me the seven on the left.
- Exactly.
You have a book my master desires.
I don't read books.
Give it to me, Akkadian,
and I give you my word,
I will not leave you butchered and cleaved.
I will give you a death
worthy of a Scorpion King.
I have turned down that same
offer many times before.
But you are one,
we are many.
We are two.
The woman?
(LAUGHING)
The woman! The woman!
All right. I'll take the three on the right.
Fair enough.
Hyah!
(ALL SHOUTING)
Tala! Get Amina outta here!
Amina! Amina!
(GRUNTING)
I'm gonna smash ya!
(GROANING)
Well done, Scorpion King...
(ENKIDU ROARS)
Enkidu, no!
They're just horses. We don't hurt them.
That Akkadian, he stole you.
No one stole me. I left.
You only have two commands now.
Protect me, and obey me.
Not like that in your books,
is it?
(ENKIDU GROWLS)
I don't like him.
Aqaba.
AMINA: A city. So many people.
How do we hire a boat to cross the sea?
We sell the horses.
(PEOPLE CHATTERING)
Fresh fish! Fresh fish.
Don't talk to anyone.
We're not here to trade in gossip.
I will not speak to these strange people,
because I do not know them,
and I have nothing to say.
You. Don't talk at all.
(GRUNTS) I like to talk.
(ENKIDU SNIFFS AND GROWLS)
Enkidu, no!
You filthy creature! Did you fart?
Sell the horses, get to the port,
hire a boat, cross the sea to Amonesh.
I'll meet you at the tomb.
(SPEAKING NATIVE LANGUAGE)
Scorpion King!
Been looking for you.
Here I am.
Enkidu, take Amina. I'll meet
you at the port. That way.
Get him!
I want him alive!
Go!
- You're gonna bleed!
- And you're gonna die.
(GROANS)
(SCREAMS)
Get on!
Hyah!
Jump, blacksmith! Jump.
Are you in?
I told you to stay with Amina!
And I had to save your life!
Again!
Men!
NEBSEREK: Tarqa!
King Tarqa.
Son of Balthazar. King of Nubia.
The King of Nubia, he is your brother?
Yes.
Tarqa.
Son of Balthazar, the king warrior?
He died fighting for his people,
with honor and dignity.
Let me carry this burden for you,
for you have much
to accomplish on this quest.
I am the sole heir of Nubia, blacksmith.
I am a queen with no kingdom.
Now, I know your pain.
I am sorry for your loss.
But your choice is a simple one.
You can fight on,
avenge your brother and your people,
and maybe you will die.
Or you can turn back now,
make a new life for yourself.
But when you leave this world,
many years from now,
and give a full account of your life here,
what story would you like
history to remember?
This is what you meant about quests?
AMINA: So, you're the famous Scorpion King?
MATHAYUS: Someone I used to be.
AMINA: But someday, you may regain
your kingdom, build it anew.
MATHAYUS: There's nothing left of my kingdom.
In Aqaba, you saw somebody
you wanted to kill.
And in killing that person,
you'd have likely been killed.
Yes.
She killed someone very close to me.
There are many stories about vengeance.
There is honor in payback.
TALA: The lost city of Amonesh.
Enkidu, you will have to wait for us here.
I cannot protect you if I'm not with you,
and I cannot obey you if I cannot hear you.
But we'll have torches in there.
No flames!
But there's no other way.
MATHAYUS: I may have another way.
But you'll have to trust me.
A tomb. I hate tombs.
Don't let the fire touch me.
Is the fire touching me?
No, it's not touching you.
Ah, yeah.
Come, Enkidu.
(ENKIDU BREATHING HEAVILY)
No fire! No fire!
ENKIDU: Amina! Amina! Don't make me wait.
Stop, it's okay.
- It's okay.
- Yeah.
AMINA: "King Memtep."
This inscription's just details of his life.
The tomb builders would have
never carved the secret text
on how to break the curse of Anubis
on the walls for robbers to easily decipher.
It would have been hidden,
or concealed in the funerary artifacts.
In a sarcophagus?
No.
That's where the sword was found.
It would have been separated.
Everything's been plundered and robbed.
The Sphinx.
An idol full of secrets and mystery.
The guardian of knowledge.
The Sphinx dies for truth,
but this is an androsphinx,
the male of the species, known
as the messenger of truth.
Break it open.
I'll give it right back.
No!
Enkidu, I'll bring it back. I promise.
Bring it back!
MATHAYUS: It's a history written in Sumerian.
Yes.
AMINA: These hieroglyphs say King Memtep
was beset by enemies on all sides.
He called out to the God of the Underworld,
who forged a sword to steal
the souls of his enemies,
giving King Memtep strength
and power beyond measure.
And the king grew terrible in his might,
for he was cursed,
and tormented by the screams
of the tortured souls.
King Memtep returned to Amonesh to find
his royal concubine had birthed a girl child.
His daughter's skin bore the names
of those slain by the sword.
Anubis told King Memtep
the only way to end the curse
was to destroy the Book
of Souls with the sword.
It was the god's cruel trick
that to save himself,
the king must end the curse
by killing his only daughter.
But a powerful mage saved the girl,
stealing her away forever,
and King Memtep went mad from the curse,
driving the sword into his own heart,
so entering his own name
into the Book of Souls.
King Memtep was your father.
The mage I thought
was my father raised me as his own.
He meant to protect me.
That's impossible. That would make you...
I have lived for centuries,
and I will live for countless millennia more.
The only way to break
the curse of Anubis is to...
I must be destroyed by the sword.
The Book of Souls must be
destroyed and the souls freed.
And I am the Book of Souls.
The Book of Souls, hidden
in the body of a beautiful woman.
(GRUNTS)
Men are simple, aren't they?
The Scorpion King.
I've sedated him.
This is the Scorpion King
everyone whispers about.
Legends always start with a whisper.
Hmm, he doesn't look like
very much in these chains.
Before I take his head off his shoulders,
let us see how he fights.
Alert me when he wakes from his slumber.
Are you sure this is wise?
Kill him now and be done with it.
He's already half-dead, priestess.
Half-dead men are dangerous,
especially a man like this.
The jackals want to see
this great warrior killed in battle.
We must satiate their bloodlust.
He is weak and wounded
and no match for the sword!
No!
Princess Tala.
I am your queen now.
If called, are the men ready to fight?
The men will fight, my queen.
What is this?
The Book of Souls.
Written on ancient vellum,
illuminated in the blue light
of the evening sun.
Such beauty.
So, you thought to defeat me
by destroying the sword,
and with it my power?
I see you're a book with a will of your own.
Such contempt in your eyes.
Burn the bitch.
TALA: Rise, blacksmith.
Become the Scorpion King again.
MENNOFER: We honor the covenant
between the God of the Underworld, Anubis,
and the bearer of his sword,
our god-king Nebserek.
Nebserek! Nebserek! Nebserek!
MENNOFER: Here on this sacred ground,
we gather at the sacrificial fires
to put forth...
TALA: Remember who you are, Scorpion King,
demigod, the last Akkadian.
(ROCK CRUMBLING)
MENNOFER: ...written in the prophesies,
The Book of Souls shall burn
and be thus destroyed.
Let no man stand against us!
I am one man!
But one can stand against many,
for a friend.
(GRUNTING)
Calm your blades, jackals.
He's mine!
How was your sleep, Scorpion King?
I'm just a blacksmith.
I admire a man who stands tall,
even when he's overmatched.
The time for chanting has not yet come.
Enkidu, it's time.
- NEBSEREK: The people want...
- I did not protect Amina.
I failed her.
We have not failed.
- Not yet.
- NEBSEREK: He threatens my reign.
You stand on the ruins of my people,
broken many years ago
by your Akkadian empire.
We were forced to live like jackals,
eating scraps to survive.
But one jackal
was not prepared to slink away,
and grow old, starving and defeated!
I dug deep,
deep into the sand and found the one thing
that can rebuild an empire
ruled by an eater of souls.
With this sword, I am invincible!
ALL: (CHANTING) Nebserek! Nebserek! Nebserek!
You fear no man.
I fear no man.
I have faith in you, Enkidu.
Show me who you are.
This is your time.
This is your moment!
- Amina needs you!
- (GRUNTS)
On my command, unleash hell.
Nebserek! Nebserek! Nebserek!
No!
You must believe!
I cannot burn!
You cannot burn!
Break it down!
ENKIDU: Amina! I'm coming!
(SCREAMING)
Give me your soul, Akkadian!
Never.
AMINA: Enkidu!
I cannot fail.
Must destroy sword!
- I cannot...
- No!
Fail!
Amina!
(SCREAMS)
If I can't have your soul, Akkadian,
then I will send you to the afterlife.
No, I create my destiny,
and I will not die by your hand.
But you will!
No!
Break this curse, Scorpion King.
I won't hurt you.
The evil will not rest.
It will come for the sword again and again.
I am the sacrifice that must be made,
to destroy the sword and free the souls.
I'm not afraid.
Is there no other way?
Thank you for showing me your world.
Goodbye, Amina.
NARRATOR: History will tell
of this fearless warrior
who never forgot his destiny again.
He was known by many names,
Akkadian,
Assassin,
Blacksmith,
and Liberator of Souls.
But the name he made
for himself will be forever etched
in the sands of time,
Mathayus, the Scorpion King.
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org