- Thank you so much.
- That looks fabulous.
Thank you, Geoffrey.
You're welcome.
We'll also take a bottle of red as well.
Thank you.
Certainly.
Right, now...
Thank you, Barry.
You're welcome.
Thank you.
- That looks wonderful.
- Beautiful day.
Where are you going?
To eat my sandwich.
You'll ruin
your appetite for prawns.
I don't like prawns.
Darling,
don't wander off.
For God's sake,
leave her alone, Deirdre.
Go play
with your ball.
Don't be so annoying!
Darling, what about snakes?
There aren't any snakes
on the beach.
Just let her enjoy
herself for once.
- Edward?
- Yes, ma'am.
Hello, there.
What are you,
a little bird or something?
Are you hungry? Take a bite.
It's roast beef.
It's good. Come on.
I won't hurt you.
Mommy! Daddy! You've got to come see this!
I found something!
Cathy, darling,
lunch is ready!
Are you looking at this?
I'm afraid there
isn't enough to go around.
Paul?
Cathy?
- Will you hurry up?
- Hurry up!
You're him, right?
Excuse me?
The scientist? The guy?
I saw you on TV.
I believed you.
Who shall I tell
Mr. Hammond is calling?
- Ian Malcolm.
- I've been summoned.
Dr. Malcolm!
Oh, my God.
Hello, Dr. Malcolm.
Kids, kids.
It's so great to see you.
It's so great.
Look at you.
You came to see Grandpa?
Yeah, he called me.
Do you know what it's about?
I don't, either.
This joint's kind of creepy, isn't it?
Is everything okay?
Well, not exactly.
Dr. Malcolm.
Dr. Malcolm. Here to share a few
campfire stories with my uncle?
You can convince The Washington
Post and Skeptical Inquirer
of what you want
but I was there.
I know what happened and so do you.
Do you actually believe that
everyone who chose discretion did so
for a nefarious motive?
Even Lex and Tim?
- Leave them out of it.
- It's not a game.
No. You signed
a nondisclosure agreement
before you went
to the island
that forbade you from
discussing what you saw.
You violated that agreement.
I did. And you lied about
the deaths of three people.
You misinformed
the public,
which made me
look like a nut.
Hasn't been so good
for my livelihood...
We made a generous compensatory
offer for your injuries.
A payoff and an insult.
When you spin reality,
cover up evidence,
it hurts more
than my reputation.
As I recall,
your university
revoked your tenure
for your selling
wild stories to the press.
I didn't sell anything.
I never took a cent, and I told the truth.
Your version of it.
There aren't "versions"
of the truth.
InGen can't keep
spewing out...
InGen is my
responsibility now.
I will jealously
defend its interests.
- Your responsibility?
- What about Mr. Hammond?
It is our board of directors
I must face, not my uncle.
Trust me, your problems are
about to be rendered moot.
In a few weeks' time,
they'll be long forgotten.
Not by me.
Careful.
This suit cost more
than your education.
You were right
and I was wrong. There!
Did you ever expect
to hear me say such a thing?
Thank God for Site B.
Site B?
Isla Nublar was
just a showroom,
something for the tourists.
Site B was
the factory floor.
That was on Isla Sorna,
80 miles from Nublar.
We bred the animals there, and
nurtured them for a few months,
then moved them
into the park.
Really? I did not know that.
After the accident
in the park,
Hurricane Clarissa wiped out
our facility on Site B.
Call it an act of God.
We had to evacuate.
The animals were released
to mature on their own.
"Life will find a way," as you
once so eloquently put it.
By now we have a complete
ecological system on the island
with dozens of species living
in their own social groups
without fences, boundaries,
or constraining technology.
And for four years
I've tried to keep it safe
from human interference.
That's right. Hopefully,
you've kept the island
quarantined and contained.
But I'm in shock
about all this.
I mean, that they're
still alive.
You bred them
lysine-deficient.
Shouldn't they have
kicked after seven days
without supplemental enzymes?
Yes! But, by God,
they're flourishing.
That's one of 1,000 questions
I want the team to answer.
Team?
Yes.
I've organized
an expedition to go in,
thank you,
and document them.
To make the most spectacular
living fossil record
the world has ever seen.
Go in and document?
You mean with people?
Yes, the animals won't know they're there.
Very low impact.
Strictly observation
and documentation.
Our satellite infrareds
show the animals
are fiercely territorial.
The carnivores are isolated
in the interior of the island
so the team can stay
on the outer rim.
Don't worry. I'm not making
the same mistakes again.
No, you're making
all new ones.
John! So, there's another
island with dinosaurs,
no fences this time, and you
want to send people in,
very few people,
on the ground, right?
Who are the four lunatics
you're trying to con into this?
It was difficult to convince
them as to what they would see,
in the end had to use my
checkbook to get them there.
But there's Nick Van Owen,
who is
a video documentarian,
Eddie Carr, who's a
field equipment expert.
We have
our paleontologist
and I was hoping that perhaps
you might be the fourth.
We've been on the verge
of Chapter 11
ever since that
accident in the park.
There are those
in the company
who wanted to
exploit Site B
in order to bail us out.
They've been
planning it for years,
and I've been able
to stop them until now.
But, a few weeks ago, a British
family on a yacht cruise
stumbled across the island and
their wee girl was injured.
She's fine.
But the board
has used the incident
to take control
of InGen from me.
Now it's only a matter
of time before this
lost world
is found and pillaged.
Public opinion is the one thing
I can use to preserve it,
but to rally that support
I need a complete
photo record
of those animals alive and
in their natural habitat.
So you went from capitalist to
naturalist in just four years.
That's something.
It's our last chance
at redemption.
John,
no.
Of course, no.
And I'm going to contact the
other three members of your team
and stop them from going.
Who's the paleontologist,
by the way?
She came to me,
I want you to know this.
Who did?
Leave it to you, Ian, to have
associations, affiliations,
even liaisons, with the best
people in so many fields.
Not Sarah.
Paleontological behavior
study is a new field,
and Sarah Harding
is on that frontier.
Her theories on
parenting and nurturing
amongst carnivores
have framed the debate.
What are you doing?
Where's your phone?
It's too late.
She's already there.
The others are
meeting her in three days.
You sent my girlfriend
to this island alone?
"Sent" is hardly the word.
She couldn't be restrained.
She was already
working in San Diego,
doing some research
at the animal park.
It's only a couple
of hours' flight from there.
She was adamant, absolutely
adamant about, here you are,
about making the initial
foray by herself.
She thinks
she's Dian Fossey.
"Observation without
interference," she said.
She went on and on.
You know how it is.
After you were injured in the
park, she sought you out.
Then she went all the way
to a hospital in Costa Rica
to ask somebody who she didn't
even know if the rumors were true.
If you want to leave your
name on something, fine.
But stop putting it on
other people's headstones.
She'll be fine. She's spent years
studying African predators.
Sleeping downwind and all.
She knows what she's doing.
And, believe me,
the research team will...
It's not a research
expedition any more.
It's a rescue operation
and it's leaving now.
You can't shave three
days off my deadline
and expect to be ready.
I'm not supplied.
I haven't tested any of this.
Why give her
a satellite phone
if it doesn't work?
Why doesn't it?
Could be solar flares, the satellite,
or maybe she turned it off.
I need half air on the tires.
We're flying pressurized.
Does she know
how to use it?
You kidding?
She's faxed me refinements on 50%
of the plans for this stuff.
Don't do that. You got to baby
it a little bit. Love it.
I'll love it
when it works.
It'll work
when you love it.
You coming along?
I don't usually,
but I can't resist.
Thanks for
the two-minute warning.
Nick Van Owen,
this is Ian Malcolm.
Nick's our
field photographer.
How do you do?
You do
wildlife photography?
Wildlife, combat,
you name it.
When I was with Nightline, I was
in Rwanda, Chechnya, Bosnia.
I do volunteer work with
Greenpeace once in a while.
Greenpeace?
What drew you there?
Women.
80% female,
Greenpeace.
Noble.
- Noble was last year.
- This year I'm getting paid.
Hammond's check cleared, or I
wouldn't go on this wild-goose chase.
You're going to the only place in the
world where the geese chase you.
Dad! Dad!
Kelly, my honey, you found it.
What took you so long?
Sorry, I couldn't
get a cab.
Sweetie, that's okay.
Listen, I've got to tell you something.
I've got to talk to you.
I don't even know
this woman.
You've known Karen
for 10 years.
She doesn't even have Sega.
She's such a troglodyte.
Cruel, but good word use.
Why can't
I stay with Sarah?
She's out of town.
Karen's fantastic.
She'll take you places.
You'll have a fantastic time.
Stop saying "fantastic."
Where are you going, anyway?
It's only for a few days.
I wouldn't be going if it wasn't really important.
I'm your daughter
all the time.
You can't abandon me
whenever opportunity knocks.
That hurts my feelings.
Your mom tell you to say that?
Dr. Malcolm,
downstairs, please.
I know we've had
some hard going.
But in the last few years, we've
started to work things out.
Yeah, but crack
on me a bit.
Ground me or something.
Send me to my room.
You never do
any of that stuff.
Why would I?
You turned out so
beautiful, brilliant, powerful,
funny, and generous.
The queen, goddess.
My inspiration.
Dr. Malcolm.
I could come be your research
assistant, like I was in Austin.
This is nothing
like Austin.
Anyway, you have
your own stuff.
Your gymnastics competition.
You've been training for months.
Gymnastics?
I scrubbed out, Dad, I got cut from the team.
Thanks for knowing.
I'm sorry, honey.
I know how much
that meant to you.
You like to have kids.
But you just don't want
to be with them, do you?
It wasn't me who dumped you
and split for Paris,
so don't take it
out on me.
Dr. Malcolm, downstairs!
Honey, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
You want some good parental advice?
Don't listen to me.
How are
we doing here?
The specs say it can't deform at 12,000
PSI, so we just have to test it.
Let's clear.
Are we clear?
What's this?
A High Hide.
You know, you go up and hide, high.
It goes up to where
the trees are
and keeps the researchers
out of harm's way.
Actually, it puts them at a
very convenient biting height.
What's the time?
Do you have the time?
Do I have the time? Why?
We're leaving
in three hours.
This is so cool.
Lindstradt air rifle.
Fires a subsonic Fluger impact delivery dart.
It works better than
your satellite phone?
That's funny.
I loaded it with the enhanced
venom of Conus Purpurascens,
South Sea cone shell.
Most powerful neurotoxin
in the world.
Acts within 0.002
of a second.
Which is faster than the
nerve-conduction velocity.
So the animal's down before it
even feels the prick of the dart.
Is there an antidote?
Like if you shot
yourself in the foot?
Don't do that.
You'd be dead before
you even realized
you had an accident.
He says
he's unloading us here.
He won't go
further up the river.
He's heard too many stories
about this island chain.
He'll drop us off
and anchor offshore.
What kind of stories?
Stories of fishermen that
came too close to the island
and never returned.
He has a radio.
He has a satellite phone.
When you need him, call and
he'll be here in two hours.
But he will not stay here.
He won't stay anywhere
near these islands.
They call the islands
"Las Cinco Muertes"?
What does that mean?
"The Five Deaths",
he says.
I put a location sensor in Dr.
Harding's phone,
so we should get a reading.
I'm so relieved.
Don't push my buttons.
We're almost
on top of her dot.
She should be around here.
Over there.
Sarah!
Sarah Harding!
How many Sarahs do you think
are on this island?
What?
Something big.
Wow.
This is magnificent.
Yeah. "Ooh, ah," that's
how it always starts.
But then later there's
running and screaming.
Wow.
Nick!
I guess you got the jump
on us, didn't you, Sarah?
Yeah.
Ian, I never thought
in a million years
Hammond could get you
to come here.
- Hi, Eddie.
- Hi, Sarah.
Got a granola bar
or something? I'm starving.
Did you see those animals?
A family group, a pair-bond
and a sub-adult,
long after the juvenile
was nest bound.
Every egg clutch I've seen has
crushed, trampled shells.
Hatchlings stay in the birth
environment a long time.
That's conclusive.
I can put that controversy to
rest if I get a shot of the nest.
Have you been attacked?
No, that's my lucky pack.
That's how it always looks.
Okay, Sarah...
- Is that a Nikon?
- Can I borrow that?
I'll be right back, baby,
I promise.
When Hammond
called you,
why didn't you say
something to me?
I knew you would have
stopped me from coming.
I would have
tied you to the bed.
I know how they
survived without lysine.
I don't care.
The herbivore species
that are thriving
eat mostly agama beans, soy,
anything lysine-rich.
And the carnivores
eat the herbivores, so...
Wait.
Stay there. Be quiet.
I'll be right back.
No!
Stay there.
She's much too close.
What the hell is she doing?
Too close.
She has to touch it.
She can't not touch.
She's going
right up to it.
Once she sees something,
she has to...
Is this even possible?
What?
This? What did you
think you'd document?
What did you think
you'd see?
Animals. Maybe,
big iguanas.
Fruitcakes.
They get very angry
when you run out of film.
Sarah!
Shoot them!
They're just
protecting their baby.
So am I!
I think they're leaving.
Wow.
These images are incredible.
Legendary.
Guys shoot their whole life, they
never get stuff half this good.
Just give me the Pulitzer right now.
Today, please.
The competition's over,
close the entries,
I'd like to thank
everyone who lost.
Don't light that!
Dinosaurs pick up scents from miles away.
We're here to observe and
document, not interact.
Which, by the way, is a
scientific impossibility.
Heisenberg
Uncertainty Principle.
What you study,
you also change.
I'll risk it. I'm sick of
scratching around in rock and bone
making assumptions
and deductions about
the nurturing
habits of animals
that have been dead for 65 million years.
I'm sick of it, man.
Then you fill my head
with stories for four years.
Of course I came down here.
Stories of
mutilation and death.
Weren't you
paying attention?
Please! Don't treat me
like I'm a grad student.
I've worked around predators
since I was 20 years old.
Lions, jackals,
hyenas, you.
Where's the fire?
I'm trying to change 100
years of entrenched dogma.
Dinosaurs were characterized very
early on as vicious lizards.
There's great resistance to the
idea of them as nurturing parents.
Robert Burke said
the T. Rex was a rogue
who abandoned its young at the earliest opportunity.
I can prove otherwise.
Fire! Dr. Malcolm,
fire, base camp!
No! Water makes
the smoke billow. Use dirt!
Who started the fire?
I just wanted
to make dinner.
I wanted it ready
when you guys got back.
Do you see any family
resemblance there?
You practically
told me to come here.
I... What?
You said,
"Don't listen to me."
I thought you were trying
to tell me something.
Kelly, you knew exactly what I meant.
You have no...
You want to lock her up
for her curiosity?
Where do you think
she gets it?
Thank you, Sarah.
Don't start
the teaming-up thing.
Out of the conversation.
Please. Really.
Eddie?
What?
Why in the hell doesn't
this thing ever work?
It's not a landline.
You're not in a phone booth.
You got to wait
for a decent signal.
Violence and technology,
not good bedfellows.
Hammond wants your equipment as
close to the animals as possible.
Great idea. And why don't you
smear on a little sheep's blood?
Eddie, is there
any reason to think
the radio in
the trailer might work?
Don't tease me.
If you feel qualified, try
flicking the switch to "on."
Okay, I'm taking
my daughter out of here.
Anyone coming with me, this is
your last chance to get out.
When you're out
in the field...
Nick, if you're staying,
I'll gladly deliver
a letter to your wife
or loved one
so you can say goodbye.
Eddie, if you have
any personal effects
it's the least I can do.
I'll be in there, guys.
Our presence needs
to be 100% antiseptic.
If we so much as bend
a blade of grass...
Dad, are you mad?
No, I'm not mad.
I'm furious.
What is this?
This looks like your room.
I was going to clean it up.
Right now.
What is this?
There are 100 switches!
Don't be mad. I was going to call
to let you know where I was.
I always do, don't I?
I'm the best kind
of girlfriend there is.
One who travels a lot. You like that, right?
You love your independence.
I've gotten used
to being apart,
but that's not
how I want to live.
Kelly, this is tall talk.
Just for a minute.
It's like a height restriction
at an amusement park.
If you wanted to rescue me, why
didn't you bail me out from
that museum fundraiser three weeks
ago, like you said you would?
This is a slightly
different situation.
What about the dinner with your
parents you never showed up for?
Why not rescue me
when I really need it?
Be there when
you say you will?
I have made a career
out of waiting for you.
You know,
Sarah has a pretty good...
It's so important to your future
that you not finish that sentence.
Please, outside!
Ian, come on. Look.
I love that you rode in here
on a white horse. I really do.
It's very touching,
very dramatic.
I just need you to show up in a
cab every once in a while, too.
What are you doing?
Don't go out there. It's not safe.
Stay in here. Come back.
Shut the door.
Okay.
I know what I'm doing.
You guys should definitely go.
But I'm going to stay.
I love you.
I just don't need you right now.
What you need is
a good anti-psychotic.
I'll be back
in five or six days.
No, you'll be back
in five or six pieces.
What bothers you is that I'm not
afraid of this place, and you are.
Of course I am. That's the whole thing.
All I want is...
What's that sound?
Here we go. I'll get you
out on one of these, now.
Hello! Over here!
I don't get it. It says InGen
on the side of that chopper!
I don't get that.
Why would Hammond send two teams?
Cut the
umbilical, Dad!
Doesn't he trust us?
We haven't even started.
This is as good a place
as any for base camp.
That's first priority
after we're finished.
I want it up and running in 30 minutes.
That's half an hour.
Understood? Over.
Cancel that order.
What? Why?
This is a game trail,
Mr. Ludlow.
Carnivores hunt
on game trails.
You want to set up
base camp or a buffet?
Let's find a new spot,
shall we? Over and out.
Peter, if I run your little camping
trip, there are two conditions.
First, I'm in charge.
If I'm not around, Dieter is.
You just pay us,
tell us we're doing well,
and serve us Scotch
after a good day.
Second condition, my fee.
You can keep it.
All I want for my services, is the
right to hunt a tyrannosaurus.
A male. A buck only.
How and why are my business.
If you don't like those
conditions, you're on your own.
So go ahead,
set up base camp here,
in a swamp, or in the middle
of a Rex nest for all I care.
I've had too many safaris
with rich dentists
to listen to any more
suicidal ideas.
Okay?
Okay.
Cycle, break off the stray from the
herd and flush him to the right.
Snaggers, stay ready.
He's bringing them out to you. It'll be a
Pachy... Pachya...
Oh, hell.
The fat head with
the bald spot. Friar Tuck.
Stop.
Pachycephalosaurus.
Carnivore?
No, herbivore,
late Cretaceous.
See the distinctive
domed skull?
Nine inches of solid bone.
Now, careful.
See, the Pachy's neck attaches
at the bottom of its skull,
not at the back
of its head.
When it lowers its head, its
neck lines up with its backbone,
which is perfect
for absorbing impact.
Snagger, Friar Tuck's
on the loose,
just about to cross
your path.
Dieter,
get in the outrigger.
You're closing in
on a carina...
Say that
again, Roland. A what?
The one with the big red horn.
The pompadour. Elvis.
Take me out.
Okay, Carter, reel me in.
Easy!
Not too close.
Go for the legs!
The legs! Watch the tail!
Burke!
Come here.
Recognize this trackway?
Yes, I do. Tyrannosaur.
Roland.
Where do you think
you're going?
To collect my fee, Mr.
Ludlow. To collect my fee.
Oh, my God.
Procompsognathus triassicus, found
by Frass in Bavaria in 1913.
Is it dangerous?
No, I wouldn't think so.
The Compy's been presumed to
be a scavengers, like jackals.
It gives me the creeps.
It's like it's not scared.
There haven't been any
visitors to this island.
There's no reason
for it to fear man.
Now it does.
It's the Rex nest.
Infant's probably only a couple weeks old.
Never left the nest.
Offspring that young, the parents
won't leave him alone for too long.
Make your blind here,
wait for the buck to return.
No. If the nest is upwind,
then so are we.
When he comes back,
he's gonna know
we're here without us
having a chance.
The trick is to get him
to come where we want him.
This is why Hammond was in
a hurry to get you here.
He knew they were coming.
My God,
they are well-organized.
Those are some
major-league toys.
Maybe I should ask
to use their phone.
Their dish is bigger
than yours.
So they actually want
to build another park here?
After what you said happened
on the other island?
They're not
building anything.
They're taking these
animals out of here.
Back to the mainland.
I think I should tell you.
Hammond told me these people might show up.
He thought we'd be finished by the
time they started, but if they weren't
he sent a backup plan.
What backup plan?
Me.
InGen is seeking
limited partners
to defray some
of our expenses.
The prospectus you've been
given by the board details
our projected hardware
and construction expenses.
As you can see
by my two friends here,
the software is
already fully developed.
One might say,
"lt'd be up and running."
In a moment, I'll take you
on a stroll through the camp
and you'll see some larger,
more impressive specimens.
Wow.
You don't bring people halfway
around the world to visit a zoo.
You bring the zoo to them.
San Diego is
the perfect setting.
People already associate our beautiful
city with animal attractions:
San Diego Zoo, Sea World,
San Diego Chargers.
Mr. Hammond
knew this.
Before he ever
dreamt of an island
he began construction
on an amphitheatre
very near to where you're sitting
now, the InGen Waterfront Complex.
But he abandoned it
in favor of something
far grander
and ultimately impossible.
And so, the facility
sits unused, unfinished,
when it could be
completed and ready
to receive visitors
in less than a month.
Ajay,
look out! Jump!
That's the last time
I leave you in charge.
- Oh, my God.
- Are you out of your mind?
She's got
a broken leg.
Let's get in the car
before they hear us.
You have any idea
what that is?
Come on,
open the door.
You're nuts.
Man, Ian's not
going to like this.
What's going on?
Isn't it obvious?
We're not alone
on this island.
It's not set
to the frequency.
Look here.
What the hell is that?
- It's right here.
- Hello?
No, not Enrique. Ian Malcolm.
Are you on the boat?
No, is this the boat?
We're on Isla Sorna.
We need to talk to the boat, Mar del Plata.
I'll get him.
All right. That's it.
I got you.
Hurry up.
Let's go. Go. Come on.
Watch his tail. Get the door.
Boy, is she mad at you.
I feel sorry
for that guy, Enrique.
No lectures, please.
Honey, stay back.
Don't stand up, okay?
I got it!
Watch his head.
Ian, he's hurt!
No, honey, no.
I'm going
to get the table.
He'll snip at you.
Watch his tail, he's swinging his tail.
Set him down.
All right?
Okay, I got him.
Got him?
Yeah.
It's okay.
There you go.
What must I do,
hit her with a stick?
No, don't get close, honey.
Watch out!
Don't stand too close.
He smells.
No, lady, enough!
Wrong frequency. God.
Nick, don't let him
get those things around you.
Hello,
it's Ian Malcolm.
Okay,
let's take a look at this.
Easy, easy.
Just calm down now.
Okay,
here are the metatarsals.
Tibia, fibula. There it is.
There's the fracture.
Right above the epiphysis.
How bad is it?
If we don't set it,
he'll die. It won't heal.
He won't be able to
pivot on his ankle.
He won't be able
to run or walk.
A predator
will pick him off.
Carlos, come in.
God damn it,
you bastard, listen...
Other animals
are going to hear this.
Come in, please.
Can you hear me?
I've got to get out of here.
I want to leave.
I'm calling the boat.
I want to go someplace else.
I don't want to be here.
I want to be somewhere safe.
Isn't it safe here?
I want to be
somewhere high.
What? What is it?
What's going on?
Information, please. What?
You're much happier not knowing.
Get us up. Here we go.
There we go.
I'm so stupid.
I shouldn't have come along with you.
Can you set it?
Yeah, I just need
something temporary
to break apart and
fall off as he grows.
Whenever you're ready.
He's fighting, Dr. Quinn.
What's the frequency
for the boat?
- 15888.
- It's third from the top.
Okay, we're high.
This is the safest place you can be.
Like Sarah said,
the plants make it
so the animals
won't know you're here.
You're just trying
to make me feel better.
I remember the stories
you told.
This is nothing like that.
We're in a completely
different situation now.
Is there any way we can
communicate with the trailer?
He's moving again,
more morphine.
We have no idea what his metabolism is.
We'll kill him with too much.
I need your hand here.
Put some pressure there.
No answer. What a surprise.
How do I get down?
Tie this belt around you.
Where are you going?
Stay here. Come on,
stay here. Please!
Squeeze this rope hard.
The harder you squeeze,
the slower you go.
If you don't
squeeze at all...
I get the idea.
Dad, please stay here.
Stay here, please.
Honey, the queen?
The goddess?
Your inspiration?
Now you're talking.
- Now you're talking.
- All right.
I'm coming right back.
I give you my word.
But you never
keep your word!
I would have squeezed
just a little bit harder.
Okay, I'm almost finished.
Damn it.
I need another adhesive.
Something pliable
that I can...
Spit.
Your gum.
Get the amoxicillin
and fill a syringe.
Quick injection of antibiotics
and he's out of here.
For once in your life, would
it kill you to pick it up?
Help me get it out of here.
No, we just set its leg.
Mommy's very angry.
This isn't hunting behavior, Ian.
They're searching.
They came for their infant.
Let's not disappoint them.
Let me get his head, okay?
Careful. Be careful.
I got him.
Muzzle off.
Yes, Eddie?
They're going
back to the jungle.
- I know. I see.
- How's Kelly?
She's fine.
She's right here.
Hello?
Kelly, are you okay?
Yeah, I'm good.
Stay there. Don't move.
I'll be right back up. Understand?
Yeah, I understand.
I beg people
to listen to me.
I use plain,
simple English.
Shut up.
That should make an interesting
chapter in your book.
The debate over
the parental instincts
of the T. Rex
is now academic.
Hang on.
This is gonna be bad.
They're pushing
us over the cliff.
Oh, my God.
Come on, come on.
Once we're out of here...
Into the woods.
Straight into the woods.
Come on!
This is where they hit us.
Hang on to something!
Sarah!
Oh, God, please!
Don't move!
I'm coming down for you.
Here I come. Stay still.
Here I come, Sarah.
The satellite phone,
get it!
Okay.
Give me your hand, honey.
Heads up!
Your lucky pack.
I got her.
- Nick?
- We're in here.
Hold on!
I'm coming.
God damn it!
What did this?
Kelly. What'd you
do with Kelly?
She's okay.
She's in the High Hide.
Who's hurt?
What do you need?
We need rope.
Rope. Anything else?
Three cheeseburgers
with everything.
No onions on mine.
And an apple turnover.
Hold on.
I'm coming!
- Bring the rope.
- Let's go.
- I'm coming.
- Now, now.
Eddie, you all right?
Yeah. I'm coming.
We need the rope.
Throw it down here. Hurry up!
Good throw.
Did you tie this to anything?
We're sliding down!
Up you go.
Eddie! Hey!
Go.
Increase your rate of climb.
Our communication
equipment's been destroyed.
And if your radio and satellite
phone were in those trailers...
They were.
Then we're stuck here.
And stuck together,
thanks to you people.
We came to watch.
You came to strip-mine the place.
Back off.
At least we came prepared.
Five years of work
and electrified fence
couldn't prepare
the other island.
You think your
Marlboro men will help?
You're looters.
You came to take.
You have no rights.
An extinct animal brought
back to life has no rights.
It exists
because we made it.
We patented it. We own it.
You looking for a problem?
And I found you, didn't I?
Stop!
Come on!
I know you.
You're that
Earth First bastard.
What's Earth First?
Professional saboteurs.
Environmentalists!
Criminals.
Knock it off!
Listen to me.
Moving the baby to
our camp may have
changed the adults'
perceived territory.
Their what?
That's why they
attacked the trailers.
They're defending
this entire area now.
We have to move now.
To where? Our boat
and their airlift
are waiting for
orders we can't send.
All right.
There's a communications center here
near the old operations building.
Everything ran on
geothermal power.
It was never meant
to need replenishing.
If we can get here, we can send
a radio call to the airlift.
You know the frequency?
Here in this book.
We'll mind those.
How far is the village?
A day's walk, maybe more.
That's not the problem.
What is?
What is the problem?
Velociraptors.
Their nesting sites are in the
island's interior, which is why
we were keeping
to the outer rim.
Wait. What's a Veloc...
Velociraptor.
Carnivore. Pack hunter.
Two meters tall,
long snout,
binocular vision, strong dexterous
forearms, killing claws on both feet.
The Rexes
may track us, too,
if they feel we're a threat
to them or their infant.
No, we'll lose them once
we leave their territory.
Don't bet on it. Tyrannosaur has the
largest proportional olfactory cavity
of any creature in
fossil record, except one.
Right.
The turkey vulture
could scent up to 10 miles.
Right. This is all
very thrilling,
but I say we should
head for the village.
We could head back
down to the lagoon.
And sit out in the open, next
to a heavily used water source
hope that your
captain comes back?
He won't.
He knows better.
Then we head
for the village,
we might find shelter
and we can call for help.
Rex just fed, so he
won't stalk us for food.
Just fed? You mean Eddie?
Show some respect.
He saved our lives
by giving his.
Then his troubles are over.
My point is predators don't
hunt when they're not hungry.
No, only humans do.
You're breaking our heart.
Saddle up! Let's get this
moveable feast underway.
Excuse me, cowboy.
You want some gum?
You seem like you have common sense.
Why the hell are you here?
Somewhere on this island is the
greatest predator that ever lived.
The second greatest predator
must take him down.
You going to use that?
If he doesn't
surrender, yes.
Let me see it.
No.
The animal exists
for the first time
in tens of
millions of years
and the only way you can express
yourself is to kill it.
Remember that chap about 20 years ago?
I forget his name.
Climbed Everest without any oxygen.
Came down nearly dead.
They asked him, "Why did
you go up there to die?"
He said, "I didn't.
I went up there to live."
I didn't wish you luck
on your new venture.
You're off to
a promising start.
My team is intact.
I'm sorry for the loss of your man.
It's easy to criticize someone who
generates an idea, assumes the risk.
When you try to sound like Hammond,
it comes off as a hustle.
It's not your fault.
They say talent skips a generation.
I'm sure your kids
will be sharp as tacks.
Hammond's reach exceeded his grasp.
Mine does not.
Taking dinosaurs
off this island
is the worst idea in the long,
sad history of bad ideas.
And I'll be there
when you learn that.
Go.
Take a break. Five minutes.
Are you injured?
No, it's the baby's.
I set its broken leg.
It won't dry
in the humidity.
Roland, a word?
I'd love to know
where we are.
Making friends with Ahab?
Carter, I'm going
to the ladies' room.
Wait for me here. Okay?
It's not polite to
sneak up on people.
Carter! Where are you?
I got turned around in here.
Shit!
Carter, let me
hear from you!
Hey, Carter!
Carter!
Roland!
Okay, break's over.
Moving on!
Carry me.
I got it.
Carter.
Get off!
When did you last see him?
10, 15 minutes.
Come with me. And you.
If he's alive, we'll find him.
The rest of you
keep right on.
Ten minutes,
you'll reach the ridge.
Wait for us there.
No one tells
the little girl.
Right. Let's carry on.
Everybody up.
Come on. Up, up.
All right, guys, let's get
the hell out of here.
Come on.
Roland?
Did you find him?
Just the parts
they didn't like. Map.
The operations building
is right down in there
about a mile and a half from
the base of these cliffs.
How do you know that?
I've seen it.
The climb down
won't be easy.
We'll let them sleep
one more hour.
Then we hit it.
Oh, no.
What is that?
Kelly.
Stay down! Don't move!
Don't run!
Don't look,
just run! Run!
Bastard!
You son of a bitch!
He can't reach you!
Stay back!
He can't reach us!
No!
Oh, my God!
A snake! Help me!
Stay back!
It's okay.
It's coming back!
Dad!
Thank you.
Don't go
into the long grass!
Not into the long grass!
Move it.
Keep moving.
Move it!
Hey, hey!
Look at this.
What is it?
I think it's Ajay's bag.
Go, as fast as you can.
Go!
I see structures there.
They said the communications center
is in the operations building.
I'll get in there and send the radio call.
See you there.
Wait for us.
Every second counts.
If you can keep up,
you're welcome to try.
Okay, here we come.
No! Rest.
Oh, man.
Damn it!
Be there.
CQ, this is InGen Operations
Harvest Leader to Harvest Base.
Repeating, I'm calling for InGen
Operations Harvest Leader
seeking InGen Harvest Base.
Go ahead, Harvest Leader.
The operation has suffered
severe casualties.
The survivors are now
in mortal danger.
I need you to send
rescue immediately.
Our co-ordinates
here are
9 degrees 58 minutes north,
85 degrees...
Nick!
Nick Van Owen?
Here, here!
Inside! Anywhere!
Come inside!
Go.
Where do I go
when I'm out?
I'm right behind you...
Look out!
Watch out!
Up here!
Kelly, no!
Hey, you!
The school cut you
from the team?
Get out of here! Go!
Come on. Let's go!
Let's go!
What about
the other survivors?
Another
chopper's coming.
- It's okay.
- It's over now.
That's one souvenir they
won't be taking with them.
Find
the infant tyrannosaur.
Roland can show you
where the nest is.
I want it on my jet.
I'll take it directly to the
infirmary in San Diego.
Hurry. I want
to be airborne
before the female
knows we're here.
Roland?
You probably saved InGen.
We lost everything
we came after on this trip.
But this animal and its
infant will bail us out.
Congratulations.
You've got your trophy!
A buck only.
But it's alive!
Everyone will line up
and appreciate it and
what you did for us.
What's the matter?
He didn't make it. Ajay.
I'm sorry.
Really, I am.
I remember the people
who've helped me.
There's a job for you in
San Diego, if you want it.
No, thank you.
I've spent enough time
in the company of death.
Oh, my God.
Fifteen years ago,
John Hammond had a dream.
Like John himself,
the dream was grand.
It was outsized.
It was bold.
It was impractical.
It was not to be.
But half an hour from now,
John Hammond's dream,
re-imagined, will come true.
For.01 of the cost of
building a destination
resort thousands
of miles away...
Is this
the Ludlow affair?
It's private property.
We're on the list.
Turn around,
get back in your car.
This is Dr. Harding,
I'm Dr. Malcolm.
We have Mr. Ludlow's
test results.
There's good and bad news.
Tonight we will christen
Jurassic Park, San Diego,
with a mega-attraction that
will drive turnstile numbers
to rival any theme park
in the world.
I want to thank each
one of you for coming
in these wee small
hours of the morning.
The ship is here.
It's early?
You better come now.
It's so exciting!
See that couple?
Sir, you need
to look at this.
Let them see this up close.
Yes, sir.
Let me check.
I want a direct line to the
Coast Guard right now.
Look. That's their transponder
signal, Venture 5888.
They're coming in,
but I can't raise them.
Try again.
Skipper, SS Venture,
this is InGen
Harbor Master.
Do you copy? Over.
Skipper, SS Venture, you are approaching
the breakwater at flank speed.
Reduce at once. Over.
SS Venture,
reduce your speed at once.
SS Venture, this is
InGen Harbor Master.
You are entering
a docking area.
What's everybody
looking at?
We should've stayed
in the damn car.
You okay, Mr. Ludlow?
I don't know.
How do I look?
Go up this one.
Oh, my God.
Where's the crew?
All over the place.
I smell a fuel leak!
Check the cargo hold!
There may be crew
down there.
Everybody off the boat!
No! Get away from that!
Now you're John Hammond.
Why wasn't
it tranquilized?
It was, with two
darts of Carfentanil.
It was over 10 milligrams.
That'd put it
in a coma.
It stopped breathing.
We gave it naltrexone to counteract.
But we didn't know
how much.
You gave an antagonist
without knowing the dosage?
You put it in a narcoleptic state.
It's a locomotive now.
We're prepared here.
Any more dinosaurs
on the boat?
No, we brought the infant
back on the plane.
We had this
to tranquilize it.
Do you have
the infant?
It's safe.
Ian.
The animal's dehydrated.
First, it'll go to a water source
then look for the next
thing its body needs.
All the containment
equipment is here.
We got to get it
to the dock.
The boat might
be seaworthy.
I know what
you're gonna say.
When we brought the baby
to the trailer, it came.
There's no reason why it won't
do the same thing here.
Yep.
Where's the infant?
In a secured facility. Why?
Where's the facility?
There's a dinosaur
in our backyard.
Benjamin,
what are you doing?
What are you doing?
What?
Come on. There's a dinosaur
in our backyard.
The problem is,
you need to read to him.
No.
I will tell you
what it is.
You have to serve him dinner,
he won't be up all night.
It's the stupid fish tank!
He needs
a proper nightlight.
Put something over it!
It may as well be daytime.
Just turn it off.
Slow down. Slow it down!
There it is.
He's sedated.
Really heavily.
Give me a hand.
When the adult
sees us again
with his baby,
isn't he going to be like:
"You!"
There may be some
angry recognition.
Who knows?
He may be just happy to see us.
What the hell
are you doing?
We're taking the kid.
If you really want
to stop us, shoot us.
How will we find
the adult?
Follow the screams.
Get to the other
side of the bus!
There.
Oh, my God.
It's too drugged.
He won't know we have it
unless it makes some sound!
Wake up. Come on.
He knows.
Ian, slow down a little.
I don't think so.
This guy's
almost fully awake.
You know
where you're going?
Yeah, the waterfront's on the
other side of these warehouses.
Is there a way through?
God. There could be.
There we go.
You have to follow me now.
- Got him?
- Yep.
Here we go.
Ready?
Where's the Rex?
Is it behind us?
There's the water.
Shoot it.
Tell them to shoot it.
No, you idiot, the adult. Shoot the adult.
I want the baby back alive.
Dr. Malcolm!
What have you done with it?
I want that infant!
Are you there?
There you are.
Wait.
There's a first-rate shot
of the ship's deck
and the cargo hold that,
for the moment,
contains the animal itself,
presumably with the infant alongside.
By our calculations,
they should be nearing
the halfway
point of this trip.
Jim, can you
still hear me there?
- Yes, I can, Bernard.
- We are halfway to the island.
It is 206 nautical miles
from our present location.
The ship is moving
at 20 knots
which will put it in at about 11:30 a.
M., Eastern time.
One of the Navy's primary
concerns has been safety.
If we look at the ever-growing
escort around the ship
they're taking no chances of a
repeat of the San Diego incident.
Let's take a moment
to run the tape
of our interview earlier
today with John Hammond.
He's the former head
of InGen Bio-Engineering,
the man who is now
spearheading this movement
not only to return the
animals to their island
but to keep
the island itself intact.
It is
absolutely imperative
that we work
with the Costa Rican
Department of
Biological Preserves
to establish
a set of rules
for the preservation and
isolation of that island.
These creatures require
our absence to survive,
not our help.
And if we could
only step aside
and trust in nature
life will find a way.