Created and Encoded by --  Bokutox -- of  www.YIFY-TORRENTS.com. The Best 720p/1080p/3d movies with the lowest file size on the internet. World of Warcraft - Outland PVP (EU) - Torporr (name)
(WIND HOWLS)
- I'm gettin' somethin' on the sonar!
- MAN: What is it?
Strong reading from
underneath the cap rock, sir!
- Possible oil flow?
- Still analyzing.
(ELECTRONIC WARBLING)
It's...
Sounds like...
Tiny hammers.
Let's go skating!
(CHUCKLES)
(TOYS SQUEAKING)
(QUACKING)
(BEEPING)
- They're coming right at us!
- Take us to Elfcon 3!
Take us to Elfcon 3.
(ALARM SOUNDING)
(THUDDING)
(WHOOSHING)
These guys aren't stopping.
- Take us to Elfcon 2!
- Let's go to Elfcon 2.
We have a partridge in a pear tree.
You take us to Elfcon 1.
Let's rig for silent running.
- Look alive, everybody!
- Okay, we're at Elfcon 1.
(KLAXON BLARING)
(WHIRRING)
(ELECTRONIC BEEPING)
(SILENCE)
(SIGHS)
(AIRPLANE SOARING)
(ELECTRONIC WARBLING STOPS)
- I lost it!
- What do you mean, you lost it?
Wait!
What the...
Sir, you're gonna want to hear this.
(CHRISTMAS SONG PLAYING)
You better watch out
You better not cry
You better not pout
and I'm telling you why
Find out where
that music's coming from.
Okay.
(BEEPS)
Santa, I've got her on the locator.
He knows when you are sleeping
He knows when you're awake
He knows if you've been bad or good
So be good for goodness'...
Yeah, yeah, yeah
You better watch out
You better not cry
You better not pout
- And I'm telling you why
- Whoo!
- (HUMMING TUNE)
- Santa Claus is coming to...
(MUSIC STOPS)
- What now?
- It's just gone.
In the middle of the chorus!
MAN 1:
Nobody needs to know about this.
MAN 2: Maybe we should mention
the Smokey Robinson thing, sir.
ELF OVER TANNOY:
We're at Elfcon 4. All clear.
(ELVES CHEERING)
Curtis, what do you say we get
you headphones this Christmas?
It's all right, everybody.
Let's get back to work.
Curtis, you're 900 years old. Grow up!
- SANTA: Bernard.
- (SIGHS)
You know I didn't break any of the rules,
according to The Santa Handbook.
The handbook! Curtis, do you go
pee-pee with that thing?
It says elves are encouraged
to listen to music.
It makes them more creative,
more productive and more alert.
Look out!
(REINDEER BABBLES
WITH EXCITEMENT)
(TRIUMPHANT LAUGH)
- (REINDEER SCREAMING)
- (LOUD THUMP)
- It's okay.
- BOY: Let's go!
- Is he all right?
- ELF: He's okay, Santa.
Wow.
That's gonna leave a mark. Ooh.
Is that Blitzen? Looks like Prancer.
- Who is that?
- It was Chet.
A reindeer in training.
Oh. (SCOFFS)
Well, please tell me
that it's early in his training.
Wow! Nice fall.
Curtis, when are you gonna tell him?
Not now!
It's so cold up here.
How can you not be freezing?
You have not seen cold
till you see where my dad lives. It's...
Don't be embarrassed.
My parents are divorced.
- No big deal.
- I'm not embarrassed.
- Why don't you talk about your dad?
- He doesn't like me to.
- It's complicated.
- Is he a spy?
No, he...
He works with toys and these
little people. Kids.
Can we just do
what we came here to do?
Sure.
(SIGHS)
All right.
Charlie, this is really dangerous.
Someone could catch us
at any moment.
Kinda exciting.
Well, you know, Danielle,
I may not come out of this alive.
(CHUCKLES)
So, in case
we don't see each other again...
Whoa! (SCREAMING)
(PANTING)
(SIGHS IN RELIEF)
Are you okay?
Whew!
(SPRAY PAINTING)
(CHRISTMAS SONG PLAYING)
- Almost done.
- Okay. I'm not leaving.
I've been a naughty boy
I didn't get a toy
Santa Claus left nothing
Underneath my tree
He knows that I've been bad
But being good just ain't my bag...
(MUSIC STOPS)
(FOOTSTEPS)
Hello, Charlie.
Hello, Principal Newman.
(BOLT TIGHTENING)
SANTA: Okay, try it now.
(ENGINE REVS)
(ELVES CHEERING)
Okay, all right. Here's what we need.
Get one more bolt on that flange,
and it's ready for Christmas.
Good work, guys. Whew!
Perfect job on suspension, you guys.
Thinkin' outside the box. I love it.
- Do you want a cookie, Santa?
- Do I want a cookie?
Yes! What's fresh?
Ooh!
Sweet, just like you.
Alexander, let's think.
Take the hat off.
Too much counterweight.
Thanks, Santa. You're the man.
That's why they give me the big belly,
so I don't fall over! (CACKLES)
Hey, Joey!
How's that static-free tinsel coming?
Hey, guys, Santa wants
to see the new tinsel.
(ALL LAUGHING)
I could come up there
and take care of this the ugly way.
Or we go outside
and play some football.
(CHEERING)
Curtis, you need to tell him right now!
I don't know. He's so happy right now.
And why do I have to be the one
to tell him?
Because I'm the head elf.
I don't give bad news.
It's one of the perks of my seniority.
Now, tell him!
Come on, pork chop. Bring it on.
Who you callin' pork chop, meatloaf?
Meatloaf?
You wanna talk some trash?
I'll talk trash with ya.
- But first, I'm gonna blitz.
- Ready, set!
- I'm comin' after you, buddy.
- Seven swans a-swimming!
Six geese a-laying!
ALL: Five golden rings!
Hike!
Hey, who's got the ball?
I can see it. Let go of me.
He's too quick! He spins!
He moves! He's on the way!
And he might go all the
way! Whoo!
Rumblin', stumblin', bumblin'!
SANTA: They pile on! (GROANS)
Okay, you win!
(GROANS)
You guys aren't elves. You're wizards!
No matter how many times you run
that play, I never see it comin'.
Santa? We need to talk.
(TRAIN WHISTLE BLOWING)
- That's weird, isn't it?
- BOTH: Uh-oh.
- These fit yesterday.
- Hot cocoa for you.
This is not a good time, Abby.
I sent Dasher down
for some Brazilian cocoa beans.
- What's the bad news?
- What do you mean?
Whenever you play the designer
bean card, you have bad news.
What are you doing
with the naughty-and-nice list?
Don't shoot the messenger.
- It's Charlie.
- Sheen?
- I thought he straightened out.
- Not that Charlie.
My Charlie. My son Charlie?
He's on the naughty list?
(SHRIEKING)
- There's gotta be a mistake.
- We don't make mistakes.
I'm sorry, Santa. Please excuse me.
How could this happen?
Is this what you were trying to tell me?
Great! You told him!
Let's get you dressed for that meeting.
I can't have the meeting here.
I'm gonna have to see Charlie.
- Number two, tell him now.
- Tell me what, guys? Come clean.
- Santa, there's a clause.
- That would be me.
No, I mean there's another
Santa clause.
Curtis, in case you haven't noticed,
this time of year,
the malls are filled
with other "Santa Clauses."
Yes, but there's another Santa clause.
There was a first clause,
but also a second clause.
BOTH: Get on with it!
When the last Santa fell off your roof
and you put on his coat, you found this.
Right. "He who wears the coat
"takes on the responsibilities
of Santa Claus."
And the rest would be history, right?
But it seems our number two elf,
the keeper of the handbook,
overlooked the single
most important detail
in the history of Christmas!
Wow.
One mistake in 900 years.
Look.
- I can't see that.
- Better now?
- Or now?
- Well...
- Better now?
- It's gettin' there.
- Or now?
- I can't see anything.
I see. Good, good, good. I see it. Okay.
"The card holder acknowledges
a woman of his choosing...
"True love...
Not valid in the state of Utah...
"Holy...
"Matrimony"?
- I gotta get married!
- Yes.
It's the Mrs. Clause.
(SCATTING WEDDING SONG)
What if I don't want to get married?
Oh, dear. The de-Santification
process has begun!
The de-Santification?
Are you telling me that clause
says if I don't get married,
I don't get to be Santa anymore?
(SIGHS)
What about the kids?
What about the elves?
- What about you guys?
- It's not completely hopeless.
You still have time to find a wife.
- How much time do I have?
- 28 days.
28 days? So I've gotta find
a wife by Christmas.
Actually, Christmas Eve.
- I guess it's over.
- No! You can't think that way!
Please, don't give up hope.
'Cause if you do, then we have to.
(BOTH SIGHING)
- (BOTH SHRIEKING)
- Whoa!
Christmas is getting very complicated.
MOTHER NATURE: (FAINTLY) Santa?
Santa?
- Are you with us?
- I'm sorry, yes. Yes, I am.
Well, on behalf of Father Time and
the Council of Legendary Figures,
I'd like to thank you
for being such a gracious host.
- Hear, hear.
- What a lovely place.
Without further ado, let us convene
the year-end conference.
(BANGS GAVEL)
- Tooth Fairy.
- Thank you, Mother Nature.
Fellow council members,
I'd like to again propose
a new name for myself.
- Oh, please!
- Good heavens!
In the past, you have rejected
Tooth Man, Tooth Guy and Tooth.
- Because they stunk.
- Today, I'd like to submit
- Captain Floss.
- Nice!
- Plaque Man.
- (SNORTS)
- And Roy.
- (LAUGHS) Roy! No.
No kid's gonna put a tooth
under a pillow for a man named Roy.
This from someone in a diaper
who shoots people's butts!
Wait a minute. I got it. I got it. I got it.
Now, how about this? The Molarnator.
The Molarnator! I like it.
Thank you, Santa.
Can we vote now on the Molarnator?
All in favor of a name change
for Tooth Fairy?
All right. And all opposed?
Easter Bunny?
- Sandman?
- (SNORING) What...
What happened? Was I asleep again?
Name change for the Tooth Fairy.
Yes or no?
No. I'm sorry.
All right. Next item on the agenda.
Santa? Status report.
Okay. First, welcome to the North Pole.
Great to have you here.
This is our big time of year,
so things are busy as usual.
There's a little speed bump
in the road this year.
- You all know Charlie.
- Oh! I love Charlie!
- Great kid.
- Good boy.
- Sweet kid.
- Good teeth.
Well, Charlie got himself
on the naughty list.
- What?
- Oh, my!
I'm struggling with the timing,
'cause it's...
I gotta be up here and
I've also got to take care of Charlie...
That's every parent's dilemma,
how to balance work and children.
Most people lose sleep over that.
Tell me about it! I have 33,000
offspring. All in private school.
Well, to top it off,
I have to get married by Christmas Eve.
- What?
- Otherwise I stop being Santa.
- No!
The de-Santification process
has already begun.
Wait a minute.
You do look thinner, and...
- Your beard is shorter! Right?
- ALL: You're right!
Apparently, it's called the Mrs. Clause.
Don't mess with me, Santa.
I'm pre-El Niño.
No, I'm not messing with anybody.
What I'm saying is,
I have to find a wife in...
27 days, 20 hours and 17 minutes.
Wow.
It's what I do.
(CHUCKLES)
Wait a minute. Cupid!
Cupid, come over here.
- What do you need?
- Shoot me with a dart.
- Then I'll fall in love.
- First of all, they're arrows.
Second of all, no can do.
- Why not?
- Arrows have no effect on us.
If they did, I would have shot myself,
met a nice girl,
left the business years ago.
- Enough with the questions.
- You can't stop being Santa.
I don't want to.
Kids are 86% happier
since you've taken the job.
- He's right.
- SANTA: This is all I want to do.
But what am I gonna do?
Well, you...
You can't be two places at once.
Maybe you can be.
Okay, everyone, can I get the room
for a minute? Thank you.
Can I just... One minute.
Take a cocoa break.
Have a nice long break.
Relax, everyone.
I want to show Santa
some improvements on the pantograph.
Thanks. Walk with me.
I've tripled the RAM
and reconfigured the circuitry.
I see you've externalized
the power source
to make better use
of the electromagnetic energy.
No, it's just there
'cause it looks really cool.
Yeah, it does. (CHUCKLES)
Wait a minute. You tripled the RAM.
I see where this is going.
I am not getting in that machine.
Besides, creating a copy of Santa
won't solve our problems.
- The elves'll know.
- But this would be a special toy!
- How's that, Curtis?
- I added a fuzzy logic circuit.
The duplicate will look
and think just like you.
When you're with your family,
dealing with Charlie, looking for a wife...
The toy will be up here melting
in front of my fireplace.
No, the toy Santa will be dealing
with business up here.
I can deal with business up here.
Santa, if the elves find out
we've made a switch... (GASPS)
No! No! This machine is not the answer.
(CLATTERING)
(MOUSE SQUEAKING)
Hey! Hey! Hey! You! You! Shoo!
(DEVICE POWERS UP)
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
(ENGINE POWERS DOWN)
(SQUEAKING)
Look, you can't get
much better than that.
And I promise, it won't hurt a bit.
- I'm goin' in.
- Oh, I can't watch this!
(WHIRRING)
(DEVICE POWERS UP)
(ELECTRICITY CRACKLING)
SANTA: Ow! Ow!
It's perfect!
That's because it's me, Einstein.
- Santa, are you all right?
- Yeah, I got a shock in there.
Is there supposed to be a shock?
(BOTH SCREAMING)
ALL: It's naked!
Throw something over it.
- It's incredible!
- Yes, it is.
(SANTA CHUCKLES)
Can he talk?
Hello?
(GABBLES)
Ho, ho, ho!
- Not bad.
- Not bad yourself.
(CHUCKLES)
I can't put my finger on it,
but there's something
about you that I like.
There's something about you that I like!
Hah.
Watch him. I'll be right back.
He's coming right back.
(CHUCKLES)
Ha-ha-ha!
- Bernard, I need your help.
- What do you mean?
What I mean is I gotta go see Charlie,
and I want you to convince the elves
that toy Santa is me.
- Hmm. Have you seen that thing?
- I've seen it.
Keep the elves at a distance and say
that I've changed my look, it'll work.
Oh, Santa, we're in way over
our heads here.
If anybody can do this,
it's you, number one.
I'm not gonna lie to all the elves.
I myself think he looks
absolutely terrific!
Better and fresher somehow
than he has in years.
There's now a more supple veneer
to his skin
and an added luster
to the thickness of his hair.
You could almost say there's a...
A toy-like quality to him.
Most importantly,
he's very happy with his new look,
and I would caution you all
not to point or stare
or use the word "plastic."
Okay? Okay.
Thank you. That's all.
Back to work, please.
(EXHALES)
(IRRITABLE GRUMBLING)
Comet, because I don't want
to take Prancer.
I want to take a trip with you.
When's the last time we had a cruise?
- I love you, buddy.
- (WHINES)
Besides, Prancer had too many apples.
We know what that means.
Before you go,
take a look at your watch.
Hey! Can't go anywhere without that.
- I've done some work on it.
- It's beautiful. It really is.
- You like it?
- The workmanship's fabulous.
It has a power reserve that measures
how much magic you have left.
- It's at 10.
- That should be enough.
But if you use up any magic
for any reason, the level drops.
Santa, if it gets to zero,
you won't be able to return to the Pole.
Uh-oh.
Then let's not let it get to zero!
- Now, look at me.
- Mmm-hmm.
What's the most important thing?
For you not to touch Santa?
For you to come back! (LAUGHING)
(COMET GRUMBLES)
Thank you.
Comet, please
just chill out a little bit, okay?
Come on! It's not like
we're pullin' the sleigh. Right?
There's no packages. It's one stop.
And I think I might have forgot
we're gonna go see Charlie.
(SCHOOL BELL RINGING)
Scott! Hey! You trimmed your beard.
Yeah.
Come here, big guy.
(CHUCKLING)
Whoa. Lost some weight there, huh?
Slim-Fast?
You don't know how fast.
- We should get going.
- Oh, okay.
How do you always know
when there's a problem?
I see you when you're sleepin'.
I know when you're awake.
Which is a pretty frightening concept
when you think about it.
We're really worried about Charlie.
He keeps upping the ante.
This time he defaced school property.
- It's classic acting out.
- I'm blaming myself for this.
- We're both his parents.
- Where is he?
He's waiting for us
in Principal Newman's office.
Something about her makes me
want to deface public property.
Hello, Mr. Calvin. Laura, Neil.
- BOTH: Miss Newman.
- Principal Newman.
Haven't seen you since
the last time Charlie was in trouble.
I've been traveling for work.
Oh. If you spent more time with your
son, there'd be fewer problems.
Then I wouldn't spend
so much time with you,
- which is always such a pleasure.
- Oh.
A battle of wits. It's a shame
you come unarmed. Excuse me.
Ouch.
Good morning, Principal Newman.
Mr. Picardo, I want you to look
into my eyes. What do you see?
It's dark. And it's cold.
It's your future, Mr. Picardo.
Keep this up
and you will spend your life
stabbing trash.
- Do I make myself clear?
- Yes.
- So what are you gonna do?
- I'm going to geometry.
Have a nice trip.
(SIGHS)
It's an affront to authority
and blatant disrespect for property.
If this continues, I'll have no other
recourse than to suspend...
Excuse me. Is there a rest stop between
here and the end of the lecture?
I'm more interested in why
this happened in the first place.
So am I.
Charlie, we're all worried about you.
It feels like you're trying
to get someone's attention.
What's bothering you?
- Dr. Miller?
- Neil.
- Neil, any theories?
- Well, frankly, I have several.
Here we go. Let's just order a pizza.
- Scott, you're not helping.
- Ugh!
I was listening to a tape series
on child development last night.
You know what the problem is?
Excuse me, Neil.
It's four weeks until Christmas.
- That's a holiday in December.
- Oh.
Have you noticed the hallways?
Not a decoration, not a twinkle light,
not an expression of the joy
kids are supposed to be feeling.
- What kind of school is this?
- A public school.
A top-rated public school.
That takes effort. And money.
Spending any of that money
on holiday decorations
would take away
from the things that truly matter.
Forgive me, but I think
holiday cheer really matters.
What are we going to do?
We are worried...
Let me handle this.
You know what you did is wrong. Right?
- I guess so.
- There's no guessing.
Guessing is gone.
It was wrong what you did.
And you're not gonna do it again.
Promise me.
- Okay.
- There you go.
He won't do it again.
Meeting is adjourned.
It most certainly is not! Charlie...
You know what else?
Here's a little donation.
Why don't you buy yourself a wreath?
I am Santa Claus. Boo! (LAUGHS)
Yeah. No, no,
I think that this is gonna work.
Good job, Curtis.
Would it kill you
to give a wholehearted compliment?
Ho, ho, ho.
- Ho, ho, ho.
- Santa?
- I need you to look at this.
- All right!
Nice!
No. I mean, I need you to read it.
Well, let's try to be specific, shall we?
I'll take a look at it over at my desk.
- How does he know where it is?
- I programed him that way.
He has most of Santa's memories.
Okay, we need you to study
everything that's in that book
because it is the key to being Santa.
Right! I'll memorize everything
in the book.
I'll follow all the rules.
'Cause rules are very important!
- I like this guy.
- I can barely read this.
Hi, Santa.
- Hi.
- Oh. You look...
Like he got a good night's sleep.
Like you got a very good night's sleep.
How about a nice chocolatey cocoa?
- Careful, it's hot.
- Of course it is.
(GULPING)
Ah!
Whoa!
That's delicious! I like cocoa!
Cocoa's superior refreshment!
(LAUGHS)
Get me some more cocoa! Whoo!
Right away, Santa.
Oh! Whoa!
I think Santa feels a little buzz!
Whoo!
Let me get this straight.
You were de-Santified?
And you only have 27 days
to find a wife or you're out?
Yeah.
What are you gonna do?
We dated for three years
before you got up the courage
to propose.
That's a pretty serious
commitment issue, isn't it?
Yes, Sigmund.
I was afraid I'd mess up the first time.
- I'm more afraid now.
- Dad, you can't give up.
There's never been a better Santa.
I appreciate that.
It's for the best.
If I had spent more time with you,
you'd spend less time
in the spray paint industry.
Don't do that to yourself.
You have been a great dad.
And being Santa has made you
an even better man.
I'm gonna go out on an emotional limb.
Don't try to make me cry.
Believe it or not,
you have a great capacity for love.
I know you can find someone wonderful
to spend the rest of your life with.
Don't let the facts that you
have no time, no prospects
and a paralyzing fear
of intimacy get you down.
Hmm.
Have you ever helped anyone? Ever?
You know what I'm gonna do?
I am gonna look through my phone book
and see who's still single out there
and not too bitter.
There's divorced moms at school
who'll go out with anybody.
As promising as this sounds,
I don't need help with this area.
Your old man was a high-school legend.
A double letterman.
I had a Mustang.
So as far as dating goes,
I think if anybody can stir up
the old mojo, it would be moi.
Come on! I don't think
there's a woman out there
that doesn't want a piece of this.
- LUCY: Hi, Mom!
- Lucy!
- Uncle Scott!
- How's my little sweet pea?
Oh, I haven't seen you in a long time.
- Tell me what's been happenin'.
- I learned to swim underwater.
- And I'm not afraid!
- That's amazing!
Maybe we'll have to go to the mall
and get some ice cream.
(GASPS)
- Plenty of women at the mall.
- Charlie!
BERNARD: Santa, look forward
and put on a smiley face.
Say hello to your elves.
Ho, ho, ho!
You're doing a wonderful job!
Santa, when you said the bigger
wheels, is this what you meant?
Ho, ho, ho!
You're doing a wonderful job!
You're doing great.
Dial it down on the ho-ho-ho's,
but otherwise, you're gold.
Ho, ho, ho!
Ho, ho, ho, ho, ho, ho!
Why don't you just say it?
"You were right, Curtis. I was wrong."
Okay, okay, I admit it.
They're happy. They're working hard.
Everything's going to be fine.
This book is very interesting reading.
There's a lot of rules
they're not following.
That's what I've been saying all along.
Things have gotten a little too sloppy
around here.
Yes! Sloppiness means mistakes.
Mistakes aren't a good thing!
I might have to make
some changes here.
- What do you have in mind?
- Let me show you.
There's many things. Look here...
Neil, are you sure you don't have
any other clothes I can borrow?
I mean, the idea tonight
is to attract a woman.
- What are you talking about?
- I look like a limesicle.
I think it makes you look hot.
What do you think, Laura?
Honestly, what do you think? Huh?
Doesn't he look hot, Laura?
I think it's what's inside
that really counts.
- Thought you liked the sweater.
- We'll talk later.
I'm off. I may need to borrow a car.
I'm parked behind Neil.
The minivan, I just had it washed.
The minivan.
Okay, then. Well, wish me luck.
I got a needlepoint sweater
and a minivan.
(SIGHS)
See ya in about eight minutes.
(INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS)
Scott? Hey.
- Tracy!
- Yes!
- It's nice to meet you.
- Nice to meet you.
- Here, why don't you sit down?
- Oh, thank you.
Thank you very much. (CHUCKLES)
(SIGHS)
So, I'm so glad we finally got to do this.
- I'm pretty nervous.
- Oh. Are you? (LAUGHS)
Laura says we have a lot in common.
I hear that you love
this time of year also?
It's my favorite time of year
and my busiest time of year.
- Whoa. Look at the sweater!
- Yeah! (LAUGHS)
Some sweater. Like I should talk!
(CHUCKLES)
I also have my Christmas
charm bracelet.
- That's beautiful. Look at 'em!
- Yeah.
I wear it all year long
just to keep the spirit alive.
That's gorgeous. A little teddy bear
and packages. That's very nice.
- So what work do you do?
- I'm in the toy business.
- No way!
- Way!
(BOTH LAUGHING)
- That sounds so creative.
- I love it.
- I love creative people.
- Yeah?
Yeah.
So what do you do?
I'm hoping someday to break
into the music business.
- As a singer-songwriter.
- No way!
Way!
(BOTH LAUGHING)
- What's your favorite music?
- Country-western.
- (ENTHUSIASTICALLY) Oh!
- Yeah.
- Do you like Shania Twain?
- Yeah!
(SINGING) The best thing about
singing at Christmas
Is the cocoa, caroling and fun
- You know that one?
- I know that song.
Whoah-oh-oh!
Go totally yuletide
Takin' a sleigh ride
You're good.
Santa shirts, reindeer skirts
Whoah-oh-oh!
Hey!
(OFF-KEY) Watchin' the windows fog
drinkin' some eggnog
That's good.
Whoah-oh-oh!
Fill up a stocking
Spray on some flocking
(SHOUTS) Put up a tree! Sports on TV!
(NASALLY) Uh, whoah-oh-oh
I want to be free
yeah, to feel the way I feel
Ah, ah, ah, ah
Man!
I feel like some Christmas
Oh-oh, wow wow wow!
(WHISTLES)
Whew!
You hated it?
It kind of scared me a little bit.
No, I just. I...
I just... I wasn't prepared
for a performance, so if I...
I put myself out and that was
not an easy thing to do.
If you can't support a woman's ambition,
then I don't think there's any reason
to continue this date.
(KNOCK ON DOOR)
- Dad?
- Hey, sport.
How'd it go?
Well...
Let's just say
I'm not bookin' a church yet.
(CHUCKLES)
Boy, I'll tell ya,
women are hard to figure out.
- Tell me about it.
- You too, huh? Girl trouble?
- Well, there's this one girl.
- Mmm.
We just used to be friends
and hang out at the mall and stuff.
Then one day, I looked at her,
and I got this weird feeling
in the pit of my stomach.
I started worrying about what to wear
and what my hair looked like.
- And then I wanted to kiss her.
- (GASPS)
How did she do that?
I don't know. But they all can do that.
Look at that. The snow globe!
This is so beautiful. I remember
when Bernard gave this to you.
He said all I have to do
to see you is shake it.
Now, all you have to do
is yell down the hall.
And I'm there whenever you need me.
Yeah.
I'm a little tired, Dad.
I'll see you in the morning.
Okay.
- Good night.
- Night.
Can you turn the light off, please?
Yeah, 'cause
it's such a big reach for you!
(GRUMBLING)
What do you mean it's not straight?
(GABBLES)
- Sure, it's straight.
- Uh-uh.
Maybe your head's crooked.
(GABBLES)
- Prancer's not this picky.
- COMET: Yes, he is.
- Hi, Comet.
- Hi!
I've got something for you.
Hey, Lucy, what have you got there?
Careful with the sweets.
He tends to overeat.
Uncle Scott, are you Santa Claus?
What? Why would you ask me
something like that?
'Cause you have a reindeer,
and only Santa has reindeer.
Nonsense.
A lot of people have reindeer.
Name five.
(CHUCKLES)
Well, most of them live in Finland.
I can't pronounce their names.
Besides, reindeer are too stupid
to make good pets.
Well, I think you're very smart.
(GIGGLING)
Well, I think he's learning
at an excellent rate.
Oh, really? This morning he ate
a bowl of waxed fruit.
Wait a minute.
I need the naughty-and-nice list.
No.
It says I'm supposed to check it twice.
- Santa already checked it.
- No, I didn't.
- The real Santa.
- I am the real Santa!
- I'm sorry?
- I'm in charge here.
- What?
- I check the list twice.
That's the rule. I like the rules.
- You know how I feel.
- You're misunderstanding.
No, I'm the rule-maker.
I like the rules. Santa likes rules.
I've got a good idea.
How about we have some fun?
Huh?
- It's good to have fun.
- Right.
Santa, look over there.
See those elves?
Go ahead. Go play some tinsel football.
Break!
- What's the object of tinsel football?
- Come on down.
If you don't have the ball, get it.
If you have the ball, run to the end zone.
Okay, I'll go get the football.
Ready, hike!
(BLOODCURDLING CRY)
I've got the ball. What are you
gonna do? Who's gonna stop me?
Come on!
This is a lot of fun!
(GROANING)
Oh, so sorry! (LAUGHS)
(PLASTICKY SQUEAKING)
Come here! Stop!
Slow down when I'm talking to you!
Come here, you! Come on. (YELLS)
He's headed east
toward the main entrance!
Hello, Charlie.
(PANTING)
- Hello, Principal Newman.
- (SCHOOL BELL RINGING)
CAROL:
Are Laura and Neil on their way?
No, I volunteered to go solo.
You look...
You've lost weight. Feeling all right?
I was until I got this phone call.
Charlie, you promised
you weren't gonna do this again.
What's the matter with you?
I'm gonna have to punish ya.
I'll ground him for two months.
- I thought you were on my side!
- I'll go one better.
- You're suspended.
- But, Dad!
I'm as upset about this as you,
but isn't there a punishment
that doesn't mean
takin' him out of school?
- What did you have in mind?
- We could...
(STUTTERING)
Community service?
Hah.
That's not a bad idea.
Okay, Charlie. I want you
to start by cleaning up this wall.
I want everything off of there by tonight.
And then clean off every mark
off every locker in this hallway.
- Every one?
- Do as she says, Charlie.
But I have homework, tests to study for.
Not my problem.
I have a detention group on Saturday.
So we will all get together
at the rec center
and scrape off graffiti at 8:00 a.m.
- See you both there.
- You say both of us?
(LAUGHS) No, I'm very busy.
I do a lot of other community service.
That's good. You just got
yourself elected parent rep.
And, Charlie,
we'll talk about the suspension.
(SIGHS)
Curtis, what is he doing
in the naughty-and-nice center?
- What's going on?
- I'm checking the naughty-nice list.
- I'm checking it twice.
- I already told you!
It's been checked. Don't worry.
I do worry. There's a lot of mistakes.
I'll give you a big fat for instance!
In Denmark, there's a guy
named Sven Halstrom right here.
He's a Dane. He was wiping
his nose on his sister's shirt.
Yuk! That's not very nice!
And yet, he's on the nice list.
We try to cut most children
slack this time of year.
I don't understand that!
Kids are misbehaving everywhere.
They're running with scissors.
They're sticky.
"I'm not gonna stop this car!"
"No, we're not there yet!"
"Brush your teeth!"
"Pick up those clothes!"
It goes on and on.
But they're just kids!
Everybody misbehaves some time.
But according to The Santa Handbook,
naughty kids get lumps of coal
in their stockings. Right?
We will make stockings.
In my opinion, they should all
get coal in their stockings.
- Don't you?
- No! That's not how it works!
Get me the naughty-nice list.
Get me every list!
Get me everything.
(RAP SONG PLAYING)
Mr. O'Reilly, Mr. Leary.
You in charge of the gangbangers?
They're students, actually, and yes.
Keep 'em away from the car. It's new.
I don't need some delinquent
kids scratchin' it up.
They're not delinquents.
And don't worry about your car.
I'd worry about your legs
in those shorts.
I thought only swimmers
shaved their legs!
- Good morning.
- Brought you coffee.
- Thank you.
- So you have a nice-guy side.
- I'm a man of many sides.
I'm a puzzle.
I'm a Rubik's Cube with pants.
- (LAUGHS)
- A laugh! Actual laugh.
- Dad, it doesn't come off.
- It's not supposed to come off.
Hence, you've got to be careful
where you put it.
Hence, tagging is serious.
Hence, your presence here.
Don't say "hence" anymore, Dad.
It's really annoying.
(SCHOOL BELL RINGING)
Nicely done!
How do you do it? I have trouble
with one. You have hundreds.
- Hi.
- I was really good this year.
- (CHUCKLES)
Is that so? Are you absolutely
sure about that, Pamela?
I want a doll house
and a swimming pool.
A swimming pool?
I'm sorry. She insisted on talking to you.
- It's not a problem.
- Okay.
I'll tell you what. If you can
promise me you'll be good,
I can guarantee
you'll have a great Christmas.
- Okay! Yeah!
- (LAUGHS) Come on.
Kids get so nutty this time of year.
- Is she a neighbor?
- No.
How did you know her name?
The necklace, it said Pamela on it.
Oh. I guess I missed that.
I'm gonna go check on this group.
You cost me, Pamela.
I just couldn't sleep
thinking about all those rules.
Am I wrong? Am I right? Does it matter?
Couldn't have been
the three gallons of cocoa I had!
But you understand rules, don't you?
You're highly decorated.
And look at that face. There you go.
There's a face only a mom would like.
I don't have a mom,
so I wouldn't know about that.
Now, it's time for the big event.
Guess what?
Son, it's showtime!
You're in the spotlight.
Get bigger with it.
It's your big chance. I need a little help.
I need a little muscle.
I need a little nudge.
Let's call yourself the little nudge!
This won't hurt, except
for the electric shock through you.
See ya on the other side!
- Oh. Hi.
- Hi.
It looks like you're going out.
Sorry. I should have called.
No, it's okay. Come in.
- You sure?
- Uh-huh.
- Is there a problem?
- No, no. I just...
I wondered if...
If you would... (STAMMERS)
Do you want to go get some noodles?
Or pie?
But I don't want to
keep you from your date, so...
Oh, it's not a date.
It's the faculty Christmas party.
Oh.
Is that your idea of a night on the town?
Noodles and pie? (GIGGLES)
- Yes. What would be your idea?
- Pizza and a movie.
- Thick or thin crust?
- Thin.
Good! Movie?
Two for the Road.
Audrey Hepburn, Albert Finney.
Movie's okay, but the car was the star.
'53 MG TD.
Racing green, wire wheels. Beautiful.
I'm impressed. That is a great car.
My favorite car.
Didn't like driving 'em in the rain.
You have to push it to start it.
Other than that, it's perfect.
It's perfect, though.
- I could drive you to your party.
- That would be great.
Except for, eventually,
I'm going to have to get home.
Well, I could pick you up.
So you're going to drop me off,
then come back and pick me up?
- Yeah.
- Why don't you just stay?
- All right, I'll stay.
- I'll get my coat.
So, Mr. Andretti, what are you driving?
You know, I think you're gonna like it.
(LAUGHS)
(HOOVES CLOPPING)
CAROL:
Mind if I ask you something personal?
Please.
- You look really different.
- The weight.
It's Indian teas and
it's a lot of salves and stuff. It's...
- Do you want some cocoa?
- Yes.
Cocoa. You have thought of everything.
Well, this time of year, I really shine.
Yeah, I can't wait till it's over, though.
Streets are crowded,
the malls are jammed,
people max out their credit cards...
It's noisy.
When did you become such a cynic?
Oh.
I don't know.
I used to love Christmas, too.
It was the only day
that my parents didn't fight.
- Oh.
They were at each other all the time.
But on Christmas,
they tried to make the holiday special.
My dad went through this charade
so I'd believe in Santa Claus.
He put a cot by the fireplace
so Santa could take a nap...
Like he has time to take a nap!
Consider the amount of gifts
he would have to deliver.
Why would he nap?
He would probably need some coffee.
Yeah. And there was cocoa
and cookies.
And carrots for the reindeer.
That's a good gesture.
The reindeer love carrots.
And the thought
is important to them, too.
Yeah. And I'd wake up, and the cocoa
and cookies would be gone,
and the cot would be mussed
and the carrots gnawed.
They swallow them.
If they're fresh, they'll eat 'em like that.
They love red bell peppers, too.
You know the stories. If you read...
(LAUGHING)
And there would be incredible presents
under the tree.
One year was a rocking horse,
and I named it Harvey.
And the next year
was a little red wagon,
which I made a lemonade stand,
which was great.
And the last year was...
It was just a Baby Doll.
She was pink and soft and beautiful.
- Beautiful?
- Yes.
I believed in Santa so much
I'd get in fights at school
with kids who tried to tell me
that he didn't exist.
And one day,
I came home with a bloody nose.
That's when my parents
decided to tell me to
grow up.
I was devastated.
Good, Carol! This is great
sleigh-riding conversation!
- I'm a terrible sleigh-riding...
- It's fine conversation.
A person just wants something
to believe in, you know?
Yes, I know. Yes, I know.
Okay, we have cocoa.
We have a blanket.
We have a horse-drawn sleigh.
The only thing that's...
- What?
- (LAUGHS)
- It's snowing.
- Oh.
As if by magic.
That's what I was gonna say,
that it should be snowing!
(DELIGHTED LAUGH)
It's been a blue
Holiday
Since you've been gone
Oh, my darling
Won't you
Hurry, hurry home
It's been a blue
Holiday
I owe you one.
It's a great party.
Look. That guy moved.
- Would you excuse me?
- Mmm-hmm.
(SONG CONTINUES PLAYING)
(FEEDBACK)
(ALL MURMURING)
Could I have your attention?
Your attention, please!
There we go. Hi. I'm Scott Calvin
and I just thought I'd step up here and...
And say the word that
we've all been longing to hear.
Fire!
Okay. What I think, folks,
is that a lot of you have forgotten
what the true spirit
of Christmas is all about.
If you're not willing
to dance or laugh or flirt
or risk the buffet,
I don't think we have much choice.
So before the choir gets out here,
I say we rock this house
- with a secret Santa! Huh?
- Oh.
Carol, happy, happy Christmas!
I think they're just decorations
for the carolers.
Ah.
She's afraid these are decorations
for the caroling.
I think Carol is right about the caroling!
I'm talking about the packages that
(WHISPERS) are backstage.
There aren't any packages backstage.
Oh, there's none back there.
(SIGHS) So I was mistaken
when I saw this bag of gifts.
Maybe I'm wrong, but it sure
looks like a bag of gifts.
Oh, it's heavy like a bag of gifts.
Look at this! What's in here?
It's very heavy, very heavy.
John Pierce.
Doesn't your mom call you JJ?
Merry Christmas, JJ.
No way.
This is Toss Across!
I used to love this when I was a kid!
But I never told anybody.
Where did... Who did this?
Grace Kim.
Yes, there you are! Merry Christmas.
- Thank you.
- Tom Astle.
- Me! Sorry, Gordon.
- Hey!
- Haven't changed a bit!
- Gee, thanks.
- Lizzy Garcia.
- Here.
- There. Merry Christmas.
- Rock 'Em Sock 'Em Robots!
Mint condition! This is incredible!
The Holly Hobbie Oven!
Come on up
and get the rest of your presents.
(CLAMORING)
- Marie?
- Here!
There she is. Katie. Jerry.
- Cory. Cory?
Here!
(CHRISTMAS SONG PLAYING)
(EXCLAIMS)
(LAUGHING)
(WOMEN LAUGHING)
(ALL EXCLAIMING)
Oh!
- Carl, you need a net.
- Not me!
This is great. (LAUGHS)
Hey, party animal, you want to play?
- I can't figure it out.
- It's beanbag tic-tac-toe.
No, I mean the secret Santa thing.
Someone tracked down
all those wonderful antique toys.
Probably someone who knows
his way around eBay.
- Yeah.
- Yep.
It was you. I know it was you.
I just can't figure out...
How did you do it?
Sometimes you don't need
to know all the answers.
Speaking of which...
Even the principal
needs a Christmas gift.
Merry Christmas.
Come on, open it. Rip it open.
Come on.
We're not gonna save the paper.
It's Baby Doll.
(VOICE BREAKS) Come here.
CAROL: Did you call the office?
SCOTT: No.
- Did they call you?
- It's not like that.
- Did you investigate us? (LAUGHS)
- No, I wouldn't do that.
Did you... I told you about
Baby Doll an hour ago and...
Did you send someone to...
- No.
Well... I don't know how you did it.
It's like some kind of magic.
Yeah, sort of like some kind of magic.
And pretty much the last that I have.
What? Well, what... You know what?
(CHUCKLING)
I don't want to know.
What you did in there tonight
for everyone was wonderful.
Thank you.
I'm sorry.
I shouldn't have done that.
- Is that okay?
- Yeah.
Got this weird feeling
in the pit of my stomach.
I'm...
I'm not real good at this.
Where did that come from?
I don't know.
Hi! Merry Christmas!
Ho, ho, ho!
(MACHINES STOP)
Can I have your attention?
Stop the work, please.
Everybody, stop the work.
- Merry Christmas!
- (QUACKS)
That's nice. I have a little
announcement to make.
From this moment forward,
we're not gonna make any more toys.
(ALL MURMURING)
The children of the world
don't deserve presents.
They're running rampant
with naughtiness.
This Christmas, we're gonna
give those greedy kids
exactly what they deserve.
A beautiful, high-quality
yet low-sulfur variety of coal!
(UPROAR)
Quiet!
We have to focus,
all of us, on the goals ahead.
And just to make sure
that that happens...
Thank you, sweetie.
(CHUCKLES)
I hate to blow my own horn.
(HORN SOUNDS)
(GASPS)
Stay where you are! Don't be afraid!
Back! Back!
I was up late, couldn't sleep.
Milk wouldn't do it,
cocoa is a little sweet,
so I decided to make
an army of toy soldiers.
They don't have a good sense
of humor like me.
I would do what they ask you.
Which is what I'm going to tell you!
Don't listen to him!
This guy's not Santa!
- He's not Santa?
- BERNARD: He's a toy!
He has a rubber face
and a plastic tushy!
(PLASTICKY SQUEAKING)
Trust me! Don't let him ruin Christmas!
Thank you
for those kind words, Bernard!
Well, now that we all
have an understanding,
have a joyous and merry Christmas!
Merry Christmas!
(SCREAMING)
Okay, ready? Go!
This is what I call community service!
Here she comes. Duck down!
(DOOR OPENS)
SCOTT: Hey!
Attention you hooligans
behind that snowbank!
You have snowballed the wrong house.
Drop the snowballs,
kick them away from the snowsuits
and keep the mittens
where I can see them.
Your dad is hanging
with Principal Newman?
- Is he dating her?
- No.
Go to your homes.
Pelt the ones you love.
- And a merry Christmas!
- (CAROL LAUGHS)
- That is really gross, man.
- Shut up.
There are things about me
you should know. Personal things.
We don't need to rush things, Scott.
I think you need to know these things.
Okay.
Remember the mistletoe,
how it just showed up?
- Yes.
- And the sleigh.
- How magical that was?
- Yes.
Secret Santa Claus?
- That was me.
- Yeah?
I'm not this size much.
I'm usually much bigger than this.
So am I sometimes.
I have a big white beard that's beautiful.
- I don't.
- I work a long way from home.
When I get back home,
I sleep for a long time.
See? Okay. It's not so bad so far.
You work far away from home
and you sleep a lot.
You've never been to prison
and you don't wear socks with sandals.
- Well...
- (LAUGHS)
(SIGHS)
I'm Santa Claus.
What?
The suit, the red suit's real.
The North Pole is a place.
There are elves. They make toys.
They're beautiful and it's real.
- I exist.
- That's not funny.
- It's magical.
- Cut it out.
I'm telling the truth.
I told you something personal
from my childhood
and now you're making a joke
out of it and it's not funny. It hurts.
I know how hard this is to believe,
but connect the dots.
- Think what's happened.
- I know what's going on.
- Think about the little girl.
- You felt something for me.
Now you're acting like a mental patient
because you're scared.
- I deliver gifts in a sleigh.
- Incredible.
I go down chimneys with burning logs
and I still deliver gifts.
I'm not scared. That's not what this is.
If you're trying to push me away,
it's working.
Carol, don't make me leave.
Please.
CHARLIE: How could you pick her?
SCOTT: I didn't.
CHARLIE: You don't care anymore.
I care more about you than anybody.
But it's a two-way street.
- You won't confide in me.
- You want it? Here it is.
(SHUSHING)
- What? Talk to me.
- I don't live a normal life.
- You live a great life here.
- Just listen to me!
My friends get to go around
saying, "My dad's a plumber."
"My dad's a pilot." "My dad's a dentist."
You know what?
My dad is the best thing of all
and I can't tell anyone.
You have no idea how hard it is,
walking around with that secret.
And now you're going out
with Principal Newman!
And you don't even tell me about it.
My whole life has become
about secrets, and I hate it!
(CHARLIE SNIFFLES)
I'm sorry.
Forget about
Principal Newman, all right?
And forget about Santa. I'm done.
(SIGHS)
My time's up.
Who cares anymore?
- Hi, Charlie.
- Hi, Lucy.
- What are you doing?
- Just shoveling.
Oh.
Charlie, is Uncle Scott Santa Claus?
No. Why would you think that?
I don't know.
- How come Uncle Scott was sad?
- What makes you think that?
I asked him to stick a straw in his nose
and blow bubbles in his milk.
- And he said no.
- Whatever.
- Can you talk to him?
- I don't think so, Lucy.
- Did you have a fight?
- Sort of.
- Are you gonna make up?
- I don't know!
- Are you gonna be mad forever?
- Lucy!
- What?
- These are hard questions.
No, they're not. They're easy.
And you can't be mad
at him forever, Charlie.
He's your daddy and you love him.
(SIGHS)
(SINGING)
Dashing through the snow
In a strip-mining machine
Flatten the hills we go
Come on!
Put a smile on that face, little troll!
Wait a minute. I got a joke.
This'll cheer you up.
- Knock, knock!
- Who's there?
(LAUGHS)
- Aren't you?
- Aren't you who?
Aren't you supposed to
get back to work?
All of ya! You little idiots! Back to work!
Got any twos?
Hmm.
Go fish.
- (BACKFIRING)
- Whoa! Whoa! Whoa!
- Whoa!
- (CRASHING)
- What was that?
- I don't know.
- Want some more hot chocolate?
- Mmm-hmm.
Okay.
(DOOR BELL RINGING)
- Would you get that, honey?
- Yeah, sure.
Is Scott here?
Who are you?
Curtis, a friend from Buffalo.
- Are you an elf?
- (LAUGHING) Of course not!
Why would you ask
such a silly question?
How come you have pointy ears?
It's because I never ate
my green vegetables.
Do you eat your green vegetables?
Uncle Scott!
Yeah, I'm right here. What's wrong?
Oh! Curtis! What are you doin' here?
There's a little trouble at the plant.
It's okay. Curtis is a very old friend.
We have a large firm.
We work together in...
- (WHISPERS) Buffalo.
- Buffalo?
We work together in Buffalo.
So, we're gonna talk business.
- What business?
- It's none of your business.
Soon, I'm gonna be seven.
And then I can know things.
- Good night, Curtis.
- Good night, Lucy.
Good night, Lucy.
- What's up?
- Toy Santa's out of control.
He's locked up the elves,
shut down the workshop,
he thinks everybody's naughty
and he's gonna give everyone coal!
- Why didn't Bernard tell me?
- He's under house arrest.
Bernard?
Fly back with me to the North Pole
to save Christmas!
I can't. I have no magic left.
I'm out of magic. Look.
(GRUNTS)
- I thought you had Comet.
- Yeah, we...
Yes! Come on!
Hey, Comet. We just...
(GROANS)
Comet?
Look at me.
Comet.
(GROANS)
What are ya doin'?
Eating sugar is bad for you.
(GABBLES)
What do you mean, you didn't eat this?
Who did?
A squirrel?
Get this. You gotta fly both
of us back to the North Pole.
Yeah, tonight.
(GROANS)
Okay. I'll help you up.
All right? Ready?
You've got to help me a little here.
(GROANS)
Pull.
(GRUNTING)
Good. Okay, we almost got it.
That's okay.
Okay, now, help me.
Can ya move anything?
(LONG GROAN)
Fire in the hole! Get away!
(FARTS)
(SIGHS IN RELIEF)
- Whoa!
- (WHISTLES)
Eat some roughage, will you?
- Oh. What about the jet pack?
- It burned up on reentry.
What am I supposed to do?
Grow wings?
I hope he doesn't have
too many stops to make tonight.
You and me both, pal.
Okay. Let's just get it over with.
Okay.
One, two,
three!
(GROANS)
- What's going on down there?
- Are you sure about this?
What? The old toaster trick?
When we were kids, we used to do
this to get a little extra cash.
- Works every time!
- I can't watch this.
- You ready, buddy?
- All right. Let her rip.
One,
two,
three!
Ow!
(GROANS)
Oh, Scott!
- Scott, are you all right?
- Mom!
- Yes?
- I lost another tooth.
Should I put it under my pillow?
Yes!
By cuspids!
(SHUSHES)
(WHISPERING) This way. Come on.
Curtis, get the door.
It's a Tooth Fairy ambush.
What do you people want?
I only carry $20 in change.
(SHUSHING)
Tooth Fairy, it's me, Santa.
I've lost the weight
and the beard, but it's me.
I know Santa. Santa is a friend.
And you, sir, are no Santa.
I am too.
How did I know I could capture you
by holdin' on to a wing?
You wanted to change your name
to Captain Floss or Plaque Man.
Or, as I recall, Roy.
And it was Santa's idea
to call you the Molarnator.
- Who's the kid?
- One of my elves. He's an elf.
Ow.
Santa!
(LAUGHS)
The Molarnator at your service!
- A little altitude, please!
- What?
Could you possibly fly
a little higher? Ow!
- What?
- Ow!
- (CAR ALARM BEEPING)
- Never mind!
Principal Newman?
What is it, Charlie?
You keep asking me
if there's something bothering me.
Well, there is. I...
I couldn't talk about it before, but...
I want to talk about it now.
Okay. Go ahead.
- My dad is Santa.
- Oh, please. Not you too.
Hold on.
If you have no feelings
for my dad, then fine.
But if the only reason
for not being with him is
that you don't believe in him,
you're making a big mistake.
Oh, Charlie.
Here.
I want you to take this.
Look into this and
try to remember what it was like
when you were little
and you still believed in Christmas.
Seeing isn't believing.
Believing is seeing.
(LAUGHS)
You haven't seen anything yet!
- Curtis?
- What?
- (THUMP)
- CURTIS: Ow!
- What do I do?
- Slow down.
Okay.
Piece of cake. Attaboy. There you go.
Why can't you fly higher?
Tooth Fairy, I want to thank you.
I'll never forget this.
I wish I could do more, but I gotta go.
Denver just started
a new peewee hockey league.
Before you go,
I want you to know that nobody,
nobody was braver
than you were today.
You should be proud of your wings.
- They're not too girly?
- Not on you.
(CHUCKLES)
Wouldn't it be easier
to go through the workshop?
No. That way Santa and
his soldiers would be expecting us.
Sound military strategy involves
taking your enemy by surprise.
It's good strategy.
Sometimes being a despot
is a tough business.
(LAUGHS)
Come on.
(HUMMING)
It's Scott, isn't it?
Yeah. What are you supposed to be?
A better, stronger version
of what you used to be,
with a flawless complexion, I might add.
- Look, it just glistens.
- Listen to me. I'm back now.
So untie us. Let the elves go
and give me back the coat.
(MUMBLES)
No can do! It's Christmas Eve!
I have coal to deliver!
And I don't want
those naughty kids to suffer! (LAUGHS)
Boys! One, two, three!
And one, two! Try to keep up!
Let's go. Move it on!
Try to... This is just too tight.
(SIGHS)
This is all my fault.
I thought I could create another Santa.
My elfin pride blinded me to all reason.
There's only one Santa.
Well, I've done a pretty rotten job.
I didn't check the list twice.
My kid thinks I betrayed him.
I hurt the woman I love.
I ruined Christmas.
(SIGHS)
Charlie!
How'd you get up here?
Scott!
I got to fly in with the Tooth Fairy.
- Are you okay?
- Yeah.
Brush between meals
and don't forget the floss.
And if anybody cares, I'm exhausted.
And she has a beautiful smile.
- Thank you for everything.
- No. Thank you.
I am... (LAUGHS)
The Molarnator!
Whoo!
Come on!
(ALL CLAMORING)
Hyah!
(WHISTLES)
Get out of the way!
What are you doing?
- You gotta save Christmas.
- How am I supposed to save...
(CRASHING)
- No, no, no.
- Please. Don't worry.
ELVES: Whoa! Whoa!
Slow down.
Stay.
- Oh!
- (ELVES EXCLAIMING)
CHET: Oh, Chet...
Ouch! Ow! Oh, oh, oh!
Thanks. Excuse me, pork chop.
Okay. Chet, this is it.
You ready to rock and roll?
- Chet?
- Yeah. He's still in training.
- Has he had much flight time?
- About a minute and a half.
- He's had a lot of crash time!
- Curtis!
- He's just a baby.
- All right.
Let's see what this baby can do.
- (CHET HUMMING)
- Oh, boy.
Ready to go, buddy?
You know what we gotta do.
Hyah!
Chet! Whoa, whoa, whoa. Chet, Chet.
(CHET CACKLES WILDLY)
You gotta focus, Chet.
Okay, everybody! Outside, now!
Almost there, boys. Let's go!
(LAUGHS)
- Chet, whoa!
- (MAD CACKLE)
(CHEERING)
Snowballs, on three!
One!
Two!
Three!
Okay, elves!
Let's get 'em!
(ALL YELLING)
Not so far!
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
- Chet!
- Whoo!
Back for more action, eh, Scooter?
Chet, Chet!
(LAUGHS)
(CHET BABBLES)
Cut the chitchat, Chet!
Why is this such a problem? Come on!
Where do you think you're going?
- Go, go!
- Hyah, boy! Come on!
Faster!
The lead. The one in the front, Chet!
Leave my reindeer alone!
- Go! Go! Go!
- (CHET BLOWS RASPBERRY)
Come on! We got to get them
before they get out the hole.
Stay away from my lead reindeer!
- (CHET MAKES BUGLE SOUND)
- Whoo!
Holy Hannah, he's an action hero!
(LAUGHS) Hyah!
(SCREAMING)
What are you doin' up there?
I can't see where I'm driving.
You are a sad, strange little man.
Whoa.
You're gonna fall, I hope!
That's a good way to lose an eye!
(LAUGHS)
Look out! You're scaring me!
Can I help you?
Honey, I'm home!
(SCREAMING)
Loser!
(YELLING)
(SCREAMING)
(CACKLES)
Hey, I'm supposed to wear this coat!
How about a little elbow?
There you are. That's gotta feel good.
You want the shoe?
Take it off. Go ahead. Go on!
(BOTH GASP)
BOTH: Huh?
What are we gonna do now,
smarty-pants?
Watch out! The building! Left, left!
Oh, well. The town'll break the fall.
Look out!
Yo, Tony! Hey, Brian, stop me!
(GRUNTS)
(GROANS)
(ALL YELLING)
Get off of me! Now remember,
rules are very, very important!
I want hot chocolate.
SCOTT: Hey, guys, back up.
I've got a special place for him.
TOY SANTA: You idiot! Wait a minute,
something's shocking me.
- You were great.
- Sounds like you were, too.
- We've got 10 minutes.
- Where is Carol?
- Carol! Are you all right?
- Yes!
- Where are you going?
- I gotta deliver gifts.
Aren't you forgetting something?
- No.
- You gotta get married.
Excuse me?
Carol, I...
I cannot continue being Santa
unless I find a Mrs. Claus.
Oh.
So that's what the whole
noodles and pie thing...
- You just needed a wife.
- No.
No?
- Yes.
- Yes?
Yes, I was looking for a wife.
No, I didn't figure on falling in love.
You love me?
- This is all happening so fast.
- Well, there's no pressure.
Good.
I mean, if I don't get married,
I just won't deliver the gifts,
and children everywhere
will stop believing,
the elves will lose their jobs,
the North Pole will disappear
and Christmas will be gone.
- Get down on one knee.
- Hmm?
Do it. Now.
Say "Carol."
- Carol.
- Uh-huh.
Yeah?
You say this is happening all so fast.
But you've known me your whole life.
When you were little and alone...
- BOTH: Santa...
- I can take it from here.
Santa was always there for you.
And I will be, as long as you
continue to believe in me.
I know I'm asking you
to leave everything at home,
but I can guarantee you
that this is worth it.
This place...
This place is all about magic
and love and wonder.
And occasionally a thin-crust pizza
and a movie and a long winter night.
Is there a school here?
Yeah, we have one, a school,
but the elves need a new principal.
'Cause as of late, some of the elves
have been acting a bit impish.
Carol,
- I love you.
- You do?
Would you be my wife?
(WHISPERS) I will.
(WHISPERS) Thank you.
I've got it from here.
I will.
By the powers vested in me by me,
I now pronounce you Santa
and Mrs. Claus.
(BELL TOLLING)
Well, go on now. Kiss her!
ALL: Aw!
(GURGLING)
(ALL CHEERING)
(LAUGHS)
- Dad, we gotta go.
- Walk me to my sleigh.
We gotta go! When we get back,
we start making some more toys.
All right. Well, Mrs. Claus,
you might want to get some rest.
You see, tomorrow begins
vacation season for me,
which means a three-month
honeymoon for us.
(CHUCKLES)
Nothing tropical.
You do not want to see this in a Speedo.
Don't be home too late.
And so it begins.
Boys, we've got some toys to deliver!
Hyah! Hyah!
(WHISPERS) Lucy?
What, Charlie?
Come downstairs.
I want you to see something.
(WHISPERS) Lucy.
Watch this.
(GASPS)
Uncle Scott?
- Do you have any twos?
- Go fish!
You are Santa!
I knew it was you all along.
- And you were right.
- Uncle Scott,
you look all rosy.
Are you feeling better?
I'm feeling much, much better.
Is there anything else
I should know about?
I don't know. But Charlie has
something he wants to tell you.
Okay.
You know, I was exactly your age
when I found out my dad was Santa.
- But I couldn't tell anybody.
- I can't tell anybody either?
No. But knowing it isn't a burden.
It's a gift.
Most kids stop believing in Santa
when they grow up.
But I get to believe in him forever.
I love you, Charlie. Thank you.
But do we still get toys?
If you ever get to bed
and go to sleep like the other kids.
Okay.
- Merry Christmas, Lucy.
- Merry Christmas, Santa.
Sport, I gotta fly.
(REINDEER HOOVES THUNDERING)
(REINDEER HOOVES)
- Easy, boys, easy.
- (CHET GROANS)
You're gettin' it, Chet.
(REINDEER SIGHS HAPPILY)
Look, Charlie!
Merry Christmas, Comet!
All right, boys!
Hyah! Ho, ho, ho!
- Hyah!
- (CHET MAKES BUGLE SOUND)
Merry Christmas to all!
And to all a good night!
(CHET BABBLES)
Nothin' wrong with a straight line, Chet.
- Chet! Chet!
- (CHET CACKLES WILDLY)
(CHRISTMAS SONG PLAYING)
Everybody loves Christmas
Everybody has fun
That time ofthe year
That holiday cheer
A good time for everyone
Everybody loves Christmas
Oh, count the ways
You know it's almost here
Oh, Christmas Day
Christmas Day
Hey!
What the heck are we doin' out here?
Look, if we're gonna dance,
dance like this. All of us!
Everybody, you idiots!
Hey, lady!
Watch this!
Ever seen a toy do this?
(LAUGHING)
Where you going? Whoo!