Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
Once, long ago,
in the deep blue below,
there was a kingdom.
A king, a queen, and six sisters...
Princesses of the sea.
The ocean realm was theirs
and the princesses were free to go
wherever they wished...
except for one place.
The surface.
Each princess, on her 15th birthday,
was allowed to venture to the above,
but only for one day.
Finally, the time came.
The littlest mermaid's 15th birthday.
And what she saw above
would alter her existence forever.
A prince. A true love.
When the prince fell, the little mermaid
found herself so drawn to him.
Despite stories
she had heard of the dangers above,
she had to save him.
She lingered over the prince,
gazing at him.
She wondered what this feeling was.
What would it be like to be with him?
To actually have legs?
She had never felt this way before.
As another human approached,
she gave the prince one last look
before descending back into the sea.
She watched from behind a rock
as the prince awoke.
He opened his eyes,
thinking that the one who stood before him
had saved his life.
The little mermaid was so sad.
She had left her heart above,
and wondered if a mermaid
could ever be with a human.
She swam into the darkest depths
of the sea
where there lived a wizard.
And she told the wizard of her love
and her desperation for legs
like those who lived above.
The cunning wizard made her an offer.
He said he would grant her a wish
in exchange for one thing.
Her soul.
But if she were to go above
and not be able to find love,
her soul would be his
until true love came.
The little mermaid agreed.
The promise was forged,
the bond made.
But upon finding her prince,
she found his heart still belonged
to the woman on the shore.
The little mermaid was visited
by the wizard
who had come
to collect on their agreement.
She pleaded with the wizard
but it was too late.
Above the sea,
the wizard would keep her locked away,
ensuring she would never find true love
and her power would be his...
forever.
If I told you a secret,
would you be able to keep it?
- Really, truly, you would keep it?
- Yes.
Yes, I would keep my secret.
Well, I don't remember the story
exactly like that.
Don't be silly, Grandmother.
Everybody knows
there's no such thing as mermaids.
You wouldn't say that if you had met one.
You've met a mermaid?
Yes.
But you don't believe, so...
So why should I tell you the story?
You wanna hear it?
- Yes, yes, yes, yes!
Yes.
This begins with a little, little girl.
And she believed in mermaids
and in fairies and in leprechauns
and all magical creatures.
And her name was Elle.
♪ Bend and break
Bend and break... ♪
♪ ...Bend and break, my fair lady ♪
Dear Dr. Malcolm,
thank you for your preliminary diagnosis
of my niece Elle.
Life has been difficult
following the loss of her parents.
Yet somehow, her spirits remain high,
mostly due to her imaginative belief
that she is somehow a mermaid
and that being the reason
for her condition.
But no doctor anywhere seems to know
- what truly ails her.
- Quick, get help!
Only that her
breathing patterns worsen.
I fear her life may be in danger.
I will continue to search,
in hopes that one day,
the mystery behind her condition
is revealed
and a cure is found.
- Breathe. Breathe.
- Faithfully yours, Cam.
Cam, hurry, it's Elle.
It's OK.
Elle, it's OK. It's OK.
It's OK. It's OK. It's OK.
It's OK...
It's OK. Look at me.
You can't push yourself that hard.
I've told you.
I know.
It's just that everybody else was...
Playing?
We're gonna find a cure.
I promise.
But until then,
you'll have to be more careful.
Did you see that?
What is it?
- Good morning, Mr. Harrison.
- Good morning, Margaret. Any calls for me?
They're on your desk.
Morning, young man.
- Morning, sir.
- How's the story going?
Great.
Yeah. Well, I want it to stop.
Look, this just came in.
I want it to take priority.
It's the cure-all sweeping the region.
A water from Mississippi
said to have healing powers.
Really? Healing water?
I mean,
we've followed stories like this before.
Wood witches? Woken mummies?
They never lead anywhere.
No, not like this.
Hundreds of people are testifying.
- But, I...
- But nothing.
All right, maybe it's true,
maybe it's not.
But there's definitely a story here,
and, uh, possibly a cure for her.
Look, Cam, I know it can't be easy.
Coming from, how do you say,
across the pond?
It's already settled.
Travel and accommodations.
Don't just sit there. Get going.
Pack your bags.
- Thank you, sir.
- Don't thank me. Thank, uh... him.
"Dr. Locke's Miracle
Mermaid Elixir."
Right.
They're here, Elle!
What's taking so long?
We'll only be gone for a few weeks.
I know you'll miss him.
But it won't be for long.
Do you promise?
I promise.
A long journey from home.
Elle seems to have turned her intrepidness
for our little adventure
into joyful excitement.
Seeing the smile on her face
only makes me want to believe.
But my logical skepticism runs high
of this Dr. Locke
and his magic mermaid water.
If only life were as simple
as a made-up fairy-tale.
"Eighty eight, Wood Street."
This must be it.
Welcome to Mississippi.
Oh, let me help you with that.
Eh!
Well, let me take... take this from you.
Cameron it is, right?
Journalistically speaking, yes.
But you can call me Cam.
- And who's this little darling?
- I'm Elle.
Oh, aren't you just
a precious little thing?
- Thank you.
- And polite, too.
Come on, now. Let me show you all inside.
- You have a beautiful home, Lorene.
- My family's owned this home for years.
Let me show you around.
Unh!
Over here is the living area.
And straight through, this is the kitchen.
Oh...
I already baked these for you. Have some.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
Thank you so much. Thank you.
Now, come on,
let me show you the rest of the house.
This is the sleeping quarters.
Now, it ain't much,
but it's a bed and a roof.
- It's a perfect, Lorene. Thank you.
- You're welcome.
Be kind of nice to have some company.
I think we're gonna like it here, Elle.
Oh, I forgot.
I haven't shown you guys the garden.
Even has a tree-house.
Elle!
Elle, be careful!
Wow!
Isn't this kingdom beautiful?
It's princess should be more careful.
Praise to Jesus.
Come on, dear.
Peggy Gene.
Cam, I want you to meet Peggy Gene.
Hi.
Peggy Gene is one of my closest friends.
It's very nice to meet you, Peggy Gene.
It is very, very nice to meet you too.
Aww. Who's this little nugget?
- I'm Elle.
- Elle.
Aren't you the sweetest little apricot
in the land?
Look at you.
Those little cheeks are so cute.
You're like a bug in a rug.
You'll have to excuse Peggy Gene.
Oh, I'm sorry.
I haven't been around many people lately.
But ever since that healing water
fixed my leg,
I'm just flitting around
like a little social butterfly.
- Healing water?
- Hmm.
I'd love to talk to you about that.
Why, sure. Though Lorene knows
where to find me,
but I will be at the church all day long
and I will talk, talk, talk to you, boo,
all about that healing water.
And if you like,
I can invite some other people
'cause I understand you're making a story.
Hey, Peggy Gene, Peggy Gene.
I'll see you tomorrow at the church.
Yes, yes.
I'll see you tomorrow at the church. OK.
See you both. I'll see you tomorrow.
- OK, you take care now. All right.
- OK.
Come on, let's get some of this nice food
I told you about.
Well. Hi, Eugene.
- Howdy, Lorene.
- All right.
Here, sweetie.
You say you like them wrapped...
So you really do
know everyone in town, huh?
Pretty much.
Well, outside of those that are
coming here about that healing water.
I understand that's why you're here too.
You ready?
Let's go.
Come on.
Hello.
Hi.
What's your name?
- I'm Elle.
- Elle?
Can you read mine?
Of course, child.
You are special in all the world.
There's a powerful magic... in you.
A spirit of the ocean.
You should keep these.
Thank you.
And what about you? You don't believe
in all this magic, do you?
I'm skeptical.
Come, see.
There is some magic
that is real.
And some...
that is illusion.
Whoa!
Beware of the one who will try
and take your most precious treasure.
You must not let him.
Well, the show is about to start.
You don't want to miss this.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Bye!
This place is very strange.
Step right up. Step right up.
Come and witness the magic.
Witness the wonder.
Ladies and gentlemen.
Come one, come all, to the shop of art.
Feast your eyes on that
which you've never seen.
It is said that they are pure myth,
pure legend.
But my dear friends, let me introduce you
to your dreams.
Alive,
breathing
and swimming.
The little mermaid of the Mississippi.
Elle. Elle.
Elle.
She was real.
It's just, uh, cheap tricks, Elle.
There are no cheap parlor tricks here.
Fairy Floss!
One please.
Thank you.
The fairies worked really hard
to make this.
I'm sure they did.
What?
Sorry to bother you, I...
I was just wondering if I could buy...
Can you read? "Sold out."
What?
It's just, um, sold out till when?
Till further notice.
Well, he was polite.
Can I ride? Please?
I don't think you're big enough.
Am so!
Man, I'm ten times stronger
than the Strong Man.
Have you seen these? Bam! Bam!
Well, well, look at this.
I've never seen a freak so pretty.
She isn't a freak.
She's a fake.
Whatever she is, she sure is sweet.
Hey, leave her alone.
What you gonna do about it?
Better take a step back.
Pretty scary, foreigner.
We'll take it from here.
Did you see me?
How high I got?
You're such a big girl now.
Come on. Let's go.
So Elle believed the mermaid was real?
She knew it was real.
I know too.
And what about Cam?
Cam, like most grownups,
needed more proof of the impossible.
And that's the thing
about what you believe.
There's a whole other world
out there to see.
And Cam just had to figure that out.
I still can't believe
I saw an actual mermaid.
She was so beautiful
and I know she was real.
Can we see her again tomorrow?
Can I meet her?
Elle, we talked about that.
What you saw was just a trick.
You believe what you want
and I'll believe what I want.
And I believe she was real.
All right. Good night.
Sleep well.
- Cam?
- Yes?
I wish Mom and Dad could have seen her.
Me too.
But, wait.
How can the mermaid live
if she's not in the sea?
Have you ever heard of a sea lamprey?
Well, it's a fish that can live
in both river and sea.
Lets you know that nothing is impossible,
especially here in Mississippi.
It has that certain magic about it.
That's a good one.
You both will enjoy that one.
So what happened
after you drank the water?
Well, I'm not crazy anymore.
I was deaf as can be
before I drank the water.
And you haven't been experiencing
any side effects?
I can do this.
What happened after you drank the water?
Well, I was having migraines.
Now I just get headaches.
It's real magic, I think.
Magic.
M- M-M-Magic.
Magic, huh?
Believe it or not, I was darn near bald
before I took the water.
I never thought I'd fall in love again.
Now I seem to love everyone.
What do you think about the magician?
Oh, I think he's wonderful.
So dark and mysterious and handsome too.
I prefer the mermaid.
Sorry, what was the question?
Probability... Hoax.
Hello.
Cam Harrison.
Thank you for seeing me
on such short notice.
Please.
- Have a seat.
- Thank you.
So, Mr. Locke, is it?
Firstly, I wanted to ask you
about the healing water.
Can you tell me what it does for people?
By now, you must have asked my customers.
What did they tell you?
They had some unusual stories, yes, but...
You do not believe.
That's what I wanted to talk to you about.
Where is it from? How do you make it?
The first rule of magic,
is to never reveal the how or the why.
But it's not magic, is it?
Surely, if it works,
there must be some medical formula.
If you do not believe,
then why are you here?
Apologies if I've offended you.
I'm just writing for my readers.
Let's try some other questions.
Can you tell me about...
the mermaid?
It appears your time is up, Cam Harrison.
Please...
The blue fairy makes the blue flower.
The pink fairy makes the pink flower.
The white fairy makes the white flower.
And the yellow fairy
makes the yellow flower.
Yes. I know. I know.
We really shouldn't be out here
much longer, Elle.
I don't think it's a good idea.
Lorene's gonna be looking for us
and I don't want to get stuck out
in the middle of the woods.
- Wait, Elle.
- Hey! Hey, you!
You're...
You're the mermaid.
I am.
But...
How do you have legs?
Well, mermaids get their legs
every low tide.
But... shh!
It's a secret.
I won't tell.
You know, where I come from,
we have a fairy tale.
About a little girl born on land,
blessed with the heart of a mermaid.
Right, uh...
So what were you doing in the woods?
Am I not allowed
to go for a walk in the woods?
- So...
- What's your name?
Elizabeth.
I'm Elle.
This is Cam. He's my uncle.
I'm sorry, I have to go.
See?
I told you she was real.
I told you. You do what I say.
- Stop!
- Stay out of this!
Strike me then.
As you wish, darling.
Enough!
That is enough for today.
But I cannot promise
what tomorrow may bring.
As for you,
do not meddle in my affairs.
It's OK, girl.
Why are you so afraid?
It's OK.
I don't know what she is
but she is special.
Good girl.
What did you see?
Something I haven't seen
in a very long time.
She may be the one we're searching for.
What are we gonna do about it?
We wait.
Now, leave me.
♪ It's so enchanting ♪
♪ I'm trapped and drowning ♪
♪ Here for everyone to see ♪
♪ They don't notice ♪
♪ How far away I am ♪
♪ From everyone and everything ♪
♪ Silly to have gambled
With my heart out on the line ♪
♪ I guess that's just the way it goes ♪
♪ But I'm holding on ♪
♪ I know a day will come ♪
♪ When I can be myself again ♪
♪ And I hope someone will love me ♪
♪ When this story ends ♪
♪ Round in circles ♪
♪ Pointless wandering ♪
Hello?
♪ And the crowds lines up again ♪
♪ Give a smile, girl ♪
♪ You make them happy ♪
♪ Bring your parents, bring a friend ♪
♪ Silly that a main attraction ♪
♪ Would long so much for love ♪
♪ I guess that's just the way it goes ♪
♪ But I'm holding on ♪
♪ I know a day will come ♪
♪ When I can be myself again ♪
♪ And I hope someone will love me ♪
♪ When this story ends ♪
♪ If someone could ♪
♪ Someone right for me ♪
♪ Finds a way ♪
♪ To take me home again ♪
♪ I believe it ♪
♪ One day I'll be home ♪
♪ Still I'm searching ♪
♪ Round in circles ♪
♪ While the crowd lines up ♪
♪ Again ♪
Who's there?
You?
What are you doing here?
Sorry, I...
The place was closed and I...
You shouldn't be here.
He knows everything.
Who knows?
What are you talking about?
Cam Harrison.
I just had some further questions
about the show,
about the healing water.
I wish I could help you. Truly, I do.
But we are closed.
Now if you do not mind...
I really hope not to find you
trespassing again.
Stay away from her.
Who is he? And who is she?
It doesn't matter.
- I don't...
- You shouldn't be here.
Look, I know something strange
is happening. Whatever secrets...
Just go.
Go.
All aboard!
Now, this here's
the pride of the Mississippi.
Well, you heard what the man said.
All aboard.
I wonder if we'll see a mermaid
in the river.
Keep your eyes posted.
You got it, Captain.
Well, while you two are mermaid watching,
I'll be in the study
doing some actual work.
Whatever you say, first mate.
OK.
Mermaids...
do not...
exist.
What are you working on?
Nothing.
It's just... It's just some story I...
I like stories.
I... I'm not sure that's such a good idea.
It says you don't believe in mermaids.
It's a work in progress.
I wasn't really expecting someone to be...
to be rummaging through my things.
Well, you're the one
who's always following me.
You know, I'm...
I'm... I'm surprised
you're on this boat at all.
Then again,
you must get tired of the water,
being an actual mermaid and all.
Water is a part of me, I guess.
Part of us all.
When I was little,
my mother would swim with me.
Deep into the ocean,
further than most would go.
I remember looking through the water,
wondering what it must be like
on the other side.
Yeah.
When I was born,
our family would go
to the beach every summer.
I remember wishing we'd get caught
in a whirlpool,
stuck in a time warp and...
somehow just... just last forever.
It's my favorite memory of us.
Before Elle got sick...
and the accident happened.
Now, I...
I just want to keep her safe.
My father was the same.
She's special.
She's strong.
I'll try and remember that.
She's all I have left.
The reason I'm here.
The healing water, is it...
Is it real?
I believe there's magic
in a lot of things,
water being one of them.
But not his.
Not Locke's.
The dance is starting!
Elizabeth?
Come dance with me.
Hold on.
All together.
Peggy Gene, are you OK?
Listen.
It fades.
- What does?
- The magic.
It doesn't last.
You be careful with that man,
do you understand me?
Don't you let him near the apricot.
She will rot.
Don't you let that apricot rot,
do you understand me?
I won't.
- No.
- Come here.
Here, let Cam show you.
I'm afraid I'm not a very good dancer.
Sorry. I'm sorry.
Oh, I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
The moon. Come.
Why are you always
staring at me like that?
Because I want to see you.
Don't you want me to see you?
It's not that, it's just, um...
A little, you know...
intense.
Well, if you don't look,
then how do you see?
How do you really see a person?
We should be free
to open our eyes and look.
You can't take that away from us.
Who can't? Locke, you mean?
I'm... I'm sorry. I didn't mean to.
You know, you don't have
to apologize all the time.
You're right. I'm sorry, I mean...
Look.
- Isn't it...
- Beautiful.
Looks like the wheel is stuck.
We'll have to wait for high tide.
- High tide?
- Yeah.
Sorry, I have to go.
Elizabeth.
Elizabeth!
You're afraid.
They always are.
You're...
- How can this be?
- You won't understand.
I...
I want to.
It happened a long time ago.
I was free.
I lived with my family in the sea.
I was tricked.
He took a part of me and he has it still.
So wherever he goes, I must.
We're bonded.
Locke?
For years,
he's taken me from town to town.
Selling the water I swim in
as healing water.
So that's where he gets it. You.
Yes, but you shouldn't get involved.
Well, I think it's too late for that.
Why can't you just run away? Escape him?
We're connected.
As long as he has part of me with him,
there's no escape.
There has to be something...
a way, somehow.
There is.
What's wrong?
It's Locke.
He knows I'm here. He's summoning me.
No, no. You can't go back to him.
You don't understand, I have to. I'm his.
No, Elizabeth.
I'm sorry, Cam.
So Cam believed now, right?
He did.
He had to believe what his eyes saw.
Despite every logical bone in his body,
he couldn't deny the truth,
and that kiss was still in his mind.
But there was much
that he did not understand,
especially when it came to Locke.
Thank God.
I've had half the town looking for you.
- Why? What happened?
- Well...
- I-
- I was wondering what happened to you
- and I left Elle in the room playing.
- What happened?
- And then... And then when I went back...
- Lorene, what happened?
- And then when I went back she...
- What happened, Lorene?
She was gone and the window was open!
Where is she?
I don't know. I don't know, Cam.
Why does he have you trapped in here?
Did you do something wrong?
No.
He said I had the heart of a mermaid
and that was a powerful kind of magic.
You do. I see it too.
But be careful.
He's not like you and I. He's a bad man.
Do you understand?
When I was young, I was just like you.
When I'm older,
I want to be just like you.
Oh, he's coming.
You'll be OK, just remember what I said.
OK.
Let her go.
I cannot.
You see, she's the one
I've been searching for.
You don't need her, you have me.
You?
I plan to rid you from this earth...
and take your powers...
once and for all.
Go, go, go, go. Go find Elle.
Elizabeth tells me you wish
to be like her.
Is this true?
What if I could make it so?
What if I could grant you any wish
you so desire...
in exchange for a simple thing?
Anything?
Anything you can dream of.
You won't trick me.
You're not like us.
You just wanna control everyone.
In time, you will find
that I can be most persuasive.
I know where she is.
It's all right, come with me.
They said you would come for me.
I'm gonna get you out of here.
- Where'd they put the keys?
- The guard has them.
Over there.
It's all right.
We're gonna get you out of here. OK?
It's sold out.
Sold...
Let's go, let's go.
Locke knows Elizabeth told you.
He won't stop coming. Not now.
We have to save her.
- We have to save Elizabeth.
- We will, Elle.
She can't leave without her soul.
If she does, she dies.
Locke keeps it hidden somewhere safe.
I don't know where it is.
I think I know where that might be.
Come on.
That's it.
Easy.
He's with us.
It's time.
We can trust him.
Ladies and gentlemen, let me introduce you
to your dreams...
We have to hurry,
I can't hold it for very long.
Wow!
We have to hurry.
But I can't.
How is that possible?
It won't last long.
It'll be high tide soon.
- You must go.
- Wait.
There's something we have to do.
Come on.
She's free.
Let's go.
- You OK?
- So what now?
We have to get you to the ocean.
How long do we have
before time begins again?
With Locke, it's uncertain.
Then we need to move.
The train! Should be a straight shot
from the station.
Harbor trains run toward the ocean. Hurry.
Cam, wait.
Cam.
I'm too old to be jumping on trains.
I'll just hold you back.
You're one of a kind, Lorene.
Thank you.
- Bye.
Good luck, Cam.
- Take good care of her.
- The train is picking up pace...
- Let's go.
- ...we have to hurry.
We can make it.
It's OK. Here.
Here.
I think this belongs to you.
Thank you.
Thank you all.
We had to do something.
Seventeen years.
He found me when I was young.
Promised he could help me.
Help me not be so...
different.
He promised me the same.
Found me trying to block out
all the world's thoughts
and said that he could fix it...
if I just listened to him.
There is nothing wrong with who you are.
You must really miss your families.
I'm glad you have this one.
Come one, come all.
Let me introduce you
to your dreams.
Alive,
breathing,
swimming.
The little mermaid of the Mississippi.
Elizabeth!
They have it!
The soul!
They're on a train headed for the ocean.
Boys are going after them right now.
Stop them.
And this time, once and for all.
You got it, boss.
They're here.
Stay back!
Elizabeth, look out.
It's OK.
We have to go.
Now.
There's a truck close by.
- There are no keys.
- We don't need keys.
Stay with Elizabeth.
Elle? Elle, it's OK, it's OK.
It's OK, I've got the medication.
It's not here.
Stop! We left the medicine on the train.
- I'm not leaving.
- Come on. Let's go.
- Elle, we're going. Let's go.
- No!
I'm staying! I'm staying.
Come on, Elle, come on! Let's go. Come on!
I'm staying. Elizabeth...
She's my friend.
Stop treating me like a little girl.
I can make it further.
Just trust me.
This once.
All right, Elle.
I trust you.
We have to go.
Go.
He's close.
Keep moving. I'll take care of him.
No, you can't.
You don't have a choice. Now go.
Go!
I've been waiting a long time for this.
Man against monster.
You wish.
There's nobody here to save you now.
You neither.
It's starting.
We have to hurry, she's changing.
We have to get her to the ocean.
How much further?
Just past the trees.
You have to hurry.
We're stuck.
Can you carry her?
Yeah.
Here we go.
You need to get to the ocean.
What about you?
I can take care of our old friend here.
Buy you some time.
I had such great hopes for you.
Such a disappointment.
You hoped that I would be cruel like you.
You know better than anyone,
no two souls are the same.
Indeed they aren't.
One is always darker.
You won't win this time.
Let it be light versus night.
There is no power
greater than mine.
Oh, no.
No.
She's free. She doesn't belong to you.
Nothing in this world is free,
Cam Harrison.
It's all right. It's all right.
I won't let them take you.
She's good! She's not like you!
I won't let you have her!
Take it.
No, no.
Locke's powers grow with it.
So can yours.
No, no. You're too weak.
It's the only way.
Her soul is mine.
Pity they must now die.
My powers are forever!
Not you or anyone else on this earth
can defeat me.
I believe.
What have they done to me?
Magic.
Now, he is imprisoned.
Elizabeth.
She needs water!
Give her to me. It's all right.
It's all right.
The vial.
Elizabeth, please...
Come on.
Elle?
Elle? Elle? It's OK. It's OK. It's OK.
Take a breath. Breathe.
Shh. Shh.
You're OK.
Let me take her.
The water can heal her.
- You're OK.
- Shh... shh... shh.
You're OK.
It's OK.
Thank you.
Deep water is magic,
just like her love.
Whenever she can't breathe,
all she need do is swim.
I'll miss you.
I see you found your story.
Think anyone will believe it?
All that matters is that you do.
Come outside and play.
All the fairies are out today.
And they love mermaids.
Then we mustn't keep them waiting.
No!
Come on.
All that matters is that you do.
And she gave him
the biggest gift
a person could ever give another...
Love.
So from that time on,
no matter where he went,
she was with him. Mm-hmm.
Now that's another story. OK.
What happened to Elle?
Are you OK, grandmother?
Just time for a swim.
How'd the story end?
Let's go... I don't know.
Come on.
We'll go see.
Let's go. Come on.
Grandmother?
♪ There must be so much more out there ♪
♪ A brighter world
That's waiting just for me ♪
♪ A place that's filled with hope
And people singing ♪
♪ Place where you can hold
Each dream you dream ♪
♪ I'll be on the waves
A brand new mystery awaits ♪
♪ So here's the chance
That I will have to take ♪
♪ All my life I followed
What they told me ♪
♪ Where to go
And when it's time to start ♪
♪ But I hear a song of love
And ever after ♪
♪ Though it's time ♪
♪ To listen to this heart of mine ♪
Please rate this subtitle at www.osdb.link/6zgpb
Help other users to choose the best subtitles