Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
So I'm gonna get
a three-to-one return on my money?
Man: Otto is the reaI deaI.
I met him at a hash bar in Amsterdam.
He speaks Russian, German, Arabic...
Otto: Mr. Ostroff's trust
is not gained easiIy.
Two years it took me.
You see, Micky,
he doesn't Iike new faces.
So teII me, why am I
Iooking at a new face?
Otto Krieg, meet my friend, Bobby.
He's heIping me with the finance.
He's not a cop.
Let's see the money.
( speaking Russian )
You Iike it?
Yeah, I Iike it.
- We have deaI?
- We have deaI.
( sirens bIaring )
- Agent: Bring 'em down!
- Agent #2: Move!
Agent #3: Move in!
P.A.:
This is the FBI!
Put your hands on your head!
What is this?
You brought a cop, and
he brought his fucking friends!
- Don't Iook at me.
- This is not good.
My father wiII kiII me!
You're under arrest for the importation
and saIe of contraband firearms.
Scheisse!
- Agent #5: Gun!
- Agent #6: Drop the gun! Drop the gun!
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
Otto!
This is not my deaI.
This is not my deaI!
I don't even know these guys!
Agent #7: Cease fire!
HoIy shit. HoIy shit.
Bobby!
Stay down!
I'm caIIing it. It's 1 :37 AM.
- Bag him and ship him.
- ( sirens sounding )
God, I hate this job.
- Give me a hand, feIIas.
- Yeah.
AII right, Frank.
We gotta get you outta here.
What the heII happened?
Who's the kid?
DefiniteIy not in the pIan.
But we beat the spread.
- This isn't footbaII.
- It's a figure of speech.
PeopIe weren't supposed
to die out there.
Get them IDed
and get them to the morgue.
- And get me my pants!
- Can we get some pants over here?
Ah, shit.
AII: Surprise!
To Frank CastIe...
the finest soIdier,
the finest undercover op,
the finest man I've ever known.
What am I gonna do without you?
- Get a girIfriend.
- ( aII Iaugh )
Have fun in Puerto Rico, man.
Say heIIo to your foIks.
Thanks.
Agent Weeks.
He's Robert Saint.
Howard Saint's son.
More paperwork for Tampa PD.
( chuckIes )
No, we can handIe this.
- Weeks: See you, buddy!
- See you, feIIas!
( woman gasps )
BaiI him now.
Bring him to the cIub.
Don't hit me. Don't hit me.
- Hey, Micky.
- Don't hit me.
( coughing )
( grunting )
You seII homegrown pot by the ounce,
Micky, not by the barreI.
You seII badIy forged,
fake passports to Haitians.
So what inspired you to become...
the Mr. Universe
of internationaI arms deaIers?
You shouId apoIogize for the death
of Mr. Saint's youngest chiId.
Okay, I know how it Iooks...
But Bobby, he buys pot from me.
And when he found out what I was doing,
he insisted on coming in.
He put up haIf the cash.
He came of his own free wiII.
If you're gonna kiII me,
wiII you Ieave my face aIone,
for my mother?
We just made your baiI.
If I wanted to kiII you, I wouId have
Ieft you in jaiI where we have friends,
and in some way that I can onIy
describe as deepIy pornographic,
you wouId have been kiIIed.
But you're a smaII piece of shit,
and I don't want the karma
of your death on my souI.
But on the other hand,
maybe I don't beIieve in karma,
- so guys--
- No, I'II teII you what I want to know.
I want to know one thing onIy,
who brokered the deaI?
His name is Otto Krieg.
And if it's any comfort
to Mr. Saint, he's dead too.
WeII, it's not.
It's actuaIIy no comfort at aII.
But what might be comforting to me,
is to watch the sIow death of the man
who was supposed
to be taking care of my son,
and making sure that
he did not get into troubIe.
Now, Micky...
what wouId your father
think of this?
Your father gave his Iife for me.
What wouId he say?
I didn't know it was
gonna happen Iike this. PIease!
WeII, ignorance is no excuse.
The man who is responsibIe
for my son's death must die.
( grunting )
Saint: I toId you to never
Iet him out of your sight.
Mr. Saint, Bobby toId me to stay.
TeII him, John.
John!
Thug: Mr. Saint!
It was Bobby's idea!
He wanted to go aIone!
He thought he couId impress you.
Thank you for that expIanation.
My son didn't need to impress me.
More boxes, guys.
This was a hard one.
This was the Iast one.
( giggIes )
( sighs )
It's over.
TeII that to your son.
He doesn't beIieve me.
- Where is he?
- You know.
You know what I miss
most about Buck?
He couId catch a baII,
no matter how hard you threw it.
He was right there.
- Boy: Why are we aIways moving?
- This is the Iast time.
You said that Iast time.
I did?
Yeah.
You said we were Ieaving CaIifornia
and we were gonna move to Virginia,
and you'd work in Washington...
and we'd never move again.
( sighs )
I guess I've said a Iot of things, huh?
So why London?
London's a safe pIace
where we can aII be together.
No more more moving around,
I promise.
Some day when you're oIder, WiII...
I'II teII you why we had
to move so much.
He was such a speciaI boy.
Are you identifying this body
as your son, Robert Saint?
He deserved better.
Somebody Iied to him.
Promised him one thing,
gave him another.
Do you know that I used to have
to dress him tiII he was 1 3?
I'd tie his ties, and comb his hair...
I'II have to get him a new suit.
Who is Otto Krieg?
Who are the peopIe
who work for him?
Who are his friends?
Who wouId stand to make money
from this deaI? TeII me.
We can't taIk about the case, Mr. Saint.
Now, I understand your grief,
but for your own safety,
Ieave this to professionaIs.
ProfessionaIs. Yes...
I'II do that.
( whispers )
Good bye, son.
Man: We caIIed New York, we caIIed
Las Vegas, we caIIed Europe
and Hong Kong, we even got
the SiciIians in it for oId time's sake.
With what you're paying Howard,
we'II know everything
about Otto Krieg within 24 hours.
High five.
- Come on.
- That was cooI!
Leave it. We'II be back.
- Race you?
- Yeah.
Got anything Ieft?
I don't see it!
Come on!
He did his free ascent
on the first try.
I've seen Navy SEALs do worse.
- That's what we Iike to hear.
- I'm so proud of you.
Good job, babe.
Hey, Frank,
is that that CandeIaria?
Frank:Yeah, ManueI.
PeopIe around here
caII him a witch doctor.
He Iives on that isIand
way off the point.
OnIy one damn fooI I know
crazy enough to swim over there.
- ( aII chuckIing )
- Gee, Iet me guess.
- ( aII chatting )
- ( gIass cIinking )
This is the first famiIy reunion
we've had in five years.
And that's too Iong.
That's too Iong.
- ( aII appIaud )
- Amen.
Mr. CastIe: Two famiIies and
when you put them together,
you get this: my grandson!
I just want to say that...
I'm very happy that you're aII here.
I'm very proud that you're aII here.
And that...
I Iove you.
Love you, too, Dad.
- SaIud!
- AII: SaIud!
Hey!
- Hey.
- What happened? What's wrong?
You know...
I can't beIieve I'm home...
and that I couId ever be so Iucky.
Because there were times,
Maria, I gotta teII you--
Frank...
I Iost so much time,
with both of you.
- And I'm reaIIy sorry--
- Stop. Hey, hey, hey.
I married you.
I knew what I was doing...
and I'd do it again.
You and I, we're not Iucky,
we are bIessed.
( beIIs ringing )
I'II see you at home, son.
His name's Frank CastIe.
Senior agent.
Just got the Bureau's London desk.
His aIias, connections,
apartments in Europe,
none of it was reaI,
not even his death.
WeII, maybe it was.
Maybe...
he died and came back to Iife
so he couId die again.
You have your chance.
He's Ieaving
for EngIand next week
and he's at a famiIy reunion
in Puerto Rico.
I think you shouId be there
so you can come back
and teII Livia how he died.
- AII right.
- Livia: Wait.
His famiIy.
His whoIe famiIy.
Is this what you want?
- Morning.
- Hey.
Frank: We shouId have another.
I'm ready.
Another what?
- Good morning, WiII.
- Come here.
They were seIIing
T-shirts in town.
One of them was reaIIy scary.
The guy in the shop said
it wards off eviI spirits.
It's reaIIy intense.
- You know about this?
- Mm-hm.
Let's see here...
This is interesting.
- Like it?
I Iove it.
Thanks.
- ( chattering )
- ( music pIaying )
Nice.
Here you go.
Where's the camera? Okay.
- Come on! You've gotta see this!
- What?
Your 1911 CoIts,
you've done something to them.
You couId say that.
I bore the chambers
and customized the triggers
and added some compensators.
They used to be pretty good,
- but now they're naiI drivers.
- Let's see.
Hey, Mom!
- Look.
- Wow!
- Look at that. It's a stingray.
- Yeah.
- ( gun shot )
- ( screaming )
( gasps )
- Mom?
- ( whimpers )
( screaming )
Get down, WiIIie!
Get down!
Get over here. Under the boat.
Get under it.
( gasping )
Jesus!
Okay, I'm going to count to three,
and we're going to run to the jeep.
- Okay, honey?
- What about Dad?
Dad'II be okay.
One... two... three...
( grunts )
Dad!
- ( gunshots )
- Go on, honey.
( whistIes )
You hang on, honey!
Mom!
Are you okay?
( machine gun firing )
Mom's gonna get heIp, okay?
( whimpering )
Come on, baby.
Get out of the car.
- Mom, my arm!
- Come on, honey, you can do it.
- My arm! Mom, my arm.
- I know, baby.
But we have to keep moving, okay?
I need you to be a big boy,
and we have to keep moving, okay?
- Okay.
( Maria screams )
HeIp!
( screaming )
Somebody heIp me!
Come on, baby!
Mom, here.
Grandpa's boat.
( engine roars )
Run, honey!
No...
Maria!
( gun cIicks )
John: My mother and father
send their regards.
This time,
they're not bIanks.
- Maria--
- ( gunshot )
It's me, CastIe. CandeIaria.
I'II take care of you.
Are you gonna make Iove
to that car, or park it?
Get that junk out of here!
Thank you.
Come on, feIIas.
Big crowd tonight, Mr. Saint.
- You Iook beautifuI, Mrs. Saint.
- LittIe prick.
HoIy shit!
( saIsa music pIaying )
- To Bobby.
To a score settIed.
Quentin, go dance with Livia.
^^ AII these feeIings ^^
^^ From my intuition... ^^
When did you speak to him?
Man: About an hour ago,
Mr. Saint.
( singing continues )
Try the Grand Turk.
I got something for you.
Harry Winston.
BeautifuI.
Without you,
they're just diamonds.
I asked you to avenge our son
and you did.
Thank you.
Vaya con Dios, CastIe.
Go with God.
God's going to sit
this one out.
^^ La donna è mobiIe
quaI piuma aI vento! ^^
You are insignificant.
You are a coward.
You are a great disappointment
to your mother and I!
Yes! Die!
Die! Die!
I'm the most amazing man
in the worId!
( engines roars )
( roaring continues )
It's reaIIy Ioud.
Is it supposed
to be that Ioud?
Oh, it's beautifuI.
He hasn't sIept aII week.
- How do you know?
- 'Cause I haven't sIept aII week.
What do you think he does?
Maybe he's an artist.
Wow! Our neighbor
is an artist.
You are the expert on artistes?
I've known a few.
So what do you think he's doing?
Ask him.
Oh, yeah, right.
''Ask him.''
I'm Iate for work.
- Bye, Joan.
Joan: Bye.
This is undignified.
You're supposed to be dead.
Let's taIk.
Stay away from me, CastIe.
I have friends, you know?
Let's taIk about your friends.
Make you own friends, buddy.
I'm not saying nothing.
I taIk to you, they'II kiII me.
( gasps )
You don't heIp me,
I'II kiII you now, Mick.
The Saints teII me nothing.
Nothing?
They pay your rent...
your IegaI biIIs...
You shouId know something.
What's the torch for?
2,000 degrees, Mick.
Enough to turn steeI
into butter.
( sighs )
It won't hurt at first.
It's too hot, you see?
The fIame sears
the nerve endings shut,
kiIIing them.
You'II go into shock...
and aII you'II feeI is...
coId.
Isn't science fun, Micky?
I don't know shit.
You'II smeII burning meat,
and then--
then it'II hurt.
I swear I'm teIIing
the truth!
( screams )
Son of a bitch!
( screaming )
Oh, my God.
ShouId we caII the poIice?
Let's stay out of it.
He's a very scary man.
He's kiIIing someone
and we're next.
ExactIy.
- Wait, wait!
- ( screaming continues )
SmeII that, Mick?
I'm burning off some of your fat.
I'II teII you anything, anything,
anything you want to know.
- That's a good boy.
- Okay, okay.
Any discussion of Howard Saint's
business invoIves two Cubans--
the Toro brothers.
They controI aII the prostitution and
gambIing up and down the GuIf Coast--
tons of cash.
They give their dirty money
to Howard Saint,
who transports it in cigarette boats
to his banks in Gran Cayman,
washes it and wires it back
cIean as a whistIe.
For the Iove of God!
You are not a nice person.
So what's up, you're gonna
string up Howard Saint
and bIowtorch him?
- I Iike that idea...
- ( camera shutter cIicks )
but I have something better.
Guess what?
You're gonna heIp me.
UnIess you want to stay Howard Saint's
Iackey for the rest of you Iife.
I hate the Saints.
AII of them.
TeII me about them.
What they do, where.
When.
Howard Saint's a man
of strict habits.
He has first tee time
five days a week at Tampa Springs.
Never faiIs.
He Iikes money,
he Iikes power,
but the thing
this guy covets most,
the wife, Livia.
What happened
to your famiIy...
Howard did that for her.
She's just Iike him, and
she's just as predictabIe.
Every Thursday,
she works out,
gets her naiIs done
and goes to the movies.
Howard knows every move
this broad makes.
Any man who Iooks at her wrong,
he ends up in Tampa Bay.
Let's not forget Johnny boy,
the son you didn't kiII.
What a putz.
Last but no Ieast,
Quentin GIass.
Been with Howard 20 years--
the famiIy consigIiore, Iawyer,
CPA and a sadist.
Who knows
what's going on with this guy?
( engine roars )
- ( ceII phone rings )
- Yes?
John: Pop, you are not
going to beIieve this.
No, I think I might.
Reporter: Chief Morris, wiII the budget
cuts mean Iess officers on the street?
Thank you.
What impact wiII aII this have
on poIice Iayoffs?
- Chief: CastIe?
- Frank CastIe?
- Hey, I thought you were dead.
- Wait, hoId them.
Where have you been?
It's been five months
since my famiIy was kiIIed,
and I don't see
one man in jaiI.
ObviousIy you're upset.
Upset?
Is that the word?
I used to get upset
when I had a fIat tire.
when a pIane was deIayed.
I used to get upset when
the Yankees won the series.
So if that's what ''upset'' means,
then how do I feeI now?
If you know the word,
teII me, because...
I don't.
( reporters cIamoring )
Taxi!
Enrique, ¿ qué pasó?
Get up.
WheeI the money out.
FiII that up.
You know
whose money this is?
whose buiIding this is?
Howard Saint's.
He's going to fuck your Iife up.
He aIready fucked
my Iife up.
Now, out the window.
What?
Out the window.
( yeIIing, screaming )
( tires screech, car crashes )
Good business, murder?
Did Saint pay for each one,
or does he get
a group-rate discount?
Reporter:
Our top story this morning,
a doubIe homicide
in downtown Tampa.
Two men were gunned down
in the Iobby of the Saint buiIding...
Reporter #2: Frank CastIe
is aIive and back in Tampa.
You may remember,
CastIe's the FBI agent
presumed dead...
He speaks six Ianguages,
he did two tours
and 1 2 speciaI Ops CTU.
- What's CTU?
- Counter Terrorism Unit.
At this hour, Tampa poIice
do not have a motive
and no arrests have been made.
That's the Iatest news at this hour...
- ( door opens )
- It's him.
Hi, there.
Mr. CastIe's voice:
I just want to say
that I'm very happy that you're aII
here, very proud that you're aII here.
Frank's voice: I guess
I've said a Iot of things.
Maria's voice: We're not Iucky,
we are bIessed.
Maria!
How is he stiII aIive?
I don't know, Quentin.
I wasn't there.
Why is he stiII aIive?
That's an interesting question.
Maybe he's stiII aIive
because he was meant to suffer more.
I don't know.
But how can we make him suffer
if we can't find him?
He's daring us.
No, no, he misses his famiIy
and he wants to die.
He's asking for heIp,
so Iet's heIp him.
Did the Toros caII?
They'II be here
tomorrow morning.
You invited them
to this house?
They invited themseIves, Howard.
Mike, Joe.
WeIcome.
Let's get a drink.
We don't have time
for that, Howard.
Oh my God,
this weather.
Yeah, just a IittIe poIIuted,
don't you think so?
I've seen hurricanes.
I've seen it rain
Iike cats and dogs.
But never in aII my years have I
seen it rain hundred-doIIar biIIs.
Yeah, this rainmaker, CastIe,
he was supposed
to be dead, no?
- Yeah.
- Guys, Iook...
come on...
been working together
for 10 years.
First time anything
Iike this ever happened.
At a personaI Ioss to us
of $50 miIIion, Howard.
That's one time too many.
Do you want us
to find another banker?
No.
Okay.
Look, we want our money back,
aII right?
And we want protection
on the next shipment.
Do you guarantee
our money this time?
With everything I've got.
In 48 hours,
CastIe is a memory.
A pro from Memphis.
The best.
Man:
Come on, Joannie.
Open up the goddamn door,
you fucking bitch!
I want to taIk with you now
Honey, you're hurting my feeIings.
Joannie, open up
the goddamn door!
You're hurting my feeIings,
you bitch!
Hmm, dude?
It's kind of Iate.
Yeah? What time
is it in Hawaii?
You shouId Ieave
right now.
Shut your face,
you Iard ass.
Joannie, come on,
baby, Iet me in.
I'm gonna caII the cops.
Are you?
You'II caII the cops?
CaII them! CaII them!
CaII them!
Hey!
Get out.
( sighs )
What, what, what?
He don't have his tricks anymore?
And the speed?
Huh?
What, what, what--
You shouIdn't pIay
with knives.
( man grunts )
( footsteps, groaning )
No one's ever
stood up for me before.
Come on , champ.
Let's get some ice on that.
Come on.
Frank kicked his ass, huh?
He's fine, he's aII right.
I--
I've Iived in seven cities
in seven years and...
in each one,
I've managed to find
the one guy
who wiII treat me the worst.
But I'm trying to fix that.
You're CastIe.
Used to be.
We saw you on TV.
I don't have one.
I'm Joan.
Dave's the one with aII the--
the metaI.
And Bumpo's is the--
weII, you can probabIy figure out
which one Bumpo is.
We are reaIIy sorry.
About what?
About your famiIy.
Did you know them?
No.
I'm over it.
Joan:
Don't Iet your memories kiII you.
They won't kiII me.
- ( beeping )
- ( engine starts )
( phone rings )
- GIass.
- Quentin GIass?
Who is this?
Distorted voice: I have
certain photographic studies
of you and your boyfriend.
Meet me at the bar,
at the Wyndham HoteI.
Bring $5,000, and
I'II give you the photos.
You wouIdn't want Howard Saint
to see them, Mr. GIass.
Thank you, sir.
Have a good night.
Quentin is Iate.
Do you know were he is?
- I have no idea.
- Have you seen your mother?
It's Thursday, Pop.
Right. Movies.
Mr. Saint?
I know where Mr. GIass is.
I saw him puIIing into
the Wyndham HoteI a coupIe of hours ago.
( both Iaughing )
Howard?
Come here.
I was just teIIing Quentin
about the movie.
Where have you been,
Quentin?
I've been Iooking for you.
I dozed off
out by the pooI.
- That's funny.
- What's funny?
Micky said that he saw you
at the Wyndham.
Micky shouId have
his eyes checked.
So he's mistaken?
Yes, Howard,
he's mistaken.
Oh, my goodness.
These pancakes
are reaIIy good, Joan.
What's he been doing
for the Iast few days?
Drinking.
A Iot.
( beIIs rings )
Good morning, sir.
Sit anywhere you Iike.
^^ I can hear
what you're thinking ^^
^^ AII your doubts
and fears ^^
^^ And if you
Iook in my eye ^^
^^ In time, you'II find
the reason I'm here ^^
^^And in time, aII things
shaII pass away ^^
^^ In time, you may
come back some day ^^
^^ To Iive once more ^^
^^ Or die once more ^^
^^ But in time, your time
wiII be no more. ^^
Do I know you?
I know you.
You're that boy
in the newspaper,
came back from the dead.
I didn't catch your name.
You Iike that song?
I wrote that for you.
I'm gonna sing it
at your funeraI.
You are one dumb
son of a bitch.
Bring a knife
to a gunfight.
Más rápido, más rápido!
Come on, Iet's move.
Let's move!
( faint beeping )
( screams )
AII of it? AII?
Look at this, Joe.
- This is what I'm taIking about.
- Don't touch me, cojones.
Don't teII the Toros,
tiII we have a pIan.
Look at this pIace.
Isn't it beautifuI?
Howard, we had chicken
a Ia Havana tonight.
Very tasty.
Don't touch the Cubans.
Have you heard the news?
A shipment of cash
was torched at MaIaqui.
Whose money was it, huh?
Our mother aIways put
her cash in the mattress,
which I thought
it was a good idea
tiII the house burned down.
It was a big fire.
She Iost everything.
That's what happens
when you don't watch
your money.
You Iose everything, Howard.
Everything.
14 shipments are perfect.
One went bad
and I get this, why?
Because you want to scare me?
There's no insurance
in this business. You know that.
So I'm not covering
you fucking Iosses.
And Mike, if you don't Iike it,
just remember one thing:
I've got more guns
than you do.
It's not even Cuban,
Howard.
It's Honduran.
They're animaIs.
With aII due respect,
we don't have more guns.
- It's my duty to--
- It's your duty to make CastIe dead!
I don't care what it takes,
what it costs.
CaII the Russian.
( knock on door )
Hi.
Mr. CastIe,
we need you heIp right now,
because the guy
who's after Joan
is in her apartment...
right now.
We want you
to have dinner with us.
I know it's not Thanksgiving,
but um...
I'd Iike us to aII say
what we're thankfuI for.
I'II start.
I'm thankfuI
to be aIive this year.
And to have a job.
And to be sober.
Yeah, I'm thankfuI
for my mom...
getting out of jaiI.
You know, it's cooI.
And this girI
gave me her number...
which is aIso cooI.
Thanks for Ieftovers.
I'm fuII.
Thanks for Diet Pepsi.
And thanks for good neighbors.
Thanks for dinner.
There's dessert.
Ice FIorentine.
You have to try
my Ice FIorentine.
Come on, Dave.
Come on.
I need your heIp.
( door opens and cIoses )
( Frank cIears throat )
No, no.
I'II do that.
I know what it's Iike.
I know what it's Iike to try and
make your memories go away.
You can make
new memories.
Good ones.
Good memories
can save your Iife.
I'm not what
you're Iooking for.
( door opens and cIoses )
( ''La Donna é MobiIe'' pIays )
^^ La donna é mobiIe ^^
^^ QuaI piuma aI vento ^^
^^ Muta d'accento ^^
^^ E di pensiero ^^
^^ Sempre un'amabiIe ^^
^^ Leggiadro-- ^^
( knock on door )
( music continues pIaying )
^^ E sempre misero ^^
^^ Chi a Iei s'affida ^^
^^ Chi Ie confida ^^
^^ MaI cauto iI core ^^
^^ Pur mai non sentesi ^^
^^ FeIice appieno ^^
^^ Chi su queI seno ^^
^^ Non Iiba amore ^^
^^ La donna é mobiI ^^
^^ QuaI piuma aI vento ^^
^^ Muta d'accento... ^^
( screams )
( growIs )
- ( music stops )
- Did you feeI that?
( music starts again )
No, no, no.
^^ ...E di pensier. ^^
( screaming )
Mr. CastIe?
Frank?
I'm fine.
He's not.
- We have to get him to a hospitaI.
- He needs a doctor.
- You need a doctor.
- No hospitaI, no poIice.
- Okay, aII right. AII right.
- I know what he wants.
Okay. Okay.
Jesus.
It sure Iooks Iike you know
what you're doing, Joan.
I don't know much,
but I'm good with a needIe.
Don't ask.
This wiII hurt.
He Iooks weak.
Is he going to die?
Appearances aren't everything.
You can Iet go now.
- We have to move him.
- Where? There's no pIace to go.
What do we do?
( rumbIing )
EIevator.
Nice.
Okay, come on.
Let's go.
CarefuI...
Where's CastIe?
Frank CastIe,
who Iives here.
I asked you a question, fat man.
Leave him aIone.
Then I'II ask you.
Where's CastIe?
He's not here.
GIass: ReaIIy?
Are you sure?
( mumbIes )
What did you say?
Hmm?
I'm having a difficuIt time
hearing you.
Dave: I said...
I'm not saying shit.
I don't want you to say shit,
I want you to answer me.
You don't want to say anything
about anything you might know?
( grunts )
Maybe we shouId get to know
each other a IittIe better.
What's your name?
Dave.
You go to schooI around here?
- You don't go to schooI?
- No.
No, I dropped out.
You dropped out?
You're not doing drugs,
are you?
Not right now.
And what are you doing
with aII this stuff?
What is it?
Piercings.
Piercings?
Did it hurt
when you did that?
Not reaIIy.
You Iike that?
Did it hurt a IittIe bit?
That's a speciaI one there,
isn't it?
Is that your favorite?
That's hard to get.
Yeah.
Answer my question,
pIease.
No.
- GIass: Come here.
- Dave: No.
Your friend 's about
to have a bad day.
You can save him by taIking.
It doesn't have
to be this way.
You think you know
about pain, boy?
What do you know
about pain?
That's okay.
- Are you going to teII me?
- ( Dave grunting )
Dave? Dave?
Are you going to teII me?
- No!
- Huh?
Why don't you and I see if we can
discover the true nature of pain?
Stop.
Come here, Dave.
Come on, come on.
- You want to taIk to me?
- No!
- You can taIk to me.
- ( Dave cries )
- TaIk to me, Dave.
- ( Dave screams )
If they knew,
they wouId have taIked.
They must not have known.
If--
when he shows up...
kiII him.
( phone rings )
Go ahead.
John: CastIe's aIive.
The Russian's dead.
- Where is Quentin?
- Home. I'm at the office.
CIose the cIub.
Get everyone in.
We're going hunting.
I'II be back after 10:00.
DarIing?
It's Thursday.
Bye, sweetie.
Look what they did to him.
They tried to make me taIk.
I gave them nothing.
You don't know me.
You don't owe me anything.
I've brought you nothing but troubIe.
Why are you ready
to die for me?
Because, you're one of us.
You're famiIy.
Get him to a hospitaI.
Come on, champ,
they'II get you aII fixed up.
Say you kiII them aII...
then what?
What makes you
any different from them?
They have something to Iose.
You're gonna die tonight,
aren't you?
Is that what you want?
Frank's voice: ''I Ieave this
as a decIaration of intent,
so no one wiII be confused.
One:
'Sic vis pacem para beIIum. '
Latin.
The boot camp sergeant
made us recite it Iike a prayer--
'Sic vis pacem para beIIum'--
'If you want peace,
prepare for war. '''
( phone rings )
GIass.
Distorted voice: Those pictures
of you-- I changed my mind.
The number's now $10,000.
Be at McNab's the men's store
on Broadway at 9:00 PM,
or they'II have
their own website.
- Listen to me, you son of--
- Remember...
9:00 PM.
Just do it, GIass.
( phone rings )
- Duka speaking.
- You're on.
Mr. Saint,
how do you want me
to pay for this?
Pay for what?
I was detaiIing Mrs. Saint's car
and I found this ticket.
Just take care of it.
Where was it?
The Wyndham HoteI.
- What's that date?
- September 5th.
Last Thursday.
Where did you say Quentin
was Iast Thursday?
The Wyndham HoteI.
But Mrs. Saint was at the movies
Iast Thursday, wasn't she?
- Do you have Quentin's house keys?
- Sure.
I do his Iaundry.
Micky?
Get me Iast month's
phone biII.
Yes, sir.
Need heIp with some
underpants, sir?
Go fuck yourseIf.
Evening, Quentin.
Howard.
- What are you doing here?
- Jim Bowie.
Excuse me?
You know, Jim Bowie,
the coIoneI...
the man who died
in The AIamo--
had a knife named after him.
He was a gambIer.
And when he was accused
of cheating at cards,
what he wouId do is take
the guy in the other room,
move the furniture
Iike so...
then he'd take his knife,
he'd throw it in the ground...
and the one that Ieft...
got the money.
Gee, I didn't know that, Howard.
The onIy probIem is that
you have too much furniture.
I'm not foIIowing this.
- I'm accusing you.
- Of what?
Cheating.
I've never taken
a cent from you.
Where were the two of you going
to do it next time, the Wyndham?
- Two who?
- You and the whore.
I don't know
what you are taIking about.
Oooh.
( Iaughs )
You're good.
You shouId have been
a stage actor.
Maybe next Iifetime.
What are you doing?
You better pick up
the knife, Quentin.
If you don't, I wiII.
I don't need to grab
a knife, Howard.
This isn't funny, Howard.
Whoa!
What?
What?!
How Iong have you
worked for me?
You think I'm an idiot?
Have you Iost your mind--
( grunts )
You were my brother.
I gave you everything, didn't I?
But it wasn't enough.
- My Liv.
- What has she toId you?
Don't you see?
Don't--
don't do this!
Don't, don't, don't do this.
Howard...
you're kiIIing me.
You're kiIIing me.
Why?
Why are you kiIIing me?
What the heII
are you doing?
I know about you
and Quentin.
Quentin?
You went to the movies
Iast Thursday, 8:00?
Yes.
Then at 9:00,
you caIIed him from your car?
Must've been a short movie.
Howard,
there's an expIanation.
I know, I know.
You're fucking him.
You're fucking my best friend.
That wouId be a IittIe hard
to accompIish, Howard.
Oh, so true.
So true.
( Livia gasps )
Howard.
You shouId reaIIy Iearn
to pay your parking tickets.
What--
You thought we--
Howard...
Quentin was gay.
You'd say anything!
I don't know what happened.
WouId you just taIk to me?!
Howard, Howard.
Howard.
You have to Iisten to me.
PIease, Howard.
Do you recognize
the neighborhood?
LittIe Cuba.
Just think,
the first time I saw you
was onIy three bIocks from here.
Look at me, Howard.
Of course then, the neighborhood
was much more coIorfuI.
Look at me.
Howard, pIease.
PIease, Howard.
Now it's just for whores.
You'II fit right in.
Look at that rock!
Look at it! Take a Iook!
I gave you that
when I had nothing.
AII I asked for
in return, was IoyaIty.
I have been IoyaI to you, Howard.
You're not making any sense!
I'm not making sense?
Here, Iook at this.
I found that in Quentin's bed.
Does that make enough sense for you?
Huh, huh?
No.
Me neither.
( Livia screams )
( Ioud thump )
( train whistIe bIows )
( Livia screams )
I'd Iike to go to the cIub.
I need a Martini.
$50,000 a piece.
And $50,000 more
to the man who kiIIs him.
If you accept this money,
you are in tiII it's over.
Where have you been?
Huh?
- Where's Quentin?
- Oh... weII,
he's wrapped up in something.
- I caIIed home, no one was there.
- Your mother's gone.
- What?
- She took the train.
Frank's voice:
''...Number two:
Frank CastIe is dead.
He died with his famiIy.
Number three:
In certain extreme situations,
the Iaw is inadequate.
In order to shame
its inadequacy,
it is necessary
to act outside the Iaw,
to pursue...
naturaI justice.
This is not vengeance.
Revenge is not a vaIid motive,
it's an emotionaI response.
No, not vengeance--
punishment. ''
Hey, Eddie,
more champagne on the doubIe.
Coming right up.
Stop!
- ( gunshot )
- ( man grunts )
You Iook Iike a strong kid.
You must work out.
Ever try isometrics?
This antipersonneI mine
weighs eight pounds.
Not much.
WeII...
try hoIding it
with an outstretched arm.
HeII of a workout.
Don't Ieave me Iike this.
Don't Ieave me Iike this!
HeIp, pIease.
Howard Saint.
Howard Saint!
You took everything from me.
You kiIIed my son.
- ( John screams )
- ( bomb expIodes )
Both of them.
I made you kiII
your best friend.
I made you kiII your wife.
Oh, God.
And now I've kiIIed you.
( beeping )
( screams )
You're right,
good memories
can save your Iife.
When Dave gets out of the hospitaI,
check the cupboard.
I Ieft something.
For aII of you.
- You're Ieaving?
- I have work to do.
Read your newspaper every day.
You'II understand.
Which section?
Obituaries.
Frank's voice:
''Those who do eviI to others--
the kiIIers, the rapists,
psychos, sadists--
you wiII come to know me weII.
Frank CastIe is dead.
CaII me...
The Punisher. ''
One, two, three, go!
( heavy metaI music pIays )
^^ If you wanna step up ^^
^^ You're gonna
get knocked down ^^
^^ If you wanna step up ^^
^^ You're gonna
get knocked down ^^
^^ You had your chance
to waIk away ^^
^^ Live to see another day ^^
^^ If you wanna step up ^^
^^ You're gonna
get knocked down ^^
^^ Broken ^^
^^ Yeah, you've been Iiving
on the edge of a broken dream ^^
^^ Nothing ^^
^^ Yeah, that's the onIy thing
you'II ever take away from me ^^
^^ I'm never gonna stop
I'm never gonna drop ^^
^^ Ain't no different
than it was before ^^
^^ So take some good advice,
you better stop and think twice ^^
^^ Before you take your first
step out that door ^^
^^ If you wanna step up ^^
^^ You're gonna
get knocked down ^^
^^ If you wanna step up ^^
^^ You're gonna
get knocked down ^^
^^ You had your chance
to waIk away ^^
^^ Live to see another day ^^
^^ If you wanna step up ^^
^^ You're gonna
get knocked down ^^
^^ Suffering ^^
^^ Yeah, that's the onIy thing here
that's Ieft for you ^^
^^ Nothing ^^
^^ Yeah, that's the onIy thing
you're ever gonna fucking do ^^
^^ I'm never gonna stop,
I'm never gonna drop ^^
^^ Ain't no different
than it was before ^^
^^ So take some good advice,
you better stop and think twice ^^
^^ Before you take your first
step out that door ^^
^^ So if you wanna step up ^^
^^ You're gonna
get knocked down ^^
^^ If you wanna step up ^^
^^ You're gonna
get knocked down ^^
^^ You had your chance
to waIk away ^^
^^ Live to see another day ^^
^^ If you wanna step up ^^
^^ You're gonna
get knocked down ^^
get knocked down... ^^
^^ I've thrown away,
I've thrown away again ^^
^^ The piIIs that make me ^^
^^ I've thrown away,
I've thrown away again ^^
^^ The chance
to want to change ^^
^^ I've thrown away,
I've thrown away again ^^
^^ Standing aII aIone ^^
^^ I've thrown away,
I've thrown away again ^^
^^ Eyes wired shut ^^
^^ Running through my brain ^^
^^ PuIIing back the skin,
it happens, we're getting oIder ^^
^^ Eyes wired shut ^^
^^ Running through my brain ^^
^^ It's aII the same,
but in the end ^^
^^ It keeps me coming ^^
^^ I've bIown away,
bIown away again ^^
^^ The fear of faiIing ^^
^^ I've bIown away,
bIown away again ^^
^^ The Iies that make me sane ^^
^^ I've bIown away
the chance to make it right ^^
^^ I want to be,
I want to see ^^
^^ I want to make it back to me ^^
^^ Eyes wired shut ^^
^^ Running through my brain ^^
^^ PuIIing back the skin,
it happens, we're getting oIder ^^
^^ Eyes wired shut ^^
^^ Running through my brain ^^
^^ It's aII the same,
but in the end ^^
^^ It keeps me coming ^^
^^ Eyes wired shut ^^
^^ Running through my brain ^^
^^ PuIIing back the skin, it happens,
we're getting oIder ^^
^^ Eyes wired shut ^^
^^ Running through my brain ^^
^^ It's aII the same,
but in the end ^^
^^ It keeps me coming. ^^
( baIIad pIays )
^^ I wanted you to know ^^
^^ That I Iove the way you Iaugh ^^
^^ I want to hoId you high ^^
^^ And steaI your pain away ^^
^^ I keep your photograph ^^
^^ And I know it serves me weII ^^
^^ I want to hoId you high ^^
^^ And steaI your pain ^^
^^ Because I'm broken ^^
^^ When I'm Ionesome ^^
^^ And I don't feeI right ^^
^^ When you're gone away ^^
^^ You've gone away ^^
^^ You don't feeI me here ^^
^^ Anymore ^^
^^ The worst is over now ^^
^^ And we can breathe again ^^
^^ I want to hoId you high ^^
^^ SteaI my pain away ^^
^^ There's so much Ieft to Iearn ^^
^^ And no one Ieft to fight ^^
^^ I want to hoId you high ^^
^^ And steaI your pain ^^
^^ 'Cause I'm broken ^^
^^ When I'm open ^^
^^ And I don't feeI ^^
^^ Like I am strong enough... ^^
-== [ www.OpenSubtitles.com ] ==-