Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org
Please, no! Someone help me!
Anybody! Please!
No! Get away from me!
Daddy?
Daddy!
I'm hungry.
I know. Me too.
Don't worry. It's all
gonna be over soon.
Hello?
Someone there?
♪ Told you it's the Sandman ♪
♪ Here comes the Sandman ♪
- Daddy?
- Oh, jeez! Oh!
Hey, I told you to
wait in the car.
It's here, isn't it?
Mm-hmm.
Okay, let's go. Let's go.
Watch it.
Okay.
We have to go out
the back, okay?
Let's go. We gotta go.
Go, go, go.
Go, go, go. Okay, almost there.
Daddy!
Okay, they probably
have a key up front.
I'm scared.
All right, remember what Dr.
Elliot told you to do
whenever you get scared?
Just close your eyes and
count back from five.
Okay?
Okay.
I'll be right back, okay?
Five.
Four.
Three.
Two.
One.
See? Everything's gonna be...
Daddy?
Daddy!
♪
♪ Don't have a horse
in this race ♪
♪ Or a smile on my face ♪
♪ I don't need to come
clean when I meet you ♪
♪ I'm a live machine ♪
All right, you can
lean back a little
and rest your head in your hand.
♪
Wanna bring in the stool?
Sort of drape your leg over.
And lose the bra.
Okay, hold it.
Move those to the selects.
- These two?
- Yeah.
All right.
How come you don't pose?
'Cause somebody has
to take the pictures.
Yeah, but you're hotter than
half the girls in here.
- Only half?
- Uh-huh.
And I suppose you'd want me to
take my clothes off too, right?
Is that an offer?
There is just one
little problem.
What's that?
You'd have to figure out how
to take the lens cap off.
- I'd have figured that out.
- Oh.
Eventually.
This is Claire.
When was the last time
you saw your brother?
It had been awhile.
He moved around a lot.
He ever say why?
When you have a rough childhood,
it's hard to feel comfortable.
Any idea what he
was doing upstate?
Is this about my brother's
death or my brother?
Answer the question.
No. No idea.
And you had no contact with him?
Every once in a while I
would get an email, okay?
That's it.
What is this about? Did
he do something wrong?
Parker, Arizona.
Crawford, Colorado.
Farmington, New Mexico.
Each of these were taken when
your brother was either living
or staying within five
miles of the scene.
Now, I'm gonna ask you again.
Do you have any idea what your
brother was doing upstate?
All right.
I think we're done here.
Do me a favor.
Stay available...
just in case we have
any more questions.
Wait.
My brother's daughter, Madison.
Where is she?
The child is exhibiting
extreme signs of
post-traumatic stress.
It's not surprising,
given the circumstances.
The police interviewed
her at length,
regarding the death
of her father,
but she was uncooperative.
Has she said anything
about that night?
Madison thinks someone
named "The Sandman"
is responsible for the
death of her father.
The Sandman?
Children often make up boogeymen
to deal with their
real life fears.
Fear of the dark,
fear of the unknown.
I think this Sandman
is Madison's way
of dealing with the
death of her parents.
Is this for her protection?
Ours.
No! Let go of me!
I don't wanna be here anymore!
- I wanna go home!
- Be still!
No! No!
- Let go of me!
How about I give you
something to calm you down?
No!
Hey!
Madison!
- Grab her.
- Come on!
Take her back to the room!
Like I said.
Uncooperative.
Her eyes are so soulful.
I'm Mrs. Farmer.
Department of
Children's Services.
Claire.
My brother told me she
was born en-caul.
It's where the amniotic
sac is still intact.
Apparently, it's special.
It's supposed to
be a sign of luck.
Madison is a lot things.
I wouldn't say
lucky's one of them.
Miss Blake, do you have a
moment where we could...
go somewhere and chat?
Yeah.
The good news, Miss Blake,
is we have a system in place
to help children like your niece
receive the care that she needs.
You mean with someone other
than with her family.
I assumed, with your background,
you wouldn't be seeking custody.
- What does that mean?
- Miss Blake...
Don't you think we should be
talking about this first?
Do you have any experience
raising a child?
No.
- Are you married?
- No.
What about your career?
Okay, look.
I understand that I'm not a
perfect housewife, okay?
But my brother would have
never wanted his daughter
raised by strangers.
Even if those strangers
were better equipped
to see that his daughter
received a proper upbringing?
Am I gonna need a lawyer?
Can you afford one?
Miss Blake, because you are the
girl's only living relative,
no one can prevent you from
taking custody temporarily.
Permanent guardianship,
however, is another matter.
Daddy?
Help! Somebody!
What's happening? Madison?
- She's having a nightmare!
- Madison?
Get away from me!
Four milligrams of ketamine.
Madison, hey, can you hear me?
Can you hear me?
Hey.
There you are. It's all right.
It's just a dream.
Is he gone?
Who?
The Sandman.
Yeah.
He's gone.
You're safe.
Hey, do you know who I am?
Aunt Claire?
You can just call
me Claire, okay?
Hopefully you're gonna come
live with me really soon.
How does that sound?
Don't make promises.
She's just a little girl.
She needs some hope.
She needs to stay here
for further examination.
Indefinitely.
He's scary.
He just wants what's
best for you.
Can you stay with me
till I fall back asleep?
I'll do even better and stay
with you while you're asleep.
How's that sound?
Shortly after she arrived,
Madison started exhibiting
symptoms of night terrors.
After one of the
orderlies was hurt,
we started a policy of
restraining her at bedtime.
Typical patient might suffer
one to two episodes a week.
Madison suffers three
to four a night.
We recommend that Madison
remain in our care
for further observation.
Miss Duffy?
You know you're not supposed to
be out of your room after 11.
Miss Duffy?
I know you're in here somewhere.
Megan, what are you
doing down there?
He... He...
He was... there.
Oh, don't worry about him.
That's just Stanley.
Hi, Stanley!
Let's go.
It's just right through there.
Hey! There she is!
Wyatt, this is Madison.
Madison, this is my...
This is Wyatt.
Hi, Madison.
So what do you think?
I painted the walls,
I got some toys.
Oh. Bow and arrow
for a little girl?
- Yeah.
- Mm-hmm.
Where'd you get all this stuff?
Goodwill.
I had like a $5 budget. Come on.
Yeah, you're right.
I'm gonna...
Yeah.
Oh, this is a good song, right?
♪
When can I go home?
Well, um...
This is your home.
It's your new home.
Here with me.
Um, what about Wyatt?
Wyatt? Sometimes.
I know this is a big change.
It's really different.
I know I can't replace your dad,
but I promise you,
no matter what, I'm...
I'm gonna try my best.
You wanna get settled, and
I'll make us some dinner?
See you in a minute, okay?
Hello?
Claire?
- Help! Help me!
- Hey, Madison, hey.
You're okay.
It's just a bad dream.
That's it.
Is he gone?
Who?
The Sandman.
He followed me.
Honey, it's just
you and me here.
I promise.
What happened?
He grabbed me.
Madison...
Can I sleep in your bed tonight?
Of course, come on.
The investigation suffered
another setback today
when this man, Colton Blake,
previously named a
person of interest,
was found dead himself
last weekend,
apparently of a heart attack.
Police found his body
at the general store.
Investigation is looking
further into it.
Blake is survived by sister
Claire and daughter Madison.
Madison is currently in
the custody of her aunt,
who lives in Los Angeles.
Now, the unusually hot weather
looks like it's gonna continue
through the end of the
week, and DWP is...
Whatever it is, she thinks
it followed her here.
All of the nightmares about her
parents and the boogeyman...
I don't know. It feels like
it's just Madison's way
of working through her grief.
Yeah, and last night, get...
Get this, she woke up last
night with bruises on her arm.
I swear they weren't
there before.
No, you should see the
way she kicks and flails
in her sleep.
It's a wonder she doesn't
put me in the hospital.
No, I know.
I understand.
All right, I'll
talk to you later.
Madison? Madison,
it isn't funny.
You're gonna give
me a heart attack!
There was an old woman
who lived in a shoe.
She had so many children,
she didn't know what to do.
She gave them some broth
without any bread.
There was an old woman
who lived in a shoe.
She had so many children,
she didn't know what to do.
What'd I tell you about
getting out, boy?
What'd I tell you about that?
Sit down.
You know, I saw a girl
on the news last night.
Looked just like you.
Your daddy killed
them, didn't he?
Yeah.
That's why you were running.
Yeah, go ahead, run away.
Hey.
What's going on?
Here she comes
again, that woman.
Hey, what the hell
was that about?
The police were looking
for her father, you know.
He's dead. Don't you think
she's suffered enough?
What the hell you doing
with a kid anyway, huh?
All that loud music,
people coming in and out
all hours of the night
I work out of my house.
Well, not for long,
which, incidentally,
is what I told that woman who
came by your house today.
Yeah.
What?
What the hell?
Goddamn it!
Ah.
Come on.
What the...
Start.
Start, come on, start!
Start!
Come on!
Damn straight. Okay.
Ahh...
Good. Let's check your arms.
Raise your left arm for me.
Does that hurt?
Let's take a look.
Madison, can you tell
me what happened here?
Can your aunt?
I'm, uh...
I'm renting an old house, so...
You know kids.
Try to be more careful, okay?
I'd like to see her
again in a week,
see how they're healing.
Sure.
Ms. Blake, let's make
sure there aren't
any more accidents, okay?
Go inside, okay?
I'll be in in a minute.
Whoa, whoa. Stay off
the property, please.
I live across the street.
Can't you just tell
me what's going on?
Carbon monoxide poisoning.
Looks like the garage door
may have malfunctioned.
All this for an accident?
Hey! Hey, I've seen you before.
Who are you? What
are you doing here?
Ma'am, is there
gonna be a problem?
No! There's no problem.
I'm going.
So did something
happen to Stanley?
Um, there was an accident.
Are they sure?
Sure about what?
That it was an accident.
Madison...
do you know something about
what happened to Stanley?
Madison.
- Madison!
- Go away!
Madison, do you know what
happened to Stanley?
I said go away!
All right, Colton, let's see
what you've been up to.
Oh, Jesus.
So you think your brother is
responsible for all of this.
The police were asking
a lot of questions,
and then Stanley...
Okay, look, even if your brother
was responsible for any of this,
he's dead.
- I know.
- I thought you saw the body.
I know.
Okay, so what did
Madison have to say?
Nothing.
She won't talk to me.
I don't know what to do.
I do.
Madison?
You in here?
Honey, wait, no.
Madison, we need you
to tell us something,
and I want you to try to be
really honest with me, okay?
Did your daddy ever...
Did he ever hurt anyone?
Honey, please, you can trust us.
He said he was
trying to protect me
from the bad people.
That's what he
said he was doing?
Trying to protect you?
Daddy never hurt anyone.
Who did, Madison?
Who killed all those people?
Wyatt.
Please don't be mad.
Sweetheart, I'm not mad.
I just need you to tell me.
I promise you can trust me.
Sometimes, when I
get really scared,
he comes out and hurts people.
What do you mean, he comes out?
I can't control it.
It just happens.
Like with Stanley and Daddy.
Honey, your dad had
a heart attack.
And Stanley was an accident. I
spoke to the police myself.
He wanted to get rid of me.
Look, are you saying...
that you think that
you made this guy
come out and kill people?
I didn't mean to!
I didn't want to
hurt any of them!
I just got scared.
The Sandman is a
character in a book.
You can't bring it to life.
I can!
Ever since I was little,
Daddy said I could
make things happen,
but he said it's okay 'cause
it's gonna be over soon.
What did he mean by "over soon?"
All right, cool. I've
heard enough of this.
Madison, we're trying to
have a serious conversation,
and you're not playing.
I don't think that you should
have this book anymore, okay?
Come on.
I'm not lying!
Why don't you just sit here,
and you think about it!
- Wyatt?
- When you're ready to talk,
we'll come in, and we'll listen.
I told you!
Yeah, yeah, I heard.
The Sandman, okay?
Why don't you pay a semblance
of respect to your aunt,
after everything's
she's done for you!
But you don't wanna do that
because you're acting
like a spoiled child
who wants to make up things out
of books and kills people.
Stop yelling at me!
- Look, this isn't a good time.
- I hope I'm not interrupting.
Mrs. Farmer, please,
it's been a long day.
And you are?
I'm Wyatt, her
sometimes boyfriend.
Can I ask what this is about?
This afternoon, I received
a rather alarming call
from your pediatrician.
He said your niece had a
number of bruises on her arm.
What's she talking about?
Nothing. Look, I
explained to him
that she was playing
in the house.
- She fell.
- He also told me
he was unable to rule
out physical abuse.
Okay, hold on. Claire
would never hurt a child.
Maybe it wasn't Claire.
Unfortunately, even the
suspicion of abuse
is enough to suspend
temporary custody
until an investigation
can be completed.
I have a letter from the
state authorizing me
to remove Madison
from your home.
- Wait, what?
- Ms. Blake,
don't make this any harder
than it needs to be.
Okay, just hold...
Maybe we ought to consider
this a good thing.
No! You're not taking her.
Ms. Blake, allow
me to remind you
that if you don't
participate willingly,
I will be forced to
take punitive action.
Fine, go ahead.
Have it your way, Ms. Blake,
because I will be back with
the proper authorities.
Great! And we'll be here!
Claire, seriously.
Madison, honey, Wyatt
and I are gonna outside
and have a little adult
conversation, okay?
It's me.
No. Unfortunately the
aunt's being stubborn.
We're probably gonna
have to call the police.
You know what?
I'm gonna have to call you back.
- Are you out of your mind?
- What?
You know she could come back
with the police and arrest you.
Do you what would happen if
they got their hands on her?
Claire, this isn't some
kid who just wets the bed
or plays with matches, okay?
You are way, way out
of your league here.
My brother spent a long
time trying to protect her.
Ever think maybe he was trying
to protect peopfrom her?
There's a big difference
there, don't you think?
Our whole childhood, we
were just shuffled around.
My mom was a drunk.
My dad was gone before
I was even born.
All we had was each other.
I owe it to him to protect her.
Madison?
Are you in here, sweetie?
Don't you think it's better
that she's with someone
that knows how to handle her?
Who? The bad people?
Wyatt, that's what
she calls them.
How many people has she hurt?
Because what I think
we should be doing
is talking about the
definition of "bad" here.
Madison, I wanna help.
Go away.
It's not safe for you here.
I'm gonna to take you
someplace better,
where you'll be happy.
I'm happy here!
You can't stay here, Madison.
I know you don't
understand right now,
but one day you will.
There's no need to worry.
I'm not the one I'm
worried about.
Hey, what's going on?
I'm sorry.
You're doing fine.
Remember your breathing.
You're doing great.
Something's wrong.
What's happening?
What is going on? No!
What is happening?
Breathe, breathe.
Female, 28, intrapartum.
She's crowning!
Wyatt doesn't like me.
That's not true.
Right?
Madison, I think we should talk
about what happened last night.
You said it was all
gonna be over soon.
What did you mean by that?
Is that what you were doing
when your daddy died?
Did your dad find a
way to stop this?
We gotta call the police.
And say what? There's
nothing left.
There's no body,
there's no evidence.
What do you suggest? I'm
not just gonna sit around
while she wishes everyone
into a cornfield.
I told you how important
she is to me.
And you saw what she
did to that woman.
What she almost did to you.
I'm... I'm worried about you.
She wouldn't hurt me.
Like she wouldn't
hurt your brother?
The detectives were asking
what he doing upstate.
What if my brother found a
way to help her stop this?
More like he was wishing
not to get thrown in jail.
Would you watch her
for a couple hours?
- Are you serious?
- Please, I just...
I don't want her to go outside.
That's the smartest thing
I've heard you say all day.
Are you gonna help me or not?
Couple hours.
That's it.
Okay.
Thanks for letting
me take a look.
You know, she hasn't
stopped crying about it.
I gotta say, Ms. Blake,
we've been over this car
half a dozen times,
and no one's come up
with a stuffed animal.
I know. I just figured if I
looked, maybe I'd find it.
She hasn't said
anything, has she?
She's an eight-year-old little
girl who lost her father,
spends most of her time
crying in her room.
Detective.
I'll need you to sign
this access form.
Hi, you've reached Dr. Amanda.
Please leave a message.
Hi, my name is Claire Blake.
I believe you spoke
to my brother Colton
about my niece Madison.
Call me, please.
Hello?
Wyatt?
Where are we?
Well, it's a surprise.
Is Claire coming?
I thought that this should be
something we could do together.
Get to know each other
a little better, hmm?
Okay.
Why don't you go ahead?
I'll be out there.
You can do this.
Are you coming?
Pretty cool, huh?
Yeah.
Hey, how about that
doll right over there?
Where?
Right over by the...
the truck.
You see it?
Just to the right.
I don't see anything
but old junky cars.
What are you doing?
Madison.
- Were you gonna hurt me?
- Calm down.
This is why you didn't
bring Claire, isn't it?
Do you want her to get hurt?
I don't.
Madison, okay.
Okay, I need you to calm down.
Madison, okay, look, I
made a mistake, okay?
Madison?
Please.
I think you should run now.
What? Wha...
- Sir.
- Bring her in, Heller.
Yes, sir.
♪ Yo-ho, all aboard
'cause here we go ♪
♪ Time to hoist the
anchor and sail off ♪
♪ Come and take a journey
to places unknown ♪
♪ So pack your bags and
plot your course ♪
Extra whipped cream,
just like you asked.
Thanks.
Thank God.
I was so worried about you.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
Where's Wyatt?
Madison?
What did you do to Wyatt?
I'm ready to go home now.
Sure.
Can we stop somewhere
on the way home?
Yeah, okay.
I need to take this. I'll
meet you there, okay?
- Hi.
- Claire?
Yes. Um...
Is she with you now?
- Can you help her?
- Yes.
Are you familiar with the theory
of hypnotic image therapy?
Well, it started as a
way to treat soldiers
who were suffering
from acute PTSD.
Doctors used hypnosis to
rewrite their nightmares,
so they no longer
felt threatening.
You want to hypnotize my niece?
Your brother believed she was
using the power of the caul
to manifest a
nightmarish figure.
The Sandman.
However, if we could remove
this so-called Sandman
from her mind...
She wouldn't be able
to bring it to life.
Exactly.
You haven't seen what
she's capable of.
I don't know if messing with
her mind is such a good idea.
Your brother believed it
was a risk worth taking.
All I want is to give Madison
a chance at a normal life.
I'm so sorry for
everything I've done.
I know people say I'm special,
but I don't want to
be special anymore.
I don't want anyone
else to get hurt,
especially not Claire.
Do you think they
know I'm sorry?
Honey, yes.
Of course they do.
Madison?
Your father may have found
someone that can help you.
I don't know anything about
her, but if there's a chance...
Yes, yes.
Yes.
Look out!
Get the girl! Move!
You shouldn't have hurt Claire.
Careful.
We got movement.
Multiple bogeys. Repeat,
multiple bogeys.
Negative on visual, sir.
Careful.
What just happened?
I'm having trouble
with my scope.
Where's your signal?
Damn thing!
Night vision's out.
I got nothing.
Target secured.
Where is she?
- What have you done to her?
- Don't worry.
I have absolutely no intention
of hurting your niece.
My department has studied
a lot of caul children
over the years.
But none of them as powerful
or as dangerous as Madison.
No.
Now, can you imagine having
the abilities that she has,
without the patience or the
discipline to control them?
Please, please, just
let me see her.
She mentioned something to
the doctor called "Sandman."
She ever mention that to you?
You wanna know
about the Sandman?
That's a children's book.
Her father read it to her
when she was a little girl.
She says it gave her bad dreams.
I truly believe
that in her fear,
she literally brought
her nightmare to life.
Extraordinary.
Look, she's just a little girl.
All she wants is for it to stop.
But I don't want it to stop.
I wanna nurture it,
I wanna develop it,
and I wanna train it.
You've seen what
she's capable of.
Come here. I wanna
show you something.
Madison!
What is this?
We're completely
shielded from her.
Makes it safer.
I'd like to start with
a levitation test.
We can begin.
Our most successful
subject to date
was able to levitate this
ball more than three inches.
Let's see how young
Madison can do.
Madison, I'd like you to
try levitating the ball.
No.
Madison, please.
The sooner that you
cooperate with us,
the sooner I can let
you see Claire.
You'd like that, wouldn't you?
Good.
Then, please.
Concentrate.
Focus on the ball.
Extraordinary.
I want to go home.
Soon, Madison.
I want to go home now!
What's going on?
Sedate her! Now!
I believe that with
the proper regimen,
we can train her to
control her impulses.
So you want me to go
before the committee
and explain what?
That we're going to tame an
eight-year-old mass murderer?
She's not malicious.
Neither is the sweet
family pit bull,
until it mauls your
three-month-old child.
I believe in her potential.
Sorry, Dr. Valentine.
I'm initiating cleanup protocol.
Give me a chance with her.
She's too valuable.
No.
I'm sorry, Dr. Valentine.
We've been asked
to clear the room.
No.
- We have to leave now.
- No.
No, no, please!
- No!
- We have to leave now.
- It's out of my hands!
- Please!
It's out of my hands.
Lock it down!
No, no, please! I
have to help her!
Go to the end of the hall,
down to sublevel five.
Follow the steam pipes.
That'll get you out of here.
Take my car.
You drive away from here
and never look back, understand?
Hey!
Let's go.
She went down this way!
Stay here.
Here!
Madison.
Easy, now, easy.
Don't do it, kid.
Madison, no.
Oh! Wha...
No!
Let's go.
Which car is it?
I want you to watch
the pendulum.
Empty your mind.
There is nothing
but the pendulum
and the sound of my voice.
You see nothing else.
You feel nothing else,
just the pendulum.
Back and forth.
Your eyelids are feeling heavy.
You feel yourself
drowning in the darkness.
Let go, Madison.
Let your body sink deeper...
and deeper.
I'll count down from five.
When I reach one,
you will be asleep.
Five.
Watch the pendulum.
Four.
Hear my voice.
Three.
Your body is sinking.
Two.
One.
Hello?
Where are you?
I'm in the office.
Go to the door and
tell me what you see.
I'm in the morgue.
This is important.
I need you to find the Sandman.
I don't want to.
I'll be right here
with you, I promise.
I can't.
I need you to find him,
so I can pull him out.
Do you understand me?
Please.
It's important.
Do what she says, Madison.
Hello?
Anyone in here?
He's here.
Okay.
Okay, listen, this is important.
I need you to grab him.
And no matter what happens,
do not let him go.
I can't!
Yes, you can, Madison, grab him!
I got him!
Hurry!
Heed these words.
When this nightmare ends,
you will be free of
this child forever.
You will be bound to
this child no more!
I can't hold on!
I can't hold on anymore!
When I snap my
fingers, you'll awake.
Wake, Madison!
You okay?
I'm fine.
Do you think it worked?
You think he's gone?
You okay?
Is something wrong?
She brought him to life!
Claire!
Run!
Five, four, three, two, one.
Leave her alone!
Claire!
Come on!
Wake up!
Come on. I have an idea.
You stay.
Now!
♪
♪ Out of the shadows ♪
♪ The dark side ♪
♪ Image is forming
before your eyes ♪
♪ The demon's coming ♪
♪ He hears your cries ♪
♪ Your deepest fears
materialize ♪
♪ Don't go down ♪
♪ You better hide ♪
♪ Don't make a sound ♪
♪ Till the morning comes round ♪
♪ You better stay awake
'cause he's on his way ♪
♪ Beware the Sandman ♪
Well, it's official.
You're stuck with me.
Are we gonna stay here?
Uh, I don't know.
I was thinking maybe
somewhere new.
Can we move to Hawaii?
Hawaii?
I was thinking
more like Arizona.
Which reminds me, little lady,
we need to talk about you
going back to school.
Mom!
What?
Should we celebrate tonight?
Get some takeout?
Can we get ramen noodles?
Or we could splurge and get
some real Japanese food.
♪
♪ Here comes the Sandman ♪
♪ Take me to Dreamland ♪
♪ Please, Mr. Sandman ♪
♪ I want to dream
about you and me ♪
♪ Just close my eyes
and I can see ♪
♪ The one that I adore ♪
♪ Come walking through my door ♪
♪ You're the only one
I'm wishing for ♪
♪ Here comes the Sandman ♪
♪ I want to dream
about you and me ♪
♪ Just close my eyes
and I can see ♪
♪ The one that I adore ♪
♪ Come walking through my door ♪
♪ You're the only one
I'm wishing for ♪
♪
Please rate this subtitle at www.osdb.link/5uhc3
Help other users to choose the best subtitles