Come on!
Look out girls, here we go.
Look to the left.
Paddle!
- Can you see her?
- Mummy!
Come on!
Hold on!
Christ!
Yes!
- Mummy!
- Hi, guys!
Oh, Jessie. Yeah!
That was amazing.
- Oh, you girls were screaming.
- All right, Jessie?
- That wasn't so bad, was it?
- No, it was a piece of piss.
Whoo!
Bitch!
- Bit more, bit more.
- Go on, Paul. Fish her out.
There. Got you.
- You all right?
- Yeah.
It's freezing. I can't feel my fingers.
Heave!
Jessie, Jessie.
Ah, come here. Oh, babe.
It was just amazing.
Would you like to do that?
Come on, Jessie, it's freezing.
Let's go back to the car.
Go with your Daddy.
- I'll just help the girls.
- All right.
It's OK, you go on. We can finish up here.
You sure? Thanks, guys.
I'll see you at the hotel.
See you.
Jess, shall I phone Rachel's mum?
See if Rachel wants
to come to dinner on Thursday?
Yeah? OK.
When she comes round,
she can help us plan your birthday party.
Are you going to invite any boys this time?
Are you OK? You seem a bit distant.
I'm fine.
Jess?
Jessie!
Sh, sh. I'm sorry. She's gone.
- I'm sorry.
- No!
No, no.
No, no, no.
She's gone, Sarah. Shh.
Shh.
Well, it's mud, blood and beer...
or sweet Jesus.
Great. Turn that shite off.
That's frightening.
Listen, we don't have to do this, you know.
We can head back and stay in town.
Get wasted, go to a barn dance.
Now that is frightening.
You're right, we don't have to do this.
But I'm not going to be the one to tell Juno.
She's a piece of work, man.
She always brings us out into the middle of...
Well, look at it.
- She came to Scotland last year.
- Yeah, and left pretty quickly.
Sarah! Beth!
Juno.
You look fantastic.
Ah, come here. Oh.
Let me look at you. Wow!
Everything is going to be fine.
Better. It's going to be great.
Becca and Sam can't wait to see you.
Why don't you go in?
- Give me these.
- Yeah.
Thanks.
- OK?
- Yeah, OK.
Ooh, very nice.
- How is she?
- Well, she's here.
One step at a time, eh?
Hey, hey, hey!
Who are you calling a fucking cheater?
I'm calling you a fucking cheater.
Hello!
Hey!
Hello.
- You do look really good.
- Oh, you look amazing.
- Hey!
- Let me put the bags down.
Oh, so nice to see you.
- We're starving.
- OK, go, go.
- What have you got?
- Er, well, there's a bit of...
Sam. Sam.
Thank you so much for your letter.
It meant a lot to me.
Oh, Sarah, look,
I'm so sorry that I couldn't be there.
You know, mid-terms and...
You know, Sam is going to be Doctor Van Ney
in like a year's time.
No!
- Please tell me it's longer than that?
- I am so proud of my little sister.
- Who wants a drink?
- Yes! Me!
- Brandy shot?
- Yeah, yeah.
- So, Beth...
- Mm-hm?
I hear it all starts falling apart past 25?
Is that what they teach you
at medical school, yeah? To take the piss?
- Cheeky bitch!
- Ow!
Can anyone make me feel any older?
- Oh, here we go.
- Hello.
- Hi, you must be the teacher.
- Beth, Sarah, this is Holly.
Juno's protégé.
- I always thought Juno would eat her young.
- Oh, nice.
I'm well able to handle myself,
thanks very much.
I've heard about you.
You're that mentalist that jumps off buildings.
- Base jumping. You should try it, seriously.
- So you live in America now?
Ran out of things to jump off in Galway,
you know.
I'm always searching for the next big high.
- Sure you'd know all about that.
- Sorry?
Juno showed me a photo
of when you used to climb together.
I found this classic picture. Ah!
- Oh, no!
- Look at the state of us!
- Oh, my God. That's bad.
Sexy!
Love each day.
Used to be something Paul used to say.
Anyway... cheers.
Here's to our adventure.
- Skol.
- Cheers.
Come on, light, you bastard.
So, have you done Boreham Caverns before?
I saw it in a book once.
It's for tourists. It's not adventure.
Might as well have hand rails
and a fucking gift shop.
If you're a caver, jumper, climber...
...you just do it and not give a shite.
Or the thing that's bigger than you will get you.
You want adventure, Holly?
When have I ever let you down?
What?
Holly, tomorrow is going to be awesome. OK?
Take this. You need it.
What about Josh, Sam?
Are you guys still together?
Kind of. Sort of.
Different... shifts.
Oh, my God.
- Oh, my Jesus!
- What do you think, eh?
Don't say a fucking word, all right?
It was a Christmas present.
Shut up.
- What about you Holly? Got a man?
- Oh...
I'm a sports fuck like Juno.
- What?
- Rebecca, too, I think.
But when I'm older,
I want to have lots of babies.
Beth, did Sarah tell you that...
Oh!
Wakey.
I feel like road kill. Give me five minutes.
Five minutes.
Good morning, my little ones.
Wakey, wakey.
- Good morning.
- Is that what you call it? It's fucking freezing!
Holly!
We're leaving at seven. Don't be late.
Try that.
The queen is dead.
Long live... the fucking queen.
Beth, you're not driving.
- If you drive we'll never get there.
- Paper, scissors, stone.
- Come on.
- Oh, you're a dick.
- Go on.
- OK.
- There you go.
- No, wait, babe. Best of three.
I'll drive. Right?
Ladies, group photo.
You'd better hurry it up. We're running late.
- I look like shit.
- We all look like shit. Just give me a smile.
- Hat? No hat?
- No hat.
- No hat, no hat.
- All right.
- Run, run, run, run.
- Say "sausage"!
Sausage!
- Sarah, slow down a bit.
- I'm having fun.
She's having fun.
Whoa! Turn, turn, turn there.
- Let's off road.
- Great.
You should have some water.
Trying to set this watch is impossible.
The buttons are too fucking small.
- Leave it alone.
- Why do you wear it, anyway?
- My boyfriend gave it to me, it's sentimental.
- It's fucking mental.
Any guy that gave that to me, I'd dump him.
Juno, are you sure this is the right way?
- Relax, I've never been lost in my life.
- Marvellous.
- So have you done these caves before?
- No.
But they are only level two.
Quite safe, don't worry.
- I wasn't.
- The only danger is that I might fall asleep.
Boreham Caves.
More like boredom caves.
- Nice parking.
- Thanks.
This one time in Galway.
When I free-climbed the cathedral,
a priest chased me
down the whole of the ground floor.
That was brilliant.
- I shouldn't have wasted the effort, though.
Holly, shut up.
Rebecca, leave her alone.
OK, guys, let's get moving. We're running late.
Come on, keep up.
Hey, Holly, wait up.
Move it, short arse.
Oi, Carter, get to the back.
Come on, you lazy bastard.
You finally caught up with me.
- Juno, are we there yet?
- There's a river about half a mile ahead.
When we reach it,
we follow it up to the mouth of the cave, OK?
How does she know there's a river up ahead?
I can't hear a thing.
She can probably smell it.
She came up here last week
to check the route out.
It's rule number one -
file a flight plan and stick to it.
- And rule number two?
- Don't go wandering off.
You think it's dark when you turn out the lights.
Well, down there it's pitch black.
- You can get dehydration, disorientation...
- Yeah, yeah, yeah.
- ...claustrophobia...
- Blah, blah.
...panic attacks, paranoia, hallucinations,
visual and aural deterioration...
Hey!
Eurgh.
Yeah, lovely, Holly. A real Kodak moment.
- Don't touch it.
- You wouldn't want to piss it off.
What do you think did that, Sam? A bear?
What is this? Nature Detectives?
- It could have been Big Foot. Come on.
- Sam, stop poking it with a fucking stick.
This is it.
- You're having a laugh!
- Afraid not.
I'm an English teacher,
not fucking Tomb Raider.
You'll be fine.
OK, Sarah, Beth, you're up next.
Sam, stay with Becca.
Do what she does and you'll be fine.
Holly, safety first.
I don't want any stunts this time.
- You OK? See you down there.
- No.
Make sure your cow's tail is locked
there and there. You hold on to this like that.
Look, I have done this before, you know?
- I'm only looking after you.
- And I appreciate it, in small doses.
You gotta see this place.
It's beautiful!
You won't believe this, Beth.
- Oh, shit!
Shit, shit, shit.
Oh, my God, I'm gonna die.
Ah, piece of piss.
Oh, my God!
It's incredible.
Clear!
It's Holly.
Shit, move!
Holly, you do this safely,
in order, following my lead. OK?
Take it slow and easy.
Juno.
- Smart arse.
It's OK. It's OK. It's OK.
They're gone. They're gone now. Look.
One bat, two bats.
50 bats.
Holly, fuck off.
Which way?
There's only one way out of this chamber
and that's down the pipe.
OK.
It's a drop.
OK?
Holly, chuck us your bag.
Oh, my God!
Find anything good?
- Jesus Christ!
- Come on, let's eat.
- Holly, would you take a break?
- I just want to take a few more shots.
This cave is a lot cooler than I thought.
Hey?
Not hungry.
Are you OK?
Juno, I won't break. I'm fine.
- I asked you for this.
- I know.
Um, Sarah?
I haven't had a chance to say that I'm...
really sorry I didn't stay around longer
after the accident.
Anyway...
...we're all here for you now, OK?
Yeah.
Look, sorry. I'm feeling a bit out of it.
It's probably jet lag.
- So I'm just going to take a look around, OK?
- Yeah, OK.
Why don't you try and find us
the way through, huh?
Hey, don't go too far.
What's up with her?
She looks like she's seen a ghost.
She's fine.
I've found the next passage!
- That's it? It's a bit small, isn't it?
- Hey, hey, hey!
- I don't get this.
- What?
This is not how I imagined it
from reading the book.
That's why I don't trust books.
Leaves too much room for interpretation.
Something wrong?
- No.
- It's nothing.
I'm taking point, guys.
Careful. Just find the way through.
We'll wait here.
Sarah?
- Shit.
- Are you still behind me?
Yes.
Shit!
Sarah?
Guys, it's Sarah, I think she might be stuck.
I am stuck!
All right, Sarah.
Calm down, just relax.
I can't fucking relax.
Fuck, fuck!
Sarah, you have to calm down and the only way
you're going to do that is to breathe.
OK, breathe slowly. Just keep breathing.
I can't. I can't.
- I can't fucking breathe.
- Sarah, OK, listen to me.
Just listen to my voice, yeah?
Sarah, I'm coming. I'm coming back.
OK? OK.
Sarah, OK?
Listen to me, keep breathing. OK? Hey.
Hey, hey.
OK. OK. OK.
- Look here at me, Sarah, hey?
- Help me.
What are you so worried about, Sarah?
Look at me.
OK, breathe. Breathe, OK?
Hey, hey, hey. Listen to me.
- Listen to me. What are you so afraid of?
- I can't fucking move!
You can move. Sarah, look at me, look at me.
The worst thing that could have happened to
you has already happened and you're still here.
This is just a poxy cave and there's nothing left
to be afraid of, I promise.
OK? OK?
Hey. Hey, listen, listen.
Listen to me, you'll love this one.
How do you give a lemon an orgasm?
God damn it, let me hear you say it.
What do you do? You tickle its citrus.
OK, that's better. Come on.
OK, OK. All right, we're going to move now.
Take hold of my arm, all right?
We're going to move slowly.
That's it, grab my arm, OK?
OK, come on.
Just slowly. Pull on me, OK?
The rope bag. I forgot the rope bag.
OK.
OK, fuck the rope bag. OK, move, now!
Now!
Hurry up!
Sarah, come on!
Sarah, keep hold of the rope!
Sarah?
Oh, ah.
- Are you OK?
- I'm all right.
Is everybody OK? Is everybody OK?
- Don't fucking touch me.
Rebecca?
I'm here, I'm OK.
Beth, are you injured?
No, I'm fine.
- Nobody move until the dust has settled.
- Don't worry, Juno, we're not going anywhere.
You might be right about that.
Jesus.
So what's the story now?
According to the guidebook,
this cave system has three ways out.
This is just one of them.
Isn't that right, Juno?
Juno, that's right, isn't it?
Check the book.
- I didn't bring it.
- What?
No point.
For Christ's sake, Juno.
I knew it. I knew this wasn't right.
You filed a flight plan to mountain rescue?
If we don't report in, they'll come looking for us.
That's how it's supposed to work
except I put in a flight plan for Boreham Caverns
and this isn't Boreham Caverns, is it, Juno?
We're in the wrong fucking cave?
Holly was right.
Boreham Caverns was a tourist trap.
- Don't try and pin this fucking shite on me!
- This is not caving. This is an ego trip.
Rebecca,
I didn't know this was going to happen.
This is exactly what we believe in.
We said, if there's no risk, what's the point?
Don't try and justify this.
Where... Where are we?
It hasn't got a name. It's a new system.
I wanted us all to discover it.
No-one's ever been down here before.
- You're fucking kidding me.
- Oh, God!
How the hell do we get out?
There may not be a way out.
Look, there's no going back now.
We have to find a way out of this chamber
and keep pushing forward.
What the fuck do you think you're doing?
We all trusted you. You told me
this was going to be good for Sarah.
Have you any idea what she's been through?
No, cos you couldn't get away fast enough,
you selfish cow.
You know what, Beth?
We all lost something in that crash.
Just get us out of here.
Look, cave systems
sometimes break ground. It's a small chance.
But if we stay here, we'll die.
Let's go.
Wait!
- What?
Don't move, Sam. Just don't move.
Stay right there.
Oh, shit. No more.
Thanks, Beth.
Now I know how far down it is.
So, what now?
One of us has to get all the way across there
so they can rig a line for you guys.
I have three cams, I need at least three more.
Where's the other rope bag?
Where is it?
We lost it, when the cave collapsed.
Sorry.
Help me.
Come on, Becca.
- Aargh!
- You got it.
Come on, come on.
Come on, Rebecca.
What are you waiting for?
- Fuck.
- Are you OK?
What's wrong?
It's nothing. I'm all right.
OK.
All right, more slack.
More slack, thanks.
Fuck!
Fuck, fuck, fuck.
- OK.
Well done.
OK.
Throw me the right rope.
Come on.
Yeah!
- Now, you make it look easy.
- Yeah, well, you make it look hard.
- Oh.
Don't look down, Beth. Keep going.
- Just keep going.
You're OK. You're safe.
Good. There you go.
Was this about me or you?
It's about us,
getting back to what we used to be.
I wanted us to claim this place, name it.
I thought maybe your name.
Or maybe yours.
You're doing well. Come on.
Come on.
There you are. Come on, give me your hand.
Juno?
We'll need everything we've got.
Haul it in.
Fuck.
Yes!
Reach.
Reach out.
Aargh!
Juno!
No!
Juno, it's OK, we've got you.
OK, pull!
Sam!
Holly, let me pass.
Rebecca, show me your hand.
Let go, let go.
- What does it mean?
- It means we're not the first.
It's a piton, right?
If cavers were here,
there's a better chance of us getting out.
This equipment is at least 100 years old.
No-one uses stuff like this any more.
Besides, if anyone had been down here
and made it out,
they would have named it already.
Becca, are you OK?
I'll live.
Holly, how does it look?
It's tight again, but I can get through.
OK, keep going. We'll be right behind you.
Hey, there's something down here.
Guys, it's amazing,
but the batteries on our lights will run out.
- So I suggest we keep moving.
- Wait a minute. Wait.
- What is it, Beth?
- Juno, light up one of your flares.
- We don't have time for this.
- Just light a flare.
- Really lovely, Beth, but it's fucking useless.
- No, look at it. What do you see?
You've got the mountain, the cave...
and there's two entrances.
- You are a fucking genius.
- I have my moments.
- This means there's another way out?
- Let's find out.
Come on!
- Bastard!
- Which way?
Holly, give me your lighter.
- Come on.
- Here.
Fuck!
- Come on! Come on!
- Shit!
- That one!
- Hey! Holly!
Holly, slow down!
Holly! Careful!
Daylight! I can see daylight!
Holly! Careful! Slow down!
Holly, it's not daylight!
- Help me!
- Hold on!
Guys! Hold...
Holly!
Sam! Get down here!
Holly! Answer me!
I think I hurt my leg!
Don't move! We're coming down to you.
Oh, fuck!
No! Fuck!
Someone better get down here!
- Oh, that's fucking disgusting.
- Beth! Not here, not now!
We need help. Everybody grab a corner.
We need to move her out of the water.
Nice and easy now. And... lift!
Argh!
- You fuckers!
- Juno, find something to make a splint out of.
- It's OK, I've got her.
- Hey, Juno, use one of the ice axes.
You'll be all right, sweetheart.
OK.
- Sarah!
- Juno, I'm gonna need your help here.
- Juno!
Take hold of her arm.
You'll have to hold her down.
What are you gonna do?
I need to dress the wound and rig up a splint,
but I can't while the bone is protruding.
I need to push it back in.
- I hate you.
- I know.
Do it.
Bite down on this.
- Keep hold of her.
- Just fucking bite down, OK?
Go!
Come on!
Just keep biting down, baby.
Come on.
OK, someone get me a medical kit.
OK, OK, OK. Calm down. It'll be all right.
What are you doing?
I just saw something ahead in the tunnel.
Sarah, I promise you,
I'm gonna get you out of here.
But I can't do it unless you're with me.
Sarah?
Sarah!
Sarah, look at me.
There's nothing there.
That's the best I can do.
It'll hurt like hell and you can't put any weight
on it, but at least you can move.
They combed these mountains centuries ago.
Anyone trapped would be a skeleton now.
- That is just what it looked like.
- What?
- Sarah thinks she saw someone.
- Saw what?
I don't think I saw someone, I saw someone.
No, you heard something
and saw what you wanted to see.
- It's the dark. It plays tricks on people.
- I can describe exactly what I saw.
- What did you see?
- A man. I saw a man.
Are you sure?
- Yes!
And it's not the first time. I thought
I saw someone before, but now I'm sure.
Look, if there is somebody down here,
then maybe they can help get us out.
Sarah, there's no-one down here.
Forget about it!
Hey, we have to get Holly out of here.
OK? This is all that matters right now.
- Beth!
- It's OK.
Is it? Fuck!
Fuck me.
You've got to keep warm.
Why are we walking away?
There was daylight back there.
It wasn't. It was phosphorus in the rock.
We're two miles underground,
the only light down here is ours.
Argh! Well, it looked like fucking daylight to me.
Right tunnel!
I got you. OK?
Jesus! What is this place?
Holly, where's the infrared button?
Dead animals.
Hundreds of them.
This is not good, guys.
Can we get out of here? Which way?
Come on.
- I don't know.
What do you mean, you don't know?
There's no breeze. It could be
any one of these tunnels. Take your pick.
Oh, fuck it! Hello!
- Please!
- Is there anybody there?
Hello!
It's there! It's up there!
It's there on the roof!
Fucking hell, did you see...?
What the fuck was that?
I don't know!
It moved so fast, I could barely see it!
- I've never seen anyone climb like that!
- I told you I saw someone!
- That was not a human being!
- Screw this.
Let's take our chances and pick a tunnel. Move!
What's happening?
Oh, shit! It's circling us.
- Where is it?
- This way! Move!
- Holly! We've got to move. We've got to move.
- Come on! Move it!
Come on, Holly! Move it! Let's go!
- Juno, the flare! Get rid of it!
- Fuck!
Holly, keep moving, come on!
Holly! Holly!
Sarah!
Holly!
Sarah! Run!
Sarah!
Get off!
Get away, you fucker!
Don't leave me.
Oh, fuck. My battery's gone dead.
Where are they?
What's happened to the others?
Becca, please say we're gonna get out of here.
OK. OK.
OK.
Go. Go!
Mummy. Mummy.
If you're really ready...
Oh, fuck. Fuck.
Turn the light off.
Quiet.
Sarah! Sarah!
Sarah!
It can't see us.
Sam? Becca?
Becca!
- Becca!
- It's Juno.
Becca!
The noise she's making, she'll bring
every one of those things down on her head.
As long as it's not on mine.
Becca!
Sam!
Anyone?
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Oh...
I'm sorry.
Fuck. OK.
OK.
It's all clear.
Sam, run!
We heard you crying for Sarah.
Where are the others?
They... They took Holly.
Beth...
Beth's dead.
Sam...
...what is that thing?
I don't know. Well, it does look human.
Come on, we need to find the way out
before those things find us.
No.
Sam, tell us what we're fighting.
Well...
...they're totally blind.
And judging from what we've seen,
I'd say they use sound to hunt with. Like a bat.
And they've evolved perfectly
to live down here in the dark.
Whatever they are,
they go to the surface to hunt.
And they bring their food back down here to eat,
through an entrance.
Listen, if we can stay quiet enough
and evade these fuckers...
...I think I found the way out.
You think?
The climbing gear we found - whoever
brought that down here marked their route.
- I found those markings.
- Well, what are we waiting for?
Sarah.
I'm not leaving without Sarah.
Sarah!
Oh, God.
Oh, God. No.
Sarah...
I'm getting you out of here.
Don't touch me. Don't touch me.
I heard Juno calling me.
I'm gonna go and find her,
and we're gonna come back and get you out.
No, stay away from her.
- What?
- She did this to me.
- She left me.
No, she didn't. No.
- Shh.
- Sarah...
Don't trust her.
You find your own way out.
It's OK. It's all right.
I'm not gonna leave you, Beth.
I'm not gonna leave you.
I'm not leaving you here, OK?
Come here. Beth!
This is Juno's.
It's from Paul.
Oh, no.
Sorry.
Please... Oh, that's them. Please, come with me.
Please.
Sarah...
...don't leave me like this.
No, please don't ask me to do that.
- Please.
- I can't. I can't do that.
I can't do that.
Please.
OK. Ssh.
Close your eyes.
Hurry! Move!
Sarah?
Look, she's dead, Juno. We can't wait for her.
Come on!
Sarah!
Sarah?
Run!
Oh, fuck!
Fuck.
- Come on!
- Juno, stop her! I'll be right behind you!
Sam! What are you doing?
Come back!
Becca!
You haven't got enough rope!
Sam! Turn around!
- What are you doing? Turn around!
- Sam, baby!
- Sam! Sam!
- Sam, turn around. You can come back.
Please, baby, listen to me. Please!
Sam!
No!
What are you doing?
Sam!
Sam! No!
What happened to you?
Rebecca?
What about Beth?
Didn't make it.
You saw her die?
Come on.
Come on. Come on.
No! No!
Oh, God!