Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org
Subtitles by explosiveskull
Resync by GoldenBeard
See you later!
Come on, guys.
Leave him alone.
Hello?
Boy.
Wow. That was amazing.
Why don't you play outside
with your friends?
I don't know.
Come here.
You don't know, huh?
Sometimes they make fun of me.
Hmm.
Is that real?
Yes.
It's real.
Everything here is real.
Whoa. Is that real?
That cat is real.
Real monster.
What's that?
This?
This is Lloyd.
Hmm.
He looks like
a very brave fighter.
No, he's just a kid.
He can't do anything.
He might look different, but...
But he can do great things.
Whoa.
You just have to look at it,
from a different
point of view.
Whoa!
This is his teacher.
Very old,
very wise
and very handsome.
Have you ever heard the legend
behind the legend of NINJAGO?
No.
I will tell you.
But to truly see it,
you must forget
everything you know.
And see things in a new way.
The story of NINJAGO
is the story of a boy.
His name is Lloyd.
And his dad is the worst guy
in the history of the world.
Today on
Good Morning NINJAGO...
Buenos días, NINJAGO!
G'day, NINJAGO!
Guten Morgen,
NINJAGO.
Bonjour, NINJAGO.
When Garmadon attacks...
...we are there!
When Garmadon crashes
the stock market,
we're there again!
When Garmadon defaces
Whistler's Mother,
we're still there!
We are the only news team
watching Garmadon's
volcanic lair
24 hours a day.
- This is...
- Good Morning, NINJAGO!
- I'm Robin Roberts.
- And I'm Michael Strahan.
And I am pumped
to be bringing you the news.
- Pumped!
- Whoo!
Well, looks like everyone
is on pins and needles
waiting for
Garmadon's next attack.
Attack forecast!
Our experts predict
a 95% chance
of a Garmadon attack today.
Yikes! NINJAGO,
you better stay inside.
You better stay right there.
Don't you dare come out!
At least until our
Secret Ninja Force steps in.
Thank goodness
for those Ninjas.
But who are these
Secret Ninjas, Robin?
We have
so many questions.
Burning questions!
Fire Ninja.
Where is he on a scale of
one to awesome?
I'm not gonna lie.
I'm awesome!
Earth Ninja.
When will he upgrade
to digital?
No, I would never do that.
Ice Ninja.
Is he a real boy or a robot?
How dare you. I'm a wild teen.
Lightning Ninja.
Is he the bravest ninja
of them all?
I'll take that as a yes.
Water Ninja.
She's a girl and a ninja!
Can she really have it all?
You fellas
need to inform yourselves
of where we're at culturally.
And finally the Green Ninja.
He fights in the air,
on the ground,
and in the kitchen
with a refrigerator.
But what is he hiding?
And who is he really?
Local birthdays!
Celebrating birthdays today
are this hot dog guy,
this panda
and, uh-oh...
Lloyd Garmadon.
The son of
the evil Lord Garmadon.
Must be tough
to be that kid.
Hello?
Hello.
What do you want?
- Uh... You called me.
- Hang on a second.
Mm. I must have
butt dialed you. Who is this?
It's Lloyd.
- Lloyd Garmadon, your son.
- No.
My son is totally bald
and has no teeth.
Yeah, well, surprise.
I'm not a baby anymore.
Duly noted.
How old are you?
You're seven, right?
- You're seven? Huh.
- Sixteen.
Just add nine to that.
- Well, good talk, son.
- Wait.
Are you sure there isn't
a special reason
why you might have
called me today?
On this day.
Specifically today.
Look, I didn't call you.
My butt called you.
Oh.
Well, no time to chat. Sorry,
Daddy's got to go to work.
- Gotta get that Green Ninja.
- Yeah.
Glad the teeth
finally came in. Bye-bye.
Lloyd! Good morning!
Mom, hey,
um, here's a thought.
What if I didn't go
to school today?
What? Oh, no!
You don't want to
miss school, honey.
These are the best years
of your life.
Um, have you...
Have you been to high school?
'Cause, uh...
It's judgey. Pretty judgey.
Oh, honey.
You just need to give them
a chance to see the real you.
Yeah, I don't think
I can actually show people
the real me.
That's not true.
All you've got to do
is just show them
the person you are
on the inside.
Right here.
Where it matters most.
Oh, and also don't forget,
if your dad attacks
the city again today,
just be sure to...
Duck and cover
until the Secret Ninjas
give the all clear.
- Oh, and also, don't forget,
- LLOYD: Yeah?
Have a happy birthday, honey.
Thanks, Mom.
I'll try my best.
Of course you will!
Hello!
Shh.
Hey.
Cool.
Shh.
That's the kid
I was telling you about.
His dad ruins everything.
Hello, fellow teenager!
Zane, hey!
Man, my mom is on my case
all the time. She's all...
And I'm like, "Lay off, Mom.
I'm just a teenager."
I hear that.
Bro!
Dude, gimme a hug, man!
- Gimme a birthday hug.
- Kai.
- That's a good one.
- Birthday hug?
Let me get in on that.
I'll increase
the pressure dramatically.
Zane, Zane, Zane...
Watch out!
- Lloyd!
- Nya!
- Yo, bro.
- What's up, sis?
Oh, hey, actual bro.
Hey, Nya!
Where'd you get that bike?
At the great
stuff store? Uh...
Guys, check out
my new paint job,
'cause I did it myself!
The Lady Iron Dragon.
My hero!
Hey, everyone, look!
It's Garma-dork
and the dork squad!
You wanna hear our new cheer?
L-L-O-Y-D.
His dad is bad and so is he.
Boo, Lloyd!
Great chant!
I'll bet you got a number one
hit on your hands.
And straight in
at number one with a bullet.
It's Boo, Lloyd.
Hey, ladies.
L-L-O-Y-D.
His dad is bad and so is he.
Boo, Lloyd!
Boo...
Citizens of NINJAGO!
Get ready
to welcome your new overlord!
Who goes by the name of...
Garmadon!
What's my name?
Say it again!
Garmadon!
I can't hear you!
- Garmadon!
Don't wear it out!
Okay, General Number Six.
Yes, sir.
You and your team
of crab men
- overthrow the police station.
- I can do that.
General Number One,
- take the TV station.
- 10-4!
What?
General Number Five,
- crash the stock market.
- Okey-doke.
General Number Three,
knock over that table.
General Number Two,
pop that kid's balloon.
General Number Four,
make the school bus
dangle precariously
over an overpass or something.
I've never seen that before!
We're gonna die!
Now,
all I have to do is climb
to the top of NINJAGO Tower,
and then I will rule
over NINJAGO.
Wait. What?
I said I will rule
over NINJAGO, forever!
Where are the ninjas?
- MS.
- Uh-oh.
It's Garmadon!
Thanks, Lloyd.
You know what
to do. Duck and cover!
Can I have
a bathroom pass?
I think you mean, "May I."
"May I have a bathroom pass?"
You know what?
Do whatever you want.
Come on, come on!
Ninja, go!
Ninja computer
system initiated.
Come on!
Ninja team,
shout out your call signs.
- Ha-ha!
- Kai, light it up!
Whoo! Fire mech!
So ninja!
Fire mech ignited.
All right,
take it away, sis!
Water mech.
Ready and standing by.
- Zane!
- Come on!
- Your turn, buddy!
- Ice mech.
Loading. Loading. Loading...
Ready, Jay?
Yeah, yeah, I got this.
Lightning mech, ready.
Wait! No, not ready. Ready.
Cole, do you wanna kick
Garmadon's butt?
Earth mech.
Turntables
at 33 and a third RPM.
Ready and standing by.
Green Ninja.
All ninjas, hit it!
All right, ninjas, follow me!
As long as we have
these mechs,
we're unstoppable!
If we were the Beatles,
you would be John,
you would be Paul,
you would be George
and I would be their computer.
Run!
Everybody, run!
Get away from the docks!
We're all gonna die!
- Whoo-hoo!
- Yeah!
Ninjas!
There they are. Ninjas.
Go, Ninjas! Go!
Thank you for coming
to help us, Ninjas!
We love you,
Green Ninja!
Jay, you take the air.
10-4, good buddy.
Nya, water.
It's a dangerous
and fascinating environment.
I know, right?
Kai, Zane, and Cole,
you guys take downtown.
Already here, dude.
Taking some heavy fire.
Hold on, Kai.
I got you covered.
Have you heard
my latest track?
It's a smash.
Thanks, Cole.
Jay, you've got bogeys
on your six.
You've also
got them on your three,
one, seven, five,
six, eight, nine, and two.
I've got good tone.
Firing.
Too close for missiles.
Switching to crabs!
Crab! Crab! Crab!
Oh, crabs! Crabs!
Get your affairs
in order, Lightning Ninja.
Ah! I gotta charge up
my supersonic dynamo.
Come on, charge!
Charge!
Hurry up!
Charge, charge, charge!
Charge! Hurry up!
Charge, charge!
Clear!
Whoo-hoo!
Whoo! Bam!
Zane, you are the man!
Yes. I'm a normal
human teenager.
Nice work, guys.
I'm going after Garmadon.
Somebody help us!
Classmates, hold on.
Roar!
Oh, no!
N-I-N-J-A!
N-I-N-J-A! Ninjas!
Thank you, Green Ninja!
You're our hero!
I wanna be him
when I grow up!
Hey, Lloyd, your dad...
I mean, uh...
Garmadon's almost
at the mayor's office!
I'm on it.
We've got you surrounded,
Garmadon.
You're too slow, Green Ninja.
You can't catch me.
Where am I?
Am I over here?
Or am I over there?
You are right behind
that building.
I can see your shark tail
sticking out.
Oh, let me grab that.
Where's Garmadon now?
Am I over here, here, here?
Or am I over there,
there, there, there?
It's like a house of mirrors
in here.
Do you think
you're hiding right now?
Do you actually think
I can't see you?
Well, if you can see me,
why don't you shoot me?
Ow! That was, like,
in my kidney!
Why do you want to conquer
NINJAGO so badly?
Because there's something
very, very special here.
What?
I'm gonna let the walls down
for just a second,
Green Ninja.
Go... Go on.
About 16 years ago,
I lost something
I should have never given up.
What is it? Just say it.
It's okay, you can say it.
I had this guitar in college,
and I traded it stupidly for,
like, a jacket or something.
That's what you were
referring to?
Yeah. What else would I be
I don't know.
Maybe something else.
- Think about it.
- What? No!
Are you sure
there's not any other
sort of connection
you have to the city?
- Nothing?
- There is someone
in the city I love very much.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
I remember when I first
laid eyes on him.
Go on.
The last time
I saw him was, uh,
I guess about
16 years ago, too.
Yeah?
I was just
an irresponsible kid and...
Uh-huh.
There was this
guy who made,
probably, the best sushi
I've ever had in my life.
You never knew
what was coming next.
And you didn't even order.
It was one of those places
where you don't
even get a menu.
Omakase.
Is that the name of the place?
No, that just means
he brings it to you...
That is!
That's the name of the place.
...and you don't
choose, he chooses.
- That's the place.
- Omakase.
Anyway, just to clarify,
nothing, nothing else, if you
really racked your brain,
there's no other connection?
Yes. There was a boy
that I had in my life.
What happened to your child?
He was bald, had no teeth,
couldn't chew,
always crying, couldn't walk.
Couldn't even walk.
I mean, I was like,
"What are we gonna do
with this kid?"
I'm like, "I don't want
a hairless, crying son
"for the rest of my life."
- Zip it! Zip! No!
- And that was when
I made the decision
to go away and live my life.
Stop talking!
You're done!
Mega missile
mode. Right claw missile.
Left claw missile.
Feet bombs.
Tongue rocket. Spine missile
one, two, three, four.
Tail rocket, one, two...
Eye missile.
Other eye missile.
Toenail missile. Wrist rocket.
Head missile.
Other head missile.
Backup head missile.
Metacarpal missile.
Butt torpedoes.
Oh. Phew.
Just one day till retirement.
Jeez, where did
that come from?
I did not see that coming.
Your missiles are very
accurate, Green Ninja.
Too bad for you,
I upgraded all of my shields!
That's all I seem to have
at the moment,
just some upgraded shields.
Face it, Garmadon.
You will never
take over NINJAGO,
so why don't you just give up
and go away for good?
Well, anything's open
for discussion.
Oh, yeah, except that.
Shields down!
Here, catch! Shields up!
No!
Did you see that?
Oh, yeah, we saw it.
I mean, who taught
you how to catch, man?
Nice catch, loser!
Oh, yeah? Well, take this!
That's amazing!
Who taught you how to throw?
It's funny you ask.
Um, no one, because I, uh...
I never had a dad
to play catch with me.
Well, it shows.
'Cause that was
the worst thing
I've ever seen in my life.
Or, uh, you know,
teach me how to ride a bike,
or shave...
Or how to defuse a bomb!
You know what's funny?
Is I know how to do
all those things.
- Do you?
- Yeah.
Oh, good to know.
And they're just sitting
there, idle in my brain.
Just wasted. Floating away.
- Never taught them to anybody.
- Mm-hmm.
And they'll
probably die with me.
Really?
When I die, if I die.
- Just leave NINJAGO already...
- Which will never happen.
- ...please!
- I will never die.
- And get out of my life!
- Ever. Ever.
I...
Get out of your life?
Weirdly kinda personal,
isn't it?
- Uh-oh.
- Oh, man.
Um...
No.
You've got a lot of issues,
Green Ninja.
I hope you get the chance to
work 'em all out
by the time I'm back.
And when I return,
I'll have something really
wicked in store for you.
Something big!
Uh, did he just say
he's coming back?
Can't those Ninjas
get rid of him for good?
Oh, great. Now I have to
rebuild my Pilates studio.
That stinks.
I don't know how,
but I bet Lloyd Garmadon
has something to do with this.
You can sure
say that again.
I don't know how...
Is that Green Ninja
still staring at me?
Yes, sir.
Ugh. What a weirdo.
Volcano base,
this is Alpha Squad.
Arriving shortly at LZ.
Bakery team,
the victory cake
goes back in the fridge.
The victory cake
There is
a magma spill on Deck Three.
Avoid Deck Three
if sensitive to magma.
Just passed
Garmadon in the hallway,
he seems pretty angry.
He's requesting
a mandatory staff meeting
by the fireplace.
Is that
the room with the lava
or the room
where people get fired?
It's both.
Well, generals,
congratulations.
We finally conquered NINJAGO.
I'm not certain we did that.
- I was being sarcastic!
- Whoa!
Every time I try
and conquer NINJAGO,
that meddling Green Ninja
thwarts me.
I mean,
who are these super ninjas?
Every time I come up
with a new plan,
they still beat me!
And they don't even have
cool suits!
You guys have, like,
crab outfits
and shark outfits.
I mean, maybe we're spending
too much on outfits.
That sounds right to me, sir.
Oh, come on!
Look, you guys gotta
think for yourselves.
I'm not your father,
all right?
Is that a weird
thing for him to say to us?
General Number One,
do you wanna be a follower,
or do you wanna be a leader?
Uh... A leader?
How dare you.
I mean, follower!
You! What's your title?
Uh, I'm General
Number Two, sir.
Well, now,
you're General Number One.
- Oh.
- And you, what's your title?
General Three?
Well, now you're
General Number Two.
You see
where I'm going with this?
No.
I told the Green Ninja
I was coming back
with something big,
something wicked,
something with some pizzazz.
General Number One,
go ahead. Give me some ideas.
Well, sir,
I was thinking maybe
we could work
on the morale of the troops.
They're always scared of being
fired!
We could do the
same thing we did last time?
Whoa!
What if we dress up
as the Secret Ninjas?
It's time we develop
a code language.
Intimidation. We paint angry
eyebrows on the troops' faces.
What if you just ran
for mayor?
Whoa! Whoa!
Oh, come on. How hard is it
to come up with a genius idea?
Anyone? Come on,
jump ball.
This is a safe place.
Go ahead. Just grab it.
- Excuse me, Lord...
- Nerd! You're interrupting.
Sorry, sir. We just cooked
this up in engineering.
Give me that!
Garma-daddy likey!
- Lloyd...
- Yeah?
That's your dad.
You were open, man.
It was highly poignant.
For me,
it's easy to fight him
'cause he's, like,
not my father.
But for you,
that must be so complicated.
Not that complicated.
You also really pulled
at my heartstrings, man.
I felt for you.
With... With the missiles.
No. With the other...
The other stuff.
The dad stuff.
Yeah, but, like, exactly what
are you referring to?
- Watching you and your father.
- The vulnerability.
You got so emotional.
Emotions were the last thing
that was going on out there.
- Um, yeah.
- Mm-hmm.
It's okay, Lloyd.
Nobody's parents are perfect.
I mean, my mom is weird
and collects seashells.
Your dad levels cities
and attacks innocent people.
So, they've all got
their quirks, you know?
Uh, where's that
tranquil music coming from?
Hey, look, everyone!
Master Wu is back.
- Hello, students.
- Master Wu!
- Shock.
- How was your trip?
It was a deep
spiritual journey
that took me to depths
inside myself
I never knew existed.
Yeah. You have
a pretty serious tan line.
Don't judge me.
So, did you see us kick
Garmadon's butt?
- We vanquished him.
- Ba-ba bam!
I saw you fight
and I saw Garmadon retreat.
But you did not defeat him.
What?
There's nothing ninja
about you ninjas.
We're so ninja. I don't know
what you're talking about.
You will never
truly defeat Garmadon
until you see things
from a different
point of view.
You have the power to win
the battle without fighting.
When you start using
your mind,
you won't need mechs
and machines.
Your call signs
are not just cool names.
They are the elemental powers
you were all born with.
Nya, you can create water
on your own.
- And Kai, fire!
- Wow!
Jay, lightning.
So ninja.
- Cole, earth.
- Whoa!
We both spin.
And Zane, ice.
Ice is nice.
These elemental powers
are why I chose you
to form
the Secret Ninja Force.
It is the highest level that
you can achieve as a ninja.
I wrote a book about it.
It's called Ninjanuity.
Copyright, Master Wu.
And what about me?
What am I?
Lloyd, yours is the most
important element of all.
Okay. Hit me with it.
Your elemental power is green.
- What's that?
- Green.
Okay, so, uh, just to recap.
Fire. Ice. Water. Earth.
Lightning. And...
Green.
Don't think
it's an element though.
- Lloyd...
- Can I be gold?
- No.
- Wind isn't taken.
Can I be wind?
- No.
- Earth, green, and fire.
- Rolls right off the tongue.
- Lloyd...
Could I be
the element of surprise?
No. That's the Fuchsia Ninja.
Surprise.
There are
so many elements left.
This feels kinda purposeful
that I don't have one.
Enough, Lloyd.
Come with me for mentor talk.
The rest of you,
practice Spinjitzu.
That's easy. Watch this.
Exertion.
For three hours.
Three hours! Are you kidding
me with this guy!
And read my book!
Oh, man!
Master Wu,
you don't understand.
Right now, on that volcano...
Garmadon is making something
really big.
He's building something huge.
And something
surely shark themed.
And he's gonna come back
sooner rather than later.
So, what do I do?
Nephew, weapons alone
will not solve your problem.
I have every kind of weapon
in my dojo.
Big weapons, little weapons,
sharp weapons, dull weapons,
even the Ultimate Weapon.
But the strongest weapon
is inside you.
Wait. I'm sorry,
what did you just say?
The strongest weapon
is inside you.
No, no, no. Before that.
The thing right before that.
What? You mean...
The Ultimate Weapon!
And you've been
hiding this why?
In the wrong hands,
the Ultimate Weapon
could spell doom for NINJAGO.
Put that in my hands.
Why does it matter
how we beat Garmadon
as long as we beat him?
Because, nephew, right now,
your hands
are the wrong hands.
Lloyd,
I'm his brother.
I, too, feel responsible
for the safety of NINJAGO.
But I will not always
be here to train you.
- Why?
- Because,
I'm super, super old.
Oh.
That's why I need you to
lead the Secret Ninja Force.
But you must promise
to walk a different path.
One that only
the son of Garmadon can walk.
No matter how hard it may be.
Honestly, I would
happily give up
being a Secret Ninja
if it meant I didn't have to
be the son of Garmadon.
I know you've had
a hard life, Lloyd,
filled with many knocks.
Why don't I play you a song?
Perhaps it will speak to you.
Thanks, Uncle Wu.
No, no.
I don't know where he is.
No, he hasn't come home
from school.
No, he did not join forces
with his father.
That is ridiculous.
Like your husband's a saint.
I am trying
not to freak out right now,
but I have called 18 people
and I cannot locate my son.
Yes, I know you said you never
wanted him to play
with your kids,
I just didn't know if,
maybe...
- Lloyd!
- Hey, Mom.
No. I've got him right here.
He just walked in. Bye-bye.
Oh, my gosh.
I was so worried about you.
Uh, I'm fine. I just took
the long way home.
Why did we get
on a family plan
if you're not gonna text me?
I'm so sorry.
I didn't mean to worry you.
I love you and I'm sorry.
I don't know what I'd do
if anything
ever happened to you, okay?
Thanks, Mom.
I'm just really glad that
those ninjas saved the day.
Yeah. Yeah, I was there.
What?
Watching with
the other regular kids.
Okay. Well,
you must be starving.
I don't know,
I'm not really that hungry.
But I'll make your favorite.
Dumplings!
Oh! Enticing,
but I'm just gonna...
I'm just gonna go to bed,
I think.
Just really tired.
- Oh.
- Good night, Mom.
Okay, well, good night.
And back
at number one with a bullet,
no surprises there,
is Boo, Lloyd, the remix.
L-L...
L-L-O-Y-D...
L-L-O-Y-D.
His dad is bad and so is he.
Boo, Lloyd!
- Huh?
- What is that?
Hey, Green Ninja, I'm back!
And look
what I brought with me.
Breaking news.
Garmadon is attacking the city
in a never-before-seen mech.
Run! Run!
- Garmadon!
You all came out to greet me?
Don't run away.
That's a nice little
hot dog stand you got there.
Scu-smash!
The Ninjas are going to have
their hands full
with this thing.
Ninja, go!
We got a message
from your brother Garmadon.
You wanna hear it?
Oh, yeah? What did he say?
He says you're a big stupid
dumb-dumb with a dumb face
and a big butt
and your butt stinks
and you smell like a butt.
That sounds like my brother.
Get him!
- Jay.
- Yeah?
You take the air.
Kai, Zane and Cole, downtown.
- Nya, water.
- You got it.
I'm going
after Garmadon.
Why don't I take
your dad this time?
I got this. I'm totes profesh.
Wait.
What does that mean?
I think he's trying to say
he's a total professional.
Then why is he
totes abbrevin'?
I'm pretty sure
Lloyd's nervous.
What?
That's crazy talk.
Incorrect.
Hey, I got this!
Stand down, Garmadon.
Well, hello, Green Ninja!
It's time for you
to ninja go away for good.
Take this!
Mega missile mode.
Left claw missile.
Toenail missile. Wrist rocket.
Feet bombs. Spine missile one,
two, three, four.
Tail rocket one, two.
Eye missile.
Other eye missile.
Tongue rocket. Head missile.
Other head missile.
Backup head missile.
Butt torpedoes.
Your weapons are powerless
against my new mech.
What?
Well, take this!
Releasing full payload.
Here it comes...
Alert! Alert! Alert!
You having trouble with that
dragon mech, Green Ninja?
Bye-bye.
Wait. No!
Jay, what's happening?
Garmadon has
taken out Lloyd.
- What?
- Wait, what?
I'm sorry.
What did you say?
Repeat.
Garmadon has taken out Lloyd!
Looks like the police,
the army
and the coast guard have
all been rendered useless
by Garmadon's forces.
Guys, Garmadon's
almost at city hall.
Can one of you
please stop him?
I'm swamped down here.
I'm a little busy.
Look at me go!
Who wants a shark?
You want a shark?
You get a shark!
We're shark bait!
Come on, come on, come on.
Just walking up the tower.
Uh, Lloyd would be
really beneficial right now.
Where are you, Lloyd?
I'm a ninja master!
You are no match
for me! Whoo-hoo!
I came here to drink boba
and kick butt,
and I am all out of boba.
Hey, NINJAGO!
Oh, wait. That's bad.
Garmadon
is conquering NINJAGO!
Robin, this is a day
that will live in infamy.
- I just made that up.
- No, you didn't.
Yes, I did.
Copyright, Michael Strahan.
It's mine now.
Whoo! I've done it!
I'm finally the ruler
of NINJAGO!
Forever! And ever!
Stand down, Garmadon!
Green Ninja?
And the legendary
Ultimate Weapon?
Ugh, it's not fair.
I'm sick and tired of you
trying to conquer NINJAGO!
All right, Green Ninja.
Now, listen. Just calm down.
You don't have to use
that thing.
So you're gonna leave NINJAGO?
- Yeah.
- Forever?
I promise.
Why is your hand
behind your back?
What are you doing back there?
Are you crossing your fingers?
That's physically impossible.
How could I be crossing my
fingers? I have these things.
I'm warning you, Garmadon!
Fine! No crossies!
No crossies!
Just chill. Okay.
Look,
I'm getting rid
of all my sharks.
See? No sharks.
And the sharks
in your ankle holster.
I don't have any sharks.
- What's in your ankle?
- It's a couple dolphins, man.
Now you're acting loco.
I mean...
Hey! Get rid of 'em.
Fine. You happy now?
I'm done. You win.
What are you doing?
What are you doing right now?
Easy, Green Ninja.
Don't come any closer!
Easy.
I'm warning you,
Garmadon.
Let's just keep
this interaction very chill.
I'm the definition
of chill right now!
I know.
Stand back!
Put down the Ultimate Weapon,
Green Ninja.
We both know
you're not gonna fire it.
Oh, yeah?
This is your last chance.
Get out of NINJAGO,
now and forever!
No.
All right, fine.
You ready for this?
- Yeah.
- It's coming.
- Okay.
- You've been warned.
- I'm waiting.
- Here it comes.
- Any time.
- All right,
here it comes!
Oh, my gosh!
He actually shot
and it exploded, and then...
But nothing is happening.
Why is nothing happening?
What the heck?
It's like
the Ultimate Lamest Weapon.
Come on!
Why won't you work?
Get off my Vespa!
You hear that?
What have you done?
Whoa.
Aw!
How do I turn this thing off?
Ah.
Come on!
Generals,
grab the Green Ninja.
Keep away.
Whoa. Whoa.
Wait!
Wait! No, no, no!
Remember, Green Ninja,
I didn't fire this thing
first. That's on you.
But, since you got it all
warmed up,
let's try it
on some moving targets.
No!
What the heck!
Stop it, Garmadon!
Just stop it!
What is this thing?
I'm gonna throw up!
Prolonged scream.
Five ninjas down,
one to go.
Bang! I win! Cue the music!
Whoo!
Awesome job, sir!
What? Are you gonna cry?
I'm not gonna cry.
I bet he's gonna cry.
I'm not gonna cry...
Dad.
La-Loyd?
That's right!
It's me! Your son!
And it's Lloyd, Dad.
No. L-L-O-Y-D. I named you.
You ruined my life!
How could I ruin your life?
I wasn't even there.
I wish you weren't my father.
And we're back in
three, two, one...
Welcome back, NINJAGO.
I'm Robin Roberts.
And as you can see,
our city is in the midst
of total annihilation.
And for a city
that gets attacked
pretty frequently, Robin...
...that's really
saying something.
As we struggle
to survive,
we're left
with so many questions like,
"Who has
truly conquered NINJAGO?"
The monster?
Or Garmadon?
We did it!
Party time!
Incoming!
We did it!
Let's go.
"I wish you weren't
my father."
Huh?
Is it just me, or was that
kind of a weird thing to say?
"I wish
you weren't my father."
And the tone,
it was so disrespectful.
Yes, sir.
Plus, he tried to shoot you.
Yeah! Right before you
totally conquered his city!
We
conquered your greatest foe,
turned out to be
your son though...
I'm sure he meant it
as a compliment,
but it's a weird thing, right?
General Number One!
Sir!
Have you captured my son yet?
No, not yet, sir.
And yet, here you are.
Partying on the rooftops
with a paper umbrella
in your drink.
What about
La-Loyd's ninja friends?
You captured any of them yet?
No, sir.
And what about my brother, Wu?
What about my ex, Koko?
You found her?
No, sir.
Well, you certainly
had no trouble
finding the bar, did you?
We're on it, sir.
We searched the whole city
from top to bottom.
You're not on the list.
Oh! My clipboard!
Look, here she is now.
Hey, Koko.
Glad you made it to the party.
Pretty on the chain, isn't it?
Wipe that smile off your face,
Garmadon.
Ugh, same old Kokes.
It just kills you to see me
having any fun, doesn't it?
Oh, by the way,
uh, quick question.
What was it again?
Oh, yeah. Why did you
turn our son against me?
Me? You turned him
against you, Garm.
You're a maniacal
twisted villain.
All right, look,
enough with the compliments.
Whose idea was it for him
to become a ninja?
Lloyd is not a ninja.
Who's the absentee parent now?
What are you talking about?
La-Loyd. He's the Green Ninja.
One of my greatest enemies,
honor-bound
and sworn to destroy me.
You know what he said to me?
He said that he wished...
What have you done with him?
Where's Lloyd?
My gosh, woman,
what happened to us?
- Ugh.
- I miss that fire.
You know, I've always tried
to get Lloyd to see
that he shouldn't be ashamed
of who his father is.
But now,
I'm starting to think
he could be right.
Oh, no. No, no. Please.
Please, no.
Uncle Wu...
Oh, my gosh!
You guys are okay!
Barely.
You used the Ultimate Weapon.
Not cool.
Dude,
our mechs are totaled.
And now,
that cat's destroying NINJAGO.
We were the only people
that didn't hate you,
and now we hate you!
Deleting all data related to
treating Lloyd as a friend.
Guys, I'm sorry.
I put everyone in danger
and now Master Wu is dead.
Hello, students.
Master Wu!
You're alive!
Duh! I'm a ninja master.
If I was gonna die, it would
be to teach you a lesson.
Lloyd, you have
awakened Meowthra.
Meowthra?
Yes, Meowthra.
The six-toed fluffy demon,
with her sandpaper tongue.
Her reign of terror
will stretch on and on
until all of NINJAGO is her
own personal litter box.
There's only one hope.
One thing that can drive
Meowthra away.
- What?
- What is it?
The Ultimate Ultimate Weapon.
Whoa!
Where is this thing?
On the other side
of the island,
hidden where only a true
ninja master can find it.
You must follow
the right path.
Otherwise you will end up
trapped in the deadly
Jungle of Lost Souls,
unable to cross the Bridge
of Fallen Mentors,
and mired in the Canyon of
General Unhappiness.
And if you're still alive,
you'll be crushed
by the Temple of
Fragile Foundations.
It's a journey many have tried
and none have returned.
That does sound difficult.
And terrifying.
But you know what?
We're ready.
No, you're not.
It will take great patience,
courage, and hard work.
All the skills
of a true ninja master.
So, I will make this journey
on my own. Bye.
- Wait, wait, wait!
- Master Wu, wait!
Hold on a second, please.
Master Wu,
I know I let NINJAGO down.
It's true, Lloyd let
NINJAGO down. Sorry, dude!
We want to fix
his terrible mistake.
- Train us to be true ninjas.
- We have the potential.
- Come on!
- Wait! We'll do anything.
Please, Master Wu,
you can't do this alone.
I know we're not
ninja masters yet,
but you said it yourself.
It's important
to look at things differently.
Is there anything I can do
to change your point of view?
Hmm.
Students, are you willing
to give Lloyd a second chance?
Uh...
- Too soon.
- No.
- Pass.
- Just processing, so...
Mm-mm, mm-mm.
Lloyd, you have
a long way to go
to regain your friends' trust.
Luckily, there's a long
journey ahead of us.
Thank you, Master Wu.
Thank you.
The fate of NINJAGO
is in your hands.
Are you ready?
- Yes, I am on it!
- Oh, yeah!
- Yep!
- Maybe.
Let's go!
Sir, I think we found them.
There's a group of
brightly colored ninjas
heading towards the obviously
dangerous jungle.
Mm. Zoom in a little closer.
Closer.
No, closer. Closer.
Yes! Right in on my stupid
brother's dirty beard.
What's he saying?
Something about a weapon.
The Omelet Omelet weapon.
It sounds delicious.
Delicious, yet quite possibly
dangerous.
He's talking about
an Ultimate Ultimate Weapon.
That's what I said,
the Ultimate Omelet Weapon.
Sir, where are you going?
This is pure warrior stuff.
Alone in the field,
tracking ninjas.
Finding out exactly
what La-Loyd meant
when he said, "I wish
you weren't my father."
So, I guess
I'm going to the jungle.
Dope fluting, Master Wu.
Thank you.
Students,
your elemental powers come
from this lush green world.
Feel the energy
flowing through you.
Good. Good.
The power is inside you.
Now say to yourself,
"I've got the power."
I've got the power!
What was that?
Mm. Ninja tracks!
I sense the presence of evil.
Students, true ninja knows
when to fight
and when to become one
with the elements.
Quickly, blend in the shadows.
You are all terrible ninjas.
I will take care of Garmadon
on my own.
I'm close.
- He's close.
- Real close.
Really close.
- You!
Oh, hello, brother.
Where are your
little ninja nerds?
Nailed it.
They are surrounding you,
perfectly hidden.
Ready to strike.
Oh, really?
Students, next lesson.
How to fight
like a true ninja...
Ow! Ow!
Ow!
Huh?
Ah.
Oh, look at me!
I'm Master Wu!
Today's lesson is something
totally boring!
Looks like you need a lesson
in learning how to shut
your stupid face.
Well, here's something
you won't learn in school,
the Seven Deadly Butterflies
of Shaolin.
One, two, three, four,
five, six, seven!
I don't need a deadly
butterfly to beat you.
Hyah!
We are totes
blending in right now.
I can still see you!
- Oh, man.
- Come on, this way.
Ho-ho! Wu's your daddy?
- Huh?
- Ha!
Get off of my head.
Hey, bro,
get off my foot!
- Get off!
- No, you get off my foot
so I can kick you in the head.
Whoa!
Ow.
Master Wu!
- Look out! He's behind you!
- Where?
Oh!
Really? Tighty-whities? Still?
Face it,
you're out of moves, Wu.
Oh, yeah? How about this one?
Oh-oh.
I call it the Caged Monkey..
Oh, you have got
to be kidding me!
Gasp.
And that, my students,
is how you fight
like a true ninja.
Well, a true ninja
would have counted
all seven butterflies.
What? I did.
One, two, three,
four, five, six...
Seven.
No!
Master Wu!
Lloyd, always remember...
Yeah?
Stay on the right path
to find your inner peace.
- No, no, no.
- Oh, my gosh!
Master Wu, we need you,
please! Don't leave!
Uncle Wu!
Did he say inner peace?
The right path?
Why is he bringing
these things up
so late in our adventure?
Well, well, well.
Looks like your precious
ninja master's gone.
Now, come on, La-Loyd.
Open the cage.
Let out your papa.
So, now you wanna be my dad?
I'm not gonna
ask you again, La-Loyd.
Open the cage right now.
One...
Two...
Three...
I thought that was
supposed to work with kids.
Listen, La-Loyd and friends
whose names I don't know...
- I'm Jay.
- It's not a question.
Oh.
Now, for you to make it
through this journey alive,
you're gonna need someone
to teach you the ninja way.
What do you know
about being a ninja?
Oh, I know plenty, La-Loyd.
You don't get to be a warlord
without knowing a thing or two
about the ninja arts.
The dark ninja arts.
What is that?
You're a ninja?
Indeed, I am.
As a matter of fact, I wrote
the book on Ninjelligence.
Why are there
so many one-star reviews?
I think that's trolls,
personally.
- Oh.
- We don't need your book,
Garmadon. Wu is our master.
Well, Wu is gone.
And you're gonna need me to
get you out of this jungle,
or you're all gonna die.
Oh, great!
We're all gonna die.
We're not gonna die, Jay.
And while
I'm keeping you alive,
maybe I'll teach you some of
my sick dark ninja moves,
like the Buzzkill.
Wow.
- The Miso Slap.
- Wow.
- Or the Chainsaw Chop.
- Or the Dance of Doom.
- Wow.
Hang on just a second.
This is Garmadon
we're talking about.
We can still make it to
the Ultimate Ultimate Weapon
on our own.
We just have to remember
what Master Wu taught us.
All I can remember is
we really need a ninja master.
And you are not
a ninja master.
So what are we gonna do?
We take him.
Fantastic!
You know what's funny?
I had La-Loyd
when I was 158 years old.
- Wow.
- Wait a minute.
- You're 174?
- Yes.
Master Wu says he's 167,
and he's your younger brother?
He's my younger brother.
Correct.
How is that possible?
You look much...
Younger.
- Thank you.
- Yeah, do you moisturize?
Yes, that's when I got
the upper hand on Master Wu.
- "Upper hands."
- Yeah, upper hands.
How did you gain two arms?
Oh, don't put it like that.
I don't know if that's
the best way to say it.
- Well, he's got four arms.
- Correct!
You know, a lot of people
don't ask me about it.
So, I'm glad
that he's comfortable asking.
Lloyd's never asked me once
about my arms.
- Have you, Lloyd?
- Don't talk to me.
I was bit by a snake.
- No!
- Yes.
So the snake
had a bunch of arms?
- They don't have arms.
- Exactly.
Do you mean like a spider?
Oh, no, I was bit by a snake.
And the snake
had been bitten by a spider.
And then the snake bit me.
- Oh.
- Are you guys actually
buying any of this?
How else would you explain it,
La-Loyd? You weren't there.
So, when the two extra arms
started growing,
were you like, "Yes, this is
awesome!" Or were you like...
No, at first, I was, like,
totally freaked out,
and sometimes
I get self-conscious about it.
Hey, uh, Garmadon.
Can I ask you
another question?
Yeah, go ahead.
It's about the arms. Um,
can you shake your own hand?
- Look! Check it out, ninjas.
- Oh, my gosh.
Oh, he's his own best friend!
Oh, the double shake!
I love your bad boy charm.
Look at this. This is one of
my favorite things.
I look like I'm making out
with two people, don't I?
- I'm impressed.
- Wonderful amusement!
Hey, you know what?
We should, uh...
We should be
practicing silence right now.
Sorry.
It's just, when you talk,
I don't wanna listen,
but when he talks,
I wanna listen.
I agree.
I've always said
he's weak-voiced.
I think we're gettin'
off point a little bit,
just a little bit.
You see what I mean
about the weak voice?
"Like a little bit!"
- That's how he talks.
- Do it again.
"A little bit!"
Oh, that's not how I...
That doesn't sound like me!
His sounds more like this.
Look what he's doing to us!
We have to focus.
He's turning our minds.
Thank you, Zane. You get it.
My sensors indicate
a fork in the road.
Hmm.
The right path is long,
and arduous, and enlightening.
And the left... A shortcut!
Why would
they say "possible"?
They would know, right?
We're taking the shortcut.
Let's roll!
No, no.
Okay. Just wait.
Master Wu said we should stay
on the right path.
What?
You wanna listen to the guy
who fell off the bridge,
or the guy who didn't
fall off the bridge?
Hey, Zane,
could you record this
and then
never play it back to me?
Yes.
Um... Guys?
Maybe this isn't
such a great idea.
This is my least favorite
place I've ever been in.
Did you hear that?
- We're backing it out.
- What?
- We're backing out.
- What did you just say?
- Go, go, go.
Back it.
Continue to back it out.
Alert. More danger.
- I'm gonna throw up.
- What do we do?
There's too many of them.
Wait a minute.
Oh, my gosh. La-Loyd,
they look like
my former General Number Ones.
You guys look great.
Your skin
has such a lovely glow.
Have you all been
tanning lately or something?
We were fired.
Out of a volcano.
Oh! Right, right, right.
Yeah, but other than that,
you're well?
Uh, Garmadon,
did you fire all of these
generals out of a volcano?
No! Not all at the same time.
Don't worry. These guys
are like family. They love me.
Right, Generals?
Oh, we're family all right.
Ninja, go!
Guys, wait!
We need to use
our ninja powers.
What do we do? We're worthless
without our mechs.
Come on. Remember
what Master Wu told us.
Nya, you can make a flood
to wash these guys outta here.
The only hope
for water is
if Jay has another accident
in his pants.
Yeah, she's right.
We gotta get outta here!
- Ow, that hurts.
- Let's go.
No, no, guys.
Use your elemental powers.
We have the power!
We've got Garmadon
And this random kid
We are going to kill them
Oops, we shouldn't have
said that
I command you
to release me and my son.
That's an order, Generals.
I can't hear you!
I said, I command you
to release me and my son.
Hey, the reason
Bob can't hear
is 'cause
his eardrums blew up
after you shot him
out of the volcano!
I can't hear you!
You stupid butt!
What? Can you believe
what they're saying?
It's like I'm being treated
worse than anyone
in the history of the world.
A good thing you never have to
experience anything
like this, La-Loyd.
Yeah. Yeah. No one ever says
mean things to me
when my dad knocks over
their Pilates studio,
or their waxing salon,
or their kayak repair store,
or that place
that sells toner cartridges.
And you better believe
no one ever makes fun of me,
for not knowing
how to throw or catch a ball.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Hold on.
I know it's funny,
but what kind of jerk
would make fun of you
for that?
You're kidding, right?
You gotta stand up
for yourself,
and shoot them out
of a volcano.
That's how I roll.
You gotta get yourself
a volcano, kid.
Yeah.
Blowing stuff up
and never putting it
back together.
That is what you're best at,
isn't it?
Well, hello!
We have got a present for you.
Fire him! Fire him! Fire him!
Oh, an exact reproduction
of my volcanic lair.
And let me guess,
you're going to fire us
out of it.
Oh, no, we're gonna fire you
into the volcano.
The 15 million kelvin magma
will melt your skin
before you can even feel
the heat!
Omar, take them to the top.
Okey-dokey.
Up you go!
Whoa.
What is that?
- Hey!
- What's up?
Zane! Are you okay?
I think I might be
an adrenaline junkie.
I got you, dude!
I got you!
I really could've walked out
by myself,
but thank you. Ow!
Wait, where's Lloyd?
- Um...
- Uh...
Oh, no.
I can't believe we just ran
off and left him back there.
This is terrible.
We are horrible friends.
And sub-par ninjas, too.
That's right. That's right.
Wait. Guys...
Fire him! Fire him!
- Um...
- Oh, no!
Lloyd!
- He's in trouble.
- Oh, man.
What are we going to do?
We can still do this, guys.
We just gotta figure out
how to be real ninjas.
You know what would be
really brave?
Making camp,
sleeping for the night,
wake up in the day.
Yeah, that's brave.
Wait, Zane, don't you have,
like, 700 gigabytes
of martial arts movies
on your hard drive?
- Correct!
- Great! Roll 'em.
Zane's
Martial Arts Movie Club.
- The Deadly Groundskeeper.
- Cop Tale Three.
- The Iceman Puncheth.
- Furious Fire Fist.
- Wall-puncher.
- Good Girls Versus Bad Guys.
- Killer Bills, Volume 2.
- Board Game of Death.
- Spear Dancer.
- The Mainframe.
- Caffeinated Master.
- Hip Man.
Judo Future Boy.
Locke Two: The Joy Locke Club.
I Told You
You're Wasting Your Time
I Vowed To Give Up
That Way Of Life.
- Look Who's Punching.
- Look Who's Punching Too.
- Whoa!
- Ay, ay, ay!
I learned so many things
so fast.
- That's right. That's right.
- I'm ready.
Time to get down and dirty.
Ninja style.
- Oh, yeah.
- Right!
Whoa, is that a whale?
Guys, no swimming.
We just ate!
Time to blend in.
Fire him! Fire him! Fire him!
La-Loyd...
Yeah.
Um... I...
I just...
- Lloyd!
- Guys!
Oh, hey!
Oh, my gosh!
How did you all get up here?
Oh, man.
We did all that stuff
that you and Master Wu
told us to do.
Ninja style, bro.
Whoa!
All right.
Let's get outta here
and make it to
the Ultimate Ultimate Weapon.
That's not gonna be easy,
girl ninja.
Because I fired
a ridic amount of generals.
All right, all right.
I got an idea.
If we can hold these
generals off long enough,
we can build a way
out of here.
Great idea.
You kids start building.
La-Loyd and I will
throw you bricks.
Lloyd, I need a two-by-two.
Here it comes.
That was terrible.
Throw me a couple one-bys.
I got it. Check this out.
How can you be so bad at this?
Yeah. You got a mental block?
Hang on, everybody.
You ninjas, keep at it.
La-Loyd, you're coming
with me.
I'll be in charge
of the tunes.
I'll just put it
on shuffle here.
Please not Jim Croce,
please not Jim Croce.
Ah! Jinxed us. Whatever.
All right!
Ninjas, keep building!
La-Loyd, I'm gonna teach you
how to throw.
Come on!
- Nya, look alive!
- Thank you.
Yeah!
Run for it.
Lloyd!
Over here, I'm open.
Okay. All right.
I can do this.
Quiet your mind, La-Loyd.
Okay.
Throw like no one's watching
except your judging father.
Not helping.
Oh, right.
You got this. Do it.
- Ha! La-Loyd.
- Yes!
Look at that.
I actually taught you
- how to do something.
- Right?
- Nice! Dude, that was awesome!
- You did it, Lloyd!
Cole, catch.
- Kai.
- Right here, I'm open!
- Great throw.
- Give me another. Quick!
Zane, your turn, buddy.
Whoa!
You've got
a cannon for an arm.
Seriously,
an awesome throw.
La-Loyd, something's
happening to my face.
It's turning upwards
in an unfamiliar motion.
Oh, I think they've deployed
nerve gas!
It's happening to you, too!
Listen, listen. We're smiling!
What is this "smiling"?
Go with it!
It feels good, right?
It does.
Oh, this whole experience
is so foreign to me.
- I know, right?
- Yeah!
All right, here it comes.
La-Loyd!
Time to fire you out...
La-Loyd, are you okay?
Yeah, yeah!
I think it was my arm.
Is it bad?
- Whoa!
- I don't wanna look!
It looks okay, I guess.
Scale of one to 10,
how bad is it?
Oh, I'd say it's about
a seven-point...
Arm-ripped-off.
My arm is what? What did...
Say it one more time?
Just, don't look down.
Don't look down
below your neck.
Don't do that face.
Why are you doing that face?
It's just a harmless little...
I gotta puke. It's disgusting.
Should I look?
I looked! I have no arm!
I have no arm! No!
I told you it was bad.
Ah! That's way worse
than anything
I could have thought!
That's bad!
You're gonna be fine.
Let me text your mother.
Dad, no! I need you!
Stay with me!
Be here with me right now,
all right? Do something.
All right, I'm gonna find it.
What does it look like?
It looks like my left arm,
except it's the right one.
Oh, of course, yes.
Okay, everybody, fan out,
form a grid.
Find La-Loyd's arm.
It's got a little hand
like a cup holder
and a black sleeve and
a little piece of green on it.
You'll know it
when you see it.
It's La-Loyd's arm,
for heaven's sake.
- Does this look like it?
- No.
All right,
let's try this arm out.
That's a leg.
Have you ever had
an arm that kicks?
- I mean, that could be cool.
- Can't say I have.
Hey, how about this one?
That's a sword.
That's a sword!
Oh, man, to have a sword arm,
that'd be sweet!
You know, the idea of it
is a lot cooler
than the reality.
Oh, oh, wait...
Wait a minute. Found it!
- Here we go!
- Okay.
I'm gonna pop that arm
back into place.
Okay, wait, wait, wait.
But it's only gonna hurt
for a second, right?
Hurt for a second? No!
This is gonna be agony
for a while.
Who gave you
that misinformation?
All right, all right,
all right.
Just do it, just do it,
just do it.
Okay. On the count of 12...
No, no, no, no.
I don't wanna do 12.
Let's do... Let's do, like,
a, you know, three.
Okay, three.
One,
two...
Ah! I wish your mom
was here to do this.
You're killing me. You got...
You gotta just do it.
All right. One,
two,
three.
Wow.
It, uh...
Feels, uh...
It feels pretty good.
Feels pretty good.
You did that,
put my arm back on
like a real dad.
You...
You called me "Dad."
Yeah.
Wow! I guess I...
I guess I did.
I really stepped up there
in kind of a "Dad" way.
Right?
Lloyd, come on!
We gotta get outta here!
- Come on!
- Run! Run!
Guys, we have to go.
- Hurry! Hurry!
- Come on!
Let's get moving.
Come on, everybody, let's go!
I can't believe
it worked.
Temple, here we come!
Hey, La-Loyd,
let me show you
how to fly this thing.
Hands, 10 and two.
I build and drive mechs
all the time.
I think I'm good.
Oh. Okay. Yeah,
you're probably right.
Um... What, uh...
What were you saying?
10 and...
- Oh, two! 10 and two.
- Two. Two.
- Yeah, just 10 and two.
- Okay, all right, all right.
That's kind of a rule of thumb
- in driving.
- That's good to know.
And don't forget
to check your rear-view.
You wanna see
what's back there.
You have blind spots
everywhere.
Rear-view, check.
Keep your eyes peeled.
You really wanna be
looking ahead.
Noted, thank you.
You want me to really
open this thing up?
Sure. Yeah,
let's see what it can do.
Okay.
Yeah!
Okay, that's enough!
- That's too fast.
- You didn't like that?
I mean, I liked it.
If I was driving,
- I would be fine with it.
- Sure, sure.
Right. I felt a little scared.
Were you scared?
Um, yeah. I'm not gonna lie,
I might need
a change of armor.
I want you to guard
the brake a little bit.
Okay, okay, got it, got it.
You're doing great, buddy,
this is going real... Goat!
Goat, goat, goat!
Is everyone okay?
- Not really.
- Huh?
Behold, the Temple
of Fragile Foundations.
The helicopter crash has
destabilized the entire area.
And I'm not blaming anyone,
but if I ever see
that goat again,
he and I are gonna have words.
And you can bet
some of those words
are gonna have four letters.
And I'm not talking
about "goat."
Give us the first letter.
This is my new least
favorite place I've ever been.
I've spent a lot
of time here, and trust me,
doesn't get any better.
Wait a minute.
So, you know this place?
Who doesn't know
their childhood home?
Yeah, this place
is so unstable
I had to move to a volcano
just to feel safe.
Well, shall we?
Stay close.
I will lead you
through this perilous...
Oh, look, a light switch.
Do you guys have
a bathroom I could use?
Nope.
Fresh fruit!
- Finally, food!
- I'm starving!
Ow! I think I chipped a tooth.
Yeah, my parents were really
into plastic fruit.
Whoa! Check out
those old photos.
Look at that!
Aw! They're so cute!
Look at his baby goatee!
I mean, Master Wu
looks like a really old man.
He even
schooled you back then.
Whatevz.
Come on, let's go find
the Ultimate Ultimate Weapon.
Wait.
That's... That's you.
And that's...
It's Lady Iron Dragon,
my hero!
Yes, Lady Iron Dragon,
aka La-Loyd's mom.
Wait, what?
Mom was a ninja?
That's right.
She was the most awesome
ninja warrior I'd ever seen.
I remember the first time
I laid eyes on her.
It was during a raging war.
I was pillaging
a peaceful village
with my skeleton army
when I spotted this beautiful
warrior queen
from across
a crowded battlefield.
She was fighting for good
and looking great doing it.
Even as she decimated
my evil forces,
I couldn't take
my eyes off her.
I was speechless.
I summoned all my courage
to approach her.
I asked her
if she fought here often.
She said, "I do."
And let me tell you, La-Loyd.
When our eyes met,
sparks flew.
It was love at first fight!
Your mother and I
were a true power couple.
I thought we were gonna
conquer the world together.
It was the happiest
time of my life.
Wait a minute.
If you guys were so perfect,
then why did you leave us?
It's...
Complicated.
One day, we came upon NINJAGO.
I told your mother
that I wanted to build
our son's future
on the ashes
of that fine city.
But it was at that moment
that your mother realized...
...that the life
of a conquering warlord...
...was not the life
she wanted...
For you.
I could've changed.
But I didn't.
And before I knew it...
She was gone...
And you were gone.
La-Loyd,
your mom was the best.
She expected the best of me
and only ever wanted
the best for you.
I never should
have let you go.
Lloyd! We found
the Ultimate Ultimate Weapon!
Here, in the bedroom!
We think it's in that box.
Open it, open it, open it!
Whoa!
What a bunch of junk.
Maybe there's something
important under it.
This is the Ultimate
Ultimate Disappointment.
- Correct.
- No. Wait.
There's a piece for each
of our elements.
Fire.
Whoa!
And earth.
This rocks!
- And water.
- H-2, oh yeah!
And ice.
Cool.
And lightning.
Ah!
And I'm... Green.
But I'm so happy for you guys.
Yay.
You know, La-Loyd,
after spending
all this time with you,
seeing the amazing ninja
warrior you've become...
Yeah?
You know, I've realized
that we don't need
to fight each other
when we can fight
alongside each other.
Really?
Yeah.
La-Loyd, will you go back
to NINJAGO with me
as father...
...and General Number One?
Wait, what? You...
You're General Number One?
Exactly!
But... But you just said how
you regretted letting me go.
Because you'd make the perfect
General Number One.
We're an amazing team,
La-Loyd.
You, me,
the Ultimate Ultimate Weapon.
We'd be unstoppable.
No. I don't wanna be
your General Number One.
But just imagine it.
We can rule NINJAGO, together.
Come with me, La-Loyd.
We have so much lost time
to make up for!
And since I'll no longer
be attacking the city,
no one will hate you anymore.
And I'll never forget
your birthday again
because we'll celebrate
your birthday every day!
And think of all the things
I could teach you.
Tie a tie, ride a bike,
conquer a city.
And if we leave now,
we can unleash
the Ultimate Ultimate Weapon
on Meowthra
and conquer NINJAGO together.
Come on!
Dad, please don't.
Come back to NINJAGO with me
and save the city.
- What?
- You'll be a hero.
But that's not who I am,
La-Loyd.
People would never
see me as a hero.
But it doesn't
have to be this way.
This is your chance
to make a change.
I didn't want it to be
this way either,
but here we are.
Dad, please, don't go.
If I couldn't change then,
what makes you think
I could change now?
No, no.
- Stop!
- No, no, no!
- Back off!
- No way!
Hey, that's my sister!
- Get off my face!
- Bam!
- I got it!
- Give that back!
I can help you.
We can do it together.
If you just give me the box,
we can talk about it.
I can't.
You'll just leave.
- I got it!
- Look out!
- Cole!
- Gotcha! Nice try.
We're like
the Harlem Globetrotters.
Hey!
- Over here, over here!
- Get outta my way.
Lloyd, catch it!
- Run, Lloyd! Run!
- I got it!
I got it! I got it!
Predictable but regrettable.
Bummer.
Oh, La-Loyd.
Dad.
I should have taught you
how to catch.
No!
So long, La-Loyd.
Get outta the way! This whole
thing is coming down!
We don't have those pieces.
Yeah, and we don't
even have our mechs.
We're doomed!
- Oh, no! We're gonna die.
- What do we do?
Our chances
of survival are 0.00...
Stay on the right path
to find your inner peace.
Did he say inner peace?
The power is inside you.
Inner peace?
Find your inner peace.
Inner peace! Inner piece!
Guys. Guys, we don't
need those pieces.
The Ultimate Ultimate Weapon
is inside of you.
- What?
- Yes, you have the power.
Look within.
Harness what you already have
inside and let it out.
I believe in each of you.
Nya, you can create water.
Kai, you can make fire.
Okay. All right.
I can make a fire.
The power is inside
of all of you.
Now, calm your mind.
Concentrate.
Build up your powers.
Just think about earth,
fire, water, ice.
And you, Jay, lightning, baby.
Do it!
Jay, you got the power!
Say, "I've got the power!"
I've got the power!
I've got the power.
Good work, Cole.
Go, go, go!
I've got the power.
I too, have the power.
Here we go.
Come on, hurry up.
What now?
- Kai, your turn.
- Got it.
I've got the power!
I think I made it worse!
Jump, Lloyd. Jump.
Master Wu?
Guys, I can hear the dead,
and Master Wu says to jump!
Great jump, students.
Master Wu!
You're alive!
Of course.
I'm a ninja master
who lives life on the edge
and cheats death
at every turn.
- Wow!
- Really?
No. I thought being dead
would make you listen
to me more.
And I was right.
Master Wu, we found
our elemental powers.
All because Lloyd wouldn't
give up on our training.
Lloyd saved us.
He also decoded your
needlessly cryptic metaphors.
Lloyd, I'm so proud of you.
You helped your friends
be great.
And that makes you
truly a ninja master.
Now, let's go save the city
from the giant kitty.
I second that!
This cat
is destroying everything!
Where are the Ninjas
when we need them?
We have to evacuate!
Run! Run!
Hey, NINJAGO,
Garmadon's back!
Generals, stop anyone
that gets in my way.
Yes, sir.
Whoa,
it's the Destiny's Bounty.
I've always wanted
to shoot at it.
Attack!
Alpha team, on it.
We have company.
Hold on tight.
Hey, where'd they go?
All right, Ninjas,
follow me.
Ninja, go!
- Yeah!
Nya, we need to get
to Garmadon and that cat fast.
You got it.
All right, you beast.
Get ready to feel the wrath of
the Ultimate Ultimate Weapon.
Hmm?
Here they come.
Come on! Let's go!
Follow Nya.
Take that.
What?
- Zane, freeze these guys out.
- Copy.
Kai, make a smoke screen.
Yeah, baby! Fu-fu-fuego!
Where'd they go?
I can't see them anywhere.
Okay. Well, how about this?
Hyah!
These things aren't working.
Jay, now's your chance, buddy.
Roger that.
Let's rock!
Hey, cat, back off!
I'm Garmadon, baby.
I'm the greatest
warlord of all...
Somebody help me!
- Dad?
- Please!
Go, ninjas, go!
Hip hip hooray!
The cat ate Garmadon!
Now all we have to do
is take out the cat
and NINJAGO is saved.
- Get him!
- Take out that monster!
Blast that cat
with your awesome hand powers.
La-Loyd! Please help me!
Oh, I can use my fire.
But is that too much?
Or I could blast him
with my water.
Cats hate water.
You were right, Master Wu.
I need to walk the path
that only the son of Garmadon
can walk.
Oh, my gosh!
The Green Ninja
is Lloyd Garmadon?
Lloyd.
All we have to do is scare off
Meowthra and we've won.
- No.
- What?
Uh, Lloyd,
where are you going?
Lloyd? Come back.
Here, kitty,
kitty, kitty.
Yeah, come here.
Lloyd, no!
It's okay. He's got this.
That's a good kitty.
You're okay.
Yeah, you're okay.
Yeah, yeah,
that's a good kitty.
What a sweet, sweet kitty.
Everything's gonna be
just fine.
Hey. I know it.
I know it. You don't mean
to destroy everything.
When, uh...
When people look at you,
they see a monster.
But I know that
you just feel
scared and alone.
I know how that feels.
To be judged unfairly.
So, um... I just wanna say
that I forgive you.
And...
I'm sorry.
When I said "I wish
you weren't my father,"
I didn't really mean it.
What I...
What I should've said is
I wish we didn't
fight all of the time.
I wish I could've
spent more time with you.
And that you could've seen,
like, everything
I've been through,
but you weren't there.
I wish we could get
that time back, and...
I need my dad.
I just... I need my dad.
Oh! Whoa! Whoa!
Dad!
- Are... Are you okay?
- Yeah, I'm fine.
You're alive!
Son?
Yeah?
Did you mean
all that stuff you said?
To the cat?
Every word.
Well, I know for a fact
that the cat feels exactly
the same way.
Dad? Are you crying?
No!
It's just that
I'm kind of allergic to cats.
- Lloyd!
- Mom!
Let me look at you. Let me
look at you. Are you hurt?
Let me see
your fingers and toes.
Okay. You still don't have
fingers and toes. That's good.
- Is everything okay?
- I'm... I'm fine. I'm good.
Lloyd, I was
so worried about you.
Mom. Mom, wait!
I'm, uh... I'm sorry.
It's okay. I'm just...
I'm just so happy
you're all right.
No. Mom, I'm really sorry.
I took you for granted.
All you ever did
was support me.
The real me.
The person I am on the inside.
Oh.
I'm really sorry, Mom.
I love you so much.
I love you, too.
Bring it in.
Let's hug this out.
Okay. That's cool. Uh...
I found two people
to hug me over here.
Uncle Wu,
I know why you wanted me
to be the Green Ninja.
Oh, you do?
Yeah.
Green is the color of life.
It flows through
all living things,
connecting them all.
The way I connect the Ninjas.
Hi!
Or the way I connect
my family,
whether we're together or not.
Some powers are ones
you cannot see,
but those are the most
important powers of all.
Lloyd was a hero.
Who are you talking to?
He saved Garmadon
and he saved his family.
We're standing right here.
And the whole city of NINJAGO.
Where are you going?
They even made Meowthra
the mascot.
She's so fluffy!
I love her.
Wu, come back!
Koko and Nya
opened a school
to teach former shark generals
life skills.
And Garmadon taught Lloyd
something very important.
Hey, catch!
Whoa.
And Lloyd taught everyone
that even if you're different,
you can still do great things.
Whoa!
So does that mean
I'm a ninja now?
No.
All you did
was listen to a story.
Doesn't make you
a martial artist.
Or does it?
Okay, okay, okay.
Listen, to be a master,
it takes patience,
hard work,
courage, and...
Whoa.
Good.
Your training begins at dawn.
Whoa.
Can we bring the cat?
No.
Okay, kids.
There's one last thing
I have to teach you ninjas.
Get on your feet. You ready?
Here comes the Dance of Doom.
A mark.
Jackie Chan!
B mark.
Subtitles by explosiveskull
Resync by GoldenBeard
Please rate this subtitle at www.osdb.link/5aws7
Help other users to choose the best subtitles