Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
Mom, Mom!
Uncle Jonas is here!
No, it's not Tuesday today.
But he is. He's here.
So, after
the Germans surrendered,
when did our king return
to Norway from exile?
Um...
June 7th, 1945.
And on what date
did the Norwegian Parliament
hold its first election
after the war?
Um...
- July 6...
- Don't guess.
Uh...
August...
On what date
did the Norwegian Parliament hold
its first election since the war?
Uh.,.
August... August 12th, 1945.
You have to help him more.
I'm going to tell your wife
that he's your son.
And then she can tell
the rest of your family.
Then you'll never see me again.
Stop! Please!
Wait!
No!
Jonas!
No! Jonas! No!
Mom!
Mom?
Mom, come on,
we've gotta get outta here!
Mom, come on!
Open the door!
Mom, come on! Open the door!
Mom!
No!
Don't leave me!
Shit.
Morning.
Fuck it!
Piece of shit.
Harry Hole?
Hello.
Dry rot throughout
the whole building,
and I'm afraid
we've found some mold
behind the walls.
Aspergillus, toxic,
and pathogenic.
Yeah, your landlord let me in
to spray the apartment.
I'm gonna have to take
all these panels off,
and this is above your bed.
Jesus Christ.
Is there anywhere else
that you could stay?
The air in here is so bad, you're
actually killing your house plants.
I'm not disturbing you, am I?
You are familiar
with Emanuel Vigeland.
The brothers' work was most likely
influenced by their father,
who turned to drink, had an illegitimate
child with a younger woman.
You can clearly see
in each artist's case,
the recurring themes of love,
perverted and betrayed...
The good news is that with
this new version of the EviSync,
from version 3.6
to version 4.0,
allows you to
manually push the data
back to the server
using the cellular network.
The EviSync will automatically
upload all the new data
to the central police server
here, every 12 hours.
We've also done some work on the
fingerprint scanning software.
So, you will notice
a significantly faster
opening time after scanning
your fingerprint.
But please make sure
that your fingerprint scans
are done cleanly,
and clearly from the start.
If you are experiencing a
high number of false scans,
this is probably because your fingerprints
were scanned incorrectly from the start.
That must be nearly a whole
week of mail this time.
Did I miss anything
while I was away?
My uncle died.
Close, were you?
A leave of absence has to be
formally requested, in writing.
Doesn't matter who you are.
Backdate it,
but I can't keep
covering for you.
I'm dealing with it.
I need a case to work on.
I apologize for
Oslo's low murder rate.
Let's, uh,
stick to the uncle story.
You scared my clients away.
I didn't forget Oleg's birthday.
I got him concert tickets.
What did you do?
We took him for a pizza.
Oleg misses you.
He doesn't get along
very well with Mathias.
What about you?
I'm not going to answer that.
He wants to meet
his real father.
I don't think
he's ready for that.
Thank you for
walking me back home.
See you at the game.
Tell Oleg I'm sorry I missed it.
Hi!
The snowman.
What?
Snowman!
I'll take a picture.
Beautiful, honey.
Mum!
Hi.
Hello.
Can I borrow your scarf?
You want my scarf? Here.
I told you
I had to leave by 8:00.
And I told you that I had
to help one of my students.
No, thanks.
It's the smoking room.
Yeah, but it's the only place
I can concentrate, so...
I'm, um...
I'm Katrine Bratt.
Harry Hole.
I know who you are. We, um... We actually
studied your cases at the academy.
I didn't know
they date back that far.
Yeah' you're up there
with the legends, so...
I don't know who you are.
No, I'm new. I, um...
I transferred from Bergen.
Actually, they've put me
in your office.
Okay. Bye.
Mom?
Mommy?
Mommy.
Okay, where can I drop you?
I'm on a call.
It's okay.
I'm in no hurry.
So, why don't you have a car?
I don't have a license.
Missing persons?
Yeah, it's a woman.
The call just came in.
So, this machine is called
“EviSync and I will record you,
so, there's a little camera on the
other side. You're aware of it.
Right.
Would you like to walk me
through what happened?
Well, I saw Josephine in
the garden in her pajamas.
And I thought, "What is she
doing out in this cold?"
So, I came over to check.
And she said she couldn't
find her mother.
I tried calling the father, but
apparently, he's away on business.
How long has she been missing?
Two days.
She said she was going to visit a
friend, and she never came back.
Why did you come to me?
I've been suspended.
Because you're a friend.
And you're a great detective.
But I don't want anyone
knowing about this just yet.
Not yet. I don't
wanna go to the police.
Can you tell me, was
your wife seeing anyone?
I, uh, checked
her credit card bills.
She's been to see
a pregnancy doctor.
Well, that... That's
great news, Frederik.
We haven't shared a bed
in three years.
This is Birte Becker.
Please leave a message.
This is Bide Becker.
This is Birte Becker.
Hello, Mr. Donkey.
Can I sit down?
It's a nice place you've got here, Mr.
Donkey.
Did you do this by yourself?
My mom helped me.
Was she in a good mood
when she got home?
Mmm.
And what about your dad'?
He was grumpy again
'cause Mommy was late.
Did she call to say
she'd be late?
My dad doesn't want me
to have a phone.
She didn't phone the house?
Is he grumpy often?
Has your mother
been upset lately,
when your father's been grumpy?
Have you ever seen her cry?
No. But I saw Daddy cry.
When?
A few nights ago.
He saw me, too.
What did he do?
Locked himself in the bathroom.
Where was Mommy
when he was crying?
She'd gone out.
Oh...
Shit.
Yeah, is this Filip Becker?
Yeah, I'm gonna have to call you back.
I better go. Thank you.
He cried last week.
Why did you build the snowman
facing the house?
I didn't build the snowman.
This is Birte Becker.
Please leave a message.
This is Bide Becker.
Do you want a coffee,
or something?
No.
Look, you're not gonna try
and sleep with me, are you?
No.
Okay, good.
She'll show up.
She's having an affair.
She left her coat and her
handbag in the house,
and the front door was open.
Even if you're having an affair,
you do not leave
your child like that.
And, Harry,
she's not the only one.
Look, this is Hege Dahl.
Missing two weeks.
Similar age, young children.
Unhappy marriage.
Talk to the husband.
411 to dispatch-
Dispatch, do you receive?
Go ahead, 411.
Up in Mount Ulriken.
It looks like a homicide.
Adult female. It's hard to see from
here, but there's a Jot of blood.
A group of
school children found her.
I've got a problem.
Rafto just showed up.
What the hell's he doing there?
He's been suspended.
Try telling him that.
We'll' send the
kids down with their teacher.
Make sure there's a care
officer to meet them,
and someone to deal
with the parents.
One of the children,
they heard a noise'
and they went to see
what it was.
Listen, listen.
John, John.
I'm gonna need you
to calm down. Calm down.
It's important that you answer my
questions and give me the information.
- Who's in charge?
- Svenson.
OFFICER 2; Jesus.
I! Gets worse.
Rafto just arrived.
Perfect,
the drunk and the halfwit.
Just keep them apart, will you?
I'll see what I can do.
Where are you going?
Rafto!
We're closed.
It's all right.
You have something of mine.
It's not yours.
Cold case.
I have clearance to take it
out, you don't.
So, what'?
You're gonna report me?
Eli Kvale. Tell me.
She was married.
She left three children.
The 12th of November, six
years ago, she went missing.
And the day she vanished,
it was snowing.
Hege Dahl disappeared
the 8th of November.
The day she went missing,
it was snowing.
Not unusual, it's winter.
Now, Birte Becker.
The night she disappeared...
Snowing.
Yeah.
I think it's the falling snow
that sets the killer off.
And furthermore,
they're all married,
they all have children.
Did you talk to Filip Becker?
Nine times out of 10,
the husband did it.
He was interviewed and his alibi is solid.
He was 100 miles away.
Have you eaten?
No.
No, I haven't. I'm hungry.
"Twenty-eighth,
handball."
Josephine's handball match.
"Third, F. Lunch."
That's lunch
with her friend, Frida.
I really... I don't see
the point in doing this.
I won't keep you much longer.
"Ninth, Vetlesen."
He's her doctor.
Tenth...
Do you have any idea why
your wife went to see him?
Who?
Dr. Vetlesen.
No.
"Tenth, yoga."
ls there any reason
you can think of
why your wife might
disappear so suddenly'?
Your marriage,
was everything all right?
Were either of you
having an affair?
Daddy!
Come on!
I promised her we'd
walk around the neighborhood
to see if we could find
her mother.
I'm just gonna get
my jacket, darling!
Come out! Dad!
Step inside.
Mmm. I thought
you wouldn't remember.
Is he still
giving you a hard time?
If you want, I can talk to him.
Oh!
Just have fun tonight.
He misses you.
Hi, Harry.
Good to see you.
Sorry I'm late, honey.
Have you had anything to eat?
No, I'll grab something later.
No' no, no,
but I've got vouchers.
Yeah?
Yep.
Hot dog, or hot dog.
Well, hot dog, then.
Harry?
I'll get something to eat
with Oleg after.
So, how are things with you?
All right.
Yeah?
A bit tired.
You've been working
too hard, haven't you?
I can't sleep.
You should try Valzetai.
It's a new one.
It'll help you sleep.
I can give you
a prescription right now.
Really?
Yeah.
With that?
She won't allow me to
try and find my father.
Your mother should be
the judge of that.
She won't listen to me.
She's worried about you.
All she cares about is herself.
All she cares about is you.
That's why she dumped me.
I'm such a bad influence.
She's concerned.
Concerned about what?
The fact that you
run away from home.
The fact that
you've been drinking.
So, you're gonna give me a
lecture about drinking?
Don't be a prick.
Your mum told me
the school's arranged
a father-and-son
camping trip.
If you want, I can come.
But you're not
her boyfriend anymore.
So?
Yeah. Yeah,
I want you to come.
You sure?
Yeah.
Good.
So, what's the big surprise?
Uh...
Let's find out. Someone at
work got me the tickets.
You've got a message.
Let me see what it says!
I gotta make a call!
You staying here?
Harry, there's another
missing woman. In Geilo this time.
That's not our jurisdiction.
I think we should have
a look at this.
I'm gonna be with you
in two minutes, okay?
Her husband
specifically asked for you.
- Hello.
- Hi.
Oh, didn't expect you so early.
Something came up.
Oh.
Hi, Harry.
- Hi.
- How was the concert?
Yeah, it was great.
We spoke.
I'm taking him on the
father-and-son camping trip
thing.
See you.
Hey.
Bye.
Take me home. We'll go in the morning.
Who reported her missing?
Her husband,
last night, 20:05.
Sylvia Ottersen, 33 years old.
Self-employed.
Married twice.
But no children.
Hello?
Hi.
Can I help you?
Yeah, well, we're with
the Oslo Police.
We got the missing persons call.
Oh. Who's missing?
Sylvia Ottersen.
I'm Sylvia Ottersen.
What, you're
Sylvia Ottersen? Why...
Why would your husband
report you missing?
No idea. He's not the kind
to play practical jokes.
Is he here?
No.
He's gone to the station
to pick up my sister.
Okay. Well, I guess
it must be a prank call.
We didn't know where you were,
so, we had a look inside
the house.
I turned your music off.
Sorry about that.
Thank you.
Can I just ask you, is it
just you and your husband,
or do you have any children?
No, it's just us.
Okay, thank you.
What the hell
do you think you're doing?
You know damn well
what I'm talking about.
Calling the police,
telling them I'm missing.
You think that's funny?
Don't you understand?
It's over.
I don't want to see you again.
No, it wasn't your child.
It was mine.
If you call one more time,
I'm going to the police.
HQ to DC Brett.
DC Brett.
Yeah, speaking.
We've had
a missing persons report,
a woman named Sylvia Ottersen.
No, she's fine.
We just left her.
Well, the call came in
two minutes ago.
Her husband asked specifically
for Inspector Hole.
How could...
Turn the car around.
Sylvia?
Sorry we're back,
Mrs. Ottersen.
We just wanted to make sure
you were all right.
I'm Ane Pedersen.
Sylvia is my sister. We're twins.
Who are you?
Is that enough?
Yeah, keep going.
Did you find Hagen?
He's at the dinner at City Hall.
Keep it clear if you can.
She was a free spirit.
And she always liked men,
ever since we were teenagers.
She was a good person.
She didn't want to hurt anyone.
It's just the way she was.
I know your sister
didn't have any children.
It was just that
there was something
in her reaction,
that when I asked.“
She was pregnant.
She wasn't sure
who the father was.
She got rid of the baby
a few weeks ago.
Ladies and gentlemen,
introducing our guest of honor,
king of industry,
philanthropist,
and head of Oslo's Winter
Games bid, Arve Stop!
So lovely of you
to be here for us.
I'm not on the list,
but I know many of these people.
I'm supposed to be on the list.
I'm a close old friend
of Arve Stop's, you see.
There's been some kind
of misunderstanding.
I have a person named Vetlesen.
Come on up.
You can come here.
He says
he's a friend of Arve Stop.
No. Wait, wait. No,
it's fine, it's fine.
No, just relax, just relax.
I run over a dozen companies.
When people ask me
why I've given up so much of
my time to lead this bio',
I tell them it's because s'
never had these opportunities.
When I was a boy,
the only winter sports
I engaged in were
the uphill snow shove! And the
50-meter firewood carry.
Thar is why I believe
passionately that this Cup
is about much more than just
publicity for our fair city.
Homicides?
Just missing persons for now,
but the pattern is disturbing.
And I received this.
Prints?
It isn't just the letter.
He reported her missing
before he killed her.
He was watching us
the entire time.
What do you need?
A small team.
I'll set up a separate
incident room at the mill.
All right, but I don't want
a word of this to be leaked...
To the press.
Press. Yeah, not until
this fucking bid is over.
You look very pretty tonight.
You know that.
And now you're trying t0... You
see, now you try to smile.
Smile, smile.
That's great.
Does this strike you as the
proper time and place for this?
Wait.
Idiot.
What? Arve?
What? No, don't cry.
It's...
Why...
Shit.
Hey.
Hey!
Get out.
Get out!
Hey!
Oi, mate!
Annette Elden, 33,
disappeared 12th of December, 2006.
Her head washed ashore
near Arendal,
rest of the body never found.
Forensic reports indicate
saw marks on her neck.
Status, unmarried,
two children
by different fathers.
Harry, I've got the names
and the addresses
of Sylvia Ottersen's boyfriends.
Now, she went to the clinic
the second of November,
but they won't break
patient confidentiality.
They do, however,
perform abortions.
What is it?
- Magnus, get me the list.
- What list?
The list of doctors
at the Gellion.
I'm thinking that he's going after
women that he disapproves of.
Here. All the doctors at Gellion
from the last five years.
How did he know? How did he know
Sylvia Ottersen was pregnant?
"Idar Vetlesen."
Birte Becker had an appointment
with the same doctor.
Dr. Idar Vetlesen?
Yes, that's me.
Step in.
Birte Becker and Sylvia Ottersen
were both patients of yours?
No, they were both
patients at the clinic.
I never met Sylvia Ottersen.
Can you tell me who treated her?
No, I'm bound by
patient confidentiality.
She's dead.
Oh...
Oh, no.
Right. Well,
doctor confidentiality.
In theory, would it be possible for
you to access her medical files?
Even if you didn't
treat her yourself.
Well, in theory, yes.
The doctors at the clinic have
access to the files of every patient
should they choose to look
at them, which I did not.
What did you see
Birte Becker about?
Well, that is confidential.
How do you know Awe Stop?
Awe?
Well, I've known Arve for years.
I do research
in premature birth.
We have a small charity, and Arve Stop
is one of our biggest supporters.
Huh. Wouldn't have
thought that a man
who goes on so much
about family values
would support a clinic that
specializes in abortion.
Well, we specialize
in many different areas.
And Mr. Stop supports our
research in premature birth.
So, do you see
each other socially?
Yeah, well, that
depends on how you mean...
It is quite simple, actually.
Do you have friends in common?
Yes, we mix
in the same circles, so...
Why are you...
Have you ever practiced in other
parts of the country, Dr. Vetlesen?
Yes.
I have' in Eidsvoll,
in Lillehammer...
I see you have a picture of Mon
Plaisir pavilion in Bergen.
Yes. Yes, in Bergen.
Do you live alone?
Yes, I, uh...
lam a reluctant bachelor.
Is there anyone in
the house right now?
Because I thought I saw someone
in the window when I passed.
Well, if you want to
take a look around,
I will need to see
a search warrant.
In fact, if you don't mind,
I would like to call my lawyer
before I answer any more
of your questions.
That won't be necessary,
Dr. Vetlesen.
You can bring your lawyer
when we see you next time.
Hey. Hey.
What was that?
What?
He isn't a suspect yet. We need his
permission to search the house.
I know that.
Why'd you ask him
about Arve Stop?
I saw a picture of
them both together.
And?
And it was an innocent question.
Jesus. Anyone can see he's
trying to hide something.
Like a Netflix
type thing. Oh, hey.
Cloudberry.
If you hadn't told me
to look out for it,
I'd have assumed she was
attached to his security detail.
Cloudberry?
It's her password.
Does this
strike you as the proper time
and place for this?
Awe Stop.
Idiot.
She filmed him
at rallies,
at restaurants, at home.
Hi. Do you want a ride?
No.
Bye.
The 8:45 train to
Bergen is leaving from platform five.
Oh, sorry.
This is the
8:45 service to Bergen,
stopping at Gol,
Finse, Voss, and Bergen.
The next station is Gol.
Hi, Harry.
Hi.
Hiding in the playroom, are we?
Yes.
Don't worry. I'm getting
off at the next stop.
Going far?
Bergen.
Ah. Rather you than me.
Then again,
I am attending
a three-day conference
on bio-identical
hormone restoration.
I thought you were
a plastic surgeon.
Well, you know, cosmetic surgery
needs to move with the times, too.
We're swapping the scalpel for
hormone replacement therapy.
If you can slow down
the aging process,
there won't be any need for
face lifts, will there?
I'll bear that in mind.
So, how's the prescription
working?
Sleeping like a baby.
Splendid.
So, you canceled the Oleg thing.
The school trip, weren't
you supposed to...
Oh, shit.
I'm sorry, Harry.
Ah... I'm sure he's fine.
He knows how busy you are.
Shit!
Look. Look, you're not
his father, Harry.
What does that mean?
Well, uh...
I don't have to be his father
to care about him.
I was just trying to say that
it's a big enough responsibility
for a real father, isn't it?
Let alone you and me.
I'm sorry, Harry.
No.
Did you hear from him?
- Why can't I go? Can I go with you?
- Just go.
Hi, Oleg.
It's Mathias.
You know what? I forgot to
check my messages last night,
and Harry called to say that
he couldn't make your trip.
No, I know.
No, well, he couldn't
get through to you,
or your mom apparently, so...
No, it's totally my fault, Oleg.
Yes, yes.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, Oleg. Yes.
Yeah.
So, see you in a few days, then,
when I'm back from
the conference. Yeah.
You didn't have to do that.
Hey, Aasen. Somebody
here to speak to you.
Aasen.
My family owned
all of these buildings,
and that house over there, too.
Arve Stop worked for us
back then.
He was bright, ambitious.
My father really
believed in him.
The business wasn't going very well,
so, we, uh, offered him a stake.
Within a year,
he had forced us out.
Sold the land for a fortune.
Have any of my colleagues been
in touch with you recently?
A Young lady?
I look at this picture now.
I see Laila staring at him.
No idea at the time.
Family man, eh?
Do you remember the name
of your wife's doctor?
Sure. Morton Freiberg.
Did she ever see someone
called "Vetlesen"?
Vetlesen? No.
Dr. Idar Vetlesen.
No.
Any idea where I might
find the officer
who's in charge of the case?
Rafto?
He died.
Yeah, he died
around the same time.
Detective Rafto.
Can you connect me
to Haukeland Hospital?
Rafto.
What is this'?
Am I under arrest?
A cake!
Yeah, I need some information
on a patient, Laila Aasen.
No, I don't...
Listen to me. I don't know
the admitting doctor.
But perhaps she was there
for an abortion.
Happy birthday to you.
Well, then, I'll come down there
with a fucking warrant myself.
Happy birthday, dear Svenson.
Happy birthday to you.
- Rafto.
- RAFTO; Idiot.
Hip, hip, hooray!
Fucking incompetent
sons of bitches.
Rafto!
In, in! Get back!
Get back in!
Happy birthday to you.
You idiot!
I heard he was
a great detective.
He was a suicidal maniac.
They were gonna
suspend him, anyway.
They found stuff in his drawers.
Items he'd stolen from
various crime scenes.
Is this him?
Where'd you get this'?
From a colleague.
Yes, that's him.
He had this cabin
up on the coast.
Used to go up there
to get smashed.
He was probably drunk
when he shot himself.
What's this on the floor?
They look like coffee beans.
Maybe he was trying
to sober up after all.
You didn't check?
The cabin was locked
from the inside,
and he looked like that
when they found him.
There wasn't anything to check.
Did he have any family?
Wife, who left him a year
before he killed himself.
I think there was a daughter.
Do you know where she is now?
Not a clue.
Is the cabin still there?
What are you doing with
my fucking gun, you idiot?
Here's the papers you asked for.
Where's Harry?
In Bergen.
- Hello?
- Mr. Hole?
This is Harry Hole's phone.
Can I speak to him?
He's not here right now, but I
can take the message for him.
Right, okay.
Uh, this is Rebecca,
NRS at Telenor.
We picked up a signal from
a missing person's phone.
Case number MP two.
Um... I don't have any files in
front of me. Um, who's that?
I'll check.
Birte Becker.
What, is it transmitting now?
Yeah, just got it
in minutes ago.
Yeah, but wait.
Is it moving right now?
No.
I'll send you the coordinates.
No, just...
What's the address?
Uh, Parkway 1, 0139, Oslo.
You're sure that's correct?
Yes, Parkway 1.
Hey, are you all right?
This is Birte Becker.
Please leave a message.
Yes?
In his own garage?
Yeah.
Ah. The great Harry Hole.
How many bodies?
Birte Becker
and Ms. Dahl.
Where's Katrine?
Suspended.
She got a call telling her
they traced the Becker phone,
and didn't think to tell anyone.
I asked you where she was.
That's not my problem right now.
He shot himself straight on.
How do you do that
with a shotgun?
It's too long,
you'd have to angle it.
The pellet marks should
be up there somewhere.
Luckily, we have experts
to determine that.
You sure he was alone?
The garage door was closed.
One set of footprints.
We found two bodies in the
house, and Birte Becker's phone.
It was a suicide.
Case closed.
Mathias, listen, I have
no idea where he's gone.
Yes, I've checked my messages,
he hasn't called.
Oh, well, how can you help?
You're at your bloody conference!
Can I keep this?
No.
Yeah, sure.
She's not picking up.
Katrine!
Get off!
Stop!
I guess congratulations
are in order.
You know it wasn't that creep.
Vetlesen didn't commit suicide.
Someone killed him
because we got too close.
Like your father.
My father would never
have committed suicide.
He would never have
left me like that.
Get off me.
Get off me. Get off me!
Get off me!
Get off me, you fucking drunk!
Get off!
Get off.
Yeah.
I'm a drunk.
Like your father.
Laila Aasen and Awe Stop
were having an affair,
and that's the last thing
my father was investigating
before he got killed.
You broke into Vetlesen's house
because you were afraid I'd
find out this was personal
and take you off the case.
Vetlesen was his pimp!
And they were both in Bergen
when the murders started.
I know how much you want this,
but you can't force
the pieces to fit.
I called the Gellion Clinic, and
Vetlesen wasn't even working
the day he was supposed to
meet Birte Becker.
They found two dead
bodies in his house,
and Birte Becker's phone.
Yeah, well,
isn't that convenient, then?
So, Hagen has his killer and Arve St0p's
safe, and no questions are asked.
Do you actually think
he killed them?
I don't know.
I don't think
either of us do for sure.
Maybe this will bring
your balls back.
I'm gonna need your weapon.
It's right there
in front of you.
Why did he call you Cloudberry?
Because I liked Cloudberry jam
with ice cream.
Oleg ran away again.
It doesn't really matter if
we win or lose this bid tonight.
What matters most is that
we celebrate the way
this has brought us together,
and use that energy to restore the
values that make Norway great.
And so, it doesn't matter if, uh,
56 minutes and 33 seconds from now,
but who's counting?
If the World Cup goes to
Beijing or Denver or Montreal.
Because I believe
in my heart, tonight,
Oslo has already won.
Cheers!
I tried calling. I thought
he might be with you.
Uh...
He's okay.
He's at a friend's house.
Just didn't bother calling me.
What did you argue about?
He doesn't want
to leave the city.
I thought that change
would be good for him.
Well, for me, too.
Where?
Um, Mathias has a house,
uh, up in Telemark.
And because he consults
all over the place,
it's not too inconvenient
I saw him the other day,
he didn't mention anything.
Is that really what you want?
I don't know what I want.
I miss you.
Weir', in my head, I know
it's 50-50, but in my heart, 100%.
Thank you for coming.
Mr. Stop?
Mr. Stop, I'm sorry.
I, um...
I just want to thank you.
I really liked your speech.
I found it very, very moving.
You see, I, um...
I was an orphan, myself, so...
Well,
it doesn't have to be
a disadvantage, young lady.
It can motivate us, too.
Oh.
On, yes.
I work in Bergen with young
people in a care center,
and I know how
very busy you are,
but if you're ever
in the city...
I started my career in Bergen.
Write to me.
I'll see what I can do.
Yes. I'm so sorry.
I know...
I know people are waiting to talk to you.
Thank you.
Not at all.
Oh.
Yes.
Mr. Stop wanted me
to let you know.
Oh. How much he enjoyed
your conversation.
It's, um, room 472.
He'll be free
after the announcement,
if there's anything else
you'd like to ask him.
Thank you.
RAKEL; Mathias.
Where are you?
I just tried calling you on the landline-
I'm at Harry's.
Yeah?
Because I phoned Eric's parents,
and Oleg wasn't there,
either, so, I...
I know. I found him.
He was with another friend.
Are you okay?
Yes, I'm fine now.
Mathias...
I've got to run to one of
those boring dinners,
but I'll call you in the
morning, when I'm back. Okay?
Shit!
You couldn't have
asked another doctor?
What?
Two minutes,
ladies and gentlemen.
Hello?
And to all our viewers
around the world, thank you
for joining us here
tonight at the Hotel...
No! No!
No! Stop! No!
...of Beijing, Denver,
Oslo, and Montreal.
No!
...as with every competition,
there can only be one winner.
That the 15th Winter Sports
World Cup has been awarded to...
...three, two, one!
...Oslo!
Stop! Stop! Stop! Stop!
Congrats to us all.
Whoo-hoo...
That's the last of
her files to download.
There's nothing after that.
Get me a list of
all the phone calls
and appointments she made
while I was away.
Magnus!
Yeah, sure.
When was this taken?
Two days ago.
- No, no, no!
- I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry!
I'm late to get her to school!
I have to get to work.
I am sorry. I have one
quick question I need to ask you.
We have been over this
hundreds of times.
I know we have been
over this 100 times,
but I need to
sort something out.
Dr. Vetlesen was not
working at the clinic
the day your wife was
supposed to see him.
He wasn't there.
- So, she got the day wrong.
- I...
- How... Josephine, in the car.
- Daddy!
How the hell am I supposed
to remember what day we saw him'?
Sir, I'm just trying to
find your wife. Please help me.
How the hell am I supposed
to remember what day we saw him'?
Sir, I'm just trying to
find your wife. Please help me.
How the hell am I supposed
to remember what day we saw him'?
Sir, I'm trying
to find your wife.
How the hell am I supposed
to remember what day we saw him'?
Sir, I'm trying
to find your wife.
...what day we saw him?
Sir...
what day we saw him? Sir...
Yes, I want all those files.
Give me your car keys.
What?
And your phone.
Yes?
You told me Vetlesen was your
wife's doctor when we spoke.
And that you had no idea
why she'd gone to see him.
Yes.
But you told my colleague
you both went to see him.
She must have misheard me.
She recorded the interview.
Darling, go back inside. I'll
come in in a minute, okay?
Good girl.
She isn't mine.
Birte and I were trying
for another child.
We thought it might
save our marriage.
We had blood tests done at the
clinic for hormone treatment,
and it came out that
she wasn't mine.
I am infertile.
I've always been infertile.
Can't have children.
But she is mine.
Do you understand?
How can I not love her?
But you didn't see Vetlesen
the day you found out.
No, we saw some
hormone specialist.
A visiting consultant.
Do you know his name?
Yes?
Just a second.
Damn it.
I said I'm coming!
You never called.
Is Oleg back?
What'? Oleg?
He's at school.
And Harry?
Is Harry here?
No.
No...
How did he convince you
to give him those pills?
He didn't.
You didn't have to do it for me'
I didn't do it for you.
It was never about you.
I'm outside his house.
I can't reach Rakel. Send
someone to her apartment.
Oleg.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Why do you have Mum's phone?
Come on.
You and I have more in common
than you think.
I didn't know who
my father was, either.
Magnus, track Rakel's phone.
Sorry, I just...
All right.
Okay, Harry, we just
picked up her signal,
heading west towards Telemark.
It is a red Volvo registered
to a Mathias Lund-Helgesen,
Rjukan, 2421.
The house is pretty remote.
There's an access road,
but that's it.
And there's a big lake
around it.
Helicopters are grounded
because of the weather,
but Delta is on their way.
Anything on Mathias' family?
Okay, I've got something here.
Jonas Lund-Helgesen, former police
officer, lost his job in '89.
A scandal involving a woman
drowning in a car.
Probable suicide.
She had a son.
Stop!
Father unknown.
Please!
He was sent to an orphanage.
Who led the investigation
into the woman's disappearance?
Some local talent
in the village nearby.
What's his name?
Jonas Lund-Helgesen.
Jonas! No, please, stop!
Harry?
Harry? We've lost him.
Sit down, Harry.
Pass me the gun.
I didn't think you'd find me.
Perhaps the pills helped,
after all.
I spoke to Filip Becker.
What's going to happen
when Josephine Becker finds
out he isn't her father?
She'll still love him.
Wrong answer.
Let's try again.
Was it right for Sylvia Ottersen
to kill her unborn child
simply because she couldn't keep
track of who the father was?
That was her choice.
Too short.
Maybe she was afraid.
What about you, Harry?
You have a woman who loves you.
A boy who's devoted to you.
Why did you abandon them?
They deserve better.
Too easy.
Because I'm selfish.
I'm an addict.
There isn't enough room
for them.
You know, when I first
saw your picture in the paper
with all those medals,
I thought, "That man must
have a perfect family."
And here you are.
Last question.
This boy,
who doesn't even know
who his father is,
who's had to put up
with so many men
like you and me
taking his place...
Does his mother deserve to live?
Why don't you ask him?
You all right?
Kill him.
Kill him!
Come on!
I'm ready! I'm here!
I know why you blame her.
You've been wrong
the whole time.
It wasn't her.
It wasn't your mother
who didn't want you.
It was your father.
It would've been better for him
had you not been born.
The pathologist detected
traces of the drug, ketanome.
But the direct cause
of death was drowning
as a result of
blood filling her lungs.
Twenty-four stab wounds
were found in her mouth,
all at regular intervals and at the
same depth, seven centimeters.
Pathologist can't determine
what kind of weapon was used.
And he's never seen
anything like it.
I'll take it.
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today