Watch Movies, TV Series and Live Sports
Signup Here -> WWW.ADMITME.APP
Subtitles by explosiveskull
Hm?
Let's go.
So what are we doing here?
Well, my grandfather
used to tell me,
the future can give you
anything you want.
Come on. What are you doing?
What are you doing?
If we wait long enough,
the future will create it.
Maybe through technology,
or maybe just from making you
not want it anymore.
Either way, the answer
is in the future.
What's wrong, Boss? Come on.
You wanna go back
to obedience school?
Yeah.
I didn't think so.
What's in it, Boss?
Oh.
Boss!
Hello?
Hello...
Boss, let's go.
Jackie.
- Professor Hopper here.
- Hey!
You didn't get shot
by any hunters. Awesome.
So I found the van.
No sign of the hippies. Uh...
Listen, I need you to put
a climbing pack together for me.
- Oh, really?
- But you can't tell Taylor.
If he finds out
I'm doing an expedition
without him, he'll get upset.
It's better this way.
Do you want her
to have, like,
10,000 of your babies?
It's like you're 13.
- Yeah.
- Just shut your mouth.
You shut your mouth...
Tay-Tay. Best friend, buddy.
Pal...
Oh, hi, Jackie.
And... Taylor.
Did he really say
not to tell me?
Mm-hmm.
Hey, the whole point
of the favor was discretion.
- Come on, Boss. Come on.
- Here, Boss.
Sorry.
I had a teeny-tiny car issue
so Taylor had to drive.
Besides, he wanted to help.
So you saw it?
You saw the van?
When do we go?
I appreciate you setting
this up on such short notice...
- No problemo.
- I appreciate your offer.
Taylor did all the hard work.
Situation's changed.
I'm going alone.
- All righty.
- Who's gonna watch your back?
Boss, of course.
I'm serious.
Nobody's been on this land
in decades.
You guys don't have anything
to worry about.
- It's gonna be fine.
- Perfect.
Then we'll be back
in no time, right?
I'm going alone.
You guys will be fine without me
for a couple of days. Okay?
If you're worried
about your evaluations,
which you should be,
they've already been submitted.
And they're glowing.
If you can believe that.
Even yours.
Oh, look! Twinsies.
Okay, great. Thanks.
Gotta get up early.
You really think
you're gonna find them?
Maybe.
But if I really get lucky,
I might just find
what they were looking for.
Come on, Boss.
It's not plan A.
It's just in case.
God, you're such a worrywart.
You're just gonna
hold down the fort, huh?
Great.
You're still there, huh?
Moisture?
It's a wall.
Jackie, come on.
Wake up.
Come on, Jackie!
Uh, hi, good morning.
We still have to go.
Even if we have to get
a ride to the gate
and hike for a few days.
No. We are not hiking
for a few days.
There's no signal within, like,
a hundred miles of that place.
How would anybody know
when to pick us up?
You've gotta know somebody
who would let us borrow
their truck.
Somebody...
- Anybody...
- What are you doing
- with my phone?
- Nope.
- I'm not calling her.
- Name one other person
who has an off-road vehicle
who would bend over backwards
for you at 6 a.m.
on a Saturday morning.
And it's not her vehicle.
It's her dad's jeep.
And there's no way that
she's gonna loan it out to us.
We'll just rent a truck,
it's fine.
- No. We don't have enough time.
- No.
- Cara?
- Hang up the...
Hey, this is Jackie,
Taylor's friend
from the archeology program.
Say goodbye.
I am great,
thank you for asking.
Look, Taylor has something
he wants to ask you about.
Come on. Take it.
Sorry, did we wake you up?
- You're doing what?
- What?
What is she doing?
What if I had another option
for you that was
a little more adventurous,
that would definitely
give Veeves an A?
The only thing is,
you really need to bring by
your dad's sweet-ass
four by four.
Awesome.
I'll text you
Jackie's address and...
come by like, ASAP,
and we'll explain on the way.
Veeves...
Mm-hmm. Cara's half-sister.
Actually, how are you with kids?
Uh... awesome.
Okay, so I'm gonna leave
this disclaimer here,
just in case I get a bad grade.
Cara's hijacking
my school project
to help out a guy she likes.
But there's a catch.
Dad just made her take
a refresher course
on how to drive stick.
Let's see how that went.
Okay, Dad. I got it, I got it.
- I got it.
- Honey,
treat a manual transmission
like you would a relationship.
You gotta give a little
to get a little.
Find the balance.
Dad...
- What?
- He's just a friend.
Okay? And I really don't need
your relationship advice,
- but thank you.
- But he was a four-sport
letterman in high school.
He plays Rugby!
Do you want me
to give him your number?
'Cause it sounds like
you like him.
Now, would I let you
borrow the jeep
if I didn't like the guy?
Our purpose in recording this
is to show problem-solving
through adverse
and unfamiliar situations.
So, what is our adverse
and unfamiliar situation?
Well, Jackie and I,
we're teaching assistants
for this really great guy
in this semester
named Professor Hopper.
And, uh... he's been obsessed
with finding these hippies
that went missing
- back in the '70s.
- Mm-hmm.
They were tripping shrooms
or something,
and they went off looking
for the Fountain of Youth...
- What?
- And they never came home.
The Fountain of Youth? Really?
Look, I'm not asking you guys
to get your hands muddy.
You can stay in the car
when we get there, okay?
Yeah, all right.
Well, when you told me
that you got a plan
to get Veeves an A,
you really
should have elaborated.
Wait, we forgot about Furby.
- Furby?
- Mm. Is it imperative
that he come?
I don't... He just...
He smells weird
and he always has that
cheese puff crust
on his fingernails.
If Wallace is away
from his mother too long,
he gets what we call
"anxiety-rhea."
- Mom!
- But he has pills for that.
Do you have
the house phone?
I won't be here.
But, you know, just in case.
Great. Um...
we'll have him home by tonight.
- No booze?
- No, ma'am.
- No drugs?
No girls?
Absolutely no girls.
I know he's at
that age because...
I walked in on him
the other day, in his room,
without knocking
and you can imagine
what he's doing.
- Yeah, I promise you...
- Let's go.
Let's get in it.
Let's get out of here and...
- Perfect.
- Don't do that.
- I love you, Wallace!
- Okay.
Love you, Mom.
You can clip the cameras
to your bags
to keep your hands free.
Here you go.
They're Wi-Fi ready.
Password is... "fart party."
What?
And one for you, my love.
Mm-mm,
you gotta earn it.
Ow!
All right, so who wants
to give Furby the rundown?
I don't need an explanation.
That's how big
my love is for you.
- Come on, man.
- Thank you, fart party.
We are going
to find the Fountain of Youth.
Well, whatever
my baby wants.
Just as long as I can show you
the fountain
of Furby afterwards.
- Ew!
- Come on, Furby.
So gross, dude.
Well, look at that.
It would have been impossible
to find without a satellite map.
Hey, Furby.
You wanna narrate?
The state of decomposition,
seen now on the van,
- is evident that...
- Oh, my god.
- Never mind.
- Hey, come on.
- This is gold over here.
- This is definitely it.
- Wow.
- Hey, Jackie. I...
brought my projector
if you wanna curl up in there
and watch movies later.
Ew, no. Creepy.
Jackie.
- The Hoppers?
- Yeah.
Why didn't he tell us?
I don't get it.
It means
that Hopper didn't just go
looking for some random hippies
that got lost trying
to find the Fountain of Youth.
He's trying to find
his missing parents.
Guys, we should totally
take a picture for my vlog.
Help me out. Come on, come on.
It will be the greatest
profile picture ever.
All righty.
Okay.
Everybody say...
"Team Hopper."
Team Hopper!
Everybody say, "Team Furby!"
- Team Furby!
- Why?
You guys suck.
Furby, come around
and pull this back door open.
Yes, my Queen.
Aah!
- Sorry.
- Oh, geez.
Where'd you get this kid.
Please don't tell my mom I fell.
Are you okay?
What happened?
- I tripped.
- You okay?
I found this.
- What?
- No, just wait. Okay?
It might be a booby trap.
Relax. It's not The Goonies.
What's The Goonies?
- Seriously?
- What?
You haven't seen
The Goonies?
You kinda do look like Chunk.
- What is that?
- Ladies and gentlemen,
- we have a winner.
- Whoa, is that a cave?
Easy, kid.
You're just here to document.
Wow.
This is huge.
- Firsties!
- No, Veeves.
- Please stay next to me.
- Mm-hmm.
No one said
anything about caves.
Caves have bats and...
and bears, and...
monsters...
and...
Spiders!
- Hey, hey, hey.
- They're everywhere.
- Let me go.
- Hey, they're crickets.
Furby.
Take a chill pill, dude.
- Hey, be nice.
- Don't hurt yourself.
Crickets, spiders...
Whatever. They tried to eat me.
Where's Jackie?
I'm over here.
The rope keeps going.
I'm gonna crawl further.
Dude, it goes
over a cliff.
Don't go too far.
You complete me.
Wait.
It's been severed at the top.
- Hey, clear the rope.
- Go ahead.
Guys,
this room is massive.
We've got our work
cut out for us.
It looks like somebody went down
but they didn't come back up.
Someone cut Hopper's rope?
There's no way
this is Hopper's rope.
It's way too old.
How far down does it go?
Um, like...
I can't tell.
It's too deep to see the bottom.
Are there any crickets?
Some, yeah.
I'm out.
Professor Hopper,
are you down there?
So, we should
probably do a second line
on the descent to play it safe.
What does that mean?
All right, stud muffin.
You're up here on lookout
until we get back.
So, how long are we talking?
Mm, it depends how long
it takes Cara to have a fit.
- Veeves!
- Great.
- Wait.
- Okay.
Not to overstep my bounds
but, uh...
your girlfriend could be
really annoying sometimes.
Cara's not my girlfriend, dude.
Uh, she's not?
No. Sometimes I don't
even think she's a girl.
Oh, she's totally a girl.
Furby,
how about you just shut up?
- She has all the fun parts.
- Furby, shut up!
All right.
Take this. Just in case.
Yeah. Or we can yell.
It's 20 feet away.
We don't know how far
that thing lead.
And yet, you still go.
Yeah.
There's trail mix
and water in my duffle
if we're gone too long.
Later, Furb.
I'll miss you.
Counting on you, stud.
Counting on me for what?
Oh, I don't know, dude.
It just sounded nicer than
"Don't screw anything up."
We'll radio you at the bottom.
So, what is it?
One chime for "yes,"
two chimes for "no,"
and three chimes
for "I love you?"
Uh...
You really got
to focus here. Okay?
I would have killed
to do this stuff
when I was her age.
I'm 13. I've been
rappelling before, so chill.
Yes. But did you have
a safety instructor,
and footholds, and helmets,
and safety cables
in case you fell.
Actually, I didn't.
And that's what made it
so much fun.
- Hey, Jackie. Wait up.
- Relax.
It's gonna be fine.
Jackie knows what she's doing.
Let Veeves have some fun
for once.
Or if you want,
I got another harness.
You can come with us.
You owe me big.
You know that right?
Yeah.
Hey, be careful.
I got it.
Veeves.
Veeves!
It's fine.
They would have yelled up
if there was a problem.
- You think?
- Yeah.
She's just being
a little sister
because you're being
a big sister.
Veeves, come on.
- Veeves!
- Veeves.
Hey, shut it, punk.
Taylor, Taylor!
You're fine. You're fine.
We're halfway down.
I can't believe
I let you talk me into this.
It's crazy.
- It's like damp.
- What?
It's weird.
You can feel it.
There's like
this invisible boundary,
where the air
completely changes.
What the hell?
What?
Boss?
Boss!
Oh, shit.
Boss, someone's here.
We gotta go.
Boss! Come on.
Get in the car, boy.
What the hell?
Let's go.
Come on. Come on.
Hello.
I'm unarmed.
Please don't shoot me.
I'm from the University
Archeology Department.
I came to explore your cave.
My battery has died.
I seem to have lost my dog.
I'm gonna check your truck
for jumper cables.
I'm not here to steal anything.
Just maybe your car battery.
Jackie?
Jackie!
Shit.
Taylor!
You guys in here?
Hello!
I don't remember
eating breakfast this morning.
I think I'm having some kind
of an episode.
Hello?
Oh, wow.
I think I see the bottom.
Look who changed her mind.
- Easy on the landing.
- You look like a pro.
Glad you could join us.
We were getting lonely.
- Easy...
- Yeah. Well, how about you
- answer me when I call you.
- Uh...
I didn't hear anything
and I don't think
Jackie heard anything.
Yeah. Well then,
check your ears.
You're so weird, dude.
They're kinda boring.
Let's go explore.
Let's do it.
Adventure time.
So pretty.
- I know, right?
- Whoa.
Guys, we're gonna go
check out this tunnel.
Hey, Veeves.
Stay close. Come on.
- Stay close, Cara.
- Veeves.
Ooh...
- Stop.
- What?
It's not me.
Okay, careful. Watch your step.
Here we go.
I wonder how far back that goes.
- I wonder...
- It's crazy in there.
Did you hear that?
Okay...
Come here.
Oh, my god,
oh, my god, oh, my god.
Guys, what was that?
You guys,
we gotta get out now.
No, we didn't come this far
just to leave now,
- because of some weird noises.
- Taylor, seriously?
- Yeah, I'm staying.
- Weird noises,
those were screams!
Let's go.
Wait.
I'm not leaving without Hopper.
Cara, wait.
I'm the fastest climber.
Furby and I can
pull you two up faster
than you could ever
pull yourselves up.
- She's right.
- Okay?
I'll come back down
once they're up.
- Okay. Uh-huh.
- You ready?
One, two, three.
Whoa, no!
Jackie!
- Jackie!
- What...
What happened, Jackie?
I got it.
Awesome.
It's okay, I got it.
What? They cut the rope.
Thank you.
Oh, shit.
Furby, I swear to God, man.
- He cut it?
- Geez!
Furby wouldn't cut it!
Furby!
Stop messing around, man.
I swear to God.
Drop us the rope back down,
dumbass.
You almost killed Jackie.
Furby?
How'd he do that?
Hey, dude.
- Are you okay up there?
- Shit.
Okay, let me just
take it off.
I know Furby since kindergarten,
he wouldn't do this.
What is it?
Got caught on Cara's harness
when she fell.
How bad is it?
They feel broken.
Sorry, Hopper.
Looks like your two
best climbers just got benched.
- Is yours that bad?
- Yeah.
Guys, we have to figure out
an exit plan.
Our exit plan is for Furby
to stop being a dick
and throw down another rope.
Yeah, but could you
climb it with that hand?
I don't really have
a choice now, do I?
Cara, you're gonna have
to climb freehand.
What?
No, it's like 90 feet.
If she falls, she's dead.
Um...
Give me that radio.
I'm gonna get an A for sure.
Furby...
Stop messing around, man. Okay?
We got something down here
and I need you to throw down
the other end of the rope
right now.
Furby?
Hit the chime button.
- There's something down there.
- And they have a radio.
Professor Hopper?
This is Taylor, we're here
to get you out of here.
Help... me.
- Cara?
- Taylor...
Who is this?
It's me, over...
Help... me.
Professor Hopper, is that you?
Furby...
What?
Did he just say "Furby"?
That doesn't sound like Furby.
Who is this?
Who's on this channel?
Dude... It's Furby.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
What are you doing?
What's it look like I'm doing?
I'll figure out
what the hell is going on.
No, you can't go
in there alone.
- Let's go.
- No, no.
You can't go alone.
And you're staying here
with Jackie.
The one person who doesn't stand
a chance to defend herself,
I'll take my chances
with you guys, thanks.
Are you kidding me? No.
If it were Hopper,
he would've said so,
so sit your butt down.
Right now.
Who's gonna stop me?
See? You see now?
Why I didn't wanna bring
a 13-year-old into this cave?
Well, there would've been
no problem,
except for her stupid friend
who cut the rope.
He didn't cut the rope.
Honey, I think
the class project is over.
This is the kind of thing
only a camera
can prove actually happened,
and you don't want to have
a record of it?
If she's shining the light,
she might as well be rolling.
Well, we can sit here
and wait forever,
or we can do
what we came down here to do
and figure out
what's over there.
I hate all of you.
Bye, guys. I'll be here.
I feel like I got put
in a time-out.
"Just go wait
by yourself, Jackie."
"Yeah, go ahead.
Stand in the corner."
Blair Witch will see you now.
I don't hear it
chiming back anymore.
Do you think maybe
they just turned it off?
Let's hope so.
Watch your head.
Professor Hopper?
Now this cave's
got to be really old.
Professor Hopper?
Look at the formations.
Oh, so you're a cave expert now.
I watched
the Discover Channel with Dad.
There's light ahead.
Guys?
Furby?
Why is the light
moving like that?
I don't know.
I've never seen
anything like it.
That's so weird.
Look, the tunnel keeps going.
It's probably just Furby
screwing with his flashlight
or something.
Hey, Furby!
Hey, give me a boost.
- Got it?
- Yeah, I'm good.
There's a rope...
Oh, my god.
Oh my god, Taylor,
take Veeves to the other room.
Why?
Just take her to the other room!
- What's wrong?
- Damn it, Taylor!
- Take her to the other room!
- Yeah.
Come on.
- What's she freaking out about?
- I don't know.
She's your sister
so we're gonna listen to her.
What is that?
- Shh.
- What?
Hey, guys. What's up?
- What are you doing?
- Oh, not much.
Just... Can't walk, and...
You guys definitely left me
in that scary room
for what felt like forever.
But, uh, you know,
enough about me.
How you doing?
How's your day been?
- There you go.
- Taylor!
- That room is creepy.
- Right there.
There you go.
- What did you see up there?
- No! Sit.
I'm not your dog, dude.
Take it easy, Cara.
We're all dealing
with the same thing.
Take off your camera.
What's going on?
Whatever it is, it'll be okay.
Oh, my god. Cara.
Enough with the suspense, guys.
What is it?
Stay over there!
- We can't just leave him here.
- Leave who?
Jackie don't let her
come over here.
Is it Hopper?
Don't move. Okay?
I mean it.
No.
- Wait, stop.
- Oh, my god. Cara!
No, Veeves, no!
- Is that Furby?
- No!
Hey, no, no, no!
Is he okay?
Is he
gonna be all right?
Is he gonna be all right?
I think his neck is broken.
How did this happen?
I don't know
but we're gonna be okay.
It's gonna be okay.
I think he tried to climb down,
and somebody cut his rope.
Who would do this to us?
Who would cut Furby's rope?
He didn't even want
to come down in the first place.
Why would he descend alone?
Oh, wow.
The camera's still on.
Is there anything Furby
didn't bring in that backpack?
Grappling hook
would've been nice.
Team Hopper!
Okay. This is it.
Counting on you, stud.
Counting on me for what?
I don't know, dude.
It just sounded nicer
than "Don't screw anything up."
We'll radio you at the bottom!
So, what is it?
Like, one chime for "yes,"
two chimes for "no," and
three chimes for "I love you"?
Uh...
Not sure if the rescue rangers
are playing a joke on me.
But it's been radio silence
for like half an hour.
Crikey, we better head over
and check it out.
Hello?
Hey, guys. What's the deal?
I'm trying not to think
about it too much
'cause I'm not really
wired that way.
But it's kinda strange,
you know?
And, "by strange," I mean scary.
And, "by scary," I mean,
I wish I haven't started
thinking about it.
And now that I've been
thinking about it too much,
I kinda hate myself.
Now I have to poop.
So, I was trying to find
a place to do a twosie,
and, oh, look what I found.
A cave, a rope, and a jeep.
Do you guys think this is
where Hopper went down?
Because I do.
Good work, Sherlock.
You went down the wrong hole.
So I found
Hopper's dad's journal,
and it looks like he had
a little too much herbal fun
in the '60s,
if you know what I mean,
and got obsessed with a bunch
of fandom youth mythology.
Just a bunch
of drawings and stories
about Spanish conquistadors
trying to find some cave
that the natives said
contained magical healing waters
or something.
It says the queen sent
a dozen expeditions
to find this water
and bring a vial of it
to her dying husband.
All but one of the expeditions
either died at the hands
of the natives,
or returned empty handed.
The last expedition disappeared
somewhere northwest
of the Alamo.
That sounds familiar.
And it's the last thing
I wanna read
before it gets dark.
Guys, why is it sunset?
There's no way it's that dark.
It's one o'clock.
He must have a filter
on the camera.
It's some kind of a joke.
- Hear that...
- It's gotta be a joke.
...are after something.
How is it a joke? It's dark,
and that's your dad's jeep.
- So, I don't know what...
- Guys, if Furby's dead,
he's probably not joking.
It's midnight now
and you guys aren't back.
My cell has no signal
and is dead.
I've no idea how to drive
this thing, so...
Cara, when you see this,
have fun dealing with the wrath
that is my mother.
Okay, so I'm not gonna lie,
I got a little freaked out
by the coyotes
so I turned the projector off
and read a little more
of Hopper's
dad's journal instead.
So this magic water
healing story
has been pass down
through his family
but it wasn't until Hopper's dad
had kids of his own,
and his daughter got sick,
till he went looking
for the cave.
Which means, that this chick
is the reason
my friends are missing.
And coyotes
are gonna eat me tonight.
Oh, hello.
My mom probably
had a heart attack
'cause I didn't come home
last night.
And you know what sucks?
It just occurred to me that
no one knows we're here
because we told them we're going
- to Hamilton Pool.
- What's happening?
Taylor...
- This is a total mind fuck.
- Jackie...
So, not only am I
all alone up here,
but I have no idea
how to get back,
no way to get back,
and no one's looking for me.
Mm-hmm.
It's Tuesday now.
The jeep is dead
because I listened to the radio
all night because...
I might or might not be
afraid of the dark.
I ate all the food I could find
and drink all the water.
And at this point
I've decided...
That my friends
are probably dead.
And the only way
I'm gonna survive this...
is if I climb down
with Hopper's rope
and look for his car keys.
All right,
this part's for my mom.
I'm really sorry
I didn't call you
to tell you where I went.
I was just really excited
to make some new friends.
And...
I think they really like me
this time.
And, if for some reason,
you guys find this...
I really hope you make it home.
Cool, calm, collected.
All right, let's party.
Here we go.
Cool, calm, collected.
Like a real man.
Cool...
Calm...
And collect...
What the heck is that?
What is it?
- Whoa!
- He sees something.
Oh, my god.
Please turn it off.
So you got your answer.
Are you satisfied?
Or do you wanna keep going
until we're all dead?
It doesn't make sense.
The timecode spans several days.
We've only been in here an hour.
Maybe we fell asleep
on the way down or something...
All of us?
Are you kidding right now?
I never fell asleep.
Did you fall asleep?
- Did you fall asleep?
- No...
- Nobody fell asleep!
- Jackie, calm down!
Well, what do you
want me to say?
Don't you think
if I had an answer,
I would share it with you?
You may not have an answer,
but you're the only one
with an option
that the rest of don't have.
Yeah, what option is that?
You're the only one
who has a chance
of climbing out of here?
- Maybe I can do it?
- No.
It's Veeves or it's you.
Or we go deeper into the cave,
we cross our fingers
and we hope...
No, no. It's way too dangerous.
You saw what happened to Furby.
Yeah, well, it's more dangerous
if we stay down here.
There is somebody up there
cutting the ropes.
Yeah, well, I don't have a rope
for them to cut.
- So, what does it matter?
- No.
None of this was supposed
to happen.
You went looking for someone
who went missing
while he was looking for
someone else that went missing.
What'd you think would happen?
I don't know.
I thought that we were
a step ahead
because we found the rope
leading off of the van.
Okay, I'm sorry.
You're gonna be okay.
You're with Taylor and Jackie,
for a little while.
- Why?
- Jackie's right.
I'm the only one
who can get us out.
Still rolling.
You never know.
Can I count on you?
Hey.
Just hold on.
Here.
Take this with you.
It's a GPS beacon.
It'll send out an SOS
from anywhere in the world.
It'll work once you
get to the surface.
I packed it once I realized
how stupid it might be
going looking for somebody
who went missing
while he was looking
for somebody that went missing.
And, hey, don't come down
without help, okay?
Why do I get the feeling
you know what's going on here?
I don't.
You won't tell me?
Fine. I mean, I'd like to know
what I'm climbing up to.
I think you owe me at least
that much, don't you?
I think it's the sun.
I think it's days and nights.
That's why the timecode
didn't match the videos.
Seriously?
That might be the dumbest thing
I've ever heard.
It's just an idea.
Please don't fall.
I'll be right here
if you need me.
Remember,
alert the beacon first,
- then drop the rope.
- I know, I know!
Alert the beacon, drop the rope.
Don't look down.
- Okay.
- It should beep twice
when it picks up a satellite.
How you doing?
Almost there!
I can feel
the air changing again!
Okay.
Taylor!
Taylor, the rope is gone!
There's something wrong
with the air!
Taylor!
Okay.
Damn it!
I'm gonna get a signal!
Come on!
Shit!
Come on! Please work.
Oh, my god. Seriously?
Oh, come on.
Come on!
Come on.
Okay...
Taylor!
You won't believe what happened.
What do you mean
"what happened?"
I have never seen
anything like it.
Everything's gone, okay?
There's no trees,
there's no grass.
There's just rock everywhere,
these formations.
Wait,
what about the GPS?
I tried to activate the beacon
but I couldn't get a signal.
It worked
before we left,
I checked it in the jeep.
Well, I walked
all over the place,
I couldn't activate
the stupid thing.
- Hello?
- Come on, I got you.
- A little help?
- I think...
- I think a bomb went off.
- Here, let me help you.
When... when we came down.
- There's something in the sky.
- Here, sit down.
There's a whole lot to tell you.
- I'll tell you when I get down.
- If you guys can stop
running off. It's just an idea.
Come on, I got you.
Be careful,
you're almost down.
Cara, come on, dude.
"Come on" what?
You were gone for, like,
two seconds.
If you don't wanna climb
all the way up, just say so.
I don't get it.
It's not really
a good time for jokes.
No, I'm not joking.
Just watch the stupid playback.
Just watch it.
Okay.
How you doing?
Almost there.
I can feel the air
changing again.
Taylor!
Taylor the rope is gone!
There's something wrong
with the air!
Taylor!
Shit.
Hey.
Will you say something?
...gonna get a signal!
Veeves...
play mine.
This isn't possible.
How is this possible?
Why is that?
How you doing?
Almost there.
- Taylor!
- What?
You won't believe
what happened!
What do you mean
"what happened"?
Believe me now?
Everything's gone, okay?
There's no trees...
Guys, I was up there
for 30 minutes.
This is seconds.
Why are the tapes different?
What the hell
is going on, Taylor?
I realized something
when we watched Furby's tape.
A night had passed
in his footage.
But the rope was still running
from the cave to the van.
It wasn't a person
who cut the rope...
It was friction,
over a long period of time.
What?
Time is passing differently
down here,
than it is on the surface.
What?
It's the sun.
Rising and setting.
It's the only way
that Furby's tape
was days ahead of ours,
even though we all came in
at the same time.
What? How long
have we been down here for?
I have a date this weekend.
Seriously?
We've been in here weeks,
maybe months already.
I'm sorry, Veeves.
I shouldn't have
brought you here.
Why am I the one crying?
You're 13.
I'm not crying
because you're my big sister.
And I know
you'll get us out of here.
Whoa.
So, every time that happens,
that's a day?
Wait.
The Fountain of Youth.
So, it's like if time stops...
you stay young forever.
Guys, this really is
the Fountain of Youth.
Nothing?
Okay.
We have to get out of here.
We've gotta have enough rope
in between what we've got here
and what we've got in the
other room to get out of here.
For what?
You want me to climb back
up there with all that rope?
I'm running out
of ideas here.
Take some time to rest.
Just give me
like ten minutes.
Ten minutes?
We don't have ten minutes.
It's gonna take Taylor and I
at least half an hour,
to climb out of here.
How long is half an hour
down here?
Cara, you found Furby
facing down, right?
Yeah. Why?
In the video,
he was on his side.
And his radio wasn't smashed.
So, what smashed his radio?
Whoa.
What the heck is that?
Aah!
Great, this is it.
Furby,
stop messing around, man.
I swear to God.
Drop us the rope
back down, dumbass.
You almost killed Jackie.
Furby?
Wait, Furby was still alive?
Hey, dude.
Are you okay up there?
So, it really was him
on the radio.
Furby,
stop messing around, man, okay?
We got something down here,
and I need you to throw down
the other end of the rope.
Right now.
Furby?
Professor Hopper?
This is Taylor, we're gonna
get you out of here.
Help me.
Who is this?
Taylor, help me.
Professor Hopper?
Is that you?
Furby...
Who is this?
Who's on this channel?
Dude, it's Furby.
What the hell?
Wait!
Ah! Help!
No. No, no, no!
What just happened?
There's someone in here.
And it's not Hopper.
I'm gonna be sick.
Don't worry about me.
Just watch the tunnel.
And, Veeves,
watch for falling rocks.
She's gonna be fine.
But no matter what,
you can't look up, okay?
Thanks. I get it.
You got it, Cara!
You got this.
Just take it
a little bit at a time.
Oh, my god.
Sorry. I'll shut up.
Okay, okay.
Veeves,
this is exactly what we're
trying to avoid right now.
It's Furby's footage.
Don't watch that.
I noticed
something earlier.
What?
He sees something here. Wait.
You can slow
the playback.
Do you see that?
That, right there.
The sun's path keeps changing.
What?
Why is it doing that?
Oh, my god.
It's not just the sun.
- What?
- It's the seasons.
This thing is the sun
shifting on the horizon.
Oh, my god,
you're right.
That's not just one revolution.
It's hundreds.
Wait, what did she say?
That's why everything
was so different on the surface.
We've been down here
a really long time.
What?
Guys, what's going on
down there? What's on the video?
Guys, this is bad.
This is really, really bad.
Guys,
what's on the video?
Those are entire years.
It's the solstice, that's the
only thing that makes sense.
Seriously?
Each of those is a year,
not a day?
How long is that?
Taylor, we've been
in here for hours.
So...
Holy shit...
- Whoa!
- Oh, my god.
Cara, look up!
- Ah! Whoa!
- Jackie!
- Go!
- Are you okay?
Come on.
The hell is that?
Cara, be careful!
We're being rescued.
Hey, Cara, climb up it!
This thing is huge.
Dude...
Wait, there's something
coming down.
What is that?
That is a giant.
Hurry, hurry, hurry!
Veeves, stay back.
Come on, let's go.
Oh, my god.
I don't wanna go back up.
Dude, look!
Where did he come from?
Okay, okay, okay.
All right, go.
- Go!
- How far does it go?
- Are you okay?
- Yeah.
We can stay
ahead of him.
His suit looks hard to move in.
On your leg, okay?
I'm good.
Guys, it hurts.
I can't... I have to stop.
What is this place?
I think we lost him.
He's moving pretty slow.
Wait, no, no. Go, go, go!
- Okay!
- Go!
It looks like
the ground's wet.
Go, go!
Faster.
Let's go faster.
I think I see light
up ahead.
Wait, it's fire.
Why is there fire?
Guys, there's someone else
in here.
- Veeves, take Jackie.
- Shit. Ow.
- You good?
- Uh-huh.
Come on, I got you.
There's no pulse,
but she's warm.
- She just died.
- Oh, my god.
- What?
- This is Hopper's mom.
What?
She's been here
for 40 years.
I think we lost him.
Taylor, look,
from the photos.
Oh,
that's Hopper's dad.
Who are those guys?
And what are they doing
with a gun?
Oh, shit.
Go, go now.
Come on, hurry. Go.
Go. Hurry, hurry.
Let's go.
Shh!
Oh, my god, guys.
What about Taylor?
You stay here.
You don't move from Jackie.
- Do you promise me?
- Okay.
Be careful.
Come here.
It'll be okay.
Taylor... Taylor!
Oh, my...
You can't.
You can't leave me here!
Oh, my god.
You've got to wake up.
Come on, just wake up.
Oh, my god.
Wake up.
Please...
No.
No, no!
No! Don't touch him!
Ah!
No, no, no, no!
What are you doing?
Stop! You'll kill him!
Oh, my god.
What happened?
Come on.
We have to get
Veeves and Jackie.
No, wait.
There's another one.
Stay back.
We have to help him.
What's wrong with him?
Cara!
Stay back.
He needs his mask
to breath.
What's wrong with him?
Oh, no.
He's out of time.
Okay...
Veeves!
They're okay. Let's go.
What's he doing?
Did they
just fall asleep?
Cara!
Veeves!
- Oh, my god.
- You're okay!
We're all right.
Are
these guys sleeping?
How did you
manage that?
We didn't do it.
He did.
What year are you from?
Tell us
what year are you from.
What happened to him?
He can't breathe our air.
We've reached
the two-week mark...
- Holy cow.
- in the search for five...
missing students.
The three college
and two middle school students
disappeared 14 days ago
and are thought
to have been headed west
in a green Land Rover Defender.
Travis and Williamson County...
Please. Just tell us
what year you're from.
Joining us tonight
is the father
of two of the missing.
Cara and Veeves Pintauro.
Thank you for speaking
with us tonight, Rich.
We appreciate it.
Yeah, Carter,
I'm asking for help
from the public tonight.
It's been two weeks
since I've seen my daughters.
So, I'm asking anybody,
please look at these pictures.
And, if you've seen them,
contact your local authorities.
I need my girls back.
Please, I don't know
what you're saying.
What is he saying?
I don't know what you're saying.
We must
continue to go into space
for the future of humanity.
I don't think we will survive
another thousand years
without escaping beyond
our fragile planet.
We want to leap into the future.
We want major breakthroughs.
American footprints
on distant worlds,
are not too big a dream.
They're calling it
"The Arc."
Fifteen miles long
and two miles across.
The ship may hold
up to 250,000 people.
Once in orbit,
it will put to use
the world's first
hyper-accelerator,
capable of sending ships
as far as Mars,
in a matter of hours.
As we take off...
As we take the final steps
toward the colonization,
of our new home planet, Mars,
and hope that one day
we may return to planet Earth.
That happened
while we were down here?
Is this really real?
We've been in here that long?
It was like thousands
of years went by.
Long enough for people
to be eight-feet-tall
and speak a different language.
So then we're just stuck
in here?
Forever?
Even if we can get
to the surface...
everything we've known is gone.
That can't be right.
What about everybody back home?
- What about Mom and Dad?
- Hey, hey.
We still have each other.
And Jackie and Taylor are here
with us, we'll figure it out.
We'll figure it out.
What are we gonna do?
Okay, we have two options.
We either get out
of here right now,
or we accept that we are staying
in here forever.
Because if that guy is what
humans have evolved to, then...
what are we gonna
be dealing with
by the time we get
to the surface.
No matter what's up there,
we have a way out now
and we should use it.
Taylor.
Look.
Oh, my god!
What is it?
Hopper was here.
He must have gone down
on another tunnel.
Taylor, we have to go.
I know what I said...
But if we don't find him, this
would've all been for nothing.
- What?
- Hopper's the only one
who's gonna know
what to do right now.
Oh, my god.
Seriously?
Wait a minute.
What about the cowboy's gun?
Thanks, Jackie.
There's four shots left.
You guys get Furby,
I'll be right back.
If you hear gunshots,
don't wait for me, okay?
Just go.
Hopper?
Hopper!
Professor Hopper.
Professor, it's Taylor.
She's stuck.
- What?
- We're too late.
She was my sister.
She's trapped.
Everything slows down in there.
Just like everything
slowed down
as soon as you walked inside.
That's it.
You actually found it.
This whole cave
is a system
geared, designed
to protect The Fountain.
Each layer's a different speed
than the last.
Taylor!
We need your help with Furby!
Jackie?
Jackie, down here.
Stop. Don't go in there.
If you go in there,
I'm not gonna be able
to get you out.
Taylor!
Come on.
Come on, Hopper, we gotta go.
- Come on!
- Wait. I can't move.
- I can't move.
Okay. Okay, come on.
It's bad.
They stabbed me
straight through.
Oh, my god.
The water's only a few
hundred feet, let's go.
- Come on!
- Stop!
I'm done.
Can't you see I'm done?
Well, maybe I'm not?
I'll bring the water
to you.
I'm gonna be dead
in five minutes, just go.
Just go.
It'll take me forever
to walk back.
Even with your help.
Get out now before there's more
of 'em.
I'll take that though...
Buy you some time.
- Taylor?
- Just get out of here. Go!
Taylor we need
your help with Furby.
Go.
I didn't come this far
to leave without you.
I got what I came for, Taylor,
just go!
I'll be right back.
Taylor!
He's not that far away.
I can probably get there
and back in a few minutes.
Even if I have to carry him.
Uh... Well, this time,
I'm going with you.
How long is this supposed
to take?
My ankle just took seconds.
All right. Hopefully,
Furby won't take
that long either.
Yeah. That's unlikely.
Veeves!
I think we're good.
Be ready to light it
no matter what.
Shall we try to put
the space guy in or...
I mean he did us a favor, right?
Uh, guys...
Oh, shit.
They're coming,
we have to go now.
- Veeves, light it. Let's go!
- Taylor, they're waking up. Run!
Taylor,
grab the lightsaber thing.
Hurry, hurry. Go!
Guys, go!
Faster, come on!
Come on, let's go!
Hurry!
They're right behind us.
Whoa! Holy shit!
The light stopped moving.
How does it work?
Whoa!
Hurry. Go!
- They're coming.
- Go, go. Come on, Veeves.
Go!
I'm right behind you.
Guys! Come on, go!
Hurry, hurry, hurry!
- They're here!
- Oh, my god!
Hurry!
- Veeves, how you doin'?
- I got this.
- Jackie?
- Killin' it!
Go faster.
Guys!
Something's really,
really wrong here.
really wrong down here too.
What is that? Is that water?
Between water
and psycho-Flintstones?
I say keep climbing.
Cara, be careful.
Cara!
- Oh, shit!
- Oh, my god!
Hold on tight!
Oh, my god! It has my arm!
Cara!
Taylor!
Grab me! I got you!
It has my leg!
- Come on, Cara!
- Help!
It has my leg!
Guys?
No, don't!
Cara!
Oh, my god.
Oh, my god!
Whoa!
Jackie, are you okay?
Whoa! No. No. No.
Taylor,
they're climbing!
Guys! Look!
Oh, shit!
- Cara?
- Hold still!
It's a bumpy ride once you break
through the water.
One at a time.
Veeves, you go in first.
- Wait!
- Ready?
Oh, my god!
Taylor, off the wall.
- Where are we going?
- I'll see you on the other side.
Just get off the wall.
Oh, my god, Cara. I don't know!
It's gonna be fine.
Just hold your breath. Ready?
Oh, man! What about Furby
and Hopper?
Once you break through,
we'll have all the time
that we need.
Just hold your breath.
Are you ready?
I don't like this.
Whoa! Whoa! Whoa...
Guys?
Whoa!
- Holy shit!
- Hey, Furby!
Holy shit!
Wanna go to Mars?
Welcome back!
Dude,
this place is awesome.
Oh, here they come.
Veeves.
Mom?
Daddy!
Yeah.
We got a lot to talk about.
What the heck
is this place?
Well, it's not quite home,
but at least we're all together.
Together? Like...
together-together?
Let's get you guys
dried off.
No, goof.
Come on, I'll show you around.
A lot has changed but we're
kind of a big deal around here.
Subtitles by explosiveskull
Watch Movies, TV Series and Live Sports
Signup Here -> WWW.ADMITME.APP