[opening music]
Watch Movies, TV Series and Live Sports
Signup Here -> WWW.ADMITME.APP
[music builds]
[music ends]
[mother] Jaywon? Come on baby,
it's time to get up.
[soft music]
[mother] Jaywon, let's go,
we need to get ready for school.
Come on now, I don't
have time to fight with you.
[soft music]
[mother] You want milk or juice?
Juice.
- Juice what?
- Juice, please.
You're going to have to get
yourself home from school again,
today and tomorrow,
I have got to work late again.
But I promise
I'll pick you up on Friday
and we'll do something
after school,
probably go to the park
or something, ok?
Look, Jay.
I know it's a new neighborhood,
and it's new kids,
you don't know one from another,
but you have
to make you some friends, baby.
You hear me?
Alright, you're going to
make me come into your school
in my house shoes and my robe on
and embarrass you.
I don't even have a robe.
But I'll get one.
[mother] Let's go babe.
[teacher]
So once the unit's cancelled,
you multiply across the top,
multiply across the bottom,
hundred and forty-two thousand
divided by sixteen O nine,
you're going to get somewhere
right around 88 miles
every one hour.
Great Scott, right?
[teacher] No? Seriously?
I'm getting old.
Test tomorrow,
Dimensional analysis, alright?
Not only do you need to know
your metric to metric
conversions,
but you also need to know
your imperial to metric
conversions.
Remember that worksheet
that I gave you? Yeah.
Not going to happen this time,
make sure they're up here,
no excuses.
Questions?
[student] What if
I can't study tonight, man?
I've got uh...
I've got things to do.
Yeah. Well... Yeah, cute.
Then you fail. I don't know.
Make up your mind, man,
your future.
[school bell ringing]
There it is.
Go ahead,
get your stuff and go.
[teacher] Come prepared
tomorrow, no excuses.
[student] Hey Mr. Williams,
I know you failed the game
last night, 21 to seven.
[teacher] Dude, don't do that
to me man, that's rough.
I'll tell you what,
those graphs, though,
those graphs...
[soft music]
[thud]
Oh, sorry man.
Looks like you're going
to have to go fetch it.
[foreboding soft music]
What? You've got
something to say?
[teacher] Excuse me, gentlemen?
Oh, sorry Mr. Williams.
We were just taking.
[teacher] Yeah, we've got
some place to be, let's go.
[Roman] Let's go.
[soft sad music]
[soft pats]
[tense sad music]
[soft background chatter]
Hey, Jake One, come here,
I've got to ask you something.
Where did you get that hat?
Are you retarded?
I'm talking to you.
Hey yo, Jerome? Jean-Marcus?
Where you be getting
your head-set, yo?
What, do you have
something to say?
- Give me my hat.
- What?
Come on, say it one more time,
I didn't hear you.
- I said, "Give me my hat."
- Monkey.
Give me my hat.
[student laughs]
[soft thud]
Hey, this is
my hat now, alright?
[cellphone rings in background]
[Roman] Finally.
[car hooting]
[distant upbeat music]
[soft sad music]
[distant thunders]
[keys jingling]
[door slams]
[sighs]
[heavy rain falling]
[thunders in background]
[sad music]
[Jaywon sobbing softly]
[soft thud]
[sad music continues]
[sniffs]
[blows]
[gentle anticipatory music]
[foreboding music]
[electronic beeping]
[pants softly]
[soft clinking]
[door squeaking]
[mother] Jay I'm home.
Did you eat?
[mom shouts] Jaywon?
I know you hear me calling you.
[grunting softly]
[foreboding music]
[grunts softly]
[soft beep followed
by mechanical buzzing]
[intermittent beeping continues]
[muffled electronic noises]
[electronic buzzing builds]
[soft bang]
[bang]
[mother] Jay I'm home.
Did you eat?
[soft background buzz]
[foreboding music]
[mom shouts] Jaywon?
I know you hear me calling you.
[tense music]
[rhythmic beeping]
[beeping continues]
[anticipatory music]
[soft click followed by buzzing]
[buzzing and beeping]
[loud bang]
[mother] Jay I'm home.
Did you eat?
[music halts suddenly]
Is it ok if I sit here?
Oh, I guess so.
You don't talk much, do you?
I guess not.
It's ok. I guess I don't
really talk so much either.
[soft background chatter]
Aren't you
going to eat anything?
I'm not really hungry.
So why did you get food?
I don't know.
You know, I heard
that not eating
can actually make you fat.
- That doesn't make any sense.
- I know.
[soft splash]
[Roman] Ah! Dude I'm so sorry
I just ruined your stupid
little hat. [giggles]
Oh what?
What do you want to do now?
You want to cry
in front of everybody?
[soft buzz]
[student 2] I got your back man.
[Roman] Yeah, he's not
gonna do anything.
[soft buzz]
[bang]
[soft background chatter]
[Heather] Is it ok
if I sit here?
Uh, yeah.
Are you ok?
You look really confused.
Uh, I feel confused.
- Math sucks for everybody.
- Huh?
- It was a joke.
- Oh.
- Sorry.
- It's ok, I'm not that funny.
I think you're amazing.
[Heather] I think
this is the most
I've ever heard you talk before.
If I keep talking
will you stay here?
You're pretty funny,
you should talk more.
- You think?
- Yeah.
You remind me of a friend
I had before I moved here,
he gave me this bracelet.
So, why did you move here?
My dad died.
Oh. I'm sorry.
[soft splash]
[soft thud]
[Roman] Oh, you think
you're quick, dude, now?
Come on get up and do something
then, Jake One.
- His name is Jaywon.
- Oh, you're his girlfriend now?
Leave her alone.
[Roman] Oh, what are you
going to do about it, Tayshon?
Leave her alone.
- And my name is Jaywon.
- [laughs] I'm so scared man.
[soft thud]
[Roman] What are you
going to do, monkey?
[student 2] I got your back man.
[Roman] Yeah, he's not
going to do anything.
[soft buzz]
So, were you there then
in class last week?
Yeah, 'cause Jeremy
totally farted.
[both giggling]
- Yeah, it was pretty funny.
- Yeah.
You know I live
very close to you, right?
- You do?
- Yeah.
I have this trampoline,
it's kind of cool.
You can come over
and use it if you want to.
Ah, cool. Alright.
[liquid spilling softly]
[loud thud]
[all laughing]
You're just going
to take that, Roman?
[all laughing]
[loud punch]
[grunts]
Are you ok?
Roman is such a tool.
[teacher] Roman!
What did you just do?
Are you ok?
[teacher] Let's go,
you're coming with me.
[door opens]
Hey, Jaywon!
Ok, so, I texted my mom
and she said
you can come over later.
[Jaywon] Uh, yeah, sure.
[door slams]
- Jaywon?
- Yeah, sorry.
Ok, so I'll come by later?
- Yeah, sure.
- Great.
[foreboding music]
[Roman's father shouting]
Again Roman? Again!
Are you fucking serious? Again!
[father shouting in distance]
[shouting] Do you know
how hard I fucking work
to kick your ass at school?
Do it outside the school,
not in the school.
Do it outside!
[shouting] I'm sick of you!
Get a fucking job!
You get a job,
you pay for school!
I'm fucking--
[tires screaking]
[tense music]
[car hooting]
Jaywon, come on!
I switched my shift!
Let's go to the park
or something! Hurry up!
Let's go have some fun!
[mother] Uh, I'm so happy
to be off of work.
Be happy you don't have to worry
about work and a 12 hour shift.
All you've got to do
is go to school, you come home,
you eat, and that's your day.
What happened to your lip?
I bit my lip at lunch, today.
[giggles] You still
don't know how to chew?
You eat just like your daddy.
And how was school?
It was... it was fine.
Why is my baby smiling?
Oh Lord praise that in Heaven,
my baby is smiling!
Ok, ok, I'm not going
to bug you about it.
I just want you to be happy.
Oh, I'm so happy for you!
Ok, let's go straight home.
Oh, let me get
some chicken and rice.
You love that rice,
Lord knows why.
You want some chicken and rice?
Uh, yeah, sure.
Do you mind if I go
to a friend's house
- later on today?
- A friend?
Oh, I don't know what they put
in the water today,
but I'll take it.
Yes Jay, you go hang out.
But make sure you do
your homework first, ok?
Ok.
[soft music]
[water running]
[humming softly]
[knocking on door]
[knocking continues]
[Jaywon] I got it mom.
[exhales softly]
[door opens]
[loud punch]
[soft thud]
[water running]
[foreboding music]
[humming softly]
[Jaywon grunts]
[soft thud]
[hitting and grunting]
Jaywon?
[loud punch]
[Jaywon grunts]
[loud bump]
[Roman grunts]
- [Roman] Hit me again.
- [Jay] Why are you in my house?
[struggling and laughing]
[struggling]
[soft thuds]
[Jaywon struggling]
- [mother] Jaywon what's going--
- [Jaywon struggling]
- What the hell?
- [Roman] Come on.
[door locks]
I think you boys
need to leave right now.
[mother] You hear me?
If you don't get your ass
out of my house,
I'm calling the police.
[foreboding music]
You niggers think
you can do whatever you want.
Jaywon, call the police, now.
[sighs]
[desperate music]
[shooting]
Mom.
[Jaywon] Mom!
[Jaywon] No.
[confrontational music]
[grunting]
[loud bump]
[thud]
No! No, no, no,
what are you doing?
What is right, Roman!
Just stay out of my way!
Got me?
[panting]
[door opens and slams]
[foreboding music]
[door squeaking]
[tense music]
[car leaving]
[music ends]
[distant electric beeping]
[gasps softly]
[panting] Mom. Mom!
[both panting softly]
My sweet baby.
[Jaywon] Mom, no, please.
[phone dialing tones]
[woman] Nine-one-one,
what's your emergency?
I need help, please.
Someone shot my mom.
[woman] What is the address
of the emergency?
711 Holland Drive.
[sniffs] Please, hurry.
[woman] Is the shooter
still there?
I don't know,
I don't know where he went.
[woman] Alright, stay there.
Someone is on the way.
[sniffs] Alright, please hurry.
She's going to die.
[sniffs] Mom, stay.
[whispering]
I just love you so much.
[Jaywon] Mom.
[soft sad music]
[sighs]
[sniffing]
[soft buzz]
[bang]
[electronic beeping]
No. It should have worked.
[sniffing and panting softly]
[Jaywon] Mom, please.
[soft beeping continues]
Mom. It should have worked.
I'm going to fix this.
I'm going to make it work, mom.
[sniffing and sighing]
My sweet baby.
[soft buzz followed by a click]
[piano music]
No, no. It should have worked.
[electronic swish]
Just please help.
[background buzz]
[whispering] She's going to die.
[sad song playing]
[device hits the floor]
[Jaywon gasps and sniffs]
[soft bang]
[sad song continues]
[soft buzzing]
[background buzzing continues]
[soft bang]
[pants]
Mom. Mom!
- [whispering] I'm so sorry.
- No.
I did this, mom.
[sobs] It's my fault.
[mother] No. No, come here.
The world doesn't move
because we tell it to,
so sometimes we've got to go
with what we get.
And you got
so much special in you.
Ok? I need you to know that.
Promise me. Promise me
that you'll remember that.
[sad song continues]
[mother] Alright, you'll
make me come up to your school
in my house shoes and my robe on
and embarrass you.
[mother] Why is my baby smiling?
Sometimes we've got to go
with what we get.
You got so much special in you.
Ok? I need you to know that.
[sad song continues]
[music ends]
[water running]
[door squeaking]
[Jaywon sniffs]
Jaywon?
[police radio in background]
[engine in background]
It's all set here,
he's ready to go.
[woman] Ok.
Let's get you out of here.
[police radio chatter]
[soft music]
[indistinct background chatter]
Jaywon! I'm sorry.
I'm sorry sweetie,
we've really got to go now, ok?
Wait!
'Cause we're friends.
[both sigh]
[woman] Buckle your seatbelt
for me, will you?
[woman] We're going to take you
somewhere safe, ok?
[soft music]
[music continues]
[soft buzz]
[metallic beeping]
[futuristic metallic sound]
[eerie music]
[electric buzzing]
[electric buzzing builds]
[soft explosion]
[foreboding music]
[electric whizzing]
[chalk ticking on blackboard]
[soft eerie music]
[swishing]
[chalk tapping on blackboard]
[loud buzzing]
[sighs]
[buzzing]
[swishing]
[chalk tapping on blackboard]
[soft eerie music]
[loud buzz]
[gasps]
[glasses hit the floor]
[laughs softly]
[foreboding music]
[soft electric buzzing]
[anticipatory music]
[laughing in excitement]
[silence]
[giggles]
[present Anna]
[confrontational music]
[gun loading]
[tense music]
[sobbing]
[click]
[screams and cries]
[panting]
[gun loads]
[music builds]
[Anna panting]
[click]
[gasps]
[gunshot]
[bullet clinking]
[sighs]
[gunshot]
[future Anna gasps]
[bullet clinking]
[sobbing]
- [continues sobbing]
- [coughs]
[panting]
[present Anna]
[coughs]
[sobbing]
[future Anna]
[soft buzz]
[tense music]
[foreboding music]
[confrontational music]
[coughs softly]
[shouting]
[dramatic music]
[gunshot]
[soft thud]
[music ends]
[sniffing and sobbing]
[sighs deeply]
[sobs]
[grunts]
[panting softly]
[soft buzz]
[gentle piano music]
[orchestral music continues]
[music fades]
[soft buzz]
[electronic metallic noise]
[foreboding music]
[futuristic electronic noise]
[loud electrical buzzing]
[buzzing builds]
[soft explosion]
[loud buzz]
[eerie music]
[futuristic electronic noise]
[electric buzzing]
[electric buzzing builds]
[soft explosion]
[foreboding music]
[electric whizzing]
[futuristic beeping
and swishing]
[dull bang]
[slow piercing piano notes]
[lady gasps softly]
[panting softly]
[piercing piano notes]
[moans softly]
[panting]
[grunts softly]
[window opens]
[piercing piano notes]
[moaning softly]
[sighing loudly]
[gasps]
[panting and gasping]
[eerie music]
[grunts]
[sighs]
[loud creaking]
[screams]
[grunts softly]
[grunting]
[screaming]
[shudders]
[panting]
[eerie music]
[soft squeaking]
[panting]
[soft tap]
[gasps]
[breathing heavily]
[loud squeaking]
[screams]
[grunts]
[window squeaks and slams]
[old lady clears her throat]
Hmm.
[paper rustling]
[old lady panting]
[keys jingling]
[door slams]
[soft thud]
[panting]
[objects falling]
[soft thud]
[sighs]
[tense music]
[cheerful music]
[energetic rubbing]
[kiss-calling cats]
[cheerful music continues]
[chinaware breaking]
[quick steps]
[cheerful music becomes
slightly creepy]
[cheerful music resumes]
[loud creaking]
[cheerful music becomes heavier]
[energetic rubbing]
[chinaware crushing]
[cheerful music]
[wallpaper cutting and tearing]
[tearing continues]
[cheerful music ends]
[soft buzz]
[radio frequency buzz]
[retro music playing]
[energetic rubbing]
[Anna]
[building manager] Mm.
[sighs]
[eerie soft rustle]
[hotel doorkeeper]
[Anna sighs]
[retro music]
[flies buzzing in background]
[bed squeaking]
[Anna moans softly]
[breathing heavily and gasping]
[startling softly]
[tooth tinkling]
[gasps]
[dramatic music]
[music builds]
[door opens]
[Anna]
Hm!
[door opens and slams]
[cheerful music]
[bottle pops]
[building manager]
[liquid spilling]
[keys jingling]
[cheerful music continues]
[coughing]
[keys jingling]
[wheezing]
[tense music]
[door opens]
[wheezing softly]
[tense music]
[wheezing and coughing]
[Anna continues coughing]
[panting]
[building manager]
[building manager sighs]
[door opens]
[Daniel]
[door closes]
[car hooting]
[Daniel]
[car leaving]
[sighs]
[snoring]
[tense music]
[fire crackling]
[eerie music]
[buzzing]
[squeaking]
[radio buzzing and playing]
[soft shaking and clanking]
[coffee running]
[retro cheerful music
playing on radio]
[pouring coffee]
[blows gently]
[floor creaking]
[music ends]
[Anna breathing with difficulty]
[floor creaking]
[gasps]
[rustle]
[eerie and foreboding music]
[girls speaking indistinctly
in background]
[building manager]
[indistinct]
[soft eerie music]
[foreboding music]
[liquid spilling]
[screams]
[Anna]
- [girlfriend] Hey!
- [Anna] Out!
[door closes]
[building manager]
[door opens]
[breathing softly]
[gentle piano notes]
[soft sad music]
[dark music]
[soft crackling]
[eerie sounds]
[house creaking]
[soft crackling]
[soft foreboding music]
[futuristic beeping
and swishing]
[gentle tranquil music]
I usually walk the perimeter
at 12:00, 3:00 and 6:00.
Six is when
the morning guy takes over.
Right.
Hank is usually a little late,
but just by a couple of minutes.
Man, I know the feeling.
There is nothing I would like
more than a cigarette right now.
But I can't.
- Ten days, so far.
- Hm!
Yeah, you'd think it will be
the booze or the cigarettes
that will take
a toll on your heart.
But it's not.
It's women.
- They get you in the end.
- Oh yeah, I hear you. No doubt.
Well, you're young enough.
You should do ok.
That's about it.
The office is right over here.
All the numbers are on the wall.
Hank likes a decaf, and myself,
I like the real thing.
[Sam] I like to keep things
in order out here.
When will you be back?
Not sure.
Maybe I'll check on you
in a couple of weeks.
Not everybody likes working
the graveyard shifts.
Never tried it.
Figured I needed something
to pass the nights.
[Sam] You'll find out
real quick if it's for you.
Some people
don't like the isolation,
makes them crazy.
[Sam] Me? It helps me
collect my thoughts.
Sounds good to me.
Alright then. Got the numbers?
Yeah, got it.
[dark slow music]
[radio sports commentary]
[liquid pouring]
[cheering crowd on radio]
[crackle interrupting
radio transmission]
[radio transmitting clearly]
[clock ticking]
[slightly spooky music]
[tense music]
[music becomes eerie]
[music builds]
[buzzing]
[alarm clock buzz]
[buzzing continues]
[soft music]
[vehicle hooting in distance]
[music becomes eerie]
[distant soft squeak]
[foreboding music]
[knocking]
[man] Oh, shit.
[agitated music]
[rustling]
[restless fast music]
[grunts] I don't know,
I think she overdosed.
I don't--
I can't get to her.
[music continues]
[window crushes]
[car door opens]
[man sighs and pants]
[frantic music]
She's going to be dead
by the time--
[ghostly music]
[soft ghostly music]
[soft piano and violin music]
Huh, cancel that.
[hangs phone]
[birds chirping]
[soft slow music]
[car approaching]
Morning.
You must be the new guy.
That's me. Kenny.
It's good to have someone
on the night shift again,
it's been a while.
Been a while?
What about Sam?
[Hank] Sam?
How do you know about him?
He used to work the night shift,
what's it been,
probably seven years or more.
[giggles] Seven years!
Yeah. He had a heart attack
one night and died
when a young woman
killed herself on a ship.
- A young woman?
- Yep.
In a maroon Grand Prix,
right over there.
It's funny,
'cause he always used to say
that it was the cigarettes
and booze that would get him.
- Yeah.
- We'd go through a lot of guys,
but you're good, right? I mean,
not everyone can handle
the graveyard shift, you know.
Most of them quit
after the first night.
It takes a special breed,
I think.
It's not always like this?
The first night?
Like what?
Nothing.
I'll see you at six.
Alright man. Get some sleep.
[energetic closing music]
[beeping]
[soft music]
[loud electric buzz]
[soft piano and violin music]
[retro music]
[apartment cheerful music]
[soft piano music]
[music ends]
Watch Movies, TV Series and Live Sports
Signup Here -> WWW.ADMITME.APP