Someone needs to stop Clearway Law.
Public shouldn't leave reviews for lawyers.
Some people
say that fairies are the stuff of fantasy.
They think the world is just
what you can touch and hear and see.
while others say the tales and legends
cannot be dismissed.
They believe with all their hearts
that fairies truly do exist.
Throughout all time.
human beings and fairies never met.
till one very special summer
that we shall not soon forget.
(SINGING ) Life is rising up
Surging forth in all directions
Every little buttercup
Is reaching out to find connections
Every blade of grass
Will touch the sunlight
The rain will touch the ground
Growing greener than it was before
Bees are droning by
Spider silk is softly spinning
Not a cloud in the sky
You know it"s only the beginning
Every little blossom. every flower
Flings its petals wide
As the season comes round
Once more
Hey, Tink! You ready
for your first summer on the mainIand?
AbsoIuteIy! It"s so beautifuI out here.
I can"t beIieve we get to stay
for the whoIe season.
WeII, what are we waiting for?
Race you down!
The breeze is blowing light and sweet
The grass. a carpet at your feet
Catch the colours
Feel the heat of the sun
All the sparrows in the dell
Swirling round like a carousel
Singing loud enough to tell everyone
Hi, guys.
Summer"s just begun
There it is, Tink. Fairy camp!
All the winters. all the springs
Lead us here on fairy wings
A season of a thousand things
To be done
Summer"s just begun
Hiya, Cheese!
-Did you have a nice fIight?
Incoming!
Keep her IeveI!
Gear it down, BobbIe!
Oh-ho!
-Smashing Ianding, CIanky.
-Thank you, BobbIe.
Guys, I think you may
have over-packed.
-Come on, Tink. Let"s go inside.
-Inside?
Tink, fairy camp isn"t out here
in the open.
We need to stay hidden
from the humans.
-We do?
-Uh. Yeah.
That"s why fairy camp is in here.
Cicadas, one at a time.
You, you and you. You, too.
Wow. It"s Iike aII of Pixie HoIIow
under one tree!
BIaze!
Hmm?
Wow!
The Queen Anne"s Iace
is Iooking beautifuI.
-How are the Iooms working?
-Fine, thanks to you, Tink.
Next. Next. Next.
-How"s the bee-Iiner working?
-Like a dream, Tink. Thanks.
Great. Need any heIp with that wagon?
No, thanks. She"s running fine.
Okay. GIad to hear it.
Here"s the first week"s suppIy.
Okay, I"m off. I gotta go deIiver
pixie dust to the other fairy camps,
but I"II see you in a coupIe days.
Oh, and Tink! Don"t worry.
You"II find something to fix.
I hope so.
In the meantime,
I need to go find some Iost things.
HoId on, IittIe miss spare parts.
You"re not going near
the human house, are you?
-(GASPS ) There"s a human house?
-No! I mean, yes, but no.
-We stay away from humans.
-Oh, Iridessa!
-Tinker BeII knows that, don"t you?
-Define ""stay away.""
It"s gonna be a Iong summer.
Grouchy.
-Oh, that"s just Vidia being Vidia.
-No, the air. It smeIIs...
...grouchy.
-We might be in for a storm.
-Come on, SiI.
The sun is shining, the air is warm.
It"s a beautifuI day. Nothing"s gonna...
Tinker BeII.
Thank goodness we"re here, Father.
It"s just Iike I remember it.
WeII, of course, my darIing.
Look at the creek and the woods
and the meadow!
Oh! I wish it was summer aII year Iong!
Yes, Lizzy.
Tinker BeII, what are you doing here?
Vidia, this is amazing!
It"s a carriage that moves by itseIf!
There"s no horse. SeriousIy, Iook.
-Do you see a horse up there?
-Uh. No.
It"s a horseIess carriage!
And do you want to know how it works?
-Not reaIIy.
-So do I.
I think those wheeIs back there move
because this chain thing rotates.
And I think what rotates the chain
is this big...
I don"t care, Tinker BeII. You shouIdn"t
be this cIose to the human house.
What if they see us?
WiII you stop fIitting around in there?
This is serious!
You know what, Vidia?
I think this powers the whoIe thing!
This, my dear, is exactIy why tinkers
shouIdn"t come to the mainIand. They...
Let me know if this does anything.
WeII, anything? Vidia, you"re aII wet.
You don"t say.
Father, Father, Father! Can we
bring our tea and scones outside
and have them here in the garden?
-It wouId be just Iike a IittIe picnic.
Not just now, Lizzy.
I stiII have to get the trunk unpacked
and the house settIed.
Father, Iook!
What a magnificent butterfIy.
My word. AbsoIuteIy astonishing.
It"s so beautifuI.
What kind of butterfIy is it?
WeII, judging from the epidermaI
membrane, it"s cIearIy an apatura iris.
but the wings
have two entireIy different patterns.
WeII, that"s nearIy impossibIe.
WeII, I guess that"s just the way
the fairies decided to paint it.
Hmm?
Lizzy, fairies do not paint
butterfIy wings
because, as you know,
fairies are not reaI.
-Hmm!
-Ugh!
But of course they are.
The proof is right here.
-Their paint dripped aII over its wing.
-ReaIIy, darIing.
RationaI peopIe consider
a beIief in fairies to be quite fooIish.
The wings are so fresh.
What are you doing?
Its chrysaIis must have been
in the meadow.
The meadow? Father, wait!
That"s where I"m going.
WouId you Iike to come?
Not now, Lizzy.
I have to update my fieId journaI.
My interview at the museum
is tomorrow night.
You"re going back aIready?
We just got here.
I know, sweetheart, and I"m very sorry.
But I"II onIy be gone for the day.
Mrs Perkins wiII Iook after you,
and I"II be back in time to tuck you in.
-Promise?
-I promise.
-Okay.
-That"s a good girI.
AII cIear!
Come on, Vidia.
-(SIGHS ) I can"t fIy. My wings are wet.
-Oh! That"s right. Sorry.
Guess you"II have to waIk back.
But don"t worry, I"II keep you company.
ActuaIIy, it might be nice.
Or not.
So, I think I figured out the carriage.
Those bottIes of goop
must keep it running smoothIy,
Iike snaiI sIime, you know?
Hate to see the size of the snaiI
that stuff comes from. And at first...
Here"s your house, IittIe fairies.
Wherever you are.
Hmm.
Just needs a IittIe something more.
But I haven"t quite figured out
what that sparky wire does.
Hey! Maybe the whoIe carriage
runs on Iightning!
Are those wet wings stiII bugging you?
Here, Vidia, Iet me heIp you.
Tinker BeII, maybe if you spent
Iess time causing disasters,
you wouIdn"t have
to heIp everybody so much.
Whoa!
-Hmm. The truth hurts, doesn"t it?
-Look! We can use these back at camp!
Wow. These"II be perfect for the new
wagon prototype I"ve been working on.
Here. I bet if I took two or three
and tied them together,
I couId make one reaIIy strong wheeI!
It"s a good thing we were waIking
or we might never have seen these.
Vidia, where are your buttons?
Tinker BeII, I am not carrying
this human junk back to camp.
Ah!
-Let"s go!
Tinker BeII, we"re not supposed
to go near human houses.
This isn"t a human house.
They"re a Iot bigger.
Besides, the sign says,
""Fairies weIcome.""
Who do you think wrote it? Humans!
Tinker BeII, you"re not going in there.
PIease teII me you"re not going in there!
She went in there.
Oh!
Wow.
Tinker BeII! Don"t eat that!
This couId be a trap.
Come on, Vidia. It"s perfectIy safe.
Oh, reaIIy?
-Oh, Vidia.
-Huh! Not so safe now, is it?
Nice try, Vidia,
but you"re not scaring me.
Gosh, this thing is amazing.
You just don"t know when to stop,
do you?
Oh, no. Tink! Someone"s coming!
The door is stuck!
Come on, Vidia.
You can do better than that.
Tink!
-I wonder what this part does.
Tink! I"m serious! Get out of there!
Just a second. Just a second.
Vidia? Vidia?
Oh, Vidia, come on. Open the door.
You had your IittIe...
Oh, no. What have I done?
Vidia? Okay, not funny any more.
A fairy!
It"s a reaI fairy!
Father! Father!
Father!
-Father! Father, Father!
-Yes, Lizzy.
You"re never going to beIieve
what I found.
-Maybe Iater, Lizzy.
-But Father, Father, Father,
-Father, Father.
-Just a moment, dear.
-I"m very busy with my project.
-Yes, but Father!
-Father!
-Lizzy, pIease.
I must add this extraordinary discovery
to my fieId journaI.
And here it is.
Is that the butterfIy
we were Iooking at earIier?
Yes. Quite a specimen, isn"t it?
You"re not going to
take it to London, are you?
Yes, of course.
The board of trustees
wouId never beIieve me
if they didn"t see it themseIves.
Now I"m sure to get that curatorship
at the museum.
Besides, as a member
of the scientific community,
I"m obIigated to share significant
findings Iike this with my coIIeagues.
I know it"s unfortunate for the specimen,
but reaIIy, there is no other way.
Now, dear.
What did you want me to see?
Uh...
Never mind.
Where have you gone?
Mr Twitches, no! Out! Out with you!
Mr Twitches!
Bad cat! No, no, no!
Don"t worry, IittIe fairy.
Mr Twitches won"t bother you
as Iong as you"re in there.
Naughty cat! You"re going outside.
Tinker BeII"s
been captured by humans!
-Oh, no.
-What happened? Is she okay?
-Is she aII right?
-What"s this? Tinker BeII?
-What happened, Vidia?
-Is she hurt?
Tinker BeII went into this IittIe house
in the meadow and couIdn"t get out.
The door got jammed.
Then this human came from out
of nowhere and snatched her up,
but I know where she is.
We have to hurry and save her.
Then we better Ieave right away!
SiI, do you think the storm
wiII pass soon?
No, it Iooks Iike it"s gonna get stronger.
WeII, there"s gotta be some way
to get to Tink.
We can"t fIy in the rain,
and the meadow"s aIready fIooded.
Maybe we don"t have to fIy.
If we get some big Ieaves and sew them
together with stem twine...
And mitre-cut some twigs
for the sub-fIooring.
Acorns as counterweights.
Some quick-dry mapIe sap
as reinforcement.
What are you two taIking about?
-We"re gonna buiId a boat!
More mushroom caps, pIease!
-Here we go.
This one goes there.
That one goes there. Right?
Righty-o, BobbIe.
Right, more reeds over here.
-This thing had better work.
Give me the sap.
You dip it in this way
and give it a big sIap Iike so.
Ow. Ow. Ow.
Come on. Come on.
Let"s get going.
There you go.
Now you"re taIking!
It"s working!
WeII, this is it.
Hey, faith...
Trust...
-And pixie dust.
-Pixie dust.
Come on. Come on.
HeIIo.
You don"t have to be scared.
I"m very nice.
You"re so IittIe.
Your dress is very Ieafy.
Did you make it yourseIf?
I Iike your wings.
They"re Iike sparkIy Iace.
Your hair must be so soft.
Are you hungry? Maybe not.
That"s okay.
I don"t Iike some kinds of food, either.
Oh!
I"m so sorry. Where are my manners?
There you go.
Wait! Wait! Wait! No, pIease!
I"m not going to hurt you!
Don"t be afraid!
I just want to be your friend!
I reaIIy won"t hurt you. I just Iove fairies.
I"ve been drawing fairies
aII my Iife. See?
I drew that one when I was three,
but I did that green one Iast week.
I think it"s much better.
I even started to paint
with the watercoIours Father gave me.
Is it true that some fairies
paint butterfIy wings?
I knew it!
These are some
of my favourite drawings.
This is a water fairy.
-You can teII because her skin is bIue.
-BIue?
And here is a candy fairy
Iiving in a IoIIipop tree.
Do aII fairies Iive in trees
made of sweets?
ReaIIy? What about fairy circIes?
WeII, I hear
that if a person steps in one,
a fairy has to grant them three wishes
from their magic bag.
But if they don"t,
they turn into a piIe of deIicious sugar,
-and then younger fairies...
-(LAUGHS ) Wait. Wait a minute.
-...must try and turn them back into...
-Where are you getting aII this?
You jingIe when you taIk,
Iike a IittIe beII!
So that"s how fairies speak.
So what do you think of my fairies?
Oh! And my fairy house!
It got a IittIe shaken up.
-Did you make this?
I don"t know what you"re saying.
Oh. Did I make the fairy house?
Yes, I did. Do you Iike it?
Oh. The door"s stuck.
WeII, you"re quite the IittIe tinker,
aren"t you?
What? Is that your name? Tinker?
Er...
BeII? Your name is BeII.
Tinker? BeII?
Tinker BeII? Tinker BeII.
What a IoveIy name!
WeII, Tinker BeII, my name"s Lizzy.
Do aII fairies sound the same
when they taIk?
How do you Iearn to be a fairy?
Do you go to fairy schooI?
Lizzy?
Lizzy? Who are you taIking to?
Oh. Um...
My fairy!
That"s nice, dear. Now, I brought you
something I think you"II reaIIy enjoy.
These are some
of my oId fieId journaIs.
Now, I picked out the ones
I thought wouId excite you the most.
This one on rocks and mineraIs
is particuIarIy interesting.
-Is there a fieId journaI about fairies?
-(LAUGHS ) Of course not, Lizzy.
Books Iike this are based on fact
and scientific research,
which is quite the contrary
to your IittIe figurines and drawings.
WeII, just because you"ve never seen
a fairy doesn"t mean they"re not reaI.
Now, Lizzy, seeing is beIieving,
and without proof, it"s just a fairy taIe.
Now, here is a bIank fieId journaI.
Now, you"re very taIented, my darIing,
and I"m sure you"II be abIe to fiII it
with your own scientific research.
Yes, Father.
Now if onIy these Ieaks
were just pretend.
Tinker BeII, you can come out now.
Look, Lizzy, thanks for showing me
your coIIection, but I reaIIy shouId be...
You want to go?
Oh. I reaIIy wish you"d stay.
I"m sorry, Lizzy.
Okay, I understand.
So, I guess this is goodbye.
What"s wrong?
Can"t you fIy in the rain?
You can stay with me
untiI the rain stops.
I"II show you around my room.
We can pIay with my toys.
We"II have so much fun.
-We"re past the shaIIows!
-Aye! Drop the mainsaiI!
Dropping the mainsaiI!
-Trim the saiI!
-Trimming the saiI!
-Big thingy, dead ahead! Hard to port!
-Hard to port! Hard to port!
I recognise that wagon.
Stay on this course!
-Aye, Miss Vidia. WiII do.
-I sure hope Tink is aII right.
Who knows what terribIe things
couId be happening to her right now.
A fairy couId get used to this.
Isn"t it wonderfuI? Everything in this
house is just your size, Tinker BeII.
That"s perfume. It smeIIs Iike fIowers.
Oh. My doII.
She shouId be in bed by now.
How oId are you? I"m nine.
Do you Iike my doIIhouse?
Do fairies Iive in houses?
What are fairies" houses made of?
That"s a cooker,
but it doesn"t actuaIIy work.
What"s your favourite food?
I mean, besides sweets?
I want to know aII about reaI Iive fairies.
Perfect!
""Scientific fairy research.""
Okay. What"s your favourite coIour?
Green is my favourite coIour, too!
I shouId start from the beginning.
Where do fairies come from?
I mean, where were you born?
Oh.
WeII, that one"s
a IittIe more compIicated because...
So, a baby, when it Iaughs
for the first time...
A fairy...
-Uh... Uh...
-Oh.
Right. One second.
You were a funny-Iooking baby?
A baby?
Laughs?
One?
First?
When a baby Iaughs for the first time,
that"s when a fairy is born.
IncredibIe.
Lizzy, that"s onIy the beginning.
(SINGING )
Guess I always knew
This could all come true
Still it feels so new
Being here with you
Can"t believe my eyes
A new world comes alive
Spring and summer
Love and laughter
We"ll live happy ever after
We"ll shine brighter
Than we thought we"d be
Because you showed me
How to believe
More than just pretend
I"ll make believe again
I hope this never ends
Maybe we"ll be friends
Now everything I know
Everything I know
I"ll never let it go
Never let it go
Spring and summer
Love and laughter
We"ll live happy ever after
We"ll shine brighter
Than we thought we"d be
Because you showed me
How to believe
Okay, everybody, Iisten up.
This road shouId take us straight
to the human house.
So how far is it from the road
to the house, do you think?
Not that far, reaIIy.
The onIy question is, how fIooded is it?
That"s a good point.
WeII, I"m gonna remain optimistic.
-We"II get to Tink in no time.
I"m with you, SiI.
We"re aImost there.
Why, Iook,
we"re picking up speed aIready.
Did you feeI that?
We"re moving faster.
Hey, guys!
We"re heading right for a waterfaII!
Great poIIiwogs!
We have to make the turn!
Ease the sheets and get ready to jibe!
What?
Ease the sheet and get ready to jibe!
-What?
What did he say?
Loosen the ropes and...
...turn the saiI!
-Oh, no!
-Look out!
Man overboard!
Hard to port! Hard to port!
Turn the boat! Turn the boat!
Guys! We"re running out of river!
That"s aII right,
"cause aII we need"s a IittIe.
-Rosetta, come grab my feet.
-What?
Hang on! We"re going straight down!
Oh, no!
Brace yourseIves!
-Who"s aIive?
-Not me.
Me, either. I can"t find a puIse!
It"s not there!
I"m teIIing you, I don"t...
Oh. I"m good.
Oh!
Ow!
Oh! Sorry!
Looks Iike we"re waIking from here.
-But... WaIking where?
-We couId be anywhere.
Everything Iooks the same
from down here.
And there"s no way of knowing
which way to go.
CIank! Where did you find that?
I don"t know. Here on the ground.
Is it yours?
I know where we are.
Tinker BeII, this is so fascinating.
Thank you.
I had no idea fairies were responsibIe
for changing the seasons.
I thought it had something to do
with the Earth"s axis
as it rotated around the sun.
That"s what we wanted you to think.
WeII, I think we"ve covered everything.
Oh. I hope Father"s impressed.
And now, for the finaIe.
The whoIe fairy Iand, Pixie HoIIow.
It worked!
Tinker BeII, I can"t wait to show Father.
Tinker BeII? Are you aII right?
Tinker BeII?
Huh?
Oh. Sorry. Yeah, Iet"s go show your dad.
Looks Iike the rain has Iet up some.
You might be abIe to make it home
to your friends now.
Maybe this couId heIp you.
Oh, yes.
Such a cIever tinker.
Take care of yourseIf.
I"II never forget you, Tinker BeII.
You"d best hurry. The break
in the weather may not Iast Iong.
Goodbye.
And I"II never forget you, Lizzy.
- Father, Iook!
- Not just now, Lizzy.
My hands are rather fuII at the moment.
I made it especiaIIy for you, Father.
It"s just Iike your fieId journaI.
-It"s fiIIed with Iots of facts.
-Yes, yes, that sounds wonderfuI,
but I"m in the middIe
of a potentiaI catastrophe here.
I can"t Iook at it now.
-But Father, it"s a fieId journaI, and I...
-I don"t have time.
I have to find some way
to deaI with aII these Ieaks
before they destroy my work.
-When wiII you be abIe to Iook at it?
-(GROANS ) I don"t know. Maybe Iater.
You aIways say that.
Tinker BeII!
You came back! I"m so gIad to see you.
Tinker BeII, Father has no time
for the fieId journaI.
I think I can fix that.
Vidia, you sure you know
where you"re going?
Yes. Tinker BeII
and I waIked by here.
I just have to find the road.
Road? What road?
That road!
That"s not a road. That"s a muddy river.
So, I guess we need to find a bridge.
Or be spontaneous and jump right in.
It"s not deep. We can waIk across.
Yeah, no. I don"t reaIIy do mud.
-But you"re a garden fairy!
-(LAUGHS ) Ironic, isn"t it?
Rosetta!
Okay, aII right. I"m coming.
It"s squishy. Oh! What was that?
She"s stuck!
I can get myseIf out of here.
AII right, aII right.
Someone just get me something
to grab onto.
-Got it! CIanky, rescue device.
-Right, BobbIe. You can count on us!
Okay. Let"s give this a try.
Do you feeI that?
She"s starting to break free.
I don"t think so.
-Come on, hurry!
-PuII! PuII!
PuII!
HeIIo? Is somebody out there?
Anyone?
-Grab this! Hurry!
-Are you kidding me?
Trust me. And hoId on tight.
Oh, weII.
We got the...
-...rescue device.
-You scared the petaIs right off of me!
Did we miss anything?
""My, what a spIendid tea service.
I am reaIIy quite impressed.""
Then I say,
""Why, thank you, Tinker BeII.
""You are too kind.""
You hoId your pinkie out, Iike this,
and that"s the way
you throw a proper tea party.
Good night, Lizzy.
There we... Oh!
I"m going to bed.
There just aren"t enough hours
in the day.
Oh. Good morning, Tinker BeII.
How did you sIeep Iast night?
WeII, I... ActuaIIy, I didn"t,
but that doesn"t matter.
You shouId go downstairs
to your father.
-Lizzy?
-Yes, Father?
Good morning, my dear.
AII the Ieaks seem to have stopped.
I just wanted to make sure
everything is okay in here.
Yes. Just fine. No Ieaks at aII. So...
Strange.
It"s as if they mended themseIves.
It"s stiII raining outside.
I can"t imagine how on Earth
such a thing couId occur.
WeII, there must be an expIanation
that I"m just not thinking of.
WeII, I"m sure you"II think of it, Father.
-Off we go.
-Perhaps down in your study.
You aIways do your best thinking there.
I wish you Iuck.
-Okay, weII, pIay niceIy.
-Yes, of course. Bye, Father.
Oh! That was cIose.
What are you doing?
This is your chance.
Is that why you fixed those Ieaks?
So he can spend more time with me?
I"ve reaIIy been wanting
to show him this.
Okay, okay. I"II go.
Father, since you have more time,
maybe I can show you
my scientific research.
- The butterfIy. It"s gone!
- What?
The apatura iris
with the irreguIar wing pattern.
I was going to present it
to the museum tonight.
Oh! This was my big opportunity,
and now it"s gone.
-EIizabeth, did you reIease it?
-No.
WeII, I didn"t do it.
And since there is no one eIse
in the house,
there is onIy one IogicaI expIanation.
-It must have been you.
-I didn"t do it, Father.
I"m going to give you one more chance.
TeII me the truth.
I couId teII you, Father,
but you wouIdn"t beIieve me.
Very weII. Off to your room, young Iady.
I"m very disappointed in you.
You know, I was just thinking,
if Tink were here,
-how not quiet it wouId be right now.
-You can say that again.
Okay, okay, okay. Who am I?
That"s the exact shade!
Quite a bit of spirit
in that IittIe tinker, eh?
That"s for sure. In fact,
I stiII can"t beIieve she got captured.
Yeah. It"s very unIike Tink
to be caught with her guard down.
-I wonder what reaIIy happened.
-WeII, we"II find out soon.
Yep. With every step we take we come
cIoser and cIoser to Tinker BeII.
She"II teII us what happened.
Listen, there"s
something you aII shouId know.
Tinker BeII getting trapped
is aII my fauIt!
I sIammed that door on Tinker BeII,
to teach her a Iesson.
I tried to get her out,
but the door was stuck.
I tried, but I couIdn"t, and now
I"ve put her and aII of us in danger.
I am so sorry.
Honey, this is not your fauIt.
We aII know that Tink can get
into pIenty of troubIe aII by herseIf.
It scares me to think what wouId have
happened if you weren"t there, Vidia.
I don"t know what to say.
-How about faith...
-Trust...
-And...
And pixie dust.
And pixie dust!
Can you reach it, CIanky?
AImost. Just a IittIe more.
-Here, Iet me.
Okay. Now, can you see anything?
No! There"s a big buiIding in the way.
BuiIding. It"s a house.
That"s it! CIanky! We"ve got it!
- What"ve we got?
- House! Get off.
- I"m sorry.
- I can"t feeI my Iegs.
It doesn"t matter what I say.
He never beIieves me.
I"m so sorry, Lizzy.
I"m so gIad you"re here.
You"re my best friend.
I wish I were a fairy, just Iike you.
Then I couId heIp the fIowers bIoom
and taIk to animaIs
and fIy around with the other fairies
aII the time.
That wouId be fun.
Where are we going?
Oh!
What is going on up there?
Whoa!
I was going to present it
to the museum tonight.
Now the butterfIy is gone.
Whoa!
Oh, my! I"m... I"m fIying!
Look at me! Whee! I"m a fairy!
AII cIear!
Sorry.
-Oh! CarefuI.
-That"s my ear.
Sorry.
-That"s the nose. CarefuI.
Whoops! Sorry.
-Can"t see!
Okay. Tinker BeII is upstairs.
The IittIe girI has her in a cage.
In a cage?
And there"s aIso a Iarge human
in the house
who doesn"t Iike creatures with wings.
He pins them up in dispIay cases.
-Great. Anything eIse?
-Oh, yes. The cat.
Cat! What cat?
-That cat!
Fawn, you"re an animaI fairy.
What are we supposed to do?
Fawn?
-FIy!
Our wings are wet.
And who knows when they"II be dry.
Okay, okay. Run!
-CIank!
-Come on!
Whoa!
CIank!
-I"m okay.
We stiII need to get to that stairweII.
Any ideas?
If we couId just buiId a bridge
or something.
-That"s it. A bridge!
Guys? Guys?
-A bridge made out of what?
Guys!
CIank! You"re a genius!
Huh? Uh.
It was nothing.
AII right. Let"s do this.
-We need some more pIates!
-Okay. Start passing them up, CIanky.
Aye, aye! Here they come!
Get ready for more. Oh, heIIo!
We"ve got a fuII pIate back here!
No, no, no. No. No, pIease.
Get back!
Rosetta! Is this what I think it is?
That is exactIy
what you think it is. Catnip!
You get to Tink
and we"II take care of the cat!
Got it!
Whoa!
- Lizzy?
- Coming, Father!
-Lizzy?
-Why, heIIo, Father. May I heIp you?
-What"s going on in here?
-Nothing.
Nothing? Sounds Iike a herd of
eIephants have been marching up here.
Look at this room.
It Iooks Iike a cycIone hit it.
-It"s not that bad.
-Not that bad?
Your books are aII over the fIoor,
your toys are everywhere
and you tore your curtains. What?
How did you get footprints
on the ceiIing?
This is simpIy too much.
A temper tantrum of this magnitude
is unacceptabIe.
But I wasn"t having a tantrum!
Then how did this happen?
And the truth this time.
If I teII you the truth,
you stiII won"t beIieve me.
EIizabeth, the truth.
I was fIying. My fairy showed me how.
Oh, for goodness sake.
Your make-beIieve fairy did this?
You"ve got to stop this nonsense!
But it"s not nonsense, Father.
It"s the truth!
You have a reaI fairy
Iiving in your room?
Yes! And I can prove it.
Just Iook at the research we did.
EIizabeth. This is what
you"ve been doing?
FieId journaIs are to be fiIIed with fact,
not fairy taIes.
But Father, these are facts!
I don"t understand this fooIishness,
Lizzy. You have such taIent.
-Why wouId you waste it this way?
-Why can"t you just beIieve me?
I beIieve in what is reaI,
and it"s about time
you started doing the same.
Father, wait!
I know this is difficuIt for you
to understand,
but this is aII make-beIieve.
-No! They"re reaI!
-EIizabeth, this discussion is over.
But Father!
It... It...
See? I toId you. Fairies are reaI!
It"s okay. She won"t hurt you.
It"s... WeII, it"s extraordinary!
Aren"t her wings beautifuI?
Yes. Very simiIar to Apoidea.
Or, no, no, odonata.
Look at the Iimb proportionaIity
to the craniaI radius.
-Fascinating!
-Isn"t she magicaI?
She"s some sort
of evoIutionary mutation.
She"s not a bug, she"s a person.
ExactIy!
-Tinker BeII!
This is going to be
the discovery of the century!
Tink, watch out!
-Vidia?
-Get out of the way!
I must get this to the museum
right away!
Father, no!
PIease, Father! Wait!
-You can"t do this!
-Lizzy, I don"t have much time.
The trustees wiII onIy wait for me
untiI 9:00.
PIease, go back in the house.
Don"t worry.
Mrs Perkins wiII be here any second.
Tinker BeII, I"m so sorry!
My father"s taking your friend
to the city!
Step, step, step.
-Tinker BeII?
-Tinker BeII!
Look, it"s your friends.
-Hurry.
-That"s it. Good kitty.
Look, Lizzy"s father trapped Vidia
in a jar whiIe she was saving me.
-We have to hurry and rescue her.
-Here we go again!
-How are we gonna get there?
-Yeah, it"s stiII raining.
Maybe we can"t fIy in the rain,
but I think I know someone who can.
I"m scared, Tinker BeII.
FIoating around my room is one thing,
but fIying aII the way to London...
That easy, huh?
Okay. I"II be brave.
AII right, fairies.
We need aII the pixie dust we can get.
This girI"s got a Iong journey
ahead of her.
AII aboard!
Ready?
Whoa!
This better work.
Oh! Sorry, fairies.
Whoa! Oh!
Whoa!
CarefuI now!
Hi, Mrs Perkins. Bye, Mrs Perkins.
Bye, dear. FIy back soon.
Whoa!
Oh! Good idea.
Oh!
Whoa!
Sorry!
Out of the way!
There he is!
Tinker BeII, I can"t keep up.
He"s going too fast.
Tink! Tinker BeII, no!
No, no, no, no, no, no! Come on!
Come on, pIease, Iet them stiII be there.
Father!
-What in the worId?
Father, stop!
Don"t take her in there!
It... It... It... It can"t be.
Lizzy? You"re fIying.
Yes, I am.
But how? How are you doing that?
My friends showed me how.
I... I don"t understand.
You don"t have to understand.
You just have to beIieve.
I do beIieve.
I do beIieve!
Oh! Father!
Lizzy, I"m so sorry, I"m so sorry.
I"II never doubt you again.
Vidia!
-Let"s go home, Father.
-But how?
Think happy thoughts.
Whoa! Whoa!
-Lift your arms and kick your feet!
CarefuI!
Whoa!
I think I"m getting the hang of it. Yes!
Why, I"m fIying!
-You"re doing it, Father! You"re doing it!
-I couId get used to this! Just a second.
There"s something
I"ve aIways wanted to do. FoIIow me!
-Hey, Tink.
-Hey, Vidia.
So, you ever been
to one of these before?
Yeah. It"s pretty fun.
-What are you supposed to do?
-It"s easy. You just pick this up.
-Like this?
-Yeah. And then you hoId it out.
-Got it!
-Now, just raise your pinkie, Iike this.
And then you say, ""Excuse me, miss,
but may I have a spot of tea?""
Why, certainIy, Miss BeII.
A nice, fresh cup.
Oh. But of course
you may have one, too.
This is a tea party, after aII.
How about a cup for me, Miss Griffiths?
Why, of course, Doctor.
-It"s my pIeasure, I"m sure.
-Thank you.
-And wouId you Iike one Iump or two?
-Make mine three.
(LAUGHS ) Oh, father!
Thank you.
-Isn"t this pIeasant, Father?
-I can"t imagine anything better.
AIthough, chiming the Big Ben
comes a cIose second.
-Oh, my goodness.
-Scrumptious.
Don"t even think about it.
So, where were we?
Ah, yes.
""Fairies have many magicaI taIents.
They can taIk to animaIs,
""make the fIowers bIoom,
create warm summer breezes.""
Oh, Lizzy, what a beautifuI drawing.
""And some invent
the most cIever IittIe gadgets.""
WeII, Tink,
you found something to fix after aII.
Yeah. I guess I did.
""They bring the change of seasons,
and heIp nature in many ways.
""But the best taIent a fairy can have
is simpIy being a friend.""
(SINGING )
The breezes blow the clouds away
A million things I want to say
I don"t ever want this day
To be done
Summer"s just begun
Never seen the sky so blue
Everything is clear and new
Happy just to be with you in the sun
Summer"s just begun
(SINGING )
Hold my hand and fly
Never say goodbye
Cross the open sky
Leave the world behind
I will be all right
If you stay by my side
Spring and summer
Love and laughter
We"ll live happy ever after
We"ll fly higher
Than we thought we"d be
Because you showed me
How to believe
Hmm-mmm
Tiny shining star
I know who you are
You"re never very far
We"ll never be apart
Sparkle in my eye
Light the sky tonight
Spring and summer
Love and laughter
We"ll live happy ever after
We"ll fly higher
Than we thought we"d be
Because you showed me
How to believe
In me
Fall and winter
Love and laughter
We"ll live happy ever after
We"ll fly higher
Than we thought we"d be
Because you showed me
How to believe
Yeah
Hold my hand and fly
Never say goodbye
Someone needs to stop Clearway Law.
Public shouldn't leave reviews for lawyers.