Watch Movies, TV Series and Live Sports
Signup Here -> WWW.ADMITME.APP
If I could reach the
top of the world
Be all I am It'd be so beautiful
If only I could be brave
and I could be strong
I would know where I belong
If only
I wanna feel free to be who I am
What I'm about is
more than I've been
Ready to show the world who I am
Oh!
A little bit of sun.
Oh, look!
Hey, Zarina!
Oh.
Out of pixie dust again, sug?
You know me, Rosetta.
I could give you some tips
on conserving your supply.
I may just take you
up on that, Dessa.
A Dust Keeper Fairy
who's always out of pixie dust.
Ironic, isn't it?
Right there. Nice. Okay.
Rinse time!
Time to dry!
Hey, Z! Wings okay?
Just enjoying a stroll.
But thanks, Fawn.
Nice wind, Vidia.
Thanks. What's a "stroll"?
Oh, no!
So I could be who I am
Yeah, yeah, yeah
I'm closer to where I'm meant to be
If I try I know that
I can get there
I'm not gonna stop 'cause I believe
That there's so much more to me
So much more
I wanna feel free to be who I am
What I'm about is
more than I've been
Ready to show the world who I am
Started it out, but I'm holding in
Find my own place to stay
So I can be who I am
Uh...
We put the dust in the bags
and they stay there, right?
And yet, we sprinkle dust
on top of something,
and it floats.
Well, that's just how
pixie dust works.
Well, yes, I know,
but "Why?" is the question.
Know what I mean?
Not even a little?
Never once had the thought?
Good morning,
- Dust Keepers!
- Oh!
Good morning, Fairy Gary!
All right, let's see.
On blue dust duty
today we have, uh...
- What were we on?
- "Y."
Ah! Yes. Yvette.
Yvette is out for the
day, Fairy Gary.
Dust-Keeper elbow flared up again.
That's fantastic!
I mean, poor, poor Yvette.
Well, um, that brings us to...
Zarina, you're up!
Uh-oh.
Can you believe it?
I mean, one day early.
It's so exciting!
Uh... Six clicks to the right.
Yes, thank you.
- Wow.
- Careful, now!
After last time,
I'm sure I don't have to remind you
just how potent and powerful...
- No touching, I promise.
- Attagirl!
All right, then. Exactly 26 specks.
But why 26?
- And here we go.
- Why not 25?
What would happen
if we put in, say, 27?
- We put in 26.
- But why?
Ah, Zarina, you're the most
inquisitive fairy I've ever known.
Correction, it's a tie.
Let's just say, you're the
Tinker Bell of Dust Keepers.
But why do you say it
like it's a bad thing?
Because we don't work
with twigs and acorn caps.
We work with pixie dust.
It's our lifeblood.
There's no room for error.
Blue dust.
One of nature's
mightiest multipliers.
It takes the golden dust
from a trickle to a roar.
No matter how many times
I see it, just... Wow!
Indeed.
Okay, but if there's blue dust,
why can't there be other colors?
Because there aren't.
And maybe those other colors
do other things.
What if there was,
I don't know, purple?
What if there's pink?
The day someone finds
pink pixie dust
is the day I trade in
my kilt for trousers.
Well, what if we don't find it?
What if we make it?
Listen carefully, Zarina.
We do not tamper with pixie dust.
It is far too powerful.
But if we don't,
we'll never fully understand
what it's capable of.
That is not our job.
We're Dust Keepers.
We nurture the dust, maintain it,
measure it, package it,
and distribute it.
A beautiful tradition,
day in, day out,
passed from one generation...
- ...to the next, to the next, to the next.
- Oh!
- Oh! Ahh!
- Oh, no!
Fairy Gary!
Are you okay?
Technically, I didn't
touch it this time.
The cap?
Let me be absolutely clear, Zarina.
Dust Keepers are forbidden
to tamper with pixie dust.
Hmm.
No result.
No result. No result.
No result. Ugh!
Huh?
Hmm.
Two parts sunflower seed,
a dash of moonflower.
Huh.
It worked!
Oh! Hey, Zarina!
- What brings you...
- Tinker Bell...
- ...here?
- Remember how you were
the first one to use lost things,
and everyone thought
you were kind of crazy?
I believe Fairy Mary
called them "junk."
Exactly! But now, even she uses them
and tinkering is better than ever.
Well, that's nice of...
And remember how you crossed
the Winter border
when you knew it wasn't allowed,
but you just had to anyway?
I like to think it was
more of a grey area.
- Good. Now, keep that in mind.
- Whoa!
You...
You're bending light.
You're bending light?
But you're not a Light Fairy.
You're a Dust Keeper.
Amazing, right?
Uh, but, how?
Whoa!
You found orange pixie dust?
No, Tink. I made
orange pixie dust.
That's never been done before.
Exactly! I knew you'd understand.
Now, I can finally figure out
everything pixie dust is capable of.
Oh, what does Fairy Gary
think about all this?
Uh...
- He doesn't exactly know.
- What?
He doesn't really think
we should tamper with pixie dust.
- Do you mind stirring?
- Uh, okay.
I guess he thinks it's
just too powerful.
- Oh! You can't stop.
- Oh! Uh...
Is that blue dust?
You're doing this with blue dust?
Yes, and it just takes
the tiniest bit.
Can you believe it?
- Back up a little.
- Uh...
Huh.
- Wow.
- Purple pixie dust.
Wind!
Purple equals fast-flying talent!
Huh.
Uh...
- Garden talent next!
- Uh...
- Zarina?
- Pink pixie dust...
Maybe you should, you know,
slow down a bit.
Five pieces of petal
for every three drops of extract.
- Uh, should it be bubbling like that?
- Mmm-hmm.
Two? This time you're adding two?
Uh-huh.
Zarina! Are you okay?
Tinker Fairy Gary some trousers,
because I just made pink pixie dust.
Zarina, this seems
kind of dangerous.
Do you know what this means, Tink?
I've finally found my "lost things."
Dust-keeping will change forever!
Zarina, I really think
you should stop!
What?
Oh, no! No, no, no, no, no.
Whoa! Look out!
Huh?
Oh, no!
No!
OW! Oh!
Oh, no!
Whoa!
Huh?
No...
Hmm?
Oh!
How did this happen?
Oh, no!
What happened?
- Tink, are you okay?
- Oh, my.
- Yeah.
- Who grew these?
I'm so sorry. I'll help
rebuild the depot.
I'll come in early, I'll stay late!
You were told not
to tamper with pixie dust.
I think it's best
if you don't come in at all.
What are you saying?
You are no longer a Dust Keeper.
It's simply too dangerous.
We'll start rebuilding in
the morning, Queen Clarion.
Welcome one, welcome all
to the Four Seasons Festival!
Tonight, every talent
from every season
will gather together
to celebrate all the realms
of Pixie Hollow.
Wow! Can you believe it?
Everyone in Pixie Hollow is here!
It's so great to have
the Winter Fairies join us.
I'll say it is.
It's enough to give you the vapors.
Tinker Bell, don't you Tinkers
ever stop tinkering?
Can't seem to get
this latch to open!
It had better not stick like that
for our grand finale.
- Is it starting?
- No, that's just Clank.
The thing is pretty
loud, eh, Bobble?
Indeed, my bugling buddy.
Sure makes me thirsty, though.
It's starting!
Ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh!
Bobble...
Oh, no! Already?
Hold these!
But the show just started!
Ask them to wait!
Hey, guys, I can't see!
Oh! It's Periwinkle!
- Beautiful.
- Oh, look at that.
Hi, Peri!
That's my sister.
All right!
Oh, wow!
- Yeah!
- Yay!
Go, fairies!
R0, did you do those?
That wasn't in rehearsal.
Wasn't me.
I never work with poppies.
The pollen makes me sleepy.
Wait. Is that...
Zarina?
- Zarina?
- Hmm.
She's back?
What's with that wild hair?
Oh, look at those flowers!
Ooh!
Spring must be next!
That's my favorite.
Oh, I hope Clanky doesn't miss it.
Oh!
- Wow! Oh!
- Huh?
Oh, lovely! Oh!
- Guys, guys! We gotta hide!
- Oh!
Now, now, now!
They've really outdone
themselves this year.
What a show.
Whoo!
Excuse me. Sorry.
Yes, me again. Coming through.
No, no, don't get up.
Oh, sorry, I should have flown.
- Thank you, Bobble.
- What did I miss?
Wake up!
Please! Anyone?
Clank, help us! Down here!
Clank!
- In here! In the box!
- Oh! Oh, oh...
- Ms. Bell?
- Help, we're stuck.
Right. How does it open?
Push the button!
Thank you so much.
You've got to see this.
Oh, no.
- Are they...
- No. Goodness, no.
They're in a deep sleep.
For how long?
At least a couple of days.
Why would Zarina do this?
Clank, did you see her?
No, no.
Yes, yes, I saw her
flying towards the dust depot.
The blue pixie dust.
Ooh, this is bad.
Uh, yeah.
Without it, the tree
can't make pixie dust.
And if the tree
can't make pixie dust...
We can't fly.
On! Can't... Can't fly...
- Deep breaths.
- Can't fly...
- Okay. Okay.
- That's it. Deep breaths.
What could she want it for?
I don't know. But we
have to find her.
Clank, stay here
and watch over everyone.
I'm on it.
Especially the Winter Fairies.
Make sure they get
a steady stream of snow.
Right!
Right.
The blue dust has a strong glow.
If we can just spot it...
There!
Whoa, she's moving fast!
Oh, sorry!
Where is all this fog coming from?
It's mist. We must be
getting near the coast.
We're losing her!
Over there!
Oh, my!
Oh, no.
It's...
Pirates.
Great, now there's pirates.
Maybe they're nice pirates.
Right.
They must have captured her,
forced her to take the dust.
Well, we have to rescue her.
But they're...
Deep breaths. Deep
breaths.
- Okay.
- Hmm.
- Magnificent!
- Quite right.
A fine haul.
We got their blue dust!
Well, it's not theirs anymore.
It is theirs no longer.
I just said that,
you daft potato muncher.
Potato...
They're holding her
in the bottom of the boat.
You've got a right
wee brain, you know that?
Still smart enough
to know we got their dust!
Let me just say that your plan
worked perfectly, Captain.
"Captain"?
Here's to perfect plans.
Ave! Perfect!
Guess she doesn't need rescuing.
But now the hair makes sense.
What do we do now?
Let's just get the dust
and get out of here.
A little bit of pillage,
a little bit of plunder.
Oh!
Fairies!
Ahh!
Get her! Get her!
Whoa!
Got it.
- Here!
- She's getting away!
They took the blue dust!
Captain!
Give me back that dust!
Zarina, why are you doing this?
Fawn!
If you give it to me,
I'll give you quarter.
Quarter? I think we need all of it.
"Quarter" means mercy!
Ooh.
This dust belongs to Pixie Hollow.
You had your chance.
Wake up.
Tink, wake up.
What happened?
The last thing I remember was
Zarina throwing that dust at us.
Your dress.
I know. Um...
ls everyone all right?
I guess so.
I'm not. Look at my outfit!
Orange is not my color.
She's right.
Listen, we have to get out of here
and go after Zarina.
Silvermist, can you part the...
Shut it Off! Shut it Off!
I didn't do anything. I just...
Tink!
Tink, could you stop
not doing anything?
It's okay, I got this.
Whoa!
Silvermist, are you okay?
That's weird.
Here, let me help you.
It's so bright!
- Bright!
- Fawn, I can't see!
- What did you do?
- I don't know.
Ew, ew, ew, ew.
Get them off. Get them off!
Get them off!
Wait a minute.
Do you realize what this means?
Oh, my gosh!
Zarina switched our heads!
No. No, no, no.
She switched our talents.
- Excuse me?
- What?
I must be a Water Fairy now.
Oh, so, that's why
your dress is blue.
And I guess you're a
Fast-Flying Fairy.
I'm a... I'm a Light Fairy.
Ow.
- Garden Fairy!
- Oh.
Looks like I'm an
Animal Fairy now. Huh.
Lucky me.
No, no, no, it can't be.
- You're a...
- Don't say it.
Tinker Bell, take these things
back right now!
Okay.
Tinker.
Guys, come on,
we gotta get out of here.
Well, you're the Water Fairy.
Part the waters.
Um, use both hands this time.
Well, you don't see that every day.
You guys better hurry!
I can't hold it!
Oops!
Guys, are you...
.“okay?
Yeah.
Guys, I think I broke something.
Whoa!
Uh...
Nice, little, harmless,
sharp-toothed, hungry croco...
dile.
Fawn!
It's okay. When babies are born,
they imprint on the
first thing they see.
Uh, guys, sorry to interrupt
whatever that is,
but the pirate ship is gone.
- What?
- Oh, no.
Sil, Fast Flyer, check it out.
Oh, yeah.
Where is she?
You guys, I saw it, up the coast!
Let's go!
Oh, right, you can't fly.
Wet wings.
Still, there's got to
be a way to... Ah!
Excuse me, Ro.
Hmm. Structurally sound enough.
Strength-to-weight
ratio seems good.
If I had some rope...
Oh!
You're thinking like a Tinker.
Okay, fine.
Get me some vines.
Not a problem.
Will these do?
Okay, ready?
Wait for me!
Sorry. Gotta...
Can I please have that?
- Oh!
Go!
There's the pirate ship!
You can slow down now!
Easy for you to say.
Hold on!
Well, at least our wings are dry.
Yeah.
Twenty-one
gun salute to the captain!
Right, 21.
- Nice boom!
- Oh, yes! Nice!
Ohh!
Music to my ear!
That's right!
Encore!
Beautiful!
Yes, yes, yes!
Cease fire!
What? Cease fire?
What for?
That was only seven.
I say 21.
Right!
Twenty-one, obviously, on the
metric system, which is fine.
Come on,
we've got to find that dust.
If I may, good sirs, I believe
the proper acknowledgment
would be a toast.
A toast it is!
Now, there is a good cabin boy.
A beautiful suggestion.
- Quite thirsty, myself.
- Uh-uh!
If it pleases the captain.
You tell those scurvy
scallywags that...
What did she say?
She said, it does!
What is better
than a good mug of grog?
Two mugs!
Your tea, Captain. Earl Grey, hot.
Please, sir, may I have some more?
To our cunning captain.
Okay, you gotta love the boots.
Just one year ago,
we'd lost everything.
Our ship turned adrift, and then
we found her.
Exactly. We needed a captain.
And when we humbly asked
if she could make us fly...
She didn't stop there.
No! She did one better, she did.
Better indeed!
Soon, she's going to
make the whole ship fly!
To flying!
Fly?
First the Tower of London, arr!
The guards won't know what hit it
We'll swoop right down
and take the crown
And the Crown Jewels with it
And when we fly to Paris
Oh, the treasures I'll be grabbin'
The Mona Lisa will look lovely
Hanging in me cabin
Hey-ho
Imagine the places that we'll go
No one can stop us When we're so
High in the stratosphere!
Hey-ho
We'll be the freighter
that plunders
Every one of the world's
seven wonders
When we're up in the skies
For who can fight a
frigate that flies?
No one can fight a
frigate that flies
Next we'll roam to Rome, me lads
And here's what I'll be stealin'
I'll rob the Sistine Chapel
Of the Sistine Chapel's cieilin'
And for all the folks in Egypt
It will be a dismal day
They'll be crying for their mummies
When we take their mummies away!
Hey-ho
Imagine the places that we'll go
No can stop us when we're so high!
They will all cower in fear
Hey-ho, from Delhi to Rio to Venice
There's no city that
we will not menace
When we're up in the skies
For who can fight a
frigate that flies?
No one can fight a
frigate that flies
- Oh, how high we will be!
- We will be
'Cause the blue fairy dust
Surely packs a mighty wallop
Only takes a dollop
- Soon it will set us free
- We'll be free
From the chains of gravity
Then we'll hoist up the sail
And we'll set course for the sun
'Cause when you've got wings
No wicked deed cannot be done
And we owe it all
To our great and glorious captain
Although, now that you mention it,
why are we taking orders
from some fairy, anyway?
Heh, heh, heh...
Two, three, four!
Hey-ho, imagine the
places that we'll go
No one can stop us
when we're so high
- Givin' a pirate cheer
Arr!
Hey-ho, we'll be
the freighter that plunders
Every one of the world's
seven wonders
When we're up in the skies
For who can fight a
frigate that flies?
Hey-ho, there's not
a town or a county
That will not yield its bounty up
When our ship draws near
Hey-ho, there's not
a city or village
That we will not plunder or pillage
When we're up in the skies
For who can fight a
frigate that flies?
And every nation
will give a donation
When they see us sail the skies
In a frigate that flies!
Hey!
Ah!
- Whoa.
- Tink.
It looks like...
The Pixie Dust Tree back home.
Zarina must have grown it.
So, that's how they're
going to fly.
She's going to make pixie dust.
Ahoy, you biscuit-eating
bilge rats!
Prepare to dock starboard!
Docking starboard!
Captain says, raise the sails
and step lively!
Raise the sails!
Heave!
Bring her around, Mr. Yang!
Bringing her around!
- Let go anchor!
- Get out all lines!
Casting lines!
- Come on, get moving.
- Are you talking to me?
Captain says, restock the ship.
We set sail at dawn.
Yes, Captain.
Load ship, right away.
Hey, watch where
you're swinging that thing!
Work faster, now!
That's it!
Come on.
Locked.
Come on, you lubber,
get on with it.
Someone's coming!
Pirate!
Hide!
Animal Fairy, you're up.
Excuse me, mouse. Uh...
Mr. Mouse.
Would you mind terribly moving on?
We need this space to
do a little hiding.
Oh!
Much obliged.
Bye-bye!
Aw, what a cute little mouse.
It was a rat.
Ew!
Hey, shoo, rat!
Uh, permission to enter, Captain.
This is our chance.
Now!
No!
I had Oppenheimer
make you your favorite.
The dust.
I know how much you like a little
something sweet while you work.
Well, you're quite welcome.
Hmm? Oh, uh...
Uh, yes, of course. Sorry.
Ah, right, second drawer.
Look at that.
It sparkles like a
thousand sapphires.
You're quite the little genius.
It's hard to believe the other fairies
didn't appreciate your talent.
- Sil?
- She looks seasick.
This never happened
when I was a Water Fairy.
You know,
I remember when I couldn't
- understand a single jingle.
- Oh, no!
Huh?
I'm fine.
Fawn!
- Sorry!
- What are you doing?
- What Dess does.
- That's not what I do.
Well, stop it!
You shouldn't take
light so lightly.
- What?
- What, what? What?
No, nothing, nothing!
Ooh.
It's still so hard to believe that
this blue dust can make flying dust.
Yes, but only if you...
Ah!
So, the secret is the infusion of the
blue dust directly into the tree.
You okay?
Start throwing out the line.
All right, Tink, open the drawer
as much as you can.
So, once the golden
dust has been produced...
Sil, hold the line.
The sluice will coat the
ship with the perfect amount,
and at that point,
we take to the skies!
Very impressive, Captain.
No pirate I know could
have imagined such a scheme.
Whoa!
Ahh!
- Oh.
- Vidia!
You've turned out to be quite
the pint-sized prodigy,
if I may say.
It's been an adventure
and an honor.
Your sword, Captain.
Hmm.
Y'all okay?
Yeah. They're headed for the tree.
Come on!
Whoa! What is up with your...
Hey, hey, we should
catch up with Tink.
Shh.
All right, just give me the strap.
That's it, hold it in place.
Right, watch the
angle of the flume.
Too much pitch,
and she'll overflow.
Aye aye, Captain!
Make sure the seams are sealed.
Captain doesn't want
to lose a single grain
of that precious dust.
Oh, that golden dust.
Dess! Quiet!
Sorry. I barely touched it.
Well, don't touch it at all.
- Just hover.
- Yeah, hover.
All right, all right.
As soon as she's gone, we'll grab
the dust and get out of here.
Maybe we should try
and talk to her.
Yeah, because that worked out
so well back at the waterfall.
Hey, shoo.
Hey!
Shoo, shoo!
Hey, hey, hey...
Go, go, go!
Oh, no. No!
No, no, no, no, no!
Stop growing. Stop growing.
Please, branch, no!
We 9011 you!
Did you really think
by switching our talents,
you could beat us?
Looks that way.
Got them!
Zarina!
Well done. Got them all
in one swell foop, I did.
Zarina, don't do this.
Come back with us. Come back home.
I'll never go back to Pixie Hollow.
You don't belong here.
This is exactly where
I belong, Tink.
We appreciate what she can do.
We treasure it, actually.
Put them below,
and keep your eye on them.
Oh, right.
Maybe I'll use, uh, this one?
While you still have it.
Captain, are you all right?
Captain says, back
to work, gentlemen.
All righty, mates, you heard him.
And, right.
Perfect fit.
Welcome to your new cabin.
Oh.
Me stock is ready.
- Oh, well, now, look at that.
- Oh, lovely.
Oh, that is good
eating right there.
Isn't it, Mum?
"Yes, it is, darling."
Oh, let me see.
What shall I make tonight?
Well, I've still got some lard
and some old cabbage.
Okay, we need a plan.
Here we go.
- Whoa!
- Mmm.
- Ah!
- Oh!
It worked!
- Yes, she did it!
- It worked!
- it's working!
- Pixie dust!
Look at it! Amazing!
We're going to fly!
From a trickle to a roar.
Fly like a happy bird!
Cold gruel, with a
little bit of sawdust.
A dash of rodent,
sauteed of course.
Some carrots? No.
Hey, where you think
you're going, little fella?
Now is our chance. Go, go, go, go!
Come on, all together.
I'm going as fast as I can!
Oh, not today, my darlings.
Would you be kind enough
to hold this for me?
Perfect.
Anybody else got an idea?
Absolutely astonishing.
Just imagine, flying like a bird.
Of course,
you do that all the time.
What's it like?
How do you even steer?
It's pretty simple, actually.
Lean left.
Lean right, fly right.
Whoa, whoa, whoa...
This is...
Are you afraid?
Hmm?
Afraid?
Lead on, Captain.
Oh, I'm doing it.
I'm...
I'm flying!
Look out, mates!
- Whoa, whoa, whoa.
- Look at him go.
What's so funny? Whoa!
Whoa, whoa...
You can't fly like that.
Put your legs together.
Whoo!
Oh!
On.
Just try to keep up.
Whoo-hoo!
Whoo.
Ave ave, Captain!
The lad is flying!
It works! It really works.
And pretty soon, we'll have enough
dust to make the whole ship fly.
Right, Zarina?
And as long as we have the blue dust,
we'll never run out of flying dust.
- Right again?
- Right again, James.
Well, then, we won't
need you anymore.
Our plan worked perfectly.
Fairies are such
gullible creatures.
Aren't they, lads?
No match for an Eton education
such as mine.
He's a smart one, isn't he?
The power of the pixie dust
is finally ours.
We've had enough kissing up
to that pint-sized prima donna.
No quarter for her.
Let's make her walk a
tiny little plank.
- Yes, tiny!
- A tiny plank!
She can fly, you cretins.
- Oh!
- You know, he's right.
That is why he is the captain.
She'd just fly away. I get it.
Mi capitan.
What if we tie her wings together?
There's no stopping us.
We'll plunder every port
in all the seven seas.
Prepare to get under way,
you scurvy scallywags.
We've got a ship to fly.
Ha. And as for you, you'll
make a fine little nightlight.
Swoggle me eyes.
Now, there's a sight.
Oh, don't feel foolish.
I was just too clever for you.
That's all.
Ah! Yes.
Now, you see, my little fairy,
navigating the Never
Seas is one thing.
But to chart a course for the sky,
not only do you need
longitude and latitude,
but you also need altitude.
Hmm. Oh...
Now, let's not be a sore loser.
Once we're past the second star,
the world will be my oyster.
And I don't even like oysters.
We'll be in and out of every port so fast,
they won't even know what hit them.
No, no, no.
Nice try, but it's fairy-proof.
Brilliant, right?
Oppenheimer!
That ticking is driving me mad!
Right. It's just a clock, you know.
Well, not to worry.
Pretty soon,
we'll be flying so high
it'll make these high seas
look downright low!
- Crazy.
- Like we have a choice.
Come on, guys,
we're gonna get out of this.
Well, we wouldn't even be in it
if our new Garden Fairy didn't
grow branches willy-nilly!
You're not saying this is my fault.
Hmm. If the flower fits.
How can I cook with all that
infernal jingle-jangling?
There's only one thing to do.
Oh, much better.
Don't you think, Mum?
None of it would've happened
if you would have come over
to help me with the bee!
Are you saying this is my fault?
Well, if the rose fits.
Let's not point fingers.
It's Zarina's fault.
- Guys? Guys?
- Right, what about her?
Yeah, let's talk about that.
Guys, look!
Great. Just what I need.
Uh-uh-uh. Bad crocodile. Bad croc.
I am not your mother!
Wait. Rosetta,
he can get us out of here.
You're right.
Good. Good crocodile. Come here.
Come here, stocky.
Come to Mama.
Shh! Quiet.
Okay. Now, pull us off the table.
Come here. Come to Mama.
That's right, sugar.
What is going on here?
A stowaway, is it?
Oh, no!
Oh, no, you don't.
Hello.
Hurry! Hurry!
- Gotcha!
- Rosetta!
A little extra flavor.
Ooh!
Good job, crocky.
You are such a good little boy.
Yes, you are.
What a good little
widdle snuggle wuggums.
That's his mama.
Okay, enough.
Let's get out of here.
Wait, Vidia.
We can't just race out there.
They'll see us.
Hmm.
Make ready to sail!
Aye aye, Captain!
I love the life of a pirate.
But I hate rats.
Move it, Port.
I'll move it in me own good time.
Huh, see anything?
Nope. All clear up here.
Well, it's not clear down here.
It stinks!
I know, isn't it great?
- Smells just like skunk.
- Huh.
Spoken like a true Animal Fairy.
I Wish.
All right, you guys. Remember,
right arm, left foot. Got it?
Aye aye.
Sil, I'm right, you're left.
- Right.
- No, left.
- I mean, left.
- What?
- And you're right.
- Let's go.
AYE aye!
Big pole.
Back, back, back.
Forward, forward, forward.
Hey, you swabs, work faster!
Hey!
Oppenheimer!
Don't forget the kippers.
And you, back to work.
Ah, muy bien.
Ah, we're gonna fly, mate!
We're gonna fly!
It's a do-si-do.
I can't dance!
Uh-Oh.
Look out!
Fly!
Would you watch where I'm going?
Go, go!
Come on!
- Hurry UP!
- Okay.
We got it!
Return that blue dust!
Or your friend is done for.
That's right.
Captain Zarina
has been relieved of duty.
Ha.
You truly are a talented fairy.
Prepare to cast off!
Weigh anchor and get ready to fly,
me hearties!
Casting off!
It's working!
I can't believe my eye!
Weigh anchor!
We're flying!
It's perfect.
We can fly!
Oh, my! Up, up and away!
Shiver me timbers, we're flying!
Bon voyage, little captain.
No!
Come on, hurry!
Hurry!
Help! Please!
Help!
Help me!
Here, I'll dry you off.
We're flying!
Are you okay?
You saved me.
Why?
Let's just say,
we're offering you quarter.
I'm so sorry.
They're headed for the second star.
If they make it past
we'll never find them.
The blue dust will be gone forever.
Then let's stop them
before they get there.
Captain.
Port, Starboard, get up the mizzen
and raise the royal.
Aye aye, Captain!
Raising the royal!
More pixie dust!
Who's in the mood to plunder?
You guys turn the ship around.
- I'm getting back that blue dust.
- Right.
Look alive, men!
The second star, dead ahead.
Nothing but smooth sailing.
Huh?
Yeah!
Fairies! Fairies!
It's the fairies!
She's back?
Well, get them off my ship.
Gladly.
It's actually quite amusing.
Stand your ground, men!
Yang, the helm!
Ave ave, Captain!
Ladies, until we meet again.
- Great.
- Ha.
You dare to fight the
captain, do you?
Only until I get that dust.
Well, this should be fun.
Come here, you little cuties.
Okay, this isn't working.
Fawn, the spyglass!
Brilliant!
You tiny thing.
No!
Man overboard!
I did it!
Stop them, you imbeciles.
They're six-inch fairies!
Fawn, the wheel!
Sil, whirlwind!
Take that! Whoa, whoa...
Blast it. The second star!
They turned the ship around!
Yup, we sure did.
Get this ship back on course!
Aye aye, Captain!
Now!
Why you...
Bull's-eye!
No fair! Come back here!
Fairies, fairies,
nothing but fairies!
Stop moving so fast.
Ha-ha! Just one more, pirate.
Jingle-jingle. Ha!
Uh-oh!
- Nice work.
- Just thinking like a Tinker.
No, no, no!
Take that, you little...
Oh, my!
Avast, crocky! Charge!
No!
Get it away, get it away,
get it away, get it away!
Yeah, that's it.
Don't make me use my teaspoon.
Oh, no. Oh, no,
you don't, you little...
Oh! You ate my mummy's clock?
What was wrong with the spatula?
Sic him!
Oh!
That's my crocky.
There's nothing I
revel quite as much
as a worthy opponent.
You're stronger than you look.
Hey, need some help?
Anchor's away!
Grow some seaweed, sunflower.
Whoa!
Ahh!
Now, that's some seaweed!
I've had just about
enough of this.
Ha!
You, too!
You're not going anywhere.
These ought to fetch
a hefty price, eh?
Back on course.
Give me that dust!
No!
The dust! Not my dust!
I got the dust.
Oh, you're okay.
Oh, thank goodness.
Let's get you out of there.
Lean right,
fly right.
I'll take that!
Now, where was I?
Ah, yes. The second star.
You simply don't give up.
Well, I guess I'm
stronger than I look.
The second star.
Oh...
Zarina!
You fought well, little fairy.
But it's over.
The dust is mine.
The ship is mine.
Your adventure has come to an end.
Oh, go ahead, take it.
What's one speck between friends?
No, really, I think you
should have it all!
Huh?
From a trickle to a roar.
Whoa!
We're free!
Look at him go!
He's very fast.
Yeah, you think?
Is it time to get
that blue dust back?
Watch this.
Can't fly without dust.
Blast!
Goodbye, James.
Curse you, fairies!
Curse you!
Tiny she-devils they are, really.
Huh?
Oh, no, no, no!
I am not a codfish!
I'm a pirate!
All right.
You got the dust!
We did it!
We can go home!
Oh, I'm gonna soak in a nice,
hot milkweed bath.
Get the smell of pirates off me.
That was what I was thinking.
You said it, Ro.
Here, please,
take this back to Pixie Hollow.
Uh, Zarina,
we didn't just come for the dust.
Oh!
Um, Ro? There's something
you should know.
It's about your hair.
First, I lose my talent,
then I become a mother.
I do-si-doed in a stinky shoe,
and now, my hair?
Oh, yeah. Oh, yeah
Well, you don't know who you are
Sky is the limit
And I just wanna flow
Free as a spirit on
a journey of hope
Hang on, guys!
Cut the strings and let me go
I'm weightless, I'm weightless
Millions of balloons
tethered to the ground
Hey! There it is.
Home.
And... now!
Bobble!
You're awake!
This is the best show yet!
Uh, girls?
Queen Clarion,
we got the blue dust back.
Which I didn't know was missing.
We also got Zarina.
Zarina!
Oh, you're home!
Yeah. And from now on, I promise...
You know, Zarina's
pretty much mastered
that pixie dust thing of hers.
Yeah, she even grew
a pixie dust tree.
Now, we've got an extra.
Does this talent of
yours have a name?
"Alchemy."
Pixie dust alchemy.
You should really
see her in action.
- Oh, you definitely should.
- Very impressive.
Hmm.
Well, we do have an audience.
Oh!
Wow!
Thanks.
Well, how's my hair?
L'£'S good!
Yeah!
Oh!
Whoo-hoo!
All right!
Gorgeous.
If I could reach the
top of the world
Be all I am
It'd be so beautiful
If only I could be brave
and I could be strong
I would know where I belong
If only
I wanna feel free to be who I am
What I'm about is
more than I've been
Ready to show the world who I am
Started it out, but I'm holding in
And find my own place to stay
I can be who I am
I'm closer to what I'm meant to be
If I try I know that
I can get there
I'm not gonna stop 'cause I believe
That there's so much more to me
Man in the water!
Oh, dear.
Oh, my.
Oh!
That's a very nice hook.
Just give me a hand.
I wanna feel free to be who I am
What I am about is
more than I've been
Ready to show the world who I am
Started it out, but I am holding in
Find my own place to stay
So I can be who I am
I can be who I am
First the Tower of London, arr!
The guards won't know what hit it
We'll swoop right down
and take the crown
And the Crown Jewels with it
And when we fly to Paris
Oh, the treasures I'll be grabbin'
The Mona Lisa will look lovely
Hanging in me cabin
Hey-ho
Imagine the places that we'll go
No one can stop us
When we're so
High in the stratosphere!
Hey-ho
We'll be the freighter
that plunders
Every one of the world's
seven wonders
When we're up in the skies
For who can fight a
frigate that flies?
No one can fight a
frigate that flies
Next we'll roam to Rome, me lads
And here's what I'll be stealin'
I'll rob the Sistine Chapel
Of the Sistine Chapel's cieilin'
And for all the folks in Egypt
It will be a dismal day
They'll be crying for their mummies
When we take their mummies away!
Hey-ho
Imagine the places that we'll go
No can stop us when we're so high!
They will all cower in fear
Hey-ho, from Delhi to Rio to Venice
There's no city that
we will not menace
When we're up in the skies
For who can fight a
frigate that flies?
No one can fight a
frigate that flies
- Oh, how high we will be!
- We will be
'Cause the blue fairy dust
Surely packs a mighty wallop
Only takes a dollop
- Soon it will set us free
- We'll be free
From the chains of gravity
Then we'll hoist up the sail
And we'll set course for the sun
'Cause when you've got wings
No wicked deed cannot be done
And we owe it all
To our great and glorious captain
Two, three, four!
Hey-ho, imagine the
places that we'll go
No one can stop us
when we're so high
- Givin' a pirate cheer
- Arr!
Hey-ho, we'll be the
freighter that plunders
Every one of the
world's seven wonders
When we're up in the skies
For who can fight a
frigate that flies?
Hey-ho, there's not
a town or a county
That will not yield its bounty up
When our ship draws near
Hey-ho, there's not
a city or village
That we will not plunder or pillage
When we're up in the skies
For who can fight a
frigate that flies?
And every nation
will give a donation
When they see us sail the skies
In a frigate that flies!
Hey!
Watch Movies, TV Series and Live Sports
Signup Here -> WWW.ADMITME.APP