Watch Movies, TV Series and Live Sports
Signup Here -> WWW.ADMITME.APP
Look high in the sky
on this Never Land night.
For a glowing, green star
the fourth from the right.
As it falls from the heavens
and streaks through the air.
You will know it is a comet
a sight strange and rare.
A harmless display?
A treat for the eye?
Perhaps.
But be careful
for appearances lie.
This comet, you see
has been here before.
The ancients described it
in old fairy lore.
Beware the green tail
as it trails along side.
And spills into corners
where shadows abide.
Take heeds, and you will know
that before the dawn breaks.
"Deep down in the darkness
something awakes"
TINKER BEll AND THE LEGEND OF
NEVER BEAST
Translation and Review
By Angel
♪ I am going to fall.
♪ Head first and fast like
an avalanche.
♪ Maybe I will land.
♪ Maybe I will crash.
♪ I will take that chance.
♪ Because there is nothing but air
in between me and everything.
♪ Nothing to keep me
from flying aimlessly.
♪ Shamelessly laughing
at destiny.
♪ And no one knows
how high I go.
♪ Or what makes
the atmosphere glow.
♪ I could follow
the narrow road.
♪ But maybe I will let
it all go.
♪ And just float.
♪ I will float.
♪ Float.
Tinker, it is perfect!
Just like you ordered, Fawn.
One extra-large wagon.
What for is it?
I mean, why is all the mystery?
I just love how your
mind is always working.
I can take it from here.
Baby ducklings!
Or baby bunnies?
It is a movable nursery,
Right?
Bull is eye!
I cannot get a thing past you,
Tinker.
Well, anyway, catch you later.
You are up to something.
Who, me? Never.
Yep, you definitely are.
I know that Look.
I invented that look.
What for is the wagon?
Okay, okay.
Just try not to scream.
Deal?
No deal. No deal. No deal!
It is okay, Hannah.
Tinker is with me.
You have a...
Deep breathe in.
...Hawk!
Yep.
Fawn, hawks eats fairies!
Adult hawks, yes.
Hannah is still technically
a baby.
That whole "must-eat-fairy" urges
has not quite kicked in yet.
She does not look so
babyish to me.
Well, she was when
I brought her here.
She had a bad wing,
but I fixed her up and now...
Wing is all better.
You cannot have a hawk
in Pixie Hollow.
What if the Scouts find out?
That is where the blueberry
wagon comes in!
We just have to get Hannah
out to where she belongs
without causing, you know...
...Widespread panic.
Good job!
Here you go.
Good.
You are doing great,
Hannah.
Hang tight until we are in
the clear.
Are you sure about this,
Fawn?
Remember, we are just taking
berries to the forest.
Nothing to it.
But do not berries usually
come from the forest?
Everything will be fine.
Just fly casual.
Exactly how often
do you do this kind of thing?
Come on.
Fawn?
Just keep smiling.
See, Tinker? I told you
this would work.
All you need is a little faith,
trust, and...
Pixie dust?
There you are!
We have been looking for you
all morning!
Did you guys see
that comet last night?
No, but did you see that big
green ball of light that flew by?
What is with the berries?
Just bringing them to the forest.
For the animals.
Do not berries come
from the forest?
Not this particular
variety.
Which is?
Extra berry full delicious tastic!
Can we help?
No, no, no!
We are fine.
Why would we need help?
For goodness'sake.
There is an easier way
to do this.
Wait! No, no!
You do not know what you are doing!
It is called "helping."
A simple "thank you"
would suffice.
What are you all
at staring that?
Hawk!
That comet is an astronomical
puzzle, to be sure,
but careful observation,
and application...
Hannah!
Hannah, stop!
Come back!
Everyone, get inside!
Iridessa!
No!
Nyx?
Hannah?
Hannah!
Go! Get inside!
Hurry!
Go!
Come on!
Wait! Everybody
calm down!
I promise, she does not even
like the taste of Scout Fairy.
Babies are such picky eaters.
It is okay, Hannah.
Everything is going to be all right.
Get away from the hawk, Fawn.
Let us handle this.
There is nothing to handle, Nyx.
I said stand down, Fawn.
Is everyone all right?
Yes, Queen Clarion, this time.
But how am I suppose
to keep us safe.
If Fawn keeps bringing dangerous
animals into Pixie Hollow?
Last time it was rats,
and a snake!
Actually, last time,
it was a vampire bat.
Fawn  just got a big heart,
that is all.
Hannah needed her help.
Does this look like the face
of a dangerous predator to you?
Come on, back me up, guys!
- Fawn...
- I know, I know.
Nyx is right.
I have done this once or twice,
or several times before.
Yes.
However, perhaps my latest
endeavor was crossing the line.
- Indeed.
- I hear what you are saying.
Maybe harboring a baby hawk
was the best idea.
Fawn, I know you.
You have always let your
heart guides you.
Which is admirable, but...
But I also need to listen
with my head.
Next time, I promise,
I will.
Well, Hannah-Banana,
I had said come back and visit,
but it is probably best to keep this
a long distance thing.
Now, let us try that wing.
Good morning, students!
Beautiful day for a fresh start,
do not you think?
All right, then, let us see
that hopping.
Nice work, Nico.
Perfection, Paige!
Calista, remember it is hopping,
not walking.
What, have not you heard?
I am strictly by the book now.
Yep, we are talking model citizen
all the way.
Looking for the definition
of responsibility?
Look no further than
this girl!
Well, that was interesting.
Now, that is hopping.
Hello?
Come on, Fawn, listen
to your head.
Heart gets you in trouble,
head is your friend.
And yet, head is making me
talk to myself,
out loud,
in the forest.
No, no, no.
Model citizen.
Starting first thing
tomorrow.
What are you?
Okay, think.
Territorial, possibly carnivorous.
Unspeakably big!
What to do?
Play dead!
No, no. Freeze.
No, the opposite!
Make myself look big!
What was that?
Did you hear it?
Hear what?
The roar!
Did you hear the roar?
Sorry, did you say something?
You bet I heard it.
Little faster.
Visualize the acorn right
in front of you.
Excellent.
What was it?
No idea.
But let me know as soon as
you find out.
Gently, now. To the left.
No, the other left!
That roars...
- This morning?
- What was it?
I do not know.
I do not specialize in roars.
Now, grunts and growls,
on the other hand...
Who would know?
Well, if it came
from anything big...
- Loud...
- Scary...
And dangerous, try...
Fawn.
Come on, big guy.
Over here.
Wait! I was only
trying to help!
So, I guess I will just be
on my way, then.
Those thick forelimbs
are ideal for digging.
Nope. No, no, no.
You all fixed up,
so off I go!
And that massive jaw is perfect
for supporting those heavy rocks.
Okay. Sorry,
sorry.
Just leaving.
But, you know, it is as if
you are a cross between
Didelphis marsupials
and Bison occidentales...
That spits.
Well, I do not know what
that about is.
And I do not know what
I really do not know what about is.
What are you building?
You know, it is my job.
As an Animal Fairy.
To understand and study animals.
And the Queen did say.
I should listen to my head.
You have convinced me.
I will do it for the Queen.
Now stay here.
Okay?
I will be right back.
I just need to get my stuff.
Do not go anywhere.
Just stay.
Stay.
Fawn.
Nyx.
I have been looking everywhere
for you. So, where have you been?
Off hiding a hippo?
Yep, he is bunking with
the bobcat.
Did you hear that roar
this morning?
Can you describe the roar
in question?
What kind of roar was it?
The loud, hair rising,
monstrous kind.
Animals make all kinds
of roars.
I mean, you have your growls, howls,
whoops, hollers, shrieks, rumbles.
So. Was it like this?
No. A roar.
As like...
No.
No!
Fawn!
Yeah. If you hear that one. Run.
Would you hand me that?
Look, this thing
might be a threat to Pixie Hollow.
If you find out what made that roar,
I need to know.
Are we clear?
What will you do if
you find it.
My Job.
And I will do mine.
♪ Strange sight.
♪ You stand in the light.
♪ You are wrong but you are right
my heart is beating wildly.
♪ Strange how I am scared
but delighted.
♪ Afraid, but excited, too.
♪ You have a cold heart.
♪ You are reckless and distant,
but I will be persistent.
♪ I will understand you.
Hello?
♪ Strange.
♪ How I am drawn to the danger.
♪ I reach out my hands to you.
♪ Do you long to be left
all alone?
♪ Set apart with a heart
made of stone.
♪ Let me help, let us begin.
♪ Let me learn.
♪ Will not you let me in?
♪ All the light.
♪ Let it show.
♪ You are a strange sight.
♪ Some new kind of wonder.
♪ With good hidden under.
♪ I am sure that it is true.
♪ Strange how your dark
does not faze me.
♪ No, I will not give up
on you.
♪ Do you long to be left
all alone?
♪ Set apart with a heart
made of stone.
♪ Let me help, let us begin.
♪ Let me learn.
♪ Will not you let me in?
♪ All the light, let it show.
♪ If you are caught in the shadows
and turned all around.
♪ Lost in the darkness
you will be found.
♪ If you hear my voice.
♪ Follow the sound.
♪ Because I am here to guide
you home.
♪ Do you long to be left
all alone?
♪ Set apart with a heart
made of stone.
♪ Let me help, let us begin.
♪ Let me learn.
♪ Will not you let me in?
♪ All the light, let it show.
♪ Do you long to be
left all alone?
♪ Set apart with a heart
made of stone.
♪ There is a light
that you shine.
♪ There is a love.
♪ I see it in your eyes
all the dark.
♪ Let it go.
♪ You are not alone.
I cleaned out the skunk
pen yesterday.
Good morning!
Looks like somebody is
a night owl.
What is this?
Okay.
So, where to?
Anywhere but Scout Headquarters.
Look, if I am going to cover
for you.
I need to know,
What for is the tower?
One beaver I know, Bob...
Great guy!
He makes dams big enough
to store food for three winters.
And, of course, marmots build
these terrific burrows,
out of rock piles for hibernation.
Then you have your northern orioles
and those hanging nests of theirs.
I mean, talk about brilliant!
But I am thinking you are not
storing food.
Or preparing for hibernation.
Or nesting.
Seriously,
What for is the tower?
You do not have to be
so gruff about it.
That is it. "Gruff!"
Yep, "Gruff" suits you to a...
Guess we are building
another one.
But before we start,
I was just thinking,
why not enjoy yourself a bit
while you work?
Just hear me out.
No reason I should have all
the fun with the pixie dust.
Come on!
Now we are talking.
Fairies and Sparrow men,
presenting the three time
defending champion
of the Pixie Hollow Games
Tower Building event,
the amazing, incomparable, Gruff.
Will he hold off
this year is pint sized,
yet feisty challenger?
And he nails it!
But it is too much!
The fairy wins!
The fairy...
No.
And done.
This may be our best spring yet.
Incoming!
No.
The boulders came from
that direction?
Affirmative.
If Fawn had not shouted
that warning,
we had be flatter than
a pumpkin seed.
Two pumpkin seeds!
Fawn?
Gruff, I think it is time.
We make like a tree and lea.
Come on, Gruff.
Where are you?
Gruff! No time for rock
collecting!
You have to get out
of here!
Gruff!
Nyx.
Snodgrass.
No, Gruff!
Wrong way!
We have to go!
Okay. New game, Gruff.
It  called Chase the Fairy!
Now, follow me!
Knock it out with
the Nightshade powder!
That is my big,
furry monster.
Maybe it is time to make
proper introductions.
Interesting.
35.25 miles to the right.
Fascinating.
Get me every animal volume
you have in here, immediately.
Bup-bup! Please.
I am in the middle of
a high-level, special, royal project.
Did I say "royal"?
Top secret...
Hello.
How may I help you?
And this is just the "A's."
You know, books are a workout
for the brains,
and the biceps.
And so I said...
Listen QC, Clar'.
Most Sparrow men could not stomach
this kind of pressure,
but then again,
I am not most Sparrow men.
And besides, that mysterious green
comet is not going to analyze itself.
Tell me everything you know about this.
Everything.
Over dinner?
Okay, I see.
I have misread the situation entirely,
have not I?
We will always have the "A's."
First, thank you guys so much
for meeting me here.
I am sure you are wondering
What about this is.
Whatever it is, it had better
be good.
I was mid-exfoliation.
Mid-exfoliation!
So, as you know,
I really learned my lesson
about being smarter
when it comes to dangerous animals.
-  We know.
-  Honey, you are doing great!
Yeah, you are doing really well.
However...
And here we go.
Fawn?
Ladies, say hello to Gruff!
No.
Hi? Gruff.
What is that?
I actually do not know.
I have never seen
any animal like him before.
Ever.
What does he eat?
Not fairies.
Well, that is a relief.
So, I am going to take him to the
Queen and show her. He is harmless.
Then I will tell her how he
destroyed Sunflower Meadow.
well, how I destroyed...
You know what?
Maybe it was both of us.
You guys destroyed
Sunflower Meadow?
He did it.
It was an accident.
Okay?
And what do you call that?
Again, I do not exactly know.
But I am working on it.
I am hearing a lot of "I do not know"
in this conversation.
Uncertainty makes me
uncomfortable.
Come on!
Have I ever put you guys in danger?
- Yes.
- Sure.
- Frequently.
- Yeah.
I still cannot sit up
straight.
Hawk!
yeah.
The point is. I want to do
the responsible thing this time.
Just like I promised.
I am guessing you already have
a plan in mind?
"Operation Gruff a Go Go!"
Open up, big guy.
My skin is going to break out.
Okay, so I will go in
and set the stage.
Then, on my signal, get him in
position, and I will bring her out.
Do not worry.
She is going to love you.
Here I go!
Model citizen,
all the way!
Good luck!
Be brave!
You can do it, sugar!
She is doomed.
Queen Clarion, I have been
thinking about what you said.
Which is why I am here to tell
you that...?
I...
You know what?
It can wait. I will come back.
Fawn, I am glad you are here.
So am I.
Nyx has discovered
a dangerous animal in Pixie Hollow.
We could really use your expertise.
I am on the verge
of perspiring over here.
Do you see the signal?
I had my first direct sighting
earlier today.
This is no ordinary predator
we are talking about.
It is bigger and faster.
Than anything, we have ever seen.
I combed through every animal text.
In the library and came up empty.
But it turns out,
I was looking in the wrong place.
Back to the forest!
What?
Mission abort!
That comet that went by the other
night, it was here before.
972 years ago.
And each time it passes
it wakes the creature.
What is this?
This is the Never Beast.
Once the comet brings it out of
hibernation, it starts building.
Four rock towers.
One in each season of Pixie Hollow.
Green clouds fill the sky.
The creature transforms.
And then,
a lightning storm so powerful,
it consumes all of Pixie Hollow.
Back home.
Come on, Gruff.
If we do not act fast,
this storm will destroy us all.
How do we really know
this is true.
And not just some crazy legend
or misunderstanding?
On three!
One, two, three!
I should get that checked out.
That is odd.
My mouth was open!
It is always open.
Guys! Guys, now is our chance!
Quick!
Look, animals do not control
the weather.
Ordinary animals do not.
Furthermore, this creature,
with the horns and the bat wings.
An animal that big could not
possibly fly,
under his own power.
Bottom line, either we capture
the Never Beast.
Or life as we know it is over.
Nyx, let us not do anything
rash until we know more.
See if you can locate
the creature first.
Yes, Queen Clarion.
I just do not want innocent
animals to get hurt.
And I do not want innocent
fairies to get hurt.
I am not the enemy here.
Both of you are conscientious
and talented fairies.
And I trust you,
both of you,
to do what is right for
Pixie Hollow.
What is the word?
She trusts me to do
the right thing.
Which is?
We go after it at dawn.
What happened?
You were suppose
to get him out of here.
we tried, sugar.
Giant thing would not budge.
I think he did not want
to leave you.
I missed you too, Gruff.
Sorry to break whatever
this is up.
But what happened
to doing the right thing?
Nyx got there first.
And?
And...
Nyx found this
harebrained legend.
About a creature called
the "Never Beast".
Who builds rock towers and shoots
lightning to destroy Pixie Hollow.
So now she thinks
he is some kind of monster.
I know. Crazy. Right?
Well, early day tomorrow.
Am I tired?
Really? I am wide-awake.
Good-bye, now.
Come on, guys.
You do not really think
any of that stuff is true.
It is just, I know he is not
what they say he is.
Even if you are right,
it is not safe for him here.
Hey, big guy. Done for the day?
Rest up.
Because first thing tomorrow.
We are going to find
some place great for you.
Just until things settle down.
Gruff, you see those stars
over there?
If you connect them,
they make a monkey.
See his tail?
But if you turn it upside down,
it is a swan.
See?
That one is a squirrel.
And over there, with the spikes?
Hedgehog! See it?
I knew you would get it.
You just have to know
how to look.
Imagine. You, a monster.
Of all the ridiculous ideas.
I know they are wrong
about you.
They do not see what I see.
Gruff?
It is starting.
What is that?
It is so green.
I have never seen anything
like that.
Gruff?
Gruff? Come on, Gruff.
It is "chase" the fairy,
not "run away" from her.
Fawn!
The Scouts, they were gear up
and moving fast.
Please tell me
you took him away already.
About that.
I sort of, temporarily,
misplaced him.
You lost him.
I got this.
I just have to find him
before the Scouts do.
Wait! He is going to build
two more towers.
One in Autumn,
one in Winter.
I thought you said
the legend was not real.
Technically,
I said he is not what they think.
But everything Nyx warned us about,
it is happening.
The clouds are green!
Look, it does not matter
what Nyx is legend says.
All I know is, Gruff would
never hurt us.
Please, Tinker. Trust me.
I will take Winter.
Hei? Tinker!
Thanks.
Gruff? Gruff?
Just like the other two.
Just like the drawing.
Over here!
It is head towards summer.
Gruff?
Gruff! There you are.
We have been looking everywhere
for you.
Gruff, it is I, Tinker!
Fawn's friend!
The Scouts are coming for you.
You have to hide!
Gruff?
Tinker!
Tinker?
What did you do?
No.
Help!
Nyx!
Is she going to be okay?
She needs to rest,
stay off her wings for a few days.
She will be all right.
- Thank goodness.
- That is a relief.
See, Fawn, she is going to be...
Fawn?
Gruff?
Come down.
I need to see you.
Gruff?
Stand firm!
Nightshade powder!
Steady! Hold your ground!
Let us move it out!
You did the right thing.
- Everyone get inside. Hurry!
- This way! Hurry!
Come on, Calista.
Get inside!
Scribble, get inside!
Fly away!
Get out of here!
At least I loved once.
Whatever this is,
it should have stopped by now.
Just stick to the plan.
Immobilize the Never Beast,
and the storm disappears.
Does the storm know the plan?
Get everyone to cover
until this blows over.
Help us!
Get to the shelter!
Move!
And secure the doors!
Stop this! I order you,
stop this now!
Do you need anything else?
Bring some extra bandages.
Tinker. We need to get
to the shelter.
It is not safe here.
I have to find Fawn.
Tinker!
Fawn.
It is over. He cannot hurt
you anymore.
Gruff?
He is exactly what Nyx said
he was a monster.
No, Fawn.
He is my hero.
When I found him in Winter,
he was acting really strange.
Gruff, it is I. Tinker!
Fawn's friend!
The Scouts are coming for you.
You have to hide!
Gruff?
If he had not pushed me away.
The tree would have crushed me.
I could have been killing.
Or worse.
He was protecting you.
He saved my life.
And I betrayed him.
Where are you going?
To do the right thing.
Hang tight, Gruff!
We are getting you out of here!
We need help.
Pull harder!
For goodness' sake,
there is an easier way to do this.
Thank you.
Go! Take cover!
Come on, Gruff!
Gruff, let us go!
Gruff?
- Come on, Fawn!
- Get out of there!
Life or death moment, here!
Listen to me.
You are having a reaction
to the Nightshade.
You can see my glow!
Do not worry, Gruff.
I am going to get you out
of here.
Well, I did not see that coming.
Nyx got it backwards.
He is not here to destroy us.
The towers.
They draw in the lightning,
so he can collect it!
It is what he has been preparing
for the whole time!
I understand.
We are going to the towers.
- No!
- It is too dangerous.
For once, my head and heart,
They are actually telling me
to do the same thing.
Fawn, you cannot!
It is okay.
That said, if things do not go well,
still, you can have my rock collection.
On.
All right, big guy.
Just follow my glow.
Okay, Gruff! That is it!
Pull up!
I am up here!
Higher!
Gruff, fly higher!
Are you okay?
Is that Fawn?
Two down, two to go!
One more, Gruff!
No!
Gruff!
Nyx!
What are you doing?
Saving Pixie Hollow!
No, he was saving Pixie Hollow.
Nyx, we do not have much time.
The fire is spreading fast.
Listen to me.
Get out of here. Get everyone
to safety.
Go!
Gruff, it is too late.
How can we catch it all?
Follow me.
Can you see them?
There!
Fawn!
Help them!
No!
Fawn.
Fawn?
Fawn, wake up!
Is she okay?
No!
This cannot be.
Gruff?
That is my big,
furry monster.
Fawn!
Every fairy should know the true
story about the Never Beast.
He is the brave guardian
of Pixie Hollow.
He is our hero.
And his name is Gruff.
Easy, easy. A little more.
Good job!
Hei? Gruff!
Thanks, Gruff!
Well, how about that?
They finally see
what I see.
Took them long enough.
Hey, Gruff.
Hi, Gruffy.
What do you all think?
We should do now!
Actually, I made a list.
Of course you did.
We should go truffle
snuffling!
With that sense of smell.
Speaking of smells.
How about a bath?
I have a lilac shampoo.
That could do wonder for that fur.
I know a hot spring
that is just his size.
With a waterfall!
Fawn?
Gruff?
Looks like he needs a nap.
A little rest will perk him
right up.
Will not it, Fawn?
His work done.
It is time for him
to go back into hibernation.
About how long are we talking?
A month? A season?
A Year?
More like a thousand years.
But that means.
We will never see him again.
It is time.
♪ Do you long to be left
all alone.
♪ Set apart with a heart made
of stone.
♪ There is a light
that you shine.
♪ There is a love.
♪ I see it in your eyes.
♪ Every day, every night.
♪ I know time may divide.
♪ But fate is something
we refuse to hide.
♪ And it is real and
it is right.
♪ Something strange
out of sight.
♪ We say good night.
Anyone who sleeps
for thousand years.
Deserves a decent bed.
And a fluffy pillow.
Make that a "Gruffy" pillow.
A spring-filled water bowl
that never runs dry.
A night light,
so you never have to be scared.
A little fresh air
to keep you cool.
And the enduring respect
of a grateful Scout.
Hey, big guy.
I will not see you again.
But I know you will always
be there when we need you.
I am really going to miss you.
I love you, Gruff.
♪ So many years.
♪ Such a long, long time.
♪ Even for a star up
in the sky.
♪ I could count the tears
and the long, long nights.
♪ But I would rather just
remember how you smiled.
♪ In a thousand years.
♪ I know that our love
will still be here.
♪ So close your eyes,
my dear.
♪ Knowing that our love
is going to last.
♪ One thousand years.
♪ The time flies by,
♪ in a blinking eye.
♪ No matter how we try
to make it last.
♪ But if souls are strong.
♪ They will go on and on.
♪ And we will hardly know
the time has passed.
♪ In a thousand years.
♪ I know that our love
will still be here.
♪ So close your eyes,
my dear.
♪ Knowing that our love
is going to last.
♪ One thousand years.
♪ We will disappear.
♪ If we can keep
each other here.
♪ Inside our hearts.
♪ We will never be apart.
So do not you fear.
♪ Dry your tears.
♪ In a thousand years.
♪ I know that our love
will still be here.
♪ In a thousand years.
♪ So close your eyes,
my dear.
♪ Knowing that our love
is going to last.
♪ One thousand years.
Watch Movies, TV Series and Live Sports
Signup Here -> WWW.ADMITME.APP