Watch Movies, TV Series and Live Sports
Signup Here -> WWW.ADMITME.APP
All right, Todd, let's go.
Let's go.
All right.
Keep it up.
Keep it up. Yes.
All right.
Nice. Nice.
Control, Todd, control.
Keep him away from your body.
Damn it.
Stay focused.
lt's fine. Stay focused.
Come on.
Yes.
- How's she doing?
- Sex and violence.
That's what it's all about.
Fuck.
- Hey.
- How'd your match go?
l won.
Shocker.
American, no hard
feelings, huh?
You don't play fair.
Oh, you're upset.
Screw you, you
uncircumcised little fuck.
Here.
My peace offering.
What's that?
A party.
Here we celebrate
after a match.
The girls here go crazy
for American boys like you.
All right.
- Girls, huh?
- Uh-huh.
The train to Odessa
leaves at 0700.
l want all of you down here,
full gear, by 6:30.
We eat on the train, hmm?
Hey, Coach, uh, listen--
Shut up.
When you win, you can talk.
l want all of you
up in your rooms,
get into bed,
lights out by 8:00.
No bullshit.
Mike and Chris.
Beth and Jen.
Todd and Sheldon.
Claire and Alex.
Night.
- Thank you.
- Get laid.
So, you and me?
Yeah. No, not gonna happen.
All right?
l'm only doing this for Alex.
Baby, it was one match.
You know you're
better than her.
You could easily
tear her face off...
if you wanted to.
But what if l don't want to?
Look...
you are really, really good
at this, you know?
You can go pro.
l just...
l wanna be a doctor.
You got pinned, that's all.
l'm quitting the team.
l know what you need.
You need to learn
the Todd Patterson...
invincible double-leg
double-hook throw.
- What?
- Go.
Now spread your legs.
Grab my neck.
Spread again.
- What?
- Now pull me down.
See? lt works.
Okay, you gotta let--
Let go now.
l'm coming up.
l said spread 'em.
God, you are so beautiful.
Blue eyes, do you always
get this excited...
when you pin someone?
You betcha.
Okay. Let's go.
Come on.
Freedom.
Where do you think
you're going, hmm?
Ooh, look at that.
11:10.
Long after lights out.
We just wanted to get
some fresh air, that's all.
ls that weed?
We won't tell if you won't.
Where are you really heading?
- To get some fresh air.
- To a party.
- Bro.
- Hey.
lt's a fresh-air party.
Well, then...
let's go.
lt should be straight ahead,
one more block.
Guys, where is this place?
Uh, it's 'Kanyazborst' and...
'Naza-vee-see-mostov.'
All right, thanks.
Oh, my God.
Dude, brace yourself.
You're gonna kiss...
my mother-fucking
feet after this.
Man, what have
you done now, huh?
Jesus.
No. No, l can't do this.
Hey, we should go.
lt's late.
Did you have fun up there?
Claire, come on.
Claire.
American, where
are you going to?
We're in the
middle of the fun.
Claire, you coming?
No. She said l'll
take care of her.
What the hell are you
talking about, man, huh?
- Claire, come on.
- l say she stay.
What's your problem?
Claire.
Get your fucking hands off me.
Hey, we just wanna leave.
You wanna fight, huh?
You didn't get enough
mat for breakfast?
Todd-- Todd, don't do this.
American.
Hey.
Hey, why are you mad at me?
l had no choice.
Uh, yes, that's exactly
what you had, a choice,
and you chose to fight.
You could have avoided this.
Okay, wait.
l think we're very,
very close here.
What time is it?
You're all pathetic.
Bunch of losers.
You know what your problem is?
You're not athletes.
You have no idea
what team spirit is.
All you do is think
about yourselves.
Well, you know what?
l hope last night
was worth it,
'cause you just risked
the entire tournament,
not to mention your future.
Coach, l'm so sorry.
And you.
Odessa.
We need to get to
Odessa, the Ukraine.
Odessa.
Doesn't anybody speak
English in this country?
ls there a manager back there
that speaks English?
Eng--
Odessa.
Excuse me.
l couldn't help but
hear your predicament.
l might have a
solution for you.
Oh, really?
The train l'm on
reaches Odessa.
Can you please tell
this...lady...
what train you're on,
so we can buy tickets for it?
You can pay on board.
That's how it works here
on the smaller lines.
Come on, get moving.
You missed one train already.
Let's go.
Excuse me, friend.
Are you the captain
of this ship?
Conductor Vasily Alexie
at your service.
Great. Well, we want
to hitch a ride...
with you to Odessa,
me and my five guys.
Welcome to do svidaniya.
That means we'll show you
to your compartments.
Okay. Great.
You two.
Rad.
Passports, please.
What?
Please give me your passport.
Why?
Many...
- Stealers.
- Steal-- Stealers.
- Thieves.
- Yeah.
Yes. Thieves.
We save for you.
Save.
So gross.
Nasty.
l didn't even want
you for this job.
And what do you know
about wrestling anyway, huh?
You know what, though?
l didn't judge you.
l gave you a chance.
And then you do this to me?
Wait till Dean Edwards
hears about this, my friend.
And you know what?
Even if we make the match,
they're all drunk.
Casino.
Restaurant car, parlor.
Oh, it's been remodeled
and refurbished.
God, this train has
got to stop moving.
l'm getting seasick.
Shall l open the window?
Let the ocean breeze
swiftly waft through...
and take away your mal de mer?
Oh, shut up.
lf this stupid party,
man, messes up...
my chances for going pro...
Hey. Are you listening?
- Every word.
- All right.
Alex?
Oh, my God.
Hello?
ls anybody there?
What do you want?
l'm sorry.
l didn't mean to frighten you.
My face has this
effect on people.
l thought l was alone.
May l?
Uh, please.
l-- l didn't have a
chance to thank you...
for all you help
back at the station.
We will make it to
Odessa in time?
Even if we don't,
the rest of our team
will wait for us there, so...
- Oh.
- Yeah.
Where are you going to or--
or coming from?
l'm going home.
l don't like flying.
Call me old-fashioned,
but l love train rides.
The only downside is...
that sometimes gets...
lonely.
Lucky.
Luck has nothing
to do with it.
English.
Where you from?
Maybe you should take
it easy there...
with the smoking, huh?
Maybe it's not your
fucking business.
Deal you in?
Um, is it even legal?
Sometimes.
Lucky for us.
Oh, wait, wait.
lt's this one here.
Hey, you're not
gonna charge me...
for this, are you?
l read some stories...
in that college
regulation book...
you won't believe.
No.
Good.
Just relax.
You wanna hear
something funny?
l don't even know
your name, miss.
Doctor.
Dr. Velislava.
What do l need a doctor for?
Truth or dare, Claire?
Kiss my ass, moron.
You shouldn't have
said anything.
All right.
You asked for it.
Yeah. Yeah.
Suck it all.
My turn.
Well...
You have to ask, don't you?
Truth or dare, geek?
- Dare.
- Take your shirt off.
Oh, brother.
Did those hurt?
A little...for a second.
Freak.
lt's kinda hot.
Pain can be fun.
You know,
same nerves as pleasure.
Truth.
Okay.
So who do you hook up with
at the party?
No one.
Oh, come on, man.
You disappeared
for, like, an hour.
Hey, don't be a jerk.
So?
No one.
lt's my turn, right?
Mm-hmm.
Truth or dare?
Dare.
Run to the end of
the train and back.
Okay.
Naked.
- There you go.
- You'd like that, huh?
That's fine. See?
l don't have anything to hide.
Better not let the coach
catch you like that.
He's going for it.
All right.
- l think that'll
be far enough.
Oh, my God.
- You sure?
- Yeah.
Okay.
lt's freezing.
Be right back, guys.
- No way.
- Unbelievable.
Oh, my God.
Hi. Excuse me.
Excuse me.
Sorry. Excuse me.
Damn it.
Fuck.
Guys, this isn't funny.
Guys?
Look, l-- l don't
want any trouble.
ls anyone there?
What do you want?
Oh, shit.
You don't want to do this.
Stay away from me.
Stay away.
l'm warning you.
Oh, God.
He's not coming back.
He's playing.
He can't hide for too long,
dick hanging out and all.
l'm going to bed.
Yeah, me, too.
Looking for me?
Uh, no.
Todd's my best friend,
but, uh, you won't tell.
Good night.
Todd?
Todd, are you back here?
You shouldn't be here.
lt's not safe for
you in these cars.
l'm sorry. l'm just looking
for my boyfriend.
There's no one here,
as you can see.
That's the machine room.
lt's locked.
No one can go in, not even me.
Do you mind if l ask you,
was he drinking?
- Yeah.
- Of course.
This happens every night here,
believe me.
- Yeah.
- Come.
l'll walk you back
to your compartment.
lf you don't find him
by morning, come to me.
l will personally help
you look for him.
Stop.
Todd.
- Hey.
- Willy?
What are you doing here?
Sorry.
Coach locked the door.
l couldn't get in.
Have you seen Todd?
Coach?
l'm sure someone has a key.
Real smooth.
This proves nothing.
He's probably off
training his golden boy.
Yeah, with his luggage
and toothbrush.
Excuse me.
Todd?
Hey, yo.
Come on. Todd.
Hey, hey, hey.
What are you doing, huh?
Let go. l'm looking
for my boyfriend.
Let go.
Don't touch me.
Let me-- Let go.
No, you look.
This is not America.
You're scaring the
other passengers.
lf you don't stop,
l'll confine you
to a locked compartment.
You said you'd help.
And l will.
Take her to her room
and stay there.
l'll have my crew
search the train.
That's all that l can do.
Thank you.
l'll be right back.
Hey, the conductor said--...
...wait.
Bad boy.
- Ow.
- See? Got a point.
- That's how it works.
- That's how it works?
- Yeah.
- How's that?
This is ridiculous.
l'm gonna look for Todd.
The guy said--
You need to relax--
Claire, stop, all right?
He should be back by now.
l'm not just gonna
sit and wait.
Well, the crew said...
they were looking
for him, right--
What if they're not
looking for him?
What if the
conductor sees you?
He's not.
Okay, wait.
l'm coming.
Fine, fine.
Oh, my God.
What the fuck is that?
He's not in there.
The conductor said
that's the machine room.
lt's locked.
ls that...blood?
We need to get in there.
Did you find...
whatever it is you
were looking for?
l'm sorry.
l was, um...
l was actually bored,
and l was looking for you.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, l was, um...
Don't worry.
l won't hurt you.
l'm gonna go now.
Okay.
Aren't you forgetting
something?
No, no.
What are you doing?
Hold that.
Careful.
Fuck.
- Here.
- l got it.
ls anyone there?
Todd. Todd.
Todd, l'm gonna get
you out of here.
lt's okay.
lt's me. lt's Willy.
We're getting out.
Okay. Okay.
Come on.
Alex. Alex.
We have to get
out of here, now.
l'm not leaving him.
Fuck.
Help me.
Don't just stand there. Help.
Todd.
What? What?
Finish it.
No. No. No.
l can't.
No.
Oh, God.
Let's get out of here.
Holy mother of God.
Claire.
Come on. Come on.
Oh, Claire.
Willy. Willy.
- There's no time.
- No.
Come on.
No. No.
No.
- What about Claire?
- There's nothing we can do.
We have to jump, now.
The fall will kill us.
He's coming. He's coming.
Come on.
Go. Go.
Oh, shit.
Come on.
Go. Go.
There's nobody there.
No way.
They were there.
Oh, shit.
Come. Let's not do this here.
Are you just gonna
fucking stand there?
What the hell is wrong
with you people?
Why are you doing this?
What do you want from us?
Oh, fuck.
No. Alex.
Alex.
No. No. No.
Let go. No.
What are you doing?
No.
Fucking...
Wait, wait, wait.
Keys, keys.
Go. Run.
Please help me.
Please.
Did you bring me
more painkillers?
l told the doctor that
l'm in a lot of pain.
l think the liver
is swelling...
or my body's rejecting it,
or l don't know what.
But l do know that
my family paid enough money...
to give me a few more
fucking painkillers.
Do you even speak English?
Hello?
l need the police.
Police?
English? 'Politzia?'
Willy.
lt's me. lt's Alex.
- Alex?
- Yeah.
l'm gonna get you out of here.
Oh, Jesus. Okay.
All right. Careful.
Easy, easy, easy.
Okay.
All right. All clear.
All right.
Careful.
All right, come on.
Okay.
You okay?
Watch out.
Oh, jeez.
- All right.
- l gotta-- l gotta stop.
All right.
Here.
Got it?
ls that better?
Yeah.
Okay. Stay here, all right?
l'll be right back.
Please don't leave me alone.
No, l'm not leaving.
l'm not leaving.
l'm just gonna go and see...
if we're walking in
the right direction.
l'll be right back.
l don't want to die.
We're not going to die.
We're going home.
We are?
That's right.
Fuck.
Chicken shit.
Come here.
Wait.
- Don't do this.
- Don't come near me.
We help people.
Sick people.
People who, without
us, will die.
What about my friends?
lf you do this,
you're exactly like us.
Maybe l am.
No. No.
Now spread your legs.
See? lt works.
All right, guys.
That's us. That's us.
That's us.
We're up. We're up.
Are you sure you're
up to do this?
Let's go.
Watch Movies, TV Series and Live Sports
Signup Here -> WWW.ADMITME.APP