It's in the center of the circle in
Kingfisher County, moving northeast.
Also, I do want to say to you folks
back to the West, a little bit earlier-
Tornado warning continues now
and has been extended officially.
I gave this to you earlier.
It's extended over into Oklahoma Cou-
They're calling all of
Oklahoma County right now...
Jo common.
- What is it, Mommy?
- We have to get up.
We must go to the storm cellar!
What's happening?
Come on, sweetie.
Hurry!
Mommy's got you.
TV says it's big.
We're going to the storm cellar.
We must move! Hand her to me!
Come on! Let's move.
Go to the center of your
house if there's no cellar.
My Lord!
Come on!
We're almost there!
Take her! Take her!
I'll get the door!
- Get in!
- Hurry!
It's coming!
Quick!
Light the lamp!
Daddy! Toby's still outside!
Toby, come on, boy!
Good boy!
It's okay, Toby.
Grab Jo!
Daddy!
Take Jo!
God!
I can't hold it.
Jesus! Oh, God!
I can't hold it!
Stay with me, Jo!
At 7 a. m. in Oklahoma City,
the temperature is 75 degrees.
Look, caps are already
starting to break.
All the models are forecasting
lifted indices from -6 to -10.
If the cells keep building, there could be
a record outbreak of tornados.
This is going to be a long day.
Are you sure she'll be there?
If I know Jo, she's already dragged
her department into the field.
Day like today, it's to be expected.
She forgets everything except work.
You're nervous.
Nervous?
No.
Do I look nervous?
Well, yeah, you do a little. You know.
I want to get it over with.
She said she signed the papers?
That's what she said.
You don't think so?
I think so.
Give me a kiss.
Okay, Professor! Hang on there.
I think I fixed it.
I got it.
Fuck me! This thing is useless!
Sorry!
Wait, wait!
Good! Give me a reading!
Okay, boss lady, hold your horses.
Which way do you want it?
The dry line is stalled.
Scan WNW, look at mid-levels for
rotation, and increase the P.R.F.
If I mistreat you girl
Sure don't mean no harm
All I'm saying is, don't fold the maps.
I didn't.
Kansas is a mess. There's a
big crease through Wichita.
Roll the maps.
The storm chasers.
Who's that handsome devil?
Gentlemen.
The Extreme! It's the Extreme!
Don't start that shit.
A manly handshake ensues.
How you doing, man?
I'm doing great.
Oh, man!
I'd like you to meet Melissa.
This is Dusty.
Dustman's been chasing
with us since we started.
Listen...
...where's Jo?
She's by the Doppler.
Broke down again.
Running out of grant money.
Why don't you hang out here for a
little while. I'll be right back.
Dusty, why don't you
explain to Melissa...
...why you're the way you are.
Come on.
Man, Jo's going to wig
when she sees he's back.
I'm not back.
The prodigal son returns.
Hi, Joey.
Hiya, Jo.
I'm happy you found us.
How you doing?
It's going good.
You see the sky today?
She's really talking.
Catch.
It's the biggest series of storms in
12 years. One lined up after another.
N.S.S.L.'s never seen anything like it.
Is that right? So, Jo,
about the divorce papers-
Do you have a sec?
Excuse me.
This thing's acting up again.
The focus mount's jammed.
There's grass in the auto-focus.
Should I clean it?
Not unless you want to sketch tornados.
Welcome back.
I'm not back.
You want the papers?
I came here for them.
They're signed and ready.
Good. Let's see them.
Right now?
That'd be nice.
What's the urgent urgency?
You act like you're getting married.
I am.
Is it Melinda?
Melissa.
Wasn't there a Melinda somewhere?
There's only been Melissa since you.
Not much for browsing, are you?
I guess I'm not.
There you go.
You missed a page.
Right here.
Where'd this come from?
What're you doing?
Can I read it first?
It's the same as December.
I didn't read it then.
Christ, would you sign it
so we can get out of here?
Please.
"We?" She's here?
She's with Dusty. Now,
please, sign the document.
With Dusty? What's wrong with you?
I want to meet her.
No, you don't.
Christ.
The suck zone.
It's the point...
...basically at which the twister...
...sucks you up.
That's not the technical
term for it, obviously.
I'm Jo Harding.
Nice to meet you.
Bill told me the happy news.
- Which?
- Us. Marriage. Jo, Melissa.
It's happy news.
I guess it seems sudden.
Sudden?
Dude, you're taking the vows?
That's sweet.
We wanted to get it done before
Billy started his new job.
That's right. Weatherman.
What?
- Don't say it.
- I said, weatherman.
- It's great.
- You have that tone.
If you have a problem-
I don't have a problem
being a weatherman.
Dr. Melissa Reeves.
Very nice to meet you.
You too.
New truck?
That's right.
Boy, oh, boy. New job...
...new truck...
...new wife. It's a whole new you.
This is awkward.
Tell me.
I thought you'd come alone.
You said you'd meet me-
It's about Dorothy.
Dorothy?
What about her?
She's here.
Show me.
I can't believe you did it.
We built 4.
She work?
Thought you'd want to be
here for her first time out.
It wouldn't be right
if you weren't here.
This is going to be good!
How sweet is that?
It's Bill's concept.
The Extreme. It came from his brain.
I had a hand in it.
It is great.
What is it?
It's an instrument pack for studying
tornados. First one in history.
It's very exciting.
Scientists have studied
tornados forever...
...but nobody knows
how a tornado works.
We don't know what happens inside...
...because nobody can take
measurements inside the funnel.
That's what she's going to do.
How?
We put her up inside a tornado.
She opens...
...and releases hundreds
of these sensors...
...that measure all parts of
the tornado simultaneously.
You see, it's like this:
These sensors go up the funnel
and radio back information...
...about the internal structure,
wind velocities...
We'll learn more in 30 seconds
than in the last 30 years.
Get a profile for the first time.
What will that do?
If we know how tornados work,
we can design a warning system.
Aren't there warnings already?
- The civil defence-
- They're not good enough.
Right now it's 3 minutes.
If we can get this information,
we can increase it to 15.
Give people a chance to get to safety.
That's what they're trying to do.
I can't believe you did it.
Well, we did it.
How do you get it in?
You get in front of it and
put it in the damage path.
And then get out again quickly.
That's the suck zone.
Excellent! We got major action!
N.S.S.L. says the cap is breaking,
towers are going up 30 miles.
Let's go.
We're moving!
It's fatty time!
Laptop.
We're waiting! Let's go!
Joey, Haynes, a little help!
Smooth.
There's Dusty!
Come on! You're always last!
Let's go!
We're going third. Preacher follow.
Get the camera!
I got it!
They can handle this.
They know what they're doing.
This is what they do.
They live for this.
Dorothy 2 & 3 ready.
Dorothy 4 ready.
Sure you don't want to go?
Go with them?
No, they'll be fine.
- Did she sign the papers?
- Shit!
She didn't?
Hurry. We can catch them!
Glad you're back!
I'm not back!
Rabbit.
Yeah, boss?
Can we do better than the 30?
Not for a while. It's best to stay
on it until we pass the creek.
Copy that.
Once we catch up to them,
take the truck and go home.
I'll get them signed, see you tonight.
This is interesting.
I'm going to tag along.
Jonas! Son-of-a-bitch!
Who is that?
Jonas Miller. He's a night crawler.
We all started out in the same lab, then
Jonas got himself corporate sponsors.
He's in it for the money,
not the science.
He's got a lot of high-tech gadgets.
But he's got no instincts.
And he doesn't have Dorothy.
I think we have fleas.
Jo, come back.
You change your mind?
Yeah. Why's Jonas here?
I'm not sure.
I bet he's asking himself
the same thing about you.
Shit! Hold on!
God damn! Son-of-a-bitch!
This essentially was a false alarm.
The radar appeared solid.
- How long till it's fixed?
-10 minutes, 15 tops.
Sounds good.
What drives me is the unknown.
What if we could predict
the tornado's path?
How many lives would be spared
by an early warning system?
And D.O.T. 3...
...is the answer.
The first digital
orthographic telemeter.
Inside, she holds hundreds
of these sensors which...
...when released into the tornado,
transmit back data on wind speed...
...pressure and dew point temperature.
Why didn't you tell me?
Don't.
And what will soon be the
center for all studies.
You shit!
Think I wouldn't find out?!
Get him off me!
What's wrong?
What's the matter?
You stole my design, you bastard!
What do you mean?!
Dorothy. You took her, you damn thief!
Oh, I get it. You want to
take credit for my design.
You're a liar.
She was our idea.
Unrealised idea.
Unrealised.
That ain't worth shit unless it flies!
Guys! Guys! All my guys,
get a grip on yourself.
We both know he'll never
get it up in the air.
Well, let me enlighten you people!
This baby has satellite comlink.
We got on-board pulse Doppler.
We got Nexrad real time.
We're going to make history.
So stick around.
The days of sniffing the dirt are over.
Better than what you sniff.
We'll see who gets there first, pal.
By the way...
...I really enjoy your weather reports.
You slime!
Come here!
Get off!
He's a corporate kiss-butt.
I'm sorry. I should have told you.
One day.
I'll give you one day.
Whether she flies or not, I'm gone.
Honey?
Is everything okay?
- Everything's fine.
- Are you sure?
Yeah, everything's okay.
I'm going to hang out here.
Why don't you get us some cold drinks?
Okay, sweetheart.
Jo, I don't know what's wrong
with Bill. He's wacko. He's crazy.
You ought to get a leash on him.
He's your problem, not mine.
This storm's going to be a lot
bigger than we anticipated.
I got reports of mesos from
Grand County to Logan.
Sharing information with me?
No, I was curious as to which
way you were going to head.
Southeast, I think.
To the counter.
Two lemonades to go, please.
- Nothing changes.
- Pardon me?
He'll wait and see what Bill does.
May I have a coffee to go?
That man is waiting for Bill?
Why?
You're telling me that Billy
knows what a storm is thinking?
Something like that. Gum?
My aunt called him a human barometer.
He hasn't really told me about all this.
If you must pee, do it now. There's not
many places to stop on the road.
You're still in love with him.
Check, please.
Not that I blame you.
I hope this isn't a desperate
attempt to keep him in your life.
We're together.
Hey, man.
What's up?
Going green.
Greenage.
- Saddle them up.
- You got it, boss.
I need a sector scan on that cell.
Keep looking for a hook.
What are my dew points doing?
Points up to 70, sir.
I got a lemonade.
We must go. Follow us in the
truck, but stay behind Dusty.
You'll be safe there. I must go with Jo.
Let's move out, people!
Where are we going?
Thanks, I'll drive.
Let's pack it up. Let's go.
It's a wonder of nature baby!
Hey, you guys!
Dr. Melissa Reeves here.
Hello, Donald.
No, you got me in my car.
Oklahoma
Where the wind comes
sweeping down the plain
And the waving wheat
This feeling of inadequacy is coming
from you. Julia doesn't resent you.
We've talked about this before.
She did not marry your penis.
Okay. All right.
She didn't only marry your penis.
So?
So...
Amazing coloring there, isn't it?
Look at the mammatas.
Those tops have got to be
spiking about 40,000 feet.
- It's a good thing.
- It's a very good thing.
You met her at the station?
- I don't want to fight.
- I'm not fighting. I'm talking.
I don't want to fight.
She's nice.
She's not nice?
- I know what you meant.
- You do?
Don't do this.
I'm making civilised conversation here.
You're biting my head off.
Jesus.
Yes, she's very nice.
No, she does not work at the station.
She's a therapist.
Yours?
You couldn't resist it.
I'm not saying you need therapy.
Wait. I need therapy?
I didn't say that.
Why would I need a therapist?
- I don't know.
- You're the doctor.
I don't know...
...inability to finish things.
Maybe rushing into things
you can't quite commit to.
You asked me.
You asked me!
Bullshit! I may have walked out, but at
least I showed up in the first place!
- You never had an idea.
- There's a road thing going on.
You never knew what
being married means...
...like stability and supportiveness
and a house and neat stuff like that!
I'll drive.
Then would you?
Goddamn.
Someone should warn
her about your temper.
She obviously has no idea.
Stay out of it. I know what I'm doing.
What are you doing?
They're getting better at this.
You know what? If you're happy...
Thank you.
I am happy. I'm a happy person.
I'm happy with the way
things are going in my life.
- I'm happy with-with-with-
- Melissa?
I know her name! Yes, with Melissa.
You look happy.
I am!
Shit. Shit!
You going to wrap this up soon?
What?
Are we going to chase this tornado or
do you want to catch the next one?
Shit!
- Is it on the ground?
- I got it.
Easy.
Bear right. It's on an easterly course.
The Weather Service has issued
a tornado warning till 11 a. m.
Dr. Miller?
I think they turned left.
Do it.
We'll intercept. Get ready to set up.
You got it.
- Get further ahead of it.
- I know what I'm doing.
Cut across.
- Get into that field.
- I'll get ahead of it.
Want to drive?
- Would you like to drive?
- I'd love to.
Distances are about 3 miles south-east.
Let's see what she does.
Go in there.
You'll miss it.
Hold on a second.
Lost your nerve?
Tighten your seat belt.
Where are you? We lost visual.
Having fun?
We must get out of this.
Really?
2 miles. Picking up speed.
Sometime this week would be good.
I'm trying.
You mad?
I will be later. Now I'm
trying not to kill us.
Funnel's getting thicker!
It's moving fast! Coming towards you!
It's turning!
- I can't see it.
- You will!
You're too close! It won't work!
Get out!
Oh, shit!
It's too steep.
This was a great idea!
That wasn't so bad. Let's go!
Why can't we spend a
normal day together?
We're in the damage path!
This is crazy! Forget it!
- No, it's going to hit us!
- We can still do this!
There's no time! Come on! Come on!
Grab hold of something!
I know!
What are you doing?!
I want to see it!
Come back!
Come on!
Look out!
Oh, God.
Oh, my God!
It's gone.
Where's my truck?
There it is.
Oh, God!
Are you okay?
You just missed that truck!
Awesome!
That's awesome!
Oh, God, Billy!
Are you okay?
- I'm okay.
- Are you sure?
She just missed the truck.
What happened to you?
Nothing, we're okay. We were safe.
It's trashed.
Hang on.
It's over. It's over. It's all over.
Are you okay?
She's okay.
There is some good news.
It did fly.
What was it like?
It was windy.
Windy.
That's intense.
Move it.
The Auto Club's here.
Maybe we should stop,
see if they need help.
They're fine.
Pay attention to the road.
You're fashionably late again.
Give me a kiss.
Get out of here! Get out of here!
Loser!
Find your own twister!
Losers!
Move on!
Tough luck, you guys!
Let's go.
I'll get them clean.
Let's get Dorothy 2 ready.
You got full coverage on that truck?
Liability only.
It's a pretty truck.
Thank you.
Don't even think about it.
No way.
This is the caboose! This is the
caboose! I'm waiting for orders.
Go ahead.
- It's your truck.
- No, you should.
The battle zone should
be north-east of 81.
The battle zone?
What're we doing?
We're going again.
But back there you almost got killed!
Just a close call.
You're going to cross 15
at Oklahoma 412. 412.
Copy that. Haynes,
what's on the Mesonet?
Winds are continuing to back.
Okay, guys, lets go get it.
Mobile lab.
Is it me, or is the
main updraft shifting?
Upper-level winds are veering.
It might dissipate. Do we have
time to get in front of it?
Rotation is increasing. Shear is
90 knots. 50 outbound, 40 inbound.
We see a very pronounced hook.
Checking for you now.
We're getting south-east
gusts at 40 miles per hour.
Approaching 150 in the funnel.
Storm motion is 225 degrees
out of the south-west.
We're in position. Proceed.
Howdy!
Must admire their spirit.
There's your pal.
What're you doing?
Look at the updraft.
The angle.
It's going to shift course.
You sure?
It's definitely a sidewinder.
It'll move left.
- Is that bad?
- Was there a road?
You're right! Go!
Donald, now's not a good time.
All right, put Julia on, Donny.
Looking very good.
About a 4 miles up, hang a right,
let's deploy and we'll be done.
Shit!
Shit, it's moving away!
Looks like they'll intercept.
You told me this thing was going
to stay on the same heading!
We're close.
I know.
Where does this road take us?
It feels unnatural, but
with Donald's motility...
...you won't have a baby the usual
way, even standing on your head.
She's a reproductive therapist.
Laurence- Damn.
We must get ahead of this storm.
Be right with you.
I can't talk now. I'll call you back.
South. Shifting due south, copy.
We have an F-2, ladies and
gentlemen. Possibly F-3.
Read me? There's very, very large
rope on the ground. Very large.
It looks like it's turning.
The atmosphere is unstable.
Repeat, unstable!
This is Rabbit!
It's heading this way!
This is Sanders.
We are driving due east on a
road we've been on for 6 miles.
We've got an F-3 sitting here
on the ground. A beauty!
Jo, it's Barn Burner!
It won't hang out long!
It's not hanging out.
We got it! We see it!
We're getting slammed in here.
You better hang back.
- Is this thing loaded?
- Yeah, go for it.
Rain bands.
Look at the surf.
Shit, horizontal rain! Hang on!
Jesus, I've never seen
clutter like this.
I don't think anyone has.
Flash frequencies are high.
We're in the core.
We got sisters!
Oh, my God.
Julia, I can't talk now.
- We're under the flanking line.
- I realise that.
We can't attack from the south.
We'll get rolled.
Watch me.
I know you're upset. You just must
breathe. We both got to breathe.
Cow.
I must go, Julia! We got cows!
Another cow!
I think it was the same one.
We got drunkards. We got no path!
Get us out of here!
- I'm trying!
- Floor it!
Look out!
Oh, God! Oh, God!
See that carousel? Did you see?
It was incredible.
Oh, honey-honey-
Did you see that?
It's all right. Come on, it's okay.
No, I'm not okay. This is not okay.
Oh, Christ, I'm sorry.
Honey, I didn't think.
When you used to tell me
that you chased tornados...
...deep down I always
thought it was a metaphor.
It's okay. It's okay.
Three times a lady!
Did you see the inflow jets?
See?! I was in the middle of it!
I'm thinking it might not
be too bad of an idea...
...if we left, because there
was too many tornados there.
Are you kidding? This thing's not over.
We've only seen the start.
You know...
...we're close to Wakita.
Aunt Meg wouldn't mind a pit stop.
We crave sustenance.
Guys, we are not invading my aunt.
Food.
We're absolutely not going.
There's the spot. Just do it.
Great.
Come on, honey.
Come on.
You must meet her, she's great.
Meg, how are you?
- How are you?
- It is so good to see you!
You too.
The other day I told Jo...
...how much I miss you.
You haven't seen my new work.
Oh, honey.
You've seen some action.
You should've seen it.
Boys!
Give me some loving!
In a lightning storm, grab your
ankles and stick your butt up.
It's the safest orifice to get hit.
I'd like to get hit, see what it's like.
Real lemonade. Meg, I'm moving in!
Look out. Make a space.
Look out.
God, you got a lot of beef.
- Where'd you get this beef?
- Did you see my cows?
No.
Cool.
You slaughter them.
Nice. Potatoes.
Grab it now.
Meg's gravy is famous.
It's practically a food group.
Shower's free.
I'm next.
I want that.
How can you watch this garbage?
Pardon me. You must see this.
Like for you to be out
there chasing tornados?
It's a thrill.
Man vs. nature. Battling the elements.
What a weasel.
As a scientist, can you
actually predict tornados now?
No, they're unpredictable...
...as my unfortunate
colleagues found out today.
But we hope to change all that
with a system I have devised.
God, he sucks.
Shut up!
Turn him off.
What a wiener.
He's so in love with himself.
I thought it was a summer thing.
He'll rue the day.
He'll rue the day he came
up against The Extreme.
- Hear, hear.
- Amen, baby.
Bill, I'm talking imminent rue-age.
Imminent rue-age.
I was just wondering, why do
you call Billy "The Extreme"?
'Cause Billy is The Extreme.
Bill's the most out-of-controllest
bastard in the game.
No, I think I came in second.
I've seen him in high gear.
You guys must get new stories.
I'll go clean up.
So...
...we get this one near Daleton.
God!
We're close and Jo's got the VID on it.
She's filming it.
Suddenly, this shitty-looking green
Valiant pulls up right in the way.
She starts yelling and this...
...loser stumbles out of the car.
He's got a bottle of Jack Daniels.
He's naked.
He's butt-naked.
Not naked.
I was not naked!
He's without apparel.
Half-naked.
Naked. So, Jo's yelling at him
to get out of the way, right?
So...
...he just strolls up to the twister...
...and says, "Have a drink!"
And he chucks the bottle
into the twister and...
...it never hits the ground.
Twister caught it, sucked it right up.
Honey, this is a tissue of lies.
There was another Bill...
...an evil Bill...
...and I killed him.
I love him!
That was a good-size twister.
What was that? An F-3?
F-2.
I'm lost again.
It's the Fujita scale. It measures a
tornado's intensity by how much it eats.
Eats?
Destroys.
That encounter we had was
a strong F-2, F-3, maybe.
We'll see F-4's today.
That'd be sweet.
Four is good. Four would
relocate your house efficiently.
Is there an F-5?
What would that be like?
The finger of God.
None of you has seen an F-5?
Just one of us.
Forget it.
Doesn't matter what you do...
...you'll still be beautiful.
You're biased.
Yes, I am.
Sounds like old times.
Yes, it does.
He didn't keep his part of the bargain.
Which part?
To spend his life pining for you
and die miserable and alone.
That so much to ask?
I don't know.
Bill always went his own way,
usually the same way you were going.
Seems like a long time ago.
Not so long, Jo.
He's here, isn't he?
That is so beautiful.
We got one!
F-3, mile outside of Parlaine!
This is for Garfield county,
including the city of Enid.
This storm has developed
in the last 15 minutes.
Doppler radar shows that
this is an intense storm.
Ride with Dusty, okay?
- What's SELS say?
- Big!
Let's go!
Where's Jonas?
- He's in Milston.
-30 miles away.
- Can we beat him?
- I'm working on it.
Thanks for stopping by.
Sorry to eat and run.
It's what you live for.
Good to see you.
It's okay.
Tasty cow, Aunt Meg.
It's for you.
Thank you.
You and me, right?
Sweet.
Nice meeting you.
Likewise. You better run.
Keys.
Please. You're welcome.
Hang on.
We'll go through town.
We'll take Meyers Road past the fire
station, then 132 to the 44 east.
If there's shortcuts, let us know.
Rabbit, time to impress me.
A mile up there's a little detour.
We'll walk in the woods.
It gets bumpy here, folks.
Let's get you wired.
Excuse me.
Okay, you're on.
An ordinary person spends his life...
...avoiding tense situations.
Repo Man spends his life...
...getting into tense
situations, Beltzer!
What do you got?
Turn left here toward that farm.
You sure?
Trust me. Rabbit is good.
Rabbit is wise.
- Mother of God.
- Jesus Christ.
This is a field.
I know. Keep going beyond it,
through that brush.
See that brush right in front of you?
Yes, we see it. What's beyond that?
Beyond what?
The brush! A brick wall,
a bearded lady, what?
It's the highway!
Where's the road?
It should be any moment.
Hello.
Shit.
She's insane.
You're insane.
You trying to kill someone?
Really?
It was nice of you to see 10
people on the road and not stop!
Very good. Let's keep
this channel clear.
Dirt bag.
We have to get off this road.
Don't guess.
I'm not. Make a right turn.
Want to drive?
Just turn!
Do we follow?
We do not.
What's he doing?
I don't know.
Find this road. It's like Bob's road.
Touchdown!
We have touchdown.
Tornado is on the ground.
Listen to this.
It's coming down Route 33.
We're on 33.
What's the path?
It's going about 35 miles an hour.
- Do you see this?
- I can't.
Where is it? Hello.
Where're you looking?
- Where?
- Direction, Rabbit.
North-northeast.
See it?
Got anything?
North-northeast, do you copy?
It's coming right at us.
Axis's gone vertical.
Sucker's really gaining strength.
Do you see it?
No.
We don't have a visual! Repeat!
We don't have a visual! Help us out!
Where is it?
I got it. It's the best
motion I've ever seen.
The base of this fatty's over 1/2 mile.
If you're going east on 7, it's coming
over the hill in a few minutes.
This is the one. I feel it.
It must be there.
Maybe it stalled.
No, I think Rabbit's right.
It's going to show its ugly
face right over that hill.
What do you think?
You going for it?
Time for deployment.
Oh, man. This is the
fun part, sweetheart.
We got hail.
Hail. We got hail.
Pull over.
That's good.
We got a big one!
Upflow, Beltzer! We have upflow.
Copy.
I'm checking it.
I'm checking. She's almost up.
Now, this is it.
I'll get her ready.
You see them?
The red truck went toward the core!
Is he talking about Billy?
Are you okay?!
Yes! Keep going!
Beltzer, we got a view!
I see it!
Okay, I got it!
That's no moon! It's a space station!
We have debris!
They're in the bear cage!
Oh, my God!
Look at this!
Take a peek!
You can really feel it
with a telephoto lens!
What's wrong?
You people are crazy, do you know that?
Are you set up? We're not
leaving till we get this.
And she's the craziest one of them all!
Okay, she's almost ready!
Hold on!
We're almost there! We're almost there!
This is fine!
No, a little closer!
A little closer!
Close enough.
Hurry! Get the tailgate!
You got it?
She's set. Help me get her down.
Hurry!
Let's go!
Damn! We got to go!
We can do it!
- Come on!
- It's stuck.
Look out!
Come on! Hurry!
Where'd it go?
Where is it?
What's going on?
I don't believe this.
What the hell!
What's the Doppler say?
The cone of silence.
Bill, Jo, it's over.
The thing was stable and then it...
It's gone.
- It's backbuilding!
- It's not through yet.
You're right. It's backbuilding.
We got a jumper!
It's backbuilding! Track it!
Yeah, Jo! Data's incomplete!
You guys should get out!
Bill, help! Help me!
We should leave.
- Forget the sensors!
- Help me!
We must get out of here now!
Beltzer'll see if it drops!
It's not going to drop anywhere
near us! It'll drop on us!
We can still do this! Wait!
Go back!
Forget it! Forget it!
Go back! It's not too late!
- Go back!
- Forget it! It's too late!
Help me!
What're you doing?
The pack's wasted! It's over!
What's wrong? We can still do this!
Listen to you! You're obsessed!
You've never seen what it can do!
- I just saw it!
- You've never seen it!
You've never seen it miss this house,
miss that house and come after you.
Christ, Jo, is that
what you think it did?
You don't know.
Why can't you forget it?!
You don't understand.
You'll never know.
When's it going to be enough?
How close do you have to get?!
Talk to me! Jo, things go wrong!
You can't explain it!
You can't predict it!
Killing yourself won't
bring your dad back.
I'm sorry he died.
But it was a long time ago.
You've got to move on.
Stop living in the past and look
at what's right in front of you.
What're you saying?
Me, Jo.
You better come here and look at this.
Velocities are maxed out.
Those two cells converge...
Inbounds and outbounds have doubled.
There have been tornado sightings.
The latest reported just to the
north-east of Canton a few minutes ago.
Wait a second. I've just been handed
this-. This is official now.
A tornado has been reported moving
through Canton a few minutes ago.
Can I have 8 coffees to go, please?
Two coffees.
Long day.
I've been thinking about the sensors.
The way they scattered out
there today on the highway.
I'm starting to wonder...
...if the funnel'll carry them.
Too light?
I don't know. Maybe the
whole thing's too light.
What can we do?
I'm not sure.
This is a very dangerous situation.
If you have loved ones in the
area do not try to help them.
You'll only be a hindrance to them.
Thank you.
Shit. Jesus, it's coming.
It's coming! It's headed right for us!
It's already here.
Everybody, underground!
Honey!
Come on!
Jo, come on!
Get underground!
Take cover, now!
Close the doors!
Doors! Doors!
Come on!
Come back!
Take my hand!
Come on, hurry!
Come on! Get in here! Get in here!
Go, go, go! Come on!
Everyone down in the pit!
Get down!
Everybody down!
Move!
Stay calm!
I got it.
It's okay!
My head.
You're okay.
- It's not okay!
- It'll be over soon!
This is insane!
Stay calm!
This is driving me crazy!
I don't want to do this!
It's okay, honey.
It's going to be okay.
Chewed my lips off wondering
if he was coming back home.
I've never been so
frightened in my life.
Was I on key?
You were.
Wow, that's a wonder.
Look at the truck. It's trashed.
Of course, tornado activity continues.
Reports from Fairview indicate
a drive-in was blown away.
We know there's injuries
and the damage is massive.
Is that what it was like up on the hill?
That? No.
We were lucky.
Those were just downdrafts
and microbursts.
The tornado just sideswiped us.
Which way is it headed?
It's banking north-east.
It looks to hit Wakita.
I'm going. I'm going. Let's go.
We're going!
Get me a route around the storm.
Light up! Let's go!
Wait!
Where's the phone?
- The lines are down.
- I'm going.
Damn it.
I'll drive.
We can jump on the 38 exchange
and cross Highway 132.
Honey, it's Meg. I got to go.
I'm going back.
Good. You'll be safe at the motel.
See you in the morning.
I won't be there.
What?
Why?
What do you mean?
I'm saying good-bye.
You know what?
I can't compete with this.
I don't know where to start.
Don't do this now.
Sooner or later it would have ended.
We both know that.
The funny thing is...
...I'm not that upset.
What does that mean?
We can do it! Come on! Let's move!
I didn't mean it to happen.
Billy, I know.
It's okay.
Come on.
You go ahead.
She needs you.
I hope Aunt Meg's okay.
What about you?
Don't worry about me.
I know my way home.
We can be to Wakita in an hour.
Come on.
Oh, my God.
They had no warning.
Jo, wait!
Wait!
Careful, this house could go any second.
Take a flashlight.
This whole place is ready to go.
Careful.
Did you hear that?
- I heard something.
- Easy.
Careful.
She's down here!
Meg, we're here! We're coming down!
Get this off her.
Hang on.
Don't move.
- Ready?
- Watch your head.
Go.
I got it.
Easy. Are you okay?
No, I'm all right. I'm fine.
Oh, God.
Hurry.
- Let's go.
- Can you walk?
Watch out!
Joey, take my watch.
Go. Careful.
We're coming out!
Get an ambulance!
Get an ambulance! Move it! Now!
Go!
Give me the lamp.
How about steak and eggs?
- How nice you all came over.
- There you go.
Nice and slow.
Easy, easy.
Grab Mose for me! I think
he's a little shaken up.
Don't worry, I'll get him!
Is she okay?
We'll probably keep her overnight.
Forget it.
- I'm all right.
- You're going to the hospital.
Okay, I'll go. But I'm
going to drive myself.
Your car's in a tree around the corner.
It's okay.
The F-4 that hit Wakita has
now moved to the Northeast.
I've just gotten word in that an even
stronger tornado has started to form...
...25 miles south where the two
storms met and combined forces.
Weather Service says this is unusual.
Oh, my God.
Look at this. Here, look at this.
We're talking about winds in
excess of 300 miles an hour.
What're you doing?
I want to see how you are. How is she?
I was worried about you.
- Look at this.
- It's nothing.
He says I have a bump on the
head and maybe a broken wrist.
Let me see that.
There's nothing to see.
It doesn't hurt.
I'm sorry I wasn't there.
Stop blaming yourself.
You got me out of the house.
It's got to stop.
I didn't have any warning.
The sirens went off a few seconds before
it hit. I didn't get downstairs.
I'm sorry.
I was listening to the
radio and... I mean...
You may not want to know,
but it's happening.
N.S.S.L's predicting an F-5.
It's going to happen to someone else.
You go stop it.
I don't know how.
I think you do.
You've been chasing these things
since you were a little kid.
It's what you do.
Go. Do it.
You all right?
I thought you were going with Meg.
What is it?
I know how to make Dorothy fly.
Of course.
I need every aluminium can you can find.
We need cutters and duct tape.
I want to get the last Dorothy on the
back of my truck. Both of them, now.
We're gone!
Are you ready?
We're good.
We're good? Good.
We're very good.
Let's go! Come on!
- You get them done?
- I think so.
Beautiful.
Good?
Great job. Be ready to record.
Ready?
Be careful.
Don't follow too close.
You got it, boss!
We're back in business.
Come on, let's go.
Half a mile more?
Sounds right.
I'll put her in the road.
Won't someone hit it?
Nobody'll be there.
Hurry!
Let's go.
Okay, that's good!
- Got it?
- Let's go!
You in position?
Ready for contact!
This is it.
It'll work.
Just another minute.
We're ready!
Come on, come on, take her!
Too light.
No, it's not.
- We're losing it.
- No, she can still fly.
Get in!
Oh, my God!
Get us off this thing!
Hurry!
What is that?
This is not good!
Hurry!
Go!
Son-of-a-bitch!
Jo, Bill, you all right?
Can you guys hear me?
We're okay.
Jo, Bill, did you see that explosion?
We saw it.
This monster's moving north-east on 80!
Copy?!
This is it.
Last one.
Last time.
Mobile lab to Mobile One.
Ground speed is increasing.
The base is a mile wide.
We can't see it anymore.
What's your location?
I am right alongside her!
She's beautiful!
We're ready to play, so pull
back and prepare to monitor.
They had to be somewhere.
Path is stable, copy that.
Men...
...this is it.
Stay sharp back there.
They have position.
They could make it.
Not unless they anchor the pack.
Jonas, can you hear me?
Not now.
Jonas, listen to me.
The pack is too light.
The twister'll toss it. Anchor it.
Sharing valuable information, Jo.
I'll consider that. Thanks.
Listen to me!
What?
Can you see them?
Jonas, what's your position?
Howdy, Bill.
We're heading north-east, parallel...
...about to pull off
ahead of it on the left.
Hang back a minute. We got
a good view from back here.
She could shift or track and if
she does, she'll come right at you.
Let's do that. He'd never
put us in harm's way.
When I want your opinion, I'll give it.
Shut up, put your foot on
the gas, and stay on course.
It's unbelievable!
What's wrong?
The base is so huge!
It must be at least a mile wide!
Do you copy?
Listen to me!
Get off this frequency!
She's shifting.
Oh, my God.
Jonas, I'm telling you!
Eddie, I know you can hear me!
Get out!
Look out!
Damn!
Stupid!
We tried.
We can do nothing.
- Yes, we can.
- Ground speed is increasing.
Get ahead of it quickly,
or she'll bury you.
We have debris!
Right!
Left!
- What now?
- I have no idea.
You still with us?
Oh, my God.
I think we're going in.
Maybe we should get off this road.
You may be right.
Are you okay?
You set up?
- We're set. You going in?
- We are.
- You ready?
- I'm on it.
Be careful.
She's up.
Where are they?
Doppler tracking is great!
Wind speed increasing!
I've never seen anything like this.
They're going to punch the core.
Ready?
Let me set the cruise control.
We're good.
On three?
On three.
Go!
Ready?
Ready.
One!
Two!
Three!
Go...
...go...
...go! Go!
Dorothy's flying!
She's flying!
Look!
We're in!
I don't believe it! We're in!
We'll be very popular!
- She's flying!
- Look at that!
It's beautiful. It's working.
It's Christmas time.
We're inside! It's working!
- Dorothy did it!
- I'm getting readings!
This is it! We did it, man!
We just made history.
You guys, it's about to shift north-east.
You should get out of there!
Do you copy?
Run!
The barn! Come on!
Look out!
Here!
Go! Hurry!
To the barn!
Stay down!
My God! Who are these people?
I don't think so.
Quick!
Oh, my God!
Come on!
Run for it!
Get down!
Come on!
Here!
These pipes go down at least 30 feet.
We anchor to it, we may have a chance!
No good!
This!
Get in!
Hold on!
Hang on!
- You all right?
- Are you?
Look at that.
It didn't take the house.
We did it.
Yeah, we did.
Dorothy really flew.
It was a good idea.
We've got so much to do.
I'll get grant approval
for a warning system.
We need a bigger lab.
You must start analysing data.
I do?
We must generate models of the
data, and I must run the lab.
You do the analysis, I'll run the lab.
You're running the lab?
I don't think so.
Do you always have to
do things the hard way?
We got it, guys! The sensors worked!
The computers went crazy! We got data!
It's the biggest twister on record!
Check out that sky.
You know what?
I think we've seen enough.