Created and Encoded by --  Bokutox -- of  www.YIFY-TORRENTS.com. The Best 720p/1080p/3d movies with the lowest file size on the internet.
Two decades had passed
since the creation of both species.
The war had begun.
Viktor increased his army,
creating a legion of vampires...
...to protect them
from the very first clan of werewolves:
a vicious and infectious breed unable
to take human form ever again.
Until he was born.
Lucian.
And although every fiber of Viktor's
soul warned him to slay this child...
...he did not.
Over the years, this child grew.
He possessed a strength and focus
that the ones before him did not.
What do you think, Sonja?
Shall we make more?
Of him?
Like him.
Lucian will always be
the first of the breed...
...the first of the Lycans.
Viktor would use Lucian's
infectious blood to his benefit...
...taking advantage
of the child's thirst...
...pitting it against him as he
was forced to feed on humans...
...Viktor's slaves.
-Get in there.
-In there.
Instead, he created a new race
of immortals:
Lycans.
Werewolf, but also human.
Unlike the others,
this new breed could be harnessed...
...enslaved to guard them
in the daylight hours of their masters.
Or so Viktor thought...
...so very long ago.
The nobles are upset, my Iord.
WiIliam's pestilence
has not been checked.
-Werewolves have killed their slaves.
-Humans upset.
Tannis, please take a note
of what pain that brings me.
Yet their Iost slaves
means our lost silver.
Enough. Have I not
increased our holdings tenfold...
...since Marcus and AmeIia
took their sleep?
We wiIl deal with the wolves
as we aIways have.
-Come on!
-Come on, quickly!
Fire!
Close that breach.
Have you nothing better to do,
blacksmith...
than play with weapons of war?
At least make yourself useful.
A little gratitude, Sonja,
to the one who saved your Iife.
I needed no saving.
Tell me, Lucian.
Does it burden your heart
to kill your own kind?
Not at all.
They're mindless beasts, my lord.
-No brethren of mine.
-Really?
Father.
You are a credit to your race.
Do you know how to remain so?
Keep your eyes on the ground.
Get rid of that.
You were sorely missed at council.
There are other demands on my time,
as you know.
I see. I hope you enjoyed
your littIe moonIit ride.
I was out patrolling.
You were disobeying.
I toId you to stay within these walls.
You risk too much
for a father to ignore.
You wiIl leave the wolves
to the Death Dealers.
And why, Father,
is my risk any greater than theirs?
They are not my daughters...
...and they are not council members.
You are.
And one day, you will become
an elder, your birthright.
Sonja, you are well thought of
at council...
...but that is a precarious thing.
They grow tired
of your games and your absences.
Dangers of the forest are no greater
than those of the council chamber.
You wiIl learn the dance of politics,
to be ruthless and cunning.
And above all,
you wiIl be Ioyal to your family.
To me.
After aIl,
without the loyalty between us...
...we are no better
than the beasts at our door.
Put your back into it.
Pick that up.
Move it, you scum.
More spin.
Get up.
Lycan.
No rest, dog.
Enough.
You dare raise your hand to me?
-I said, that's enough.
-So says the master's dog?
You wiIl not always be his favorite,
and when you fall...
...l will be there.
Let us hope so.
What are you looking at?
Get back to work now!
Get back to work!
Back to work.
The matter before the council
is simple.
We are under attack.
Six times in haIf as many weeks...
...William's kind
have reached our very walls.
What mayhem would foIlow
ifjust one of them got through?
Your fear, Coloman, is misplaced.
Are we not protected
by an army of immortals?
Superbly, my lord.
However, the nobles are not,
and as I have pointed out...
...they are the grass
on which we graze.
If we cannot protect our humans,
it makes us look weak.
And how would you
project strength?
As our Death Dealers
patrol the night...
...so our daylight guards
can patrol the day.
Lycans patrol outside the walls?
Have you lost your mind?
They are born of beasts...
...and the savagery of this
despicable fact cannot be bred away.
I think your fear of this idea
is misplaced.
We can create
a privileged class of Lycans.
Greater rations, finer quarters and put
them under the hand of one we trust.
Perhaps your pet, Lucian.
The one who saved
your daughter's life today.
In fact, I think we shouId
hear her thoughts on this matter.
She seems
to have been needed elsewhere.
Find her.
I wilI take your suggestion
under advisement.
Thank you, my Iord.
It would be gratifying
to be able to reassure the nobles...
...when they arrive tomorrow
that we have their interests at heart.
-Move it!
Go on, slowpoke.
Over there. There.
-Move it!
-Don't go slow. Keep going.
Move it along!
My Iady?
Is it true what you told my father...
...that you feel nothing
when you kill them?
They're just animaIs...
...incapable of thought or feeIing...
...so why should l feel anything
for them?
Sonja, if l were to leave from here,
would you come with me?
Leave?
Do not say that.
Do not even think it.
They would hunt you down...
-...and mark you like aIl the others.
-Not if I could remove this.
Look.
I made it.
This will be my freedom.
Lucian, promise me
you won't use it.
-Please.
-Is that your answer, then?
You wiIl not come.
So you want me
to stay here for you?
-Like this, like an animaI?
-Lucian.
Vampire and Lycan,
we are both children of Corvinus...
...yet my family are slaves.
I wilI use this key...
...and I will leave this place...
...but l can never be without you now.
-Any news of my daughter?
-She's most defiant.
She refuses to see me.
-Will not answer her door.
-Why are the young so blind?
She risks her seat on the council,
and for what?
I cannot imagine.
We must prepare, my lord.
Human nobles are on their way.
It's sharp.
No wolf will stand before it.
Ready the horses.
Let someone else go.
-Why?
-Last night, after I Ieft you--
Just let someone else go.
In case it had escaped your notice,
blacksmith...
...l am quite capable
of looking after myself.
And besides...
...you can watch over me
from the wall.
Get your back to the rear.
Lady Sonja, your father
has ordered you to stay behind.
I intend to see our guests
safeIy through the gate.
-Gate master.
-This is not a request.
Your father is ruler of the coven.
So he keeps reminding me.
Get back!
Careful, bIacksmith...
...lest your eyes betray your secret.
Steady. Steady.
Shut it, my child. Shut it.
Form up!
No.
Get your men out there now!
Down, boy. Your leash is too tight.
-Step away.
-There's too many of them.
They'll be massacred.
Stop him!
Ride out. Ride out.
Easy.
Dimitri.
Lucian!
Sonja!
Lucian, no.
No, stop!
He did it to save me.
Am I not master of this house?
You know you are forbidden
to remove your shackle.
Yes.
Yet you break my Iaw
after I gave you your life.
Your days of plush living
are over, slave.
Father, leave him be.
-I told you--
-HoId your tongue!
You have defied me
for the last time.
Get her out of here.
Burn the bodies.
Burn them aIl.
For removing the colIar...
...30 lashes.
You have stung me, Lycan,
with your betrayal.
You were like a son to me.
I gave you your life.
You gave me chains.
I would have thought, after all
these years, you would have known...
...you cannot have one
without the other.
Do it.
I toId you l'd be there when you fell.
-What?
-Stop this.
-He is one of our protectors.
-They are but beasts.
-This could stir up the others.
-Let them. Do you fear them?
It will be worse
if we do not punish them.
Do you see now, Coloman?
You would trust them...
...outside the walls?
We cannot even trust them inside.
By my count, that's 21 .
Continue.
Oh, what a terribIe sound.
Bloody stink.
Stay away from him,
or they'll punish you too.
Your concern for Lucian
was most touching.
A sIave.
He had just saved my life.
Was it not you who told me
to show a little gratitude?
And yourself?
Gratitude for the one
who saved your daughter?
I am awash with it.
That he lives shows the breadth
of my magnanimity.
Were it other circumstances...
...l would have had him fed
in pieces to his own kind.
But his punishment is now over.
-He will be freed.
-Freed?
Your judgment is clouded, Sonja.
We do not keep order
with sentiment.
Lucian was forbidden to remove
his collar and yet he did so...
...for however fine a reason.
He will remain in prison...
...a cautionary tale.
Janosh and the other nobles
will soon arrive.
Your presence is expected.
I saw what you did out there.
Very brave...
...for a human.
Have you come
across them before?
Only in stories.
Were you not afraid of them?
Yes...
...but l wanted to live.
Are you afraid of me?
-Yes.
-Well, do not be.
I wilI not bite...
...much.
-You are like them?
-No.
A Lycan, yes, but not like them.
Those you fought with tonight
were animaIs, the spawn of William.
Purebloods, if you will.
No trace of human Ieft.
Savage, mindless beasts.
-As it has been told.
-But I saw you.
They obeyed you.
Yes.
Yes, they did.
Hey.
-Oh, you should not be here.
-I had to.
My Iove, I'm sorry.
-Your back.
-No, no, I'm all right.
This is my fault. If
I had not gone out--
Then you would not be who you are.
This is not your fauIt.
I cannot remain here.
I have to leave this place.
My father will be watching you more.
Your Death DeaIers,
are there none you can trust?
Their loyalty to my father
is greater than their loyalty to me.
Tannis.
-Tannis cannot be trusted.
-No, he knows about us.
-How?
-I have no idea.
If he still has not told your father,
he wants something.
Sonja, find out what it is.
Bring them in.
Janosh.
Do you not own
the largest silver mine in these lands?
It has been overrun, my lord.
Our workers infected...
...turned to beasts.
Most unfortunate...
...and costIy.
I think half the rights to your mine...
...should cover
the expense of our assistance.
What assistance?
We have alI seen
the fires on the way here.
We have learned of the deaths
of Baron Covasha and his family.
The wolves are at your door as well.
So why should I pay tribute...
...when you cannot
so much as protect your own house?
You have alI but
bled me dry already.
We have alI heard the stories.
Look into his eyes. They are true.
This place is cursed.
They are no more human...
...than the devils
that invade our lands.
If devils you caIl us, rest assured,
better the devil you know.
-Unhand me.
-Certainly.
Would anyone else
like to be heard?
-Toss it here.
-Bring food to these filthy mongreIs.
-Here you go.
-Eat it up like dogs.
Like dogs.
We are not animals.
Is this what you want, to be their
entertainment, their playthings?
Their pets.
Cowering beneath the whip...
...and then fighting
amongst ourselves.
Is this what you want?
I have lived
by their rules my entire life.
I've protected them...
...envied them.
And for what?
To be treated like an animal.
We are not animals!
We do have a choice.
We can choose
to be more than this.
We can be slaves...
...or we can be Lycans!
Morning is upon us, my chiId.
It's time we left
this wretched night behind.
-Gladly.
-There are difficult decisions ahead.
-I would like your help with one.
-Of course, Father.
With Lucian gone...
...we must promote
another Lycan in his place.
Gone?
Coloman thinks
he will stir the others.
We must remove him.
That will be difficult.
He has been with us so long.
Perhaps Gyorg.
Or Thrasos.
They would be...
...trustworthy.
Excellent suggestions.
I wilI consider them strongly.
You, my child, are the
most precious thing in my heart.
What have you told my father?
-What have you told him?
-Nothing.
-Why?
-Why what?
Why have you told him nothing?
Would your father weIcome
the man who brought him news...
...that his
beloved daughter was consorting...
...with a Lycan?
He isn't well known for his gratitude.
And I am not yet in a position
to use this for my benefit.
What sort of benefit?
There are 1 2 council seats.
And we don't die often.
Sadly, no.
So, what if I gave up my seat
at council?
Simply left it to you?
Why would you do that?
Can you keep a secret?
I wilI need something in return.
Two minutes.
Any longer is too risky.
I'm sorry. There was no other way.
So Tannis?
You were right. He will help us
in exchange for a seat on the council.
-Your father knows nothing?
-I'm sure of it.
-Sonja, this can work.
-Lucian, it has to.
Some will come with me.
-Sabas and Xristo, Raze.
-My love--
-I'm certain I can--
-Lucian, there is no time.
Father will have you killed tomorrow,
after the humans are turned.
You must leave at sunrise.
-And you?
-The important thing is you stay alive.
Best chance you have is when
Viktor and the Death Dealers sleep.
I wilI be
at my father's side when you go.
Hurry.
If this works, I'll meet you
in three days, after sunset.
There's a clearing by the river.
I'll meet you there.
-And if it doesn't?
-I will meet you at the clearing.
Face the waIl.
-Get out.
-You animals.
You. Get back.
Be brave, human.
You know what your problem is?
You don't understand
the natural order of things.
Things change.
Be ready when they do.
Consider it a parting gift.
Wait.
Do you not realize
this is a gift I am giving you?
It's a curse.
-What have they done to us?
-You'Il find out soon enough.
They turned us into-- Like you?
Yes.
Why?
He wants to use you
for his own protection.
I wilI die first.
Well, that may not happen.
The time has come.
At sunrise, l leave this place.
Anyone willing
to take the risk may follow me.
There is a new life waiting
beyond these walls, my friend...
...and you can be a part of it,
one of us...
...or stay and serve them.
The guards are coming.
New dogs today.
Let's see how they look.
You've come too Iate.
He's already gone.
Are you with me?
Sabas, Xristo, free the others.
The rest of you with me.
Freedom is yours.
Move!
This way.
Down here.
All right, move. Run, run, run.
Keep moving.
Keep moving. Keep moving.
Keep going. Move.
Fire.
Raze.
There is nothing you can do.
I wilI come back. l promise you.
No!
My Iord.
My Iord, Lucian is escaping.
Forest, go. Go!
My Iord.
Move here. Move it.
-You, get in there.
-Move.
-Are all these accounted for?
-Each and every one.
Tannis.
Come on. Move.
Yes, my lord?
Where is the key
I gave you for this?
-I locked it in the armory myself.
-How, then, is it open?
I have no idea.
I think I have.
-Kill him.
-No.
Please.
Check the armory.
There has to be an explanation.
Show me.
-I've never been outside the walls.
-Enjoy it while you can, Xristo.
Soon enough we're gonna
have to fight our way back in.
We didn't all make it, and I won't
leave our brothers to rot back there.
We humiliated Viktor.
It is they who will pay the cost.
But we were lucky
to make it out alive.
And there's but a handful of us.
We have no weapons.
True, for now.
The noble who brought you,
can you lead us to his estate?
-Yes.
-Good. Come on. Come on.
It has to be here.
I put it here.
Here.
He must have made another one.
I never doubted you.
Now, I have no wish to remove
one shackle from around your necks...
...only to repIace it
with one of my own.
You have a choice.
You can run and hide...
...or you can stay and fight.
Any man who fights with me
shall have his freedom...
...and, if he wishes it...
...immortality.
Pick up your weapons.
Together we're strong.
There are other estates
to the west of here.
I want you to go there.
See how many will join us.
I wilI meet you back here
in two days' time.
-Put it over there.
-Over here.
Father.
Did I startle you? I'm sorry.
No.
You did not.
It occurs to me...
...that l have been thoughtless.
So deep have I been in my own
anguish at Lucian's betrayal...
...l gave no thought...
...to your feelings.
My feelings?
They worm their way into our Iives...
...and we forget the travesty
of their birth.
I myself had tenderness
towards Lucian.
He could have been anything.
A Death Dealer, perhaps.
Yes.
Perhaps.
But he was not as we are...
...was he?
Did you help him escape?
Help him?
Of course not.
Are you lying to me?
There are many things
that I have done against your wiIl...
...but he is a Lycan.
I'm sorry, my dear...
...but you leave me no choice.
Father, please--
I wanted to believe your lies
though I knew it could not be true.
Not my own daughter.
How could you?
Father...
...l love him.
You have betrayed me!
To be with an animal!
I loved you more than anything!
She does not leave this room!
No. You're under orders to wait.
Here.
This rate, we'll have enough men
by the end of the week.
-Has there been any sign of Sonja?
-Nothing.
She shouId have been here by now.
With respect, Lucian, l do not see
the wisdom in waiting for her.
She's not one of us.
Have you forgotten
she is the one who set us free?
But she is a vampire.
If she has deceived you,
she could lead them here.
Death Dealers
will undoubtedly be on the hunt...
...and they will eventually find us,
but not by her doing.
I trust Sonja with my life, and as Iong
as l'm in command, so shaIl you.
Told you not to say anything.
Lucian has sacked two estates
in Brashov, my lord, and made off...
...with the contents of their armories.
The slaves have joined his ranks.
Freedom is as much a disease
as William's pestilence.
-You need to bring your pet back.
-Thank you, CoIoman.
The obvious escaped me.
I do not need to lift a finger.
Lucian will return of his own free wiIl.
I have something he wants.
My Iady.
-Luka. What is it? Where is she?
-Sonja has been arrested.
He knows about the two of you.
He will kill her.
I thought you should know.
Nothing yet, my lord.
-It is a trap. You know that.
-I will not let her die aIone.
They followed you here.
If you go, we will lose them.
Let me tell you a secret.
They thought they followed me.
What they followed is the idea of being
free. That's what brought them here.
Now, you can hold them together until
I get back, and lead them if l do not.
-Are you all right?
-Yes.
But Lucian, you were free.
Not without you.
We have to go now.
My Iord...
...your daughter has escaped.
Of course she has.
This way.
-That one.
-Yes, sir.
Now.
How dare you
raise your hand to me?
-I do not want this.
-I am your father.
-Do you think you can defeat me?
-I don't want to defeat you.
Killing me
won't save your precious Lycan.
Please call off your men,
for the sake of your grandchild.
A miracle, Father.
A union of the bloodlines.
I curse the day your mother gave
her Iife to bring you into this world.
That thing inside you...
...is a monstrosity.
Sonja!
This is over.
Remove him.
Do you understand
what you have done?
This night was not about you.
It was about him.
I could have given Lucian
to the council.
They need never have known
of your indiscretion, but after this...
...never.
No.
If l had not left,
none of this would have happened.
Then you would not be who you are.
You were right.
No one should live a life Iike this.
Others are free because of you.
Things are forever changed
because of what you have done.
-But I have failed you.
-No.
Lucian, my love...
...you have not failed me.
The choices I made
have led me here.
Not you.
You said yourself there are risks
that you were willing to take for me...
...as was l for you.
For us.
Open the door.
-No.
-Get up.
-No. No.
-Come on. Come on.
No. I'll kill you.
All of you!
The accused has committed
high treason against the coven.
She has consorted with animals.
She has abetted in their escape.
I have saved this coven
many times over.
You have killed your own kind.
And you've commingled
bloodlines...
...resuIting in the thing
germinating within you.
Your past gIory does not excuse
your present guilt...
...nor does your station
as a council member.
The punishment for these crimes
is death.
How vote you?
Aye.
-Aye.
She's your daughter.
Aye.
Take her to the chamber.
No, you-- You cannot do this.
My Iady, come with us.
-Come quietly, pIease.
-Viktor.
Viktor. No!
No, Viktor!
No.
Lucian.
No, Sonja.
Don't. Just look at me.
Keep your eyes on me, Sonja.
Look at me!
I love you.
As I love you.
Your face will not be here
when this is over, wiIl it?
Goodbye, my love.
No.
No!
Sonja!
-Fetch my knives.
-Yes, my Iord.
My Iord.
Go. Go. Quickly. Go.
Now go free the others. Go!
Follow me.
-Do you want your revenge?
-Yeah.
It is out there. Now go.
We have greater concerns
than your precious scrolls.
Go to the elders, now!
Kill the dogs!
Viktor.
You defiled my daughter.
-I loved her!
-You killed her!
I should have crushed you
under my heel the day you were born.
Yes, you should have...
...but you didn't.
Lucian!
Lucian.
It is finished.
No.
This is just the beginning.
But let me tell you a little something
about your beloved dark father.
He's the one who killed your family.
Not the Lycans.
But when he got to you...
...he just couldn't bear the thought
of draining you dry.
You, who reminded him so much
of his precious Sonja...
...the daughter
he condemned to death.