Created and Encoded by --  Bokutox -- of  www.YIFY-TORRENTS.com. The Best 720p/1080p/3d movies with the lowest file size on the internet.
The war had all but ground
to a halt in the blink of an eye.
Lucian, the most feared
and ruthless leader ever
to rule the Lycan clan
had finally been killed.
The Lycan horde
scattered to the wind
in a single evening
of flame and retribution.
Victory, it seemed,
was in our grasp,
the very birthright
of the Vampires.
Nearly six centuries had
passed since that night.
Yet the ancient feud proved unwilling
to follow Lucian to the grave.
Though Lycans were
fewer in number,
the war itself had become
more perilous
for the moon no longer
held her sway.
Older, more powerful Lycans
were now able to change at will.
The weapons had evolved,
but our orders remained the same:
Hunt them down and kill them off,
one by one.
A most successful campaign.
Perhaps too successful.
For those like me, a Death Dealer,
this signaled the end of an era.
Like the weapons
of the previous century,
we too would become obsolete.
Pity, because I lived for it.
Hey!
Bloods!
It's all right. It's all right.
You're gonna be okay.
You're acting like a pack
of rabid dogs!
And that, gentlemen,
simply will not do.
Not if you expect to defeat
the Vampires on their own ground.
Not if you expect to survive at all.
Pierce! Taylor!
Put some clothes on, will you?
We have a serious problem.
I'll have to run a few tests.
It's definitely an irradiated fluid
of some sort.
Ultraviolet ammunition.
Daylight, harnessed as a weapon.
You expect me to believe
that a mangy animal
came up with a bullet specifically
engineered to kill Vampires?
No, I'm betting it's military.
Something they stole.
Some sort of high-tech tracer round.
I don't care where
they got these things.
Rigel is dead, and Nathaniel
could still be out there.
We should gather the Death Dealers
and go back down there in force.
Absolutely not. Not now.
Not for a random incursion.
The Awakening is a few days off,
and this house is in unrest as it is.
Random? They opened fire on us
in full view of the public.
And from the commotion I heard
down in that tunnel-
You said yourself
you actually didn't see anything.
Look, I know what I heard,
and I know what my gut tells me,
and I am telling you there could be
dozens of Lycans down there.
Who knows, maybe more.
Hundreds.
We've hunted them
to the brink of extinction.
Kraven's right, Selene.
There's not been a den
of that magnitude for centuries,
not since the days of Lucian.
I know that, Kahn.
But I'd rather have you prove
me wrong by checking it out.
Very well,
have your men tighten things up.
I'll have Soren assemble
a search team.
No, I want to lead the team myself.
Absolutely not!
Soren will handle it.
Hundreds, really?
Viktor would believe me.
I'd never dream
of treating you like that.
Of course you wouldn't.
Now run along and make sure she's dressed
and ready for the arrival of her guests.
It's a waste of time, you know.
What is?
Well, I seriously doubt Viktor would
want you freezing to death in here,
staring at his tomb for hours on end.
No, he'd want the Death Dealers out there
right now, scouring every inch of the city.
Kraven. I'll never understand
why Viktor left him in charge.
He's a bureaucrat,
not a warrior.
Come on, we need to get you ready.
For what?
The party.
Amelia's envoy will be here
any minute.
Oh, yes.
You should definitely wear this one.
It's perfect.
They were after you.
He's attractive.
For a human.
Who's attractive?
You know I was planning to have you
at my side this evening.
Take Erika.
She's dying to be at your side.
If you ask me, you take this warrior
business far too seriously.
You can't undo the past,
no matter how many you kill.
And besides...
what's the point
in being immortal
if you deny yourself
the simple pleasures in life?
Do you see this human?
What of him?
I can't be positive,
but I'm beginning to think the Lycans-
Blast.
Put on something elegant
and be quick about it.
Kraven, I'm serious.
I think they were following him.
Other than food,
why would Lycans stalk a human?
Any progress?
Let's find out.
Negative.
You heading home?
Yeah, Nicholas gave me
a couple hours off.
By the way...
he said you did a terrific job
tonight with the surgery.
Yeah.
Take it easy.
We were ambushed.
Death Dealers, three of them.
And the candidate?
We lost him.
You lost him.
Look at this mess.
Ag rounds. High content.
Prevented him from
making the change.
No use in digging out the rest.
Silver's penetrated his organs.
Regeneration's impossible
at this point.
Let's take these out.
Relax.
The Vampires didn't realize
you were following a human.
Did they, Raze?
No.
I mean...
I don't think so.
You don't think, or you don't know?
I'm not sure.
Negative.
I really must have a look
at this Michael.
Must I do everything myself?
Our noble houses may be
separated by a great ocean,
but we are equally committed
to the survival of the bloodlines.
And when Amelia arrives
to awaken Marcus
in just two days' time,
we shall once again
be united as a single coven!
We want to thank our hosts
for their generous hospitality.
He comes in, he does his job,
and then he goes home.
Other than that,
I really don't know what to tell you.
Interns pretty much work
around the clock.
We don't have much of a life.
You know where we can find him?
No. Um...
You can try him at home,
or you'll have to wait till he gets back.
He's not in some kind of trouble,
is he?
This is Michael. I'm not in right now.
Please leave a message.
Michael, it's Adam. The police were
just in the hospital looking for you.
They were convinced you were
involved with a shootout.
I told them there's no way you'd be
involved with something like that,
but they're looking for you.
Right now.
Why are they after you?
Shit!
Hello, Michael.
What the fuck is going on?
Stop the car.
Stop the car!
Back off!
Okay.
All right.
But you've lost a lot of blood.
If you don't stop the car,
you're gonna get us both killed.
I'm not screwing around!
Neither am I.
Now shut up and hold on.
I'll be fine.
Shit!
A second escape. Impressive.
Perhaps Raze wasn't
overstating matters.
Raze didn't bring back this.
If Michael is indeed The Carrier,
the Vampires could-
Relax, old friend.
I've tasted his flesh.
Just two days till full moon.
Soon, he will be a Lycan.
Soon, he will come looking for us.
It's a shame we don't have more.
Positive.
Lay still. Your skull's
taken a good knock.
You've been unconscious
for a while.
Do you have any idea
why those men were after you?
Where am I?
You're safe.
I'm Selene.
So for once,
the rumors were true.
The whole house has been absolutely
buzzing about your new pet.
You're going to try to turn him,
aren't you?
Of course not.
So why did you bring him here?
He saved my life.
Why are you here?
Kraven sent me.
He wants to see you. Now.
This is completely unacceptable!
You go against my orders and spend
the night away from the mansion
with a human? A human you've
since brought back to my house.
As far as I'm concerned,
this is still Viktor's house.
Look, I don't want to argue.
I just you to understand that Michael is
somehow important to the Lycans-
Oh, so now it's "Michael"!
Kraven, would you just hear me out?
It's just beyond me why you're so
obsessed over this ridiculous theory.
Lucian wouldn't be
the slightest bit interested in a human,
Michael or otherwise.
Wait a minute.
You're infatuated with him,
aren't you?
Now, that's a ridiculous theory.
Is it?
Leave us!
I sure hope you never get
pissed off with me.
Hold on.
Check this out.
Go ahead. Squeeze off a few.
Eject the mag.
You've copied the Lycan rounds.
Silver nitrate.
A lethal dose.
They won't dig these out,
like they do with our usual rounds.
Straight into the bloodstream.
Ain't nothing to dig out.
Tell me, Kahn.
Do you believe Lucian died
the way they say he did?
Kraven been telling
war stories again, is he?
That's my point.
It's nothing but an ancient story.
His story.
There's not a shred of proof
he killed Lucian, only his word.
I've never underestimated
Kraven's lust for advancement,
but Viktor believed him,
and that's all that matters.
Now, where you going
with this anyway?
Nowhere.
Engaging Death Dealers in public
and chasing after some human
was not what I had in mind.
You were told to set up shop
and lay low!
Calm yourself, Kraven!
The human doesn't concern you.
And besides, I've laid low
for quite long enough.
Just keep your men at bay, Lucian.
At least for the time being.
Don't force me to regret
our arrangement.
You just concentrate on your part.
Remember, I've bled for you
once already.
Without me, you'd have nothing.
You'd be nothing.
Of the scores of brave souls
who entered Lucian's fortress
a single Vampire survived:
Kraven,
who was richly rewarded
for not only setting the great blaze,
but for returning with evidence
of the Lycan master's demise,
the branded skin,
cut from Lucian's very arm.
I've been looking for you everywhere.
Not now.
He's been bitten.
Your human,
he's been marked by a Lycan.
Did Kraven put you up to this?
No.
I saw the wound with my own eyes,
I swear it.
But what about the Covenant?
You know it's forbidden!
And ever since he bit me,
I've been-
I've been having these hallucinations
and... And these delusions.
All I know is, it feels like
my skull is splitting in half.
Okay, so a full-grown man bit you?
Jesus.
Are you sure this wasn't a dog?
I said, it was a man.
It was a man. Okay. Okay.
Okay, I got it.
He was after me.
And that woman from the subway-
What woman?
Haven't you been listening to me?
She took me hostage!
All right. Just- Please.
I'll help you get this all sorted out,
all right? I'll be right back.
Let go, Michael.
Let go.
Just calm down, okay?
I'm gonna be back in a minute.
That's a promise. All right?
All right.
Hey!
Please forgive me...
but I desperately need
your guidance.
Kahn wants to see you.
To my knowledge,
an Awakening has never been
attempted by one such as myself.
The elders hold the power to organize
their memories and thoughts
into a single, cohesive vision,
a detailed record of their reign.
I can only hope Viktor
will hear my plea.
Please forgive me,
but I desperately need your guidance.
I apologize for breaking the chain and
awakening you ahead of schedule,
but I fear we may all be
in grave danger.
Especially you, my lord,
if left in your weakened state.
For I believe that Lucian
is alive and well.
Here. Now. In this very city,
preparing to hit us
during the Awakening ceremony.
Even more disturbing...
is that if I'm correct...
it would mean that Kraven
is in league with him.
What's so pressing?
Take a look.
Selene!
I want to speak with Selene!
Is that Michael?
Is it Michael?
What the hell is going on?
What's happening to me?
I'm coming out.
If you go to him, you'll never
be welcome in this house again.
Now that Viktor's awake, we'll see
what he has to say about that.
Get in.
Look, I warned her. I warned
her, but she didn't listen.
She never listens.
I should've told you sooner.
Told me what?
Her human, Michael...
he's not a human at all.
He's a Lycan.
What?!
What's this ruckus?
You can never come here again.
They'll kill you. Do you understand?
Why? Who are you people?
Leave us.
Whether you like it or not,
you're in the middle of a war
that's been raging
for the better part of 1000 years.
A blood feud between
Vampires and Lycans.
Werewolves.
Consider yourself lucky.
Most humans die within an hour
of being bitten by an immortal.
The viruses we transmit
are deadly.
And if you bit me, what,
I'd become a Vampire instead?
No, you'd die.
No one's ever survived
a bite from both species.
By rights, I'd stop the car
and kill you myself-
Then why are you helping me?
I'm not!
I track down and kill your kind.
My only interest is finding out
why Lucian wants you so badly.
Do you know why I've
been awakened, servant?
No, my lord.
But I'll soon find out.
You mean when you find her.
Yes, my lord.
You must let her come to me.
We have much to discuss,
Selene and I.
She has shown me
a great many disturbing things.
Things that will be dealt with
soon enough.
This coven has grown weak,
decadent.
Perhaps I should have left someone
else in charge of my affairs.
Still...
her memories...
are chaotic.
There's no sense of time.
Please, my lord,
let me summon assistance.
You're in need of rest.
I've rested enough.
What you will do
is summon Marcus.
But he still slumbers, my lord.
Amelia and the Council members
are arriving tomorrow night
to awaken Marcus.
Not you, my lord.
You've been awakened
a full century ahead of schedule.
That bitch has betrayed me.
Now he knows everything
she's been obsessing about.
Wait.
Are you to be trusted?
Of course.
Meet me in my quarters
in 20 minutes.
It's time I filled you in
on a few things.
I'm seeing these
things, these hallucinations.
They're not hallucinations,
they're memories.
You've been bitten. His memories
have been passed to you.
This is one of the places we use
for interrogations. It should be safe.
Ziodex Industries.
We own it.
First there was synthetic plasma,
now this.
Once it's approved,
it should be our newest cash crop.
It's cloned blood.
What are these for?
Lycans are allergic to silver.
If we don't get our bullets out quickly,
they die during questioning.
What do you do with them after?
We put the bullets back in.
How are things progressing?
We're ready.
Why do you hate them so much?
I've already told you,
we're at war.
So you're just following orders?
Why can't you just answer
the question?
Fine.
Something was in the stable...
tearing our horses to pieces.
I couldn't have saved my mother.
Or my sister.
Their screams woke me.
My father died outside,
trying to fend them off.
I stood at my door...
about to run
to my nieces' room when.
Twin girls.
Barely 6 years old.
Butchered like animals.
Jesus Christ.
The next thing I knew,
I was in his arms.
The war had spilled into our house.
He'd been tracking
the Lycans for days.
He drove them off and saved me.
Who?
Viktor.
The oldest and strongest of us.
That night,
he made me a Vampire.
He gave me the strength
to avenge my family.
Since then,
I've never looked back.
I saw your pictures.
Who is the woman, your wife?
It may be wise to keep a
closer eye on our cousins.
I'll have Raze
see to it immediately.
I'm afraid that I'm going to have
to place my faith in you, my friend.
Time is running short.
I tried to swerve,
but he hit us anyway.
He sent us right into
the oncoming lane.
When I came to, I...
I realized that part of the engine
was in the front seat.
And she was pinned there,
6 inches from me...
in this horrible position.
I think she was in shock
because she just
kept asking me over
and over again if I was all right.
She was more worried about me.
You know, if I knew then what
I know now, I could have saved her.
There's no doubt in my mind
about that.
But instead she died right there...
about two minutes before
the ambulance arrived.
After that, I didn't see
any reason to stick around.
I spent a summer here with
my grandfather when I was a kid so...
After I got my degree, I just-
I took off.
I came over here to move on,
to forget.
It seemed like a good idea
at the time.
And have you?
Moved on?
Have you?
I need you to keep what I'm about to
tell you under the strictest confidence.
It can wait.
Who started the war?
They did.
Or at least that's what
we've been led to believe.
Digging into the past is forbidden.
I should be heading back.
What about me?
Viktor will know what to do.
I'll come back tomorrow night.
I'm not staying here alone.
You will if you want to live.
No, I want to go with you.
What are you doing?
When the full moon
rises tomorrow night,
you will change, you will kill,
and you will feed.
It's unavoidable.
I can't leave you free
to roam around. I'm sorry.
A single round won't kill you, but
the silver prevents transformation.
At least for a few hours.
If I don't return in time,
do yourself a favor.
Use it.
Yeah?
My lord. She's here.
How could you do this to me?
Embarrass me like this?
The entire coven knows
that I had plans for us.
There is no us!
You'll go before Viktor...
and tell him exactly what I tell you to!
From here on out, you'll do as I say.
Is that in any way unclear?
Come closer, my child.
Outside.
Come on, move it.
I've been lost without you, my lord.
Constantly hounded by Kraven
and his never-ending infatuation.
It is the oldest story in the book.
He desires the one thing
he cannot have.
Now, tell me...
why have you come to believe
that Lucian still lives?
Yeah.
But I've given you
all the proof you need.
Incoherent thoughts and images,
nothing more.
Which is precisely why the Awakening
is performed by an elder.
You do not possess
the necessary skills.
But I did see Lucian. I shot him.
You must believe me.
The chain has never been broken.
Not once.
Not in 14 centuries.
Not since we elders first began
to leapfrog through time.
One awake, two asleep.
That's the way of it.
It is Marcus' turn to reign,
not mine.
There's been a complication.
But I had no choice.
The coven is in danger,
and Michael is the key-
Ah, yes.
The Lycan.
Please.
Give me the chance
to get proof you require.
Fine.
I will leave it to
Kraven to collect the proof...
if there is any.
How could you trust him over me?
Because he is not the one who
has been tainted by an animal.
I love you...
like a daughter,
but you leave me with no choice.
These rules are in place
for a good reason,
and they are the only reason
we have survived this long.
You will not be shown
an ounce of leniency.
When Amelia arrives, the Council
will convene and decide your fate.
You have broken the chain
and the Covenant!
You must be judged!
You should've listened to me
and stayed out of this.
Now you'll be lucky if I can convince
the Council to spare your life.
Tell me.
Did you have the nerve to cut the skin
from his arm, or did Lucian do it for you?
Mark my words.
Soon, you'll be
seeing things my way.
No one opens this door.
Understood?
I can't afford to have my future queen
run off with that Lycan again.
Shit.
Change of plans. Amelia will be
picked up by Soren and his team.
That's our job.
Not anymore.
Why are you helping me?
I'm not. I'm helping me.
What's going on?
The perimeter sensor's been tripped.
We're locking down the mansion.
It's Selene. She's escaped,
to go to him, to Michael.
I want that Lycan's head on a plate.
We need to go.
Get down!
Go. Go.
Jump.
Are you fucking kidding me?
Any luck?
False alarm.
The dogs would've been all over it
if anything had gotten near that fence.
Amelia should have arrived by now.
Yes.
Look, I want you to slip off the property
and find out what's keeping her.
You've got it.
Maybe we should pull over
and dose him.
Fuck him. He'll be all right.
We're almost there.
Oh, shit. He's not gonna make it.
Pull over. Pull over!
Get the kit.
Stick him. Stick him.
My lord.
Viktor wants
to speak with you.
My lord.
I sent for Selene...
not you.
She's defied your orders and...
fled the mansion, my lord.
Your incompetence
is becoming most taxing.
It's not my fault.
She's become obsessed,
thinks that I'm at the core
of some ridiculous conspiracy.
And here's my proof.
Now, I want you to tell them
exactly what you told me.
All right, all right.
We've been searching for someone
with a special trait.
A direct descendant
of Alexander Corvinus...
Hungarian...
a warlord...
who came to power in the early
seasons of the fifth century.
Just in time to watch a plague
ravage his village.
He alone survived.
Somehow, his body
was able to change the disease,
mold it to his benefit.
He became the first true immortal.
And years later,
he fathered at least two children
who inherited this same trait.
The sons of the Corvinus clan.
One bitten by bat, one by wolf,
one to walk the lonely road
of mortality as a human.
It's a ridiculous legend. Nothing!
That may be...
but our species
do have a common ancestor.
A mutation of the original virus
is directly linked to his bloodline.
There is a descendant
of Corvinus lying there...
not three feet from you.
Yes.
But he's already a Vampire.
We needed a pure source.
Untainted. An exact duplicate
of the original virus...
which we learned
was hidden away in the genetic
code of his human descendants
and passed along
in its latent form...
down through the ages...
all the way to Michael Corvin.
For years, we tried to combine
their bloodlines.
And for years we failed.
It was useless.
Even at the cellular level,
our species seemed destined
to destroy each other.
That is, until we found Michael.
The Corvinus strain allows
for a perfect union.
A triple-celled platelet...
which holds unspeakable power.
There can be no such union.
And to speak of it is heresy.
We'll see.
Once Lucian has injected himself
with Michael's blood.
Lucian is dead.
According to whom?
I need you to do something for me.
I can assure you, my child
Kraven will pay with his life.
Soon, this house
will lie in ruins.
Not before you.
No, no, no, wait. Wait!
You and you alone
will know the truth of this.
If Lucian was able to get his hands
on the blood of a Pure-Born,
a powerful elder like Amelia...
or yourself...
and inject it along
with Michael's blood.
Abomination.
Half-Vampire,
half-Lycan,
but stronger than both.
I need to speak with Kahn.
My lord.
The Council members
have been assassinated.
What of Amelia?
They bled her dry.
It has already begun, huh?
I'm sorry I doubted you.
Fear not, my child,
absolution will be yours...
the moment you kill the descendant
of Corvinus, this...
Michael.
You've been given an enzyme
to stop the change.
It may take a little time
for the grogginess to dissipate.
That's enough!
Just... go and see
what's keeping Raze, will you?
I really must apologize.
He's in desperate need
of a lesson in manners.
Speaking of manners,
where are mine? Forgive me.
I'm Lucian.
I need to go.
I need to get back.
There's no going back.
There's no going anywhere.
The Vampires will kill you on sight.
Just for being what you are.
One of us.
You are one of us.
What are you doing?
Bringing an end to this conflict.
Your war, it has nothing
to do with me.
My war?
No!
No! No!
Sonja!
They forced you to watch her die.
Sonja.
That's what started the war.
I saw it happen as if I were there.
We were slaves once.
The daylight guardians
of the Vampires.
I was born in servitude...
yet I harbored them no ill will.
I even took a Vampire for my bride.
It was forbidden...
our union.
Viktor feared
a blending of the species.
Feared it so much...
he killed her.
His own daughter...
burnt alive...
for loving me.
This is his war...
Viktor's...
and he's spent
the last 600 years
exterminating my species.
What are they gonna do to Selene?
We have company.
I thought we had a deal.
Patience.
Kraven.
These are matters
to be discussed in private.
Please escort our guests
downstairs.
The Council has been destroyed.
Soon, you will have it all.
Both great covens and an ironclad
peace treaty with the Lycans.
Who I trust will not be forgotten
when the spoils are tabulated.
How do you expect me to assume control
now that Viktor's been awakened?
There's no defeating him.
He grows stronger as we speak.
And that is precisely why
I need Michael.
If Viktor were so easy to dispatch...
you'd have done it yourself
centuries ago.
Exit shaft! Move it!
Son of a bitch!
Oh, shit!
It's Viktor.
Yes.
And if you had done your job,
he'd still be in hibernation.
Where the hell is Raze?
Is there another way out?
I guess it never occurred to you
that you might actually
have to bleed to pull off this coup.
Don't even think about leaving.
Silver nitrate.
Bet you weren't expecting that.
Come on! Move! Move! Move!
Move! Move!
Lucian.
Selene!
Not yet.
I have to get you out.
Viktor's on his way.
And he won't be satisfied
until every Lycan's dead.
They'll kill you too,
just for helping me.
I know.
I know what started the war.
That's enough.
You're coming with me!
I hope I live long enough to see
Viktor choke the life from you!
I bet you do.
But let me tell you a little something
about your beloved dark father.
He's the one who killed your family.
Not the Lycans.
Never could follow his own rules.
Said he couldn't abide the taste
of livestock.
So every once in a while, he went out
and gorged himself on human blood.
I kept his secrets...
cleaned up the mess.
But it was he...
who crept room to room
dispatching everyone
close to your heart.
But when he got to you,
he just couldn't bear the thought
of draining you dry.
You, who reminded him so much
of his precious Sonja...
the daughter
he condemned to death.
Lies.
Believe what you want.
Now come on.
Your place is by my side.
So be it.
Bite him!
Half-Vampire...
half-Lycan...
but stronger than both.
What the hell are you doing?
You may have killed me...
cousin.
But my will...
is done regardless.
Where is he?
Where's Kraven?
Forgive me, my child.
It wasn't the Lycans.
It was you.
Leave us.
How could you bear my trust
knowing that you'd
killed my family?
Yes.
I have taken from you.
But I have given so much more.
Is it not a fair trade, the life I have
granted you? The gift of immortality?
And the life of your daughter?
Your own flesh and blood?
I loved my daughter!
But the abomination growing
in her womb
was a betrayal of me
and of the coven!
I did what was necessary
to protect the species,
as I am forced to do yet again.
No!
Time to die.
Though I cannot predict the future,
the consequences of tonight
will reverberate through the halls
of both great covens
for many years to come.
Two Vampire elders
have been slain,
one by my own hand.
Soon, Marcus will take the throne.
And a tide of anger and retribution
will spill out into the night.
Differences will be set aside.
Allegiances will be made.
And soon...
I will become the hunted.