Plenty of sunshine today...
With seasonal temperatures,
we should reach our normal
high over this afternoon.
Clear skies tonight...
Increasing cloudiness tomorrow,
sticky and humid...
Hey, hey, hey, hey!
Come give me a kiss.
You must be good.
- Bye.
Have fun!
Cleve, it's 1955.
Please re-enter the clubhouse
in a more stereo typically
animated fashion.
Hey man, you know where
I could find Frank Barnes?
- Sir?
- Frank Barnes?
Good luck.
Thanks.
Excuse me, I'm looking
for Frank Barnes?
You found him.
I'm Will Colson.
We're working together
today on train 1206.
- 1206.
- That's the one.
- That's the profile?
- Yeah, want to take a look?
How you doing?
Is there a problem?
No problem.
I just don't like working
in a damn daycare center.
Yeah well.. I don't like working
at a retirement home or so.
Alright!
I'll tell you what.
I'm gonna finish my coffee.
I'll meet you on the wagon.
Sounds good.
- 1206.
- Yeah, that's the one.
You know that punk's union, right?
Heard they just made him
a shop steward at the UTU.
First year?
You know how he got hired?
His name's Colson.
His two uncles are running
things over at Thornwood,
and his brother's a
lead welder at Deacon.
The whole family's
from Stanton.
Now, that figures.
Here, they're shit-canning
guys every day...
but you got the right last name
and a rookie's pay grade.
You got a job.
What the hell are
these guys?
Dewey... Gilleece.
Sorry to break up
charm school.
What the hell is that beast
still doing on D-16?
I told you I need
that track clear.
Relax buddy, we were
just about to move it.
Like hell you are.
I've got 150 school students coming
in on some field trip on D-16.
I need that track cleared.
D-10's clear, you can
set it there.
Alright, alright!
Settle down, settle down.
Welcome to the Railroad
Safety Campaign.
We are not-for-profit program
designed to educate young
people like yourselves
about railway safety.
Hey! Settle down.
Show of hands.
Who's ridden a train before?
Me! Me! Me!
Alright! All aboard!
So what's our day?
They got us going on
light power.
We're supposed to pick up
25 cars just past Stanton,
then it's pretty much a straight
shot through Wilkins.
Any slow orders?
- No.
- You sure?
They'd be highlighted in red.
No, no slow orders.
Alright...
Dewey, what the hell
is taking you so long?
It's a 39-car consist, Bunny.
The thing's half a mile long...
for Christ's sake.
Gilleece, channel up.
Go for Gilleece.
You believe this shit?
Hey, hold up. You forgot to
tie the air in from the point.
Yeah, so?
So, you don't have
any air brakes.
You can tie the hoses
once we got her parked
and Bunny's quit
his bitching.
Okay.
I only got one rule.
One rule only.
You gonna do something.
you do it right.
You don't know how to do it.
You ask me, alright?
Likewise, if you need anything
from me, you better speak up,
because.. you're the conductor.
Once we get our freight.
it's your train.
I'm just the guy
driving it.
How long you been
out of training?
About four months.
- Four months?
- Yeah.
Wow.
Fullon yellow vest rookie.
How long have you
been railroading?
28 years.. November 13, 1981.
28 years.
What did you do
before that?
Oh...
I don't know, a bunch of
different jobs.
Yeah?
No railroading?
No, just looking to do
something different.
Something different?
What do you mean,
something better?
No, no.
Just...
- Different.
- Just different.
Hey Dewey, want to pick
it up a little bit jagoff?
I want to have lunch at
some point.
- Yeah.
- Hey.
Your lawyer just called.
You got a break.
The hearing's been moved
up to this morning.
Looks like, you'll be going home.
Well, that's great but...
Did you tell him
I was working?
I can't come in.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
He said no problem man.
- And he said it's looking good.
- Alright.
Call him in an hour or two,
see where it's at.
- I will.
- Give me a call.
We ready to pull out
or what?
Coming.
Alright.
Train's leaving.
What's our fuel gauge reading?
Fuel gauge?
- 2900.
- 2900?
Anglecock's closed.
Hand brake's knocked off.
Good, good, good.
Got all the updated division
notices and bulletin orders.
The POS releases are in.
Filled out our time slips.
We're good to go.
Good! Alright.
You're at 29 cars, you got
10 to go, you're good.
Dewey, you got 29, ten more
makes thirty nine...
You taking PB-9
over to D-10?
Dewey.
Hold your horses.
What's wrong?
Damn trailing point switch.
The track's aligned for D-16.
What's your stopping distance?
At least 20 cars to a stop.
Damn it!
Okay, so we back it up
and lose a little time.
I'm hopping out.
Do not get out of
that cab, man!
Don't worry, I'll set
the independent.
- Dewey!
- Dewey.
Come on, get back on.
Dewey!
You better get back on!
I'm on it. I'm on it.
Shit!
You better get back on, dickhead!
Hey!
Shit!
Nice job Dewey!
God damn it!
So now what the hell
do we do?
Shh... shoot.
Ooh... you're in trouble.
Just don't talk about it.
Just put your sister on
the phone, Sweetheart.
Dad!
She doesn't want
to talk to you.
Listen. Just tell her I was...
I didn't forget. I was just...
I was running late.
She's got a date tonight.
With who?
Just put your
sister on the phone.
Wait... here she is.
Nic?
Nicky?
Hello?
Listen, just...
Baby, look, I didn't forget.
I was...
Frank, the stop blocks are up.
Is there a problem?
No, there's no problem except
you got it backwards.
Turntable house goes on my end.
You're on the ballast.
On my end.
Other than that, no problem.
No problem at all.
Like I told you...
if you don't know something,
just ask.
That's all.
I got it.
I hope so.
Whatever.
Excuse me?
This shit, this "Let's make the new
guy prove himself" bullshit.
I gotta tell you I've heard it before
and it gets old real fast.
Well, that's how it is at
the retirement home.
Company wants to get
rid of us old heads.
They give all the jobs to you
new guys, you yellow vests.
I'm not trying to take
anything from anybody.
As reassuring as that is...
a lot of guys
don't see it that way.
I'm here, I'm walking in
right now.
I got a car full of donuts
for those kids.
- A coaster? What train?
- Connie?
How the hell did this happen?
It just got away from me.
It got away from you?
It's a train, Dewey.
Not a chipmunk.
I had to leave the cab
to throw a switch.
- You left the cab?
- Yeah.
And it gets worse.
The air brakes weren't tied on.
They aren't tied on, still..
We've got an unmanned train
rolling into opposing traffic.
With no air brakes?
Is that what you're telling me?
I set the independent brakes.
That'll for sure stop it.
How fast is it going?
No more than 10 miles per...
Okay, jump on the high
rail and go after it.
Now!
Okay, ballbuster.
Call the field trip!
I don't care where they
are on the main line.
They need to get into
the nearest siding.
RS Campaign, RS Campaign.
This is Fuller Yard. Do you copy?
RSC answering dispatch.
How can I help you? Over.
RS Campaign.
This is Fuller Yard.
We've got unauthorized
activity on your track.
We're gonna need you to divert
to a siding at Portville.
Dispatch, please repeat.
Please repeat.
Over!
What time is train time?
Anytime!
Divert to a siding in Portville.
Do you copy?
I copy, I'll divert into the
siding at Portville, over.
Get me 777's cargo information.
I have to call corporate
and report this.
Now, Dewey said he applied
the independent.
So, friction should stop the damn
thing after a few miles.
Still. we need to alert every
northbound train on the mainline.
First 20 miles of track
take priority.
I don't care if you're
talking about
a spot weld on a
Class 3 rip track,
or ground operations
in Afghanistan.
It's all about precision.
- Right.
- Thank you.
- Excuse me.
- Sure.
Hello.
Ned. where are you?
Oh, Connie. Hey, I'm
just driving in now.
I got to go.
How far are you
from milepost 5?
Roughly six minutes, traffic contingent.
Great, I need you to
haul ass over there
and throw the siding switch.
We got a coaster.
A coaster?
Really?
Yeah, it should roll past
MP 5 in about 15 minutes.
That should give you enough
time to throw the switch
get it off the mainline
and onto that siding.
You want me to climb
onboard and stop it?
What? No, no, no. We got two
hostlers are on their way.
You just throw the switch, Ned.
Roger that.
You can always count
on him to be late.
I'll see you later.
See you...
Yeah, I can get you where
you need to go...
'Cause I'm a country boy.
What do we do when we
get to a railroad crossing?
Stop, look and listen!
I can't hear you!
You from Stanton?
- Born and raised.
- Yeah?
My whole family's
from Stanton.
Married?
Yeah.
Well, sort of.
It's a long story.
We got a long day.
How about you?
You married?
Short story.
Once...
Got 2 beautiful daughters though,
eighteen, nineteen.
They are both waitressing, trying
to work their way thru college.
- Oh. yeah?
- Yeah.
- Where at?
- Hooters.
Hooters. You know?
Alright.
That's right, Hooters.
Wipe that grin off your face.
- I'm a fan.
- Yeah.
You're blushing.
I'm used to it.
Connie!
Corporate on line 2.
This is Connie Hooper
at Fuller Yard.
I'll hold.
Did I hear right?
You've got a coaster?
Yeah, this sort of thing happens.
We're on it.
Won't it trip a relay?
Yeah Listen, I need to speak
to Mr Galvin directly.
I see, can you have
him call me then?
No, I'm about to review the
cargo shipment on myself.
Who the hell are you?
I'm here for the Railroad
Safety Campaign.
Scott Werner FRA Region Two,
Federal Safety Inspector.
I'm supposed to give a presentation
to the children.
- go over some basic stuff.
- That's great.
Hey Bunny?
Bunny!
Can you help me out here?
Okay, see this guy
right there?
He's gonna tell you
where to sit.
- Okay.
- Track geometry, alignment...
- Thank you so much.
- I brought some gauges...
The kids are gonna love that.
It's great.
God damn it. Where the
hell is this thing?
Bunny, I need to know exactly
what's in cars 7 to 10?
Get a hold of the shipper, please?
Are you kidding me?
Where's the train?
Where does it look like
the goddamn train is?
It's not here! What are
you doing out here?
Do I look like I got a train
hidden in my back pocket?
Bunny, get me Connie.
- Get behind us jackass.
- It's Ned.
- Did you get here too late?
- Don't give me that shit.
You know you two numbnuts
are always screwing up.
You switched the track
that was supposed
to get the train on the
right track.
Connie.
Yeah, it's Ned.
Did you throw that switch yet?
Yeah, six minutes ago but
your train it's not here.
I thought it might be going a
little slower than you guessed,
but these two numbnuts
that you sent.
They just showed up and
they ain't seen it, either.
Are you saying our train
already passed?
Yes ma'am, that be my guess.
It's not a coaster.
That train under power.
That be my guess too.
Put Dewey on the phone.
Sure, she wants to talk
to you, asshole!
Yeah.
I need you to rally every
cell in that brain of yours.
When you applied the independent,
was the throttle in the
forward position?
Yeah, I had to get
it moving, Connie.
In what position was the
throttle set?
Damn it Dewey.
What position?
Connie, the throttle was
in notch 8 full power.
Okay.
It was 39 cars!
Take the southbound track.
Catch up.
See if it's still going slow enough
for one of you to climb on.
You have got until milepost 13
before the track splits.
Let me talk to Ned again.
Nice job asshole!
Ned, I want you to get back in your
car and follow the mainline, okay?
I want a set of eyes
on that train.
You got them.
Roger that!
I can't hear you!
Railroad Safety Campaign!
You're good.
Keep it coming, fifty.
Twenty feet.
Slow down.
Alright, you're good.
Yeah.
What's going on?
You got a minute?
I thought he said it
was looking good.
That's what he thought.
Turns out the judge they assigned,
was a real hard ass.
You gotta be kidding me.
Look, the restraining order is being
continued for another
- 30 days.
- Thirty days?
What am I supposed to
do for 30 days?
I'll have to stay away from my kid?
And then there's another
hearing after that, I guess.
What's taking you so long,
Will?
You call that lawyer,
you can tell him...
he can stick it up his ass.
I got to go.
Will!
Pick up the radio.
Will! Pick up the radio, over.
Are you there?
Yeah.
Yeah, get off the phone, knock
off the hand brakes.
Get up here, it's time to go.
We got work to do.
Copy.
No, it's definitely under power.
We're not sure of the
exact speed yet.
I thought all these trains had
some sort of deadman brake.
There's a wand the engineer
has to hit periodically
or the air brakes are
automatically applied.
Unfortunately, this train's air
brakes were disconnected.
Sir, I would gladly explain the particulars
of locomotive operation to you.
If we had time but right now
I really need your assistance
posting officers at all the
mainline crossings.
One question.
How do you all
plan to stop it?
We're working on it.
Go, go, go!
The split's coming up!
Are you sure you
can do this?
Just get along side
of the cab.
Get up along side of it!
I'm trying!
Go, go, go!
Remember, we don't have
a lot of track!
You got it.
Go! Go!
Dewey!
It's too fast!
Back it up!
Come on Dewey!
Go back! Go back!
Jump Gilleece!
Do it!
Get in! Watch out!
So now what the hell
do we do?
How many cars are we
supposed to cut in?
Twenty, why?
Twenty cars.
Okay.
See the switch stand
up ahead of us?
- The switch stand, yeah?
- Uh-huh.
Take a look in the rear view mirror.
You see the one behind us?
- Way back there. You see it?
- Uh-huh.
There's exactly 21 cars
between the two stands.
Don't ask me how I know.
So why is it that
there's still more than four and
a half cars that are yet to clear?
Because I...
Excuse me?
- Because I cut...
- Because what?
I cut in too many cars.
Cut in too many cars, huh?
Maybe if you weren't on
my ass the whole time.
I might be able to think
straight and do my job.
What do you mean.
"Maybe if I..."
- You been on my ass this whole trip!
- You're blaming it on me?
I'm just saying pick
a goddamn job!
- I got my job! You pick one, I pull the throttle!
- Then I pull the throttle, you pull the pin!
- It's one or the other!
- Used to pull the pin!
You're five pins too many.
Pull the pins, you're right.
Pull the pins.
I've had my training!
Alright?
Yeah, but we're out here in the
real world. This ain't training.
In training they just give you an "F".
Out here, you get killed.
- I screwed up. okay?
- Yes, you did.
Stop and roll back and
I'll cut the empties.
Roll back?
Oh Lord...
We can't stop out
here on the main.
We're more than a mile
out on the main.
More than a mile
to the next stop.
You don't take a consist this
size that distance in reverse.
Fine, then we'll make the
turn at the next siding.
The next siding's
not for 10 miles.
We do that, we're late.
I don't run late.
Just green-sheet it
and we'll move on.
Come on, we green-sheet it.
It's my ass!
- Cut me some slack.
- What do you mean it's your ass?
You're a Colson.
What the hell is that
supposed to mean?
That means you can call your uncle
and they'll take care of it.
Is that what this
is about?
No, it's about the 5 cars
too many.
We're gonna stop roll back
and cut those empties!
This may be your engine.
but it's my goddamn train.
- Yes it is your train!
- I'm the goddamn conductor!
That's true!
1206, check in.
I'll write you up and
green-sheet your ass.
- Will you?
- How about that?
1206, this is dispatch.
What's your location? Over.
- Something's funny?
- No.
What the hell are you laughing at?
What are you laughing at?
Because it's funny.
You're a funny guy.
Well-trained but funny.
Yeah, this is 1206.
We're 60 miles from Wilkins.
Forty minutes out
of Fuller Yard.
Negative 1206, clear your
train at the next siding
until further instructed, over.
What's up?
There's an unmanned train
out of Fuller,
on the northbound track, over.
On our track?
A coaster?
1206, we don't have
all the details yet.
Just proceed to the next siding
and hold tight, over.
Next siding's not for 10 miles.
Affirmative, 1206.
Just get in that siding
and sit tight
until we give you the
the all-clear, over.
Affirmative!
It's coming right at us.
More word on that runaway freight
train in rural Pennsylvania.
The train, A WVR777
otherwise known as 777,
left Fuller Yard in northern PA
sometime before 8 a.m.
this morning
and no one was on board.
Live, local, late-breaking.
The engineer, they say, made an
error in controlling the train.
Before leaving the locomotive,
he intended to apply the
independent brakes.
And then by the time he
realized his mistake,
the train was going too fast
for him to climb back on.
We're being told now
by a spokesperson
for the
Public Utilities Commission
that this employee
will be held accountable.
- Connie?
- Yeah.
Headquarters is on the phone.
It's Galvin.
Mr Galvin, how are you?
God damn it.
How could this happen?
It's an unfortunate combination
of human error and bad luck.
Luck?
I was a yardmaster for
10 years Miss Hooper.
Luck has no business
in a rail yard.
What are we worried about
in terms of cargo?
Well, obviously the diesel
fuel's a concern.
No, I said cargo.
Okay, well,
cars 7 through 10
and 16 through 19 are carrying
a chemical called molten phenol.
We're still trying to
connect with the shipper
to determine exactly
what that is.
It's used in
the manufacture of glue.
Can you hold on
one moment?
You know about molten phenol?
Yes.
Mr Galvin, we have an
FRA inspector here.
May I put you on speaker?
Region 2 Federal Safety Inspector
Scott Werner. How can I help?
Just tell me what you know
about molten phenol.
Well, it's serious stuff.
Very toxic, highly combustible.
Oh, that's terrific.
Hooper, get state police
back on the line.
Make sure they got a HazMat
team briefed and ready.
And ask them to put a
spotter chopper over 777.
I take it you've sided
all rail traffic?
On our end, yes.
Brewster's notifying its own.
Sir.
how are we going to
handle this?
I mean this train is
enroute to pass
through some highly
populated areas.
We're having a strategy call
in about two minutes.
Alright, I'll be ready.
You won't be on the call,
Miss Hooper.
- Excuse me?
- You'll be advised.
For now coordinate with
local authorities.
God knows we gotta have over 100
crossings that need to be secured.
One hundred and seventy-three.
Railroad crossings,
between here and AWVR
substation in Brewster.
Listen... Mr Galvin,
this train is half
a mile long,
and is traveling at speed,
into population
with eight freight cars of
hazardous chemicals,
and 5000 gallons of
diesel fuel.
Sir, we're not just talking
about a train here.
We're talking about a missile,
the size of the Chrysler Building.
So what is your point,
Miss Hooper?
My point is after it crosses
through Findlay,
there's about 12 miles
of vacant farmland.
But after that, it's nothing
but town after town
all the way to Stanton.
We have a very
limited window here.
So, what are you suggesting
we do, derail it?
Yes sir, I am.
While we still can.
Mr Galvin, I understand that's gonna
cost the company a lot of money...
Do you think?
Miss Hooper, we're not
gonna intentionally,
destroy one of our
own trains.
Not when we can
still stop it.
We can avoid a lot
of collateral...
I'm going to extend you my
last ounce of good will
and pretend this conversation
never happened.
He thinks I'm worried
about my job.
Ma'am, please stay in
your van.
- Come on!
- Please get back into the van.
Can you please tell us
what's going on?
Every crossing's closed off
for 20 miles.
Ma'am, for your safety,
please get back into your van.
I'm not getting back in
the vehicle.
We need to know
what's going on.
Guys, get out of there.
There's a train coming.
Hurry!
Hurry! It's coming!
- Come on.
- We got to go.
Get out of there!
Move it!
Get out of the way!
1206 to dispatch, over.
- What's wrong?
We're not gonna fit in that siding,
that's what's wrong.
1206 to dispatch, over.
1206, are you in the siding yet?
What's your location?
No, we're not in the hole.
We're not gonna make it, can't do it.
Too much train.
I'm gonna need you to
realign the switch,
so we can proceed to
the next siding.
1206, you have to get off
the main, over.
I understand that but you
gotta understand this.
We're not going to fit.
1206, stand by.
That siding's a good 3000 ft,
end to end.
Check your timetable.
It's gonna tell you the
siding is 4111 ft.
But that's signal to signal.
In reality,
it's more like 2500 ft.
You add those five cars
that you picked up...
We can fit.
No, we won't fit.
Dispatch, this is 1206.
Can you tell me where the
nearest rip track is?
1206, there's one in 6.2 miles.
How fast are you going?
55 miles an hour.
1206, go faster, over.
Why? Is that coaster still
on the main?
1206, 777 is not a coaster.
I repeat, it is not a coaster, over.
You're telling me it's under power?
Get in the goddamn siding.
1206, stand by.
1206, if you're going for it, that
rip track is confirmed vacant.
It's your call, Frank.
We need to throw the switch
if you're staying on.
We're not staying on!
Pull the brake, Frank.
We pull the brake and side up.
I crash.
I know what the hell I'm doing.
Bullshit! You're gonna
get us killed.
Hey!
1206, I need an answer, over.
Realign the switch.
Over.
The train was just going with
no one in it. Just took off.
We were yelling on the
radio earlier,
there's a runaway train
coming through.
It could be coming to our
town next.
And the high school's right
next to those train tracks.
Just a few moments ago,
a train came barreling down
these tracks...
We're still going over
the numbers.
But should 777 derail, we're
looking at a major disaster.
If even one of those
HazMat cars blew,
it could easily decimate
an entire town.
That train is carrying
eight of them.
Can you please explain to our
viewers what you witnessed...
Environmental liability, track damage,
car and locomotive loss.
We're looking at a projected
cost easily over $100 million.
And the resulting stock devaluation?
Our projections indicate it could
be in the 30 to 40 percent range.
Oh!
I say we go with
Mr Galvin's option.
I've already prepped our
substation in Brewster.
They just need a go ahead.
You have it.
Okay, everybody out.
Hoffman, you stay here.
Baker, get me a track schematic,
Fuller to Stanton, please!
This is Owens.
71, 70, 71 on the gun.
So the red means?
777 blew through a signal.
Everything in red means
trouble on the mainline.
That's a lot of red.
Connie, Mr Galvin on line 2.
This is Connie Hooper.
Have all the mainline crossings
been closed?
Yes, I've been coordinating
with PSP.
Do we have a strategy in place?
It's already underway.
By the activity level behind me,
it is evident that a plan to stop
the runaway train is underway.
But so far, no one at AWVR
is commenting.
We just witnessed A WVR employee,
Ryan Scott
boarding one of the rescue helicopters.
He is a 22 year old Marine vet who
has just returned from Afghanistan.
What the hell is this?
I need a police escort now!
Whoa!
It says here you're a welder.
Lead welder.
Listen buddy, I don't got
a lot of time.
Look! you can call my yardmaster,
Connie Hooper!
Connie sent you?
That's what I said.
I need your help.
1206, this is dispatch.
1206, we ran the math. At over
2000, you wouldn't have fit.
Good call, over.
Thank you but I need to know
where that oncoming train is.
How far away is it?
1206, we're not exactly sure.
You're not sure?
Well, find out!
I'm high above central Pennsylvania.
This train got away...
Emergency responders want to
halt all activity near the line
and possibly evacuate all homes
within a mile radius of
the tracks.
There's thousands of gallons of fuel
onboard, which is highly flammable.
But we're still awaiting
word on that.
This is Galvin's strategy?
Looks like they're putting
a train in front of 777
in an attempt to slow it down.
Now, they are sending a chopper
with Ryan Scott
and the railroad company is
still refusing to comment.
We've just learned that 26 year rail
company veteran Judd Stewart
is at the controls of the engine
that is in front of the runaway train.
This is Connie Hooper
from Fuller Yard.
Is this your guy coming off
the helicopter?
Still holding at 55.
Get her down to 40
and keep braking.
Shit!
That's it, keep going.
Keep slowing.
Get her down to 40 and we'll
set our boy down.
Unbelievable!
Do this!
Come on.
incredibly dangerous...
Do this, Judd.
Come on!
I'm under 40.
Is he on yet?
Now!
Looks like Marine Ryan Scott
has been injured.
It's a no go.
Slow down!
Just keep braking, try to slow it.
Try to get 777 off the main.
Switch has been thrown.
Slow down, God damn it!
Don't side it yet!
It's going too fast.
Bail! Bail! Bail!
Holy shit!
Maybe it derailed.
Wow! I can't believe
how crazy that was.
Oh my God!
Galvin, you asshole!
Fuller Yard, Fuller Yard.
This is 1206.
We're passing milepost 52,
heading northbound on the Main 1.
1206, who am I  speaking with?
Frank Barnes, the engineer.
This is Connie Hooper,
yardmaster at Fuller.
Why are you still on
the mainline?
We were directed to a siding
that's a no go.
We're heading to a rip track
just past milepost 5-0.
We need to know the location
of your yard's train.
It just passed milepost 47.
Holy shit.
They tried to side it but it jumped
the switch and derailed the lash-up.
Lash-up?
Who was driving?
The engineer, a 26-year rail
company veteran,
was killed earlier today in Keating
Summit, central Pennsylvania.
Judd Stewart.
Stewart?
You said Stewart?
Judd Stewart, an engineer
from Brewster.
You know him?
What's your power on the point?
5000 horses, she's not a hotshot,
but she's still got some life
left in her, over.
Give her all you got, tell Galvin we
got two guys out on the mainline
about to play chicken with
our train.
- We tried to stop it. We blew it.
- What?
That train got to go down.
The only question is how to
minimize the damage.
Be quiet!
We just learned there is yet
another train on this track,
headed directly at the runaway.
What the hell is this?
We gotta learn about it on,
damn TV?
Nicole listen, don't hang up.
Don't hang up.
Dad, I'm busy, okay?
Okay, I understand.
I just...
- Dad?
- I just wanted to tell you that I love you.
Okay fine!
Dad, what's wrong?
Nothing, nothing.
I just...
Dad, what's wrong?
Just tell your sister I love you
both, okay? I got to go.
What's wrong?
1206, how are you holding up?
About a half a mile from
that rip track, over.
Chances are, you're going to see
777's nose any minute now.
Affirmative!
Why are you braking?
Trust me, if we head in this hot,
we'll tear right off the track.
Oh Jesus.
Get her down to 40 and
brace yourself.
You need to get at least
10 cars into the siding.
Yes!
Frank, go to 6.
Yeah, I'm at 6, go!
They're evacuating Arklow.
They're going to derail
the train.
What are they using?
Standard DRE.
Yeah, a portable derailer.
What are you doing?
I got a look at that train's last
coupler knuckle, it was open.
We take off right now,
we get back on the main.
We can chase it down in reverse.
Chase?
Whoa, wait a minute.
The only way to stop that kind
of power, grab it by the tail.
Boom, gun it in the
opposite direction.
We can't just chase it down.
If it goes down,
we're gonna be a wreck
on a wreck.
Doesn't matter, there's a good
chance the derailer won't work.
It's called a derailer
for Christ's sake!
- That's what they do!
- A train that size
going that fast, it will vaporize
anything that gets in its way.
Bullshit!
They wouldn't use it if...
They're wrong, alright?
They're wrong.
Are you in or are you out?
If you want to get yourself
killed, you do it alone.
You know what? Ask your
wife what she thinks.
Wait!
If you're right and that
derailer fails,
what are the odds it
makes it to Stanton?
You saw the train,
what do you think?
1206, this is Connie Hooper.
Are you there?
1206, over.
Just wanted to see how
you boys are doing.
We're doing about 60
mile an hour, Connie.
Sorry?
Frank, I don't understand.
We're going after your train.
1206, I'm not hearing you.
The rear knuckle was left open.
So if we can catch up, we can
tie it on to our locomotive.
Try and slow down 777.
Frank, you can't.
We already are.
Portable derailer's not
gonna cut it, Connie.
Who said anything
about a derailer?
Dispatch, they said that they're
evacuating Arklow.
Two plus two is four.
It's Ned. He said he's still
following... No, No, No.
Tell him I'll call him back.
Get me Galvin, now!
Frank, that train's carrying 30,000
gallons of toxic chemicals.
They had a window before but that
train going into populated areas.
There's no way they'd
derail it now.
Are you sure about that?
Look, let me make some calls.
Make some calls, please.
What do you think? Do you
think they can catch up?
Possibly.
But even if they do,
we're talking about coupling at 10
times the normal speed in reverse.
I thought you were in favor
of derailment.
Yeah, when they were in the
middle of nowhere not now.
It's just town after town
out there!
Mr Galvin says he'd have
to call you back.
This is Connie Hooper for
Mr Galvin.
Mr Galvin is in a meeting.
Then maybe you can tell me. Is the
company planning on derailing 777?
Last I heard, Galvin was dead
set against it.
I'm sorry, I'd really like
to help you, Miss Hooper.
But I'm not at liberty to
give you that information.
No, of course you're not
at liberty to.
Frank is right.
What's the fastest you've taken
a single engine like this?
- Unattached?
- Yeah.
Fifty, 55.
Of course, I was going forward.
1206, you there?
This is 1206, over.
Frank, you're right,
about the derailment.
They're planning an attempt
outside of Arklow.
Tell them idiots, it ain't
gonna work.
That portable derailer,
it's worthless.
She already told us.
Frank, this is Oscar Galvin
VP of Operations,
patched in at his request,
open mike.
Yeah, we're derailing 777, Frank.
It's a done decision.
Like it or not, it's our
best option at this stage.
There'll be less collateral
damage in Arklow.
It's already being evacuated,
and we can't let 777
make it to Stanton.
Look! Mr Galvin with all
due respect,
I've been railroading 28 years.
I'm telling you, we got a real
chance to stop this thing.
No, we already tried.
That was from the front.
We're long hood lead back.
It's a different situation.
We got more control now.
What if I cancel the derailer
and you fail, Frank?
That train will be doing
70 miles an hour
into that elevated s-curve
in Stanton.
The damage will be
a 100 times worse.
Right! I'm just telling you, the
portable derailer is worthless.
You got too much train
traveling entirely too fast.
Maybe 1206 should just
stay on it as a backup.
Look, I am not jeopardizing more
personnel and more property,
just because some engineer
wants to play hero.
End of discussion!
That train is our property,
it's our decision!
Now you stop your pursuit
or I will fire you!
Fire? You already did.
Already did what?
You've already fired me.
I received my 90-day notice
in the mail, 72 days ago.
Forced early retirement,
with half benefits.
So you're going to risk your life
for us with three weeks left.
Not for you.
I'm not doing it for you.
Frank! let me see that thing.
Mr Galvin, this is Will Colson,
your conductor.
I'm letting you know, we're
going to run this bitch down.
Maybe you didn't hear what I just
said, Colson. I will fire you!
Well, that's too bad. I was just
starting to like this job.
God damn it, you listen to me!
You son of a bitch! You will be fired!
You're breaking up.
Sorry, you're...
- This garbage is...
- Sir, I think they're gone.
This is your headache now, Hooper.
Now you get them off the main or
consider yourself shit-canned, too!
I like them.
Bring up Beech Siding
to Arklow.
Take a look behind me, you can see
emergency evacuation measures
are currently in effect right here
in the tiny town of Arklow.
The lash-up was a no go.
1206 to Fuller Yard. Connie,
are you there, over.
Frank, I'm real sorry
about Galvin.
That's okay.
Listen, listen. Is he off?
Yeah, he's gone.
Okay, listen up.
I'm going to need you
to do us a favor.
I need you to keep us posted on
the speed and location of 777.
Location and speed, over.
Connie?
Frank, 777's nine miles
out of Arklow.
You got some catching
up to do.
9 miles out of Arklow.
What did you say your wife's
first name was?
Darcy.
So, what was the long story
you didn't want to make long?
I come home from work,
2 weeks ago
and she's texting on the phone.
I ask her who with?
She says, "Nobody".
I say, "Let me see the
phone". She says no.
This goes on, about 5 or 6 times.
Wait, you're losing me.
She's texting...
There's this guy we both
went to school with.
He's a cop, he's a PA
state trooper.
He's always had a thing for Darcy.
Going way back.
1206, where are you?
1206 here, Connie. We're just
passing milepost 5-7.
You're about a mile
and a half behind.
How far out of Arklow is 777?
Seven and a half miles. It picked
up speed, you better step on it.
I'm stepping on it, in it, around
it and through it, Connie.
Thank you, over.
She's texting on the phone. I keep on
asking for it, she keeps on saying no.
She starts to walk away
and I grab for it.
- You hit her?
- No, no, no.
I mean I scared her,
but I didn't hit her.
Anyway, I drive to
this guy's house...
and tell him we need to talk.
Let's take a ride.
He jumps in my truck
and starts in with...
"You got it all wrong,
we're just friends".
Then he stops once he sees...
the gun I got sitting
on the dash.
Oh!
I look him in the eye and say,
"she's my wife, you find a new friend."
You pulled a gun on a cop?
Frank?
Frank, 777 just passed
milepost 61.
Thank you, Connie.
- You want to hear the kicker?
- Yes, I do.
It wasn't even him
that was texting her,
it was my sister-in-law.
Anyway, by the time I got home,
his buddy's waiting for me.
Just waiting to serve me
with this restraining order.
Darcy wouldn't even look at me.
So I'm living with my brother.
There was a hearing today. The
judge ordered a 30-day extension.
It's like one day everything's
going okay and then...
And the next, it's all
falling apart faster
than you can put it
back together.
Yeah, never too late though.
The plan to derail this
39-car runaway train,
is just minutes away now.
There's a tremendous amount
of activity going on.
Will this train be able
to be stopped?
1206, Connie. We're just
passing milepost 6-2.
Milepost 6-2, over.
Still a mile gap, maybe more.
We're not gaining
on her, Frank.
Hold on.
It's just like the
shooting range!
Alright, here we go!
Come on! Let's go!
This is it! It's game time!
And remember, we're aiming
for the red circular button!
Now!
Hold your fire!
You're shooting the fuel cap.
God damn it!
Hold your fire!
We were aiming to disable it
by firing shotgun rounds
at a fuel stop safety switch,
and so some shots were fired.
That safety switch is
a mighty small target.
And it's right next
to a fuel tank.
We're not gonna catch it
before Arklow.
Frank, you're closing the gap.
You should cut your speed.
Allow yourself some stopping
distance, just in case.
No can do, Connie. If we slow
down now, we'll never catch it.
Not before Stanton, over.
It's your call.
However, we have now also learned
that two railroad employees,
are now in pursuit of train
777 in a single locomotive.
It is unclear,
what their plan is...
Connie Hooper for you.
Did I or did I not tell you
to get 1206 off the main?
I asked them nicely.
You're 100 percent sure that
derailer won't work?
Yes, 100 percent?
No.
Which one is it?
- 50-50.
- Pretty funny.
And if it does?
If it does then, we're
a wreck on a wreck.
I'm here with FRA official
Gene Devereaux.
This train is getting close.
How is this going to work?
Basically, it works like a ramp.
The train comes along,
this piece here will lift the flange
and pull it outside the rail.
That will cause the train to flip
over on its right-hand side.
Son of a bitch won't even
know what hit it.
Train's about four minutes out!
Guys, come on.
Get it started!
Guys, come on!
It has not succeeded...
What?
What in the hell was that?
That was 10 million pounds
of train, Mr Galvin!
And this is the sound
of me saving your ass!
Frank, do you copy?
Frank?
This is 1206, over.
You were right.
It barely bumped.
Jesus Christ.
We're bringing you live
coverage right now
on what could very well result
in one of the worst disasters
in the history of the
state of Pennsylvania.
Now, the particulars are
still being examined,
but authorities are far
more focused
on the potential destruction
that would result if train 777
were to derail in Stanton.
What'd you mean about
being married once?
Alice my wife,
she died of cancer.
- Four years ago.
- I'm sorry.
Me too.
Every night I'd come home,
tell her about my day.
Where I'd been,
what I hauled,
who annoyed me.
Guess I would have made
the evening report, huh?
Yes, you would have
made it, definitely.
You should call your wife.
I would but it's her day off.
She's probably sleeping.
Don't make excuses.
Wake her up.
Been calling for the
past two weeks.
She still hasn't called me back.
She won't, you got to call her.
Don't you know how that works?
You quit too easy.
Darcy!
I have been calling and calling.
What is wrong?
As we told you earlier today,
those emergency evacuations
began early this morning as they try
to move people out of harm's way.
You get a sense of the perimeter here.
You see the firefighters...
Hey, it's me.
Yeah, we're on our way.
Yeah, I know.
I'm watching it.
Two railroad employees are
presently in pursuit of train 777,
in a single locomotive.
No one seems exactly clear
on what their plans are,
should they catch up
to that train.
It's Dad.
We have just learned that railroad
employee, Frank Barnes
a 28 year veteran of the freight
company responsible for the runaway,
and Will Colson, a conductor, are
now onboard another locomotive.
We're on our way.
A single locomotive trying
to catch up
to the runaway train.
She's gotta get dressed.
And get this, they were
traveling... I can tell.
She'll be ready in a minute.
...at speeds of up to 70
miles an hour in reverse.
777 is now just miles away
from the significantly...
Come on Darcy, let's go.
Come on, get dressed.
...more populated
town of Stanton.
Let's go, boys!
Okay, you're getting close.
The gap's at a mile and 777
is 10 miles to Stanton.
Now listen, Frank. I got a guy here
named Werner from the FRA.
Now, I'm inclined to defer to
your judgment here but he...
Alright, put him on. We could
use all the help we can get.
Just press this and
hold to talk.
It's about slowing 777
once you've tied on.
I know conventional
wisdom says
to just gun it in the
opposite direction.
But you'll have a better shot
alternating full throttle
with dynamic braking.
Yeah, but we can't afford
to lose counterthrust.
Well,what you'll lose
in counterthrust,
you'll compensate for
in tractive force.
Are you sure about that?
Well, it's more of a hunch based
on some quick calculations.
It's a hunch.
I'm 70 miles an hour and he's
giving us a hunch.
Okay, thank you.
Put Connie back on, please.
It's me, Frank.
Yeah, Connie. Does this guy
know what he's talking about?
In a perfect world.
Yes, I'd say yes.
In a perfect world, okay.
We have more now on that runaway
freight train in rural Pennsylvania.
They've devised an ambitious
plan to bring it to a stop.
A single locomotive moves in
from behind,
catches up, hooks up and then brakes
in an effort to slow it down.
Passing milepost 7-6,
Connie, over.
You're only a half mile away.
Half a mile, out.
Frank, running in reverse. How are
you gonna gauge our gap distance?
I could go out there.
I could signal you by hand.
At 70 mile an hour?
I'm asking, would it help?
Alright, radio and hand signals.
We'll combinate.
And be careful.
I will.
And take that vest off too.
- Why?
- Just take it off.
I don't want to look out
this window
and see you in that yellow
vest. It'll freak me out.
Come on, Will.
Pick up.
Come on.
This is Will,
leave me a message.
Damn!
Ten cars, Frank!
Affirmative, over.
Alright, here she comes!
Three cars?
Three cars steady.
Copy.
Alright.
Steady, steady!
Two cars?
Yeah, two cars.
Copy.
Steady, over.
Keep it coming!
keep it coming!
Steady, steady!
Will Colson is trying
to hook up 1206
- with 777.
- Oh my God.
Something has gone
terribly wrong.
Will, what was that?
The grain car blew a seal!
Are we tied off?
Will, what's going on?
Right now we are looking at live
pictures of this rescue operation.
Are we tied off?
No Frank, it didn't work.
Our knuckle closed!
Will, use hand signals!
Hand signals!
We tied on?
We're good! We're good!
What?
Oh shit.
Frank, the pin didn't fall!
Say again.
The what?
Will, are we tied on?
It's not gonna work.
The pin didn't fall.
What?
The pin didn't fall!
It's not locking!
Alright, well, look.
Try and get down there and see
what you can do. Be careful!
Be careful.
Will!
It's not slowing down.
It's gaining speed right now.
He's reaching down,
trying to couple...
Will, can you read me?
He's gone!
Will Colson is down.
We do not see him.
Chopper 43, can you zoom in?
We do not see the conductor,
Colson, Come on baby.
Will, can you read me?
Will!
Chopper 43, zoom in.
There he is. Will Colson.
As he struggles to pull
himself up,
looks like Will Colson
is in trouble.
The train is coupled.
I'm now being told that the
connection has been made.
It looks as though this
train is now attached.
1206 has been successfully
attached to 777.
But it looks like
Will Colson is injured.
You Alright?
I'm great.
Hey, hey, don't touch that!
Don't touch that boot!
Here, just wrap it up
with this.
Wrap it real tight,
all around.
You okay?
I'm Alright.
Barnes and Colson have caught
up to the runaway train.
Darcy. come on. Come on.
But the train continues to speed
in excess of 75 miles an hour,
heading to Stanton.
Connie, how far we got?
How far to Stanton? Over.
4 miles.
You guys are doing great.
You're cutting it close, though.
How's Will?
He's...
He's different, over.
Ready for a little
tug-of-war?
Let's do it.
Match our speed with theirs.
Frank, we're gonna snap right off.
No, we're not, we're not.
We're just stretching, that's all.
We're just stretching.
Here in Stanton,
the evacuation procedures
continue for the entire town.
This is the town where that mainline train
track turns into an elevated curve.
They say there is virtually
no chance
this speeding,
out-of-control train
will make it through
that curve.
We should be slowing down.
Which we're not.
Shoot.
Go to the dynamic.
Alternate full throttle.
Christ! Those cab brakes
are getting a workout.
...because of the highly
toxic nature of the cargo.
Come on, Frank.
Come on baby.
Ah!
What's our speed?
We're under 50.
Connie, how far away?
Three miles. FRA's got men on the
ground ready to hop onboard
as soon as you guys
get it under 20.
Alright, tell them be
ready to hop, over.
Shoot!
What is it?
We're gaining speed.
Consist is too heavy.
We're being dragged.
Connie!
I'm here, Frank.
We're gonna be coming
in too hot.
Let them know.
The limit on that
curve is 15.
I don't know if you can take it
much faster, maybe 20, 25 max?
We may not have a choice. Just
tell them it's gonna be real hot.
What about the braking
on the freight cars?
Good, good.
Alright, I'm on it.
Just sit down. No, no.
I've got it. Sit tight.
I'll go out. Sit down.
No, in fact, come here.
You sit here. I'll go out.
Just keep it at four.
- You alright? Take it easy.
- Yeah.
- Hold that dynamic at a four.
- Four.
Integrate it with the
throttle if you have to.
Hold it at a four,
integrate the throttle.
Burn the block out,
it doesn't matter.
Hey, don't get
sentimental on me.
Makes me think I'm gonna die.
Just hold that four.
Come on Frank.
AWVR officials have no comment.
Barnes is attempting to manually
brake the last car of 777.
He's actually running on top
of the grain cars and jumping...
Way to go, Frank.
Let's go, Frank.
Looks like 777 is slowing down.
We understand
this is some sort of
an attempt to try
and stop the train.
Yes! Come on.
Come on! You can do it!
Will, how fast you going?
34.
Alright, we're dropping 33.
The railroad spokesman
just confirmed he is...
Think it'll work?
...attempting to slow 777
by manually braking each car.
Theoretically.
Provided that locomotive's
independent brake holds out.
We continue to bring you live
coverage of this breaking news event
from the town of Stanton.
Emergency management officials
have created this perimeter.
This is the police.
Get off the roof.
You are being asked to evacuate
for your own safety.
Shit!
Frank!
Yeah, I hear you.
I hear you!
We just lost our brakes!
Looks like the brakes
have blown.
Shit!
Frank!
Frank, you alright?
I'm here Will!
What happened?
We're picking up speed again.
Can you still slow it down?
We're almost at the curve.
Frank, our engine
block's overheated.
I don't think those
hand brakes are gonna
have the muscle to stop
this thing.
We're creeping up fast.
Alright, well, just hang on
to the independent.
I'll tell you when.
Elevated and strictly Class 2, speed
restricted to 15 miles per hour.
Impact with at least
three of these buildings
directly below will
be unavoidable,
as will contact with all the
fuel storage tanks situated here.
Will? Will.
We're Alright.
we're Alright.
but we're picking up
speed again.
Will!
We're coming into the curve!
Get ready!
Will!
Hit that independent!
Hit that independent
as hard as you can!
Frank.
we're gonna rip right off.
Got no choice.
Will!
Hang on!
Hit it! Hit it again!
Now!
Frank, you alright?
We made it! We made it!
We're through the curve.
777 made it. It made it
through the Stanton curve.
777 is through the
Stanton curve,
but by no means
out of trouble.
777 is gaining speed. It is out
of control and has to derail.
Frank Barnes and
Will Colson will be
the victims of the
biggest rail disaster
in the history
of the northeast.
It looks like Frank Barnes
is making an all-out effort.
Good job.
This is a remarkable effort
now to get to the front of 777.
Frank!
We're at... We're at 60 and
we're going to hit 80 in no time!
He's not gonna make it.
Looks like the gap between
cars has stopped him.
You can do it!
But the train continues to speed
in excess of 75 miles an hour.
Frank! Frank!
Will, we got a problem here.
I don't think I can make it.
Oh God.
There's Ned!
Unbelievable.
- Hello.
- Ned, it's Connie.
I'm kind of busy right now.
Connie, I'll call you back.
Hey!
Come on!
Hop in the back of the truck!
Connie?
Connie, is that truck for us?
Yes it is, Will.
You can do this.
Will, you can do this!
Come on!
Looks like he's trying
to synchronize
the speed of the pickup
with the train.
Do it, you pussy!
Jump in the back!
Yes! Yes!
Yeah!
And look at what's
happening now.
The red pickup racing
to the front of 777.
Come on, Will.
Frank!
Go! Just go!
Go, go, go!
Go, go!
Ned Oldham is running out
of parallel road.
Come on, Will.
Drive, Ned!
He will attempt to
board this train.
Come on!
Shit!
God damn it!
I overshot it!
Come on.
There it is, kid!
Do it!
Come on, jump!
Do it! Jump!
Yes!
Go Dad!
Yeah! Yeah!
Yeah! Yes! Yes! Yes!
Oh my God!
Go! Go Will!
Will Colson successfully
making it into the cab,
now in control of 777.
Chopper 43 over
this remarkable aftermath.
We're talking about the
heroic work of two men,
Frank Barnes and Will Colson.
Southern Pennsylvania will
always be indebted to them.
Judas Priest, we did it!
We did it!
I knew once we got you up there,
we'd do it. I'm Ned Oldham.
It's all about precision.
Good job, kid.
Your foot's hurt. He cut his
foot! I think it's broken.
He cut his foot!
Let's get some medics!
Get over here, kiddo.
- Ned!
- You!
Ned, were you worried?
Was I worried?
Nah, not really.
It's all about precision. I wouldn't
have undertaken such a task...
Just got off the line
with corporate.
Oh yeah?
"Debt of gratitude" to
Blah, blah, blah.
Same here.
Felt pretty good, actually.
Yeah, it did actually.
...bringing it to a
successful conclusion.
What was your first reaction when
you realized what was happening?
I felt I was in
my comfort zone.
What'd they say
about your job?
They said it's mine
if I want to keep it.
They'd be stupid not
to give it to you.
Yeah, that's what I told them.
Said they better think about
giving me a better one too.
- How about me?
- How about you?
As you can see, the result
was a positive. Ned...
Do we have any better of an
idea as to how this happened?
Well, the thing that happened...
Thank you very much, Ned.
Everybody, this is Ned Oldham.
To answer that last question...
Sorry, I wonder if you
can help me.
Connie?
I can't decide which one of you,
I'm gonna kiss first.
Me.
Problem solved.
Go get him, Connie.
Alright, bring it on.
...to Frank Barnes
and Will Colson,
the engineer and the conductor
whose actions...
Your daughters?
Chopper 43, over and out.
♫ When the song come on
in the club
♫ Turn it up. Turn it up,
turn it up. Rewind!
♫ The dance train is
coming back again
♫ Extravaganza, you should
run and tell a friend
♫ Kings and queens are posted
at the bar
♫ Bucking down It's time to
take it off
♫ Walk that walk
Walk
♫ Show me how you move it
♫ Can you walk that talk?
Talk
♫ Put some snap into it
♫ Time to show it all
♫ The spotlight is on you
You better... Let's go!
♫ Work, work, work, work
♫ Work, you better work
♫ You better shake that thing
like a donkey
♫ And go hard for it
You better work
♫ You better swing from
a paw like a monkey
♫ And go hard for it
You better work
♫ Cause big girls get down
on the floor
♫ And make it jiggle, jiggle,
jiggle You ain't know
♫ Ain't no shame. It's the name
of the game
♫ Now everybody down to
the floor Here we go!
♫ We got the rhythm
of the beat
of the hands
♫ Let's get the rhythm
of the feet
♫ Jump in, jump out
Here we go
♫ Work, work, work
You better work