Created and Encoded by --  Bokutox -- of  www.YIFY-TORRENTS.com. The Best 720p/1080p/3d movies with the lowest file size on the internet.
He's never belonged to anyone
for more than five years.
Your time has passed.
Mine has come.
They're bastards, these people.
These followers of the white Christ.
Bastards.
A much travelled man once told me
that they eat their own God.
Eat his flesh, drink his blood.
Abominable.
And they hate us... want us dead.
So you pray to the gods to protect us.
We have many gods.
They've only got the one.
Can't let him go.
We need him.
You need money, chieftain.
Like everyone else.
It's the only way to reason
with the Christians.
You might as well get it from me.
Who are you?
Hood him.
Take him away.
What do you see?
Yourself?
When I die...
...you will go back to hell.
He's driven by hate.
It's how he survives.
Why he never loses.
He'll come because he has to come.
To finish it.
Do you like it?
My father gave it to me, I think.
Are you from the clans, warrior?
No.
Why does the boy speak for you?
Are you Christians?
Yes.
You're lying.
I wouldn't do that if I were you.
I've heard about him.
He's one of the biggest savages
in Sutherland.
Killed our chieftain's son,
and most of his men, as well.
Son.
Does the mute have a name?
His name is One-Eye.
One-Eye.
You can eat with us. Then we can talk.
Or at least, the boy can.
You need a name.
And you've only got one eye.
So... now you've got your freedom,
what do you plan to do with it?
I wanna go home.
Where is that?
Don't know.
Maybe he could bring us luck.
One-Eye...
I could use a good fighter like you.
We're God's own soldiers, warrior.
Heading for Jerusalem...
to reconquer the Holy Land.
There's great honour in it.
Riches. Land.
Isn't that right, soldier?
Yeah.
That's right.
Endless warfare.
It makes more tramps than heroes.
But you should come with us
to Jerusalem.
Your sins will be absolved,
whether you live or die.
You will see your loved ones again.
Boy.
Where does he come from?
He was brought up from hell.
So where is it, this hell?
On the other side of the ocean.
We're more than flesh and blood.
More than revenge.
All of these things go.
You should consider your soul.
That's where the real pain lies.
Do you think he'll come back?
If it's God's will.
My father told so many tales
of the Holy Land.
And I never tired of listening to him.
All about its beauty.
Its wealth.
Do you know what I do
when I'm scared?
I pray to Christ.
Do you know who he is?
He sacrificed his life...
...so that we could be free
from pain and misery.
You see, that's what we're doing.
We're going to protect his land,
his kingdom.
So you have to be strong.
Never seen a mist
like this before.
So far from a shore.
It's been how long?
Days?
Perhaps it's a curse.
It's not a curse.
It's just a mist, nothing more.
This ship is yours, Lord.
These men are yours, Lord.
These swords we bear are for you, Lord.
We ask you to send the wind
to lift this mist.
We ask you, Lord, to send the wind
to guide us on the path to your land,
to the Holy Land.
We ask you, Lord,
to put your hand with our hands,
to guide us to your kingdom.
Don't do it again. You'll die.
You're dead.
You see, that's what we are doing.
We are going to protect his land,
his kingdom.
So you have to be strong.
No winds.
No current.
It's a curse.
Do you think the boy
could be the cause of this?
Of course.
How are we gonna kill him?
I'll do it.
- It was the boy.
- Shut up!
- He killed one of our men.
- Back off.
- Do something.
- I warned you what would happen.
Now, back off.
The boy said he was from hell.
Maybe that's where we're going.
You want me to die?
It's fresh water.
It's a river.
I'm gonna show them
a man of God has arrived.
So... if we're not in the Holy Land...
...then where the hell are we?
Where did you get that?
Where is he?
Hello!
He killed him.
One-Eye's gonna kill us all.
One by one.
I had a dream about this once.
I couldn't find my way home...
...and then I realised I was dead.
What are we going to do
about our friend?
Leave a sword.
If he finds it, it's God's will.
We have to keep moving,
find out where we are.
It's the fucking mud!
Get us out of the fucking mud!
- Leave him!
- Help me!
Fuck off!
- Let's get ashore and fight!
- Shut up! Shut the fuck up!
Move!
Look at this.
Stone.
That's iron.
They're primitives.
God brought us out of that mist
for a reason.
We claim this land in his name.
How do we do that?
We're half starved.
Three men dead.
One missing.
Can you hear me?
We left your sword.
Can you not hear him?
He talks.
Who?
One-Eye.
What's he saying?
He says we're in hell.
I told you, he brought us here.
We have to leave this place.
We have to go into the forest.
Is he speaking through you now?
It's the only way out.
What do you mean, out?
Home.
- We have to go back.
- Back to that mist?
- Have you lost your mind?
- We have to find salt water.
- That's the road out of here.
- No.
We stay and show them
what men are capable of
when they act in the name of God.
We've raised the cross.
Now we bring the sword.
The heathen will be converted,
their sins cleansed,
a new Jerusalem established!
You promised us riches.
And the Holy Lands.
Well, One-Eye took us to hell.
And there is no God.
No.
We need to follow him.
My lifelong friend.
Will you turn your back on me?
Go on, then.
Turn your back on God.
Only men of faith deserve the riches
of my new Jerusalem!
I will build crosses
up and down the river
to guide our brothers
when they come to join us.
They'll bring women.
Our cities will stand
for a thousand years.
And you...
...spiritual advisor
in my new Jerusalem.
Could I ever forgive my father
for bringing me to this place?
I came here to beg forgiveness
from my sons.
I wasn't there when they died in battle.
It matters, doesn't it...
...how I leave?
Yes.
Tell me...
He says I'm gonna reach the sea.
Gonna build a new boat.
Gonna go home.
What does he say about me?
You're gonna die.
Then he's lying.
If he's lying...
why are you following him?
Why did I come here, One-Eye?
Why did I have to go through this?
Tell me.
I have to go back.
I have to be with my father.
Even if he's dead.
Your sons are dead...
...and you came here to be with them.