Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
Luke!!!
Oh my God!
Luke no!!!
Luke!!
Luke!!!
A werewolf!
One of the nobles!
You're a professional hunter, aren't you?!
Is there a tongue in your mouth,
or are you just being rude?
Or is that sword just for show?
Maybe you'll say something if
I take it from you?
Try this!
Not too bad!
but...
You're not the hunter I'm looking for!!
So...
Now, leave the sword
and take your fancy costume!
No wait!
I was wrong, you really are a hunter!
...and a vampire hunter too!!
I..I'm not wrong am I?
I'm sorry.
I know what I did was unforgivable,
but I had to see what you could do.
I need the best hunter I can find!!
And I need to show you something!!
This is...
I..It's the kiss of a powerful noble.
What's your name?
It's Doris Lang.
Will you take this job for me?
I don't have much money, but...
I can feed you three meals a day.
and as for the rest...
I swear, you can do
whatever you want with me.
When did the noble attack you?
Does that mean you'll do it?!
Dang!
Hey Sis!
Dan!
Hey wait! I'll do that
for you mister.
Oh wow!
Your horse is a DL4 cyborg! Huh?
I guess you're the kind who
doesn't talk a whole lot. Right mister?
My friend Dr. Ferringo says
there are two kinds of quiet men.
The kind who stays silent
because they're thinkin' bad things...
and the ones who've seen
a lot of bad things,
and don't want to talk about them
more than they have to.
So...
I'm guessin' that you're
more like the second type, right?
I mean, you seem okay to me!
Well hello, Doris!
Greco...
I see by your collar the rumors were true.
W...what are you talking about?
Just somethin' I'd like to chew over
with your toothsome self.
So what do you want?
Spare me the biting tone.
I'm not the one they say
was nibbled on by the Count.
And what does that mean!?
It means, you might want
to keep your voice down.
Or don't you care
if sweet little Danny overhears the truth?
The thing is,
I'm hurt you didn't come to me
about this first.
After all, I'm not only the mayor's son,
but I can hire much better hunters
than that saddle tramp you found.
That's just what friends do.
I'm willing to overlook all our
unfortunate past history.
And all you have to do is ma...
What the hell is wrong with you?!
That hurt!
And I don't like being hit on either!
Look Doris,
I'm just trying to say
that I'm worried about you.
And that I'm here in your time of need.
If you think that you can
vie my gratitude that easily,
think again!
I've seen far too many decent people suffer
because of the actions of you and your cronies!
You're so adorable
when you're being self righteous.
I can't stand it.
Now how about you shut up and...
You little trollop!
No one does that to me!
Damn!
Hey boss, you okay?
Everyone, listen up!
Doris Lang was attacked by the Count!
She's been infected with vampirism!
It's true.
That's why she hired that hunter!
Oh sis...?
So you're
a vampire hunter are you?
That's right.
My God Doris...are you...?
Say something sis...
Hmm yup.
It's just as I said isn't it daddy?
No way!
She's fine!
And you're just spreading lies
'cause she turned you down!
What'd you say
you little brat!
Why I oughta kick your...
Greco!
But, pa!
That kid just called me a stickin' liar!
You're a fool who's
interrupting important business.
Wait outside!
And as for you Miss Lang,
you know the rules.
Anyone who's been bitten,
must go to the camp.
Sheriff!
No, you can't do this!
You can't take my sister!
Please think about this sheriff.
That camp isn't fit
for human habitation.
It's worse than a pigsty.
As the town doctor,
I can't condone sending this girl
to live in a wreck that
hasn't been used for 50 years.
That may be, but the law is the law.
And does the law
remember the nightmare
this town lived through 50 years ago
the last time that camp was used?
Exactly what happened 50 years ago?
There was a girl sheriff
a girl who was attacked, like Doris.
We locked her in the camp
for our own protection,
not hers.
And that so infuriated the Count
that he brutally murdered
30 villagers in retribution.
And what happened to girl Doctor?
She went completely mad
and died in the camp.
This wisest move
would be to let the girl stay free
until I've fullfilled my contract.
Those are brave words stranger,
but what if you fail?
The Count's not the only vampire up there.
If it comes down to that,
I swear that I will take my own life!
No sis!
Dan, listen...
Hello, welco...
Hello, Mr. Whatley.
I need the usual supplies.
A month's worth of fertilizer,
five packs of dried meat,
some canned goods.
Sorry, but we're all are sold out.
What?
But, Mr. Whatley!
What are you talking about Whatley?
Any fool can see
that you have plenty of stock.
Look Doc,
did you see how they skedaddled
when she came in?
She's in cahoots with the vampires.
I can't sell to her.
What?!
Cahoots?
It's only going to get harder going forward.
And it's alright to scream or cry.
How you choose to deal with it is up to you.
But promise me one thing Dan.
If you're going to cry,
don't do it around your sister.
Hold it in.
Tears are contagious
and right now she needs your
hope and encouragement.
Smile.
Even if it hurts.
That's what being a man means.
Feeling moody today are we?
You're not acting like yourself.
Protecting this girl,
counseling her brother...
and offering advice.
It's almost as though
you have a heart.
Don't tell me that
you've fall in love.
That's enough old fool!
Of course,
she did offer you
her body didn't she.
Not that you'd be interested in that.
The only bodies
that you're interested in
are dead nobles
stacked up like cordwood.
Poor D.
Fated to live a life
drenched in blood and carnage.
Are you jealous for the warmth
of a real human being?
Thank you for your help this afternoon.
I know you talked to Dan.
He's been trying hard
to keep my spirits up.
My father was a hunter too.
Werewolf, not vampire.
That's how I knew
what kind of skills to look for.
"If you should ever have to fight
against the nobility."
He said.
"You need a hunter who specializes in them."
No one else stands a chance.
So, what can you tell me about the nobles?
Tomorrow is the "Woman's Moon".
"Woman's Moon"?
You mean the red moon
that appears once a month?
Yes.
The nobles consider blood
taken under that moon impure,
unfit to drink.
Which means that if someone comes for you
it will be tonight.
So who is this noble I seek?
Count Magnus Lee.
It's said that he ruled this land
long before our village was established.
However, years ago he disappearred...
and most thought him gone forever.
But then the light reappeared in his castle
two years ago
and we knew he had returned.
Some say he's 5,000
or even 10,000 years old.
In either case, he's incredibly old,
and powerful.
Ten thousand years...
a vampire that old will be formidable.
Here they come.
How are you going to fight them?
I'll want to fight beside you.
Crosses and garlic will have no effect
on this advance guard.
The nobility expect such tricks.
That's why they'll attack first
using mutants and werewolves.
So, she's hired a bodyguard has she?
Exactly the sort of thing one would
expect from a lowly human.
Where is the Count?
I've been told a girl resides here
whose beauty is unrivaled in this land.
One whose blood is like
the sweetest ambrosia.
Or so my father says.
Leastway, he sent me
to fetch his newest play thing.
But first, in so much as she's failed
to deliver herself to his table.
The lowly human must be punished.
As for you,
you shall die a horrible death.
And then the girl will be
dealt with at our leisure.
I am Rei-Ginsei,
and my master commands me
to slaughter all fools such as you.
Now you die!
You're better than I expected,
but that ends now.
I've been playing with you.
Interesting...
I've heard rumors about a mutant
who could warp the fabric
of time and space.
Would that be you?
That it would.
And now I shall take your head.
That's impossible!
I see, he is a dhampir...
Rei, I shall handle this.
But I was about to...
I said fall back!
If that is your wish...noble mistress...
So, a dhampir?
I've never seen one before.
No doubt the bastard offspring
of some noble's human dalliance!
A more vexing problem than mere humans!
My business
is with your master and not you girl.
I'd prefer not to kill you.
How dare you!
As if some lowly dhampir could defeat me?!
Go back to your master and tell him this...
you are but transient guests on this planet.
Fated to return to the darkness.
Did he just say transient guests?
Has my daughter returned yet?
No, the fools acted without
begging my leave...
but I'll deal with them later.
A dhampir you say?
One so formidable that
L'armica and Rei had to retreat?
How very unexpected...
and intriguing.
Something to anticipate after so long.
Oh Count Dracula,
our most sacred ancestor!
Save my father from his folly.
Convince him that his plan
to bring a lowly human
into the fold of our family can only
end in pain and disaster.
I can not allow him to foolishly
taint our noble blood.
Please Dracula...
help me!
Lady L'armica,
you should return to your room now.
I don't recall giving you
leave to speak you mutant worm.
That may be...
but I was just admonished by the Count
for our failure to fulfill his orders.
And it is he, not I,
who commands you to your room mistress.
Did I say that you can touch me,
you wretch!
I know you seek to ingratiate
yourself with my father.
To become part of our noble family.
But you remain blind to the truth
of your own lowly lineage.
As if we would allow one of such debased
blood to become part of this family!
D, this is too easy...
it's a trap!
I know it is.
Ghost beast!
Let's try this!
So, we meet again hunter.
My, not only have you managed
to escape our ghost jaguar,
but your arms are still
attached to your body.
Truly you are a dhampir
to be reckoned with.
I would prefer to settle our
matter from yesterday personally.
However, the count has given
me specific instructions
regarding your destination.
So...
I told you this was a trap.
Didn't I?
Woah...
These must be ruins from the war
10,000 years ago.
Talk about putting everything else
into proper perspective.
Who are you sir?
Why don't you answer?
Who are you three?
Who are we three?
This is what we are!
So, you're lamia!
Clever...clever...
so clever...
We sisters are the infamous
Midwich Medusas!
Sister...it's been so long...
Shall we savor his taste slowly.
Yes! Let us sap his life essense.
To the marrow of his bone!
Please, have courage child.
He's certain to be back soon.
That man's forged more
from steel than flesh.
And I doubt he'll be beaten so easily.
Say...you're not falling for him are you?!
Oh my god, you are!
Trust me Doris!
He's not the kind
of man you think he is.
I'm not saying that he's an evil man,
but he has...dangerous eyes.
Dangerous eyes?
Yes.
The eyes of a warrior.
A man who lives on the razor's edge,
between life and death.
When the violence has ended
he'll be gone.
They're here!
Quiet!
Cease struggling.
The Count's waited long enough.
If the Count wants me,
then just let the other go!!
Oh no!
I couldn't deprive my comrades
of all that fresh meat!
Wait...if anything happens to them,
I swear I'll bite my tongue
and kill myself.
The Count did instruct me to
bring you in intact and unharmed.
So, I accept your terms.
Now put that back in your mouth.
It's crude.
Oh sweet Doris,
come tomorrow you shall be
both nobility
and my bride.
Why resist the inevitable?
I'd rather die!
But I'll not be held as a prisoner
in this castle for long!
I'll be gone by morning light!
How droll.
But those impertinent lips will soon be mine.
Therefore, I will forgive such impudence
just this once.
But Doris,
if you think your hunter
will come to save you,
you might want to reconsider.
Behold your hero!
D!!
As you can see the sisters are
draining him of his vital essence.
Ah,
look at the sweet ecstasy on their faces.
They've been in the throws of pleasure
for half the day.
A normal man would
have perished in minutes.
But then he is a dhampir.
What?!
D is a...
he's a dhampir?
Oh my, you didn't know?
Yes, the baseborn result of a
liason between human and noble.
These things do happen.
Surprised?
Or could it be you...
find this more arousing than expected?
No! Stop it! You monster!
Ah yes.
You should retire to your
bedchamber shouldn't you.
Sleep...
Sleep for the remainder
of this cursed sanguine moon.
For tomorrow we will wed.
So much sustenance,
but will his endurance overwhelm us sisters?
His endurance overwhelms us.
No! Sisters he wakes!
This woman is to join
the Lee family father?
This is the slattern you chose
to take my mother's place?
You can't fight your lineage, can you?
Deny it all you want,
but when push comes to shove
the fangs are coming out!
That's enough.
Someone's feeling grumpy.
Too bad. It's still your destiny.
I wonder.
Do I really need two hands?
Fine...my lips are sealed.
What is it?
What is it about her that
my father cannot resist?
But I will not allow it!
You will never join the Lee bloodline
you human bitch!
Damn you!
Golem!
Gimlet!
I can't return to the
castle, until I've finished him.
Sis.
Sis!
Doris!
Dan. Where's D?
Oh he said that he was gonna go outside
and try to fix the damage to the wall.
Man that guy is sure awesome!
First he rescues you from that
horrible place all by himself.
And when he gets back
does he take a break?
No way! He just gets right
to doing what needs doin'.
It's like he doesn't even need to rest!
A noble!
That's a noble's carraige!
What's a noble doing here?
Oh what's wrong hunnykins?
Come on, let's get a room
so we can drink some more.
Back to the cat house
you floosies!
That's no way to treat a lady!
What's the lowdown pops!?
I..I..It's one of the
nobility's servants...
Yeah, I know! Hold still.
I need the key to the secret spy room.
I bring a message on behalf of the count.
Do you now...?
and would that message involve killing me?
No, that would be a fool's errand.
One such as I could never defeat you.
The price for failure is death.
I doubt that the Count will change
the rules of his castle
just to accommodate me.
Killing that man will be difficult.
So the Count has sent you this.
No, it can't be!
Is that what I think it is?
Yes.
The Time Bewitching Incense.
Time bewitching what?
D!! Have you seen Dan?
Your brother has been taken.
That's Dan's gun!
I don't understand.
I'm the one the nobility wants?
Why would they take my brother?
Just what does that letter say?
Let me see!
Is this some kind of code?
Yes.
It's written in a language
understood only by hunters
and professional assassins.
It says, that in order to save Dan,
I must come alone.
They're obviously
attempting to separate us.
I don't understand.
If they have Dan, why not
just order me to come?
It would seem the being who wrote this
has a personal score to settle as well.
And beyond that, the nobility would
consider it beneath their honor
to use the boy as bait to lure you
into their trap.
Beneath their honor!?
As if their kind has honor to begin with!
They're blood sucking monsters!
Um...
Present company excepted.
There's no reason to make exceptions.
To be born a dhampir is to be a monster.
The blood running in my veins
is that of the hated nobility.
But it's not the same.
I know that you only hide your true nature
to keep others from
worrying unnecessarily.
And I wish I hadn't learned the way I did.
Ah, you're here.
Where is the boy?
Mr. D!
Help me!!!
Quiet! I'll get you down
once I've killed your friend.
Just hang on to your patience.
Mr. D, I'm scared!!!
Bastard!
Let's finish this.
D, watch out!
That's Time Bewitching Incense!
It...it's not working!
Dan, please come home safely, please.
If you die...
Doris, it's me. Dr. Ferringo!
Doctor!!
The barrier's still up. Let me in!
Hold on, I'm coming!
Thank God you're here.
I've been with a sick patient
in the village.
I'm sorry for the nightmare
that you've endured,
and for taking so long.
But, I thought of a place
where we can be safe.
My hand!
Someone switched candles on me!
How sad.
Done in by your own stupidity.
It makes you question your life choices.
Doesn't it?
Damn it!
Do you have to be condescending as well?
Are you sure this place
really exists Doctor?
Yes.
I first discovered it when I was
returning from old man Harker's place
via the northern forest.
And then there it was.
An ancient stone building with some
kind of mysterious writing on its walls.
A safe house.
Something in that old structure
repels the vampires.
We'll wait there until
your brother's rescued.
One of the female nobles!
Whoa, whoa!
Doris, turn this cart around!
There's no room!
But I can handle this one!
Oh no you don't.
Doctor!! What are you doing!?
I was the doctor my dear...
but I've changed!
No! No!!!
Not you too.
What brings you out here my lady?
Um, the Count has ordered me
to take this one to the castle.
Bring her to me.
Yes mistress.
How strange, until yesterday this
girl was like my own granddaughter.
But seeing her now,
I realize that I was a fool for not
violating this beautiful body.
Do you suppose the Count
will let me have a taste
before he claims her and
sucks her sweet husk dry?
You annoy me.
No!!
Doris please...
No...Doctor!!
Why is this happening?
Everyone's gone.
The doctor, Dan and D.
D?
It's the dhampir you care about?
I'd rather die than become
Count Lee's bride.
Just kill me now.
This is all my father's doing.
Fine!
I don't care where you go
as long as that old fool can't find you.
What the...?!
G...Greco?!
This stuff is great...
have Time Bewitching Incense will travel.
I thought it would blind vampires,
but judging by that show
it burns like unholy heck.
And why does someone like you have it?
Does it matter?
The important thing is I
have the Count's daughter.
And that'll let me setup a
real sweetheart deal, sweetheart.
And just what does that mean?
I thought I might draw
the Count out and kill him.
That'll be easy with this
Time Bewitching Incense.
But a favor that size requires
a little advance payment.
What...?!
No pressure.
I can leave you with fangy here.
Or say yes Greco dearest
and we'll be counting
the Count's treasure.
Stop! It's so bright!
You know, you're looking
a little pale Doris dear.
It's a good thing you have someone
like me to protect you, isn't it?
And now I've got a good look.
This one's not too shabby.
Why'd I think female nobility
would be dried up old bats?
Human stop!
Kill me now and be done with it!
Looks like there's a little life left
in the unliving dead girl still, huh?
Kill me already!
I'd rather burn in hell a thousand years
than endure your voice another second!
Why you coffin dwellin' tramp!
Kill me! Do it now or I promise I'll
kill you when I have the chance!
Oh enough already!
It's not like I can't lure the Count
out with your staked corpse!
Leave her alone!
She can't even defend herself!!
I'm just making a point!
Oh come on!
Hey sis!
Dan?
Is that you?
Sis, are you okay?
Dan, you're really alive!
Dan!
Oh man.
The Doc too...
I had completely given up
hope at that point.
I couldn't have lived if I had lost you.
You gotta be stronger sis!
It's like Mr. D says,
"If you give up, you've already lost".
Yes...but...
You're not going to kill me?
Aw don't be stupid!
Only yellow bellied rats kill girls.
I know that this seems strange to you,
but D isn't like the men you've known.
It's not in his nature
to kill for no reason.
You expect me to react like a lowly human,
but I'm not.
Love and emotions do
not exist in our world.
The only law is the
survival of the fittest.
The strong rule.
While the weak, like you humans, serve.
So many vampires believe that, and yet...
Your Sacred Ancestor
taught otherwise.
Our Sacred...
Ancestor?
D, the shower...
D...
...D!
Oh D...
Is something wrong?
I was afraid you'd left.
After everything that's
happened I thought you might be...
Well, I said some pretty terrible things
and I'm so sorry.
No, it's alright Doris.
I'm used to it.
The thing is, I keep thinking
about what happened to my father.
Even though he was a werewolf hunter.
In the end he was forced to fight vampires.
Nobody can fight forever...
and I was thinking...
that you and I can go someplace and...
That's not possible.
But...
I would only bring you pain and suffering.
But that's not true at all!
And I...
I don't want you to die D!
Enough!
No! I just want to be close to you.
Just this once.
It's all right.
Take my blood.
D please.
I can't...
Why can't you at least
be honest with yourself?
So your blood is cursed.
That girl was ready for it
to rise to the occasion.
The great and powerful dhampir.
You know what your father would have done.
That's enough!
Yeah, yeah, whatever...
Oh this bites!
But at least...
I managed to hold onto
the Time Bewitching Incense.
So you're the one who stole it!
No...no wait, please!
As you wish.
You'll die slowly.
The Incense!
You were kind enough to let me live, but
I can't be so generous.
You bastard!
Such strong languange.
Take this!
My, what a pretty corpse.
You lose.
And now we're even.
D!
D! Are you alive?!
Mr. D wake up!
You gotta open your eyes!
Mr. D?
D?
D!
Could he...
...be dead?
You've become such a stubborn child.
Please father...
I'm begging you!
You must reconsider this wedding!
You can't let that lowborn
human filth join our family!
Can't I?
My life has lasted eons
and if taking her gives me pleasure
I shall do so.
But do not mistake this
for anything permanent.
This girl is but a plaything
for my entertainment.
One that I will use and discard.
Father, can't you see how
dangerous this creature is!?
The whole family is at risk!
Foolish girl!
Taking one human into our fold
is hardly enough to cause the fall
of the house of Lee.
For if it were...
it would have fallen
when I took your mother.
The lowly human whose
blood runs in your veins.
I have lived in this world for ten thousand years
and you lack the capacity to understand
what that truly means.
When years cease to have meaning
boredom is a mortal foe.
It is a war for constant stimulation
and if that means debasing our line with humans
then so be it.
And after all...
since we took control of their lands
the humans owe us something
in exchange for the simple
existences our efforts allow them.
When you consider that...
a human female every fifty
years or so is nothing.
Father, I demand you
take back that falsehood!
But it's all true my dear.
Your mother was human.
No!
Ironic isn't it?
All the pride of a true noble
despite your parentage.
However, as I can't allow your
tantrums to disturb my wedding,
I shall leave you here
until your temper has abated.
My lord...
I would ask you to fulfill your promise.
What promise is that?
The gift of immortality and
eternal youth, as you promised.
To the contrary, you should
be grateful I let you live.
Eternal youth for your repeated failures.
I suggest you wait another fifty years
before you dare ask me that again.
You sniveling mutant fool.
Fifty years?!
Here...we go.
I swear, this guy is such a handful.
Uh-oh.
Damn!
Gotta move!
Not good!
Come on, time to wake up already!
Get a grip D!
Snap out of it!
Here it comes.
It's spotted us!
Wakey wakey!
Rise and shine!
Just move, damn it!
Now's not the time to sleep in!
Wake...up!
You big lummox!
Come on! Move...move damn it!
Moooove!
Well, we made it through that one somehow.
Sis.
Right.
Okay Sis.
Doris!!
Rei, stand aside.
Or die.
Your days are over Count Lee.
Wait fifty years you said.
Do you even remember
what fifty years is to us?
I lost my left hand because of you,
I watched all my comrades die
and for what?
But all that ends here and now!
You're going to die Count Lee!
Did you really think that
would work on me, you fool?
Good-bye Rei.
My, this day is turning out to be filled
with more wonderfully delightful diversions
than I'd ever dared to hope for.
How invigorating!
We congratulate
Count Magnus Lee
on taking his bride.
My bride and I thank you.
No female has ever caused
me so much trouble before.
Oh you.
You may call yourself nobility, but...
the real nobles died long ago.
In this world you are just transient guests.
Transient guests?
That's right!
The nobility in this castle are ghosts
forgotten by time.
It's time to return to the
world where you belong!
You never cease to amuse me.
You're a dhampir,
the product of some vampire's straying loins.
You think you can defeat me mongrel?
I'll finish you off,
and then have the girl as my main course.
Oh how pathetic you are!
One should know ones limits dhampir.
I can't imagine what you thought
hunting one such as I, but
you are no match for true nobility.
But wait...
it would be too dull to dispatch
you in the same manner as Rei.
Ah yes...
I don't know how many
you've put down with this blade...
but its steel is certainly accustomed
to killing your own kind.
And it's only fitting that you
die by your own sword.
It can't be!
What are you?
No Sis!
Don't do it!! Stop!
Dan?
Doris!
Hang on Sis.
La...L'armica, what are you doing?
Strike them down! I command you!
Father, you must end this madness, now!
Or our family will die.
W...what?!
Desire for this girl has made
you forget the pride of nobility.
F...foolish child!
No...it can't be!
You...
...the offspring of our sacred ancestor?!
D...
...ancestor...
...shall I stay and die here with my father?
I'm a man.
Not your sacred ancestor.
I am a noble...
...and if our sacred ancestor
says we must die,
then it is my duty to obey.
No, human blood flows in
your veins as it does mine.
As a dhampir you can make your own choice.
To live without the trappings
and flawed rules of the nobility.
But I...
...I am a pure noble!
My blood pure and unpoluted.
D!
Mr. D!
I am a noble, this is my fate!
Hey D!
Mr. D!
D!
D!!
Mr. D!!!
D!!!
D!
Bye!
Good-bye D!!!
We love you!!
Please rate this subtitle at www.osdb.link/8ubpe
Help other users to choose the best subtitles