Subtitle by anana
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
Here he comes!
Hail Mary,
full of grace,
the Lord is with thee.
Blessed art thou
among women,
blessed is the Lord,
Jesus Christ.
We've been
expecting you.
I'm Alan Elbourne,
and I'm the one
that summoned you here
today for this reason...
Go on.
I'm listening.
It's about my sister
Charlotte.
Two nights ago,
she disappeared.
She was in bed, sleeping.
It was the middle
of the night.
Several people told us they saw
a carriage outside our house.
The carriage...
belonged to Meier Link,
the vampire.
I organized a search party
of fifty men,
but it was no use.
We couldn't find them.
We were ambushed.
Hyah!
He took my sister
and killed my friends.
That's just a down payment.
You'll get the rest
when you find her...
$10 million.
But you better move fast.
You've got
some competition.
I've hired
the Markus brothers,
and they've got
a head start on you.
I don't think so.
Huh?
It may be too late
for her.
Your sister may already
have been tempted.
What then?
You have to get there
before that happens!
- What do you think we're paying you for?
- That's enough!
My son is emotional.
Please excuse him.
This has been difficult
for all of us.
If you knew my daughter,
you'd understand.
She's kind and beautiful
and her loss is more
than this old soul can bear.
Now I need to ask
you something.
If you find her changed,
can you see that her death
is without suffering?
Be kind to her, please.
No. No!
We can't do that!
It isn't right!
No, she won't
be changed.
- You're talking about your daughter!
- Alan, listen to me.
It's not easy
to ask him for this,
but it's something
that must be done.
I'm sorry.
You understand.
I understand
your position, but...
$10 million is not enough.
What?!
How dare you?!
Stop it!
Hold your fire!
I said stop!
I'll double the price.
I'll give you
20 million.
Just bring her back,
one way or the other.
Aah! Aah!
Did you see a carriage
go by here
with four horses
in front?
Uh-uh.
Let me go!
L-Let me go!
Aah!
You're lying.
Oh, damn.
We got company...
Lots of company.
Look out!
Oh, man.
ls everybody OK?
Yeah.
Uh-huh.
Do you believe that?
The place
is overrun with them.
He must've been here
already.
Well, come on.
Ready or not,
here they come.
It's zombie time.
Yeah!
Come and get it,
zombies!
Amen to that.
Leila, are you there?
It won't take long,
Grove.
Just stay in the tank.
Lock and load.
Uhh!
Yaah!
Not so fast, buddy.
And... fire.
Gotcha.
Rest in peace. Huh?
You hear that?
Sounds like a horse.
It's moving.
Uphill.
Let me try.
Right.
Right about...
Hmm.
Right there.
Huh?
Beautiful,
just beautiful.
I applaud you, stranger.
Tell me what
you're doing here.
If we're in the same game,
we should be friends.
Tell me your name.
Mine's Borgoff-
Borgoff Markus.
D-
Ah, so that's the guy-
the dunpeal hunter.
I've heard about him.
He's amazing.
Wake up, Borgoff.
He's the competition,
not some buddy of ours.
Come on,
what are we doing here?
We just helped him.
Think about it.
Yeah, he's right.
I agree with him about that.
We help him too much, and
he'll take all the money.
If it wasn't for us,
he'd be dead by now.
We do the work,
and he gets the reward.
Aw, you boys
should relax.
We just did the famous
dunpeal a little favor is all.
A little favor
we can't afford.
Hey, you ever
hear the one
about the owl
and the squirrel?
The squirrel
works all summer
storing away stuff
for the winter,
all kinds of
nuts and seeds.
He works real hard.
Then one day, just
before the first snow,
he goes outside for
one last look around,
when all of a sudden,
this owl swoops down
and grabs him,
carries him off.
"Ah, what a shame,"
says the squirrel.
"What's going to happen
to all
that good food?"
Heh heh heh heh!
Ha ha!
Ah,
that's a good one.
Yeah, hilarious.
You get it, you guys?
That stupid squirrel
is all, like-huh?
Leila.
Hey, Leila,
what's the rush?
What's with her?
So you're
outnumbered 4 to 1.
So what?
They do have
a head start,
but when
the sun comes up,
the heat
will slow 'em down.
Speaking of sun and heat,
I know I don't need
to remind you
of your susceptibility.
It's called
heat syndrome,
- and the last time you ignored it, you almost-
Don't worry.
I hate it
when you say that.
What-what are those?
Tracks?
Let me see.
Yes. These are definitely
their tracks.
6 hours old, I'd say.
OK. Uhh.
I'm suffocating now.
Hey, what was that?
That's funny.
I could've sworn
I heard something.
Quiet.
Sandmantas,
most likely.
Aah! Aah!
Aah!
Great flesh!
Sandmantas galore.
Talk about
your prehistoric pigeons.
They're filthy animals.
You know, they're just filthy.
Well, I guess we'd better
just turn back.
It's a shame, really,
'cause, you know,
we could've-
hey, whoa! Whoa, whoa!
Hey! No, no.
Go back, man.
Go back.
Come on.
You're crazy!
Come on, man.
Please,
let's just go back.
No, no!
Here we go! Oh!
Yaah! Not wise.
Yaah!
Aah!
Ohh!
All right, that's enough.
That was good.
OK, now, we survived that.
Could we stop?
Did you ever hear
the expression
"Too close for comfort"?
'Cause that was
damn uncomfortable.
What is it?
A resting house?
I didn't think anybody
had those anymore.
He must be in there.
Wow, it blends in nicely.
OK. Whoa.
Here we are.
OK, I can see 'em.
How many are there?
Two, I think-
- a man and a woman.
- Look out for the exit door.
OK. No door.
No door there.
Still no door.
No.
Are you sure
about that door?
No. No.
What was that?
She's out of her mind!
Door! Door!
You're dead!
Aah! Aah!
Uhh!
Uhh! Ohh! Uhh! Uhh!
I'm here
for the young woman.
I wouldn't recommend it,
dunpeal.
Taking on a vampire
at night
is a mission
for morons and fools.
Which are you?
She's here by
her own choice, dunpeal.
So unless
you're the kind of man
who would take a woman
against her will for the money in it-
and I'm sure
it's a lot-
I suggest you save
your sorry ass now
and leave us
to travel in peace.
I would if I could
believe you, Meier.
Your credibility,
however,
is less than impeccable
under the circumstances.
You kidnapped the girl.
Aah!
Meier!
Uhh!
Ow, my nose! My nose!
What happened?
What'd I miss?
She called out
his name.
It may be true,
what he said.
Nah,
she's just ignorant.
She's a child.
She doesn't know him yet.
She doesn't know
what he's capable of.
Ooh.
Oh, that poor girl.
She's-she's bleeding
pretty bad.
I mean,
she won't last long.
It's a shame, really...
To waste all
that good blood, I mean.
Come on, admit it.
You're tempted.
I mean, I know you are.
Uhh...
Ma.
Mmm.
Mother.
Wait. I was
just kidding, you know?
Come on, let's go.
We got work to do.
The money-come on,
think of the money.
Huh?
Uhh.
Hey, what did you
do to me?
I bound your wound
and stopped your bleeding.
That's all.
Oh, I get it.
You think
you can just go ahead
and tear off the clothes
of whoever you come across.
That's what you think,
isn't it, dunpeal?
You should go back home
and nurse your wounds.
What are you,
my mother?
You called out
for your mother before.
I thought you might be
needing her.
Hey!
Uhh. Uhh.
Uhh.
I see her.
When the last
vampire is extinct,
who will mourn
our passing?
Will she?
Will anyone?
Can anyone understand
this pain, this loneliness?
I told you so,
didn't I?
Hmm? I said
leave the girl alone.
She's trouble.
She's competition,
you know.
You aided and abetted
the enemy.
I hope this is
the right way.
Trust me.
I know how they think,
these vampires.
When they're threatened,
they all head
for Barbarois.
They're so predictable.
Barbarois, yeah.
I really hate that place.
It's full of lunatics
and monsters
and that old crazy man,
you know?
Does it hurt
very much, Leila?
Leila?
Huh?
Your injury-
does it hurt you?
Oh, no,
it's fine.
Inn-
Grove,
you should lie down.
You look tired.
You need to rest.
Don't worry
about me.
Leila...
Who dressed the wound?
Was it him?
You can tell me.
It was him, wasn't it?
The dunpeal hunter?
Mm-hmm.
Leila,
I'm warning you-
He-he's trouble.
He's against us.
I don't know
why he did that.
Grove, please don't
tell anyone, OK?
He stopped there,
but what for?
Let's find out.
Nolt and Kyle,
you come with me.
Leila, you stay in here
with Grove.
OK, is everybody ready?
- Always.
- Ready. Yeah.
Hey, Nolt,
see what's going on
in there, will you?
It may be a trap.
Yeah.
We'll cover you.
It'll be my pleasure,
gentlemen.
Aah!
Huh?
It's nothing but
a lousy piece of cloth.
What the hell?
Bastard.
Unbelievable.
Hey, watch out!
Huh?
So...
You dare to enter
Barbarois.
I assume it's arrogance
and not stupidity
that brings you here,
gentlemen.
Or perhaps
it's ignorance.
You're skillful hunters,
I can see,
but you are no match
for the Barbarois.
5,000 years of isolation
have made us invincible.
Aah! Uhh!
Huh?
What?
What the hell's going on?
The shadow...
Watch out
for the shadow.
What are you
talking about?
The shadow?
What do you mean?
Hey, Nolt?
Hey, Nolt, what the hell
happened to you, huh?
He-he's dead.
No, he's not!
Come on, Nolt.
Come on!
Snap out of it!
Oh, my god!
Damn it, come on!
I need you!
Oh, God!
Oh!
Oh, God,
we're getting close.
Those are the windmills
of the Barbarois.
I really wish
you'd turn back.
There must be
another way.
There isn't.
I am D the hunter.
I have business
with the Barbarois.
Oh, no.
So, I see
you have dismounted.
You have respect
for your elders.
That's very considerate
indeed.
I want you to stop
your protection
of Meier Link.
You what?
Ha ha ha. You know,
you make me laugh.
That's a good one.
I see you are
a very humorous young man.
And beautiful, too,
I might add.
Or does that make you
uncomfortable
to have an old lech
like me admire you so?
You take me for a fool.
Someone paid me
$100 million
to protect Meier Link.
Can you top that?
Well, you drive a hard
bargain there, old man.
What if I can?
You really are entertaining me,
Mr. Stranger.
I suppose you know
our reputation.
The Barbarois serve
the people of the night,
and after 5,000 years,
I don't think we're about
to change our stripes
any time soon.
Although,
if we did for anyone,
it would be for you.
I have seen
many a dunpeal,
but somebody like you,
I've never seen before.
That's why
it's such a pity
that you have to die.
I really can't let you
leave here alive,
now, can I?
I'm afraid you
have to die, stranger.
So sorry.
The Barbarois
are great warriors.
You are a warrior, too,
no doubt,
and although
you may kill some of us,
in the end,
we will prevail.
I have sworn
to protect the carriage.
Prepare to die.
Fool.
What's he doing
in there?
Borgoff,
are we ready yet?
Grove...
We have no choice.
We need your help
on this, Grove.
Think you can do it
there, man?
Give it to me.
I'm waiting.
Don't push yourself
too hard now.
I mean it, OK?
I want you back.
You know,
I really have
nothing against
the Barbarois personally.
It's a shame I'll have
to kill so many of you.
Indeed,
I admire your loyalty
and your devotion
to duty.
Yet I wonder
about the fairness
when you allow one
to fight against so many.
But if that
will entertain you...
Ohh.
I see.
Well, you make
a good argument, young man.
How interesting.
Old man...
I think the fellow
is right.
Please allow
the three of us
to entertain
our young guest here,
unless he thinks
that's unfair.
Three against one-
how unfair.
unfair.
That's enough.
You mock us with your
ridiculous antics, Benge.
I will not have you
distracting us
from the job at hand,
which is the protection
of the carriage.
We'll do things
my way. Huh?
What the devil is that?
Go for it, Grove!
Go for it!
Kill all those guys!
Kill every last
one of them!
Come on, Grove.
Hold on.
Get the carriage out, now!
Follow me, Tinkerbell.
I'm waiting for you.
Uhh!
Yaah!
Grove.
I've got to say this,
I admire that young
hunter's spirit,
although he doesn't
stand a chance
against Benge
and the others.
Still, it's a pity
I'll miss the show.
Oh, well.
C'est la vie.
Wake up, D.
What's wrong with you?
It's not fair.
I'll show you
what's not fair.
Stay there
till you rot, hunter.
Aw, phooey, suckers.
Stop.
I beg you.
Say good night.
Kyle, did you happen to see
where that girl went?
Maybe she got caught
in the wheels.
Go look.
Aah!
Nice, Caroline,
very nice.
A little crude,
but effective.
They're all yours.
That freakin' monster.
Is everybody all right?
Yeah,
but Kyle was outside.
He was up on top.
Kyle. Kyle. Where the hell
are you, Kyle?
Down here.
You OK?
Quiet.
They're still around.
No.
Damn.
That idiot.
Well, how convenient
this is for me.
Come on out here
so I can finish the job.
Your time is up.
Come on, you cowards!
You're going to pay
for the pain
you caused my brother.
Hey,
D, are you awake?
I need your help
to swallow up
this spell.
You're a slave driver,
you know that?
Aah!
Hey, remember to watch out
for the shadow, huh?
Try and stay still.
Easier said
than done.
And keep
your mouth shut.
Aah! Aah! Ahh! Ahh!
That was close.
Waah!
Well, the tank
is full of holes.
The fuel's all gone.
We can't drive it
like this anyway.
What are we
going to do?
What should we do?
Borgoff, any idea?
How's Grove?
Honestly,
not too great.
Borgoff, wake up.
What are you thinking
about over there?
Oh, nothing, really.
I was just thinking
about the carriage.
Wonder where it is
by now.
Well hell, man,
at this point,
it's pretty much
anybody's guess.
If you want my opinion,
I'd say they're either
setting sail
from the port of Ebral
or hiding somewhere
deep in the Granerj
mountain range.
I sure hope so.
Anyway, we still
have to get some fuel,
and the town of Garucia
isn't that far away from here.
Kyle, you go with Leila.
I'll stay here
and do the repairs.
"if you are seeking
the pathway to the stars,
"come to me. I pray
for your safe arrival
with all my heart."
"The pathway
to the stars..."
I don't know about
you, but I sure miss that horse.
What was his name?
Oh, the silent
treatment, huh?
Well, I got two words
heat syndrome.
Look. Look, I know
I'm a parasite,
but haven't I always been
a helpful parasite?
Now, you may not care
if you die from heat,
but becoming
a piece of beef jerky
is not a lifelong
ambition of mine.
Yeah, well, what's
the sound of one hand yapping?
How much?
Oh, no.
Keep your money.
Come on.
Just take it.
Let's go.
Leila! Oh, I see.
It's him, isn't it?
Kyle, why don't you
start back without me?
There's something
I want to do here first.
Back off.
Have I told you
you're quite irresistible
in that sexy,
skintight getup?
No. Tell me about it.
I just did.
You make sure you watch
your back with that guy, Leila.
I'd like a beer.
I've just been admiring
your fancy weapon there.
Don't worry. I have no plans
to use it anytime soon.
That's good.
That's good,
because I have no plans
to let you keep it.
Give it up.
You heard me,
little girl.
Uhh!
Hmm. Thank you.
Well, here's to you,
sheriff.
I'd buy you
a drink, but-
Thank you,
but no, thanks.
Oh, OK.
I was just gonna say
you must
be awfully busy
with that new dunpeal
hunter in the town now.
What dunpeal hunter?
I'd like to buy
that horse.
$300,000.
And if you don't like
the price, go somewhere else.
Subtitle by anana
Freeze! Put your hands
where I can see 'em! Now!
Sheriff, he paid
good money for that.
What are you doing?
Take your money and go.
We don't want you here.
We don't sell to dunpeals
in this town.
Understand?
Understand me,
dunpeal?
You understand.
Wait a minute.
That's my horse you're
talking about there,
and I'll sell it
to whoever I want
if they can afford
the price I'm asking.
You can't do that.
We have laws against it, Polk-
good laws-
and for a damn good reason.
What laws?
Don't play coy,
Polk. You know as well as I,
dunpeals aren't allowed.
Not allowed. Right.
I remember a time
not that long ago
when we had vampires
and dunpeals both
around here, but...
And that's why
we have the law!
Listen to me whether
you want to hear it or not.
You weren't even born
when this happened.
Do yourself a favor
and listen to the story.
I'm going to tell you
about the time
when the children
were kidnapped.
There were ten children
altogether-
Yeah, I heard
about that time.
The kidnappers
turned out
to be vampires,
of course,
and so the townspeople
pooled their money
to hire
a vampire hunter.
They wanted the best.
And when
the hunter came,
he was a very strong
and quiet man,
and he did his job, too,
which was to return
the children safely back
into their parent's
homes.
It wasn't easy,
but many vampires
died by his hands
before this job
was over with.
And when it was over
and the children
were back home,
the people
attacked the man.
They said he was a dunpeal
half-vampire himself,
so they punished him.
Can't say I blame them
for doing that.
You can't trust 'em.
That's all that's about.
They were right
about that part, Polk.
He did the job.
I see, then, I'll
have to take matters
into my own hands.
Let him go!
And what is that?
What does it
look like, idiot?
Put down your guns!
Polk, you can't know
what you're doing.
Put it down.
I know exactly
what I'm doing.
You don't know!
Put it down now, you old fool!
I would much rather
be an old fool
than what you are,
sheriff.
Now, don't shoot.
I can tell you
I won't think twice
about using this weapon.
I might even enjoy it.
Get on your horse,
stranger.
Thank you.
No. It's only fitting
I thank you.
It's the least I can do.
I may be just an old
fool now, stranger,
but I could never forget
a face like yours.
And I'll never forget
what you done for me
back then.
That's right.
I was one of them kids.
And I always felt bad
about that.
The way you was treated.
How nobody stopped you.
Nobody thanked you.
Instead, the ignorant bastards
ran you
right out of our town.
So it's true, isn't it,
what they say
about you dunpeals?
You don't age. Now, go.
I'm getting tired.
Where's Benge?
What's taking him so long?
Well, the horses
are rested now.
We better go. Come on.
Master, what is it?
May I help you, sir?
It's still light
outside, master!
What?
Leave her
alone, Machira.
Yes, sir.
She misses the sunlight.
Let her enjoy it.
I am D, a hunter.
Your father sent me.
Don't be afraid.
I won't hurt you.
You sit in the sunlight.
You must not be changed.
So, why do you
stay with him?
Last night
in the carriage,
you called out his name.
Why did you
call for him?
I suppose my father
has not told you
that I'm in love
with Meier.
You don't know
who he is.
You can't be
in love with him.
Well, I am. If you only knew
how good he's been to me.
I love him.
Please believe me.
No one else will.
You don't understand.
He is what he is,
Charlotte.
You can't change him.
He'll take you in time,
and when that happens,
I will have to kill you.
Fine. Kill me then.
I would rather die than
to go anywhere without him.
Don't take me back there!
I mean it!
I simply could not live
without Meier.
How sweet
that is. Ha!
She loves a vampire.
So very sweet.
Idiot!
You stupid girl!
Get up! We're going!
Leave me alone!
You'll do what I say!
Do you have any idea
how many people have died
at the hands
of your beloved Meier,
this vampire
you want to protect?
None!
You fool! And you!
You stay right where
you are, my friend.
Sorry, but I really don't
want to have to share
any of my profits.
You understand, don't you?
It's business.
Above you.
Aah!
What's wrong?
Tell me!
Too much sun!
I warned you about the heat,
but you don't listen!
Come on! You can't survive
unless you dig a hole!
You need to bury yourself!
Oh! Ha ha ha ha!
Hurry!
Leila?
Leila, are you there?
Come in, Leila.
Yeah, I copy.
Thank God!
Are you OK?
What's your position?
I'm near Lake Chiffon.
Our game is heading
north from here.
We'll catch up.
Leila, do you know
what's happened
to the dunpeal hunter?
No. I haven't seen him.
All right.
Well, take care.
Stay in touch.
Borgoff out.
Ha!
The tables have turned.
Uhh!
No!
Now, that
cleared my head.
I really should
return the favor,
don't you think, honey?
Don't get any ideas.
Hey, I'm just trying
to stay dry here.
If there was
any other place to go,
believe me, I'd be there.
As soon as the rain lets up,
I'll be gone from here
and from you.
I think I can guess
your problem.
Your family was
the victim of vampires.
You don't know what
you're talking about.
You don't know
anything about it.
All right.
Perhaps I don't.
This stupid thing,
it bothers me.
You really are a weird one,
you know that?
In spite of being
a dunpeal hunter
and all
that that entails.
How did you know
about my mother?
You called her name,
remember?
She was
kidnapped by vampires.
My father went after her.
He was trying to rescue her,
so they killed him.
And after a while,
my mother returned,
but she wasn't
my mother anymore.
She'd been changed.
The people in the village
stoned her to death
while I watched.
After that, I left home.
I met
the Markus brothers
and joined with them.
I wanted to be a hunter
to avenge
my parent's deaths.
I've seen many terrible
things since then-
lives destroyed,
families devastated,
hopes crushed.
Every time, it seems
a vampire is to blame.
I can understand why
you'd choose to do it,
but the life of a hunter's
no kind of life.
It's the only life
I'm any good for now,
and it looks like
it's the only life
you've ever known,
so I suggest
we make a pact.
Since we're both in it
for the long haul,
whoever dies first,
the other one can come
and bring flowers to
their grave. How's that?
It's the rain.
Makes me sentimental.
I don't know why I
should care about that.
It's just
I love flowers,
and I don't think
I'll be getting any.
I'm all alone,
after all.
We have that much
in common, don't we?
That we're both hunters
and we're both alone?
Oh, well.
I'm being silly.
It doesn't
really matter.
I'll do it.
I'll bring you flowers
if I survive this,
but I don't expect to.
Oh, stop. I didn't really
mean it when I said that.
And anyway,
I don't really understand
why you should
keep on doing this.
Because I'm a dunpeal.
I don't get to have
a life, not like you.
Well, with the rainstorm
last night,
they can't
be too far away.
We're even now, dunpeal.
Understand?
I have a very bad
feeling about this.
How so?
I think I finally
figured it out, Borgoff.
Well,
I'm sure you're right,
if you're thinking they're
headed for the castle.
Yeah, that's right,
the castle-
the Castle of Chaythe.
What are you thinking?
We can't go in there!
It would be suicide!
It would be insane!
What are you now,
afraid of a little insanity?
Since when
have we been sane?
We just have to get to them
before they reach the castle.
There's a bridge up ahead.
That's where we
intercept the carriage.
I remember that trick
from the time we got
those vampires at Keldo.
Yeah. It worked that time,
and it can work again now.
Leila, come in.
Come in, Leila. Over.
Yeah, it's me.
l copy.
What's up?
I'm on my way.
Uhh!
Don't move.
I'm warning you!
Try anything funny,
and you'll be blown
to smithereens.
You want to try it?
I didn't think so.
We just want the girl.
Hello there!
She's still human!
Come on,
get out of there! Now!
Borgoff,
she won't come!
We're doing you a favor!
Come on!
I said
get out of there!
Uhh!
Let that be a lesson to you,
you cowardly Barbarois animal!
Borgoff, look!
Borgoff!
What?
What the...
What, is this guy crazy?
Doesn't he know
he can't exist
outside here
in the sunlight?
I won't let you take her!
Oh, yeah?
Uhh!
Thanks a lot.
You're making our
job a lot easier.
Hot enough for you?
It's what
you deserve!
Uhh!
Over here,
hot stuff.
Hoo hoo!
Look at him burn!
Here, a little something
No!
How does that feel?
Way to go,
moron.
That got him!
What's the
matter? Don't you-
Look at him!
Hey, where
do you think-
Why'd you let her go?
I love you.
Uhh!
I can't go on without you.
What?!
Borgoff, we should just
let her kill herself,
and then we can
finish him off.
What do you think
about that idea?
We get the money
if she's dead or alive.
Hey,
you're right! OK.
Stop it!
Uhh!
Kyle!
I'll blow you to hell!
Aah!
What?!
No!
I don't want you to worry
about these wounds of mine.
They will heal.
Then we shall go to the City
of Night in Distant Stars.
When we go there,
we can be alone and
free to love each other.
It's true. Believe me.
We'll be there soon.
We're it now.
We're the only ones left,
Borgoff.
We should just give it up.
If we make it
into that castle,
none of us will
make it out alive.
We can't quit now.
We owe it to Kyle and
to Nolt to keep going on.
Listen, Borgoff-
Shut up!
I won't hear it!
Leila,
what do you think?
Grove, they fear us.
They fear us because
they know our reputation,
that we never give up
and we never can.
If we quit now, we might
as well quit the business,
and I can't do that.
I won't do it, till every
last one of them is gone.
Master, do you hear?
He's coming.
The castle is nearby.
I'll stay here
and deal with him.
We're getting close.
The Castle of Chaythe.
Soon we'll be
able to see it.
The home of Carmila,
the Bloody Countess.
You've heard of her.
For 5,000 years,
her rule of terror lasted,
and then that was that.
Your father,
the Vampire King, grew angry.
He was impatient
with her vanity,
offended by her bloodlust,
her gluttony.
He grew so tired
that he killed her
while she slept,
impaling her on his sword,
and that was it for her.
Except
she haunts the place now
with phantoms and demons,
but you don't care
about that, do you?
But I bet I know what really
gets to you, dunpeal, eh?
What really gets to you.
The thought of those
two lovebirds giving birth
to another dunpeal, huh?
That's it, isn't it?
See? I know you.
I know how you think.
I know how you feel.
I know every move
that you make.
You can't -uhh!
I'm glad we could
meet at last, hunter D.
You are a worthy opponent.
Who hired
the Barbarois?
Who were you
working for?
Uhh! It was Carmila
who hired us,
and as a Barbarois,
my duty has been fulfilled.
Now I can die in peace.
I gather
from your letter
that you've had
a rather difficult time.
I think I can understand
what it's like.
Love is not unique
to humans, you know.
We vampires
are very susceptible.
I hope I can be of service.
We're very grateful,
Carmila.
You both
must be exhausted.
Perhaps you
should rest first.
I'm sure
that the young lady
would like
to freshen up.
Hmm.
You've probably
heard rumors about me,
but I can assure you
they all stem
from jealousy and envy.
I'm not the "Bloody Carmila"
they like to portray me as.
Now, behold.
That's it.
That is the ship.
It will take you
to the City of the Night,
where you can
live peacefully at last.
You can be happy there.
There was a time,
many years ago,
when every castle
had a ship like this one
and the night sky was full
of their flashing lights.
Those were the days
when vampires flourished
and a love like yours was not
so desperately impossible.
So different from today.
Our numbers dwindling,
hunted and alone,
we are hopelessly
misunderstood,
but you two seem
to have beaten the odds.
I'm very, very happy for you.
The ship hasn't
been used in years.
I've no idea
if it will fly safely,
but I'm sure
that's a risk
you're prepared to take.
We're very grateful.
I only wish
I could go with you.
You look so beautiful.
Mmm.
Why stop?
I want you, Meier.
I want all of you.
Why not?
You don't know what
it's like, Charlotte,
to live forever
in darkness eternal,
forever
thirsting for blood
despite
your best intention.
I can't imagine
that life for you.
Not for you, Charlotte.
You're so selfish, Meier.
I carry a heavy weight
on my conscience...
Those villagers
and the bounty hunter
and my family,
they still mourn my loss, Meier.
It wasn't
your doing, Charlotte.
It was my fault
entirely.
Well,
then we're both to blame,
because
we can't know happiness,
not anymore.
I wanted you
to be happy, Meier,
and so I abandoned my father
and my brother for you.
But their pain set the wheels
in motion for our pain,
and so on and on it goes.
All we have
is each other now,
and I want to be
close to you.
Without that,
we have nothing.
All the pain I've caused
and all the agony I feel
is nothing now.
And you are everything
to me, my love.
We'll talk more on
our trip to the stars,
if that's all right
with you.
There is some
unfinished business
I have to attend to.
Do not leave this room.
Understand?
D-
Listen, Meier.
The woman says she
wants to go back home.
I don't believe it.
Charlotte.
I don't know.
Something's not right.
Of course, you don't
have to take my word for it.
You can judge for yourself.
Let's go.
Leila.
Don't go.
Leila,
don't go in there.
If you go in there,
you're never
coming back.
Oh,
I'm coming back.
No!
Borgoff, on headset:
Leila, check upstairs.
I'm on it.
Nice hat.
I know you hate me, D.
Please try and understand.
I loved your father.
What choice did I have?
Huh?!
Ahh!
Nolt! Kyle! Hey!
I don't believe it.
You two sure are
a sight for sore eyes.
Ugh!
What are
you doing? Get up.
Why aren't you
listening?
I said get up.
Go away. I wanna be alone.
Get out of here!
Can you
forgive me, D?
D?
I know it's been
lonely for you.
I was lonely, too,
until you came along.
Did you hear, D?
It's OK, honey.
It's OK to cry.
I know.
I know how you feel.
It wasn't
your fault.
It wasn't.
Yes, it was!
Let go!
Wait!
Ugh.
It's just an illusion.
Carmila's playing with us.
Excellent. What fun.
I haven't had
this much fun in centuries.
You don't mind, do you?
It just makes things
so much more interesting.
You're doing very well,
by the way,
very well, indeed.
The woman. Where
are you hiding her?
Borgoff,
what are you doing?
We don't have time for this.
Leila, are you in love
with this dunpeal?
Are you crazy?
What is wrong
with you?
Borgoff!
Dunpeal, drop your weapon.
Drop it now! Grrr!
She took you in,
didn't she?
Grr! She'll die!
I'm warning you, dunpeal.
Don't come any closer.
Enough!
Now you die!
Aaah!
No!
Aaaah!
Grove!
Grove! No!
Lei... la...
Look!
She's coming!
Carmila!
The spirit of Carmila!
Dunpeal hunter.
Your mother was human,
but your father was a vampire,
and you have betrayed
his ancient blood!
You side with humans
against us!
Our people
are facing extinction,
and you're contributing
to their demise.
You stalk and kill
your own ancestors, dunpeal.
You should be ashamed!
Your human self
is your weaker self.
Humans are nothing more
than livestock.
We prey on them
as they prey on beasts.
This is the rule of nature!
Your time
is coming to an end.
Your kind
must face extinction.
You cannot survive.
You must die.
That is the rule
of nature.
Ah. Very strong words
for a dunpeal,
but you seem to forget
our spirits are eternal.
No, Carmila.
Nothing lasts forever.
I see.
I should have
known better
than to reason
with your kind,
dunpeal hunter.
I guess my only option
is to use force.
Aaaah!
Aaah!
No!
This can't happen!
Aaaah!
Are you the son
of the Vampire King?
Who are you?
Who are you,
dunpeal?
Such power.
Charlotte,
come back.
I need you.
Please come back.
Mmm. Ohh.
Darling, is that you?
Oh, yes.
It's me, Meier.
I'm so happy, Meier,
because we are together now,
at last.
Together at last.
You made me happy,
Meier.
You let me dream.
You let me dream of
our beautiful trip
to the stars.
Our dream.
Our beautiful,
wonderful dream.
It's not a dream.
We are going to those stars,
Charlotte.
Oh, my dear one.
You and I will
get away from here.
We will fly together
to the City of the Night
where we were meant to be
free from all of this.
Where you can rest,
my love, finally, and be free.
Yes.
Freedom... at last.
My precious,
precious love.
Let's go...
Away from here.
Stop right there,
Meier.
I'm taking her back,
back to her family,
who loved her.
She knew I loved her
best of all.
You can't understand it.
You've never
loved a human.
I've never
killed one, either.
You struggle to resist
this nature of ours,
but it can't last
forever, D.
The urge for their blood
is stronger.
If that day comes,
then another will hunt me.
It's as simple as that.
Raaaahhh!
What a waste,
a sad waste.
Enough of killing.
Enough of misery and death.
I've had enough.
Uhh!
Why...
did you miss
my heart?
She's dead.
The ring is all I need.
I'll take it
to her father as proof.
Mind giving me a ride
just as far as the next town?
I'd appreciate it.
That reward money would
rightfully be mine, you know.
But, hey, I'm generous.
I'll let you keep it
just this one time.
Where is he taking her?
Away from here.
Away.
Fly. Come on!
You can make it.
Come on!
Fly away-
Dearly beloved,
we are gathered here
in this resting place
to bid farewell
to our sister.
Into your gentle arms
we commend
her gracious spirit.
Take her to yourself
and give her safe haven,
and though
she struggled in life,
now she knows
your blessed peace.
For all who question
will find answers,
and all who love
will find contentment,
joy, and peace eternal.
For now we see
as through a glass darkly,
but then we shall see
clearly, face to face.
Mister.
Wait!
Mister, wait!
Um, excuse me, sir,
but I was wondering
if you knew
my grandmother Leila.
Yes, it's you, isn't it?
My grandmother
told me about you.
So, I'd be honored
if you'd come
to our house.
My dad
would be so happy.
Please?
I appreciate your kindness.
Oh, come on.
We don't live very far.
I just came here
to keep a promise
to an old friend of mine.
She was afraid no one
would mourn her death.
I'm glad she was so wrong.
Huh?
Oh. I guess I see.
Anyway, thank you
for coming, sir.
Good-bye.
Good-bye!
Well, that was nice.
You're not so bad
after all.
You just dress bad.
Subtitle by anana
Please rate this subtitle at www.osdb.link/3qatt
Help other users to choose the best subtitles