Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org
You have new messages.
Monday, 1:42 pm.
Hi, Jimmy. I hope you get home OK...
You enjoy your flight and then...
I know how much
you hate flying so, eh, anyway
Well anyway, I'm doing a big chicken on Sunday.
- Ask him about Sunday!
Oh, your dad is cleaning out the garage
and wants to know if you want
that old punching bag hanging up.
He's getting too old for that.
Anyway, give us a call tomorrow,
eh, when you land...
or today or whenever you can.
You know what I mean, eh...
Can't wait to see you.
Love you! Bye!
Wednesday, 9:36 pm.
Jimmy, it's Griff. Eh, oh God,
I don't know what to say.
I'm so sorry.
Listen, when you get back,
you give us a shout.
I'll get 'im, I promise ya.
I love you, mate.
Talk to you soon.
End of messages.
Hi Jimmy, how you're feeling?
Alright Deb...
Hi Jimmy.
Could I get a coke, please.
Yeah.
Look, mate, em... I'm sorry
about what happened.
I'm sure you can point me in the
right direction, Cal.
I didn't see anything, Jimmy.
Sorry, mate.
You live 50 yards away.
Look, if you're only here to cause
trouble, you may as well go.
- Terry!
- Stay out of this, will ya!
Trouble?
Jesus...
leave it!
Jimmy, don't!
Don't!
Jimmy! Jimmy don't, don't.
Oh, Jim...!
Jimmy, wait!
Just tell him,
will ya?
I called the fire service.
There were four of them.
They broke in.
I heard your dad...
screamin'.
I heard him screamin'
and I just watched.
I watched from the window...
'cause I was scared.
Who are they?
- Morning.
- Bye.
- Hang on.
- I'm Late, George.
- Oh, can you get the lawn mowed later?
- Why?
Jimmy's coming home for a few days
and I want the place to look nice.
He won't be back until Friday.
Yeah, but it's goin' rain all week
after today, and it won't get done.
He's been in the Afghan desert
for months. The lawn is the
last thing he goin' care about.
Besides, I want to put the cab in for service.
You alright, love?
I just want him home for good, now.
You've gone missin' in that picture.
I'd been in labor for 7 hours!
It was lucky you were behind the counter.
With your mullet and your earring,
talk about a mess!
One minute you bumpin' about on the back
of me bike, the next we got a baby boy.
We didn't know what hit us, did we?
At 10:35 that night I knew
exactly what hit us.
I'll mow the lawn
when I get home.
Thanks, love.
- She ain't carryin' no ten grand, mate.
- Oh, fuck off, man. I've been scoping her out for months, gov.
She better be, I ain't sittin' in the car,
gettin' big old cramp for nothing, guv.
About every Friday at half four,
she does the cash run, trust me.
What are you talking about? It's pushing
five already, you know.
What?
- Where're you goin'?
- Bank run.
Here. Take this over with ya.
- You never like doing the bank.
- I will if I take your car.
- Keep it on ya.
- Yeah, I know.
There she is, just like clockwork...
- Eh, there she is, she's on the move.
Hey, let's do this, yeah. Yeah?
- We'll take a left, Bob, head her off.
- Hey, give me my mask.
Oh, God!
Shit!
Come on!
- Where's the money, bitch?
- It's not in her purse. She must have it on her.
Where is it? Where's the money?
Let's get the fuckin' shit and
get back in the car, man!
No, you've got to be fuckin' kiddin' me.
Where's the money? Where'd you
put it? Is it in the car?
- What the fuck you want, man?
- What the fuck do you think you're doin'?
Get the fuck back in your car, man!
Come on! You'll have a day, a fuckin' day!
Fuck off, man!
Get back in your fucking car!
Fuck 'em up!.
Come on, come and get it!
I fucking dare ya!
- Come on.
- Hey, Sigmund. Sigmund, look here!
- Let's cover this stuff, wood boy!
For fuck sake, let's go!
Hey, watch me, man.
Watch! Prick!
Are you alright?
And then he came at you. But,
you said he was behind you.
Mr Vickers...
Sorry. I just wanted to stop him.
I never meant to...
Yeah. Well, you should have thought
of that before you started swinging.
Let's get him out of here before the families find out.
Otherwise, we'll have Reverend McDaniel
giving us seven types of shit.
- Mr....What is it?
- Vickers.
Mr. Vickers, I'm DCI Holland. You're
gonna have to come with us.
How serious is this?
Mr. Vickers, I'm arresting you on
suspicion of manslaughter.
You do not have to say anything, though
it may harm your defense if you do not
mention, when questioned, something
that you'll later rely on in court.
Anything you say may be given in evidence.
- Do you have any questions?
- No.
Fantastic. Alright, the next time
we meet, it'll be down in nick.
- Where the fuck's my money, then?
- We had a little problem, Warren.
Hey. Oh, it got on top, firm. Man meant
to do us some fuckin' Avatar ills, still.
Where's the fuck's my brother?
Oi...
that's the thing...
Huh?
He's dead, Wass.
- You're supposed to be
lookin' out for each other.
- We do look out for each other,
but shit happens, Bob.
- What the fuck! You're supposed
to be to connect with 'im!
- We'll get 'im!
We found out where he lives. He
only made bail a few hours ago, Bob.
You find him and you finish him. Right?
And then we'll deal with it, yeah?
Trust.
Oh! No!
George!
Do you remember me?
Shut your fuckin' mouth. Or...I'll
cut your fuckin' tongue out.
The fuck you doin'?
You're going to milked me.
No!
On the other hand, fuckin' me and
wondering what's happening to
my missus is a fucking tune to me.
It seems you had some bollocks
twelve years ago. You a fucking hero?
You're a hero, are ya?
But I bet when they let you out on bail,
you come right to tell your missus
you'd never get a slap, did they?
I stopped a robbery. I killed one of them,
as well. What's for dinner?
Suppose I mention the lad, you killed his
brother, is right in there with your missus.
Come on now, don't be like that.
You need a line all set up.
You can't go through life without
a grin once in a while.
So why don't you give us a really big smile.
Give me the phone.
Now. Go start the car.
Fuck that, man, I want to see them
go up the rude way.
You know, it was the mean old fuckers
who done you, right.
You're very lucky, mate.
See, I didn't get to say goodbye to my
little brother after you smashed
his fuckin' head in with that bat.
But I'm gonna let you say goodbye to 'er.
Cause I'm a nice guy.
See, I did you a little favor.
You're not my style.
I put a little more petro...
on the bitch.
Now, hopefully she lights off first.
Fuck me, it's cold...
Don't worry, Georgy.
I'll turn the heatin' up.
How ya feelin'?
You're not doin' yourself any favors by
beatin' the shit out of people for info.
Yeah, well. Somebody knows something.
Well, maybe they do.
But doing this job for 6 years, you realize
it's every neighbor's god-given right to turn a blind eye.
Fear of gettin' a knife in their belly.
- So, stop poking around.
- And what have you got?
Nothing...
no one's talking.
One of the neighbors said they heard some
commotion about 11. Thought it was the TV.
Then called the fire brigade at 11:30
when they saw the garage going up.
Saw a black BMW speedin' off.
There's been a couple of attacks
like the one your old man
stopped. We think it's the same lot.
Whoever they are,
people are scared Jimmy.
Were they alive?
Jimmy, mate...don't...
Were they burnt alive?
Postmortem suggests they
burnt to death, yes.
Have you seen Morgan since you got back?
No...I haven't signed the divorce papers.
Can you get me the CCTV footage?
Jimmy, I've seen it, mate.
It's just weird rabbit masks.
I'll bring it to you tomorrow.
Jimmy...
He stood his ground...
your old man.
When did ya get back?
Friday.
You missed the funeral.
Tryin' to make up for it.
I e-mailed you four...
five times, Jimmy.
I had a combat mission in Helmand.
Your commanding officer said you'd
been arrested and detained.
What happened?
You know I can't tell you, Morgan.
Oh, I think you can, Jimmy.
Especially when I have to arrange and cover
for you at your own parents' funeral.
Wait!
Sorry.
You don't have to be on your own.
Stop by the flat, sometime. OK?
- Hey, yeah, you on my best case?
- Fuck, man.
Whoa, whoa, whoa...
who the fuck is this?
Hey, this is Ronnie, he's alright
and he just wants some...
- Hey, I heard your stuff's awesome, fella.
- Get the fuck out of here.
Bring him up to Caleb's in business hours.
- Yeah?
- Well, and they want half-an-ounce, I suppose.
We're havin' a party.
Well, that takes money.
This is four bills. What the fuck!
I said five.
Your guy told us four.
We only got four on us.
- We could-We'll just get
four hundred's worth?
- I said I'd get half-an-ounce.
I tell you what. You run me the four bills
and let me see your wifey's breasts.
- Naw, man. Look, let's just get four
hundred's worth, yeah? - No deal.
Babe, let's just go.
Babe, we need this gear.
I ain't asking for much,
just a quick flash.
You ain't even wearin' a bra.
This guy is sick, you know.
You actually thought I'd gonna give you
a hundred pounds off the gear...
- for a quick look at
your girlfriend's tits?
- I did, yeah.
Look, we're gettin' out of here.
Just give me my money back.
You ain't going nowhere.
That's crazy, you know.
You get the gear
when she sucks my cock.
No! Leave him! Don't!
- Stop!
- Take off your top.
They'll stop wailin' him in
when you start suckin'.
- Wait! Leave him! She's up for it.
- Dickhead.
You know,
I've got to record that shit, bro.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
What the fuck?
I told you to suck this dick. Do it properly
or I'll throw you through the window.
And you won't get no gear.
Mr Evans?
What the fuck you want?
Mr. Evans. We've had reports of a disturbance
at this address a few hours ago.
So what?
- Mr. Evans, have you been home all night?
- Yeah.
We have reason to believe that
a man has been assaulted on
your premises. Mr. Ryan Scott?
Don't ring a bell.
Can we come in?
Get the fuck out of here!
Mr. Evans, there's a young man in hospital
whose been quite badly beaten.
So what? It don't have fuck
to do with me.
So take your little fuck-puppet here and
get the fuck away from my yard.
Don't be stranger though, sweetheart.
You come back around here,
anytime you want, yeah?
- What was that?
- You heard.
What different reality do you
honestly think I would...
be interested in a tommy-sack
of shit like you?
Whoa, whoa. Come on.
Go on, girl. You have peace with 'em.
Reign her in.
You get that little pit bull on a leash, yeah?
Oi! Jenny, wait up.
You can't let them get to you.
We know he did it and we're gonna
go in and get away with it?
You've been a constable for five minutes.
Wanna make a difference?
Climb the ladder.
I'll be in the car.
The owner of the black BMW is a
Warren Evans, 3305 South Avenue.
You sure it's him?
Warren Evans had a
younger brother Joshua.
Joshua Evans was accidentally
killed two weeks ago during
an attempted robbery.
After receiving a blow to the head.
From your old man.
Hello?
What the fuck!
What the fuck! Huh?
What the fuck you doing driving into me,
like that, you fucking fool?
Huh?
Oh, you don't talk?
I'm fuckin' talking to you, bro.
Don't fuckin' look at me, bro!
What the fuck!
What the fuck, man! You crazy?!
What the fuck are you doing?
You know who the fuck I am?
Oh, you're a big man, yeah?
Got me tied up.
You cut me and we'll see what happens
to you, you fuckin' dickhead.
I'm gonna ask you once.
If I have to ask you twice,
I'm gonna cut off your left ear.
If I have to ask you again,
I'm gonna cut off your right ear.
Does that make sense? It's a very,
very simple process. OK?
Are we on the same page? Yeah?
Good boy. OK.
The couple in the garage.
Couple of weeks back.
Fuck you, man. Fuck that dickhead.
He killed my little brother.
He deserved what we did to him.
Hey. So, what was he to you?
I bet you're the son or
something, innit.
Your mom...fucked me.
Great ass.
We made 'em face each other, you know.
Before we lit 'em up.
So they could watch each other burn.
Should have seen the look on their faces.
Fuckin' priceless.
You know what?
I'm gonna let you go.
But you gotta do something for me.
- You're lying. All of this...
- I'm not lying to you.
- For real?
- Yes, for real.
Yes..
Yes, I like ya.
I need you to give me the names
of the other boys, yeah. Now...
See, take that, take that.
Now, listen, listen. Listen.
They're never gonna know, alright,
black and white.
You give me the names and you live,
if you don't...well...
Alright, alright.
Alright, fuck it.
Alright, fuckin' done.
Here, fuckin' take it, man.
But about that stuff I said before,
I took it too far, yeah. My bad.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
But just imagine...Just imagine what
it felt like...to be burnt alive.
- What you talking about, man?
- The jolly, lad.
What you fuckin' talkin' about?
Hey, man, you said you'd let me go.
What the fuck you doin'? Huh? Please, man,
you said you would be helpin'.
Let me go, man!
Please!
Please! Please!
So sorry, man!
Please! I said let me go!
Let me go!
Please! Please!
Help!
So sorry, man!
Please, I...! Please, man, you said you
would let me out of here!
Let me go man! Please!
Please let me go!
I said it before, man, please!
[Screams]
Not sleepin', are you?
The coffee's not gonna help, is it?
The sun will be up soon.
How've you been, anyway?
Yeah, um...
Yeah, good, but...the vets have moved
to a bigger building, right? Despite the...
Jimmy, I'm really sorry
about what's happened.
Do you think that was retaliation
for what your dad did?
Jimmy, promise me you're not gonna
do anything stupid. OK?
Can I use your bathroom?
Yes, of course.
Wait a minute. What's that?
- That's just nothing.
- Jesus, Jimmy, you're bleeding!
- Oh, Morgan, just leave it.
It's nothing. Noth...
- No, sit down.
- Listen. Just leave it.
- Jimmy, you need a stitch. Sit down.
Tell me what happened, Jimmy?
- Just a couple of lads in a pub, you know.
- In Afghanistan.
Alright, alright...
Something works to get the guy to talk.
Ah, it's just....
It's complicated out here.
Really? Because somebody told me there's
no such thing as a complication.
Only a problem derived by a person,
not a situation.
Who, me? Oh, that makes absolutely no
sense, so...I must have been pissed.
Clown.
I will get around to signing those.
No rush.
Right, eh...
I'm done.
Wait, eh, a minute.
We'll put a dressing on it.
You got it?
It's all better.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
Usually cats and dogs, but it'll do.
Hope you like scars.
I'm used to 'em.
How's your little scar.
The day I saved your life.
Please, I was hardly gonna
bleed to death, was I?
Well, that was 20 miles away
from the nearest hospital,
in the middle of the Brighton Bay.
Anything could have happened.
Well, ah...
Thank you.
- Hey, Morgan.
- Hey.
- What can I get you?
- Ah, cappuccino thanks.
Mr. Evans was last seen yesterday
at the gym in Kenwood Downs,
last night at around 9 o'clock.
Big question is how Mr. Evans came
to be out there and why.
Nobody really knows what Mr. Evans was
doing out here on his own in a car.
In fact, It's yet to determine whether
he was actually alone.
- Here you go.
- Thanks.
They've been on about this all day.
Who cares, right?
Just some dealer, it's just
what they come to.
...And an explosion shortly after.
It seems that this particular area,
just up the Carmel Road,
is quite popular with teen-agers
and dealers.
In fact, it's been a troublesome spot
for some time now.
Mr. Evans was arrested 3 years ago after...
police caught him in
an organized crime gang
raided a flat in Garrison, East London.
Mr. Evans admitted being involved in
the supply of cocaine and heroin.
The sources said the six-year-old
Caleb Green, jailed...
How the fuck do you know this Caleb?
Who else is it gonna be, guv?
You know they don't spend their
days much with these organized visits.
Boss was only talking about offing
Caleb last week, man.
Hm. Boy, that's a little tawdry, man.
Hey, yo. Less with the gibes, alright?
Do this.
- What you asking, fella?
- Want to talk some business.
Fuck off.
- Go, on!
- David!
- You better know what you're doing, bro.
- Tell me you didn't do it. Tell me!
- What are you on about?
- You fuckin' know, Warren, man!
Oh, you're trippin' out, bro.
I ain't got a fuckin' clue what
you're on about.
Nah!
Have one chance
so you put the gun down.
And get the fuck off me!
And I'm gonna you both walk
out of here alive.
- For whatever offense it was.
- I ain't involved, brother.
That's not even loaded.
Try me.
Get up. The both of ya.
- Someone burned out his car.
- With him in it, bro.
And you think that was me?
Why the fuck would I take the time
to do something like that?
When I off some great problem.
- If I find out it's you, OK?
- I'm what?
You try and do fucko. Now fuck off. Don't
let me see you up in my block again.
Pair of fuckin' clowns.
I need some addresses.
Did it feel good?
It's far from left.
Jimmy, you gotta let this go, mate.
What? And let you lot sort it.
I got 4 names.
What did you get?
So this is it?
This is how it's gonna be?
I'll just stand back while you go on some
urban safari across London?
Now, you know as well as I do, this is the
only way this is gonna get done.
What happens if you do get one of 'em?
What're you gonna do, take a statement?
You gonna process 'em,
while they laugh at ya,
spit in your face.
You try and put them
in some cushy little jail,
where they sit on their fuckin'
ass all day, playing video games.
This country's changed.
The riots, just are starting.
There was a time I would've bled
to keep the red in the Union Jack.
Them days are long gone.
We've got a generation of offenders
we don't know what to do with, Griff.
And you know as well as I do, there's
nothing to stop them doing it again
There's me.
Revenge will never give you closure.
Revenge?
It's not revenge,
this is necessity.
Get me an address.
- How many were there?
- Two.
I know it's really hard, Mrs. Gilbert,
can you describe them?
One had, like a, a black and white hoodie,
I don't remember the others.
It happened so fast.
It's OK.
Look, I'll be in a sec, OK?
- Sir?
- Yeah, hang on a sec, will ya.
Alright, let's get on with it. I'm teeing
off with the superintenant at one o'clock.
And I don't want to be late for this shit.
Armed robbery, two suspects,
both in their forties.
Mr. Oliver tried to grab one
of the guns, apparently.
Other guy put two in his chest.
Held Mrs. Guilbert at gunpoint
and raided the till.
Cool. That's a tidy bit of business.
- Eh, any CCTV?
- Yeah, but it's a bit faded.
What's he doin' tryin' to
disarm them-the nutter.
I don't know. Protecting his livelihood?
Yeah, that worked out well for him,
didn't it?
- Listen PC...what's your name?
- Griffin.
It's probably just an insurance jump
gone wrong. Try not to
take it too personally, mate.
She'll make a claim, get a huge payout,
everyone's happy.
And the suspects?
Eh, get the rounds dug out of
Charlie Bronson over there
and have the morgue send 'em over to me.
It may take a while, but, eh, hey...slim
justice is better than no justice.
That's enough for me. Thank you.
- You're drivin', are you?
- No, but I'm a lousy drunk.
- Oh, yeah?
Hm... Define lousy.
Put it this way:
The last time I got drunk, I entered a
wet T-shirt competition on holiday.
- That right?
- I won, of course.
Course.
So, what kind of a drunk are you?
I can be quite incorrigible.
Unlike most people,
I embrace the effects of alcohol.
I don't beat myself up about
having a good time.
And this is your assessment
of my character?
No. But I can tell you're cautious...
timid.
And I reckon you're fucking shit-scared
that if you have that glass of wine,
that dress of yours is gonna end up on my
bedroom floor.
And your panties in my collection.
I'm not wearing any.
Sorry about that, guys.
Thirsty, dear?
Now. Where were we, Ronnie?
We were about to come down
to about 30%, Alex.
Finish these desserts and you're
both get the bill.
At least that's what your
lovely wife was saying.
Oh, was she now?
That's why I like to bring her along.
Good judge of character, my Susann.
- Aren't you, babe?
- Um hm.
You've got yourself a deal.
I might move Alex, myself. Smart move.
Excuse me for two seconds.
Will you?
You know it doesn't matter
what you wear to me.
But you don't look right without an
MP5 and a fuckin' ammo rig.
I'll take that as a compliment.
She's something else.
That's that fellow's wife, mate.
Drink?
I need to get my hands on some bits.
If you're still in that business.
Hey!
Hanny!
- You alright, Trison?
- Yeah.
What the fuckin' hell's that?
Excalibur?
Not walkin' about with it.
It's slender, titanium.
That'll go through a car door.
What the fuck do I want to
stab a car door for?
- That'll work, too.
- Whoa, whoa, whoa...listen, listen.
Put that back. You're gonna have
someone's eye out.
What? You've never stabbed
someone before?
Now that is a SIG Sauer.
Peach.
Yeah, it takes 19 in the clip.
It's effective up to 50 meters.
The man knows his toys...
We'll take 'em.
I'll get him a silencer for that.
You should know, Jimmy, that ain't me,
no more. I mean, I did it
because you ask, but...
I appreciate it.
Jimmy...we go way back...
and I fuckin' know you.
That look in your eye,
it ain't good, mate.
I've got it under control.
Look, I feel your pain,
I really do.
Trust me, I'd be doing the same thing.
We should drink to Louis, mate.
So if you want to take a stand, you've gotta
be tall. Taller than you've ever been.
You understand what I'm sayin' to ya?
Take care, alright?
You need anything else, you just
let me know, alright?
- Hey, y'all.
- For what?
For Warren, yeah?
Hey, get some more in place.
I'm down for a piss kreig.
Hey yo, have you thought about
who it could've been?
No, man. You?
Fuck no, bro...
But we'll find 'im, yeah.
And when we do...
me, you and that scrawny
little shit in there...
will fuckin' ruin him, yeah?
- Hell, yes.
- Yeah?
- Right.
- That's what I'm talkin' about.
Line 'em up.
What the fuck is this?
What? You got a fuckin' problem?
Come on, then!
- You're gonna die tonight.
- No, I...
I know.
It's terrible, innit...
But it's the truth.
The only reason it hasn't happened
yet is because in your current...
unfortunate situation,
you leave me severely spoilt
with choices.
You see, I could...literally...
I could put anything in there.
Hello... Hello... Hello...
Sorry.
It was a bad joke.
You all done? You're tellin' me,
what's goin' on, bubba?
Stop fuckin about,
we're worried, fella.
Please, fucking shit-brain.
Who the fuck is this?
Where's Danny?
Danny can't talk, right now.
Who are you, mate?
You're the same guy
that did Warren, huh?
What's your fucking problem?
He deserved to burn to death
He deserved to die for what he did.
For what you all did to that copper.
About that, ya?
So what the fuck that's got
to do with you?
You think you're a fuckin' scary do ya
on the other end of the phone, yeah?
Fuckin' scary, aren't ya?
Well, let's go face to face, see how
scary you are, then. Where are you, bro.
Oh, we will go face to face.
And when we do,
I'm gonna annihilate you.
I...
I'm gonna fuckin'...
annihilate you.
Where were we?
You're gonna love this.
Now this is a little lesson...
in cement.
In the general sense of the word,
cement's a binder.
Substance sets, hardens, independently.
Binds materials together.
- Shit, no!
- Traces back to the Romans.
Till they used the term...
"Opus Caementicium" (Roman Concrete:
lime, grease, sand and water)
Hey, yeah, hey.
No, no, no!
Wow!
Two kids found 'im.
Where the bloody hell do we start
with something like this?
What is that?
Eh, mouth clamp.
I think dentists use them.
It looks like some kind of sex toy.
That's solid.
He might have swallowed up to two
liters before he eventually suffocated.
The cement has bonded all of
his internal organs together.
If you hit 'im now with a sledge
hammer, he'd probably break apart.
Fuck!
The pathologist is on his way.
No, bugger that.
I'm all over the CSI shit.
I've been waiting for something decent to
fall into my lap ever since I got promoted.
Hmm. Hold that.
You get the kids' witness statements
and let's have some coffees.
This is gonna be a long morning.
- DCI Holland.
- Anything else?
Oh, yeah.
OK. Yeah.
DCI Holand. Holland command informs me
that you have something
on your CCTV I need to have a look at.
Not me, love.
Well, someone from your telephone said...
It was me.
I rang ya.
Had these installed last year.
Mainly because after the last three
breakins we had, you lot
- said you couldn't do
anything without CCTV.
- Right.
Too busy sitting up in a warm
office doing paperwork, I suspect.
Processing criminals instead of giving
them what they really need.
- A good kicking.
- OK.
Debbie.
Can I have a word, Terry?
What?
- What are you doing?
- Protecting my pub.
Your pub? We both know exactly
who you're protecting.
It is that fearfulness.
You know exactly whose car that is.
And you can't turn a blind eye?
They know everything.
They get wind that I've let this slip,
they'll burn the place down
with us in it. You've seen
what they can do.
Yes. And I know what Jimmy can do.
He can steamroller the lot of them.
Just let him get on with it. You can't get
him up to that shark in there.
We gonna look at this, or what?
There.
So what?
Jesus Christ!
Take-Take-Take-Take it back,
come to the beginning.
Play it-Play it from there.
And pause it.
There.
I got you,
you fucker.
Shit!
Fuck!
- Mrs. Vickers?
- Yeah.
It's about your husband, Mrs. Vickers.
Right, OK.
- Well, have you seen him in
the past few days?
- No, I haven't. Sorry.
- Not at all?
No, I just said I haven't.
What's all this about?
We may have reason to believe that your
husband has been involved in a
series of crimes.
Um, what sort of crimes?
We can't say, I'm afraid.
Well, if you see him, can you give us
a call as soon as possible?
Eh, this is the detective in charge
of the investigation.
OK.
Thank you.
Those murders... on the news,
they're you, aren't they?
Jesus, Jimmy!
Morgan, they executed my fucking parents.
Well, aren't you doing exactly the
same thing, what is that? Justice?
They don't deserve justice.
They don't deserve to live.
They need their hearts torn out.
They've been there all day.
Jimmy, you know, when they told me what
happened, I... I didn't believe it.
Who does that to an old couple?
It's just...
I just wanted to find you.
What happened?
There were these six Afghan soldiers
we were training, turned on us.
Four Taliban...
killed six of our soldiers.
We needed to figure out if there were any
more among us, so they put me to work.
work on a Monday with just one client.
And I got him talking eventually.
And he knew so much,
just so much...
They would have fucking done us all.
So I couldn't let him live.
I had to hold him to keep our
space together, cause...
I went too far...
And they locked me up.
You escaped.
Yeah.
Jimmy...
Was there ever anyone else?
No!...
This can only end badly.
And what's the alternative?
You get in a car and you drive until
you don't have any fuel left.
You might have to.
And would you come with me?
Yes.
I have to finish this.
Holland.
I think we found your man.
Under no circumstances are they to
approach him. Just maintain eye contact.
I'm on my way.
Oh yeah, get me helicopters.
Yeah, and I want a SWAT team.
Yes, I know we have to call on that,
just get it done.
Hi, mate.
Got any ID on ya?
- What's your name?
- It IS him.
Put the guns down, Vickers.
Didn't expect to see you, Colonel.
Here to take me back?
As soon as you report in, son,
the better this will be for everyone.
Well, everyone's gonna have to wait.
This is not an option, James.
You're a serving soldier in this
country's most elite force.
Rooker knows the Afghan spilled his guts
to you and he wants what you know.
I've got a few things I need to finish first
and then I'll come in.
This isn't gonna bring them back,
you know.
What you are doing.
You're a good lad...
and you're a great soldier.
But you've got to let this go before
it turns into a mess that
even I can't clean up.
It'll stop when they're dead.
And then I'm out.
Out?
I've seen enough blood to last
a lifetime. I want a normal life.
What is a normal life?
A comfortable desk job at the Ministry?
Maybe driving a forklift truck around
some grubby warehouse?
Newspapers and sandwiches on your
lunch break? A flask of coffee?
People like you are beyond the
realm of social integration.
They sit here...
you sit there.
Psychologically tweaked to be superior to
all these drones that walk the street.
Align 'em and laugh.
These people, if they knew what you've done
to keep them living their mundane lives.
They'd even kiss your feet.
You're a hero, James.
You do know that if they hadn't of locked
me up, I would have been there for them.
I was due home the day
before they were killed.
Pull over.
You've got 48 hours to clean up
your personal shit.
Then this turns over to Rooker...
and he's not a pussy cat either.
Dickheads!
Joe.
What you on, mate?
You got a second?
Yeah, but I just got to get these
tools back to the armory, so...
- Have to get on the mosey.
- Of course.
- You know Jimmy Vickers, don't ya.
- Yeah.
Yeah, I ran a support op for him out of
Fort Robinson for four weeks, sir.
Is Holland closin' in on 'im?
Well, man's trauma now. I mean,
he's gone mad, right?
You know about this,
his mom and dad.
Never mind that. You still can't  go
around doing what he is doing.
But you've got to give me the facts
if I'm gonna find him.
Hang on a minute...
are you helpin' him?
Joe, I've known him since
I was six, mate.
I think this is fucked!
I don't care who you've grown up with,
he's rotten.
He's out of control.
And Holland isn't?
He doesn't give a fuck about anything.
All he wants to do is lynch Vickers to shortcut
his way right to the top.
Can you imagine a prick like
him as Superintendent?
Just keep me in the loop...
please.
- Anything else?
- No, that's lovely. Eh, just the bill.
Spencer Holland.
Hey, gorgeous. On your lunch break? This
week's fare? Thought you cops were
fish-and-chips types. Eat on the
go, crooks to catch, all that.
Yeah, I'm in a bit of a rush, too. So, eh...
Are you? Yeah, that's right. Got
your hands full with those two murders.
Murders?
I don't know what you're talking about?
Oh, fuck off, Spencer, everyone
knows about your killer.
"THREE LEFT," I heard. Sounds like a
vigilante if you ask me.
If you fuckin' write any of this,
I will end you.
Come on, don't be a prick!
I want a quick interview.
People have got a right to know
what's going on in their streets.
Right to know. Really? Are you
honestly goin' try that one on?
I know you know who he is.
How would you know that?
You're like shit at this. You can't lie,
I suppose. It's written
all over your face.
God, my editor will hump my leg
if I bring in this.
Look, I'll show the police in a
really good light. Police say:
"Zero tolerance on vigilante attacks...
DCI Spencer Holland closing
in on the psycho."
Try the salad. You've put weight
on since last time.
Look who's talkin'.
Nice to see you, Jules.
Do something, luv.
Do something.
You can move,
let me see 'em.
- No. Fuck off! Go get Suzy, yeah!
- Fuck you, wanker!
Yeah, I'll give you wanker,
you slut.
Here you go.
And, eh...this is off that bloke at the
bar, asked me to give it to ya.
Oh, no!
Fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck!
Hey, what's going on, bro?
Hey, mate. I wasn't...
Hey, mate, come on. Please.
Please, please, please, please...!
Please! Let...me breath. Hey, look,
I'm...I'm sorry, yeah!
Please! I'm so sorry, I am.
What you sorry for?
Whatever I've done,
I'm sorry, yeah?
What?
Whatever I did to you, I'm sorry.
Please! Please!!
- You see, you don't even know, do ya?
- We talk.
- Huh?
- No.
And that's the problem.
Little pricks like you, running around,
burning people alive.
And neglect to the emotional
devastation you cause.
I know who you are. Look, I'm sorry,
I'm so sorry. I didn't mean to, please...
Sorry, I'm...No, I'm...
everybody's sorry, sorry.
Sorry's fuck all!
Sorry is a cast-away word on the
breath of the hopefuls
who have gone too far to right their wrongs.
I'll tell you who I am:
The last face you're gonna see.
No, please. I said I was sorry.
Come on, man. Please
don't do me like that!
Please! I'm a...
Please, please!...
Please! No, no! Please!
Please! Fuck no! Please!
Please, please!
No! You fuck...motherfucker...
you fuck..
Oh, fuck...
sake's please!
Oh! Fuck! Oh!
Oh! All right, just quit!
What ya doin'?!
Oh, fuck me, I'll talk.
Stop!! Stop!! STOP!!
You said you got your plate full...
some fairly gruesome murders.
Nothing I can't handle, sir, we'll get 'im.
- You think it's the same person?
- Possibly.
You think that's a safe assessment?
Without a doubt.
Why'd you think I became the youngest
Chief Superintendent in London?
I didn't want to deal with
those shits anymore.
You know, in 2003, I went to New York
on holiday with the missus.
The week we were there, the binmen were
on strike. You cannot imagine the smell.
Picture that size, it was in August, too.
Listen, people don't really care
or take notice of the binmen.
They don't care how they toss
out people's rubbish...
But the binmen who stop makes you
know that, the city starts to stink.
Do you understand where
I'm getting to with this?
I need you to know who
you are in this story.
I'm the guy cleaning all the shit
up to make the streets safer.
Well, if you are,
you're an idiot.
The policeman who thinks he can clean
up the streets is a deluded fool.
You don't rock the boat.
You look after number one.
Before you know it,
you'll have your own borough.
Be nice to be the next Superintendent
in London, wouldn't it?
Yes, sir.
You wrap the gruesome ones quick.
You grab the statements,
you scrape them off the streets.
And you keep the media out.
If the Commissioner finds out
about this gettin' out,
you'll be demoted to Constable
before you can say "Katy Price
is a virgin." Do you understand?
Yes, sir.
- Anything else?
- No, just the coffee, please.
- Can I help you, sir?
- I'll have a tea, please.
Sure, coming right out.
- Bloody cold, isn't it?
- Yeah.
Do we know each other?
I'm gonna need you to hand over
everything you've got on 'im.
Yeah, well, that's not gonna happen, mate.
You see, he belongs to us...
not you.
Colonel Leach, he does belong to me
when he's taking the law into
his own hands in my borough.
Let me explain something to you.
September 2009...we get intel of
a major attack being planned
for the British mainland
on a scale that would make 7/7
look like the Teddy Bear's Picnic.
We ran an op to bring in the guy
who was planning the attack.
Taliban come down on us
like piss rain.
Worst firefight I've ever been in.
We couldn't exit with the prick so
we had to get what we
needed there and then.
It took Vickers 10 minutes alone with
the guy to get him to spill his guts.
While we were fighting off 30 Taliban,
he gives him everything.
Afterwards, Vickers executes the prisoner.
You see, these people,
they don't fear death.
They welcome it.
So you must ask yourself...
how did he get the goods?
Now we were in danger of being overrun,
so we had to get out of there.
No sign of Vickers.
He turns up three days later at
bastion, not a scratch on him.
No one knows how he did it.
If he doesn't want to be found,
he won't be.
He'll finish up on these guys and then...
...he'll vanish.
Well, I'll find 'im...
because that's what I do.
If you lay a finger on my boy,
I'll come down on you so hard...
they'll need paint stripper to mop you up.
Commissioner Shields,
I presume.
Superintendent Walsh.
- Didn't get your name?
- Carter.
And would that be a Mr. Carter?
It'll be a Chief of Staff Carter.
Thank you for coming at such
short notice, gentlemen.
You will forgive a somewhat hasty pace,
but we must get into this matter.
This man is the subject of an investigation,
is he not?
Jimmy Vickers, yes sir. He's a
suspect in a series of murders.
At no point will he be taken into custody.
Is that understood?
Perhaps we could dispense
with the cloak-and-dagger
display here and start over, hmm?
I'm Commissioner Shields, London Met.
And you are?
The man who makes sure that you and the
rest of this exquisite country are safe
every second of every day.
We're somewhat embarrassed
this individual slipped
our grasp, but I assure you,
he belongs to us.
Your man heading up the investigation will
report on the hour.
And you will report to us.
Is that clear?
Just, eh, throw us a bone here,
will you?
Suffice to say, that he works for
a unit within the confines of
our military infrastructure
that may benefits us with
his character profile.
He's SAS.
It's a problem you do not want
on your streets.
A problem that only we can deal with.
I need him back where he belongs.
What...!
Open your mouth,
open your fuckin' mouth now.
Knock on the door,
knock on the door, now.
Who's there?
I don't know what the fuck your
problem is. Or who's payin' ya.
But I'll triple it, brother.
It's in that safe over there.
Paid a lot?
What's the code?
No, no, no...
- Let me out first.
- Right.
Wait! Wait...
Twenty-one. Six.
Forty-four.
Brotha?
What the fuck now?
What the fuck!
Brotha, what the fuck you want?
Brotha, talk to me!
Talk to me!!
What the fuck you want from me?
Talk to me...
bro!
No...no...no...no!
Bro...
- Sir, did you want to see me about something?
- Yeah, I do. Come in, have a seat.
Nick, give us the room.
Major coincidence is it,
that the last officer to
access to the files of these two gentlemen,
was you.
Prior to their deaths, I might add.
James Vickers,
soldier boy...
currently serving in a somewhat shady
department of her majesty's forces.
MID isn't exactly falling over itself
to fill us in, but we understand
interrogation is his specialty
and would you believe it?
They want to know the very moment
we apprehend him.
Is he done?
Or are there more?
I need to know who's next.
You don't need to know anythin'.
All you need to do is stay out of his way.
Well, I'm not staying out
of anyone's way, mate.
I'm gonna find him and
I'm gonna lock him up.
And whoever he's after,
for whatever they've done.
The last thing he's gonna do
is let you lock him up.
He's gonna wipe 'em out.
Or die tryin'.
"Die tryin" is good enough for me.
If he thinks he can go vigilante on my streets,
he's got another thing coming.
He doesn't care about you.
He doesn't care about the law.
He only wants one thing...
revenge.
He'll do more justice in one week
than we can do in a year.
We?
Mr. Griffin, I think we can safely say
you ceased being a police officer
the moment you started helping
your little friend out.
Well, good luck finding 'im, then.
It might take you a while.
But...hey...
slow justice is better than no justice.
"The UK could face austerity until 2018."
Jules, the boardline's "cat stuck in a tree", babe.
In it, you've got Morris on your major expense
report. Marcus on the tubes strike.
Well, that's it,
London's quiet.
Well, what about these murders?
Oh, I've hit a wall on that.
There's nothin' ongoing.
I thought you had a new lead?
Yeah, I'm waiting for more
information on it.
Don't wait too long, Abby's already
sniffin' to snatch it from ya.
Whoever you're stitching on,
let's have it.
Bitch.
Superintendent, how are you this morning?
Spencer, have you seen the papers?
What paper's that, sir?
Don't fuck with me today.
We have a real problem, son.
I want you to report to me on
the hour with this from now on.
Yes, sir.
You corner 'im, you call it in,
you do not get brave.
You wrap it up, you wrap it up, now.
Do you hear me?
Yes sir. Eh, I also think...
What?
Later.
Oh right, right, right. Ohhh.
What you want, mate?
I wanta go for a drive.
Where?
Right, right, right...
What's that?
Sarin. It's most dangerous in
any of its other forms. It's a gas.
Causes spasms, vomiting. That makes
your insides put out their own fire.
But this is liquid form.
And this...is what I'm goin' put
straight into your veins.
Makes so much, love,
what this is.
You're gonna be beggin' to
put a bullet inside ya.
Look at me.
- Any last words?
- Fuck you.
You feel betta now, do ya, huh? You
fuckin' pussy. You feel betta now?
- Yeah, a little bit. You?
- I will, mate.
What?
When I see your face in a minute,
I'm gonna put so much fuckin' back.
What the fuck are you talking about?
You got in the back of my car,
didn't ya?
Thinking you're holding all the cards.
You must be fuck-all Jimmy "fuckin" Vickers.
How long have we been driving for?
Ten...twenty minutes?
You didn't know,
did ya?
Didn't even know what was
in the boot of the car.
Fucking pricey, wasn't she's, brotha?
Popped a good fuckin' plan.
- Armed policemen, put it down!
- Move it, move it now!
- On the floor now!
- Move it!
Drop it now! Drop it!
Wait, wait!
I'm gonna give you the
count of three, Jimmy.
One...
Two...
You had 'im...
Who the fuck do you think you are?
You piece of fucking shit.
Don't fuckin' touch me.
You had 'im in the hospital
and you let 'im go.
Even though you know what he did,
you let him go and he killed his wife.
Tell him...tell him you're the reason
his wife is dead.
-Tell him!!
- Alright!!
I let him go. I let him go because I
knew he'd lead us to this fuckin' psychopath.
I mean, I didn't know he was gonna go
and do that.
But you know what?
Shit fuckin' happens.
Stand down.
What the fuck are you doing?
Alpha One to control. The suspect
has fled the scene on foot.
I say again. The suspect's fled
the scene on foot.
Roger. We're down.
What, you fucking insane? Are you
just gonna let him walk?
Are none of you gonna arrest him?
Alright, Jesus Christ. If you want something
done, do it your fuckin' self.
Oh, no, no, no, no!
Shut the fuck up!
Oyi!
What the fuck you want,
asshole?
You gonna do somethin'
'bout this?
You've got three seconds,
motherfucker.
Turn around and walk the fuck back
the way you came from.
One...
Two...
Three!
-== [ www.OpenSubtitles.org ] ==-