Created and Encoded by --  Bokutox -- of  www.YIFY-TORRENTS.com. The Best 720p/1080p/3d movies with the lowest file size on the internet.
Happy birthday,
dear Janice
Happy birthday to you!
lt's my
anorexic boss' birthday.
This means there's
a certain amount
of inter-office pressure
to stand around
the conference table
eating crappy food
and pretending
to worship her.
That's so good.
Acting for five minutes
like Janice doesn't make
all our lives miserable
is the hardest work
l'll do all day.
My job title
is account manager.
l used to be called
an account service
representative,
but a consultant told us
we needed to manage
our clients
and not service them.
l have a girlfriend whom
l neither manage nor service.
That's my best friend, Barry,
fucking her on an lKEA
kitchen table
l picked up
for a really good price.
l'm finding it
hard to care about
anything these days.
ln fact, the only thing l do
care about is the fact that
l can't care about anything.
Seriously. lt worries me.
My name is Wesley Gibson.
My dad walked out on my mom
when l was seven days old.
Sometimes l wonder if he ever
looked into my baby blues eyes
and asked himself,
"Did l just father
the most insignificant asshole
of the 21st century?"
Well, if you could get me
the consignment to me
by the 28th... Yeah.
Do you have the numbers
in front of you?
Relax.
If your name had come up,
you'd be dead already.
We've had some
unexpected losses recently.
We'd like to know
where our competitor
is getting his munition.
It's clean.
Meaning?
Meaning it's untraceable.
Your competitor's very smart.
Get down!
Fuck it.
No one leaves
the Fraternity, Cross.
l have a new perspective
on the Fraternity.
Careful.
You don't destroy something
that's been around
for a thousand years.
lt's already destroyed.
He broke the code.
l have to stop this.
Really?
You know this.
So why don't you
face me yourself?
Never send sheep
to kill a wolf.
They were just
the decoys.
Goodbye, Mr. X.
Never send sheep
to kill a wolf.
They were just
the decoys.
Wesley!
What is it?
What do you mean,
"What is it"? Listen.
Well, how am I
suppose to sleep with
all that fucking racket?
When are we gonna move
so we don't have to
wake up to that shit?
I kind of like it.
lt helps to drown out
the sound of your annoying,
fucking voice.
Now, please, let me sleep.
Have you even thought
about our talk?
Yes.
Which one?
Perfect. That's perfect.
Feed Annabelle.
Sorry.
Oh, my fucking God.
I hope that's not
my billing report
sitting on your desk.
Holy shit on an altar, it is.
I want that report
on my desk in one hour.
Okay, everybody,
we're all gonna stay
an extra hour...
Want to hear
something sad?
l need an ergonomic keyboard
to keep my repetitive stress
injury in check.
Just the fact that l repeat
something enough
that it causes me
stress is fucking sad.
Nice job, dude.
You seen Barry?
He had to go
to the dentist.
Again.
Yes!
Barry!
You think they have that
morning-after pill here?
That thing works.
Crush it up,
put it in her omelet,
"Hey, baby, breakfast
in bed." You can never
be too safe.
Oh, God.
I lost my wallet
somewhere.
All this together?
No, no.
Yes.
He is the man.
How much is it?
Oh. Plus this.
$20.42.
Watermelon.
Chicks dig it.
Thanks.
See you next time.
Have a good night.
I love these
energy drinks, man.
I'm almost, like, kind of on
an energy drink cleanse,
where I do one for breakfast
and then, like, two
or three for lunch.
l'm the man?
Yeah, right,
Barry, l'm the man.
ln fact, l'm so much the man,
l have a standing prescription
for medication to control
my anxiety attacks.
God, I wish I had
something else
to relieve my stress.
Hello, Wesley.
You know,
there are people,
beautiful people,
you just wish they could see
you in a different setting,
a different place,
instead of where you are,
what you've become.
Nicole is so hot.
What?
Boom goes the dynamite.
But most of all,
you wish you weren't
such a pussy
for wishing for things
that will never change.
Good God A'mighty,
you're over here like
it's spring fucking break,
and I still don't have
that billing report.
Why do I even
keep you around, Wesley?
I'll get it done, Janice.
Like I never
heard that before.
"I'll get it done."
"I'll get it done.
I'll get it done, Janice.
"I'll get it done."
Why don't you have
anything to say
for yourself?
I'm sorry.
Well, you're worthless.
I'm the one who's sorry
I hired your ass.
You know what
the best thing is about
the end of the day?
Tomorrow it starts
all over again.
Hi. How you doing?
Good.
I'm sorry?
You apologize too much.
Sorry about that.
I knew your father.
My father left
the week I was born,
so...
Your father died yesterday
on the rooftop of
the Metropolitan Building.
Sorry.
Look, the liquor rounds
are just over there, so...
Your father was one of
the greatest assassins
who ever lived.
The man who killed him
is behind you.
This guy's just
shooting up...
Sorry. Sorry.
What... Oh, my God!
Oh, my God!
What the fuck just happened?
Please! Please!
Please drive faster.
Please be quiet.
Please drive...
Please drive faster.
Please... Please understand
that I care about my life!
I don't know what the fuck
you did to piss this guy off,
but you're gonna
have to let me out
and call the cops!
Hey! Hey!
What are you doing?
Oh, shit! Are you crazy?
Oh, shit!
I think we lost him.
Could you let me out
at the next corner, please?
Shit!
Fuck!
Oh, shit!
He's right there!
Look, I'm an accountant.
I'm just an accountant.
Oh, fuck!
He's fucking persistent,
you know.
Fuck!
You kick his ass!
Shoot him!
What are you doing?
What are you shooting
our car for, huh?
Are you crazy?
Grab the wheel.
Where are you going?
Get back in here!
Oh, my God!
Oh, damn! I'm sorry.
Gun!
What?
Under the seat!
Here.
Oh, shit!
Shit!
Look out!
Get out!
Look out! Oh, my God!
Shit!
I'm sorry!
Behind you!
Fuck.
Shit. Shit.
Hello.
I don't have any money or...
I thought he'd be
taller.
Taller?
Sir...
Sir, I've been trying
to explain to the lady here
that I'm an accountant.
I'm an account service
representative... I'm
an account manager.
And I'm sure
that if you call
my boss, Janice,
she'd fill you in
on whatever
has gone wrong.
You can contact her
by email or...
She'll put you straight.
Shoot the wings
off the flies.
I don't know
what that means.
Shoot the wings
off the flies.
I really think
you have me mixed up
with somebody else.
On three.
Either you shoot,
or I do.
One.
Okay.
Two.
I can't even see them!
Three.
Okay. Okay.
That's impossible.
A lot of things
for you weren't possible
before today.
What you experienced, Wesley,
was not a panic attack.
Your heart was beating
in excess of 400 beats
per minute,
sending abundant amounts
of adrenaline into
your bloodstream.
This allows you to see
and react faster than normal.
Only a few people
in the world can do that.
Your father could do it
and you can do it.
With a little work,
you can learn
to control these attacks.
Stay away from me.
Just stay back from me.
I have a gun, sir.
All right?
My name is Sloan.
This is Fox.
And the others you see
around you are all
very good at killing.
So, if I were you,
I'd keep the gun
pointed at me.
You don't wanna
point it at any of them.
That's better.
You're insane.
No.
Insanity is wasting
your life as a nothing
when you have
the blood of a killer
flowing in your veins.
Insanity is being shit on,
beat down,
coasting through life
in a miserable existence
when you have a caged lion
locked inside
and a key to release it.
This gun you're holding
is an Imanishi 17.
It belonged to your father.
He could conduct
a symphony orchestra
with it.
And you're going to use it
to kill the man who shot him
down in cold blood.
I can't...
The same man who tried
to kill you tonight.
Your father was one of us.
A fraternity of assassins.
The weapons of fate.
We've transferred
all of his assets
over to you.
And let me assure you,
they are substantial.
It is your
long-awaited destiny
to join us.
Back off. Back off.
You don't know
anything about me.
Stay away from me.
You stay away from me?
You stay away from me, please?
Will you let me through?
You know when
you have a dream
and you're half awake,
but it's still in
the fringe of your brain?
Then you open your eyes
and you're so damn glad
it was a dream.
This was nothing like that.
I'm sorry.
Could you just give me
one second? Thank you.
Oh, shit.
Wesley.
Hey.
What's up with you?
What do you mean?
You're... You're here early.
Is... You seem
a little pepped up.
You all right?
Well, yeah.
Yeah.
I guess I feel
kind of different.
Whatever. I'm gonna go
get some Post-it Notes.
Do you want one?
No.
Really?
Yeah.
Okay.
Jesus H. fucking Popsicle,
I still don't have
my billing reports,
but you've got time
to sit here
and Google your ass off.
Well, I know one thing.
You've got your review
coming up next week,
and I can't wait to start
checking me off
some big fucking boxes.
Attitude, poor!
Performance, poor!
Management skills, poor!
Works well with others.
That's a fucking joke.
What is this bullshit?
Who's this prick?
Some loser gets
his head blown off
at the Metropolitan...
Shut the fuck up!
She has one single
iota of tenuous power.
She thinks she can
push everyone around.
You don't need this.
I understand.
Junior high must have
been kind of tough,
but it doesn't give you the
right to treat your workers
like horseshit, Janice.
I know we laugh at you,
Janice.
We all know you keep
your stash of jelly donuts in
the top drawer of your desk.
But I want you to know
if you weren't such a bitch,
we'd feel sorry for you.
I do feel sorry for you.
But as it stands,
the way you behave,
I feel I can speak
for the entire office
when I tell you
go fuck yourself.
Yeah. That was great, bro.
Who's the man?
I'm the man.
That's a bad idea.
Couldn't find
your keys, huh?
That could be handy.
You going to teach me that?
I might need that.
So, Fox, right?
What is that?
Is that a call sign?
Is it like Maverick
in Top Gun?
You could tell me,
but you'd have to kill me?
I'm just kidding.
Peter!
Check the shuttle rotation
on this STB.
It should be 300 per minute.
This kind of cotton weave,
the opposing thread count
should be 4,000.
Hey, this is
pretty awesome, huh?
Is it a front?
Front for what?
I don't know.
Assassinations.
You may think this is
a front for something,
all I can tell you
is this is a textile mill.
And George...
George, go help
Peter up there.
Yeah.
This is a textile mill.
And a damn good one.
Yeah, that's cute,
but that's bullshit, right?
I mean, all these guys
are killers, aren't they?
I think you owe me
some answers.
All right.
Clearly I don't understand,
but do you make sweaters
or do you kill people?
That's an awful lot
of questions over coffee.
Are you sure
you're ready
for the answers?
Yes, I'm sure.
I can't go back.
Not to my life.
He's all yours.
All right. We're up.
How you doing?
I'm The Repairman.
What do you repair?
A lifetime of bad habits.
Okay.
Would you do me a favor?
Just put your arms
behind your back.
Uh...
It's okay.
I don't know...
Just behind your back.
Is this okay?
Just relax.
Is this part of it?
There we go.
You going to put a bag
over my head?
No.
There's no need for a bag.
That's not too tight, is it?
No, that's nice.
Why did you come here, Wesley?
Well, you brought me here,
remember?
What the fuck
did you do that...
How many punches
did The Repairman throw
before he was counting sheep?
Well, I haven't spent
a lot of time having my face
smashed in before, all right?
Did you spend
a lot of time
with knives?
At breakfast,
lunch and dinner.
Fuck.
It was a rhetorical
question, culo.
You interrupt me again,
I use the business end.
Here's what you need
to know, puto.
Knives are easy to hide.
They don't jam
and they never
run out of bullets.
They come in handy
when you have to do some
close contact work.
What the fuck, man?
Come here. Come here.
What?
Now, try to cut me.
Try to cut me. Hey!
Just stick me with that...
Be careful with that.
That's sharp.
Just stick
and stick and stick.
Why?
Seriously, man,
I could hurt you.
Hey!
Okay, pussy.
I'm not a pussy.
You're a pussy.
No, I'm not a pussy.
You're a pussy!
I'm not a pussy.
I got a healthy respect
for the human condition.
Fuck that, you pussy!
I'm not a pussy!
You're a pussy!
Come on, pussy.
I'm not a pussy!
Hi. How you doing?
What the fuck?
The fuck!
Just a moment.
Sorry.
Hello? Hey!
Hey, come back! Hey!
You must drink.
Drink. Yeah.
What is this?
This is the recovery room.
This bath stimulates
white blood cells
and speed up the process.
In here, bruises, cuts, breaks
heal in hours, not days.
You shitting me?
Shh.
What is that? Vodka?
Yeah.
Are you Russian?
Get up.
This is The Gunsmith.
He knows more about a piece
than anybody, and he's gonna
teach you how to use one.
How you doing?
Pretty good.
You know that
Seltzer broke his leg?
Oh, really?
Yeah, in three places.
How'd he do that?
Jumped off a building.
So, is he okay?
Yeah.
It's pretty bad, though.
Oh, my God.
Oh, my God, you guys,
that is so realistic.
He's been in recovery for,
like, three days now,
and they say they're not even
gonna let him out.
Oh, my God.
Oh, my God!
Hey, we can't shoot
a dead woman! She might
be somebody's mom...
You need to know
what it's like to put
a bullet in a body.
Why are you here?
You know, I thought
I was learning to be
some kind of super assassin.
You know,
if I wanted to get beat up,
I would have
stayed in my cubicle,
you know.
Fuck.
All right,
shoot the target.
From there.
You want me
shoot through Wilbur?
I want you
to curve the bullet.
How am I suppose to do that?
It's not a question of how,
it's a question of what.
If no one told you
that bullets flew straight
and I gave you a gun
and told you to
hit the target,
what would you do?
Let your instincts guide you.
How the hell
did he do that?
Can you do that?
Can you do that? Hello?
Hey, I think
that's my old train.
Still is.
Shit! You fucking asshole!
Come on!
Let's go.
Are you out
of your fucking mind?
Oh, shit. Oh, shit.
Oh, God, I feel...
I feel... I feel...
I feel kind of good.
He got Rictus.
Perfect shot.
Impossible angle.
Cross is taking us out
one by one.
And Wesley is the only one
who can get to him.
Cross gets closer
with each hour.
Get back to work.
See that?
It's a shuttle.
Okay.
I want you to try
and catch it.
You want me to
stick my hand
in there?
Yes. I want you to catch it.
You wanna put a gun
to my head?
I can just slow things down
like with the flies.
You need to learn
to control that
by yourself.
Fuck, fuck, fuck!
This is bullshit! Fuck this!
How's it going today,
Wesley?
No. Fuck the loom
and fuck The Repairman!
I can shoot the wings
off the back of a fly!
I'm ready!
You're ready when Fox
says you're ready.
Who put her in charge?
I did.
Wesley.
People think you use cheese
to catch these beauties.
But they go apeshit
for peanut butter.
Your father was
a big fan of this.
Watch.
Plastic explosive
and peanut butter!
Sorry, Mickey.
Five, four, three, two, one.
Hey. Hey, Russian.
Good for one. Yeah.
Imagine if you had
a thousand.
They really fucked you up,
didn't they?
What the hell
did they do to you?
Throw you in front of
a moving train for no reason?
Beat the shit out of you?
You know, you can say it,
this place is bullshit.
It's bullshit, huh?
Bullshit!
Repairman. Five minutes.
Heads up out of the question?
Fuck.
You're a waste
of my fucking time!
Why are you here?
I don't know, so hit me.
I had a shit life,
so why wouldn't I?
I wanna kick your fucking ass!
Tell me what
you want me to say.
Why are you here?
I don't know!
I don't know why I'm here.
Why are you here?
I don't know who I am.
What did you say?
I said...
I said I don't know who I am.
Do you really want
to know who you are?
Yeah. It's my room.
No.
This was your father's room.
What happened?
A member of this
fraternity went rogue.
Cross.
He started by killing
the one man who was
better than him.
Your father.
Blindsided him
on a rooftop.
Betrayed him.
Everything in this room,
books, weapons, clothes,
belonged to him.
Now they belong to you.
Find a connection
in this room, Wesley.
It may be the only way
of finding out who you are.
Now l know
why l could never care
about anything before this.
l was living a lie.
Finally,
l have a chance to step
into my father's shoes.
Grow a pair.
Live the life
l was born to live.
l've been pissing it
all away like it was another
fucking billing report.
l have to train harder.
l have to be as good
as my father.
On these shelves,
Wesley, are the records
of the Fraternity kills,
everything you will need
to kill your target.
To kill Cross,
the man who betrayed
the Fraternity and murdered
my father, l must prepare.
l have to become his student,
memorize every move
he ever made,
every attack he ever executed.
When he dropped a patient
in an airtight room surrounded
by Secret Service agents.
When he took out that
businessman in the elevator.
His bullets untraceable,
of course.
Or how no matter
what the weapon or how
he eliminated his target,
he was always
one chess move ahead.
One move more prepared.
One step quicker.
One shot more precise.
ln fact, in all my research,
l found that he never
missed a target.
Not until me.
Yeah!
First time in your life,
Wesley, you're in control.
Shoot the target.
You're crazy.
Welcome to the Fraternity.
We call this
the Loom of Fate.
After today,
you will never
set foot in here again.
Why not?
Because, like an apostle,
your task is not to interpret,
but to deliver.
Every culture in history
has a secret code,
one you won't find
in traditional texts.
A thousand years ago,
a clan of weavers
discovered a mystical language
hidden in the fabric.
They called themselves
the Fraternity.
I'll be honest with you,
all I see are threads.
Come here.
Look there.
Do you see that one thread
that missed the weave
and lies on top of the others?
Like a mistake?
No, it's a code.
If the vertical thread
is on top, it's a one.
If it's below, it's a zero.
Binary code?
What does it say?
It's a name.
A target.
Where do the names
come from?
Come out of a necessity,
Wesley.
A necessity to maintain
balance in the world.
They are orders
that must be executed,
entrusted to us so that
we might forge
stability out of chaos.
This one is yours.
I don't...
Look, I thought
you brought me here
to kill Cross.
You will.
In time.
This is your first assignment.
The loom provides,
I interpret,
you deliver.
You want me to kill
Robert Deane Darden?
Not me.
Fate.
The target will be
in the conference room,
sitting at the head chair.
There are six windows.
You will shoot
through the fifth.
Fifth window.
Now.
What did he do
that he deserves to die?
You don't know.
I don't know if he was bad,
I don't know if he was evil.
I don't know
anything about him.
We get our orders from a loom.
Fate.
And we're suppose to
take it on faith that
what we're doing is right.
Killing someone
we know nothing about,
I don't know if I can do that.
About 20 years ago,
there was this girl.
Her dad was a federal judge,
so she probably had it in
her mind that she was gonna
follow in his footsteps.
So she's home one Christmas,
and her dad's on this big
racketeering case.
The defendants want
to get a softer judge.
One they can buy off.
So they hire this guy,
Max Petridge,
get him to pay her father
a visit.
And the way he pays
people a visit
is to break in
and tie up their loved ones,
and force them to watch
while he burns
his targets alive.
And then he takes
a wire hanger
and twists it round
and brands his initials
into each one of them so
they will never ever forget.
After I was recruited
into the Fraternity,
I found out
that Max Petridge's name
had come up
weeks before
the federal judge
was killed,
and that a Fraternity member
had failed to pull
the trigger.
We don't know
how far the ripples
of our decisions go.
You kill one, and maybe,
save a thousand.
That's the code
of the Fraternity.
That's what we believe in,
and that's why we do it.
Now!
Cross.
Not yet.
Your target will be
in a black limo.
He always travels the same
six blocks of Halsted.
You have three blocks
to kill him.
Shit.
I'm sorry.
Barry!
Could you feed Annabelle?
Wesley. Hey,
where have you been?
I have really missed you, man.
Look at the big man.
You fucking asshole! What?
What? You don't
show up for weeks,
now you're just gonna stop by
and use the bathroom?
You think you're a real
big shot now, huh?
No. You know what?
You are nothing!
No, you are less than nothing.
You're not even half
the man that Barry is.
Barry, he pleases me
in ways that you've never
even heard of!
Who the hell is she, Wesley?
Your new whore?
Is that what it takes now?
You're paying for it?
Wesley?
He's the man.
You all right?
Yeah.
Yeah. I'm okay.
Go sit down.
I'm gonna find a car.
Big night.
I got to get into recovery.
Shit.
Fuck!
Bull's-eye.
What's he doing here?
Come on!
Come on. Just stay with us.
Pull back his jacket.
Breathe. Breathe, all right?
It's all right.
A thousand.
Come on!
No! No! Stay with us.
Come on.
Open your eyes!
Come on!
This bullet is the first
traceable bullet
he's ever used.
It was made by this man.
His name is Pekwarsky.
He works out of
what is now a monastery
in Eastern Moravia.
This place is where
the Fraternity was born.
He's taunting me.
He's sending me a message.
I'm gonna send him one back.
He's trapping you.
Leading you to a place
he knows very well.
Look, I know this. I...
This is what
you trained me for.
You can't go alone.
I go alone
or he doesn't show.
He's not stupid.
Look, a member
of the Fraternity is dead
because of me.
Okay.
Go.
Thank you.
I don't think
that's a good idea.
Your next assignment.
Pekwarsky?
Shit.
What are you doing here?
Lower your gun.
You recognize this?
I pulled this
out of my shoulder.
The guy who put it there
killed my father.
Now, I know you made it,
so tell me where he is.
I did mold this,
but I can't be responsible
for the people who use them.
I don't give a shit.
Tell me where he is.
Look at my finger.
I can try and arrange a meet.
Have you ever thought about
doing things differently?
How do you mean?
I don't know.
Being somebody else.
Somebody normal.
No.
Shit.
Out of the way!
Stay.
Hey!
He's on the train.
He's alone.
Thank you.
Sorry. I'm sorry. Sit down!
Sir, sit down!
Nobody's gonna get hurt.
Sir, sit... Sit down!
Sir, sit down!
Get out of the way! Sit down!
Stay down! Stay down!
Stay down! It's okay!
Sit down!
Wesley.
Out of the way!
No, no, no!
Wesley, listen to me.
Shut the fuck up!
You don't get to talk to me.
Everything they told you
was a lie.
Shut up,
you lying piece of shit.
You shut the fuck up.
You are my son.
What did you say?
What did you say to me?
Is it true?
Yes.
Why did you make me do this?
Because you are
the only person
he wouldn't kill.
You knew, God damn it.
You knew the entire time.
Well, his name came up.
So did yours.
No, it was okay.
Never mind.
No. No, it was complete shit.
I promised your father
I'd bring you back here.
What the fuck?
He said
it was the only way
you'd believe.
Your father
was never more than
a camera click away.
That's me.
He was my father.
And I killed him.
To your father, protecting you
was worth giving up his life.
Protect me?
He was trying
to fucking kill me!
No. He wasn't trying
to kill you.
He was trying to rescue you.
When Cross
left the Fraternity,
Sloan hunted you down.
Ever since Fox had her teeth
in you, he's been trying
to separate you from them.
Your father never wanted you
in the Fraternity, Wesley.
He wanted a different
path for you,
with things that
he could never have.
A home.
Peace.
No.
He hoped you would
find your own way.
Your father got
hold of this.
Decipher it yourself.
Sloan began manufacturing
targets of his own
for profit years ago.
Your father found out
about it.
And he was going
to do something about it
on his own, right?
But Sloan turned
everyone against him.
My father's name never
even came up, did it?
No. Holding to the code
made him a target.
Yes.
You want me to run?
No.
I want you to live.
You can have
a different life, Wesley.
Like your father
wanted for you.
We trained him well.
My father
was wrong about one thing.
Everything they told me
wasn't a lie.
They taught me how to kill,
how to feel no pain,
and most importantly,
that every job has
a perfect weapon.
Well, l'm the perfect weapon.
And l'm supposed to run?
No, l've been doing that
my entire life.
So l say no.
l say kill them all
and let fate
sort out the mess.
Kill him.
He's here!
Pussy.
Pussy, pussy.
Sloan!
My father wasn't a traitor.
This is a kill order.
And it's got
Sloan's name on it.
What did you say to me?
It's a name. It's a target.
I don't want this person dead.
Fate does.
Fate wanted you dead.
And he couldn't take it.
So he started manufacturing
his own targets
for his own gains.
And that's when my dad
found out and decided
to stand against him.
And that's
when you sent
a man's son
to kill his father.
You're not
an assassin of fate,
Sloan.
You're just a thug
who can bend bullets.
Is that true?
Here is what the truth is.
Your name came up.
Your name.
Yours.
Everyone in this room.
If I had not done
what I did,
you would all be dead.
I saved your lives.
Now look where we are.
We are stronger than ever.
Changing the course
of history as we see it.
Choosing the targets
we select.
We can redistribute power
where we see fit.
The wolves rule.
Not the sheep.
Now, if any of you feel
the need to follow the code
of the Fraternity
to the letter,
I invite you to take your gun,
put it in your mouth
and pull the trigger.
That is what Wesley demands.
Otherwise,
shoot this motherfucker
and let us take
our Fraternity of
Assassins to heights
reserved only
for the gods of men.
You choose.
Fuck the code.
Sloan!
Six weeks ago,
l was ordinary and pathetic.
Just like you.
But who am l now?
Account manager?
Assassin?
Or just another tool
who was mind-fucked
into killing his father?
l am all of these.
And l am none of these.
Who am l now?
This is not me
fulfilling my destiny.
This is not me following
in my father's footsteps.
This is definitely not me
saving the world.
Still trying
to figure out
who you are?
This is not me.
This is just
a motherfucking decoy.
Oh, fuck.
This is me taking control.
From Sloan,
from the Fraternity,
from Janice,
from billing reports,
from ergonomic keyboards,
from cheating girlfriends
and sack-of-shit best friends.
This is me taking back control
of my life.
What the fuck
have you done lately?