Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org
(SOFTLY) Captain!
(ALL GASP)
(CHITTERS)
Is that a trench?
It looks like there's
more of them inside.
(EXHALES HEAVILY)
Echo 2-6 to command.
(MUFFLED RESPONSE)
Colonel, we've got eyes on
three Kong in the north woods.
One of them is armed.
And our donkey
just spotted another trench.
Maybe the base is near.
Yes, sir.
Yes, sir, copy. Over.
Hey, donkey.
(GRUNTS SOFTLY)
Preacher.
The one with the gun.
As soon as the gunner's down,
you guys take out the trench.
Yes, sir.
(HORSE NEIGHS)
CAPTAIN: Fire!
Come on!
(SOLDIERS YELLING)
(CHITTERING)
(CONTINUES CHITTERING)
(SOLDIERS YELLING)
(INDISTINCT YELLING)
(SCREAMING)
(WHOOPING)
Reload!
(MUFFLED SCREAMING)
(GROANING)
Fall back! Fall back!
(SOLDIERS GROANING
AND SCREAMING)
(PANTING)
Colonel, do you copy?
Colonel!
THE COLONEL: Who is this?
Preacher, sir!
It's Preacher!
Where are you, soldier?
I need your position.
I don't know!
What do you see?
I can't see anything, sir.
We lost a lot of men,
and the captain is dead, sir.
Okay, calm down.
You're in command now.
Command, sir?
I think it's just me
all by myself now.
(DISTORTED) Take control.
Colonel, I don't think
I'm gonna make it, sir.
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry, sir.
Listen to me.
You kill as many as you can.
(GRUNTING)
No! No, no!
Sixty-three dead.
You're him.
You're Caesar.
We've been searching
for you for so long.
We heard you had
a hidden command base.
But we could never find it.
Some of us started to think
that you might be dead.
But Colonel McCullough said
you were out here somewhere.
TRAVIS: Just kill us already.
LANG: Shut up, man!
What? They're animals.
He's gonna slaughter us.
I did not start this war.
The ape who did is dead.
His name was Koba.
I killed him.
Now, I fight only...
to protect apes.
Yeah?
What about him?
We've got 10 more
just like him.
I know these apes.
They follow Koba.
They tried to kill me.
They fear
what I will do to them.
So now, they serve you.
Just to survive.
I don't fear you.
(APES CHITTERING)
You must fear.
How long you think
woods can protect you?
Humans destroy you.
Their Kerna has all power.
For them,
he more than just human.
He everything.
He say: first Caesar die...
then all of you die.
(BOTH GRUNTING)
Winter! Take this traitor outside!
What should we do with the humans?
(HEAVY BREATHING)
You're letting us go?
Tell your Colonel
you have seen me now...
and I have a message for him.
Leave us the woods,
and the killing can stop.
Do you think they will
give him the message?
They are the message,
Maurice.
He will see
we are not savages.
(WINTER CHITTERING)
The traitor attacked me! He got away!
(HUFFS)
CAESAR: Koba...
still haunts us.
Why didn't I see...
that he could not forgive
what humans did to him?
(GRUNTS)
No one could have known
how much darkness...
...was living inside him.
(HORN BLOWING)
(CHITTERING)
(ALL CHITTERING)
Father...!
(BOTH BREATHING HEAVILY)
Welcome home, Rocket.
You look tired.
It was a long journey.
Father, we found something!
Come.
(ALL CHITTERING)
Mother...!
Cornelius...
Say hi to your brother!
Look who's here, son...
Lake...
This is it, father...
We can start over... A new home.
What is beyond those mountains, son?
Show them, Rocket...
A desert!
The journey is long...
But that is why humans will not find us.
We must leave tonight!
Tonight? That's impossible!
How long can we wait, Lake?
Soldiers getting closer!
Winter...
(CHITTERING)
Your son's been gone, Caesar...
He doesn't know how hard it's been.
I know you are scared...
We all are...
But we are still planning...
Yes.
We must find a safe way
out of the woods.
There were only two of you.
But we are... many.
We will find a way
out of here.
Apes together...
strong.
(ALL CHITTERING)
Stay here, son!
Protect your mother and brother!
(RAGGED BREATHING)
(GASPS)
(GROWLS)
Caesar! What's wrong?!
How many on patrol?
Five? Six?
Get them!
Luca, get Rocket, too.
(GASPS)
(GRUNTING)
Lima four to command.
Colonel, did you... (GRUNTS)
(GRUNTING)
CAESAR: Rocket!
What happened?
I heard him talking! The Colonel is here!
THE COLONEL:
99, target acquired.
99, target acquired. Repeat.
King Kong is dead.
Let's go.
I can get out from here.
(GRUNTING)
(APES HOWLING)
(HUFFING)
(YELLING)
(GASPING)
(PANTING)
Caesar...
We can't find Winter!
He was scared! I think he betrayed us!
Have you found Cornelius yet?
We're still searching.
Let's go look for Caesar's little son.
(SIGHS)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(RUSTLING)
(PANTING)
(SIGHING)
(STUTTERS) Cornelius!
(CORNELIUS CRYING)
You're safe now.
Lake...
You loved my son.
Look after his brother
until I return.
You're not coming with us to our new home?
No.
Go with Lake.
Caesar!
You're not going after them?!
Not them. Him.
Caesar, you are our leader!
We can't leave without you!
You must.
The soldiers
will be back soon.
Father!
When I find him...
the soldiers will
all come after me.
That may give you
the best chance
to get out of the woods.
Where is he going?!
Caesar! Caesar!
The soldiers' camp is always moving.
My guards think they know where it is.
Let me take you.
You need me to back you up!
No.
Please...
I know what it's like...
...to lose a son.
I may not make it back.
That's why I'm coming.
To make sure you do.
Guards think soldiers here...
Always fires burning.
No one here...
CAESAR: Search the area.
I'm just gonna
put this down.
(GUNSHOTS)
(GROANS)
(ALL EXCLAIM IN SURPRISE)
What's he doing out here alone?
Maybe he's a deserter?
(CLATTERING)
(CHITTERING)
Look around.
Take what you can.
(MUTTERS)
(GRUNTS)
(STRAINING)
(CHITTERS)
(CHITTERING)
Something wrong with her.
I don't think she can speak.
Come.
She'll die out here alone.
We cannot take her, Maurice.
I understand...
But I cannot leave her.
(SCOFFS)
(CAESAR BREATHING HEAVILY)
Did you find the Colonel?
CAESAR: No.
Winter.
(CAESAR BREATHING HEAVILY)
(GASPS)
Where's the Colonel?
He's gone.
Gone?
He left this morning...
...took many men with him.
More soldiers are coming
down from the North.
The Colonel is going to meet them...
...at the border.
What border? Why?
I don't know.
But the rest of us are going tomorrow.
The donkeys think the
soldiers from the North...
...are coming to help finish
off the apes for good.
That day, after the battle on the hill...
The donkey we caught promised me
the Colonel would spare my life...
If I told them where you were hiding.
Forgive me!
My son...
my wife...
are dead.
(GASPS)
(WHIMPERING)
(INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS)
(GRUNTING)
(CHOKING)
(MUFFLED GRUNTING)
Now what do we do?
Wait till the soldiers go...
Follow them to the Colonel.
Koba!
Ape...
not kill ape.
(GASPS)
(MAURICE CHITTERING)
The soldiers are leaving!
(INDISTINCT YELLING)
They stopped.
(MUFFLED GUNSHOTS)
Get down!
(GIRL GASPS)
(MUFFLED GUNSHOTS CONTINUE)
What are they shooting at?
I don't know.
(GASPS)
(CHITTERING)
(GROANING)
(SOLDIER PANTING)
Why did they shoot you?
(MUMBLING)
Like her!
He cannot speak!
He will die of those wounds.
Luca...
Where did the soldiers go?!
Winter said they were
going to a border.
Yes, but which way is that?!
(ROARING)
(GIRL GASPS)
(URGING HORSES)
(CHITTERS)
(SOFT CLATTERING)
(COCKS GUN)
(SNARLING)
Bad Ape!
Bad Ape.
Who are you?
What are you doing here?
I don't think he understands.
I don't recognize him.
He's not one of us.
Are you alone here?
(CHITTERING)
Cold?
Cold.
I see girl,
I think you human.
But you ape.
Like me.
No, put down.
How long have
you been here?
Long time.
Long, long time.
(EXCLAIMS EXCITEDLY)
Home.
Old home.
Are there more like you?
More apes from zoo.
Dead. All dead.
Long time.
Human get sick.
Ape get smart.
Then human kill ape.
But not me.
I run.
You learn to speak...
Listen. Human...
"Bad Ape!"
Bad Ape. Huh?
(SCRAPING)
No.
No touch.
(STUTTERS) That's mine.
(THUDDING)
(BAD APE GRUNTS)
BAD APE: I'm okay!
(CLATTERING)
Amazing...
Always thought we were the only ones.
Wonder if there are more in the world?
More apes like us.
Eat! Eat.
(PANTING)
New friends.
Special day.
Where did you get this?
Bad place.
I find long time ago.
After zoo, I look for food...
I find human zoo.
Zoo for sick.
Big walls.
Sick human climb.
Bad human kill.
And then, all get sick.
All dead now for a long time.
Long time.
Bad humans?
Soldiers?
Soldiers.
A deserted military camp!
On the border!
Maybe the Colonel and the
troops are going there?
Is it far? Can you take us?
Human zoo?
No. No, no go back there.
Everyone dead. I come here.
Very safe here.
Never go back.
Please, you must take us!
No! No! Cannot take!
(CHITTERING)
Cannot take. No! No!
Look! Look!
More snow. Cannot go.
Must stay.
You eat, you rest.
Stay here with me.
Here, you keep.
She keep.
BAD APE: Who is...
child?
I don't know.
But she with you.
She has no one else.
I see you look at her
just now.
Look sad.
You have child?
One.
The other was
killed by human.
Soldier?
I had child.
You think
you will find him...
at human zoo?
With soldier?
I don't know.
Maybe.
Then...
maybe I take you.
(GRUNTS)
(CHITTERS)
Thirsty.
(DISTANT INDISTINCT
CONVERSATIONS)
Luca, come.
Let's go closer.
Keep them safe.
(CONVERSATIONS CONTINUE)
What are they doing?
I don't know.
What's that? A patrol?
CAESAR: I don't see riders.
(SOLDIER GRUNTS)
Hold it! (GROANS)
I saw them coming!
(LUCA GROANS)
(GROANING)
At least this time...
I was able to protect you.
(CRYING)
(CONTINUES CRYING)
Caesar...
This must stop...
It's not too late to join the other apes...
We cannot turn back!
Luca gave his life!
Please...!
They must pay.
Now...
...you sound like Koba.
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
It was a mistake
bringing you all.
This is my fight.
I will finish this alone.
Go.
Now!
Join the others.
(CHITTERING)
(PANTING)
(GASPING)
What happened?
They came out of nowhere...
Attacked us.
We thought they would kill us all...
But the Colonel stopped them!
(BREATHING SHARPLY)
There was madness in his eyes!
He said they would use us, before we died!
And they brought us all here!
(COUGHING)
Use you?
They've been forcing us to work!
What...
What kind of work?
Wait.
My little son. Is he here?
(FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING)
(CAESAR GRUNTS)
THE COLONEL: Grant and Lee...
Wellington...
and Napoleon...
Custer...
and Sitting Bull...
You're probably
not much of a reader.
But this is a big moment.
Where were you?
We came upon your herd.
We got lucky.
But I was surprised
you weren't with them.
(GRUNTING)
SOLDIER: Hey, hey, hey!
I hope you don't come
to regret sparing his life.
He's quite a good shot.
Have you finally come
to save your apes?
I came for you.
For me?
Who did I kill that night?
My wife.
My son.
I'm sorry.
I was there for you.
My God.
Look at your eyes.
Almost human.
How did you know
I was here?
I was told you were coming.
That more soldiers
from the North...
would be joining you here.
Joining me?
To finish us off.
For good.
Who told you that?
Okay.
Let's go.
(CAESAR GRUNTING)
(INDISTINCT TAUNTING)
(APES CHITTERING)
(GRUNTS)
Father!
(SIGHS)
Lake...
Forgive them.
We've been through much.
(CORNELIUS CHITTERING)
Father!
What have I done?
Battalion, halt!
Blood!
SOLDIERS:
Makes the grass grow!
We!
SOLDIERS: Make the blood flow!
COMMANDING OFFICER:
We are the beginning!
ALL: And the end!
(ALL CHEERING)
(CHEERING STOPS)
(WHISTLE BLOWING)
(ANTHEM PLAYING
OVER PA SYSTEM)
(SOLDIERS YELLING)
(ALL GRUNTING)
We haven't had food or
water since we got here...
(CHITTERS)
Why do they need a wall?
BOYLE: Hey!
(APE CHITTERS)
Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey!
(STRAINING)
(ALL SCREAMING)
(APES CHITTERING)
BOYLE: Hey!
Donkey!
Get him.
Okay, okay, okay...
(RED DONKEY GRUNTING)
(GRUNTS)
(GROANING)
(WHIPPING CONTINUES)
Leave him!
(APE CHITTERS)
(ALL CHITTERING)
(ALL CONTINUE CHITTERING)
(GROANS)
(RED DONKEY YELLING)
(CHITTERING STOPS)
(WHIPPING)
(RED DONKEY GRUNTS)
(GRUNTS)
(CAESAR EXHALES)
Tell them to get back to work.
Apes need food and water.
Tell them.
Give them food...
and water.
(GUNSHOT)
(APE GRUNTS)
(APES CHITTERING)
Five...
Four...
(LAKE GRUNTS)
Three...
(LAKE PANTING)
Two...
(PANTING)
(GRUNTS)
Hurry! Back to work!
(HEAVY BREATHING)
String him up, donkey.
Bad place.
(STUTTERING)
Bad, bad place.
What you see?
Must save them!
But how?
Must think!
What would Caesar do?
BAD APE: Oh, no!
(GRUNTS)
Why so small?
(GRUNTING)
Oh!
What did the Colonel
promise you?
You really think
he'll let you live...
after we are gone?
You let them
call you "donkey."
You are ape.
(GRUNTS)
Kerna want see you.
(ROCK MUSIC PLAYING
ON SPEAKERS)
THE COLONEL: Interfere
with the work again...
and I'll begin slaughtering
the apes one by one.
Understand? I need that wall.
Apes need food and water.
They'll get food and water
when they finish their work.
Give apes food and water...
or they cannot finish.
You know,
you are very emotional.
What makes you think you're in
a position to make demands?
Okay, let's go.
The soldiers
who are coming here...
they are not coming
to join you, are they?
I saw men outside on the wall,
preparing for battle.
They told me you were smart...
but that's impressive.
No.
They won't be joining me.
They are against you?
They fear me.
CAESAR: Why?
Because you kill
your own men?
We found bodies.
Something wrong...
with these men.
Jesus Christ,
you are impressive.
Well, you paint
quite a picture.
What you must think of me.
I think you have no mercy.
You came here to kill me.
Were you gonna show me mercy?
I showed you mercy...
when I spared your men.
I offered you peace...
and you killed my family.
(EXHALES HEAVILY)
(SWITCH CLICKS)
(MUSIC STOPS)
THE COLONEL: Mercy.
You have any idea what
your mercy would do to us?
You're much stronger
than we are.
You're smart as hell.
No matter what you say,
you'd eventually replace us.
That's the law of nature.
The irony is,
we created you.
We tried to defy nature,
bend it to our will.
Nature has been punishing us
for our arrogance...
ever since.
10 months ago,
I sent out recon units
to look for your base.
My own son was a soldier
with one of the units.
One day he suddenly
stopped speaking.
He became primitive,
like an animal.
They contacted me and said
that they thought
he'd lost his mind.
That the war
was too much for him.
Then the man who cared for him
stopped speaking too.
Their medic had a theory,
before he stopped speaking...
that the virus
that almost wiped us out...
the virus that every human
survivor still carries...
had suddenly changed.
Mutated.
And that if it spread...
it would destroy humanity
for good this time.
Not by killing us...
but by robbing us of those
things that make us human.
Our speech,
our higher thinking...
It would turn us
into beasts.
You talk about mercy?
What would you have done?
It was a moment
of clarity for me.
I realized...
that I would have to
sacrifice my only son...
so that humanity
could be saved.
I held that gun in my hand...
for a long time.
I pointed it
at my only child...
he looked at me...
trust in his eyes.
Even in his primitive gaze...
I felt his... love.
(GULPS)
I pulled the trigger.
It purified me.
It made my purpose clear.
I gave the orders
to kill the other infected.
All of them.
Burn their belongings...
and anything that might
spread contamination.
Some of the men
questioned my judgment.
I was asking them to do
what I had done.
Sacrifice their friends...
their family.
Of course, they refused.
So I had them killed too.
Others with children...
deserted into the woods.
One of those cowards fled
to my superiors up North.
They tried to convince me
this plague could be
dealt with medically.
That's when I realized that
they had learned nothing...
from our past.
You killed them too?
What did I do, Preacher?
You severed their heads, sir.
Except for the one I spared...
so that he could return,
and deliver a message.
If they wanted to
relieve me of my command...
they would have to
meet me here...
and do it themselves.
This used to be
a weapons depot.
They turned it
into a relocation camp
when the crisis
was just beginning.
But the weapons
are still here...
inside the mountain.
CAESAR: How many men...
will be coming?
Probably all of them.
But don't get any ideas.
The only thing they fear more
than me is you apes.
This is... a holy war.
All of human history
has led to this moment.
If we lose...
we'll be the last
of our kind.
It will be a planet of apes.
And we will become
your cattle.
Look at you.
You think I'm sick,
don't you?
I didn't mean
to kill your son.
But if his destiny was to
inherit your unholy kingdom...
I'm glad I did it.
(GROWLS)
PREACHER: Hey! Hey!
Get back!
Donkey, hold him!
Hey!
(GROWLING)
(CHOKING)
So emotional!
I can see
how conflicted you are.
You're confused
in your purpose.
You are angry at me
for something I did
that was an act of war.
But you're taking this all
much too personally.
What do you think...
my men would have done to your
apes if you had killed me?
Or is killing me
more important?
(PANTING)
Soldiers everywhere!
How will we get in?
(SNIFFLES AND CHITTERS)
Must get in somehow...
Must get in!
In? In?
No!
No go in! No...
(HORSE NEIGHS)
(PANTING)
Friends, friends!
No, no go in.
No go in... (YELPS)
Friend! Friend!
(BAD APE GRUNTS)
(PANTING)
Thank you, friend.
(GRUNTS SOFTLY)
(APES CHITTERING)
(WHISTLE BLOWING)
You saved our lives!
(GASPS AND COUGHS)
(PANTING)
(HEAVY BREATHING)
Sick humans...
...must have escaped down here!
No! No! No!
No! No climb!
(CHITTERING)
What?
What you see?
Wonder where we are?
(GRUNTS)
BAD APE: Oh, no, friend!
Oh...
No!
No! No!
No! Come! Come!
Come! Come back! Come!
No, come!
Come! Come! Come!
(SHIVERING)
Koba!
Sleep.
You cannot save them.
Apes all die here.
No!
Yes.
Join me.
(GRUNTING)
If he's still alive
in the morning...
he goes to work
like everyone else...
or you shoot him.
BAD APE: Come! Come, come.
She go in!
(WHIMPERING SOFTLY)
(SHALLOW BREATHING)
Thirsty...?
(BOTH CHITTER)
(DISTANT INDISTINCT
CONVERSATIONS)
(FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING)
Hide!
Quick!
Humans will kill her!
I know what to do! Go!
(CHITTERING LOUDLY)
SOLDIER 1: Arms up! Hey! Hey!
SOLDIER 2: Arms up!
SOLDIER 3: Watch it! Watch it!
SOLDIER 2: Let's go!
Keep 'em up!
Follow him down.
SOLDIER 1: Keep them up!
(SNIFFS)
(RED DONKEY GRUNTS)
(BOTH GRUNTING)
(GUNSHOT)
(PANTING)
Are there others out there?
Sweep the area.
Put him in the pen.
(GRUNTS)
(RED DONKEY GRUNTING)
(APES CHITTERING)
(SOFT CHUCKLE)
Feeling better?
(SIGHS)
Good.
Then we can talk about...
Escape.
Apes together strong!
(BREATHING DEEPLY)
COMMANDING OFFICER:
We are the beginning!
SOLDIERS: And the end!
(ALL YELLING)
(THE COLONEL SCOFFS)
THE COLONEL: Still alive.
Send him to the quarry.
Alone.
Hold on.
What is this?
How did this get in there?
Get him to work.
Thirty-seven.
(HEAVY BREATHING)
Fifty-five.
Thirty-seven steps to the adult cage...
Fifty-five to the children.
(GRUNTS)
You know...
Kerna shoot apes...
when war is done.
His war is madness.
It won't save him...
any more than
it will save you.
I save myself.
Is there anything
left of you to save?
(GRUNTS)
I do.
Apes going back to the cage?
You...
Are very brave.
Brave?
Brave!
Ape?
Me...?
You are...
Nova.
(BAD APE GRUNTING)
Come! Come!
Come see!
Come! Come see!
34, 35, 36, 37...
37!
I do.
(MAURICE GRUNTS)
(CHUCKLES) What now?
(CHITTERS)
What?
Oh, no!
No, no!
No, no, no...
(GROWLS)
Okay.
(COUGHS)
This is the ape I told you about!
Thank you.
Bad Ape.
(GRUNTS)
(BAD APE YELPS)
(CHITTERING)
(STUTTERING)
What's wrong?
(CHITTERING)
(STRAINING)
We can't keep digging!
It will flood the whole tunnel!
If we don't, we can't reach the children!
(ALL CHITTERING)
(CHITTERING STOPS)
We must keep looking down there...
Find another way to reach the children...
We must leave now!
More soldiers are coming!
Humans will destroy each other!
And us with them!
We'll have to get the
children out above ground!
How...?
(GASPS)
Hey!
You animals!
(GROANS)
Who did that?
Huh?
Who was it?
(APES CHITTERING)
Was it you?
(GRUNTS)
(YELPS)
(THUDS)
(GRUNTS)
(INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS)
(CORNELIUS COOING)
I love you, son.
(EXCITED CHITTERING)
Go, go, go.
Hurry! Let's go!
Caesar, what's wrong?
Hurry, you must go.
Without you?
No...
Maurice was right.
I am...
like Koba.
He could not...
escape his hate.
And I still cannot
escape mine.
Go, go, go.
COMMANDER: Fire!
(ALARMS BLARING)
(BAD APE EXCLAIMING
IN DISTRESS)
(OVERLAPPING YELLING)
EXECUTIVE OFFICER:
Colonel! Colonel!
Where the hell is he?
(BAD APE EXCLAIMING IN AWE)
Down! Down! Down!
Get down!
(CAESAR BREATHING HEAVILY)
(RASPING)
(HAMMER CLICKS)
(HUFFING)
(RASPING)
(GUNSHOT)
(CASING CLINKING)
(GUNFIRE)
GUNNER: Take him out!
(MEN CHEERING)
GUNNER: Come on, donkey.
Let's go! Reload!
(PANTING)
OFFICER: Colonel,
are you in there? Colonel!
Just break it down.
Donkey!
Grenade launcher!
(PANTING)
(GROANING)
God damn it, donkey!
Get me the launcher!
(GRUNTING)
(INAUDIBLE)
(GUNSHOT)
(WHISTLING)
(GRUNTING AND PANTING)
(GRUNTING)
(CHITTERING)
(PANTING)
(SOLDIERS CLAMORING)
(CHEERING)
(RUMBLING)
(SOLDIERS YELLING)
(CHITTERING)
Oh, no! Oh, no!
(PANTING)
(GROWLS)
(APES CHITTERING)
(WHOOPING)
(PANTING)
(CHITTERING)
(CHITTERS)
(GRUNTING)
(MAURICE GRUNTING)
Don't worry.
Maurice.
You are all home now.
Apes are strong.
With...
or without me.
(ALL CHITTERING)
Son...
will know...
who...
was...
father.
And what...
Caesar...
did...
for us.
(SIGHS)
(SNIFFLES)
Caesar... (GASPING)
(MAURICE GROWLING MOURNFULLY)
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today