Someone needs to stop Clearway Law.
Public shouldn't leave reviews for lawyers.
Hey, Jenny. That was a
wonderful share, tonight.
"Chapter 36, The Quarter-Deck."
"Enter Ahab. Then, all."
"It was not a great while after
the affair of the pipe,"
"that one morning, shortly after
breakfast, Ahab, as was his wont,"
"ascended the cabin-gangway
to the deck."
"'It's a white whale, I say, ' resumed
Ahab, as he threw down the top-maul.
"'A white whale. Skin
your eyes for him, men,
"'look sharp for white water, if
ye see but a bubble, sing out."'
Tommy?
Jesus!
What are you doing here?
Well, I was just passing through
and I figured why not have
a belt with the old man.
Yeah.
She looks good.
Yeah, she's hanging in there.
Well, you always did
take good care of her.
Paddy Conlon.
Man of priorities.
I got a little
something for you.
Mom always said, "Never go
anywhere empty-handed."
She did.
That's not for me
anymore, Tommy.
What? You changed brands?
Let's go inside, huh?
Tommy!
Come on, let's go inside.
I like what you've
done with the place.
Yeah, I appreciate that.
There's not much of a
woman's touch around here.
Yeah, well...
And no more women for me, Tommy.
Yeah.
It must be hard to find a girl
who can take a punch nowadays.
Here you go.
Coffee?
You haven't seen a guy in 14 years and
you're not gonna have a drink with him?
- Come on.
- I told you, I'm off it, Tommy.
I'm coming up on 1,000 days.
- Come on, it's just a drink.
- No.
He's a school teacher
down in Philly.
Remember Tess?
They had two beautiful
little girls.
So, you found God, huh?
That's awesome.
I think Mom kept calling out
for him, but he wasn't around.
I guess Jesus was down at the mill
forgiving all the drunks, huh?
Who knew?
So, you gonna ask about her,
or you just gonna sit
there all sober?
- I know.
- You know? What do you know? Huh?
Do you know it wasn't enough to
drive west to get away from you,
that once we hit the water,
we drove north, too?
When I got sober, I hired
a man to find you.
And is that one of the 12 steps?
Or does a guy like you get 24?
Just 12.
Did your guy tell you
what you needed to know?
Just that your mother
died in Tacoma.
But you were in the Marines.
That was all.
That was enough.
Well, that's too bad,
'cause you could've
gotten some good details.
You could've heard about her
coughing up blood on her knees
in a shit box with no heat.
Having me rub her down with holy water,
because, well, she didn't have no insurance.
All the time waiting for your
pal, Jesus, to save her.
Did your man tell you that?
I'm sorry, Tommy.
Well, it's good to know
that you're sorry, Pop.
It goes a long way.
I think I liked you better
when you were a drunk.
All right, then. All right,
all right, all right.
You say I can, but
you say I can't.
- What about if we all get a unicorn?
- No.
- Don't you want a unicorn?
What's going on up here?
- Oh, my goodness.
- Well, I'm not sure,
but I think Daddy
is now a princess.
- Daddy, you look so handsome.
- Do I?
- He's a very pretty princess.
- We're painting Daddy's face.
Yeah, you are.
Okay. Yeah. Em, you wanna
open your presents?
- Yeah? You wanna do present time? Okay.
- Yeah. All right, come on. Ready?
- All right! It's time for presents!
- I have to put this down.
- Here. You wanna put it down?
- Presents time!
- Everybody, come bring your presents!
- What is it? What is it?
Let's start with this one.
How about that, Emily?
- All right.
- Happy birthday, Emily.
- What did you get? What did you get?
- Babe?
It's an awfully big box.
It's her birthday. Come on.
I know, babe, but that's
why you call it a budget.
You set it and you don't budge.
- This one's mine.
- Hey, open the big box!
It's okay.
- I love you. Be good, okay?
- Bye, Mommy.
Daddy's gonna give you a bath.
- Hey, babe. I'm late.
- Hey.
Mom's saying goodbye to the girls,
she's got to get on the road.
- They've been fed, they just need a bath.
- I'm on it.
Okay, can you get them to bed
at a reasonable time tonight?
Because, after the party,
they're just exhausted.
Where's the rest of that skirt?
Babe.
Listen, if any guys give you a
hassle in that joint tonight,
you give me a call, okay?
Yeah, just like you gave me a
call when those Temple frat boys
decided to smash up your face.
I told you, most nights, I sit
on the stool and grade papers,
but, every now and then,
I need some action.
All right. Well, wait up for me tonight.
I'll see what I can do about that.
Promises, promises.
And we return here on MMA Live,
Jon Anik, alongside the billionaire
fighting promoter, J.J. Riley,
the Tapout crew is here, Punk
and Skrape are in the building.
Now, J.J., what led
to this project
that is really redefining mixed
martial arts here in the States?
Well, mixed martial arts is a sport
I've been incredibly passionate about,
and as far as where the
idea for Sparta came from,
I've always really dug the Grand Prix
format, so I tracked these guys down.
And when J.J. came to us,
he said he wanted to create
the Super Bowl of
mixed martial arts.
And he decided to put up
the $5 million purse, too.
Well, there you have it, it shall be done.
Hedge fund king, J.J. Riley,
going from the lions' den
of Wall Street to the cage,
and promoting the biggest winner-take-all
tournament in MMA history. Sparta...
Doing good. One more time.
Fitzy still own this?
I don't know no Fitzy.
Colt Boyd owns this gym.
Can I help you with something?
How does it work?
Thirty-five a month with locker.
We're open at 7:00,
lights out at 11:00.
So you want to join?
Sure.
Put your name and contact
info on the card.
Thank you.
All right. There's a
lesson in this, too, okay?
Hold on, Tito.
So, we have a body at rest,
and you have the
bat which needs...
- Acceleration.
- Acceleration, okay.
If you have enough acceleration,
you might have a chance of
breaking the body at rest.
- Okay. All right. You ready?
- Piece of cake.
Everybody got the glasses on?
Okay, go! Piece of cake!
Come on, man!
Come on, son!
All right! All right. There we go.
Well done, Tito. Well done.
Remind me not to mess with you.
Sit down, everybody.
Dial it down.
So, have we got it?
Force equals mass times
acceleration, we got it.
All right. Has
everybody else got it?
- Yeah.
- Yes? Okay, good. All right.
The third law...
How many laws this dude got?
- The dude?
- Yes, the dude.
The dude has three, all right?
Newton, the dude, says
that for every action,
there is an equal and
opposite reaction.
For example,
if K.C. does not stop the action
of sending texts in class
and tell her posse
outside to beat it,
then my reaction might be to send her
down to Principal Zito's office.
Thus setting the world
back in proper balance.
Mr. C, I put it away.
All right, before you go, I
have your tests from last week.
Just work it out.
Stop clowning.
Pick up the hands.
Tighten it up!
Use your right.
Seal his hands, come on.
Seal his hands.
Keep your hands up!
Go light!
I said, go light!
God damn it!
Where do you find these girls?
We got a tournament coming up, you're
gonna play every guy in the 'Burgh?
Oh, jeez.
Fenroy, get me some ice.
And call that Puerto Rican kid, the
one that fights out of the bottoms.
If he's here in 20 minutes,
he gets 200 bucks.
Yo, I'll fight him.
Do me a favor, guy,
go back to your bag.
We don't need anybody else getting hurt.
Take a walk.
Let's go. Watch his neck.
Yo, Rock, what did you do,
did you leave Mick and
Paulie at home today?
His phone's disconnected.
Then go through the list. Find me somebody.
Get me Joe Bones.
All I'm saying is that if you
need somebody to help you,
I'm happy to keep your
boy warm for you.
You ever fought before?
Yeah.
Hey, this guy signed a waiver?
All good.
- What's your name?
- Tommy.
- You get tuned up in here, it's on you, Tom.
- Sure, no problem. No problem.
Come on in.
Let's go. All right, let's go.
Hey. Watch that teeth.
Are you gonna be a hero?
All right.
Come on. Check that kick.
Easy.
Come on, Dog, you can do it.
Let's go, come on.
- Good jab. Good jab!
- There we go!
No, he won't. Don't let him take your back.
Don't let him take your back!
- Dog, get up.
- Get up!
Cover up, cover up!
Don't give him your back.
Don't give him your back!
- Cover up!
- Come on, Dog!
Cover up, damn it!
You owe me 200 bucks.
This one here. See, this is
the new appraisal figures
- that came in.
- Yeah.
And this is how it affects the
monthly, it turns into that.
And the total value of the loan,
over the life of the loan, is that.
As you can see, that's
just the way it is.
It puts you upside down,
that's the problem.
It's the county that did the
assessment, not the bank.
So, the numbers are what they are, Mr.
Conlon...
- Brendan.
- The numbers are what they are, Brendan.
I mean, you're a math teacher, right?
You can appreciate that.
I'm a physics teacher.
I teach physics.
Physics, okay. But the bank has got
to go by the new appraisal figures.
And, according to these figures,
you're upside down on your mortgage,
- you understand?
- God, you said that like three times.
I'm sorry, but I get that.
I am asking you, is there
something else you can do?
Not the bank, you. Can you shift
things around, restructure?
You refinanced twice already.
'Cause you advised
us to do that.
- You told me.
- Well, I presented you with that option,
but that was your choice.
I'm also showing that you netted a
substantial payout with the refi.
We had that conversation.
I was paying medical bills.
Oh, right. Sorry. Your
daughter's kidney?
- Heart.
- Heart. Right, sorry.
A lot of stories.
All right, so, if that's my
option, I have no options.
You're not even gonna try and help me.
You're not even gonna try.
No, I'm trying. Look, Brendan, I
can get you 90 days to get even.
Ninety days is not enough.
My wife and I, we have
three jobs between us.
And that doesn't cut it.
So, what do you suggest?
Well, let me ask you a question?
Have you thought about bankruptcy?
It's a viable option.
There's no shame in
this these days.
That's not how I do things.
Okay, well, then you're
looking at foreclosure.
Utter domination by Tommy Conlon, the
undefeated freshman from Pittsburgh.
The prodigy has yet to yield a single
point in the entire tournament.
Tommy, trained by his father
since the age of five.
- Talking about Paddy Conlon?
- The controversial Paddy Conlon.
Say what you will about the
methods of the former Marine,
but he's led his son to six
straight Junior Olympic titles
and now just moments away from a
High School State Championship.
And there it is! Wow!
There's just no limit to what
the future holds for this kid.
Tommy told me that he's chasing
the record of Theogenes,
apparently, a mythical Greek fighter said
to be undefeated in over 1,400 bouts.
Hi, how're you doing, sir? I'm
looking for Tommy Riordan.
- Who?
- Tommy Riordan.
My name is Colt Boyd.
What business you
got with Tommy?
Well, none yet, that's why I'm here.
I manage fighters.
So, Tommy's been
working out at my gym,
and he put a beating on the number one
middleweight contender in the world today.
So, I want to know a little
bit more about the guy.
Maybe help him out.
I have a lot of contacts, Mr.
Riordan.
Conlon. The name is Conlon.
And anything you wanna
know about Tommy,
you gotta ask him yourself.
Look, I'm just asking for some
general information here.
Like I said, anything you
wanna know about Tommy,
you gotta ask him yourself.
Look, I don't mean to
interrupt your night, okay?
He just put this address down
when he signed up at the gym.
He doesn't live here.
- All right, then.
- Okay. Good night.
All right, listen, kiddo. I need
you to put Mommy back on, okay?
I love you.
Hey. Hey, listen, I'm just pulling
in, I'm gonna have to go.
No, they got an open mic night thing
on, it's gonna be a quiet one.
All right, sleep well.
You, too. All right, bye.
It's about time for
your next contest.
Introducing first, in the red corner,
he fights out of Ripley, West Virginia.
Please welcome Mike
"The Mutilator" Moore.
Say, "Uncle!"
Go, Mike. Go!
And his opponent in the blue corner, he
fights out of Philadelphia, Pennsylvania.
Please welcome "Irish"
Brendan Conlon.
This bout is scheduled for
three, five-minute rounds,
and when the action begins,
your referee is Mr. Rick Fike.
Fighters to the center.
Come on, gentlemen.
I want you to obey my
commands at all times.
I want you to protect
yourselves at all times.
If you have no questions,
touch gloves, back up.
And on my signal, let's
come out fighting.
Fighter, are you ready?
Are you ready?
Do it!
Come on, Mike, let's go!
You gotta move with that one.
Come on, Mike!
Don't let him do
that to you, Mike!
Get up, Mike, get up!
- First five minutes, out.
- Another 15? Great.
Hey! Hey, kid!
Nice fight. Two more wins,
you take home the bacon.
Hey, good job...
Hey, babe.
Hey.
How was work?
Oh, my God!
What happened?
You said it was gonna
be a slow night.
I'm not bouncing at a club.
What do you mean
you're not bouncing?
You've been lying to me?
I went in to apply
and they were paying
nine bucks an hour.
Then I saw a sign for
this other thing.
They're putting us out of
the house in three months.
We're running out of options.
Then they put us out of the
house in three months.
I'd rather go back
to the old apartment
than see you in the back
of an ambulance again.
I thought we agreed that we
weren't gonna raise our children
in a family where their father
gets beat up for a living.
We're not giving up the house.
It's our home.
We're not going backwards.
We'll figure it out.
This is what we're
not going back to.
You wanted to talk?
Yeah.
I'm gonna start fighting.
Is that right?
Don't play babe in
the woods with me.
I know that guy from the
gym came to see you.
Colt Boyd.
Yeah. I didn't tell
him anything, Tommy.
I wouldn't be sitting here
with you now if you did.
- Paddy, can I get you more coffee?
- No. Thank you. I'm fine.
- Hon, would you like a cup of coffee? Okay.
- Sure. Thank you.
All right.
There's this tournament,
it's a big tournament.
Top 16 middleweights in the world.
Single elimination.
Winner takes all.
It's a lot of money.
- Okay.
- I'm gonna do that.
But if I'm doing it,
then I'm gonna need a trainer.
Now, that much,
you were good at.
What?
No, no, no. This doesn't
mean anything, okay?
I'm serious.
We train. That's it.
I don't want to hear a word
about anything but training.
You understand?
You want to tell your war stories,
you can take them down to the VFW.
Or you can take it to a
meeting, or to church,
or whatever the hell it
is that you do nowadays.
What about Colt Boyd?
What about him? I told him I don't
train with people that I don't know.
- The devil you know.
- Excuse me?
The devil you know is better
than the devil you don't.
- Yeah.
There's your coffee, hon.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
Chasing Theogenes. It'll be
kind of like the old times.
I just told you, this
doesn't mean anything.
Now, get that through your skull
right now or I'm walking.
All right. All right.
But you get something
through your skull, too.
You called me, so don't go threatening
to walk every five minutes.
And since this is
about training,
you dump whatever it is you need to dump
as far as those pills are concerned.
I don't wanna see them.
In fact, hand them
over right now.
I know they're on you, Tommy.
You sounded like a goddamn
maraca coming through the door.
That's not gonna do.
When you came through
that door, it was...
Three.
That'a boy.
And another thing. You
don't eat crap like this.
This is for losers and old men.
And we're gonna have to bunk up.
If we're gonna do this right,
you're gonna stay at the house.
I watch your diet. We
follow the old regimen.
You copy?
All right.
Copy.
Your brother's a liar.
- ...went in the middle of the night...
- Yeah.
And he went to a strip club,
and he said he saw Mr. C...
- No way.
- Front and center.
- Like MMA type stuff.
- You weren't there, so you don't know.
What's MMA?
- Mixed martial arts.
- Like, fighting.
Like, different
styles of fighting.
He was just, like, dropped
him on the floor...
It's true?
Take your seats.
Now, please.
Hey, yo, Mr. C.
Hey, my brother was at the
titty bar last night,
and he said you was choking brothers out.
I mean, what's up, is it true?
Yeah, Mr. C. I mean,
like, is it true?
Did you really work on
some fools or something?
- You have to tell us.
- Yeah.
All right. I want examples
of forms of energy.
Come on. It's not
as bad as it looks.
Are you being literal or figurative?
Because, literally, it looks bad.
And figuratively, it
looks even worse.
The superintendent's coming by.
Few minutes.
Oh, man.
So, come on, Brendan. Give
me a little help here.
I mean, could you explain to me
what the hell you were doing?
I need the money, Joe.
Yeah, but this is...
We can't have this.
This isn't moonlighting at
Applebee's, for Christ's sake.
Shit, Brendan.
Leaving everything else
aside, which we can't,
are you out of your mind?
You're gonna get
yourself killed.
I mean, you're a
goddamn teacher.
You got no business in the
ring with those animals.
Actually, I used to be
one of those animals.
I fought for a living.
Guess I forgot to put that
down on my application.
Yeah, I guess you did.
Look, I'm sorry, Joe.
It's just...
Look, look, the school
district is not gonna tolerate
teachers cockfighting
in strip clubs.
It was a parking lot
of a strip club.
Wherever it was, you
can't be doing it.
All right? I mean, this is a serious...
Shit, he's here.
This is a serious problem.
Guy hasn't been inside
a school since 9/11.
What are we gonna do?
You say, "Yes, sir," and
you say, "No, sir,"
and you say, "it will
never happen again, sir."
And then we just pray to God
that he's in a good mood.
UFC?
Yeah.
Son of a bitch.
- Superintendent Yorn. Good to see you, sir.
- Principal Zito.
What are you doing?
Well,
the girls have an important
piano recital in the morning.
And we have an
equipment malfunction.
How'd it go?
They're gonna review your case
at the end of the semester.
But until then, you're
suspended without pay.
Joe gave me the number
of his attorney.
How the hell are we gonna
pay for an attorney?
He talked to me for
free as a favor to Joe.
That's nice.
He said there's no
precedent for this.
You'll be back by next semester.
The next semester?
Tess,
they have these smoker
fights all over.
There's one in Lancaster next week,
there's two in Dover the week after.
Wilmington, Camden, Baltimore.
That could keep us afloat.
You're gonna put yourself through this
over and over for 500 bucks a pop?
Some of them pay a
lot more than that.
I would have to bounce for a month to
make what I made in two hours last night.
Yeah.
And these guys, they're
not real fighters.
They're just guys that have
seen too much UFC on TV.
Now, if you have a
better solution,
I'm all ears, but...
And what are we gonna
tell the girls?
It'll be fine.
I'll just leave the
house as usual,
except, only this time,
I'll be going to the gym.
The duck goes quack,
quack, quack, quack.
And the cow goes moo, moo, moo!
But that rooster That
rooster, he knew everything.
Cock-a-doodle-doo!
Let's go, kiddo.
Let's get moving.
Look what I found
in that disaster of a...
basement.
What do you say we sit down
and update this?
And you can fill me in on how
close you got to that record.
Did you continue wrestling after
you left with your mother?
Come on, Tommy.
Tell me something.
Yeah, I'll tell you something.
You can take that back
to where you found it,
you can leave the
coffee in the pot.
I can pour that myself.
And I can wake myself up, too.
Hurt my knees coming up
and down those stairs.
Yeah?
I'll leave the coffee pot on
until 0500, then I dump it.
I give command dismiss. You'll
wash your nasty bodies.
You can square your gear away.
Corporal Bradford, take this to
CSC, let them know we're back.
Roger, sir.
Detail, a-ten-hut!
7-3-4, this is Gealer Base.
Sitrep, over.
What's up, Mark?
Here, sir. William's
Company's back in.
Damn, dude! That's brutal.
- Did you see that? Oh, my God.
- What?
What's that?
Dude, Mad Dog Grimes is getting tuned
up by some dude at a gym in Pittsburgh.
Who is Mad Dog Grimes?
Shit, Bradford, the stuff
you don't know amazes me.
- Dude. Oh, my God, did you see that?
- Wow. Oh, my God.
- Wait. Rewind that.
- Okay.
Right there, pause,
pause, pause.
What's up, man?
Dude, what's his deal?
You're not gonna get your 11.
- AV, I need to see the tape.
- What tape?
- The tape!
Hoolihan, fill in for me?
Get the camera.
That's him.
Let the music sink into you.
This is Beethoven.
I want you to breathe. I don't want you
boxing like this. No more stiff, right?
You listen to the music. You
relax, you breathe. One, two...
Again. One, two. One, two.
One, two.
Good.
Good, good, good. Yos.
You're gonna get it, you're gonna get it.
All right? Two more rounds.
Do I know you?
- Oh, man!
- Wow.
- Long time, brother. Too long.
- How you doing?
- Too long.
- Look at your place.
- You like?
- Yeah.
You see this beast?
Marco Santos.
- He's training for Sparta.
- Yeah, right.
Not bad, right?
It's amazing, man.
Only the best. Move! Move!
Move! Move or die!
- You look good, brother.
- Thanks.
How are the girls?
Good. Yeah. I had another
little one, Rosie.
I know. I know because Johnny C. Told me
that she was in the hospital for a bit.
- Yeah.
You know,
I was gonna call you and
then time went by and...
I'm a piece of shit. I should've
called you. I'm sorry.
- No. Come on.
- No.
Brendan, I'm sorry.
It's all good. She's good now.
- She's okay?
- So beautiful.
It's good to see you, man. So
everything's going great, huh?
Yeah.
Well, I've got a little problem.
The guys at the bank want
to take my house away.
- What?
- Yeah.
That's kind of why I came
to see you, actually.
You know, I got most of my
dough tied up in this joint,
but how much do you need?
I didn't come here
for a loan, Frank.
I mean, I was hoping that
you would train me.
Train you for what?
I wanna get back in the cage.
Are you serious?
Come on, Brendan.
I won an event the other night.
You won an event.
That's what this is.
Let me guess. It was in a parking lot?
DJ from a local radio station,
a couple of ring card girls you
wouldn't bang on a dare? Am I right?
- Ish.
Brendan. I love you.
Why am I gonna train you?
When you were on the right side of
30, you were barely a .500 fighter.
You never listened to me.
You don't listen to anyone.
These guys are animals.
You're a teacher, right?
What are you gonna do?
You're gonna come down here a couple
of days a week after detention?
You're gonna skip out of the
girls' volleyball game early?
I've got loads of time.
Time's not an issue.
Parking lot thing kind
of got me suspended.
I need to keep
working the smokers.
Tess know about this?
Yeah?
'Cause the last time you fought,
I got read the riot act,
sitting in a hospital waiting room.
You remember that?
I was unconscious.
- You were more than unconscious.
- I was.
She's not gonna come down here with
the two puppies, screaming at Frank?
It's not gonna happen.
What do you say, Frank?
What do I say? What am I
gonna say to you? "No"?
I mean, all my time is
wrapped up with Marco.
You know, you come down, I throw you in
a rotation, you spar with these guys.
But I can't promise you much
more than that, Brendan.
That's all I need.
Great. All right.
Yeah.
- I appreciate it.
- What, are you kidding me?
- You need anything, you call me.
- I will.
Let me know when
you're coming down.
Well, I'm just gonna get
my stuff from the car.
Now?
Hey, Brendan.
Brendan, it's me, Pop.
What are you doing here?
I have some news for you.
Something wrong with your hands?
- No.
- If there's nothing wrong with your hands,
there's no reason for
you not to phone.
- That's the deal.
- Yeah. I forgot.
The phone or mail, Pop.
Non negotiable.
Hey, Brendan. You ever
seen my hands so steady?
Ever seen that?
I'm going inside.
I got 1,000 days, Brendan.
Thousand days sober, today.
Well, that's great, Pop, but
it doesn't change anything.
What do you mean, doesn't
change anything?
Have a heart, Brendan.
You listen to me.
You take your "have a heart" bullshit
and you run it down the road.
Yeah, run it out with someone
that doesn't know you like I do.
All right, listen to me. I thought
maybe we could break bread.
You know, just open some
lines of communication.
You got two lines of communication. You
got the telephone and the post office.
God! Just 'cause you
decide it's a special day,
it doesn't make it one for me.
I've got a wife and kids inside,
and they're waiting for me,
so I don't have time
for whatever this is.
I know you got a wife and kid in there.
I've got a granddaughter in there
I haven't seen in three years.
And another one I
haven't even ever met.
Yeah. Why is that, Pop?
Why is that?
Do you remember having
anything to do with that?
- Yeah.
That shit you pulled.
Never again.
And all that shit
I saw growing up,
- that doesn't happen here.
- Look...
Take care of yourself.
Tommy's back.
He's in the 'Burgh.
You say Tommy's in Pittsburgh?
Yeah, he came to see me.
He came to see you?
Yeah. He's over at the house.
We're doing a little
training at Fitzy's.
You remember Fitzy's?
It ain't Fitzy's anymore.
You and Tommy are
training together?
Yeah.
- Tommy Conlon?
- Riordan.
- He's using your mother's maiden name.
- Yeah, I know what her name is.
Well, I thought you'd wanna know he's back.
So that's why I drove all the way over here.
I thought you came to break
bread over 1,000 days.
No, I did, Brendan,
that's most important.
That, too.
All right. Did he say
if he wants to see me?
He doesn't say much, Brendan.
He's just not that happy
kid he was, you know?
- Wow. Look at you.
- What?
Mr. inside Man.
Inside? What?
You and Tommy training together like
nothing ever happened. It's unbelievable.
- Look...
- Now I know what you're really doing here.
- What's that?
- You came to gloat.
I did not come to gloat. I
came to get my son back.
Wow. There you go. Yeah,
you got your son back.
- No, I'm talking about you, Brendan. You.
- You got your son back.
You know...
Forget it.
Yeah, I'll tell you. Part of the reason...
Part of the reason I stuck around,
'cause I thought I'd finally
get you all to myself.
But you didn't have any
interest in training me.
- You thought Tommy was the one.
- Brendan, I was a drunk.
I mean, you know,
Brendan, I'm sorry.
Forget it.
You were always a frontrunner. Never
had any interest in the underdogs.
- But I was your son.
- You are my son, Brendan.
- Am I?
- Yeah, you are.
I'm just asking you
if you can find...
Find a little bit of space in your
heart to forgive me a little bit.
Yeah? All right, I forgive you.
- Okay.
- But I do not trust you.
Listen, tell Tommy, if he wants
to see me, this is where I am.
- Okay. But they're not different things.
- All right?
You gotta trust to forgive.
Night, Pop.
My God.
Is that Emily? Jeez,
she's grown, Brendan.
- Is that Rosie?
- Daddy, who is that?
It's just a nice, old man.
Come on. Let's go.
How about a cup of coffee?
Huge news just
broken here at ESPN
that Koba is coming to America
and will fight at Sparta.
Universally considered the
greatest pound-for-pound fighter
who ever lived, the mighty,
mythical Russian has never fought
on US soil in his
legendary career.
Slow to half guard. Slow to
half guard, hammer fist.
Now start on the other side. And
slip back in, there you go.
Tommy,
I got some news for you.
I got you into Sparta.
It took some doing,
but I made it happen.
You know thank you and
10% is customary?
Pilar? Hey, it's Tommy.
Tommy?
Okay. Sorry.
Good. I'm good. How
are you doing?
Okay. You know me, Tommy.
I was getting really
worried about you.
How's things? How are the kids?
The kids good?
Yeah, they're good.
- Maria's getting so big.
- Yeah?
She looks more and more
like Manny every day.
- How's little man?
- He's good. He's a good kid, Tommy.
He's a real good boy. He
takes care of his sister.
- He's a great kid. Everyone's good.
- Good.
- We're good.
You know...
Pilar, I haven't
forgotten for one minute
what I promised you.
What I promised Manny. I got
opportunities coming up, so...
Whatever you can do, Tommy.
Help you guys out. I'm gonna
take care of you guys.
I know. Manny would
really appreciate it.
- I wanna help you.
- You know what? You worry too much.
You worry so much about us.
It's okay.
You know what? We're
hanging in there.
"Captain Pollard once more sailed for the
Pacific in command of another ship,"
"but the gods shipwrecked him again
upon unknown rocks and breakers."
"For the second time, his
ship was utterly lost,"
"and forthwith forswearing the sea,
he has never tempted it since."
Stop for a second. Listen to the music.
This is Beethoven.
Could you do another thing? Or
are you gonna do the same thing?
I need you to relax and listen.
Forget about how to lose the fight.
And two, and three.
With eight weeks left to Sparta,
J.J. Riley and the Tapout crew
take time out from their
international press tour to join us.
J.J., we've never seen this
kind of Grand Prix tournament
in this country before. Tell
us, why the unique format?
Well, look, Jon, you know as well as
anyone that in mixed martial arts,
anyone can beat anyone
on a given night.
But with this type of format,
it's gonna be tough to
deny who the champion is.
You got four fights in two
nights, 16 fighters down to one,
winner's gonna be the
last man standing.
Thirty-one. Thirty-two!
Breathe, breathe.
Keep your eyes open.
You gotta keep moving. You gotta
keep moving. Keep moving.
Good! And listen to the music. You breathe.
He's getting it. He's getting it.
You see? You feel it?
Feel the music.
- Come on!
- Nice.
Come on, baby!
With Rashad Evans and Stephan Bonnar
and just five weeks left until Sparta,
as the hype continues for the war on
the shore this Fourth of July weekend
in Atlantic City. You
know what that means.
The great Koba bringing
his act stateside.
But I gotta ask you
about the other guys.
What are they thinking, entering
a winner-take-all tournament
against a guy that
seemingly can't be beaten?
They're thinking $5 million and
$5 million seems a lot of money,
but they gotta remember one thing.
They're going against Koba.
Mission impossible,
game over, go home.
Well, the winner takes
home $5 million.
You can be sure this will
dominate the sports landscape.
Fourth of July weekend
in Atlantic City.
The great Koba making his presence
felt in the United States.
Two... Come on, Tommy.
Hits you soft, right?
Flow like water.
Get on your arm, watch
what's gonna happen.
There it is. Look, look, look.
He's going to sleep.
You train with the best
to be the best, Brendan.
Pittsburgh Beatdown has become
one of the most watched videos
on YouTube this year.
Now joining us, via satellite, is the
victim of the infamous incident,
Mad Dog Grimes.
Mad Dog, what is your response to all
the hoopla surrounding the video
and Tommy Riordan?
This guy's a nobody.
It's a sparring session.
It is what it is, and he's
gonna pay for it next month
in Atlantic City.
Good. Always move. Always move.
I don't know, Marco. You're getting a
good game here from a physics teacher.
Good! Good.
You see? You see? Beautiful.
Top of the food chain. He's
the next champ, right here.
So, with Sparta now just
two short weeks away,
J.J. Riley and the Tapout
crew return to the US
after a world tour that saw them visit
10 fighters in 10 different countries.
They stopped in Philadelphia today
to check in on renowned trainer,
Frank Campana,
and top contender, Marco Santos.
You gotta relax and
stay calm in there.
The cage is your home.
You set the pace.
You set the rhythm.
Feel the Beethoven.
Be smarter than him, more patient.
Wait for him to make a mistake.
And when he does,
that's your moment.
I see it. I see it. I see it.
No, he did not tap you!
Physics teacher! That's the
best in the business, son.
You can do this, Son!
Smoother. There's more in you!
You got more in you!
We're not done yet!
He's beating you!
You better push harder, Marco!
Brendan's running away!
And the winner by tap out
"Irish" Brendan Conlon.
"...to each and every man in turn but
mirrors back his own mysterious self."
"Great pains, small gains for those
who ask the world to solve them."
"It cannot solve itself."
- Are you gonna be okay?
- Yeah.
- You wanna grab a bite?
- No. I'm gonna head home.
I gotta call the boys
and break the news.
- I'll call you tomorrow.
- Okay.
Coach!
Hey, I know this is not
a really great time,
and it's too bad about Marco.
But how about me?
Are you talking about Sparta?
Yeah.
Brendan, you've got a better
shot at starting a boy band.
I'll talk to you tomorrow.
It's a Grand Prix tournament.
Which means anything could happen.
You know that as well as I do.
Yeah.
Come on. They'd have to kill
me to get me out of the cage.
That's what I'm afraid of.
Frank, I need this.
You're real tight with these guys.
You could call them.
You're the guy. They trust you.
Brendan.
You realize what you're
asking me to do here?
- Yeah.
We go down to AC, you get
tapped out in five seconds.
How does that benefit
either one of us?
- It's not gonna happen.
- Not gonna happen?
Wish I had a nickel for every
time somebody told me that.
It's not gonna happen.
I'll make a call.
I love my coach!
Yeah, they're good. The girls are good.
They're good.
Yeah, he should.
I mean, you've been spending so
much time with Brendan these days,
it's like you're part of
the family or something.
Yeah, he's right here.
It's your boyfriend.
Frank. Hey, man.
That's unbelievable.
Wow! Wow, Frank, I can't thank you enough.
I don't know what to say.
All right, listen, I gotta
call you back, okay?
All right. Bye.
I'm in.
- I'm going.
- Really?
That's your decision?
You decided?
'Cause I really enjoyed the
conversation we just had
about making that
decision together.
You told me you were gonna fight
guys that watched too much UFC.
I saw the Koba dude
on the television,
and he's the guy
they're watching.
It's a lot of money, Tess.
I don't give a shit about the
money, Brendan. I told you that.
We're gonna end up cashing in
your life insurance policy
before we pick up
that prize money.
You don't think I
can do it, right?
I think you could get killed.
- I'm not gonna get killed.
- You're not gonna get killed,
but you promised me you're
not gonna get hurt.
You're not gonna end up in the hospital.
You're not gonna end up paralyzed.
We have no prize money,
we have no house.
- We have payments for hospital bills.
- Tess! Listen, I'll promise you this.
If I don't try in three weeks,
they're gonna take the house.
How's that for a promise?
So, I'm gonna go, okay?
But I'd really love it if
you'd be with me on this.
I'm not gonna watch you
fight again, I'm not.
I'm gonna get the
girls breakfast.
Fourth of July weekend doesn't
officially get started until tomorrow,
but fight fans are already
descending on Atlantic City
for the Super Bowl of mixed
martial arts, Sparta!
We've got the dancing girls,
we've got the paparazzi,
we've got the red carpet!
And here comes J.J. Riley,
the man who started it all.
J.J., you've made a fortune
with your hedge funds.
You turned your
back on Wall Street
and dedicated your life
to making Sparta happen.
Tell us why this tournament
is so important to you?
Growing up, we all
wanted to know
who the toughest kid in the
neighborhood was, right?
I wanna know who the toughest
man on the planet is.
And that's why I put
this thing together.
That's what all these people are
here to see, come Saturday night.
- That's what we're gonna find out.
- Thank you, J.J.
And here's something fans never
thought they'd see. Koba is here.
The legend arriving to fight on
US soil for the very first time.
- Koba! Koba!
Olympic gold medalist in
wrestling, world Sambo champion,
undefeated in his mixed
martial arts career.
Nobody's survived a round with
the Russian in five years.
He is the greatest fighter...
I mean, you've seen our logos.
No, yeah, I've seen your stuff.
It looks good.
I mean, is he fighting
after Sparta?
I mean, we're trying to
find some info on him.
No, I'm not sure.
Hey, where'd you go?
Where'd you go?
You can't leave me like that.
They want to talk to you, not me.
- Frank Campana?
- Yeah.
Hi. Julia, J.J.
Riley's assistant.
- Julia, how are you?
- Brendan Conlon?
- Yeah, hi. Hey.
- Hi. Julia, J.J. Riley's assistant.
- Right, hi. Nice to meet you.
- Nice to meet you.
A few things I want
to let you guys know.
- Press conference will start in 20 minutes.
- Okay.
Brendan, you're gonna be
sitting up on the stage.
Tommy!
Hey, Tommy! Where you going?
Can we stand with J.J.?
"Hearing the tremendous rush
of the sea-crashing boat,
"the whale wheeled round to present
his blank forehead at bay.
"But in that evolution, catching sight
of the nearing black hull of the ship,
"seemingly seeing in it the
source of all his persecutions,
"bethinking it, it may be
a larger and nobler foe.
"Of a sudden, he bore down
upon its advancing prow,
"smiting his jaws amid
fiery showers of foam.
"Ahab staggered, his
hand smote his forehead.
"I grow blind...".
Now, the only person
missing from the event
was dark horse entry,
Tommy Riordan.
Recent revelations that Riordan was
not only a United States Marine,
but a hero in the Iraq War, has
cast an even wider spotlight
on a fighter who seems to
have come out of nowhere.
Lance Corporal Mark Bradford's
Web testimony to Riordan,
who saved his life earlier
this year in Iraq,
is now spreading like wildfire
throughout the media.
Tommy!
And the bridge just crumbled.
Tommy, come here. Come on.
You got to see this.
The amtrac was upside down and water
was coming in from everywhere.
And the water pressure was too much.
We couldn't get the back hatch open.
We were all drowning, man.
It was a death trap.
I couldn't have had more
than another minute.
Then suddenly, the back
ramp gets ripped off.
There he was.
And before I could get out
and thank him, he was gone.
- He just vanished like a ghost.
- Tommy?
- Tommy, did you... Where you going?
- Taking a walk.
Tommy!
I really just wanted
to say thank you.
You saved my life, brother.
And anyone seeing this at Sparta,
anybody out in Pittsburgh,
you reach out to Tommy Riordan and
tell him Mark said, "Thank you."
Footage taken from a helmet
cam on the ground in Iraq
captured the heroic incident.
Hello?
Brendan?
Been looking all over for you.
How's it going?
It's going.
I was thinking we should
go grab a coffee.
I don't drink coffee, man.
What do you want?
You don't wanna go
sit down somewhere?
I'm good right here.
Okay.
Shit, Tommy, how was I supposed to know
I was never gonna see you guys again?
Yeah, well, you were briefed.
You had the information.
You chose the old
man and the girl.
She wasn't just some girl.
I married her.
She's my wife.
See?
That's Tess.
That's Emily and Rosie.
They're your nieces, Tommy.
I don't know them.
I know you don't know them. Of
course you don't know them.
So why am I looking at pictures
of people I don't know?
'Cause that's my family.
And who are you exactly?
I'm your brother, man.
You were in the Corps?
What?
- I said I didn't know you were in the Corps.
- I wasn't in the Corps.
Then you ain't no brother to me.
My brother was in the Corps.
Jesus, Tommy. Tommy.
I was a 16-year-old kid.
What the hell did I know?
I don't know what you know.
Why don't you go ask your
girlfriend about it?
She's my wife, Tommy.
So, that's it? I stay with Tess, I
never get to see you guys again?
Not a single phone call?
Nothing?
God, man, I don't
understand this.
What? You...
So, you won't forgive me,
but you forgave Pop?
No, he's just some old vet that I train
with, you know? He means nothing to me.
And what I hear, he means
nothing to you, either.
You got balls talking
about forgiveness.
That has nothing to
do with forgiveness.
I got children, man. I
got a family to protect.
Everything I do is for them.
I forgave Pop.
Just like I forgave you and Mom.
You forgave us?
Yeah.
Well, I'm not surprised you
made the tournament, Brendan.
You got some stones, man.
I fell in love. What the
hell was I supposed to do?
You were supposed to stick to the plan.
You were supposed to come with us.
Mom needed you, I needed you. You're
my big brother. You bailed on me.
Hey, you know, I'm glad you stayed.
Everything worked out for you.
God.
You leave, you get the opposite.
Okay?
You leave, you get
to bury people.
You're not the only one
that suffered, Tommy.
I didn't even know she was sick.
I never even got the chance to
say goodbye to my own mother.
You had no right to keep that from me.
That was not your decision to make!
You know what?
You walk around with your
pictures of your wife,
and you're all, "I forgive you."
"I forgive Pop."
"I forgive everyone."
Brendan, you know,
you're full of shit.
Are we done, Brendan?
Are we finished?
You realize you're supposed
to seek my wise counsel
while school's actually
in session, right?
- Yes, Principal Z.
- Tell him.
Okay, we wanna use the
auditorium this weekend
to watch Mr. C in Sparta.
What do you say?
So, you want to use
the auditorium
to watch a suspended teacher engage in
the activity that he was suspended for?
- Right.
- Am I hearing this correct?
Right. Okay, we thought
you would say that,
so it could turn into a
fundraiser, you know?
You know, I think you need
to talk to your parents,
because you guys might need
to be in summer school.
- Everybody wants this.
- Come on, Mr. Zito.
We've been telling everybody
about it already.
- Exactly.
- And the gym's the only place
- that's big enough to fit everyone.
- Look, it's never gonna happen.
- What if we get a petition signed?
- We'll get the whole school to sign it.
- The power of democracy.
- What are they gonna do about that?
Mr. Z, please?
Look, look, you guys. I appreciate the fact
that you love your teacher, I really do,
but there is nothing
I can do for you.
The roof is about to blow clean
off Boardwalk Hall Arena.
It might be Fourth of July weekend, but
this is Christmas Eve for fight fans.
This is Atlantic City. This
is the War on the Shore,
and this is what everyone's
been waiting for.
Sixteen of the baddest men on the planet
duking it out over a 24-hour period
for the largest purse in
mixed martial arts history.
In the town everyone knows
from the game of Monopoly,
we got ourselves a
winner-take-all affair.
Buckle your seatbelts, roll the dice,
and take a ride on the Reading.
Sparta is here!
Welcome, I'm Bryan Callen,
along with bestselling fight
author, Sam Sheridan.
Sam, when J.J. Riley
conceived Sparta,
he wanted to create,
quite simply,
the biggest mixed martial
arts spectacle in history.
$5 million, Bryan. $5 million.
J.J. Riley put his money
where his mouth is
and put up the biggest purse
the sport has ever seen.
It's unprecedented, Sam.
As is the hoopla surrounding one
Tommy Riordan, the war hero,
who has become an
overnight sensation
and captured the imagination
and attention...
Jujitsu black belt
Francisco Barbosa,
who has a 19 to four record in
his mixed martial arts' career.
Our rules of the cage are
brought to you by Tapout.
- Five minutes, Paddy.
- Okay.
It looks as though the
moment of truth has arrived,
- because here comes Tommy Riordan.
- Wow!
Tommy Riordan's captured
the media's attention,
but the question still remains.
Who is this guy?
And more importantly,
can he compete in this talent pool?
Can he win?
I wish I knew. I wish
I knew who he was.
And I say the fact that I
don't know is very strange.
In an Internet age where
there are no secrets,
this guy's a complete mystery.
I can't find out
anything about him.
Tommy Riordan is
officially Google-proof.
Get your hands off me.
Okay, let's go.
You gotta love this guy, Sam.
No walk-out music, no
sponsors, no interviews.
He skipped the press conference,
wouldn't have his picture
taken for the program.
He's breaking every rule.
The only reason, really, that Tommy
Riordan is in this tournament
is an MMA video making the rounds of him
beating up Mad Dog Grimes in the gym.
But the reason that a lot of
his fans are in the stands
is because of another video.
It's even more stunning than
the Mad Dog Grimes video.
This guy... Let me
describe it to you, folks,
for the few that haven't seen it, and
I don't know anybody who hasn't,
but Tommy Riordan ripped
the door off a tank
in the heat of battle,
saving lives in the process,
and then walked away
without claiming a medal.
- Listen...
- He ripped the door off a tank.
Tommy Riordan is a
genuine war hero.
I'm not taking anything away from the
guy, he's a very, very tough guy,
- but the tank don't hit back, you know.
- Sam...
We've seen YouTube sensations
fail on a big stage before.
Sam, he ripped the
door off a tank!
Tommy Riordan, he has
definitely got his hands full
in his first opponent,
Francisco Barbosa.
- Francisco Barbosa...
- He's nothing to scoff at.
Yeah, he's the octopus.
He's the real deal.
He's a very, very tough guy,
a very high-caliber fighter.
Now, Tommy Riordan
came out of nowhere,
and I'd imagine he's gonna
disappear just as quickly.
It's a great story,
but I think your boy is
gonna be exposed here
- as a YouTube sensation.
- Well, well,
a lot of fans here in Boardwalk
Hall hope you're wrong, Sam.
All right, gentlemen, you've
been given your instructions.
I expect a clean fight.
Obey my command at all times,
defend yourselves at all times.
Touch gloves, go
back, let's do this.
Tommy, cut off the corners,
feel this guy out,
just like we know.
Just like we know.
We're about to get the big
answer to the big question.
Is Tommy Riordan for real?
- Gentlemen, you ready?
- They are both game fighters.
- And here we go.
- You ready?
Let's go to war!
Keep your focus, Tom.
And here we go. We're
gonna see this.
Barbosa's gonna be
looking for a takedown.
He's definitely looking
for a takedown here.
Barbosa is down! Barbosa
has been knocked out!
Tommy Riordan is most
definitely for real.
And now he's walking out of the cage.
He's leaving the cage.
Hey, Tommy!
There goes another
rule, out the window!
Where you going?
Francisco Barbosa is out cold,
and he is out of this
tournament, Bryan.
- A huge left hook, launching...
- Good. Nice and easy. Nice and easy.
- ...Tommy Riordan into the second round.
- One, two. Good, good. One, two, three.
Good. Two, three.
Good. Good, good, good.
- Good. Come on. Good. One, two.
- Tommy Riordan is the real deal.
- Showtime.
- All right. Come on, give me eight.
Yes! That's my boy.
Let's go, move your head around.
You ready?
Look at me.
You can do this.
I wanna hear you say it.
I can do this.
Let's go do this.
Yeah.
J.J. Riley only had 48 hours, less
than 48 hours, to fill the spot.
And basically, he had to go
on the road to Frank Campana.
Well, then he chose
Brendan Conlon,
which is really something
I don't understand.
I just... I'm shocked.
Hey, Brendan.
Brendan, go get him.
Go. Good luck.
Let's go, Brendan.
You go get him, Son!
You know, I can understand
coming out to no music,
but why in the world would you choose
classical music as your entrance?
This is Beethoven. This
is Ode to Joy, Bryan.
My apologies, Mr.
Renaissance Man.
Go get him, Son.
If you wanna talk about Renaissance men,
you gotta talk about Frank Campana.
Very unorthodox trainer, but one
of the best trainers in the game,
and he's well known for using classical
music to teach his fighters to remain calm,
to remain patient, and to
remain composed under pressure.
You know, I'll tell you, classical music
is about as fitting to this setting
as Brendan Conlon is
to this tournament.
- Come on.
- In fact, let me show you something.
Right here. Let me tell you...
- What?
- You see that, right there?
That, right there... That, my
friend, is Brendan Conlon.
Okay? Brendan Conlon's about to
be dropped into a shark tank.
He's a feeder fish.
Come on, give the guy a break.
You know, the guy... At
least we've seen him fight.
I mean, he's fought real guys.
He's been in the UFC.
- We remember him from that.
- I remember him, too.
I remember him being
very unmemorable.
Midnight Le getting ready to climb
into the cage and go to work.
When the brackets
were announced,
he thought he'd be going
up against Marco Santos.
He's got to be thrilled to be seeing
Brendan Conlon across from him.
Hey! You asked for it.
Brendan retired from
fighting some years ago.
He's actually a high school
physics teacher now,
and Midnight had some fun with that
at the press conference yesterday.
Well, he said he was going to give
the teacher a serious lesson,
and that getting killed was no
way to spend a summer vacation.
Midnight is known for talking trash,
he's also known for backing it up.
No question, Bryan. He's
in a lot of trouble here.
- Midnight Le is an agent of destruction.
- Gentlemen.
Go get him.
All right, guys, you've been
given your instructions.
I expect a clean fight.
Obey my commands at all times.
Defend yourselves at all times.
Touch gloves, go
back, let's do this.
Go have some fun, baby.
Gentlemen, you ready?
You ready? Let's go to war!
Work your kicks!
Come on, Brendan, come on.
Move! You gotta move,
you gotta move.
Let it out! Come on, move!
Stay away from the legs! Circle!
In and out!
Get off the fence!
Get through this. Sprawl down!
There he goes!
Come on, Brendan.
Get out of there!
Come on!
Get up!
- Come on! Come on!
- Watch the back of the head!
- Relax, you're okay. You're okay!
- Midnight is all over Brendan.
Well, this can't last much longer.
This won't last much longer.
The teacher just has no answers.
Get out of there!
- And now, he's got the hooks in.
- The hooks are in.
- Brendan in very big trouble.
- The end is close.
Can Brendan make the
end of the round?
Well, he's got the choke.
- He's got 20 seconds left in the round...
- Come on.
And Conlon's face is turning purple.
This looks like it's over.
Get up! Find his legs!
Hips! Hip down!
Hip down! Get your weight down!
Get your weight down!
Well, Midnight is squeezing with all
his might. He's got it very deep.
- Ten seconds! Don't you tap!
- Ten seconds, Bryan, 10 seconds.
Don't tap! Brendan,
don't you tap!
Hold on, Brendan.
Conlon doing his
best to hang on,
'cause his whole world's about
to go from day to night.
Don't you tap! Don't
you tap, Brendan!
I cannot believe that, Sam!
I thought for sure this
guy was going to sleep.
Midnight can't believe
it either, by the way.
Jesus.
What are you doing?
You should've had him
in the first round.
Beautiful. Beautiful. He
doesn't know what hit him.
He doesn't know what hit him.
Breathe.
Deep breaths. Come on now.
Small sip, small sip. Small sip.
Deep breath, deep breath. I
want you to do something.
I want you to get
him to pull, okay?
When he pulls, I want you to hit him a
bit and I want you to shoot on him.
I'd love to be a fly on the wall,
listening to Frank Campana right now
and hear what he's
saying in there.
In and out. In and out.
In and out.
And I want you to trade punches with
him, all right? You're doing beautiful.
Let's go, seconds out!
Knock him out. Knock him out.
Knock him out.
This round, knock him out.
- Let's do it.
- He doesn't deserve to be here.
Beautiful. Breathe.
Let's go!
And here we go. The teacher
answering the bell for round two.
Nice and easy!
Set the pace! Set
the pace, Brendan!
Gentlemen! Let's go to war!
Circle around! Circle around!
Nice and easy!
Good, good!
Shoot! Shoot on him!
Get out of there! Hitch him!
Hitch him! Hitch him!
Get out of there! Get out of there!
Get out of there! Come on!
Do something.
Shoot! Shoot on him!
Shoot on him!
Yes!
Conlon shoots on Midnight
Le and gets him down.
Midnight is trying
to get to his...
- Scissors takedown.
- A beautiful scissors takedown.
- Really nice.
- Conlon showing signs of life
and not backing down.
Knees, knees!
Good!
Take his arm! Good!
- He's got a kimura lock!
- He's got a very good kimura.
Turn your hips in! In!
Up! Stay with him.
Turn your hips in!
Hips up! Turn your hips in!
You got it, Brendan. Your round.
You got it!
Turn your hips up and in!
Hips up! Very good!
He's in a lot of trouble.
That's it! Come on! Come on!
- Wow! He's got it very, very deep.
- Midnight is in a very, very bad position.
Midnight is in big trouble.
Slow down! Relax! You got it!
You got it!
Brendan Conlon is going
to finish it right here!
Brendan Conlon has got him in a
very, very dangerous position
- and Midnight is in big trouble.
- Midnight...
I don't think Midnight
has anywhere to go.
You got it! You got it!
Slow down! Relax! You got it!
You got it!
And this isn't...
This isn't happening!
- This can't happen.
- It just did, Bryan.
He tapped!
Brendan Conlon tapped Midnight!
- I can't believe that.
- Oh, my goodness!
You got him! Way to go, Brendan!
Yeah! Yeah! He tapped him out.
Honey, he tapped him out!
He did it! He did it! He did it!
He did it!
Way to go, Brendan!
Way to go! Yeah!
This is what's so great
about mixed martial arts.
There's so many ways to lose.
One tiny miscalculation,
anyone can win at anytime.
Which is probably why Frank
Campana's embracing his man.
And I honestly don't think either one
of them can believe what just happened.
Great show of sportsmanship
here from the teacher.
Well, that's a hallmark of
Frank Campana's philosophy,
something all his
fighters buy into,
and, obviously, none
more so than Brendan.
And Midnight Le is shocked.
He thought he'd get a free
pass into the second round,
but, instead, he's going home.
Dominated the fight the entire way, but
he falls prey to a very technical finish.
A very technical finish,
but that's a fluke.
- I don't care what anybody says. That is a...
- I don't know.
You can call it a fluke, but I'm gonna
call it a guy maintaining composure
and waiting for his opportunity.
Conlon beats Midnight!
Unbelievable!
I hope you got a receipt
for your goldfish.
Yes!
Okay.
We're down to eight fighters,
and soon to be seven,
as Koba prepares to go to work
for the second time tonight.
- Right hand.
- Huge right hand.
- Oh, my goodness.
Oh, my God! This is over.
Once again, Koba does
not break a sweat.
You got to be kidding me. I'm afraid
he might have broken something else.
That's certainly possible.
Koba moving on to
tomorrow night.
- Koba! Koba!
Mad Dog fighting like
a man possessed.
Like a man with
something to prove,
reminding everyone why he is a serious
contender to win this whole contest.
He wanted to send a message to Tommy
Riordan, and there it is, right there.
Here comes the underdog,
Brendan Conlon.
The teacher miraculously
passed his first test,
but now he's got
to face The Dane.
Brendan! You can do it.
Halfway through round three,
now, and the beating continues.
I honestly don't know how Brendan Conlon
can take this kind of punishment.
He has been battered
without mercy
- in both of his fights today.
- Relax! You're okay!
He's still standing, Bryan.
Beethoven!
No! No, no, no!
Good, take him down!
Look at this, he's
taking The Dane down!
Hold on to him.
He's looking for that arm.
He's looking for the armbar.
- He's got an armbar.
- He's got that armbar.
He's looking to be boss
of it, once again.
Tap, tap, tap! Come
on, tap, tap, tap!
Palms flat! Palms flat!
Thumbs up!
He's got that arm, Sam!
- Break, break, break, break!
- Yes!
Are you kidding me?
Yes!
Do it once, it's a fluke. Do it
twice, and it's something else.
Pull the bandwagon over,
I think I am hopping on.
I think I'm a believer.
You did it! Way to go, Brendan!
- I'm doing this!
- Okay.
- I'm doing it!
Okay, Son.
The crowd catching fire for
the hero Tommy Riordan.
- Tommy! Tommy!
He doesn't seem to want anything
to do with all this adulation.
He's just here to fight.
- Tommy! Tommy!
Gentlemen, you ready?
Are you ready?
- Let's go to war!
- Right at him! Right at him! Right at him!
Well, here he comes
again like a buzz saw!
- Yeah.
- He is all over Diego Santana.
He's swarming all over him, and now
he's beating on him without mercy!
Oh, my goodness!
There he goes again,
storming out of the cage!
Tommy Riordan marching
off through the crowd
and straight into the final
four, ladies and gentlemen.
- Tommy! Tommy!
- So where is he?
- Yeah. Mr. Conlon.
Make a right at
that white sign...
Hey! Can't sleep, huh?
I know that that other thing is
bothering the hell out of you.
I'm proud of you, Tommy.
What you did for that
kid in the tank,
that was really something.
How about deserting my unit?
Is that really something, too?
Yeah.
I was on my way out of the country
when I came across those guys.
What was I supposed to do?
Let them drown?
No.
- What did you do?
- What did I do?
I took off.
That's why you go by Riordan.
That's why they can't find
your service records.
What the hell happened
over there, Tommy?
That is none of
your business, man.
Come on, kiddo. You
know, I've been there.
I've done it, I've seen it.
You can trust me. I understand.
Will you spare me the compassionate
father routine, Pop?
The suit don't fit.
Tommy.
I'm really trying here.
- You're trying?
- Yeah, really. I'm trying.
Now?
Where were you when it mattered?
I needed this guy back when I was a kid.
I don't need you now.
You know, it's too late now.
Everything's already happened.
You and Brendan don't
seem to understand that.
Let me explain something
to you, okay?
The only thing that I have in
common with Brendan Conlon
is that the pair of us,
we have absolutely
no use for you.
Look at you.
Yeah, I was right.
I think I liked you better
when you were a drunk.
At least you had some
balls then, not like now,
tiptoeing around, like some
beggar with your cup out.
Take it somewhere else.
In fact, you know what?
Here's a cup.
Why don't you take this and go get
yourself some more of your shitty tapes...
- Don't do this, Tommy.
- ...and you go back to the room
- and you listen to some more...
- Don't do this.
Fish stories that no one gives a
shit about. Now get out of here.
Get the fuck out of here! Go on.
God pity them!
All shall perish except me!
Bastards. Bastards!
You bastards. You bastards!
Stop the ship, you bastards!
Ishmael. God pity them.
Stop the ship. Please,
stop the ship.
Stop the ship! Somebody.
Ahab.
You godless son of a bitch!
You stop the ship!
"'The whale! The ship!' cried
the cringing oarsmen."
"Oars! Oars! Slope downward..."
Stop it.
"'O sea that ere it
be for ever too late,
"'Ahab may slide this last,
last time upon his mark!"'.
Captain...
Stop the...
Captain, stop...
Stop the ship, Ahab.
For the love of God.
They're lost.
Stop it... The ship.
Ahab...
You stop the...
Oh, no.
- Come on, give me the Walkman.
- No.
- No, no.
- Come on.
Come on, come on. Come,
give me the bottle.
Come here, come here, come here.
- Come on. Give me.
- No.
Tommy.
We're lost.
We're lost, Tommy.
It's over. We'll
never make it back.
- Stay down.
- We'll never make it back.
I'm here.
I always loved you.
You know that, don't you, Tommy?
You and your brother.
My two boys.
- Tommy! Tommy!
Tommy Riordan coming down the
tunnel without his trainer.
Once again, no walk-out music.
I'd hardly say no music, Sam.
Bryan, it sounds like V-J
day in Times Square.
I've never seen
anything like this.
Tommy acknowledging his
comrades for the first time
and climbing into the cage.
Mad Dog Grimes has been
waiting for revenge
ever since the day Tommy Riordan
walked into his gym in Pittsburgh
and turned his life upside down.
It's been a very long and very miserable
few months for Mad Dog, to say the least.
Grimes mocking Riordan by having a
camouflage motif for his mohawk tonight,
and the Marines are really
letting Mad Dog have it.
All right, gentlemen.
All right, gentlemen, we've
been over your instructions.
I expect a clean fight.
Obey my commands at all times,
defend yourselves at all times.
Touch gloves, go
back, let's do this.
It's not gonna happen again.
Mad Dog chomping at the bit here. He
can't wait to get a piece of Tommy.
He predicted an early knockout.
He said he was gonna take
Tommy out with one punch.
And by the way, he said, "They're
gonna have to pull me off him."
We'll see what Tommy
has to say about that.
Gentlemen, you ready?
You ready?
- Let's go to war!
- Here they go and they are off!
Tommy tackles him,
and he's on top!
He's raining bombs!
- Cover up!
- Come on, work it.
- Raining bombs.
- Mad Dog is out.
Mad Dog's in trouble.
Please stop this.
Stop it! Stop the fight!
Break! Break! Break!
That's the fastest knockout I
think I've ever experienced!
Mad Dog Grimes has been poleaxed.
He is not moving.
You do that to someone on the street,
they lock you up and throw away the key.
Break out the yellow tape, Sam.
This guy's walking away from the cage
like he's leaving a crime scene!
- Tommy! Tommy!
- Everybody through. Come on, move it out.
- Sparta!
Yeah!
Mr. C! Mr. C!
I'm on your side.
Let's go.
- Principal Zito, there he is.
- Nice.
Let's go, Brendan.
Brendan Conlon came into this
tournament as 1,000-to-one underdog,
and now here he is
in the final four.
The crowd showing their appreciation.
He's getting quite the reception.
He's got a huge reception. I mean,
this guy shocked everybody.
Come on, come on. You all right?
You've got a visitor.
Second row, 10 o'clock.
You all right with that?
I love you.
And here comes the
great Russian, Koba.
Koba is so intimidating and his
reputation is larger than life.
- Koba! Koba!
I want you to look right at him when
he comes in here. Look right at him.
All right? Don't take
your eyes off him.
I'm proud of you, brother.
This is your cage.
Gentlemen.
All right, gentlemen, we've
been over your instructions.
I expect a clean fight.
Obey my commands at all times,
defend yourselves at all times.
Touch gloves, go
back, let's do this.
Should I be nervous for Brendan?
'Cause I am.
I wanna stop the fight
before it even gets going.
- Well, here we go.
- He's like a machine. Look at him.
Gentlemen, you ready?
You ready? Let's go to war!
Keep your hands up, Brendan.
Hands up.
But now, the question is, how long
can Brendan Conlon stay alive?
Angle out of it!
Keep moving!
Get out of there!
Keep moving! Keep moving!
Get away from him!
Hit him, babe! Hit him!
Get in there!
- Crushing body shots.
- Relax, you're okay.
Conlon's down, and Koba
pounces and starts pounding!
Get up! Get up!
He's just pounding on him
like a side of beef.
Go, go, go. Get up!
He's getting his ass whooped.
And now he's got him in the air!
Oh, God.
Relax, tie up his arm!
Tie him up!
I think Campana has to
think seriously about...
- How much abuse can one man take?
- ...continuing another round of this.
Go to war!
Just relax! Relax! Relax!
Off the fence!
Brendan's going for a ride!
That one shook the
entire building!
Man, he just threw him against
the fence like a rag doll.
Get up! Get up! Come on! Hold on!
Turn it in! Turn in!
And now he's on top!
Koba's on top,
and he's finishing him, here. Look at this.
On the edge of blowing it.
Get off the fence, Brendan!
You wonder how Conlon can take
this kind of beating on his arms.
- His forearms and his hands.
- Drop that neck!
How much can one man take?
Break! Break! Break!
Everybody has got to be
a little bit concerned
about Brendan Conlon's bravery
getting him in trouble here.
His bravery could get
him killed, frankly.
And by the way, he's got
nothing more to prove.
- He's lasted two rounds with Koba.
- That's true, that's true.
And you wonder what's
keeping this guy up.
Sit down. Sit down.
Breathe. Breathe!
Look at me. Look at me!
Wait up. Small sips. Hold it.
Hold it, small sips.
Why are we here? Why
are we here, Brendan?
Why are we here? Are we
here to win this fight?
Are we here to win this fight?
You tell me. 'Cause if we're
not, I will throw in the towel.
We will get Tess and
we will go home.
We'll go home, okay?
You don't knock him out,
you lose the fight.
Do you understand me?
You don't knock him out,
you don't have a home.
Let's go! Seconds out!
Seconds out!
Gentlemen! Let's go to war!
Conlon somehow answering
the call to round three.
And Koba's all over
him once again.
Brendan's giving back, Bryan.
I mean, there's signs of
life in Brendan Conlon.
He's starting to mix it up.
Pummel, pummel, pummel.
He's taking Koba down, but
the Russian's back up.
Brendan shoots him again,
pressing him against the cage.
- Yes!
- Whoa, he's fallen deep into a guillotine.
Well, Conlon trapped
in an iron vice here,
and Koba now squeezing his
neck for all it's worth,
trying to choke the teacher out.
Hips, hips, hips! Breathe!
Breathe!
Ride it out! Ride it out!
Conlon looking for a way out.
- What is this?
- Just tossed Koba. Can you believe this?
He just shook off a
guillotine and tossed Koba.
Conlon's looking for an armbar.
He's looking for that armbar,
- and he's trying to submit the Russian bear.
- Hips, hips, hips!
Yeah, you got him! You got him!
You got him!
Koba slips right out.
Conlon's staying after him.
He's squeezing the bear.
The tables have turned and the boy scout
is actually messing with the bear.
The teacher springing off the
fence and going for a mountain,
- but Koba's on his feet.
- Get up, get up!
He does not want to be on
the ground with Brendan
and his endless bag
of submissions.
Koba trying to reestablish his dominance
with brutal shots to the face.
But Conlon's showing no fear.
This is a fight!
We have got ourselves a fight!
Wow, that's a huge
elbow to the head.
And now, Conlon goes for a knee bar.
He's got it very deep!
He's got it very, very deep!
He's deep on that.
He's got Koba in a lot of pain.
We saw this with Midnight,
we saw it against The Dane,
and we're seeing it here!
Brendan Conlon...
Break it! Break it! Break it!
Not letting out!
Conlon wrenching that
knee for all it's worth.
He's putting everything
he has into it.
And Koba is screaming in pain.
Koba taps.
Koba has tapped! Brendan
Conlon has tapped Koba!
I can't believe it! Brendan
He's tapped Koba!
And Frank Campana
can't believe it.
This whole place can't believe it.
I can't believe it.
Brendan Conlon has
tapped the great Koba.
- Tess!
- You got it! You did it!
Brendan taps the world Sambo
champ with a knee bar!
- Babe, you did it!
- Brendan Conlon!
- I don't know what to say. It's amazing!
- I don't know what I just saw.
I just don't know how to
put this into context.
That's gotta be the biggest
upset in MMA history.
I have never seen
anything like this.
He tapped a world Sambo
champion in a knee bar!
Brendan Conlon has
tapped the great Koba!
Brendan Conlon, the physics teacher!
Brendan Conlon, the civilian!
He's done the impossible.
He has done the impossible.
He's pulled off a miracle.
This place is going crazy because
they've just seen a miracle.
This is CNN Breaking News.
A surprising turn in the story
of Iraq War hero, Tommy Riordan.
CNN has learned that
Riordan's true identity
is that of Marine Staff
Sergeant Thomas Conlon,
who went AWOL from his
unit earlier this year,
following the friendly fire
death of his brother-in-arms,
Sergeant Manny Fernandez.
Fernandez's wife, Pilar
Fernandez, spoke with me
in an exclusive
interview, moments ago.
The bombs started dropping.
They were coming from US planes.
Tommy and Manny were
waving their flags
to let them know
they were Americans,
but they didn't stop.
Everyone died.
Everyone except Tommy.
And, you know, my
Manny used to say,
that Tommy was the
brother he never had.
Conlon, who is fighting in the mixed
martial arts mega tournament, Sparta,
is expected to be taken into
custody by military police,
following tonight's winner-take-all
finale in Atlantic City.
If victorious, he has pledged
his $5 million purse
to the widow of his
fallen comrade.
We've just got some
incredible news,
that I'm having trouble putting
into context, but here it is.
The two men fighting for
the championship tonight,
for the $5 million prize,
for the middleweight
championship of the world,
are brothers.
All right, let's get this off.
What are you gonna do?
I'm gonna fight him.
- Mr. C, Mr. C!
- Tommy! Tommy!
Gentlemen.
Gentlemen, this is the final.
I expect a clean fight.
Obey my commands at all times,
defend yourselves at all times.
Touch gloves, go
back, let's do this.
Where's Pop?
Gentlemen, are you ready?
Are you ready?
Let's go to war!
Relax, Brendan, relax!
Get out! Get out of there!
Throw your hands!
Don't lose it. No, no, no!
Move! Move!
Tie him up! Tie him up! Control his moves.
Control his moves.
Control the arms! Keep control
in the arms! Breathe!
You're okay! Relax! Breathe!
Get up! Get up! Get up!
Relax! Breathe!
Tie him up! Get up! Tie him up, Brendan!
Tie him up!
Come on. Get him! Get him!
Get him!
Break!
What was that?
Hey, come on, Josh!
What's up with that?
Hey, step back!
Watch that late blow!
Come on!
Come on, Josh! I
mean, what is that?
Come on, come on. Sit down.
Sit, sit, sit.
Sit... Brendan, sit down.
Look at me. Sit down.
Brendan, look at me. Look at me.
Look at me, Brendan. Let it go.
Let it go, okay?
Breathe. Beethoven.
Okay. He's coming right at you, right?
Exactly like we planned.
I want you to angle out, hit and
move every time. All right?
- Angle out and move.
- Good.
Breathe. Breathe.
Come on, relax.
- Okay. He's not your brother, right?
- Time's up!
Look at me. He's not
your brother, right?
- All right.
- He's in the way.
Seconds out. Wrap it up.
Taking a little more
time for the cheap shot.
Do your job, Josh.
Come on, babe. Come on.
Let's go to war.
Breathe!
Pace, pace! Control the pace!
Cover up!
Come on, get off the fence!
Get off the fence!
Hands up! Hands up!
Head up! You're all right!
Relax! Breathe!
Yeah!
Get him!
- Huge throw. Huge.
- Look at that.
Turn in! Don't give
him your back!
Turn in! Go! Good! Good!
Come on, get out of it!
Go! Get up!
Control the arms!
Cover up, cover up. Push it!
Break free! Break! Break!
Good, good, good! Clean break!
Stop! Hey, stop!
- Come on.
- Here we go, mom.
Time to lock up your china,
the boys are at it again!
Let's go to war!
Now! Get up! Get up!
Get up! Come on, babe! Get up!
Get up! Get up!
Control it! Control
it with the arms.
Switch! Switch!
Hips!
Down, down. Hips down.
Oh, my God. That's a deep omoplata there.
He's got the seats up.
Come on, Tommy!
You've got him, babe! You've got him, babe!
Come on, tap him out!
Tom!
Break! Break! Break!
Tommy, you okay?
- Tommy!
- Go! Let's go! Go!
Calm down. Calm down.
- It's the championship. Keep it together.
- All right. All right. I got it.
Sit down. Sit down!
- Tommy! Tommy!
- I popped his shoulder.
- Relax. Breathe. Breathe.
- I heard it tear.
- You popped his shoulder?
- Yeah.
- Good. Okay.
I want you to pop his other shoulder.
Let's go.
- Josh.
- Hey, hey, no Josh.
- Hey!
- Look at me. Look at me.
- What?
All right, you got two rounds.
Two rounds.
We need both rounds.
What?
- Tommy! Tommy!
Go in there, you kick him in the
head, take him down and finish him!
Tommy, what are you doing?
Shut up. Come on.
Stand back.
Come on. What? Have
you gone crazy?
Let's go to war!
Brendan, pick your hands up!
It's over.
What are you doing?
It's over, Tommy.
You better fight!
It's over, Tommy. Come on.
Tommy, we don't have to do this.
Come on. Why do you
want to do this, Tommy?
Am I gonna have to
watch you do this?
Okay? You all right there?
Tommy!
Quick, finish him!
You finish him!
Come on.
Break, break, break!
Back up, back up!
I'm sorry, Tommy. I'm sorry.
Tap, Tommy.
It's okay. It's okay.
I love you.
I love you, Tommy.
Someone needs to stop Clearway Law.
Public shouldn't leave reviews for lawyers.