Downloaded from
YTS.MX
Official YIFY movies site:
[girl] At a time in the world where things
were feeling less and less certain,
there was one thing
you could always count on…
the Heroics.
Our planet's team of superheroes.
And our heroes…
never failed.
[triumphant music plays]
Sorry I'm late.
I had to put the ISR
synthetic aperture together.
Let's just hope it's more
than just a downed satellite…
so the whole team
can spring into action.
Let's not. [puffs]
Be careful with that thing.
When am I not careful?
All the time.
[sonic boom]
Hey, Tech-No.
What's up?
The solar array,
it's blown to bits.
[Tech-No] Seriously?
There's something coming,
a spaceship of some kind.
It just blasted
some kind of energy ray at me.
Do these clowns not know who I am?
[Tech-No] I don't mean to be a nudge,
but any idea how long this'll take?
I'm running on fumes.
[whirring]
Just a quick selfie for my socials
while I stop this thing--
[tense music plays]
Wait a minute.
There's not one ship…
[engines revving]
There's a whole armada out there.
Funny, if I didn't know better,
I'd say you sound a little worried.
[beeping]
Miracle Guy?
-[boom]
-[grunts]
-[earpiece beeps]
-H-Base! Come in, this is Tech-No!
-Miracle Guy's been hit!
-[H-Base] Hit with what?
[Tech-No grunts]
[beeping]
He's barely conscious!
[H-Base] Miracle Guy is barely conscious?
Have a catcher ready!
-[frantic beeping]
-[spluttering]
I'm out! [groans]
[ominous music plays]
[girl] This was the day
our heroes fell.
All of them.
But from that…
others would rise.
[alarm beeps]
♪ Wake up, sleepyhead ♪
[sighs]
[girl] It's funny how when you look back
on a day like this,
it always begins so normal.
I mean, look at me.
I'm actually putting real thought
into what I'm gonna wear.
Like any of this
was gonna matter in an hour.
This one says, "Talk to me,"
and this one says,
"Leave me alone."
-Perfect.
-[watch beeps]
-[man] Time for breakfast, Missy.
-Good morning, Dad. Be right there.
[reporter] In rather bizarre news,
both Miracle Guy and Tech-No
were spotted plummeting
from the sky this morning.
Must have been some kind of test drill
for the Heroics defenses,
for they deployed a giant safety net
and caught the celebrated--
Morning, kiddo.
You sleep okay?
Did you?
I see you're wearing "leave me alone."
You know, I want you
to try to make some friends.
Yeah, not today.
[Missy] Whoa.
Is that Miracle Guy?
That is just a training exercise,
probably.
A… a "what if."
As long as there's no "what if"
that involves you rejoining the team.
Relax. Even though
I'm still the leader of the Heroics,
I'm doing it from the safety
of my own office.
Good.
Because a deal is a deal.
[chuckles lightly]
[kids chatter indistinctly]
-See you later, Dad.
-Mm-hmm. Be good.
Hey…
what's wrong?
Nothing.
I'm just, uh… [sighs]
I love you.
An "I love you" at 8:00 a.m.
on a random Tuesday?
Are you sure you're okay?
I love you too.
[Dad blows kiss]
-[ominous music plays]
-[beeping]
[heroic music plays]
[lock beeps]
Got the force field's up today,
so something's going down.
Did they really see an armada
out in space?
[PA] Next stop, Heroics lobby.
We're tracking over
a hundred alien vessels.
Who do you wanna send?
How about…
Blinding Fast and Crushing Low?
They haven't gotten along
since the Crisis of Edinburgh.
-Okay.
-[machine beeps]
How about…
Sharkboy and Lavagirl?
-They still married?
-This isn't a two-hero job.
Look…
[computer whirs, beeps]
Okay, so we'll send three. Happy?
I'm afraid those are just the scouts,
the tip of the spear.
This is what we're really up against.
[computer whirs]
We've never dealt with
anything like this before.
That's impossible.
[woman] Which hero should we send, ma'am?
All of them.
Call the president. He's the only one
that can authorize a full Heroic attack.
[man] It's before noon.
He'll still be asleep.
Wake him up!
Excuse me, Marcus.
What are you still doing here?
When I said everyone, I meant everyone.
I can't suit up.
I promised my daughter.
Okay, well, I'm sorry.
They'll need all the help they can get,
and you know it.
It's time for you to rejoin the team.
Time to be a Heroic again.
[heroic music plays]
[Marcus sighs]
That is an order.
Yes, ma'am.
Good.
[girl 1] Just grab it!
[Missy] I'm trying!
[girl 2] Can't you just
fly up there or something?
I can't fly.
Use your magnet hands.
I don't have magnet hands.
Hurry! I'm getting tired!
[girl 2] How about hurricane breath?
Hurricane breath? That's not even a thing.
-Wait.
-Whoa!
[boy] What's up? Did she get it?
She tried,
but she doesn't have any powers.
[boy] But you're--
Marcus Moreno's kid.
I know. It's weird.
Not me. Gravity.
Thanks for the ball.
You're welcome.
Missy Moreno?
Yes.
You'll need to come with us.
[radio] What was described earlier today
as merely telescopic observations…
So where are we going again? And why?
…above the Earth's atmosphere is now
confirmed to be something more serious,
causing a mass mobilization
of superhero personnel…
What mobilization?
-What is believed to be an alien…
-[Missy] Can you turn it up?
Wait, wait. Did they say, "Aliens"?
[helicopter blades whirring]
[beeping]
Dad? Dad, what's going on?
[Marcus] Missy, where are you?
Are they moving you to headquarters?
I think so.
-Good.
-[signal splutters]
Dad?
Not worried, not worried…
[exhales slowly]
So I'm Miss Granada,
director of the Heroics program.
You'll be staying
in our underground stronghold
where children of superheroes
are kept safe
while their parents fight enemy forces.
We can't afford to have even one of you
fall into enemy hands.
This way.
Do I really have to go in?
Because I won't fit in.
I just don't belong.
I mean, I'm different from all of them.
Besides, my dad doesn't fight anymore.
And after my mom died, he promised that--
Yes, well, you know what they say
about promises?
You should always keep them
or you're a liar who can never be trusted?
Are you going to be a problem, Missy?
Shall we?
Everyone…
this is Missy.
She will be joining you today.
Missy, I'd appreciate it
if you would take a seat right there
and quietly continue your studies
along with the other children.
Children…
thank you for respecting my rules.
Your parents will be very proud
when I tell them
of your exceptional behavior.
Well done. [chuckles softly]
[whispers] She's gone!
[cheering]
[boy] Yeah!
[girl squeals, laughs]
-[indistinct chattering]
-[mystical warbling]
[sloshing]
[gasps]
[tires peel out]
[tires screech]
Hey, I'm Wheels.
Yes, they call me that
on account of the wheelchair.
It's a little on the nose,
but I like it because it's cool.
Okay.
You may think I'm in the chair
'cause my legs are weak,
but it's the opposite.
My muscles are so strong
my bones can't support 'em.
But lucky for me,
my brain's the same way.
It's supercharged,
so I'm good.
So, Wheels, who's your new friend?
Missy, this is Noodles.
We call him that because, well…
He stretches and twists around
like a noodle?
Yeah, basically.
And that's Ojo.
Her power is she's a genius drawer.
Like Van Gogh mixed with Monet
with just a sprinkle of Salvador Dali.
Can I see that?
A kid standing on top of floating chairs?
An exploding exercise ball?
Nothing she draws makes sense.
[Missy] That me?
-Why'd you draw me in front of the class?
-Oh, she won't answer.
She only speaks through her drawings.
♪ Don't speak
I know just what you're saying ♪
No, you don't. You have no clue.
And this is A Capella.
-It me.
-That's your superpower? You can sing?
Yep, but I have an unusual range.
I can go low… [sings very low]
or I can go high! [sings very high]
I can even go really…
[inaudible]
I don't hear anything.
It's beyond human hearing.
[feedback]
[Granada] Miss A Capella Vox,
please refrain from using your high voice.
Every dog in the neighborhood
has surrounded our building.
[laughter]
And she can sing so low
that she moves objects.
Show her how you make things float!
[sings very low]
[gasps]
All righty, let's see who's left.
That's Blinding Fast's kid, Slo-Mo.
[Wheels] He's actually moving very fast,
but somehow,
his powers have him stuck in a time warp.
[slowly] Hi.
That kid over there…
Two packs of candy for crossing our eyes.
…is Facemaker.
Okay.
Beat that.
He makes the craziest faces.
It's impossible!
I can even change my face
to look like you.
[crunching]
He's cheating! I can't compete with that!
Oh, dude!
Rewind, clean up on aisle two.
That's Rewind.
He can rewind time but just a few seconds.
[winding back]
[Facemaker screams]
They're twins. It's crazy, right?
What twins? What are you talking about?
Fast Forward, are you at it again?
You were taking so long, I skipped you
forward a bit. Sorry, not sorry.
She and Rewind are twins.
Opposite powers.
The only thing they agree on
is they don't like each other.
-At all.
They're twins. It's crazy, right?
And then,
there's our fearless leader, Wild Card.
There's not a power
in the world he doesn't have.
True.
Sure, he has every power imaginable,
but since he can't focus his energy,
they show up randomly.
Also true…
until now that is.
Teleport!
[siren wails]
And last, but definitely not least,
Guppy.
How are you making that?
My mommy is Lavagirl,
but my daddy is Sharkboy.
So instead of lava, I move water.
[sizzling]
I need hydration for my powers to work.
[gasping]
-[Missy] That's really cool.
-[giggling] Thanks.
So, new girl, what's your superpower?
Yeah, uh, so with the whole powers thing--
Wait a second.
I remember you.
You're Marcus Moreno's kid.
Yeah, my dad hasn't gone
on any missions for a while,
so I've been chilling
with the normal kids.
Why would they put a kid with superpowers
in with normal kids?
Oh, I get it.
You don't have any powers.
You're powerless?
Whatever. Can we put on the TV?
[sighs] I want to see
if there's news about our parents.
[beeps]
You know this is
an epic Heroic smackdown event
when they've called in Sharkboy!
-[cheering]
-Yeah!
[male anchor] Earlier today,
Sharkboy appeared from the ocean depths,
landing on the beach
of South Padre Island.
And moments later, Lavagirl
blasted up from inside an active volcano.
Go Sharkboy and Lavagirl!
[female anchor]
She's from the Earth's core.
And here's Mayor Doolittle
at today's ribbon cutting
for his new city hall,
rebuilt after the last time
the Heroics went into action.
-[popping]
-[gasping]
Did you see that?
Of course you didn't.
That means
it's none other than Blinding Fast,
the fastest Heroic on the planet.
[slowly] Go, Dad!
[woman] And here comes Crushing Low!
[screaming on TV]
And there goes the mayor's new building
in record time.
These battles are insanely expensive
for taxpayers,
but so entertaining.
Pass the popcorn.
This battle's gonna be epic!
[female anchor] This is unprecedented.
All of the Heroics have been called
into action against the alien threat.
We're getting some live footage now.
And look who's back in action.
It's Miracle Guy.
You didn't expect him
to actually lose, did you?
[smoldering]
[singing scale]
He's not supposed to be there.
[whirring]
Oh my God!
No way!
No one's ever taken down Miracle Guy!
Evasive maneuvers!
[buzzing]
You okay, Sharkboy?
[gasps]
[chittering]
[growling]
[groaning]
[straining]
Oh no.
I'm just getting some terrible news.
It's almost unimaginable,
but two of our heroes
have been captured by the intruders.
I thought the Heroics were unbeatable.
They are unbeatable.
It's not over yet.
It looks like our heroes are fighting
amongst themselves again.
[both grunt]
-Ladies first.
-I don't need your dated chivalry.
-Fine, I'll go.
-How dare you!
[both scream]
-Mom!
-Dad!
Go, Dad!
[winding back]
[winding forward]
-How dare you!
-[both scream]
[winding forward]
I want to see it again.
And I don't want to see it again.
[female anchor]
And here comes Mrs. Vox to the rescue.
She'll get those aliens
singing a different tune.
[Mrs. Vox sings]
[female anchor] They took Mrs. Vox!
[groans]
-[male anchor] They got Tech-No.
-[grunts]
[gasps]
-[gasps, sighs]
-[female anchor] There goes Lavagirl!
What is happening?
Our heroes are dropping like flies!
They won't get Blinding Fast.
Not him, he's too--
[gasps]
[slow gasping]
[snarling]
[male anchor]
It's all up to Marcus Moreno now.
[groans]
[ominous music plays]
[snarling]
[beeping]
Dad?
Dad, we had a deal.
I know.
I promised I wouldn't be a hero anymore.
But I'm still the leader of the Heroics.
Dad? Dad, run! Get out of there!
And a good leader…
leads by example.
Dad!
I'm sorry, honey.
[exhales deeply]
[whimpers]
[female anchor] This is… unbelievable.
-Unimaginable.
-[male anchor] Ladies and gentlemen…
the Heroics have fallen.
[sobs gently]
[somber music plays]
We're getting word that the president
would like to address the nation.
People of America,
as you have witnessed,
the Heroics have been captured.
Military forces are stepping in,
mobilizing to bring our heroes back.
But while it looks rather hopeless…
it's bad, it--
It's hopelessly bad.
How did this guy get to be president?
He can't even put two sentences together.
We have just received a message
from the supreme commander of the aliens
that has been decoded.
It reads, "We are from the planet Ogima.
Unfortunately, we have no choice
but to prepare you for…
takeover.
Please comply,
or else Earth will be destroyed.
You have three hours."
I'm afraid that was the entire message.
There are no heroes left.
God save us all.
Children, for your own safety,
we're going into full lockdown.
No one leave your seats.
As long as you stay where you are,
you are all safe.
Yeah, right. They can't protect us
from that. We just saw it.
You got a better idea?
We should probably do
what Miss Granada says.
Uh, pardon me, but--
The last look on my dad's face
will haunt me forever.
-What do they want from us?
-Do you think our parents are okay?
-Uh, excuse me?
-What?
We need to leave this room right now.
Why?
Because the aliens know where we are,
and they're coming for us next.
[scoffs] How could you possibly know that?
Can I borrow this a minute?
Ojo drew these.
Facemaker standing on top
of the floating chairs,
Noodles smashing the exercise ball…
She draws what she sees, big deal.
She drew these things five minutes
before they happened.
Ojo's superpower isn't that she can draw,
she can draw the future.
[Wild Card] Okay, cool.
Good for Ojo. What's your point?
She also drew these alien creatures
breaking into this very room.
There.
[Noodle] Whoa!
You're saying they'll come through there?
She's right. All these drawings
suddenly make perfect sense.
Ojo can see the future.
Let me get this straight.
Some new girl shows up
with absolutely zero powers,
and suddenly
we're gonna do what she says?
Seems like she's got a point.
A moment ago, you agreed
that we weren't safe here.
We're safer in here than running around
outside with you playing captain.
I just want to get out of here.
If anybody wants to join me,
you're free to follow.
Fine. [sighs]
We're getting out of here,
but only because I say so, you got that?
What's the plan?
Granada said this place is on lockdown.
There'll be guards everywhere.
Yeah, Missy.
What's the plan?
Well…
I figure this is kind of like
making an omelet.
You always start by…
Breaking some eggs.
Hey, is that updog?
What's updog?
Not much.
Just living my best life over here.
Not like I'm totally up to no good
or anything.
[mischievous music plays]
So don't ask us how we know this,
but aliens are about to attack,
and we're no longer safe here.
This place is a fortress.
Nothing's getting in.
And I'm afraid
no one's getting out, either.
Those are the rules.
Oof! Then we're definitely
getting out of here,
and so we're gonna need your access cards.
Like, now.
[chuckles]
And you think
we'll just hand these to you?
No, but it would have made this
a whole lot easier.
Cushions.
What are these for?
Tell him, Guppy.
To protect your butts
when you hit the ground.
Why don't you get back in line?
[Guppy grunts]
[groans]
Oh, no!
She's got shark strength!
[groans]
Have a nice nap.
[whip cracking]
Aliens really are about to attack,
so we'll have to leave your expert care
until you and Miss Granada know
what we know.
[alarm blares]
[chuckling]
This was a bad idea.
Wheels, next time this happens,
don't let the guard reach the alarm.
Noodles, you'll take his jacket
and cuff them.
What next time?
You kids aren't--
[gasping]
[screams]
Told you your plan wouldn't work!
-[groaning]
-No!
Rewind, send us back.
[winding back]
So we will have to leave your expert care
until you and Miss Granada know
what we know.
-[Wheels grunts]
-[groans]
Ah!
[Missy] C'mon, let's go!
Single file line! Like a fire drill.
-We'll be questioned less.
-Let's go!
-[Wild Card gasps]
-[ominous music plays]
[snarling]
Beginner's luck.
Noodles, stretch and make yourself tall!
[squeaking]
-Greetings, fellow grown-ups.
-[woman] Hey.
Hold on one second. Hey!
[gasps]
[alarm blares]
[Missy gasps]
I… I'm so sorry!
[grunts]
[panicked cry]
Seal the doors!
[alarm continues blaring]
We're in trouble.
That was our only exit!
-Not our only one!
-How are we supposed to get up there?
A Capella? You made furniture float.
Can you do the same with people?
To go up high,
I have to sing very…
[sings deeply] ♪ …low ♪
[adults whimper]
Climb as fast as you can!
[dramatic music plays]
Noodles, open up the hatch!
[Missy] Don't let them follow us!
♪ Adios ♪
-[screams]
-[thudding]
Noodles, the access cards!
[alarm blares in distance]
[Fast Forward] We did it!
Yeah, we did it.
But the tram will only take us
to just outside the force field,
then they'll catch us for sure.
Look! They're already mobilizing!
Brace yourselves!
You too, Guppy.
A Capella,
make us fly.
[vocalizes]
[kids cheering] Yeah!
[vocalizing wavers]
She can't steer!
-We'll crash into that building!
-We need to change directions!
I'm on it!
[Missy] Help him out!
[grunting]
[jeers]
Back to base.
Now.
We need to find that train.
Well,
that was a disaster.
That was awesome.
I'm so exhausted.
-[vocalizing wavers]
-Whoa!
[kids scream]
Guys…
[breathes wheezily]
I'm running…
[kids scream]
…out of…
Breath!
We get it.
What do we do?
Don't look at me.
I'm done.
-We need to find a place to hide.
-The Heroics are locked in the alien ship.
Not all of them.
You know this how?
Do you think you can get us over to here?
-[pitch rises]
-Whoa!
Okay! Okay! Okay!
What's over there that's so important?
Well, you see, my--
Okay, this is bad.
This is really, really bad.
-Five to one says we die a fiery death.
-You're on!
-[Missy] You can do it, A Capella!
-[kids shout encouragement]
[Wheels] Come on, a little more.
[clears throat]
Does anyone have a lozenge?
[Missy] Hang on!
[kids scream]
[gardener whistles]
[groaning]
[screams]
My begonias!
Get out of my flower bed,
you little termites!
Hi, Abuelita!
Ah! Ah, Missy!
-Come and say hello to your grandma!
-[Noodles] No way!
Missy, your grandmother's Anita Moreno?
The trainer of the Heroics?
She's a legend.
No, you have to be dead
to be a legend, honey.
[grandma] Oh, mi amor.
I'm alive and well,
which is more than I can say
for my gazebo, hmm?
Sorry.
We're in trouble, Grandma,
and we need a place to hide.
To hide? You're gonna
need to do a lot more than that.
That thing is moving into position.
-[warbling]
-[Wheels] She's right.
-[beeping]
-We only have two hours left.
Won't be long until the takeover begins.
Everybody, get inside. Come, come.
Come.
Come on, people,
how hard can it be to find
a dozen untrained, unfocused children?
I've got something. It's weak.
It seems to be some type
of communicator.
Belonging to this kid
patched into our system.
Can we trace it?
[man] Hold on.
[computer whirs]
Got her.
-[computer beeps]
-[Granada] Hmm.
But we're children.
[grandma] Yes,
the children of the Heroics.
If anyone is gonna save the world,
it's you,
because all of you have superpowers.
Super lame powers.
Speak for yourself.
Okay, Johnny Random.
Hmm…
This is no way to be a super team.
[Missy] Abuelita's right.
Aliens are about to invade,
and if we want to rescue our parents
and save the planet,
we're gonna need to do it now.
Are you saying that…
we can be superheroes?
Well, yeah.
I guess that kinda is what I'm saying.
♪ We can be heroes ♪
-♪ Just for one day ♪
-[groaning]
Sorry, it was there for the taking.
I need you all
to maximize your powers.
Grandma, I've been trying to do that
my whole life,
so if you have any ideas, I'm all ears.
[kids giggling]
Um, it's not about
who is the strongest or fastest.
It's about working together,
and that's why we'll need someone
to be the leader.
That would be me.
I was actually talking about Missy,
but thank you.
Follow me!
Quickly. Quickly!
Fast. Fast!
[Wild Card] But I'm the leader!
[Missy] He's right.
I'm totally okay with that.
Well, I'm not.
And we don't have time to argue.
So, what I say goes.
-[Wild Card] Yes, ma'am.
-[grandma] Hmm.
Welcome to my training ground.
-[clunking]
-[grandma chuckles]
Let's boogie.
Stand together.
Feel the rhythm.
[winding back]
[whirring]
[Fast Forward grunts]
Cálmate, Guppy!
Calm down, dear.
[A Capella grunts]
[yells]
Whoa… oh! I can't do this!
Nope, not for me.
Yah!
[laughs]
Ah. Okay, nieta, your turn.
What? I'm not ready.
And that's how you become ready,
by doing it. Mwah!
Go!
I'm picking up a leap in the sound.
[Granada] What are they saying?
-Can you hear them?
-[guard] Yes, it sounds like…
[interference buzzes]
…they're rocking out.
What?
["Heroes" by Haley Reinhart playing]
♪ I ♪
♪ I wish I could swim… ♪
Okay, work together.
[winding back]
[winding forward]
-Stay in sync.
-♪ Though nothing ♪
♪ Will keep us together ♪
-♪ We can beat them… ♪
-Good.
♪ Forever and ever ♪
-♪ We can be heroes… ♪
-Whoa, whoa, whoa!
Wrong way!
You're going the wrong way!
-[Guppy growls]
-[Facemaker screams]
[whip cracking]
Guppy, stay calm!
[growling]
Guppy! You're in a shark frenzy!
Attacking even your friends.
Your powers are useless
if you don't stay calm and focused.
Go meditate.
♪ We can be heroes ♪
♪ Just for one day ♪
[slow groaning]
Someone catch Slo-Mo!
-Noodles! I mean, no, Facemaker!
-[twins] What?
Who? Make up your mind.
I got him!
-♪ We can be heroes… ♪
-Whoa. Whoa!
Listen to me!
♪ We can be heroes… ♪
Slo-Mo, you never do anything right.
[Slo-Mo groans]
♪ Just for one day ♪
[music ends]
I don't understand your problem.
-My problem?
-Yes. You wanna come up in my face.
What's your problem?
Talk to me. What is it?
-You don't know what you're doing.
-I don't know what I'm doing?
We do work in the same organization.
It'd be nice if you communicated.
Why don't you just vanish, Invisi-Girl?
Oh, I'll make you disappear.
Don't make me use
my outside voice on you two.
♪ Ha! Ha! ♪
If you'd fought the aliens like this,
we wouldn't be captured.
That's what I've been saying.
Why don't you cheer us up
by singing one of those little songs
you sing so well, Sharkboy.
Man, you got some fish to fry.
Hey, hey, hey. Calm down, Sharkboy.
He's just baiting you.
Please, stop fighting.
You're like children. Actually, worse.
Yeah, Miracle Guy, why not pretend
there's a camera on you?
There's not a camera on me,
and it's kind of liberating.
I can be my true self,
and my true self doesn't like you,
or you,
or you.
[smoldering]
What the heck is that?
It's a… camera.
I demand you release us,
whoever or whatever you are.
-Mr. President.
-Greetings, Heroics.
[clears throat] There's something
you should know, Mr. President.
I didn't vote for you.
The aliens didn't allow much time
for me to give you this message.
It's about your children.
They've disappeared from headquarters.
[gasping]
They'll be completely helpless without us.
That's good. Back in formation!
[chuckles]
Keep training.
[knuckles cracking]
[sighs] Now, now.
You didn't expect to get it
on the first try, did you?
I'm never gonna get it.
Not with a million tries.
You know why?
Because I'm useless.
Who told you that?
Everyone told me.
In those exact words.
I have trained all
of the greatest superheroes,
Miracle Guy, Sharkboy,
Tech-No, Lavagirl.
Do you know who the greatest superhero
of them all was?
It was your mother.
But my mother was normal, like me.
Exactly.
And without your mother,
your father never would have become
someone who leads by example.
And you will too.
I'm sure of it.
Mi amor, I'm sure of it.
[Wheels] Miss Moreno!
-What?
-Better come quick!
[grandma] Oh my…
[Missy] Oh no.
[helicopter blades whirring]
They sure found you fast.
They wanna take us back
to headquarters.
Well, too bad.
-We've got a world to save.
-[grandma] Hmm.
[whirring]
Go through this tunnel.
I'll hold them off.
Go, go, go, go. Go!
I wish you could come with us.
Hug me, as if it's for the last time.
Hey, it won't be.
I promise.
That's my girl.
Go, go, go, go. Go!
[Missy] Guys? Come on!
[Guppy] It sure is dark in here.
Ojo, can I use your flashlight?
We just have to stick…
together.
Yeah, and find a way
up to the mother ship,
and defeat the aliens
who defeated all the Heroics.
[twig snapping]
Oh my. [chuckles nervously]
Visitors.
Want some lemonade?
[rumbling]
No?
Fine. [grunts]
What could we do differently
from our parents?
Everything.
Like we lure the aliens out of the cities,
so that we don't destroy more buildings.
She's right.
Our parents always have huge brawls
in the middle
of the most populated cities.
Don't we need superhero costumes?
All superheroes have costumes.
Pads, fake muscles,
tons of useless buckles.
Underwear on the outside.
Masks you can barely see out of.
That's why they were able to pick out
our parents so easily.
Because they were easy to spot.
We have to blend in.
Be…
stealth.
How?
Just trust me.
I have a plan.
-Where? What plan?
-I'll show you.
The plan is we're gonna sneak on a bus?
-[whispers]
-Oh.
Holy… doo doo.
I mean, yes, very interesting.
-[whispers]
-Uh-huh.
Okay, makes sense. Yep.
Okay. Wow, that's really smart.
Okay, everyone, Missy and I
figured out a way for us to do this.
Check it out.
Ojo drew us a clue.
A supply ship.
So what does that mean?
It means there's probably one nearby
that we'll sneak on board
and pilot up to the mother ship.
That's actually a good idea
no matter who thought of it.
-Thank you.
-[Guppy groans]
Come on, it's time
we show these aliens what's what.
[Wild Card] Hurry up, Slo-Mo!
[Missy] Look, there's the supply ship.
Just like Ojo's drawing!
[kids] Ew. Gross!
Shh. Keep it down!
Wait.
Wait a second.
Let's go.
Shut the door and let's get out of here.
-Wheels, can you--
-No! We're not all here!
What? Who's missing?
Oh… [sighs]
Slo-Mo! Cut it out! Run!
[snarling]
Hurry! They're coming back!
-Ten to one says he's tentacled.
-Dude!
-[Rewind] Come on, Slo-Mo!
-[kids shout encouragement]
[vocalizes "Chariots of Fire"]
[growling, snarling]
All right, hold me down!
Slo-Mo!
Yes!
[screaming]
Wheels, tell me you figured this out!
It's incredibly intuitive.
Whoa!
[screaming]
-Please just choose any button!
-It might be one of these.
[screaming]
[engine starts]
But now what?
Don't worry.
Any minute now, Ojo's gonna draw
a picture of all of us smiling
and hugging our parents.
Isn't that right, Ojo?
Oh, that's just great.
Hey…
why did you choose me to share
the idea of looking at Ojo's iPad?
I don't know.
I guess I know how hard it feels
when everyone expects so much from you,
and you feel like you can't deliver.
Do you believe I can?
We all believe you can.
Tell that to my parents.
I will,
right after we rescue them.
I'm gonna go check it out.
We're all good.
Am I just really small,
or is this ship really big?
-It's enormous.
-Yeah. How are we gonna find our parents?
I was thinking about that.
Mrs. Granada found us really easily
back at Grandma's house,
and I think I know how,
your bracelet.
I haven't been able to contact my dad.
But maybe the transmitter in here
that connects the two bracelets
works like a tracking device.
But I need a pair of pliers
and a heat source.
My teeth are strong
because my dad's a shark.
-Perfect.
-And I've got a heat source.
Heat vision!
Now he's a toaster.
Close enough.
[bracelet beeping]
Is it working?
Well, it's leading us somewhere.
[bracelet continues beeping]
Hey! That was really good back there.
Turning into a toaster
instead of making heat vision?
It was heat-related. That's real progress.
I guess it's progress.
You just watch.
Pretty soon, you'll be teleporting
like it's nobody's business.
It's about belief.
Um, guys…
[rumbling]
Does anybody else hear that?
What is that?
It's below us.
I can feel it.
[rattling]
[revving]
[Wild Card] Uh!
[screaming]
[chittering]
[Facemaker] Which way?
That way!
-[snarling]
-[screaming]
[vocalizes]
Look at that thing.
[door opening]
What the heck
is the president doing here?
So they're inside this thing?
All of them?
-[man] That's correct.
-How long before the takeover begins?
According to the supreme commander,
less than an hour.
[president] So soon?
[man] That's what she says,
and she's never wrong.
You don't have to remind me.
Ever wonder why we bother with all this
when she already knows
how it's gonna turn out?
All part of the process, I suppose.
What is that thing?
You heard him. It's a rocket
stuffed to the gills with aliens.
In less than an hour, they'll send it
down to Earth and start the takeover.
Well, then we have to stop them. Let's go.
Do you children have any idea
what you've done?
Stealing one of our trains?
Turning headquarters upside down?
Flying an alien shuttle
into outer space. Hmm?
[squeals] Well done!
Looks like
we underestimated your abilities
and your leadership qualities.
You took a huge risk,
but it was the right risk.
Headquarters was attacked
just minutes after you escaped.
If you hadn't broken out,
you would have all been captured.
And now you've managed to lead us
into the heart of this alien mother ship?
[gasps] Mm.
So proud!
Wait, so we're not in trouble?
Of course not.
You are heroes.
-Yeah!
-[cheering]
Yes! [chuckles]
[Wheels] Missy!
Her vital signs are all over the place.
Save your breath, Granada.
They know.
Uh-oh!
[slithering sound]
Hmm…
Well, then… round them up!
[kids grunt]
[chittering]
[Facemaker] Watch it!
[grunts]
Quit the pantomime, Slo-Mo.
-You didn't even scrape a knee.
-Mm-hmm.
[Granada] Oh, good.
Just the kind of divisive attitude
I've been counting on.
You kids are just like your parents.
The same in-fighting.
The same bickering.
Putting your own egos ahead of your team.
-Take away her water.
-[gasps]
[gasps]
They're too powerful together.
Oh, don't worry.
I won't take away your little toy.
I already know what your future is.
Imprisonment.
Life long.
Hmm.
[chuckles]
[beeping]
[clunking]
How are we getting out of here?
I…
don't know.
[sighs]
What do you mean you don't know?
I mean…
[sighs] I don't know.
I'm thinking. I'm thinking.
Enough thinking.
I'm gonna punch my way out of here.
I have to save my son.
[grunting]
That's not gonna work.
How do you know?
While you were blinking your eyes,
I went around and tried everything.
[mocks]
Uh, you were saying?
[snarling]
What are you? An alien spy?
I wouldn't do that if I were you.
I just want to see what it is.
Don't worry.
It won't even know I touched it.
[snarls]
[grunts]
[hisses]
[snarls]
A-ha!
Anita Moreno?
Hmm!
Hi, Mom.
No, no, no, don't "Hi, Mom" me.
-[exhales sharply]
-That was pathetic.
You stop training for a year
and look what happens. Eh?
You… dropped your guard.
And you…
attacked when you should have blocked.
And you rushed
when you should've calculated. Eh?
I hope your kids
paid more attention to me than you did.
Thanks, Mom.
I bet Miss Granada's
been working there for years.
They must have hacked the elections
and put their own alien in as president
so they could set a trap for the Heroics.
I'm such an idiot.
President Neil Anami.
Spell Neil Anami backwards and you have…
"I'm an alien."
Everyone thinks that the aliens
only invaded this morning,
but they've been here for years,
planning this takeover the whole time.
And now we're locked in this stupid cell
with no way out.
You're welcome.
Any luck?
[grunting]
[groans]
I need water.
Without water, I can't use my powers.
I need food. My stomach hurts.
-My arm hurts.
-My ears hurt!
We never should have come.
You led us here.
You think I wanted to get locked up
in an alien ship?
It was all of us.
We did it together.
I wanna go home.
[Twins in unison] Me too!
We all want to go home.
The key is figuring out
how to get out of this room
so we can make sure
there's a home to go back to.
Wait a second.
What did you just say?
-He said we all want to go home.
-Not that, the second part.
"Figure out how to get out of this room
so we can make sure
there's a home to go back to"?
Stop saying that.
Keep it together.
Guys…
maybe it's time to admit
we're never getting out of here.
-What?
-I mean, let's get real.
These walls and this door
must be, like, two-feet thick.
It's totally impossible.
-Wow, great attitude.
-[Missy] Yep.
We're never getting out of here,
and we're certainly never seeing
our parents again, that's for sure.
She's right. Pretty soon
we'll forget what they even look like.
The way they smelled…
It'll all just be…
gone.
Jeez, you guys are really bumming me out.
But I guess…
this really is the end.
-But I'm not ready for the end.
-[sniffles]
I was just starting to think…
maybe my sister didn't hate me.
I don't hate you.
[both] I love you.
That love we feel…
is real.
And…
it's that love…
that'll get us out of here.
Why are guys saying all this stuff?
It's almost like you want everyone to cry…
Oh!
Guppy, quick, gather all the tears.
What are you making?
I'm making a key.
Little Miss Guppy,
you just saved us.
[lock opens]
[Missy] Come on, let's go!
[clunking]
[sighs]
How long has it been this bad?
-You should've come to me.
-You?
-Yup.
-Hmm!
Don't you remember what your generation
was like when we took over?
-Good point.
-Mm-hmm.
Well, I guess it's up to the kids.
The next generation is always more…
powerful, more…
Evolved?
I got it!
What? You figure a way out of here?
Oh… no. I figured out how to switch on
these security monitors.
Surprisingly intuitive.
What?
At least now we can watch something
instead of sitting around
yelling at each other.
Wait, what's this?
A Capella?
-Rewind?
-Fast Forward?
Are those our children?
Wheels, how much time do we have?
Eighteen minutes.
Then we need to hurry
if we want to stop the takeover.
Us? Are you nuts?
We have to go free our parents
and let them handle it.
No! There's no time for that!
By the time we get there, they--
No! I'm through listening to you.
When I woke up,
everything was perfect,
then you come along
and everything's a mess.
If Little Miss No-Powers
is who you want as a leader,
fine, follow her straight into Alienville.
But Facemaker and I
are gonna go get our parents.
-We are?
-Yes. Right now.
Guys, we have to stick together.
Guys!
What can you do?
-Some people are just--
-[Wheels] Forget him.
We need to get to the rocket
so I can stop it before it launches.
How are you so sure you can do that?
Because everything the aliens build
is super intuitive to use,
almost like it was designed
for children to operate.
Get me close. I'll turn it off.
I don't understand. Why did we split up?
Where are we going?
-How do you know our parents are this way?
-Okay, this is good.
-What do you mean, "This is good"?
-Are you questioning my authority?
Uh… I don't even know
what we're talking about.
Really? The confused thing?
That's what you're going with?
[Granada] Just as I suspected.
Falling apart at the seams.
Hmm…
We need to get that one.
He has so little control over his powers,
he's liable to blow us all up by accident.
Let's go.
That's it there!
♪ We're gonna make it after all ♪
[tires screech]
Uh… no, we're not.
-[panting]
-[door opens]
Uh… guys?
What do we do now?
Missy?
Why are you so calm?
Because we have something
they don't know about, a secret weapon.
-We do?
-Yeah.
Teamwork!
Alone, our powers are special,
but together we're unstoppable!
Slo-Mo, attack!
A Capella, eardrums!
-[vocalizes]
-[groaning]
Rewind, take them down!
[knuckles cracking]
[grunting]
Guppy? Guppy?
[grunts, groans]
Guppy? Guppy, what are you doing?
-Staying calm.
-Well, not now!
[guard groans]
[grunting]
-[vocalizes]
-[groans]
Guppy, listen to me.
[grunting]
[yelling]
Shark frenzy.
[growls]
Everyone stand back!
[Guppy growls]
[Rewind] Whoa!
-[snarls]
-[panicked screaming]
[roars]
[growls]
[beeping]
Noodles, chin-up bar!
[gasps]
Go.
[tires screech]
He's a miracle.
[Missy] Great job, Wheels!
-[vocalizes]
-[screeches]
Go, A Capella!
[vocalizes]
[yells]
Ew!
[Missy gasps]
-[chains rattle]
-[gasps]
Focus on super strength!
Ugh… [sighs]
[groans]
Focus on teleportation.
[grunts, groans]
Hmm… Nice try, kid.
-Take him to interrogation.
-[gasps]
[groans]
Rewind!
I can't.
-We can do this.
-How?
We work together.
I'll help you.
[whirring]
[winding back]
Noodles, get those shackles
out of the ceiling!
[shackles clink]
-Now fast forward, quick!
-[whirring]
[winding forward]
[giggling]
-[grunting]
-[giggling]
-[keys jangle]
-Uh-oh…
[ominous music plays]
Again!
[winding back]
Looking for these?
[groans]
[chuckles]
Great job, Fast Forward.
Excellent work, Rewind.
-[winding back]
-Excellent work, Rewind.
I just like hearing her say it.
-[winding back]
-Excellent work, Rewind.
Excellent work, Rewind.
Did you see their teamwork?
Just like their parents.
[chuckling]
Okay, Wild Card, spill it.
What's the big plan, hmm?
Well, the plan was
to get me close enough to you
to turn you into the dumbest alien
that ever existed.
No way! My powers finally worked.
[laughs]
Keep laughing
and I'll blast you right back to Ogima.
We have ways of getting
the truth out of you, you know.
That'd be a first.
-Ha!
-[snickering]
We only have six minutes left!
Not a problem. Not a problem.
All I have to do is
reprogram the rocket's main contr--
What is that?
Maybe it's a…
A force field?
No, no, no, we were so close!
But there's no one here but us.
Who did this?
[Ojo] I did.
Ojo, did you just talk?
I could always talk.
I simply chose to observe
and listen instead.
And what I heard was chaos,
dysfunction,
disharmony…
just like your parents.
But that's not true.
We were working together.
Were you?
Then where's Wild Card?
That's a good question.
Hey, Wild Card, old buddy.
Are you in the ship's control room yet?
[Wild Card] I sure am.
Just like we planned, old buddy.
Ignore him.
That's some kind of trick.
I have Wild Card right here.
Don't I?
-[squelching]
-[gasps]
Boo!
[screeches]
Wow. I gave this plan
50-to-1 odds at best,
but you fell for it
hook, line, and sinker.
We got the one
with the useless superpower?
Got you far away
from the control center, didn't it?
Go to the control center, now!
Go, go. Go! Go!
[groans loudly]
[chuckles]
[laughs]
You were working together?
Surprise!
I even sent him on a secret mission.
Isn't that right, Wild Card?
Yep!
And when the team leader tells you
to do something, you hop to it.
Since when did you accept Missy
as the leader?
Since the tunnel…
when she told me you
were an alien spy.
[in unison] Ojo's an alien spy?
Yep. Ojo's a spy.
You knew.
How'd you figure it out?
You accidentally gave it away
in one of your own drawings.
Your art never lies.
-[whispers] She's an alien spy.
-Holy… doo doo.
You work for Granada, don't you?
Or does Granada work for you?
They all work for me.
What the…
Ojo's an alien!
[all in unison] We know!
[Wild Card] And now you can be impressed…
[beeps]
…and defeated…
as soon as I figure out which
button removes the shield.
Knowing the aliens, it's probably a big
button with a picture of a shield on it.
Oh!
[kids cheer]
I hate to spoil your celebration…
but there's two minutes left.
[timer beeping]
Game's not over yet.
[snarling]
[chittering]
[screeching]
[roars]
Uh-oh!
[snarling]
We'll hold it off.
You find a way to stop the launch.
[Wheels] Um…
It's not an it. It's a them!
[roaring]
Then you better hurry!
Come on, everyone.
Time to show these guys
what we're made of.
[snarling, roaring]
Come on in. It's broken.
I mean it's open.
[Missy] Wild Card,
you have to keep those shields down.
Don't worry, Missy.
I'm on it.
Oh yeah?
What are you gonna do, hmm?
Turn into a bowling ball?
Sure…
if that's what I want.
I can control my powers now.
Working with Missy helped me realize
I was so busy
trying to prove everyone else wrong
when I should have been concentrating
on proving myself right.
She believed in me.
Now I believe in myself.
Oh, right.
And you think that's enough.
[mockingly] Believing in yourself.
You tell me.
Let's do this.
Hmm.
Let's take him.
Everyone spread out!
Slo-Mo, attack!
Guppy, waterslide!
Hey, only speed up Slo-Mo.
How?
I'll help you.
Together.
[winding]
[monster groans]
[punches landing]
Oh!
Did you see that? Did anyone see that?
It was too fast…
for even me to see.
Wow! Whoo.
Attack!
Flight.
[gasps]
Shape-shift!
[pained squealing]
Electricity fingers.
[guard groans]
[sighs]
-And my personal fave…
-[gasps]
The freeze ray.
[whimpers]
[grunts]
-[beat-driven pop music playing]
-I'm running out of water!
This is too much stress.
I can't take it.
Come on, Missy.
You got this. I know you do.
Guppy, make ninja stars.
Noodles, slingshot!
Hold my leg!
Somebody pull Noodles!
[music continues]
[snarling]
[squealing]
I'm out. I need water.
Hey, Guppy.
This whole thing is covered
in liquid metal. Liquid!
Oh!
[gasps, giggles]
[shark growls]
[music grows more dramatic]
[whooping]
Go, Guppy, go!
[Guppy] Go! Yes!
Not so fast.
[snarling]
[growling]
Noodles, make a tightrope.
Somebody go on to the center
and draw them in.
No, wait!
I have to do this.
I can do this.
[wind blows]
[monsters snarling]
[vocalizes]
♪ I ♪
♪ I will be king ♪
♪ And you ♪
♪ You will be queen ♪
♪ And nothing ♪
♪ No, nothing could tear us apart… ♪
She's leading by example.
[Mrs. Vox and A Capella sing]
♪ Oh, we can be heroes ♪
♪ Just for one day ♪
♪ We can be heroes ♪
♪ Oh, and we can beat them ♪
♪ Forever and ever ♪
♪ Then we can be heroes ♪
♪ Just for one day ♪
Hey! Did you see that?
Did you see what my son just did?
Unfortunately, I was too busy looking
at my own cool kid.
-How's it going, Wheels?
-[Wheels] Great.
All we have to do is swap out
the ignition chamber's motherboard
with one that'll tell the device
it launched even when it didn't.
-That way we fooled it--
-Tell us how long.
-Oh, now long.
-[beeps]
Now put it into
the ignition chamber up there.
[Missy] Oh no.
Noodles!
I can't reach!
It's too high to jump.
Nobody would ever survive that fall.
[slowly] I… can.
Slo-Mo?
Slo-Mo!
Rewind, stop him. Reverse it!
Hold on.
I think he knows what he's doing.
[timer beeping]
We're running out of seconds.
[cheering]
He did it.
Did you see that?
[kids cheer]
Uh, guys, how are we gonna
get him back up here?
Wild Card?
We need you. Right now!
On my way.
-Stay cool.
-[growls]
Dude! You actually teleported!
Get down there, quick!
-Yes!
-Yeah!
Now swap the motherboards up there!
[alarm blaring]
[gasping]
[whimpering]
What's happening?
The takeover is happening.
[heroic music playing]
Wait. So our parents were
in the pyramid all along?
[sighs] But I don't understand.
What's the takeover?
The takeover of power…
from your parents.
You see, the next generation is always
an improvement from the last.
Things are not heading
in the right direction on your planet.
And you children
are inheriting Earth's problems,
and need to be able to fix them,
sooner rather than later.
[president] It's in the best interest
of the entire galaxy that life
on Earth survives and thrives.
So, we infiltrated both your government
and Heroics headquarters
so we could train you
and accelerate the transfer of power.
[Ojo] As you've seen from today's events,
it's not enough to be strong,
powerful,
or even magic.
If you do not use your strengths together
and with good judgment…
[coughs pointedly]
…you are doomed.
But I don't understand.
The clock hit zero.
We were one second too late.
The supreme commander knew
down to the second
exactly when the takeover would happen.
[Ojo] Your guess was close, Wheels,
but not quite right.
Everything on the ship
wasn't designed for children.
Oh, it was designed by children.
-That's correct.
-[Granada chuckles]
On our planet,
the children are in charge.
So, you're their leader?
Yes.
Just as I knew
you would be a natural leader.
It's why I drew you
at the front of the class.
So, from one leader to another,
as we each head off
to face the challenges of the universe,
can we count on you
to not just help save your planet…
but the entire galaxy?
You have our word.
When you need us…
we'll be there.
Thank you.
[whirring]
[inaudible]
I love you. Oh! [chuckles]
[gasps]
-[Sharkboy growls]
-[Guppy giggles]
[Guppy giggles]
How do you feel, son?
Strong…
you know, like, really strong.
You're stronger than I'll ever be.
[Miracle Guy sighs]
Proud of you.
[both sing]
♪ I'm so very proud of you ♪
[heavy footsteps thud]
Put it there, buddy.
[exhales slowly]
What the…
[chuckling] You're so fast.
[exhales slowly]
I love you.
I love you, too, buddy.
I love you too.
You're so wonderful together.
I am so proud of you.
You two make such a great team.
-[winding back, repeats]
-[repeats] You two make such a great team.
[Fast Forward chuckles]
Oh yeah! Come on.
-Hey, Dad! Hey, Grandma!
-Hey.
Hey!
-[Marcus] Someone's made a few friends.
-I tell you, Marcus, natural-born leader.
I should get captured more often.
Nope. Not without me, you're not.
If you ever go on any other missions,
I'm gonna be there right by your side.
Deal?
A deal is…
a deal.
-[Missy chuckles] I missed you.
-[grandma chuckles]
[Granada squeals]
[Missy] This was the day our heroes fell,
but others did rise.
As for the aliens, they'll be back,
and when they call on us for help,
we will be prepared.
We will be ready.
[heroic music plays]
So what are we supposed to be looking at?
The future.
[upbeat music plays]