Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org
Mutants...
born with extraordinary abilities...
and yet, still, they are children
stumbling in the dark...
searching for guidance.
A gift can often be a curse.
Give someone wings,
and they may fly too close to the sun.
Give them the power of prophecy...
and they may live in fear of the future.
Give them the greatest gifts of all...
powers beyond imagination...
and they may think they're meant
to rule the world.
En Sabah Nur.
Now you will rule for eternity, my lord.
Sleep.
Let the transference begin.
Death to the false god.
Protect him!
As everyone knows, the existence
of mutants was first discovered...
during the Paris Peace Accords,
after the Vietnam War in 1973.
Six days later, we all watched
as one of those mutants...
Erik Lehnsherr, attacked the President...
and the Cabinet on the lawn
of the White House.
Their lives were saved
by a young mutant who stopped him.
Now, Lehnsherr escaped and became
the world's most-wanted fugitive.
And as for her, she disappeared as well.
But she has become the symbol
of a new age...
the face of a world
that will never be the same again.
You winking at my girl?
Your girl?
I guess you do look old enough
to be her father.
Excuse me, gentlemen...
is there something you'd like
to share with the rest of the class?
Can I please go to the bathroom?
I think there's something
seriously wrong with my eyes.
Fine, Scott. And afterwards...
why don't you stop by the principal's
office and explain to him...
that you're disrupting class again?
I trust you know the way.
- Yeah, I do.
- Okay.
No, hang on! Hang on!
Hey!
Now, I know most of you were, what?
Around seven years old at that time?
Summers!
I know you're in here.
What, are you crying?
I haven't even kicked your ass yet.
Summers! You want to eyeball my girl?
Yeah!
Ten fights waged.
Ten fights won.
The Winged Warrior.
The Bird of Prey.
The Angel of Death.
ANGEL!
Yeah!
Let's hear it for the fat man!
Our next challenger...
comes straight...
from the Munich Circus.
Ladies and gentlemen,
the only one that could take on an Angel...
is the Devil himself.
I give you...
the amazing...
the fantastic...
NIGHTCRAWLER!
Caution
High voltage!
Sorry mutants!
Hey.
Did you get lost little mouse?
The fight is over there.
Fight!
Or they'll kill us both!
And it's about to get exciting.
Ah, you mean this?
Nightcrawler!
Nightcrawler! Nightcrawler!
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry!
They went that way!
You can...
transform.
You're her.
- The hero.
- I'm nobody.
I'm not a hero.
Let's get out of here.
Have a good night, Henryk.
You too, Milosz.
Hi, Honey.
Hi.
Good day?
Better now.
Where's Nina?
Out back. With her friends.
Where did you learn that song, Papa?
I learned it from my parents.
And they learned it from their parents.
And them from theirs.
And one day...
you'll sing it to your children, too.
What happened to them?
Your parents.
They were taken from me...
when I was a little boy.
But they're still here.
Inside.
And here.
With you.
Is someone going to take you away?
Never.
I guess we're more alike than we thought.
He won't listen to us.
He's just... He's being...
Scott.
Let me try.
Smells pretty old in here.
Is this a school or a museum?
One more. And last one.
There you go.
I'll see you guys.
Watch where you're going.
I can't.
Who are you talking to?
Me.
I just heard you in my head.
I'm telepathic. I read minds.
Well, stay out of mine.
I don't need some weird girl
creeping around in there.
Don't worry, Scott.
There's not much to see.
Hey, wait. I didn't tell you my name.
No, you didn't.
Alex Summers?
Hank McCoy!
Whoa! What happened to the
big, blue, furry you?
I keep him under control now.
This is my brother, Scott.
Hey, Scott. I'm Hank McCoy.
I'm one of the teachers here.
Where's the professor?
"To break forth bloodily,
then the past must be obliterated...
"and a new start made.
"Let us now start fresh...
"without remembrance...
"rather than live forward and backward
at the same time."
Now, what on earth do we think
that the author meant...
when he wrote all that?
That's going to be
your assignment for tomorrow.
Top marks, everyone. Class dismissed.
Alex.
- It's good to see you.
- You too.
You look well. It's been a while.
It has. Not too bad yourself.
Thank you.
This is my brother, Scott.
Hello, Scott.
Welcome to the School for the Gifted.
Yeah. It doesn't exactly feel like a gift.
It never does, at first.
The first step in
understanding one's power...
is learning the extent of it.
Only then can we begin the process
of teaching you how to control it.
If you do decide to stay,
I can promise you...
that by the time you're done here,
you'll be able to go back into the world...
and play a stable and productive part in it.
Why don't you take your bandages off...
and we can have a look
at what we're dealing with here?
Alex, would you line him up?
Face him in the right direction, as it were.
There's a target just across the water.
When you open your eyes, try and hit that.
You can open your eyes, Scott.
There's nothing to be afraid of.
It's quite...
Look out! Get back!
Get back! Get back!
My grandfather planted that tree
when he was five years old.
I used to swing...
from the branches of it, myself.
I think that was probably
my favorite tree.
Does that mean I'm expelled?
On the contrary.
You're enrolled.
Do you sell rugs?
You're not allowed in this area.
This rug is for sale?
I said, this...
Earthquake!
Back to bed, please, my darling.
Back to bed.
She's doing it again.
Back to bed, please, everyone.
Jesse, back to bed, please.
Come on now. Spit-spot, back to bed.
Carrie Anne, come on now. Back to bed.
Never seen it like this.
Nor I.
Don't let any of the children
come this way.
Jean.
Jean!
I saw the end of the world.
I could feel...
all this death.
It was just a dream.
No, it felt real.
I know.
Your mind is the most powerful
I've ever seen.
It can convince itself...
No, no...
It's not just the mind-reading
or the telekinesis...
it's something else.
Some dark power inside and it's growing.
Like a fire.
I thought I was getting better.
You are.
You will.
You just have to be patient.
No, no. You don't know what it's like
to be afraid to shut your eyes.
To be trapped inside your own head.
Oh, I think I do.
It wasn't so long ago that
I was plagued by voices, myself.
All their suffering.
All their pain.
Their secrets.
I'm afraid one day
I'm going to hurt someone.
Lie back.
Everyone fears that
which they do not understand.
You will learn to control your powers.
And when you do...
you'll have nothing to fear.
Her nightmares were different this time.
It could account for something I saw
when I was in my lab earlier.
There was some kind of tremor.
Like an energy surge.
I picked it up on one of my meters.
You're saying Jean created it?
No. I'm saying something else did.
Maybe she was reacting to it.
I don't know.
But the epicenter was
halfway around the world.
Halfway around the world?
That's why I was hoping you could
take a look.
Let's see what we can find.
Welcome, Professor.
Okay, the source came from Cairo.
I'll put in the coordinates.
I gotta get out of here.
Give them a report.
What? What is it?
Something happened here.
I can tell them it's real.
It's her.
Who?
- Moira.
- What?
Moira MacTaggert?
Give me the details.
She looks amazing.
She's barely aged a day.
No. I meant...
What is she doing there?
What does the CIA want with this?
She's going back to Langley
to deliver a report.
I'm going to go there...
see if she knows something
about the tremor.
And you want to go see Moira.
I want to go check her out. Check out...
the situation.
Moira MacTaggert.
It's like a ghost from the past.
You did a good thing. You saved that man.
That's not the point.
If I'm exposed, we're all exposed.
We have to go.
This is our home.
This is our daughter's home.
We are her home.
I told you who I was,
the first night I met you.
I trusted you then.
I need you to trust me now.
We can't stay here anymore.
I'll get Nina.
Sweetheart.
She's not in her room.
And I don't see her out back.
Nina?
Nina!
Nina.
Are you alright?
She's fine.
Then let her go!
We will.
We just wanted to have a word
You're not wearing your badges.
No metal.
Some guys at the factory said
they saw something today.
Something that didn't add up.
Put your weapons away.
You've been a good citizen, Henryk...
A good neighbor... a good worker.
I want to believe that's who you are.
It is.
But nobody in this town really knows you.
Yes you do.
I am Henryk Gurzsky.
Jakob, I've had dinner in your home...
And you were lying the whole time.
I brought a killer into my house.
Is this you?
Are you the one they call Magneto?
Take me in.
Please...
Just let my daughter go.
Go with your mother.
Please...
Don't leave me.
I'm not going to let them take you.
Nina.
What's going on?
She's one of them?
Tell her to stop!
She can't control it!
She's scared of you!
I'm not going to let them take you!
Make her stop!
Nina! Nina!
Nina.
Nina, Nina, no...
No, please. Please!
Please.
Not my babies.
Is this what you want from me?
Is this what I am?
You know what we do to thieves.
Pick a hand.
Enough.
If you're with her, I suggest you walk away.
While you still can.
Walk away
Who rules this world?
What language is that?
Clown-face. What's the deal?
Beat it!
I'm sorry.
You can't feel it, can you?
Now you feel it.
So you really haven't seen her
in all these years?
You never looked her up?
Not even in Cerebro?
Alex! What do you take me for,
some kind of pervert?
Yes, I looked her up once. Twice.
But not in a long time, all right?
How did you leave things?
Any hard feelings?
Not likely.
Everybody take a break.
I wiped her mind of all memories of us.
The beach, Cuba...
that whole time.
It was so long ago, Alex.
Before the world knew about mutants.
I felt it was the best thing for her.
And for you?
Didn't really matter what was best for me.
Moira...
MacTaggert, hello!
Allow me to introduce myself.
- I'm Professor...
- Charles Xavier.
- I know exactly who you are.
- You do?
Of course I do.
I have read all of your papers.
It's a pleasure to finally meet you.
Moira MacTaggert.
- Alex Summers.
- Have a seat.
Just throw that on the floor.
It's wonderful to see you again.
To meet you again, for the first time.
You've got a son?
Yes.
Does he have a husband?
Do you have a husband?
I had a husband...
but it's hard to do this job
and make it home in time for dinner.
Good, good.
We all make choices, right?
Yes, we do.
- Professor.
- Yes?
Yes.
I was, we were hoping that you would...
tell us about what happened
yesterday in Egypt.
I'm afraid that's classified information.
I don't mean to be rude...
but how did you get in here?
I have level-five clearance.
Ever since the world found out
about mutants in '73...
there have been cults
who see them as some kind of...
Second Coming or sign of God.
I was tracking one of them.
They call themselves Ashir En Sabah Nur...
named after an ancient being
they believe to be the world's first.
The world's first what?
The world's first mutant.
I thought mutants didn't evolve
until this century.
That's the common theory, yes,
but these guys believe...
that the first mutant was born
tens of thousands of years ago.
And they believe he will rise again.
They've been searching ancient sites
all around the world for clues.
These hieroglyphs...
describe a specific set of powers
greater than any man could possess.
They think he lived all that time?
Yes and no.
They believe he had the ability...
to transfer his consciousness
from body to body.
And whenever he was close to death...
he would just take on a new body.
Some of these may have been
the bodies of mutants...
enabling him to take their powers...
amassing various abilities over the years.
- An all-powerful mutant.
- Exactly.
And wherever this being was
he always had four...
principle followers. Disciples.
Protectors he would imbue with powers.
Like the Four Horsemen...
of the Apocalypse.
He got that one from the Bible.
Or the Bible got it from him.
And wherever he ruled...
eventually, it would end in disaster.
Cataclysm.
Some kind of...
Apocalypse
The end of the world.
I must say, Apollo...
the way you ape human behavior
is remarkable.
I am Apollo.
I've never seen another
mutant in this town.
You speak Egyptian?
Arabic?
English?
I'm a scientist.
My particular specialty...
Great fighter.
She's my hero.
I want to be like her.
There's some food here. Not much.
I don't believe it.
You love me.
Love you?
Illogical.
I'm not some simple shepherdess
you can awe.
Why, I could no more love you...
than I could love a new species
of bacteria.
What are you doing?
Learning.
In the streets, there is outrage against
the Soviet invasion of Afghanistan...
...in a brotherhood of our kind.
Several demonstrations.
One of them was held in Boston,
and Bruce Morton has the story.
Since the advent of nuclear weapons,
the United States does not start fights.
Weapons.
Never before has man
possessed so much power.
Soviet Union and United States
being superpowers...
Superpowers.
The weak...
have taken the earth.
For this, I was betrayed.
False gods.
Idols.
No more.
I have returned.
A new tomorrow...
that starts today.
Where did you come from?
A time before man lost his way.
Welcome to the '80s.
This world needs to be...
Cleansed.
What?
Saved.
You can't save the world...
just going around killing people.
There's laws, systems in place...
for that kind of thing.
My child...
why do you enslave yourself?
What are you doing?
Making you stronger.
My goddess.
Aphrodite.
You were right.
Yes.
The time is past.
There is no room for gods.
Why can't I go with you?
I told you, I work alone.
Wait there.
Always good to see your face.
Even if it's not yours.
Papers and passage for one.
Where's the gentleman going, if I may ask?
Don't know, don't care.
I just save his life.
What he does with it is up to him.
Mystique, the mercenary.
Don't call me that.
No matter how much you pretend
to be someone else...
Caliban knows who you are.
If there's anything worth knowing
about mutants...
Caliban knows it.
Mystique.
Why don't you ask your psychics what'll
happen to you if you keep pushing me?
What'll happen?
Psylocke gets a little jealous.
But Caliban likes you.
Caliban likes money.
Caliban likes you so much...
he wants to give you free information...
about an old friend...
from back when you had friends.
Do you remember...
Erik Lehnsherr?
My girls got a flash of him in Poland.
He left quite a few dead bodies
in his wake...
including his wife and daughter.
Should be in the news soon enough
but Caliban gives you a little head start.
- How fast are you?
- How fast?
How far can you cover?
As far as I can see
or if I've been there before.
Come with me, Crawler.
Actually, it's Nightcrawler.
And my real name is...
Kurt Wagner.
The lenses are made of
some ruby quartz I had lying around.
They should be able to
refract your optic beams...
and keep them contained
within their own vector fields.
Try them on.
Okay.
Go ahead.
Wait, sorry, no.
Okay.
- Now?
- Yeah, you're good.
All right.
Whoa.
I can see.
Thank you.
Professor, thank you. You're a genius.
No.
I'm not a professor. I wish...
Who's that?
I believe you two met. That's Jean Grey.
You bumped into her when you arrived.
- Wait, that's her?
- Yeah.
Hey.
You can see.
Yeah. It's not as bad as I thought here.
Freak.
- Someone should warn the new kid.
- Yeah. Someone should tell him.
They're still scared of me.
Hey, I have special glasses now.
They're not scared of you.
They're scared of me.
You're not the only one who
can't fully control your powers.
Wait, so...
last night, when the house shook...
that was you?
Sorry to break it to you, but you're not
the biggest freak in the school.
Well, that's a first.
Raven.
Wow.
I... You're...
Not blue?
Looks like you and I
have that in common, now.
No, no, I meant...
you're back.
Never thought I'd see you here again.
Yeah, me neither.
I'm blue.
I'm Kurt.
Oh, right.
Kurt Wagner.
Welcome.
We're closed.
I knew I felt a chill in the air.
How did you get in here?
We let ourselves in.
We are looking for mutants.
Since you know where to find them,
we came here.
Caliban doesn't know you.
We're looking for the strongest.
Everything all right?
I'm fine, Psylocke.
How much money do you have?
None.
Like Caliban said...
we are closed. Yeah?
I need your help, my child.
You don't look like Caliban's father.
Maybe a little bit up here.
You are all my children...
and you're lost, because you follow
blind leaders.
These false gods...
systems of the weak.
They've ruined my world...
No more.
What do you want?
I want you...
to feel the full reach of your power.
You've only had a taste
of your true strength.
Unlike others...
who seek to control you...
I want to set you free.
I know the kind of mutants
you're looking for.
And I know where to find them.
It's my first time in America.
I'm very excited to see your culture.
Well, you're not gonna see it here.
The only thing American about this place
is that it used to be British.
This is Scott.
He's new here, too.
And I'm already up for a prison break.
What do we say, we take this blue guy
on a little field trip?
I'm sure there's a
mall around here, somewhere.
What's a mall?
All right, now this is a matter of
national pride. Civic duty.
Scott.
What? You've been cooped up here
for a long time...
and the Professor's not even home.
I'd like to go to the mall.
Try it.
All right.
Where does he keep his cars?
Or should I say "piss off"?
This is the guy?
He used to be.
I didn't know his wings were...
Let's get out of here.
His fighting days are done.
No, they're not.
What the hell is this?
I want to give you something.
There's nothing you can give me
that I want.
Yes, there is.
Yes, my son.
Yes.
Rise, my angel.
Rise.
Wow.
Hypersonic, blast resistant,
stealth technology.
That's impressive.
How are you ever gonna get it out of here?
Well, that's okay.
I built a retractable roof
into the basketball court.
Hank, you're building a warplane
down here.
After what happened in Washington,
I thought we were going to come back...
and start the X-Men,
like we all used to talk about.
But...
Charles wants students, not soldiers.
And he thinks the best of people.
He has hope.
And you?
You know, I think we should
hope for the best.
And prepare for the worst.
I think the world needs the X-Men.
And maybe now that you're back,
you could help me convince him.
We could start it together.
Hank, I'm here about Erik.
Right. Erik.
Yeah. Of course.
Of course.
I think he might be
in some kind of trouble.
Real trouble.
Isn't he always?
Some of you spoke to the police...
about what you believe
you witnessed here yesterday.
You want to know my powers...
know who I am...
see what I can do?
I'll show you.
Think of the person you love most
in your life.
Your wife.
Mother.
Daughter.
Now that person will know what it is
to lose someone they love.
And live with that pain.
Forever.
Henryk, please.
Don't do this.
My name isn't Henryk.
My name is Magneto.
Who the fuck are you?
Stay back.
Whoever you are...
don't try to stop me
from killing these men.
I'm not here for them.
I'm here for you.
Come and see.
This is where your power was born.
And this is where
your people were slaughtered.
You shouldn't have brought me here.
Why?
Are you afraid to be here?
You can't escape it, Erik.
Who are you?
Elohim, Shen, Ra.
I've been called many names
over many lifetimes.
I am born of death.
I was there to spark...
and fan the flame of man's awakening.
To spin the wheel of civilization.
And when the forest would grow rank...
and needed clearing for new growth...
I was there to set it ablaze.
Where were you...
when my father and mother
were slaughtered in this place?
Asleep.
Trapped in darkness.
I was not there for you, my son.
But I am here now.
You don't know your own strength,
but I do.
Reach down.
Feel the metal...
in the ground.
Reach as deep as you can.
You'll find you have the power...
to move the very Earth itself.
Everything they've built will fall!
And from the ashes of their world...
we'll build a better one!
Lehnsherr was identified yesterday,
in this small town in central Poland.
Leaders from all communities are urging
their citizens to remain calm.
As police and armed forces
are mobilizing to find Lehnsherr...
...before he can strike again.
If anyone has information
about Lehnsherr...
or as he is also known, Magneto...
contact your local authorities
immediately...
and proceed with caution...
- as he is considered extremely...
- Peter.
What's up?
Just checking on you.
I'm good. Playing Pac-Man.
You sure you weren't watching this?
This news comes at a time when the world
is celebrating 10 years of peace...
between mutants and mankind.
You're going after him, aren't you?
You wanted me
to get out of the house more, right?
I can't stop you. Nobody can.
But trust me, this won't end well.
Nothing does with him.
I'm not afraid of him.
You should be.
I've read so much about this place.
But being here,
it actually seems kind of...
familiar.
Strange.
Quite.
Shall we?
I'm just saying, Empire is still the best.
It's the most complex,
the most sophisticated...
wasn't afraid to have a dark ending.
Yeah, but come on.
If it wasn't for the first one...
you wouldn't have any of the rest
of the movies.
Well, at least we can all agree,
the third one's always the worst.
Hank. Are you in here?
I'd like you to meet...
Moira.
Raven.
I'm sorry, have we met?
Hank, Alex, Agent MacTaggert,
would you give us just one moment, please?
Of course.
Charles, why didn't she recognize me?
She knew me in this form.
Well, after you
left me on the beach in Cuba...
I took her memories of that time.
Have a seat.
Lucky girl.
It's good to see you, Raven.
- Welcome home.
- This isn't my home.
It was once.
No, it was your home. I just lived here.
And I barely even recognize it now.
You know, I have plans for this place.
I mean to turn it into a real campus.
A university.
Not just for mutants, either,
for humans too.
Living and working...
growing together.
You know, I really believed that once.
I really believed we
could change them after DC.
We did.
No, Charles. They still hate and fear us.
It's just harder to see
because they're more polite about it.
I got sick of living that lie.
That's why you're not in your
natural blue form.
I'm not gonna be the face of a world
that doesn't exist.
Things are better. The world is better.
Maybe in Westchester.
Out there, mutants are still running...
hiding, living in fear.
Just because there's not a war,
doesn't mean there's peace.
You want to teach your kids something,
teach them that.
Teach them to fight.
Otherwise they might as well live
in this house for the rest of their lives.
You still sound just like him.
You sound just like Erik.
That's why I'm here.
He's resurfaced.
He had a wife and a child.
They were killed.
Along with a handful of policemen.
The whole world will be looking for him.
But you can help me find him
before they do.
Moira, I'm going to have to ask you
to keep this a secret.
I don't even know what this is.
It's Cerebro.
The new model.
I based the color on...
It doesn't matter.
What are those?
Those are all the humans of the world.
And these...
are all the mutants.
I'm connected to all of their minds.
The CIA would kill for this.
I know they would.
Where are you, Erik?
Charles?
Hello, old friend.
I'm sorry. I am so sorry!
I feel your pain.
And your loss.
You think because you can
see into my head...
you know how it feels?
You're looking in the wrong place,
Charles.
What happened to them,
it was terribly wrong.
But come back to us.
I can help you.
Help me?
Think of your wife,
think of your daughter.
What would they have wanted?
They would have wanted to live.
I tried your way, Charles.
I tried to be like them.
Live like them.
But it always ends the same way.
They took everything away from me.
Now...
we'll take everything from them.
Hank...
he's not alone.
Extraordinary.
What do you see?
The answer.
Hey, Charles, wait.
Oh, my God.
Thank you for letting me in.
Charles, get out!
I've never felt power like this before.
Charles...
Charles, get out of there.
What's going on? What's happening?
I think...
Someone's taken over Cerebro.
- They've taken control of it.
- To do what?
To connect.
Always the same.
And now, all this.
No more stones.
No more spears.
No more slings.
No more swords.
No more weapons!
No more systems!
No more!
No more superpowers.
Charles!
Hank!
What the hell is going on?
Who's turning the keys?
The men are.
Who green-lit the launch?
Hank, do something!
It won't shut down!
We've lost contact
with all Trident and Polaris subs.
The Air Force is reporting the same thing.
So much faith in their tools...
and their machines.
Russia, China...
England, Israel, India.
Everybody's got nukes in the air.
What's the target?
Where are they going?
Up, straight up.
Alex...
- What?
- Destroy it!
Destroy everything. Destroy Cerebro!
Wreak havoc!
You can fire your arrows...
from the Tower of Babel...
but you can never strike God!
Charles, are you okay?
Erik.
Charles!
Alex!
Hey!
Hey, asshole!
All will be revealed, my child.
Stop!
No!
Wow!
Where did you...
I was looking for the Professor.
I thought he lived here.
They took him.
She's the one. It's her.
Are you sure?
Is she gonna help us?
They look up to you.
Right now...
they need you.
That's not what they need.
That's awesome!
What happened?
Where's Alex?
Where's my brother?
Pretty sure I got everybody.
Alex was closest to the blast.
Alex...
We're one click out.
All right, boys. This is it.
Scott.
Medical assistance is on the way.
Please remain calm.
Hey! Moira MacTaggert!
CIA! Thank God you're here!
Wait!
Fire!
I want her.
Him.
- And her.
- Yes, sir.
Leave the kids.
- What do we do?
- Keep quiet.
X-Ray 7, I'm doing a final sweep
of the ground.
Let's get them on the bird!
Clear!
Thanks, Jean. We gotta help them.
- Kurt, can you get us in that thing?
- You want to get in there?
What if the soldiers see us?
Don't worry, they won't see us. Trust me.
Hold on.
Kurt, get us all out of here!
I can't!
When they closed the doors,
there's some kind of electrical field.
It's like Berlin all over.
Jean, get in the pilots' heads.
Don't let them take off.
I can't. I can't reach the pilots.
I can't reach anyone.
We're also getting reports
out of Europe and Asia.
This was not just a U.S. phenomenon.
It seems the entire world
has been disarmed of nuclear weapons.
The Pentagon has confirmed
multiple launches...
from Russia, as well as
the UK, Israel and China.
- Look!
- Look up there!
So far, there has been no response
from the White House.
Eyewitness reports have been pouring in
from affiliates across the globe.
Authorities are not sure if it was
an act of peace or an act of war.
Our dear Father...
hold me in the light of God.
It should have been me.
He was the one that was
gonna do something with his life.
He was always the one.
That's not how he felt.
He felt you were the one that was gonna
do something special with your life.
That you were gonna
make a difference in the world.
Maybe even change it.
How do you know what he felt?
I know what everybody feels.
Hold me in the light of God.
Protect me from danger.
Save me by Your command.
Listen to my prayer.
And keep me safe.
You're blocking me.
How?
I can shield their minds from your power.
It's one of the many gifts I've acquired
throughout the millennia.
But to see...
inside a mind...
to control it...
that's your gift.
You saw it, didn't you?
The glory of what's to come.
You're going to take part
in all this killing and destruction?
It's all I've ever known.
No, it isn't.
You've just forgotten.
No, Charles, I remember.
Your way doesn't work.
I've shown him a better way.
A better world.
No, you've just tapped into his rage
and pain. That's all you've done.
I told you from the moment I met you,
there is more to you, Erik.
There is good in you, too.
Whatever it is you think
you saw in me, Charles...
I buried it...
with my family.
What?
What's wrong with you?
Is that going to happen to all of us?
No, I just...
left my meds in the house.
What happened? Where are we?
Hey!
Hello, Mystique.
Major Stryker.
Colonel Stryker.
I wouldn't get too close to the wall,
if I were you.
It may create some discomfort.
I'm Moira MacTaggert.
I'm a senior officer at the CIA.
I know who you are, Agent MacTaggert.
You cannot keep me here, in this...
Actually, I can.
A psychic event just destroyed
every nuke from here to Moscow.
That event emanated from exactly
where we found you.
At the home of the world's
most powerful psychic.
So, you are going to tell me,
where is Charles Xavier?
It's not him you should be worried about.
There's someone else.
Someone more powerful.
If you let us out of here,
we can help you.
Do you really expect me to believe that?
You can put on any face that you want,
but I know who you are.
What you are.
Hey, Moira.
What did you mean when you said...
someone more powerful than Charles?
Once they finish these,
we'll go from there.
What's taking so long?
I can't get in.
They have a field around it,
like the helicopter.
There's gotta be a way to cut the power.
Charles...
you will send a message...
to every living mind.
You will tell them
that this earth will be laid waste.
That it is I, En Sabah Nur...
who will wreak this upon them.
Now...
deliver my message.
Even if I wanted to...
I couldn't reach that many people.
I don't have Cerebro.
You don't need a machine...
to amplify your powers.
You have me.
Guys, that could be our way out of here.
You know him? Magneto?
I used to.
Not so sure anymore.
What was he like?
Was he like they say he was? Was he...
the bad guy?
No.
I mean, yeah. He was...
Why do you care so much?
You see his speech on TV or something?
Yeah, but...
He's my father.
What?
- Him and my mom, they did it.
- No, I know...
Are you sure?
Yeah. He left my mom before I was born.
I met him 10 years back...
but I didn't know it was him.
By the time I figured it out,
it was too late.
Then, this week I saw him on TV again...
and I came to that house,
looking for him...
but by the time I got there...
Late again.
For a guy who moves as fast as me...
I always seem to be too late.
Let's hope not this time.
Yeah.
Seriously.
Hear me...
inhabitants of this world.
- What is that?
- This is a message.
I think it's the Professor.
A message to every man, woman,
and mutant in the world.
You have lost your way.
But I have returned.
The day of reckoning is here.
All your buildings...
...all of your towers and temples...
Will fall.
And the dawn of a new age will rise.
...for there is nothing you can do...
- Jean.
- ...to stop what is coming.
Jean, if you can hear me,
focus on my voice.
Cairo. Find us, Jean.
Find us. Cairo. Find us.
This message is for one reason alone.
To tell the strongest among you...
Those with the greatest power...
this earth will be yours.
protect those without.
That's my message to the world.
How was Charles doing that
without Cerebro?
Sir, what was that voice?
I know that voice.
It's Xavier, isn't it? What's going on?
- We don't know!
- We don't know, bro!
He just spoke to me.
I think he spoke to everyone.
- I could hear him, too.
- No, no...
he just sent me a hidden message.
One he knew only I would hear.
I know where they are.
Hey!
We have shots fired!
Where's it coming from?
I have intruders in Quad Six.
Send a security team. Take them out.
The generator. It's worth a shot.
Kurt?
There's some kind of animal in there.
It's no animal.
It's a man.
Who is he?
That part of him as been taken away.
What do you mean?
I mean they turned him into
some kind of weapon.
Charlie Three, report. Did you find them?
Shut it down.
Fire!
Weapon X is loose!
I repeat, Weapon X is loose!
You sure he's not an animal?
- He's into the central halls.
- Engaging target Sector Five.
We can't...
Hey!
- What are they doing?
- What's going on?
- I just lost feed.
- Hey! What's going on here?
I'll be right back.
No!
Hey! Stay where you are!
Scott, wait.
I can help you.
Jean.
Logan.
What'd you do to him?
I found a piece of his past
and gave it back to him.
Just the few memories I could reach.
I hope that's the last we've seen
of that guy.
Kurt.
- What?
Hey.
Stay away from the...
The what?
The do...
Stay away from the...
Get away from the door!
On three.
One... two...
We know where the Professor is.
I think we might have a way out of here.
- Well, you've been busy.
- We had a little help.
Let's go!
Jesus!
Oh, sorry!
This way!
This was meant to be
the center of the universe...
before I was betrayed.
Now...
it will be.
Nice.
Hey, Hank, do you think
you can fly this thing?
Yeah, I can figure it out.
Hey, guys.
Flight suits.
You got your warplane.
Let's go to war.
A gift...
from the past you left behind...
and the future that lies ahead.
You will reach down, my son.
Deep into the earth.
Rip everything they've built
from the ground.
Wipe clean this world.
And we will lead those that survive...
into a better one.
And me?
Am I to play a role in this madness?
You have the most important role of all.
Were you scared?
That day in D.C., were you scared?
No.
But I was scared on my first mission.
I was on a plane like this
with my friends.
About your age.
We called ourselves the X-Men.
Your brother was there.
We used to call him Havok.
He was a real handful...
but when it came down to it,
he was very brave.
What happened to the rest
of the kids who went with you?
The X-Men?
Hank and I are the only ones left.
I couldn't save the rest of them.
I told you, I'm not a hero.
Well, you're a hero to us.
Seeing you that day on
changed my life.
Mine, too.
I still live in my mom's basement
but, you know...
everything else is...
It's pretty much the same.
I'm a total loser.
What we're seeing is
a magnetic phenomenon...
on a much larger scale
than what we saw at Auschwitz.
The ground is full of magnetic elements.
Iron, nickel, cobalt.
The ocean's floor is lined with them, too.
It's already begun at the lowest depths.
Land masses will slow it,
but not for long.
Eventually, cities, urban centers...
anything built since the Bronze Age...
will be wiped away.
The death toll will be in the billions.
He's talking about
the whole goddamn world.
You're just another false god.
And whoever's left to follow you
when this all over...
they will betray you again.
You're wrong, Charles.
For the first time
in a thousand lifetimes...
I have you.
For all my gifts, I have yet
to possess the one I needed most.
To be...
everywhere.
everyone.
Seventh wonder, twelve o'clock.
He has the Professor
in the center of the pyramid.
He's going to transfer his consciousness
into the Professor.
If he does that, he'll have the power
to control every mind in the world.
What the hell is that?
It's Erik.
You guys help Nightcrawler
get into the pyramid.
Get Charles. I'll take care of Erik.
How are we gonna get through that?
I can get you in there.
I came here for him. Let me help you.
The rest of you, get Charles on this
plane and get him out of here.
- We're not leaving without you!
- Don't worry.
We'll catch up.
Hold on.
Hank, you go with the kids.
- Moira will be waiting on the plane.
- Wait.
What?
Not all of us can
fully control our powers.
Then don't.
You need to embrace them.
We all do.
Go. Join the others.
Protect me,
until the transference is complete.
There's an entrance. It's clear.
Kurt! Get in there!
In the pyramid! Move!
Go!
Split them up.
Professor...
Kurt, you have to hurry!
I'm trying. It's like a maze in here.
Kurt, no!
The magnetic field is too strong.
I can't get us in there.
Erik!
Mystique.
I know you think you've lost everything.
But you haven't.
You have me.
You have Charles.
You have more family than you know.
You never had the chance
to save your family before.
But you do now.
That's what I've come here to tell you.
And you?
I'm your...
I'm here for my family, too.
Get out. Get out!
Get out!
Auf Wiedersehen.
We're losing him.
I'll be right back.
Scott, glasses on!
Let's go!
- Locked on.
- Here we go.
Psylocke!
What the hell was that?
Kurt.
Everyone, grab hold of Nightcrawler!
I've never done it with this many people.
Get us out of here.
Kurt, hurry!
Kurt!
Charles...
Is he okay?
It's his energy. He's drained.
Get out.
Get out!
Professor, it's okay. You're with us.
It's okay.
I'm going to fight for what I have left.
Are you?
There's so much more to you than you know.
Not just pain and anger.
There's good, too. I felt it.
It's not just me you're walking away from.
Here, you have the chance to be a part of
something much bigger than yourself.
And it needs you, Erik.
Useless.
Charles.
I know you can hear me.
We're still connected.
Charles!
Show yourself!
Foolish child.
Peter.
End him.
Raven.
The great hero.
- I'm going out there.
- I'm going with you.
No.
It's me he wants.
Charles, you can't give yourself up.
If he has you, he has us all.
The whole world.
You are feeble.
Just like the others.
Charles!
Come!
Rescue your weaklings!
Give your life for theirs!
No.
He was right.
There is still some part of me
connected to him.
Charles!
I can get inside his head.
Will you do nothing?
Thank you for letting me in.
You want what I have?
You want to feel what I feel?
Welcome to my world!
You're in my house now!
You'll need a bigger house.
You betray me?
No.
I betrayed them.
Let's jump.
What?
Cover me.
I got you.
Come on!
They lack strength, Charles.
Jean.
Come here.
Help...
me.
Stay here.
They can't stop him.
Jean.
Help me!
Hank!
It's over, Charles. You're finished.
You're mine now.
You will never win.
And why is that?
Because you are alone.
And I am not!
Let...
go.
Unleash your power, Jean.
No fear.
Unleash your power!
Let go, Jean!
Jean, let go!
He's getting away.
All is revealed.
Charles! Charles!
- We've lost him!
- Charles.
- He's gone.
- No, Charles.
Charles...
No, he's not.
I can still feel him.
Thank you, Jean.
Charles?
Charles, do you know where you are?
I'm on a beach.
In Cuba.
With you.
What beach?
Charles Xavier.
I'm sorry.
I should never have taken those from you.
Hold on!
What did I miss?
It seems only by the grace of God...
that the ominous destruction...
seen from one end of the globe
to the other, has stopped.
At a debriefing today,
CIA Special Agent Moira MacTaggert...
revealed to an investigative committee...
The committee was further stunned
to learn that fugitive Erik Lehnsherr...
aided in defeating
this powerful and unknown...
I think our prayers were answered.
Thank you, Mr. President.
The potential destructive power
of mutants...
...is sure to fuel new controversy
and debate...
at a time when mutants were becoming
accepted around the world.
Mystique told me he is your father.
Are you gonna tell him?
I might...
one day.
I think for now, I'm just gonna
stick around here for a while.
Me, too.
The world's already begun
rebuilding its arsenals.
It's human nature, Charles.
I still have hope.
Oh, yes.
"Hope."
I was right about Raven.
I was even right about you.
What about the rest of the world?
Doesn't it ever wake you up
in the middle of the night?
The feeling that one day
they'll come for you...
and your children.
It does, indeed.
What do you do when you wake up to that?
I feel a great swell of pity
for the poor soul...
that comes to my school
looking for trouble.
You're sure I can't convince you to stay?
You're psychic, Charles.
You can convince me to do anything.
Goodbye, old friend.
Good luck, Professor.
Forget everything you think you know.
Whatever lessons you learned in school...
whatever your parents taught you.
None of that matters!
You're not kids anymore.
You're not students.
You're X-Men.
Please rate this subtitle at www.osdb.link/9ma
Help other users to choose the best subtitles