Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
He stole the chip, he's inside.
l see him.
Kirill!
Time to work.
NSA Remote lntelligence Facility
Mt. Weather, Virginia
At 0030 hours, the mission
deviated from the set parameters.
lt wasn't part of the plan
for our agent to get shot in the back.
Identity confirmed.
McGrath was uploading some data
to us when he was killed.
Take a look at this.
l'm not sure yet exactly what it is.
-A fragment of a complex molecule.
-Gibbons.
We think it's a link
to a Soviet bio-weapon...
...called Silent Night.
-James, what the hell is he doing here?
-l called him in.
We've lost three agents already.
You could use the help.
l found out your agents were killed by
this group, Anarchy 99.
They're ex-military. They can smell
the training on our agents a mile away.
Sir, l think it's time we tried
something new.
These guys aren't ours.
Who are they? ClA?
No, civilians. Convicts, mercs,
contract killers.
The best and brightest
of the bottom of the barrel.
-They're the scum of the earth.
-Programmable, expendable, effective.
l think it's our best shot.
Do we want to drop another
mouse in the snake pit?
Or send our own snake
and let him crawl in?
Sacramento, California
Come on, Pepe. This is unbelievable.
Hello!
Well, it's about time. Now, listen....
Were you coming from Tijuana?
l don't mean to be rude.
Keep it out of the sun.
l don't want the paint to fade.
Do you understand English?
l pay enough for you people.
Come on, Janelle.
You're gonna love this place.
-Dick, how are you?
-This is Janelle.
-Call 91 1 .
-Who's driving my car?
Senator Hotchkiss!
California state Senate!
Listen, somebody just stole my car!
You, in the red Corvette!
Pull over immediately!
Yeah, yeah. These monkeys are
following me because l took this car.
Obviously the car doesn't belong to me,
it's not my style.
lt belongs to Dick, Dick Hotchkiss,
a California state senator.
You remember Dick.
He tried to ban rap music...
...because he feels the lyrics
promote violence.
lt's music, Dick!
He also wants to pull every video game
off every shelf in the country...
...because he feels that the video games
diminish the intelligence of our youth.
Come on, Dick.
lt's the only education we got.
You're a bad man.
You know what we do to bad men.
We punish them.
Dick, you've just entered
the Xander zone.
l'm coming in hot with a side of bacon!
Go, go, go!
Pull it! Pull it!
Yes!
Go get the cameras! Go! Go! Go!
Moral is, don't be a dick, Dick!
You guys got the cameras?
All right, let's go, let's go!
Peace out!
Outstanding.
Thank you.
-What's up?
-You invited these people?
Of course not.
That's my dog! What's up?
Today was off the hook!
You're psycho, bro!
Psycho? That was off the chain, man!
Yo, yo, yo! What's up with that crazy
trick that we've been hearing about?
-My Superman seat-grab barrel roll?
-Word.
l'm still working on it.
You're a hard guy to get ahold of.
You know, an athlete like you should
really have his own video game.
Jordan King. l can make it happen.
-l'll hold on to this for later.
-You do that.
You know he'll never sell out.
That's why he is who he is.
So you need to relax.
Who invited you, anyway?
Shut up.
Listen, this is for real. l can get us
an advance on lnternet pre-sales.
So you need to just go to Pago Pago
or something.
Get some girls, do them all.
l don't care. Go on vacation.
lt's Bora Bora, J.
l got enough girls here.
Since when did you care so much
about money?
l just need you to lay low
till the heat's off, okay?
l run a secret website. l got tapes to
make and l can't do that with you in jail.
-Did you see that?
-l don't care. Listen to me.
l'm untouchable.
Let's go! Get out! Move!
Okay, l'll turn down the music.
lt was only a Corvette.
Let's go, baby.
Your order is getting cold.
-Want coffee?
-Can you give me some hash browns?
-Sure.
-Make them sloppy. l like them runny.
How did l get here?
Two big guys dropped you off 1 0 minutes
ago. Told me to look after you.
You look like you could use
some coffee.
You all right?
Fine.
l said, you got a problem, boy?
No. No problem.
-Nobody make a move!
-Nobody move!
Just couldn't let him leave.
Keep your goddamned mouth shut!
-Keep still or you'll stop breathing.
-Empty the goddamn register!
Get back!
Get back. Get back!
-Well done, Mr. Cage.
-Who the hell are you?
The name's Gibbons. Augustus Gibbons.
You seem upset. ls there a problem?
-What is this place?
-Looks like a diner.
That's clever.
You almost had me going there
for a while.
l was a bit groggy before,
then l started noticing things.
Like, you got a stockbroker over here,
all dressed up...
...reading the Financial Times
on Sunday when the market's closed.
Unlikely, but okay, l can go with that.
l could even go with the stick-up man
packing a cop-issue Beretta.
But you want to know where you blew it?
With her.
My aunt was in the restaurant business.
There's no way a career waitress
comes to work in high heels.
She'd have blisters
the size of pancakes.
And if she ain't real, then this whole
thing ain't real.
That's how l knew that this bozo
wouldn't get a shot off...
...even if we waited
till St. Patrick's Day.
Because there's nothing but blanks
in these guns.
Oh, and no offense...
...but their performances were terrible.
That's good. That's very good.
lt's your turn, pretty boy.
-What the hell is going on here?
-lt was a test that you aced.
-He seems to have a poor attitude.
-Excuse me?
-Should we throw him back?
-Hell, no. l love his attitude.
Let's take this to the next level.
Get on the Sat-Com.
Take what to the next level?
-Yo! Take what?
-l want everybody out in 1 0 minutes.
l don't play this game.
-Get Mike a doctor or he'll look like me.
-l got a party.
-Shut him up.
-And pay for my windows!
Why is it always the assholes
who pass the tests?
You guys haven't been
to any diners lately, huh?
Diner finalists.
-What, no coffee?
-Oh, yeah.
-Here comes the ROTC.
-Here we go.
-Where's my peanuts?
-Nice.
Can you ask for the stewardess?
-Standing by to deploy drogue.
-Roger, deploying drogue parachute.
-This will hurt.
-What the hell?
-Release drogue now.
-Roger.
This ain't right!
l live for this shit!
Not bad!
Let's do that again!
Holy shit. This is Colombia.
Cocaine, man. These are coke plants!
No keys.
-What the hell are you doing?
-You know what this shit's worth?
What now? ls this another test?
-Let's go across the river. Let's go!
-Yeah, good idea! Good idea!
You monkeys are too good for me.
l failed this test.
You guys got something to drink?
Nice to see you again, fellas.
Yeah, you too.
Boy, they went all out on this one.
You've got to be kidding.
Okay, funny guys.
l'll show you what we do
when you get in our business.
What? Hog-tie us and force us
to listen to your bad accent?
No.
We cut their Achilles tendon and watch
them flop around like a marionette.
Unless you have something to tell me,
something l need to know?
Okay. You're short.
My friend says you could use a haircut
to update your style. Get off me.
Shut up!
Two seconds ago you told us to talk.
Now it's ''Shut up?''
l don't mean to nitpick, but you're
the worst at this torture thing.
You slap me again,
l'm going to throw you a beating.
l hope they're paying you
extra for this.
You know what, funny guy?
Maybe l'll cut off your nose first.
Funny guy.
What's funny is, this actually smells
like real blood.
l hope you like it, because it's the
last thing you're going to smell.
l'm hit! l'm hit! l'm hit!
Virg! Give me a hand.
This is the Colombian army!
Give up, you're surrounded!
Try to walk, T.J. Try to walk.
Virg! Get out here!
To hell with this.
Every man for himself.
l'll get us some wheels.
Hang in there.
Good luck.
The guy on the bike,
that's the drug lord!
Let's get him!
T.J.!
X! l'm over here! X!
There he is!
We toasted his ass!
l got us a bike.
Pussies!
Look who it is. Frankenstein. Uncuff me
so l can beat the shit out of you.
Relax, X, you just graduated
at the head of your class.
What are you talking about?
You almost got us killed.
-We knew the army was moving.
-Excuse me?
lt was my idea to send you as
a decoy. How do you like that?
-You're pretty fast for an old man.
-Get up.
Walk with me.
l believe under the right
circumstances, a man can change.
For instance, last night you exhibited
courage, leadership...
...and willingness to protect
a man you hardly knew.
-So give me a medal.
-l'd rather give you a job.
Look at me. Do l look like a fan
of law enforcement?
This is your lucky day, Xander.
This is your chance
to pay your Uncle Sam...
...for all your wonderful freedoms.
The job's not that difficult.
l want you to meet people and
find out what you can about them.
What type of people?
Dangerous, dirty, tattooed,
uncivilized. Your kind of people.
Hold up.
My kind of people would say,
''Kiss my ass, scarface.''
Usually l'd take my gun,
press it to your temple...
...and ask you very politely
to do what l want.
But you're not afraid of death.
That puts us in a quandary.
-We better call this a day, then.
-Not just yet.
You ever watch lions at the zoo?
You can tell which were captured
in the wild by the look in their eyes.
The wild cat.
She remembers running across the plain,
the thrill of the hunt.
Four hundred pounds of killing fury
locked in a box.
But after a while,
their eyes glaze over...
...and you can tell
their soul has died.
The same thing happens to a man.
Leavenworth Federal Penitentiary
is no joke.
They'll take a wild man and
throw him in solitary just for fun.
No more mountains to board,
no more oceans to surf.
Just a 6-by-8 cell with no window
and only a bucket to shit in.
You can avoid that
by doing me this favor.
You don't have shit on me.
l noticed you have three X's
tattooed on the back of your neck.
l think that's rather appropriate since
you're looking at three strikes.
Grand theft, reckless endangerment,
and that bridge stunt of yours...
...makes you a three-time loser.
Maybe you ought to call yourself
''Triple X.''
But if you do what l want, l'll make
all your transgressions go away...
...and let you get back
to that pathetic excuse of a life.
Or you think maybe
l should be like you.
Get all shot up for the old
Stars and Stripes.
l bet that flag is a real comfort
every time you look in the mirror.
A small price l paid for putting
foot to ass for my country.
So, what's it going to be, Triple X?
You want to get on a plane...
...or is ''Kiss my ass, scarface''
your final answer?
Prague, Czech Republic
Yo. What's your name, slick?
My name is lvan.
-lvan? What's your name, buddy?
-My name is lvan.
You're both lvan?
Take a seat.
ldiots! Where is the American agent?
This is him, Sir.
We better order another bodybag.
Guys, what's up?
l told you to sit down.
l've just been on a plane for 1 2 hours.
l think l'll stand.
My name is Milan Sova,
Czech secret police.
Here, you are under my jurisdiction.
You take my orders,
you do what l say.
lf you become any kind of an
inconvenience, l'll shoot you.
That's great.
ls this where l'm staying?
Your government is putting pressure
on mine.
This is an internal Czech affair
that you are interfering with.
l will warn you once:
Don't shit in my lawn.
Get whatever information
your government seeks and get out.
Let's get this straight.
You may not want me here,
but l definitely don't want to be here.
Two, l've never been
under anyone's jurisdiction.
Three, if you're going to
shoot anybody...
...shoot that monkey
that sold you the suit.
Now, l'm tired. l'm going to sleep.
Be ready in three hours.
Everybody in this club
has two things in common:
-They're rich and they're criminals.
-l'll fit in, except for the rich part.
-Remember, we don't know each other.
-l wish we didn't.
Yeah, can l get a cranberry club soda?
Throw this back there?
l'll tip you something.
Put it in the back.
How much? Do l get a ticket?
That's them. Anarchy 99.
You see the guy on the couch?
That's Yorgi. He's the leader.
He owns this club and five others like
it. All, how do you say, cash cows.
American?!
Guys, l'm American.
l'm going to see Yorgi. Yorgi!
Hey, Yorgi! l hear you're the guy--
l heard you're the guy
to talk to about cars.
Take yourself outside.
Take myself outside? l'm just--
Okay. l'm not welcome.
Guess you'd rather have cops
in your club.
Want to talk?
Hey, you silly boy. Come with me
and show me the cop...
...and don't be mistake.
See that guy there,
with the suit made out of drapes?
That's a cop.
ls there a problem?
l just had a drink, you know?
l already paid. l'm going to
give a big tip, you know?
So, what is this all about?
l've done nothing.
You've done nothing?
Who do you work for?
l work in a bank. So what?
You've got to be....
What are you doing? Stop it! Stop it!
What's that, your bus pass?
Czech 5-0. Czech 5-0.
Leave my club.
How did you know?
When he was paying for his drinks, he
was flashing his badge to half the bar.
Cops like plague.
No matter how many you pay, there's
always another with his hand out.
l'm from the streets.
l know cops, believe me.
l appreciate you bringing this to our
attention. My question to you is why?
l figure, no one likes cops
crashing their party.
l figure, l do you a solid,
we could talk.
l just want to buy cars, man.
ls this guy going to hump my leg?
What's your name?
Xander Cage.
l knew it.
You are amazing on snowboard,
motorbike, everything.
-You're awesome.
-Thank you, man.
My brother is crazy too,
and a great admirer of yours.
He has seen your tapes many times.
Now we can talk business.
This way, please.
Yelena.
Welcome to the Xander zone.
Now, that's funny. That's funny.
Sit down, Mr. Cage.
My friends call me X.
So, X, what exactly are you wanting?
Ferraris, high-end pasta rockets,
1 0 to start.
This car, number 1 0, will be very
difficult to find in Europe.
That one's for me. l put it in there
to get something out of the deal.
Well, you certainly know your cars.
Yeah. Cars, bikes, boards. You name it.
l like anything fast enough
to do something stupid in.
Yes.
Ten cars is hardly worth the effort.
A lousy 1 .5 million, U.S.
Now, hold on a second.
The American buyers l represent,
to them, 1 0 cars is an appetizer.
-And it's a mil max, sister.
-How about a million four?
l was thinking more like a mil two.
Do you know what a wire transfer is?
ls she for real?
Sweetheart, is there anything
you need to do?
Let us big boys have a conversation.
''Conversation,'' a word
with four syllables.
Do you want some ice
before your brain overheats?
lce. Yeah, you could chisel some off
your heart, if you could find it.
This would work a lot faster, princess,
if l had an account number.
You have 48 hours
to complete the transfer.
-Don't waste my time.
-l wouldn't dream of it.
l might throw in a couple extra
bucks and send you to charm school.
Now that business is finished,
we party.
Bitches, come!
Yeah?
Shit, l thought this was a cell phone.
Have a nice rest?
Dial it down.
l got to sleep an hour ago.
You were given a specific list of cars.
Who told you to alter it?
The cars sucked.
They would've seen through it.
You guys should switch travel agents.
I got that info you wanted.
Hang on a second.
You guys ready for this?
Names, birthdays,
ranks in the Red Army.
Favorite foods?
How did you get this?
Kolya, Yorgi's younger brother,
happens to be an action sports fanatic.
So naturally, he's a fan.
But when you kill a bottle of vodka
in three swigs, you'll talk.
-I got something else.
-What?
Their personal bank account number.
Where did l put that?
Stolen cars, nightclubs, prostitution,
extortion.
What's the big deal?
We got criminals like this in the U.S.
Yourjob isn't to ask questions.
Well, l did my job, thank you.
l'm coming home.
Notjust yet.
You're a victim of your own success.
Get closer to these guys.
-They're cool, but not that cool.
-Go deeper.
l'll send a guy with a care package
to help you.
-l thought we had a deal.
-You change cars, l change the deal.
Do this for me, you can come home.
lf you send someone to save the world,
make sure they like it the way it is.
l have a really firm chest.
l bench, like, 225.
Like, bench. Weight room. Bye.
-That's him.
-Wait. You're Triple X?
-You're the care package?
-Agent Toby Lee Shavers.
Come on.
You have to rate high
to get Gibbons to send this stuff.
l kind of wish l was going with you,
mixed up in the fury of the situation.
Crazy. License to kill,
death, destruction, mayhem.
Got a gun under your pillow. Never know
when some freak villain will pop out.
-How long you been with the agency?
-Two days.
You're shitting me. No way.
That sucks.
Yeah, it sucks, but it beats jail.
lt sucks because l spent six years...
...in the basement of some windowless,
NSA, gadget freak room, man.
And l got a degree.
l got a degree from MlT.
Phi Beta Kappa, magna cum laude.
And they probably picked you up,
what, pumping iron in San Quentin?
You ever get punched in the face
for talking too much?
Show me the stuff.
This one made my career,
the definition of perfection:
My multi-purpose, multi-function
field revolver.
-Oh, l like this.
-Then you'll love these.
These are all attachment darts.
See the green ones?
Datura knockout darts.
Guy goes down for 1 2 hours, wakes
up, doesn't know who he is...
...and his head's splitting
like a cord of firewood.
l was shot twice by those.
And the red ones are tranquilizer
and blood-splatter darts.
Looks like a kill shot
without the aftereffects. Like death.
You've got exploding and
surveillance darts...
...and your standard .44-caliber
bullets, if you want to get nasty.
A little wet work. You know
what l'm talking about, right?
Knocked over a few 7-Elevens,
have we?
No, l had my leg in a cast for three
months. All l did was play video games.
That's a really sad story.
Check this out, on to my baby.
Eagle Eyes. Nine enhanced-vision modes.
Every little boy's dream:
the penetrator mode.
Check it out.
Oh, my God.
-She's checking you out, man.
-l'll hang on to these.
Now, on to my latest achievement.
l just put the finishing touches
on them last week.
What do you think?
-Bandages?
-No, Mr. X, watch and learn.
There's enough primer
to blow a hole in a vault...
...vaporize a human, or whatever agents
like you might find a use for.
And check this out.
The detonator. How cool is that?
-You might want to back up for this.
-lt's a bandage.
Just get behind the wall.
You ready?
l've always wanted to say this.
Fire in the hole.
lt's loaded.
So, what do you think?
Beautiful.
You like the cars?
l love the cars, they're dope.
-You like the money?
-l love money, but l do not have it.
You look like you're doing very well.
All these employees, beautiful cars.
This is no time for being funny.
-You didn't think l wasn't good for it?
-lt never crossed my mind.
A cargo ship's waiting for you
in Rijeka. Here's the address.
This place is dope.
This one's mine?
Car number 1 0.
Kolya found it hiding in Berlin.
lt was very difficult to find.
No! Please.
Allow me. You were kind enough
to give me the money.
Now, please...
...drive.
No, allow me.
-You're all right, Yorgi.
-Everything's all right with vodka.
You must come to party tonight.
Big party at one of my clubs.
-Yeah?
-Yes.
What's going on, my friend?
You tell me.
You got a sniper up there or what?
He's not with us,
he must be with you.
Bullshit! Tell your men to get down...
...or l'll give you another hole to
breathe out of. Are we clear?
All right. lt's not yours.
Let's go and get him together.
Son of a bitch.
That same cop from the club.
Filthy cop.
Most people talk a lot.
Few are up for the moment.
Welcome to Anarchy 99.
-Did you enjoy that?
-Yeah.
Good, because it will
never happen again.
-After you.
-No, after you.
-No, l insist.
That's it.
Last chance to tuck me in.
Good morning.
lt's none of my business, but a power
drill and some titanium bits...
...will get you a lot further than that
camera.
You're not supposed to be in here.
l was on my way to the bathroom.
What's your excuse?
l don't need an excuse.
Oh, you're good.
But not that good.
l came in here to photograph
Yorgi's safe.
l thought it might be worth
a lot to somebody.
Come on. You're cold,
intelligent and vicious.
lt's your eyes that give you away.
They gave you away
when l shot that cop.
What are you going to do now?
Now l'm going to take you to lunch.
Oh, and that cop l shot, isn't dead.
I have some information for you.
l can always use information. Who
is this? How did you get this number?
Yes. Important information
that you need about Xander Cage.
-So you don't like foreigners, do you?
-No, you're a pig.
ls your boyfriend a pig too?
You should recognize one of your kind.
Now, tell me about the cop.
What if l told you l'm not
who you think l am?
That l could get you out of
the mess you're in?
Really? And what mess am l in?
The mess that makes you sneak around
the castle when everyone's asleep.
The cop?
See this?
lt's called a blood-splatter dart.
The impact's real, but it's harmless.
Red paint, mostly.
Why?
l'm a secret agent.
Are you sure you don't want
to embarrass me?
-Come on.
-What's so funny about that?
l mean, look at you.
l work for the NSA.
You're funny, you know that?
Yelena, it's Kirill.
Yorgi found out that Cage
is an American agent.
Do you understand what I'm telling you?
You are in danger, my love.
The building across the street.
The statue.
Bring him outside.
l will do the rest.
What was that, your boyfriend?
Let's say you are
who you say you are.
-What can you do for me?
-What do you want?
l want immunity from prosecution,
asylum in the U.S. and citizenship.
How about a condo on South Beach
and a rich boyfriend?
Those l can get for myself.
-What do you want?
-l need to know more about Anarchy 99.
You want to know about Anarchy 99?
You've seen the girls,
the clubs, the parties.
What you don't see
is what goes on during the day.
There's been a lot of activity in the
last year. People coming in and out.
-Russian scientists.
-Well, what are they up to?
They go in the basement
and l'm not allowed in.
Now's a good time for you
to get invited.
Yorgi knows you're an agent.
Kirill is waiting with his rifle.
-Where--?
-Don't look!
There's a back door.
They'll know you warned me.
lf you go out the front,
he'll put a bullet in your eye.
-You still packing?
-Always.
Get ready to use it.
-What's your plan?
-He's still in love with you.
-He'll wait for a clear shot.
-That's your plan? Thank you. Great.
Draw!
He's on the way.
Gibbons! My favorite kidnapper.
Next time send a limo.
Oh, you've got to be kidding me.
You already broke me.
No need to get cruel and unusual.
A ticket? Now, that's funny.
-Where am l going to go now?
-Home.
Home?
Your cover's blown.
You're not useful.
That's it? l'm done?
No tricks. We have enough intel
to move forward.
-With what?
-Sweeper team: quick, clean, effective.
Don't worry about it.
lt'll all be over soon.
You mean a sweeper team
to come in and kill everybody?
Not all of them are as bad
as you think.
You had to shoot a cop. How
''not as bad as l think'' could they be?
Okay, look.
We've got a complication.
There's a girl. Yelena.
There's always a girl.
She wants out and l sent her back in
to get more intel for you.
There's no time to play favorites.
The cards have been dealt.
What do you mean
the cards have been dealt?
You don't even know her, man.
Oh, by the way, that bank number
you gave us?
Your friends and Yelena have made
some large cash transfers...
...to a group of Russian scientists
known to specialize and traffic...
...in biological weapons.
-She had nothing to do with it.
-Go home.
-She ain't--!
-That's an order.
How's it going?
Life is shit!
Yeah, well what can you do?
Through this door,
you are with us to the end.
-Are you sure that's what you want?
-l'm sure.
This is Ahab. Think of it as
solar-powered submarine.
lt can circumnavigate the globe
to reach its target.
lt need only surface to gather sunshine
and to do its business.
What is it? What's its business?
Dropping off presents to all
the good little boys and girls.
My team will be finished tomorrow.
How about you?
We're finished now.
Nikolai!
Bring the rockets.
The detonator is for you.
Yorgi! The binary agents are mixing...
...it will kill us all!
Looks like little white mouse.
Bye-bye, little mouse.
My God.
They did their job
and now they were liability.
We don't need anyone
talking about our business.
The gas gets sucked through the
extractor fans, passed into water...
...and broken down to become,
once again, completely harmless.
So quiet.
l know now why they call it
Silent Night.
Let's get some food.
Find out what's going on!
What the hell was that?
That works.
Fire in the hole.
Sova. What are you doing here, man?
First you set me up in the bar.
Then you shoot me in the back.
My boss does it to me.
l did it to you. lt's a vicious circle.
-You think it's funny?
-No.
You didn't take it personally,
did you?
l did what l had to do to get in.
We're on the same side.
l'm sorry. l switched sides.
You pushed me too far. My government
doesn't pay as well as Yorgi.
My government pays twice as much--
Think you could just walk
into the spy business...
-...and have all the angles figured out?
-What are you going to do, shoot me?
Where? ln the head, to be quick?
Or in the chest for an open casket,
so l can see your heart?
Can l think about it?
What are you doing?!
l heard you talking. l could tell
where you were in the room.
What are you doing with the lvans?
What's going on?
There's something l didn't
have the time to tell you.
l'm an agent as well.
l'm an agent for FSB,
Russian lntelligence.
You know, like your ClA.
-l've been undercover for two years.
-Two years?
What was your plan,
let them die of old age?
There was no plan.
A year ago, lntelligence gets
reorganized, l stop getting orders.
They forget about me. And l did what
l must to survive. You understand?
What do l understand?
l've been an agent for a week.
But my boss needs to know
what we know now.
-Okay?
-Okay.
The submarine's purpose is to deploy
a nerve agent called Silent Night.
lt's been missing since
the Soviet Union's collapse in '91 .
lt can kill millions.
We knew they were up to something.
You found out.
-That's excellent work, Triple X.
-There was never a sweeper team.
lf l said don't jump off
the Empire State Building....
-You're right. l'd definitely do it.
-l inspired you.
l'm an authority figure,
that's what l'm supposed to do.
Look, my men are on this now.
-It's time for you to come home.
-What about Yelena?
I'm not authorized to give her asylum.
But I promise it'll be done
by the time you get here.
Come home, Xander. That's an order.
How soon can Yorgi launch this thing?
You were told to go home!
Your people are handling--
How soon, Yelena?
Soon.
But it's not our problem anymore!
lf they get ahead of schedule,
it's everyone's.
He's got an army, a fortress.
You don't stand a chance!
l've risked my life for stupid reasons.
This is the first one that makes sense.
This is not one of your stunts.
You'll die in this, you know that.
lf you don't go back in there...
...he'll know something's wrong.
You can't ask me to go back there.
You can't.
You want to know something ironic?
l volunteered for this assignment.
l wanted to make a difference.
l fought for it.
Then finish it.
Remember what l told you,
after you kissed me?
-Never again?
-l lied.
But when you break it down,
l'm a simple man.
l'd be happy with a beautiful
Czech girl--
Hey, geek!
Got new orders from Gibbons. Get in.
-l want all that in here.
-Done.
The castle's covered
with surveillance cameras.
That's why we cannot get close enough.
Hang on. That's why l need to
knock out the communications tower...
...at the base of the mountain.
ls there anyone here
who knows how to fly a plane?
l can.
Too much turbulence
around these mountains!
Just get me in line with that tower!
l'll do the rest!
Go now!
Viktor! We got company!
Catch him fast. Kill him slow!
Nothing like fresh powder.
Yelena, my sweet dove,
did you get confused?
Your assignment was to kill the cop
after he killed X.
Not good for undercover agent
from Russian lntelligence.
l knew about you all along...
...and it was my pleasure to twist
you and use you how l saw fit.
And you.
Of all people,
l thought you'd understand...
...what l'm trying to accomplish.
Can you imagine?
lmagine a city like Prague vanishing...
...in a cloud of poison gas.
Then Hamburg, London, Washington.
lmagine not knowing who did it, or why.
And so they turn on each other.
These guys attack those guys.
Those guys invade these guys.
Soon, whole world implodes.
lmagine governments disappearing.
And in the end...
...imagine facing absolute,
beautiful freedom.
But neither of you will be there
to see it.
Like Viktor.
Like Kolya.
Cover me!
Get me out of this thing!
He took the hard drive.
He's going to launch Ahab!
Pick one.
lvan, take out that nest!
You have to turn the safety off.
Hold them off as long as you can.
See you, my friend.
Come on, baby.
Stop! He's got us pinned down.
Shit.
You got a bazooka!
Stop thinking Prague police and start
thinking PlayStation. Blow shit up!
This is not bazooka.
This is heat-seeker rocket.
Heat-seeker?
Set it.
The son of a bitch is smoking.
l told him that cigarette
would kill him one day.
Learn how to shoot, piece of shit!
Quick! Help me pull him out!
lt will hit the city in 30 minutes!
Guys. l need a helicopter.
l need transportation.
l need a--
X, there you are.
l gave you everything you wanted.
This thing will damn near fly now.
You screwed me.
Gibbons didn't authorize this.
He'll hang us both out to dry.
-Agent Shavers.
-Yeah?
l'm going to give you
a field promotion.
Take over, finish the mop-up.
You're in charge.
Yes, sir! l'm the man for the job!
l won't let you down!
Wait! Wait! Wait!
Almost forgot the manual. You'll need
this.
Hey, X. Go kick some ass.
That thing must be going 80 mph!
How do we stop it?!
We can't! The controls
are on the bubble panel.
-You see it?
-Yeah.
The hard drive's in there!
You got the manual. See if Shavers
put in anything we could use.
-He's got very bad handwriting.
-Come on!
Flame throwers, mini-bombs, exploding
hubcaps, rocket launchers!
This is a tank.
You can't use any of it on Ahab.
Silent Night only breaks down
in deep water.
-l'll have to get on it!
-What?
l'll have to get on it.
Our surveillance puts Ahab
22 minutes outside of Prague.
-We should evacuate the city.
-22 minutes for 1 .5 million people?
Call air support. We may need
to blow it out of the water.
-lf we hit that thing--
-This city will die.
And the crisis will be contained!
One city's better than 1 0.
Another thing: A blue GTO
is traveling parallel to Ahab.
Shit! Does this road
go back to the river?
Come on! Check the GPS!
Yes, it does!
Fifteen miles at the town of Davle!
There's got to be something here
we could use.
Harpoon gun, parachutes
built into seats, ejectable roof.
lt's all useless!
How far are we?
The river is just beyond
the next village.
l'm going through!
Use the rocket launcher!
-Twenty-two!
-Hit it!
That was a flamethrower!
Use the rockets!
lt's 32! l told you!
l told you he had bad handwriting!
Hit it!
Shavers loaded this thing.
We're missing something.
There are more weapons
here on the back. Look.
-Take the wheel!
-What? You're crazy!
The brake! The brake!
The gas! The gas!
X, what are you doing?
Five minutes to target.
X, talk to me!
What are you doing?
-You said there was an ejectable roof.
-Right here!
Hit it!
Shit! lt's out of range!
-There's a bridge! Cross the bridge!
-Okay.
Come on.
Come on!
-Got you!
-Yes!
-l wish l had a camera!
-What you talking about?
This is gonna be one hell of a trick.
Three minutes to target.
One minute to target.
Move! Move! Move!
Out of the way!
Eyes!
Ten seconds to target.
Target in sight.
Call the jets off.
Tell the jets to stand down!
Welcome to the Xander zone!
Zero contamination level. l understand,
sir. Zero contamination level.
You Yelena?
Mr. Gibbons.
l promised Xander
you could go to America.
l'm a man of my word.
lt doesn't make much difference now,
does it?
He's alive! He's alive! Come here!
Get him out of there, double-time.
Go! Move!
-Bora Bora!
-What? l can't hear you!
Bora Bora.
You're getting burnt.
Xander, you there ?
I know you're there, Xander. I've got
you here on satellite magnification.
Call me. We got a whole
new thing to talk about.
Something very important has come up.
Oh, by the way...
...you passed the test.
The Gibbons test.
You gotta be kidding me.
Please rate this subtitle at www.osdb.link/gx29
Help other users to choose the best subtitles