What the hell is going on?
This amount of rain is
not normal!
L-Lord Koenma!
What is it?!
The river Styx is...!
Hurry!
Water has broken through
the Gate of Judgment!
There's a crack in the
upper part of the Gate...!
Take the important files!
W-What shall we do?
- Lord Koenma!
- What is it?
The Second and Third Levels
have been submerged!
If this keeps up,
all the gates will be in danger!
The shield has collapsed!
It cannot be repaired!
It is dangerous, Lord Koenma.
Please seek refuge!
What's the matter
with you, Lord?!
I don't believe it...!
Summon Botan!
I will be in the Great Vault!
But, my Lord,
now is not the time to--
Hurry up!
Lord Koenma!
I'm here, Botan!
This cannot end up
in their hands!
Hurry and take it to Yusuke!
There is no other way to
save the spirit world.
- Do you understand?
- Y-Yes!
Go, Botan!
I must remain here.
Okay!
Go, Botan!
Hurry!
L-Lord Koenma!
Poltergeist Report
Bonds of Fire
Where did he go now?
Boy, I'm hungry.
Maybe I should just eat
my lunch now.
B-Botan!
What happened, Botan?
Talk to me!
What happened to you?
T-The spirit world is...
The spirit world,
the spirit world is...!
The spirit world is what?
Botan!
W-We must go to Kasane Shrine
and find Hinageshi.
What?!
P-Please, Yusuke.
Botan!
Keiko!
What happened, Botan?!
I don't know what's going on.
Botan...
Keiko, would you hurry and
take Botan to Genkai's temple?
So, what is at Kasane Shrine?
- I don't know.
- You don't know?!
You didn't find out any details?
There was no time for that!
You're not any use at all.
I would have found out
everything from start to--
Over there!
You bastard!
What do you want?
Get away from me!
Shotgun!
Don't worry.
Die!
Spirit Sword!
Oops. Didn't mean to do that...
- Are you all right?
- Y-Yes!
You two are investigators
from the spirit world, aren't you?
And you are...?
My name is Hinageshi.
I am a guide of the spirit world.
Botan!
What is this?
What could have...?!
How is her condition?
It's in the balance.
Something serious must have
happened to the spirit world.
Kurama!
The spirit world...was gone.
What?!
Actually, that is not accurate.
I should say it was covered by water.
B-But why?
Some immeasurably strong power
must have gained control.
No way...
What could have the
power to do that?
When I was there,
some phantoms wearing the pattern
of a cross on their foreheads...
were looking for something.
It must have been
the netherworld!
The netherworld...?
Right.
Those phantoms were demons
controlled by the netherworld.
Their symbol is that cross.
Hold it.
What is this "netherworld"?
As far as I know, there are just
the human world, the spirit world,
and the demon world.
Ah, here it is.
To begin with,
above the human world
lies the spirit world.
The two of them are in balance.
Well, humans who have died
do go to the spirit world.
And the netherworld
was originally...
above and in balance
with the demon world.
Then, several
thousand years ago,
the netherworld began a war
with the spirit world...
in order to gain possession
of the human world.
Exactly how we were able to
defeat them is unknown...
but Emperor Enma did finally
destroy the netherworld and...
banish their King Yakumo and
his men to the darkness of space.
So, how did the netherworld
come back into existence?
If the netherworld is responsible
for this disturbance...
it could become a very
dangerous situation.
We cannot repel them alone.
The netherworld...
In any case, it has
nothing to do with me.
Yukina is here?
Yukina!
She's with Botan.
Hello, Yukina!
How've you been?
Yukina...
Kazuma...
I'm sorry.
I'm glad to see you, but...
Don't.
But, why is Botan...?
An unhappy face like that
doesn't suit you, Yukina.
I, Kazuma Kuwahara,
shall resolve everything!
Soon we will all be
smiling happily again.
Yukina!
A-Are you all right?
Your temperature is
going up and up.
That is the power of love.
He is so hard to understand.
You're in the way, Kuwahara.
Yukina...
Why don't you tell Yukina
that you are her older brother?
I don't need your advice.
Hiei...
You saw the condition
of the spirit world, too.
This is no ordinary event.
How would I know?
What should we do, Hinageshi?
We have to transmit power
to the spirit world.
How?
Look.
There are places in the
human world called...
elemental sites which
naturally collect spiritual energy.
Elemental sites?
You mean storage tanks
for spiritual power?
Yes, something like that.
There are five of
these elemental sites...
representing the Earth, Wind,
Fire, Water, and the Spirit.
If they all are unsealed,
that amassed spiritual power
will be sent to the spirit world.
And with that power
it would be restored!
- Right.
- So, where are they?
I know where!
All right! Leave it to me!
Come, my servants!
Are you here?
Your three demon gods
have arrived, Lord Yakumo.
Our strategy has entered
the second stage.
Make the power of
the elemental sites ours.
- Go!
- Yes, Lord.
Okay, turn at this corner,
so north is behind you...
Where the hell is it?
Hold on a minute!
I-Is this an earthquake?
What's that?
It's...
It's the elemental site
representing Earth!
- What?!
- Let's hurry, Yusuke!
W-What's going on?
What the...?!
This is no good!
What do you mean?
Look at that color.
The elemental site has
been destroyed.
What is streaming out
is not spiritual power...
but the power
of the netherworld!
What?!
Those demons are able to convert
spiritual power to netherworld power.
So, that netherworld power--
If they steal the power from
each of the elemental sites, then...
Then...?
The spirit world will
remain inaccessible!
And there will be
nothing we can do!
- Right.
- Let's hurry!
They may be ahead of us.
We must protect the other sites!
- Okay!
- Let's split up!
I can't even repay Botan
the kindness I owe her.
Kindness?
I always made mistakes and
caused a lot of problems for Botan.
- And now I can't--
- You're wrong.
It's too early to give up!
Umm...
Oh, it's this way!
Up these stairs!
Okay.
Hurry up!
What's wrong?
Everything is completely different!
It crumbled just like that!
Netherworld demons.
They got here ahead of us again!
We may still make it!
Wait!
Look! That's the
elemental site of Fire!
What?!
Hold it!
Don't touch that!
It's over, Hinageshi!
What do we do now?
What, more?
Hinageshi!
Damn!
My body is... No!
Stop! What is this?!
S-Stop!
No. This girl is not the one.
Wait!
It seems your friend is still here.
Stop, you!
You really did it now.
You bastard!
Damn!
You are not a normal
human, are you?
You must be a tool of
the spirit world.
Who are you?!
I am Yakumo,
king of the netherworld.
It's Yakumo!
Here we go, Yakumo!
Spirit gun!
It didn't get through!
Your spiritual power is nothing.
Get out of here!
Yusuke! Are you okay?!
Yusuke!
Yakumo, king of the netherworld...
But why is he...?
D-Damn.
The Power Sphere...
source of our energy...
Plundered in the past
by the spirit world...
Once it has been returned,
our hopes will finally be realized.
The leaders of the spirit world
must have hidden it well.
They would not let it be
protected by such small fry.
Where is it?
Where did they hide it?
This must be the
elemental site of the Soul.
All right, time to open it up.
What's that?
Fools are amusing.
W-Who are you?
I am Majari, one of the three
demon gods of the netherworld.
I shall destroy that elemental site.
What did you say?
You think I'll let you do that?
I shall kill anyone in my way.
Aren't you superior?
Spirit sword!
Looks interesting.
Bastard!
Spirit sword!
Let me show you
what I am known for.
I can mirror my opponents.
I have copied your skills
and your ideas.
You have no chance at victory.
Say that after we've fought!
Bastard.
It's over there!
Don't mess with me!
All right.
I have taken your past.
Who is that?
"Who is that?"
I can't believe you would say
that to your old partner.
Kuronue...
Or do you mean to say you have
forgotten your terrible past?
Kurama Yoko.
You are still alive!
Try to remember that day.
That day we snuck into
the palace of the demon world.
- Don't, Kuronue!
- I need it!
Kuronue!
Traitor!
You deliberately cut my pendant
in order to trap me!
You sacrificed me so that
you alone could escape!
You're wrong!
That's ridiculous.
How dare you say that
after trying to kill me!
What are you talking about?
That day, I...
I...
To save you, I...
You set a trap for me. Then...
you left me to die
while you saved yourself.
Take this!
Wait, Kuronue!
It appears that we have
opened the other sites.
Shoot!
- Kuwahara!
- Wait!
Look at his weapon!
A spirit sword!
That demon is able to
mirror his opponent's techniques.
He is Majari, one of the three
demon gods of the netherworld.
- What...?
- You can't help!
If you try, he'll steal
your techniques, too!
Now, we finish it.
Kuwahara!
Stop joking around!
Even if this is the end,
I will never let you have it.
Here!
Not bad. Though I will
not be defeated either.
You don't have any
more tricks, do you?
I won't be careless again.
Fool!
I just developed a new
killing technique!
What?!
Impressive...
releasing your entire store
of spiritual energy at once.
Thank you for teaching me how.
Pitiful bastard.
I caught you!
Kuwahara.
Now you're all out of
energy, too, Majari.
What...?
I'm telling you it's useless!
Y-You...
There is something
I'm proud of too.
In a true contest of guts...
I have...
never been...
beaten!
I win.
That's it.
Kuwahara!
Hey, Kuwahara!
Hurry and unseal it.
Watch out! Jump, Yusuke!
Hiei!
The final site...!
With this,
the basis for the restoration
of the netherworld is complete.
Lord Yakumo...
Is it definite?
Yes. One more female
from the spirit world exists.
I have waited many years for this...
the moment the netherworld
will be restored on new territory.
W-Where are we?
Are we alive?
Look!
It appears that we were
somehow flung over here.
What do we do now?
That must be it.
A shield has been built around
the area the netherworld appeared in.
Why isn't the city in an uproar?
That is the power of the
netherworld.
Nobody is noticing things
that they normally would.
Where's Yusuke?
Keiko was going to get a
change of clothes,
and he said he was going
with her to check on Botan.
What's wrong, Hiei?
If no one has a good plan,
I'll take care of it myself.
Botan!
There is tremendous energy.
Who are you?
Shall I...?
Don't bother.
This is my temple!
How dare you enter
without permission!
He's strong!
What?! She is able to repel
Lord Yakumo's ghostly power!
That is it.
Wait!
S-Stay away!
So, it was actually true.
Stay away!
The Power Sphere is
inside this girl's body.
What's that?
Stay here, Keiko!
Yusuke!
Hold it!
You bastard!
You again?
You can't stand the
fact that I beat you.
Like a whipped dog.
What did you say?
Yusuke!
Keiko!
Learn your place!
I, Yakumo, have retrieved the
Power Sphere of the netherworld!
Power... Sphere...?
The moment of the netherworld's
restoration has arrived.
This is the source of our power!
B-Botan!
- Are you injured?
- I am fine.
Yukina...
Yukina!
She just fell asleep.
Damn...!
Yusuke, Keiko's
injuries are not serious.
Those bastards said they had found
a Power Sphere inside of Botan.
Now they have the Power Sphere,
the source of their energy--
Even though they have
retrieved the Power Sphere...
the netherworld is extinct.
With no place to go and
the spirit world disempowered...
Yakumo and his brethren
have one aim in mind.
Right.
It is to obtain their true restoration
here in the human world.
Botan probably knew that...
when Koenma entrusted her
with the Sphere.
She hid it inside her own body
so that those demons wouldn't find it.
She risked her own life...
knowing that its power would
overwhelm her like that.
And we never realized.
If only I had some
spiritual power remaining...
You left me for dead.
Botan...
You wanted me to notice.
If only I had been more aware...
I'm so sorry.
Keiko!
You are afraid of me.
Botan!
I shall take the
Power Sphere and this girl.
Twice... I haven't been
able to save Botan.
Please, Yusuke.
Even now,
Botan is trying to prevent them
from having their Power Sphere.
It's no joke!
You think I'll let you
get away with that?!
Yakumo!
We may have no chance, but
we cannot let it end this way!
The spirit world and
human world cannot be wiped out.
This time we will start
the attack from our side.
Botan, I swear I will...
Yusuke.
Let's take a different road.
No, it makes no difference.
You are correct.
- Kuronue!
- You know him?
He was a partner of mine
back when I was a thief.
Let me take care of it.
Kurama, are you still
against your old partner?
His old partner?
Is he okay?
Come, Kurama!
Kurama!
You are truly despicable.
In the past, you fled
and left me to die.
Now, you are trying to
destroy our dream.
Kuronue, it is true that I
could not rescue you that day...
but please believe this.
I--
Silence!
Kurama! Damn!
We can't do anything
in this fog.
This is his problem.
He has to resolve it himself.
Rose whip!
What's wrong?
You're not fighting back?
Kuronue, what you are trying
to do now is wrong.
You say it's wrong?
How dare you say that!
Listen to me, Kuronue!
Shut up!
You still haven't
remembered, have you?
Your dirty act.
Traitor!
Traitor! Traitor!
What's that eerie noise?
I thought so.
What is it?
He's causing many scythes like this
to resonate and create a shield.
Inside it, he is able to
create evil hallucinations.
So, Kurama has been tricked.
Now you can make up
for your ugly past!
I...
What's wrong, Kurama?
You want to kill me to
save yourself again?
No, he's wrong.
That time, his pendant...
I will use this scythe to
cleanse your ugly soul.
What?
Stop, Kuronue!
Forget about me
and run, Kurama!
Now, the final blow!
Die!
Y-You...
The one with the ugly
rotten soul is you!
You are not my old
friend Kuronue!
Show me your true form!
How did you discover my trick?
I could tell.
First, Kuronue always
carried this with him.
He would never throw it away.
What's more,
no matter the circumstances...
he would never
attack an enemy from the rear.
Take this!
Kuronue risked his own life,
telling me to run away.
You twisted the friendship between
me and Kuronue to your advantage!
What's this?
So even someone like you,
who is so cool...
occasionally gets angry.
That's good to know.
Not being able to rescue
Kuronue that day--
Kurama.
There is no one who does not
have scars on his heart.
If there were someone like that,
he would be a shallow bastard.
Let's go!
Okay.
Damn! What do we do?
We can cross at that
flood gate!
What?!
All right, let's go!
W-Who is that?
You maggots are
persistent, aren't you?
Oh, are you planning to
fight again?
It seems you won't
learn till I crush you...
like that old lady and
little girl in the temple.
What?!
You're the bastard who
attacked Genkai and Yukina!
And what if I was?
Bastard!
I, Kazuma Kuwahara,
shall punish you!
What are you doing, Hiei?!
Leave this scum to me.
You have no chance
without your spiritual power!
I will not let you live!
What the...?
You cannot treat me
like the others, Hiei.
You are no match for
my Evil Eye!
What...?
That's Raiko, another of the three
demon gods of the netherworld.
What type of creature is he?
A very powerful one.
He is a demon who can
draw out wickedness...
from his opponent's soul and
manipulate it with his Evil Eye.
Draw out wickedness...?
Hiei is going to become evil!
Take this, hell-scum!
Damn.
Let your eyes open to the evil
which dwells in your soul!
What...?
Awaken the evil which sleeps
in the depths of your heart!
- W-What's that?!
- No, Hiei!
If he looks into that
evil abyss for too long...
he will be pulled into
their evil world.
Evil Eyes!
That is correct.
Now the eyes will open...
and you shall
despise your friends.
Your true character is
an incarnation of evil!
Go after them!
Your power is now
at its maximum.
Smash them!
Hiei! Stop!
He's preparing for the
Black Dragon Wave!
We're doomed if he uses it!
You cannot attack us, Hiei!
Now! Fire, Hiei!
Hiei, you bastard,
showing us your true evil character!
Hiei!
Don't underestimate me!
What?!
You bastard!
Part of the shield has...!
A path has been opened!
Hiei!
Those Evil Eyes could not
seduce my Black Dragon.
W-What's going on?
Hiei wasn't tricked at all.
Hiei!
Using the Black Dragon Wave
against those Evil Eyes has...
exhausted all his energy.
Are you okay?
Don't worry about me.
There is no time. Hurry!
Okay!
- Let's go!
- Okay!
Boy, you sure are
a troublemaker.
- Here we go.
- Kuwahara!
We all have to see the
conclusion. Let's go!
That's it!
Let's go.
So, Raiko and the others
are dead.
It doesn't matter.
If the Power Sphere of
the netherworld is returned...
we will make the
human world our own.
Our years of pain shall
finally end.
Now you shall return the
Netherworld Power Sphere to me.
Even unconscious,
you are using your
final bit of energy to resist.
It is useless!
I am the only one who can
handle the Power Sphere!
You will only suffer with it.
Botan!
- Wait!
- Leave!
This is it!
What?
I will never give it to you!
Botan!
It is useless!
Let go, woman!
Botan!
I'm sorry, Hinageshi.
Involving you in this
dangerous situation...
Don't be ridiculous!
I should have realized sooner.
I'm sorry.
T-Thank you.
I knew that
you would find out.
Botan!
Y-Yusuke.
I couldn't protect...
the Power Sphere.
Get it back.
Botan! Botan!
Here I go.
I won't let you die, Botan!
I won't let you do
whatever you want!
The origin of the
netherworld's strength,
the Power Sphere
has returned.
Now I shall restore our world.
I shall become god and
master of this place!
Humans seem to be
quite stupid creatures.
Do you think
you can match me?
We don't necessarily attack
because we think we can win.
Then is the great aim of protecting
the world for a sense of justice?
That is wrong, too!
What incomprehensible creatures.
W-What is this?
What's going on...?
- Hurry!
- Okay.
Botan! Hinageshi!
I am going to create my own world.
What is wrong with that?
Why are you doing it
in the human world?
You are the ones who called me.
What?!
You said, "Please visit."
It is true...
that my world was beaten
in a battle with the spirit world...
and was sealed in
the darkness of outer space.
I waited patiently for
an opportunity.
And I collected the evil
power of those humans...
who were sent into space
by the spirit world.
I gathered enough power
to destroy the seal.
I seem to get along just fine
with that evil human power...
which the spirit world
could not handle.
Damn.
Our souls set him loose!
What happened?
Now I shall let you taste the power
of human beings' wicked hearts!
- He's just playing around!
- It's no match!
D-Damn!
Yusuke!
You should not waste your
remaining bit of spiritual energy.
He's fast!
Hurry and get behind the pole!
Botan.
Spirit gun!
What happened?
This is my world.
I said everything is
according to my thoughts.
You cannot harm me.
You are a fool, harming
yourself with your own power.
Have you wasted your
remaining bit of spiritual power?
This is no good!
I'll make this the end!
Kuwahara!
What?!
You fool. Yusuke
isn't your only opponent.
Did you forget
that I'm still here?!
What can you, a human being
without spiritual energy, do?
Kuwahara!
I'm the one fighting!
S-Stop! I'm...
You rest there!
I'll finish him off now.
Are you protecting each other?
What's so funny?
The reason you are weak...
is because you are stuck
believing in that facile friendship.
Shut up!
Don't you know
the meaning of fear?
Your body should be feeling
the disparity in our power.
The time has come to change the
human world into the netherworld!
Damn! What's happening?
Die! I shall blow away
you and your world!
Return the Power Sphere
of the Netherworld!
Give it back!
You can't keep that thing
which Botan almost died to...!
Hinageshi!
Don't mess with me!
Stop! You'll die!
Hiei! Kurama!
Yu... Yusuke... What happened
to the Power Sphere?
I have no more spiritual power.
But in there...
What's wrong, boy?
You are certainly strong...
and we may simply not
be a match for you.
But...
But, if I did nothing...
I could not forgive myself!
It is useless.
Even Emperor Enma
of the spirit world...
could not handle the Netherworld
Power Sphere and had to seal it up.
I am the only one who
can manage it.
Yusuke.
Yusuke!
Yusuke...
Now, into my hands the
sphere of the netherworld--
What? Impossible!
Yusuke!
Yusuke is burning
his soul into pure power.
Kuwahara!
Let me help you, Yusuke.
I have too much spiritual power.
Do it, Yusuke!
I can't wait.
Kurama, Hiei, let's go!
It can't be!
Does he really have the strength to
change the netherworld's power...
into spiritual energy?
The feelings of all four
have become one.
Take this!
Go!
Did we do it?
It's over.
It has finally been settled.
Where are Hinageshi
and Botan?
Let's find them!
Hinageshi!
Guys!
This is my final blow!
Take this! Spirit gun!
Botan!
Hang in there, Botan!
Koenma.
Is it you, Koenma!
A-Are we still alive?
Has the spirit world
been restored?!
Yusuke.
- It's finally over.
- Yeah, somehow.
Did that bastard really die?
I don't know.
He could be hiding among us.
That's not even funny!
But if he is, we'll give him
another good beating!