Hi there, this is your reporter, Koto.
Right now, I am in front of the changing room
of the anxious Urameshi Team as
they face the championship match.
Okay then, let's head on in right now!
Koto!
Please excuse the intrusion!
This is your active mic
performer's ambush interview!
Um... what is your mindset here,
before the championship?
Crush 'em!
Are you confident that you
can beat the Toguro Team?
Kill 'em!
Do you have any new moves, or strategies?
Burn them to cinders.
O-Oh, sorry. Ahem...
Wel, would you like to say something
on behalf of the whole team?
You'd better not get too
close to me right now.
This has been the Urameshi corner.
Moving on, we'd like to present
to you the championship match.
Ah, that was some good work.
Hmm... Okay, I'm taking it!
Yeah.
Come on, Yukina-san, let's take this together!
No, don't, Kazuma-san.
Our souls will be taken from us.
It's too dangerous.
Oh, no, it will be fine!
No! It won't!
Hurry it up!
What's all the hubbub?
--What?
--Nothing.
Your cheeks are puffy, aren't they?
And whose fault is that, dummy?!
What do you mean, "dummy"?!
I'm just concerned about you!
Hey, now, hurry it up!
Huh? Where's Hiei?
Never mind me.
Ow! What are you doing?!
--Now, now...
--Let me go! Stop!
Okay, here goes!
Okay, cheese!