Mu Mu Hakusho - Night 1
Script: Shigeru Chiba
Storyboard: Akiyuki Shinbo
Animation: Motosuke Takahashi
B-Ba-san!
N-No, you've got it all wrong! I wasn't...
"Gokai," you say?
Of course! Isn't it obvious? Never mind that...
Anyone else?
8th floor, please.
--12th floor.
--Very good.
Wha--?
5th floor, women's clothing.
Hey, Ba-san, what's the meaning of...?
Wha--?
What is this?!
Mu Mu Hakusho - Night 2
Script: Shigeru Chiba
Storyboard: Akiyuki Shinbo
Animation: Motosuke Takahashi
Oh, it was a dream?
Ah, that was a shock.
What's with these pajamas?!
And what's with these walls?!
Huh?!
Honey, are you awake?
"Honey"?
Good morning, Yu-chan.
Botan!
Come on, come on, you have to hurry and get
yourself ready, before the chief gets here.
Uh, never mind that,
what are you doing here?
--Yow!
--Oh, Yu-chan, you're not quite awake yet.
Here.
Ah, thanks. Uh, I mean...
There, you see? They're here! Hurry, hurry!
Yes, coming!
Hey, Botan!
Geez, what's going on?
I'm so sorry, he hasn't had his breakfast yet.
He really is a night owl, you know?
Not at all. You guys are newlyweds, after all.
Yes, indeed.
Hey, Kurama and Hiei!
Why are you two ganging up
with her in all of this nonsense?
W-What?!
Such a newlywed.
You guys!
Hey, Yu-chan, don't you take
that tone with your chief.
Chief?
Oh, no, it's all right. Youngsters
need to have this kind of spunk.
Right, Kurama-kun?
Absolutely.
Well now, we should get going.
Where?! To do what?!
Come on, now. Here's your lunch.
Do you have your handkerchief?
Enough, already!
Mu Mu Hakusho - Night 3
Script: Shigeru Chiba
Storyboard: Akiyuki Shinbo
Animation: Motosuke Takahashi
Oh, it was a dream?
Whoa! W-What the...?
Dammit, they're shooting at us like mad!
Kuwabara!
Haven't you gotten through to HQ yet?
No, sir. I've been calling
them for some time, though.
Damn, what are those guys at HQ thinking?
The way things are going,
it's only a matter of time
before the Earth meets her end!
Guys!
What are you up to?
Get down!
You idiot! Are you trying
to get yourseif killed?!
Ah, you startled me.
Branch Manager, look there.
Ah! They're easy targets.
Huh? Keiko!
What's that, Urameshi? You know her?
Huh? Know her? She's...
That works out perfectly.
Branch Manager,
Urameshi and I will charge in!
Good! Make sure to
secure the contract. Got it?
Yes, sir!
Let's go, Urameshi!
Enemy fighters at 15 o'clock!
Get down!
W-What the hell is going on here?!
Mu Mu Hakusho - Final Night
Script: Shigeru Chiba
Storyboard: Akiyuki Shinbo
Animation: Motosuke Takahashi
But then, get this, out of nowhere...
...he says, "I also admit that
your knees are unbearably cute,
but you show them off too much, don't you?"
Do you think that maybe he has
a thing for you, Shizuru-san?
Oh, bleah! You've got to be kidding.
That over-the-hill old coot?
Yo!
What are you two up to together out here?
--Ah-choo!
--Ow!
Oh, piease, excuse us.
Um, we're here on behalf of this interest...
The Paradise News?
Ah, we're good.
One month is all we ask.
And if you sign up now,
I'll include this squid ink lotion
and smoked mudskipper, at no charge.
But we...
We already get a newspaper.
Might I ask which one?
The Gyaku-manji Daily.
(gyaku-manji: "swastika")
Y-You're kidding, right?!
Say...
Mister, you've stepped in doggie-doo.
Oh, it was a dream?
Man, that was one weird dream!
Honey, are you awake?
Hi!