Yo! Long time no see! How have you been?
I'm sure you know this,
but don't go copying this
vídeo wíthout permissíon.
All right, see you later!
Hey, I'm glad to see you guys again.
How have you been?
I'm sure you know this,
but it's not right to copy
this video without permission.
You'll listen to that, for my sake, right?
Warning comment? What is that?
Don't copy this video without permission?
Ridiculous. Don't call me here
for something like that.
Do not take the power of the Jagan so líglítly!
Gentlemen! Did you enjoy it?
Whoops, it's time to feed Eikichi.
Oh, right! Don't go copying
this video without permission!
Eikichi?!
I can't have you copying
this video without permission.
Besides, this is just 5O
percent of my total strength.
Next, I'll show you my true self.
I can hardly waít.
Well? Did you enjoy that?
Even if you did, don't go
copying this without permission.
Bye, now. See you later.