In a crowded city, as I
bump shoulders, I'm all alone
On an endless prairie, as the
wind whistles by, I'm all alone
Which one is it that makes me
want to cry more, I wonder
Marking it with twin circles,
I feel a bit more grown-up!
It must be, that when I run
into these terribly difficult walls,
and unexpectedly, for whatever reason,
the courage and power to break
through rises up from within
All because of how, when I run
into these terribly difficult people,
they show me kindness, I bet!
Thank you very much!
Yusuke!
Give it up. No matter how
many of you gang up on us,
you're no match for us.
That's right. It's too hot for this.
Shut up! If we can just get rid
of you, this town will be ours!
Everyone, get them!
What's the use? Let's hurry
and take care of this.
--Yeah.
--Yusuke!
Bad news! Bad news!
Hey! Watch out!
I've got bad news!
What is this?! That was dangerous, you know!
Come with me! Something
terrible has happened!
Now, look, this is our summer vacation.
If this is another one of Koenma's
usual orders, I'm not following it.
It is about Koenma-sama!
He's been kidnapped!
What? Koenma?
Hey, if you keep crying, we're
never gonna find out what's up.
What happened?
Come on, tell us.
R-Right.
As it happens, Koenma-sama was
all dressed up for summer vacation...
That guy is the sort who dresses up?
...and we all accompanied him
to the beach of the Dead Sea.
Ah, this is heavenly... thongs and everything...
After a nap, as Koenma-sama was
enjoying some watermelon-splitting...
What is this?!
My name is Garuga. I am taking Koenma.
If you want to save him,
bring the Gold Seal to the
Valley of Magma by sundown today.
If you're not there by then, Koenma will die!
It all happened so quickly...
What is this "Gold Seal" thing?
Let's see... Huh...?
Here it is.
This is King Yama the Great's Gold Seal.
It proves that he rules the Spirit Realm,
and must never leave here.
If this were to fall into
the hands of someone bad,
there would be a complete
breakdown of order.
Chaos would be unavoidable.
Yama the Great might even be
driven out of the Spirit Realm.
So we're supposed to exchange this
Gold Seal for Koenma's life, huh?
Yama the Great doesn't even take
the Gold Seal with him on business.
But Koenma-sama will be...
Ah, I don't know what to do!
Good grief, that little brat
is always a problem, huh?
Ah! Yusuke! N-No, you can't!
No, Yusuke-san, you mustn't!
But without this, I can't go rescue Koenma.
I'm not really up for this, but as
long as I bring back both Koenma
and the Gold Seal, no problem, right?
There's no time to lose.
Botan, show me the way to get there!
You got it. Let's hurry.
Huh? Where did that dope Hiei go off to?
Hmm? He was here until just a moment ago.
Such an insensitive jerk. But don't you worry.
Kuwabara the man will save
that poor Koenma for you!
Oh, yeah! I'll have to ask
Kurama-san to help, as well!
No! No!
Your foolish subordinates
have exited the judgment gate.
Who is that?! Who's there?!
Have you forgotten me?
"Garuga"
Koashura!
"Koashura"
Hey, Garuga...
Yes, Koashura-sama.
What's the big idea, putting me through this?!
Ha! I, Koashura, am going to
replace you, Koenma, you numbskull,
and enter into the judgment gate!
You're going to what?!
I'm going to get my hands on the Gold Seal,
and put my stamp on all kinds of documents!
You can't have that, huh?
No, I can't! I can't have that! Don't do it!
If I have my Gold Seal taken from me,
my old man, Yama the Great,
will not just let me off with a spanking!
That crumbling rock there will
only last until sundown, I'd say.
If that Gold Seal doesn't get here before then,
you're going to go kerplunk into the magma!
Hurry! Please hurry!
Yow!
Hey, what are you doing?!
Who are you guys?
This land is under the
control of the Jaki Goblins.
We will not let you pass through unanswered.
We don't have time to mess
around with you right now.
Catch you later.
Word is that you've got
Yama the Great's Gold Seal.
What?
Why don't you hand it over to us?
Urameshi!
We've got no time! Run, Kuwabara!
Yeah!
Shotgun!!
Yusuke!
Are you sure your people that you're
relying on will actually get here?
What?! Have you done something
to Yusuke and the others?!
I'm not telling!
What?! Come on, Koashura!
Ow! Hot!
Ow!! Hot!!
You dumbass! Don't send it my way!
Why are you doing something so terrible?!
Ha! Why don't you ask yourself that question?!
How cruel was that thing you
did to me?! This is my revenge!
Nyah! Nyah!
Hey, Kuwabara, how do you
suppose those guys back there
knew that we were carrying the Gold Seal?
Yeah. It's too soon for
word to have gotten around.
We've probably already fallen
into an enemy trap. If that's true...
Botan, watch out!
--Kuwabara!
--Damn it! What are these?!
It's the Yokai Jugan! Yusuke, over there!
Hand over the Gold Seal, nice and easy!
Rei-gun!!
What?!
You bastard!
I, Shobi, will be taking this.
Give that back!
Botan!
I've caught you.
That cage you're in will
continue to grow back forever.
I'll start by dealing with the girl.
Take this!
Botan!
Who is that?! Who's interfering?!
All you can do is control dead wood.
You're not up to the task of dealing with us.
Kurama!
Hiei! What are you doing here?!
I couldn't just leave this to you.
Not when the Gold Seal is involved.
Here!
Let us deal with these guys! Get moving!
I owe you one!
Hey, don't let them escape!
You're not going any further.
Rose Whip!!
Is Yusuke going to make it in time?
Who knows?
You gave the Gold Seal to Yusuke
because you think he'll make it in time, right?
Hmph, so don't ask.
Oh, the sun will set any moment now!
We have to increase our speed!
You dumbass, this is all we can manage now!
Ah! Here come more of them!
Damn it, what do we do?!
Nothing to do but keep going!
I'll wipe you guys out!
Who do you think you're dealing with?!
Who do you think I am?!
The Valley of Magma is just past there!
Damn, we're not gonna make it
in time! Urameshi! Grab onto me!
Extend, Rei-ken!
Go, Urameshi!
Help!
Hey, if we don't save him soon,
Koenma really is going to die.
What are you talking about?
We should let him die, shouldn't we?
What?
It's their fault for not getting here in time.
But...
Wait!
I brought the Gold Seal!
Yusuke!
Hurry up and save Koenma!
Hey, Garuga, let him go.
Now, hand over the Gold Seal.
Here.
So this is Yama the Great's Gold Seal?
I finally did it!
Koenma, you're finished now!
I'm going to make you my gofer,
and work you to death for the rest of your life!
The Gold Seal! The actual Gold Seal!
Hey, Garuga, what are you doing?!
This Gold Seal is now mine!
What?!
And I will rule over the Spirit Realm!
Ah! Are you disobeying my orders?!
I have no need for you any longer.
You bastard! You mean you
set this whole thing up?
Give that Gold Seal back to me!
Ha! You think you can take it back from me?
I'll take you out with one shot!
Rei-gun!!
Gotcha!
Yusuke!
How do you like the force
of my reflective mirror?
If you fight me, there's no way you can win!
"Yasha"
That's one of the Yokai on
the most wanted list, Yasha!
My arm... Botan, get Koenma.
You're in my way! Die!
Koenma-sama!
Botan!
You bastard...
Oh, you can raise your spirit
power through anger, can you?
How do you like this?!
I wish I could compliment you
on doing so well with your injury,
but that won't work!
Yusuke!
That will teach you your place.
That's where they are!
Well, what will it be?
Beneath you is a bottomless river
of magma. Care to go for a swim?
--Hiei!
--Yeah.
W-Wait up!
Wait up.
Impossible! After the
kind of beating I gave you,
there's no way you should be able to stand.
Why do you risk your life for that little brat?
Well, Koenma is the one
who brought me back to life.
Yusuke...
So you owe him your life, huh?
In any case, I can't allow you
to have the Gold Seal.
Get those two now, while we can.
Yeah!
You don't know when to die.
I'll see that there's no trace left of you!
This will finish you!
Rei-gun!!
You fool!
Die!
What?!
--Yusuke!
--You did it!
No, not yet.
Damn it, that was a sneaky trick!
But don't think you can
defeat me with just that.
Damn, it didn't work.
You'll pay for that!
This is the last of my power!
Die!
Take a close look at your own body!
What? My reflective mirror won't open!
Take this! Rei-gun!!
Urameshi!
I did it...
Yusuke!
Botan!
Oh! It's the Gold Seal!
Once we get back to the judgment gate,
I'll dress these properly.
Yeah.
Koashura, why would you go and
pull something this outrageous?
You said something or other
about getting revenge.
Hey! Don't try to cry it away!
Well, well, when Koenma and I
were going to Spirit Realm
Kindergarten together...
...as I was about to give a
present to Kotennyo-chan,
who I liked, on her birthday...
What is it you wanted to talk
to me about, Koashura-kun?
Oh, well, you see...
Kotennyo-chan!
Here! It's a present!
Thank you, Koenma-kun. Mwah!
Someday, I'll get you for this.
What?! A childhood spat?!
Well...
You are one troublemaking little punk!
Wah! You hit me on the same spot again!
In any case, the Gold Seal
is back safe and sound,
and this mission was a complete success.
So what's become of Koashura?
Hmm, since the Yokai Yasha
gave him such a good beating,
he got off with the usual 10,000 spankings,
together with Koenma-sama.
It's no laughing matter.
If you hadn't splashed him
with magma back there,
keeping him from bouncing
your Rei-gun back at you,
there's no telling what would
have become of the Spirit Realm.
Huh? Yeah, that was quite a fluke.
What?!
A fluke?!
Well, yeah, but it all worked
out okay, so who cares, right?
Hey, don't go laughing it off!
Yusuke!
Oh, that's right, I've got a date
I'm supposed to be going on!
Bye, guys!
--Whoa, just a minute, Yusuke!
--Hey, Urameshi!
As my heart is about to burst,
the mild wind that blows
against us is gentle
Facing each other, hand in hand,
the usual twilight
envelops us and melts away
Isn't it funny? They're not
even the slightest bit alike,
your smiling face, and mine
But right now, it feels like
I'm looking in a mirror
I am not feeling sad;
everything is fine, after all
There, hiding within an offhanded
greeting, lies a "thank you"
Sayonara, bye bye,
take care of yourself
This is the line I'm drawing between us,
so catch it, if you would
Sayonara, bye bye,
take care of yourself