"Yu Yu Hakusho
Opening & Ending
Encyciopedia"
"The Spirit Realm"
Ah, so busy, so busy, so busy...
It's Botan! I'm coming in.
--So busy, so busy...
--Koenma-sama, I'm just going to pop
on down to the Human Reaim, okay?
Yeah, sure, go ahead.
Okay!
Hey, just a minute!
Is that all the screen time I get?
And after showing up again
after all this time, too!
In a crowded city, as I
bump shoulders, I'm all alone
On an endless prairie, as the
wind whistles by, I'm all alone
Which one is it that makes me
want to cry more, I wonder
Marking it with twin circles,
I feel a bit more grown-up!
It must be, that when I run
into these terribly difficult walls,
and unexpectedly, for whatever reason,
the courage and power to break
through rises up from within
All because of how, when I run
into these terribly difficult people,
they show me kindness, I bet!
Thank you very much!
Look out!
Urameshi Yusuke, age 14, hyper-delinquent.
He dies in place of a child who is a complete
stranger to him, in a traffic accident.
Back then, who would have ever predicted
the strange destiny he would have?
To put it in a nutshell, Urameshi Yusuke is...
...a simpleton who doesn't
think before he acts!
A fool whose body engages
before his brain does!
Minamino Shuichi, whose true
identity is the Yoko Kurama.
He can turn any plant into a weapon,
and becomes mercilessly hard-nosed
against anyone who means him harm.
While living in the Human Realm,
he develops feelings of affection
toward his adopted mother,
and his encounter with Yusuke
and company changes him.
Hiei, the Jagan Master with
a third eye in his forehead.
Born in a land of ice,
he uses flame techniques.
The heart of this callous, ambivalent fellow
also changes through his battles.
Kuwabara Kazuma. Eh, never mind about him.
Hey, what was that?!
As the cherry blossom among flowers,
so is Kuwabara's grit among men!
He fights for love, justice, and Yukina-san!
Hobbies include looking after cats,
and his motto is to do a good deed daily!
In any event...
...I sure am glad to have met them.
The second hand is sharp again tonight
As it chops up time
"Chi chi chi..."
I'll never be able to finish this homework
So I toss it away!
Son of a gun!
It's the dreams that tumble away, oh
That are the ones I want to go after
And if l stop, they will get away, oh
So I can't ease up on them!
It's the dreams that tumble away, oh...!
¥300.
Thank you!
Step on up!
Oh, it's you, Keiko.
What do you mean, "Oh, it's you"?
You're talking to a customer.
Char siu pork and noodles.
Coming right up.
It looks like you're making
an honest living, huh?
Thankfully, yes.
Very good, very good.
Your order's ready.
How is it, miss?
I hate to admit it, but it's good.
Isn't it? I'm not telling you
what the secret ingredient is.
Come to think of it, Yusuke,
this is the first I've ever had of your cooking.
If you like this sort of thing,
I'll make it for you every day.
Hey, your face is flushed. Are you all right?
It's nothing!
By the way, are you free tomorrow?
Why? What if I am free tomorrow?
Oh, Botan was by earlier.
She said it's been too long,
and we should all get
together at Ba-san's piace.
Hey, your face really is red.
You sure you don't have a cold?
It's nothing at all!
Hey, are you okay?
I said I'm fine!
This is incredibly delicious.
Urameshi, you've upped your game.
I'm not treating you today.
Who'd have thought you
had this kind of talent?
Isn't that the truth?
He'll be able to take over the
Yukimura Diner any time like this.
W-Why would you say something like that?!
Hey, Keiko...
Yeah, I know, my face is red!
Do you have a cold?
As my heart is about to burst,
the mild wind that blows
against us is gentle
Facing each other, hand in hand,
the usual twilight
envelops us and melts away
Isn't it funny? They're not
even the slightest bit alike,
your smiling face, and mine
But right now, it feels like
I'm looking in a mirror
I am not feeling sad;
everything is fine, after all
There, hiding within an offhanded
greeting, lies a "thank you"
Sayonara, bye bye,
take care of yourself
This is the line I'm drawing between us,
so catch it, if you would
Sayonara, bye bye,
take care of yourself
This is the line I'm drawing between us,
so catch it, if you would
Granny is as chipper as ever, huh?
Sayonara, bye bye,
take care of yourself
Granny is as chipper as ever, huh?
Sayonara, bye bye,
take care of yourself
Yeah.
Sayonara, bye bye,
take care of yourself
It's been just about a year
since the Spirit Reaim
Sayonara, bye bye,
take care of yourself
brought down the kekkai barrier.
It looks like they're slowly
warming up to each other--
both the Spirit Realm and the Demon Realm.
No matter how sunny their coexistence
may be promoted as being,
some friction is bound to come up.
They may be undeservedly
discriminated against,
just for being Yokai.
When that happens, someone
will have to stick up for them.
Leave that to me!
Kuwabara the man will defend Yukina-san,
even at the cost of his own iife!
Please rest assured, I will
take care of you, Yukina-san!
Right! Thank you.
Oh, come on, now. I mean, this is me, right?
Hey, Yusuke!
Huh? Where's Yukina-chan?
She's still talking to Ba-chan.
Huh? That photo!
That's the one I dropped earlier, isn't it?
It is?
Ta-da! Look! I brought all the
pictures we've taken together.
Most of them are from the Dark Tournament.
The Dark Tournament, huh?
That seems like it was so long ago now.
There were all sorts of folks there, huh?
And Kuwa-chan had a real strong showing, too.
Oh, please! Do go on.
I wonder how Chu, Jin
and the others are doing.
It looks like they're all fired up,
ready for the next tournament.
I can't wait to fight against them again!
Within a cracked mirror
I see your reflection
Crying, crying
As you trace the narrow
moon with your finger
Who is it that I am calling out to?
It's the back of a love
nowhere to be found
Over and over, over and over
I will tap at your window
With my back pressed by
the acceleration of night
It was as if a thread was snapping
And I just held on to you,
held on to you, tightly
As you exchange your
unbalanced kisses with me,
come closer to my love!
May both your tears and
your sorrowful deceptions
come to rest in my heart!
Hiei-kun didn't come, huh?
I tried to contact him through Enki,
but he said he's not with Mukuro right now.
That's just the kind of guy he is.
I mean, really, he has
no sense of cooperation.
I'm sure he must be doing
some secret training
to get ready for the upcoming
Demon Realm Unification Tournament.
Here it is!
Hiei, fast asleep after fighting
Sensui in the Demon Realm!
Yusuke...
Oh, I was just thinking,
if I'd met Toguro and Sensui in
the Demon Realm to begin with,
maybe our fights might have taken...
...some other form.
In a crowded city, as I
bump shoulders, I'm all alone
On an endless prairie, as the
wind whistles by, I'm all alone
Which one is it that makes me
want to cry more, I wonder
Marking it with twin circles,
I feel a bit more grown-up!
It must be, that when I run
into these terribly difficult walls,
and unexpectedly, for whatever reason,
the courage and power to break
through rises up from within
All because of how, when I run
into these terribly difficult people,
they show me kindness, I bet!
Thank you very much!
Hiei-san...
I couldn't find your brother.
He is probably already dead.
You can have this back.
No, that's okay.
You please hang on to it.
I have a feeling that it would
be better for you to keep it.
Yukina is not as much of
a child as you think she is.
When my letter reaches you,
don't break the seal
Just leave it alone,
and after some time has passed,
I'm sure you will
understand how I feel now
This is my first, and last, request
As gently as we could, it wasn't very hard
With one purpose, we foolishly embraced
As twilight closes in,
I shoot an arrow of courage
from a distant window,
toward your back, as you leave
Although it still has not
stopped raining outside,
the drenched people and the city
still believe in the sun
An old melody, and a blurred silhouette
Living the easy life doesn't
make for a very good picture
Ah, here she comes.
I'm sorry to keep you all waiting.
Oh, no, not at all.
For you, Yukina-san,
I would wait a hundred years.
I'm so sorry.
Well then, there's still plenty of day left.
Want to stop off somewhere on the way back?
You mean like that beach of memories?
Huh? Memories?
Yes, the beach of memories.
Oh, right! That's what you meant!
The beach of memories!
What are you talking about?
Heh, don't play dumb.
Yusuke, you...
...and Keiko-chan's...
...first kiss seaside beach!
Y-You dumbasses! That was just, you know...
Don't start blushing about it now!
--No, actually, it was our second.
--Yusuke!
The late summer heat today
is something else, huh?
Sis, you tell 'em, you tell 'em!
Come on, let's go.
Behind closed eyes, only longing arises
as to the sleeping season I bid good-bye
More than kindness that
sparkles in the distance,
I'd rather have just one thing that I want
Having passed through a city of cold glass,
I want to touch your hands,
and confirm your feelings
It's just a dream I'm
having with my eyes open,
for me to be hugging you so tightly
Although the wind may blow, the rain
may fall, and my heart may waver,
if it's a dream I'm
having with my eyes open,
it's okay if now I get hurt
I can be as gentle as
the sky is unpredictable
I've come to realize that
all of us are by ourselves,
somewhat accustomed to emptiness, lonely
In the gloom of my midafternoon room,
I lift up my dejected face
Let's break off the unproductive discussions,
and toss out ideas against a bitter future
The dream I'm having with my eyes open
is bound to have plenty of thorns
The tears of trusting others and
discovering their lies are painful
The dream I'm having with my eyes open
is always jerking me around
For as arbitrary as this city is,
I can't leave it behind
The dream I'm having with my eyes open
is sure to be a challenge
The shadow of someone who
snuck in a kick to the heart
If it's a dream I'm
having with my eyes open,
then I don't mind the heartache now
As capricious as this love is,
I'll use it as a springboard
It's just a dream I'm
having with my eyes open,
for me to be hugging you so tightly
Although the wind may blow, the rain
may fall, and my heart may waver,
It's nice that we could all come here again.
Although the wind may blow, the rain
may fall, and my heart may waver,
Mm-hmm, it sure is.
Although the wind may blow, the rain
may fall, and my heart may waver,
The sea is so pretty, almost like a dream.
If it's a dream I'm
having with my eyes open,
The sea is so pretty, almost like a dream.
It's okay if now I get hurt
For me, it's an even bigger
dream to have you here.
I can be as gentle as
the sky is unpredictable
For me, it's an even bigger
dream to have you here.
I can be as gentle as
the sky is unpredictable
It looks like you still
haven't gotten any smarter.
I can be as gentle as
the sky is unpredictable
Hiei! When did you get here?!
Hmph, I can do what I want.
I thought you were supposed to
be at Mukuro's, mellowing out.
What are you talking about?
A little lover's spat, huh?
I'm gonna kill you.
It's been a long time since I've
heard Kuwa-chan and Hiei's repartee.
Repartee?! Wait, who's the straight man,
and who's the funny man?
You've gotta make that clear, Botan!
It's finally upon us! The Second
Demon Realm Unification Tournament!
Who will come away the winner this time?
Will Contestant Urameshi fight
back and vindicate his honor?
Hindsight is 20/20. You should go
home now, while you're still alive.
Hmph, even if my mortal frame
falls before the whirlwind...
...I will trust in the immortality
of the soul, and move forward.
That is the way a man lives!
And now, the start of
the preliminary matches!
All right! Here we go!